One Bowl of Tea on Rice
One bowl of tea on rice.
Pickled plums, slivered nori,
and leftover chicken from dinner.
All doused in piping-hot water,
then shoveled in with salted kelp.
That was so good.
All those bowls of tea on rice I'd sneak into the kitchen to make at the orphanage...
Ow!
Damn it...
I'm gonna die of hunger.
My name is Atsushi.
Episode 1
Fortune is Unpredictable
and Mutable
Due to certain circumstances,
I'm about to die from starvation.
After being driven out of the orphanage,
I had nothing to eat, nowhere to sleep,
and, as one might expect, not a cent to my name.
Yet, I lack the courage to commit theft.
That is how I've arrived at my current predicament.
However...
If I wish to live,
I have no choice but to steal and take from others!
Get out, you failure!
No orphanage would ever welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
Shut up...
Shut up!
Die in a ditch?
I'm not gonna die!
I'm gonna live, no matter what it takes!
Alright.
I'll attack the first person who comes along
and rob them of everything they have!
Well, that was mission impossible.
I can't catch him on an empty stomach.
Next!
One, two, three, four!
I... I doubt military police would be toting their wallets during training.
But the next person who comes along... for sure!
I've got this!
Well...
I can't possibly count him.
Y-Yeah, I'll pass, please.
I... I'll pass...
Fine!
In the end...
...I saved a life?
You were floating down the river...
Are you okay?
I made it.
Damn.
"Damn"?
Did he just say "damn"?
Are you the one who interrupted my drowning?
I was just trying to help.
Huh?
Drowning?
Submersion...
You don't know what I mean by that?
I was trying to commit suicide.
...Suicide?
Suicide!?
That's right, I was trying to commit suicide.
But you just had to interfere.
Why...
...am I being
lectured?
Wait, is he scolding me for saving him?
Still, my priority is to commit a clean suicide
without troubling others.
Yet, I did trouble you,
so the fault lies with me at this point.
I should apologize in some way.
Growl
Are you hungry, boy?
Well..
I haven't eaten in several days.
Growl
Ugh...
How odd.
Growl
I'm also hungry.
Then...
By the way, the river seems to have taken my wallet.
You can't be serious.
There you are, blockhead!
Oh, hey.
Nice work, Kunikida-kun.
Nice work?
And just who caused all this work,
you suicidal maniac?!
I've had enough of you disrupting my schedule!
Oh, right!
I have a great idea.
He's a colleague of mine from work.
Let's have him treat you to a meal.
Are you even listening to me?!
What's your name?
Huh?
Nakajima... Atsushi.
Well, come along, Atsushi-kun!
What would you like to eat?
Um...
Well, if it's not too much trouble...
Oh, there's no need to hold back!
I'd like to eat tea on rice.
So a boy on the brink of starvation
wants to eat tea on rice?
Very well, let's have Kunikida-kun
treat you to thirty bowls!
Don't get all generous with my money, Dazai!
Dazai?
Yeah, that's my name.
I am Dazai.
Dazai Osamu.
You're unbelievable.
Who says “What a nice river!"
and then jumps into it in the middle of a job?!
Thanks to you, look!
See how off-schedule we are now!
You sure like your schedules, Kunikida-kun.
Ideal
This isn't a schedule!
This is an ideal!
My guide in life!
And nowhere in this book
is it written that my work partner is a suicidal maniac!
Suicidal maniac?
Shut up!
Nowhere on my projected expenses
page will you find written
that I will buy a million bowls of
tea on rice for a snot-nosed brat!
Snot-nosed brat?
Like I said, it's a job!
What kind of job?
Our job today?
It involves the military.
How are you two communicating, actually?
I'm so full.
I don't want to see another bowl
of this for at least ten years.
Why, you!
How dare you be so shameless
after eating on my dime?
You're a real lifesaver!
After leaving the orphanage and
coming to Yokohama,
I've had nothing to eat and nowhere to sleep.
I thought I'd have an untimely death.
You're from an institute?
You could say that.
But they chased me out.
That's some non-profit there.
Hey, Dazai!
We're not some philanthropists going around helping brats down on their luck, okay?
Let's get back to the job at hand.
That reminds me, you said earlier that your current job involves the military.
What is your line of work, exactly?
Oh, we're just detectives.
Detectives...?
That's not to say we only
handle lost pets and infidelity.
The Armed Detective Agency,
an organization of supernatural detectives
Perhaps you've heard of us.
What?
I've heard of this Armed Detective Agency in rumors...
Said to be an agency specializing in missions
that cannot be entrusted to the
likes of the police or the military.
A twilight armed force positioned
between the world of night and day.
I'm told many from the Agency
possess supernatural powers...
but does that also apply to these two?
Check out that nice beam up there.
Don't analyze whether you can hang yourself in a random teahouse we just found!
Don't get me wrong.
We're talking the hanging health method.
What's that about?
What, you don't know?!
It's so good for shoulder cramps!
What?!
Such a thing exists?!
Hey, write this all down!
Hanging... health... method...
I'm messing with you.
A-Are these two really with the
Armed Detective Agency?
My partner gets himself washed up in a river,
and a brat on death's door just
stuffs himself with no shame.
My schedule for the day was just perfect,
but I have to start over from square one!
So, about your job today...
I'll ensure that the job will be
finished on schedule, if nothing else!
Yeah?!
Sorry, I shouldn't have asked!
R-Right, of course your jobs are classified!
Today's job doesn't really require secrecy.
We're looking for a certain tiger
on behest of the military.
A tiger?
A man-eater who's recently appeared in these parts.
Well, not that we know for sure if it's devoured anyone,
but it's ransacked warehouses and
eaten farm produce and the like,
doing whatever it wants.
It's been spotted around here lately.
What's wrong, Atsushi-kun?
I... I... I'll be leaving now.
G-Good-bye.
Wait, brat!
You know something, don't you?
You can't.
No one can take it on!
You know of the man-eating tiger?
It's after me.
It almost killed me!
If it's been seen around here,
I have to run, now!
Hey, brat!
You'll either pay for the food with your arm or by telling us everything.
Now, now, Kunikida-kun.
Whenever you try to ask questions,
it becomes an interrogation.
The Boss's been talking to you about this.
And...
what do you know about this tiger?
My orphanage was decimated by that tiger.
It ravaged our fields,
it ravaged our chicken coop,
and even our warehouse.
No one died, sure,
but the orphanage was
already on a shoestring budget.
I got kicked out so they
had one less mouth to feed.
Get out, you failure!
The world would be a better place if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
Why me? I didn't do anything...
We don't need worthless louts!
You'll never find a place where you belong!
Just go! I hope you rot in hell!
Well, that's tragic.
So, boy, what's this talk about
the tiger almost killing you?
The man-eater always shows up wherever I go.
Just a while ago, when I was
walking around Tsurumi...
It's a tiger!
There's a tiger!
I'd seen it out of the corner of my eyes many times,
starting two weeks before I
was chased out of the orphanage.
I'm sure it's come all the way
to the city in search of me.
When was the last time you saw the tiger?
I think I saw it around Tsurumi
about four days ago.
It's true that its been focused
around there for the past two weeks.
In addition, it was sighted around
Tsurumi four days ago.
Atsushi-kun, are you free?
I have a really bad feeling about this.
You being the man-eater's target
presents an excellent opportunity.
Huh?
Please help us find the tiger.
No way!
Kunikida-kun, please go back to the Agency and give this to the president.
Hey, don't tell me you plan to catch
the tiger with just the two of you?
We should first confirm whether his information is accurate.
It's fine.
I'm not doing this, okay?!
This means you're going to use me as bait, right?
Who in their right mind would agree to that—
There's a reward.
Currently
penniless
What? Reward?
A reward?
No, no.
You're not gonna tempt me with that!
B-But just for reference,
how much would the reward be?
About this much.
Dazai-san, what are you reading?
A good book.
I'm surprised you can read when it's this dark.
I have good vision.
Complete Guide to Suicide
Besides, I already know everything
that happens in this book.
Why are you reading it, then?
A good book is always good,
no matter how many times you read it.
Will the tiger really show up here?
It will.
Don't worry.
Even if it shows up, it's no match for me.
I may not look like much,
but I am an operative of the Armed Detective Agency.
You're really confident.
I'm kind of jealous.
They called me a failure at the orphanage for as long as I can remember.
And now, I don't even know where I'll sleep tonight, or if I'll eat tomorrow.
Get out, you failure!
You'll never find a place where you belong!
No one would care if someone like me were to die in a ditch somewhere.
Yeah, I may as well be eaten by a tiger.
Now, then...
I think it'll be soon.
What?!
I... I just heard something back there.
Yeah.
I bet that's the tiger, Dazai-san!
No, I think the wind just knocked something down.
It's the man-eater!
It's come to eat me!
Calm down, Atsushi-kun.
Tigers don't just show up like that.
How do you know for sure?!
Something wasn't quite right to begin with.
Just because their finances went south,
why would an orphanage banish a child?
It's not some farming village from a bygone era.
Eliminating one or two mouths to feed would hardly put a dent in their deficit.
It'd make more sense to downsize
by transferring half of the kids to a different institution.
What are you talking about, Dazai-san?
You came to this city two weeks ago.
The tiger also appeared in this city two weeks ago.
You were in Tsurumi four days ago.
The tiger was also sighted there four days ago.
Remember what Kunikida-kun said?
The Armed Detective Agency is comprised of individuals with supernatural powers.
Though not a well-known fact,
there are quite a few individuals who possess supernatural abilities in this world.
Some use their powers to achieve great success,
while others fall into ruin as a result of being unable to control their powers.
I'm guessing that the institution
staff knew who the tiger was,
but declined to enlighten you.
You were the only one who remained ignorant.
You also have supernatural powers.
You have the ability to transform into
a wild beast in the moonlight.
That’s impressive.
You could easily...
snap a person's neck.
Whoa, there.
It wouldn't be terrible to meet one's end
being eaten by a beast,
but you wont be able to kill me.
My ability is...
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No Longer Human.
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
My ability allows me to dispel other abilities
through a simple touch.
I'm not into hugging men.
Thud
Hey, Dazai!
Oh, you're late, Kunikida-kun.
I've captured the tiger.
What, it's this boy?
He has the ability to transform into a tiger.
Jeez.
What was with this note?
"A tiger will appear in the warehouse
in the fifteenth district."
"Secure the perimeter so that it can't escape."
It's an excellent, concise note.
You've left out the most important detail!
Next time, explain in advance.
Thanks to you, I had to bring in
guys who weren't even on duty.
Take them out for drinks later.
Hey!
Yosano Akiko
Ability:
Thou Shalt Not Die
What, no casualties?
How boring.
Edogawa Rampo
Ability:
Ultra-Deduction
You've come a long way, Dazai.
Though you still have a ways to go before you even can compare with me.
Miyazawa Kenji
Ability:
Be Not
Defeated
by the
Rain
But what shall we to do with him?
He didn't know he was doing it, right?
Yeah, you're right.
Kunikida Doppo
Ability:
Doppo
Poet
What do you think, Dazai?
The ward's designated him as a major threat.
Dazai Osamu
Ability:
No
Longer
Human
I've already made a decision.
They called me a failure at the orphanage for as long as I can remember.
And now, I don't even know where I'll sleep tonight, or if I'll eat tomorrow.
No one would care if someone like me were to die in a ditch somewhere.
Yeah, I may be better off eaten by a tiger.
We'll make him one of us.
Nice!
Are you serious?
You're a real idiot, Dazai.
What gives you the right to decide that?
There, there.
Wake up, boy!
Here, in a city teeming
with the supernatural,
in a detective agency
teeming with eccentrics,
a strange tale is about to unfold.
This is only a sign of things to come.
A premonition, if you will.
Now...
Huh?
I...
Atsushi-kun.
Do you remember nothing at all
from when you were transformed?
What are you talking about?
Oh.
But your right hand's still transformed.
Right hand?
What?!
Nakajima Atsushi
Ability:
Beast
Beneath
The
Moonlight
What the?
What's this?
What the hell?!
Nakajima Atsushi!
You'll become one of us.
From this day forth, you'll be a member of the Armed Detective Agency.
Huh?
It's been a long time since I've slept on a futon.
I feel reborn.
Hey, brat.
There's an emergency.
Hightail it over to the detective agency.
An emergency?
A bomber's taken a hostage and cozied up in our office.
I don't want to go!
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, episode 2,
Episode 2
A Certain Bomb
"A Certain Bomb."
Ability: Doppo Poet.