Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo, a defender of peace
and the freedom of hair
is perhaps one of the
greatest heroes of the century!
I mean, I think he's a hero.
No, no, he's rather hero-like.
Can't you give him a break!?
Wobble
Well, leaving that aside...
You're leaving it!?
Sparkling!
In what can only be deemed as a twist of fate
Bo-bobo and the mysterious Beauty
begin their journey!
Pickle will be never seen again.
Pickle
REJECTED
Don Patch
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
He's not hajikeing at all.
Lil' Patch Army
Hang on, Boss!
Hajike Gang's Junior Boss
Wig Gang! Why can't you leave us alone!?
Beauty
Wig Gang?
It's written as
"Tears of the Hair"
But you read it "Sentimental".
But you read it
"Sentimental".
Canine Party
For a new Japan
Vote Pooch
Corruption upon corruption.
What has Japan come to?
But that's why you're here,
to change things like that.
Yeah, that's right.
The results of the election are in!
So, how big was the margin?
Pooch: zero votes
Sucks
to be
you!
We lost with zero votes!
Impossible!
But I've been thinking so much about Japan!
Why? Why? Why?
Because you're a dog...
Maybe because you're a dog.
That was live at the electoral
headquarters of the Canine Party
You won't hunt our hair! You won't hunt it!
You won't hunt it!
Okay! You did rather well.
I was kinda nervous.
Are you gonna keep ignoring him?
Soda! Give him soda!
Boss! Boss! Hang on, Boss!
Pierre! Pierre!
What was that?
And who's this 'Pierre'?
Give him some more!
Don Patch!
Boss!
Wait! My hat!
My precious hat
my mommy gave me!
You're all so mean to hide it!
Boss! Boss!
- Wig Gang!
- Boss!
You're being really rude, you know that?
I'm not one of these Wigs.
What!? Then who are you!?
You mean you can't tell just by looking?
That's why he's stuck here...
Not at all!
- Boss!
- Boss! Come back!
Boss, you're not a hat!
What!? You mean I'm not a hat!?
Note: In Japanese, the sound a "higurashi," a species of cicada, makes is "tsuku-boushi." "Boushi" is also the word for hat.
Chirp, hat...
He's not a hat...
Man, you sure are something.
You really had me thinking
I was actually your hat.
You're a high level hajikelist.
Interesting!
I challenge you to a Hajike Duel!
-Sure, if you wanna.
- Yeah!
In that case,
let's duel with the expert rules!
The Expert Rules:
A special set of rules for
high-level Hajikelists.
The rules are to go crazy
using a common theme.
Boss's definitely gonna Hajike!
It's over for this guy!
The theme will be...
The theme...
-Christmas!
-Wrong season!
Risumi
- Farewell, Risuo.
-Don't leave me, Risumi!
Risuo
My hat fell off...
He wasn't a hat!
Okay, let's begin!
Don Patch Theater
~A Sentimental Eve~
A Sentimental Eve.
Get your fish sticks here!
Nice, hot, fish sticks!
Patch the Fish Stick Vendor.
Get your fish sticks here!
How bizarre, it's Christmas...
Yet no one's bought any.
It's cold... freezing.
But I can't go back home
'til I've sold all of them. What can I do?
Hurry up! Come on, the party's gonna start!
Okay, we should get there on time.
Ladies and gents, welcome..
Ah, it's starting!
...to the fish stick party.
Fish Sticks!?
Hey guys! Let's eat some fish sticks!
Silence
Hey! Hey!
Eat my fishsticks!
Give it up.
- What's wrong with him?
- I don't wanna!
What the hell are you doing!?
It's my business!
It's my family business!
So please buy some fish sticks!
Buy them... then eat them!
Fish sticks!
The End
So, what do you think of my hajike?
Bravo, Boss!
Fish sticks! Fish Sticks! Fish sticks!
- A beautiful story...
- How?
What-?
Where-?
So, do you admit defeat?
Never. Let me show you
how to really Hajike.
What?
Three years ago in Nagoya,
on Christmas Eve.
Note: Beauty is referring to kishimen, a type of noodle from Nagoya.
Is this gonna be about noodles?
Bo-bobo Theater:
A miracle of youth and love
A miracle of youth and love.
Filmed in
Hokkaido
Yagi Residence
Proverb Quiz:
Fill in the blanks!
Question:
If I answer this question right,
I get a year's supply of Kimchi!
Yes, capsaicin!
Pearls before swine,
g______ to cats.
"Pearls before swine, g____ to cats."
I've got it!
Note: This is a japanese proverb. The answer was "koban", or "gold", but Bo-bobo wrote "konbanwa", or "good evening".
"Good evening to cats!"
That Kimchi is all mine!
Ah... I want a girlfriend...
The End
That's sad! That is way too sad!
No, I can't believe it!
That shouldn't happen on Christmas!
But he answered wrong!
By a long shot!
Say it isn't true!
I wish I could tell you it isn't true!
But it's true!
So very true!
I can't win...
Boss!
Hang on, Boss!
Don Patch!
For you to reveal such a sad past,
you're quite the Hajikelist.
In that case,
I'll give it all I've got!
Boss's so determined!
We're gonna see Boss's true Hajikeing!
Purukogi... Purukogi...
Purukogi
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
Why purukogi ...
What the hell?
That's the extent of your Hajike?
I'm not impressed.
Transform!
Shuriken
Shuriken!
He's lost it!
Screw the Hajike Duel! I'm gonna kill you!
Sure-killing!
Don Patch Shuriken Attack!
Cry! Cry!
Burst into tears!
Weird... Bo-bobo ought to
be dodging the attack!
How bizarre! It's not supposed to...
That's why I told you you weren't ready
to pilot Bo-bobo yet!
Shut up! I can do
this just fine!
Where's the finishing move?
Doesn't he have a finishing move?
Finishing Move:  Docking ♪
That's it!
Docking!
Ah? What's that?
Come to me, Aircraft #1!
Aircraft #2!
Aircraft #3!
Aircraft #4!
Formation...
Assemble!
Assembling complete.
How is this an assembly!?
That combo is so not fair, oink!
What happened to parts 1 and 2?
Naw, that combo's cool.
This technique...
Let me play too!
Wait a minute!
Boss...
It's gonna end like that?
So... who's that Wig Gang
you were talking about?
They're villains that torture the people of Hajike Village with the Hair Hunt.
But that means...
Bo-bobo, this village has been
attacked by the Hair Hunters too!
Let me go! Let me go!
What a nice head of hair!
Boss! It's Wig Gang!
It's H-block's Deputy Captain!
H-Block Deputy Captain: Tarashi
It's H-Block's Tarashi!
What?
You picked the wrong day to mess with me!
Bo-bobo, save me! Bo-bobo!
He ignored me--!
I blossomed!
Note: This is a pun on saying "He left."
Oh, you've finally blossomed!
-He blossomed!
Curses! No one ignores me and gets away with it!
This means war!
We're gonna break into their base and kick their asses right? Let's do this!
No, I must do this alone.
Why!?
Because you guys are weak.
Weak...
Dammit!
In that case, I'll go with you.
He blossomed even more!
The Wig Gang is part of
the Hair Hunters.
That's a good enough reason for
me to beat the crap out of them.
This man and I share the same fate.
In that case...
His fate is to...
become my ally.
Okay! Follow me!
Floral attack!
He's good!
The two greatest Hajikelists
teaming up together...
Hair Hunter Brigade  H-Block Base (Wig Gang)
So, how 'bout that winter uniform?
I know, right?
With those cute little white boots...
What's that noise?
English
Class
Office lady.
What is that?
I am office layayaya-dy.
Oh, good.
Now, let's move on to lesson two.
If I don't learn English,
I'll never get a good job.
What a bad day!
Ah, it's coming this way!
Reinforce our defenses!
Hanage Shinken Ougi!
Patchmi, wanna go to karaoke?
Yeah, let's go!!
Why do you guys wear wigs?
H-Block is very fashion-conscious.
So we get special
authorization to wear wigs.
So that's why they call you the "Wig Gang."
As you can see, we get tons
of love letters.
Give me love letters!
Love letter! Gimme gimme gimme!!!
What have you done with Beauty?
Hell if we know!
We'll kill you!
Sure-killing...
Porcupine Blowfish!!!!
A'ight, good distraction!
We're gonna Hajike our asses off!
These guys are strong...
Too strong...
Well, well, well, look who it is.
What business do you have here?
H-Block Captain: Maitel
So you're the gang leader?
What the hell!?
Have you heard of Medusa?
The Greek monster who could
turn you to stone with a single glance.
What? Don't tell me--
That's right!
I have the eyes of the Medusa!
Stop it!
I'm turning to stone!
You too!
Stop it!
- I'm turning into a carrot!
- What!?
Weren't you just a carrot!?
Eh--------!?
*Stare*
No, I turned into a cabbage!
Why couldn't I be lettuce!?
Don't screw with me!
I'll kill you!
Hey, I'm still changing!
Slow down, the beach isn't going anywhere.
And don't you try to catch me,
Or else I'll run away!
I turned back into a carrot!
How the hell did you turn into a carrot!?
No good. I can't beat him as a cabbage.
What are you doing?
Amateur Ballad Night
Welcome to Amateur Ballad Night.
Please welcome our first singer, Mr. Don Patch!
Hajike Highway Blizzard of Love
singing, "Hajike Highway Blizzard of Love."
Nonsense... it's useless!
Go ahead!
♪ Hajike... highway... ♫
What!?
You piece of crap, how
dare you turn me to stone!
I'll kick your ass!
Impossible! How did my
attack not work?
Don Patch, catch!
Okay! This.. this is...
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Here we go!
Falalel! Palalel!
Magical power!
And miraculous power!
With the power of magic and miracles--
Disperse the Evil Spirits!
That has nothing to do with Magic and Miracles!
Of all the times!
Hello, Maitel speaking.
Ah, Kaori! What is it?
I got the cute girls for tonight!
Wait, that was today!?
Did you remember to bring 4 hot guys?
There is no way.
That party was today!?
And I was gonna hook up with Kaori, too...
I can't find three hot guys...
You've got me.
Weren't you a cabbage?
Hey, hurry up, guys!
Don't keep a lady waiting!
You guys are definitely not coming!
And besides, I need four guys!
We'd be short one person anyway!
Look over there.
All acounted for.
Tsuchinoko Bar
So you're sure these guys will be hot, right?
Of course!
What's all that noise?
Note: Try is a touchdown in Rugby.
Try!
Dumbasses! You're only supposed to use one shoulder!
Alright, good hustle!
Party! Party! I'll win Kaori's heart!
Oh, the bath's open.
Hey, get over here.
Just a moment, dear. I'm coming.
Here I go!
We're leaving!
I can't believe you!
No! Wait, Kaori!
This is all your fault!
Dammit!
Thanks for these past 3 years, teacher
The students of Class A want to say
we couldn't have made it this far without you.
It's thanks to you, teach,
that we all succeeded.
Thank you so much!
Thanks so much!
Teacher!
Teacher? Me?
We all love you, teach!
You all...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The farewell party is at 5 o'clock
at the Karaoke bar !!
Farewell, teacher!
A Hair Hunter like you...
Has no right to teach
innocent children!
Now where is Beauty?
Who's that?
Don't play dumb! That girl
that Tarashi kidnapped!
His bad habit's kicked in again.
He's the kinda guy who loves to
hunt the hair of young girls.
Right about now, he's probably--
What beautiful hair.
Just perfect for my new wig!
I'm gonna hunt your hair...
...without hesitation!
What happened?
Who is he?
Who is this mysterious young
man who saved Beauty in the nick of time?
I think he's kinda cool!
Happiness! Happiness! Happiness! Joy!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong, you say? It's the Hajike Festival!
Can't you tell?
I can't tell. Sorry.
Hey, you should try a
little Hajike some time, Beauty!
Like hell I will!
Next time on
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
26-Year-Old Duck Underwear!
Why is it 26 years old?