I...
Apology
from an
Armed
Detective
Agency
Member
Apology
from an
Armed
Detective
Agency
Member
Tanizaki
Junichirou
I... I...
I'm so sorry!
Huh?
Even thought it was just your exam,
I was so rude to you.
My name is Tanizaki Junichirou.
I work as an assistant of sorts at the agency.
Please, it's all right.
He's really not a bad person.
And this is—
His little sister, Naomi.
Y-You're siblings?!
I'm not sure I see a family resemblance.
Oh?
You doubt us?
Of course we're blood related siblings.
We're quite similar, especially this part.
Right, brother?
Oh, but...
Don't pursue this line of
inquiry with them too far.
Er, okay.
Atsushi reads
between the lines
In any event, brat,
today you have joined the ranks
of the Armed Detective Agency.
Never be a burden to anyone,
nor shame the Agency's good name.
The rest of us are sworn
to that, at least.
Right, Dazai?
Would you strangle me with these
fragile, delicate fingers?
Are you shaming the Agency's name already!?
You bastard! Don't bother asking for
her help all the time!
I'll wring your neck with my own bony fingers!
By the way,
Two Seniors
Shaming
the Agency's
Good Name
what did you two do
before you joined the Agency?
Uh, no real meaning behind
that question, by the way.
Take a guess.
Huh?
Oh, it's a game we often play.
The rookie tries to guess his
seniors' former occupations.
Well, it's part of their training
as detectives.
Tanizaki-san and Naomi-san... were students?
Oh, bingo.
I'm impressed.
How did you know?
I heard you're a part-time worker,
and I thought you might still
be a student given your uniform.
Tanizaki-san seems near
me in age, so... just a hunch.
Honesty is a virtue.
What about Kunikida-kun?
Who cares about what I used to be?!
Public worker?
An official?!
Close.
He was a teacher.
A math teacher.
Huh...
Of course you'd use Euler's formula here!
I can totally see that.
It's all in the past!
I don't even want to think about it.
What about me, then?
You, Dazai-san?
Yes, me.
Dazai-san was...
It's no good.
I have no idea.
Don't bother, brat.
His former profession is one of the seven
mysteries of the Armed Detective Agency.
The first person to get it
right receives a reward, right?
A reward?
That's right.
No one's been able to guess right,
so the reward's just ballooned.
Ballooned...
Reward!
B-By the way,
just how much has this reward
ballooned to, exactly?
700,000 yen in all.
Seven hundred grand?!
Oh!
The man
has a fire
lit under
him ——
The man
has a fire
lit under
him ——
S-So if I get it right, I can claim it?
Currently
penniless.
at the thought
of a 700,000
reward
at the thought
of a 700,000
reward
Are you actually serious?!
A suicide advocate is true to his word.
Atsushi-kun looks ecstatic.
His determination is admirable.
Seven hundred grand will be mine!
Speculator?
No.
Writer?
Nope!
Office worker?
Wrong!
Researcher!
No.
Lawyer?
No!
Journalist?
Boo.
Carpenter!
Nope.
Fortune teller!
No.
Pilot!
Wrong.
They're all random...
Interpreter!
Non, non!
Yeah...
Japanese Chef.
Booo.
They really are.
Doctor?
No way.
Shinto priest!
No!
Actor!
No! But...
That's flattering.
I bet you were just wandering
around doing nothing.
Nope.
I would never lie about this.
Do you yield, Atsushi-kun?
Then you can take the check.
What?
If you can't pay right now,
you can start a tab.
After all, it's the
Agency's go-to restaurant,
the Vortex.
Yes, this is Tanizaki.
Yes, okay.
Got it.
We have a job?
Yes.
The client's already at the Agency.
Well, it's time to work.
Let's save the guessing
game for another time.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
So...
You've mentioned that you'd like
to request an investigation,
but what manner of investigation
are we speaking of here?
Beautiful.
You're a lady as ephemeral and
elegant as a lotus blossom.
Would you be willing to join me
in a double suicide—
What?
Ah.
Apologies for the disturbance.
Don't worry.
Please disregard what just happened.
Please continue.
Regarding my request...
Y-Yes?
Wow.
She's managing to carry on as
though everything's normal.
Well, it seems there's
recently been a group of
unsavory people loitering in
my company building's back alley.
And by unsavory, you mean...
They appear to be dressed in rags.
Some of them have been heard
speaking a foreign language.
They must be smugglers or some such.
The military police may police all they want,
but they keep multiplying
like rats on a ship.
They're inevitable in a port town.
Right.
If we had evidence that
they're running afoul of the law,
we could ask the military police.
So...
You want us to investigate the
place and get that evidence.
Brat.
Huh?
You will go.
What?!
It's a simple stakeout job.
Besides, smugglers are mostly harmless.
They're usually only good
at making a break for it.
It's the perfect first job for you.
But...
Tanizaki, go with him.
If he's going, I'm going, too!
Nakajima
Atsushi
Rookie
Detective
Nervous
about
his first job.
Nakajima
Atsushi
Rookie
Detective
Nervous
about
his first job.
Hey, brat.
It's not that I lack sympathy for
your misfortunate, undeserved life.
As such, I'll give you a hint
for surviving in this city.
Don't run into him.
If you do, run.
Who is he?
A mafioso.
Though we call them that because
we know nothing else.
They're a vicious mob
who claims the port as their territory.
They're called the Port Mafia.
They're the most dangerous gang in
this city's underground.
Of them, the one in this photo
is a very dangerous man beyond
even the Agency's reach.
Why is he dangerous?
Because he's gifted.
His ability happens to be of the ruthless
sort designed for slaughter.
Not even the cops
stand a chance against him.
I wouldn't want to fight him, either.
What's his name?
It's Akutagawa.
I found a bag on the ground.
I think its owner lost it.
Ah, lost and found.
Then if you could fill out this form...
Hm?
I've seen you before.
That's impressive.
I've already been found out.
Wait, is he the wanted fugitive?!
Stop!
The military police of this
city are a distinguished force.
Excuse me,
could help me find—
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Abi:lity
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Abi:lity
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Wanted:
Akutagawa
Ryuunosuke
Ability:
Rashoumon
Episode 3
Yokohama Gangster Paradise
Done.
What's next?
It takes two to commit double suici—
Hey, Dazai.
What about the job?
I'm waiting for a sign from above.
Huh?
With two, you can...
Double-suicide... Double-suicide...
That's scary, all right.
It's not funny.
All this talk about vicious
mafia and how you can die,
I'm not sure I'm cut out for this.
Well, even I've been able to manage.
You'll be fine.
But you're also gifted, right?
Your ability must be different
from my own useless one.
I wouldn't set your expectations too high.
My ability's not suited for combat.
You have a wonderful ability.
I love it.
Stop, Naomi.
Not here.
Oh, are you talking back to me?
I wonder what mouth's saying
such cheeky things.
We're here.
Huh?
This way.
It's kind of creepy.
That's strange.
Is this really the right place?
Um...
The name's Higuchi.
Higuchi-san.
Smugglers are a cowardly bunch.
They'll always have an escape route.
But this is a dead end.
If anyone came after them
from there,
they'd have nowhere to run.
That's right.
I apologize. I led you into a trap.
My real target was you!
Port Mafia:
Higuchi Ichiyou
Akutagawa-senpai.
Akutagawa?!
I have them, as planned.
Excellent.
I'll be there in five.
She's...
...with the Port Mafia!
Brother... Are you okay?
Naomi?
Naomi!
God, what should I do?
Oh, right! Tourniquet!
Atsushi-kun, do you have
a tourniquet on you?!
No, first, I must clean the wound...
No!
I have to get her to Dr. Yosano.
We... We have to take her to the infirmary!
Atsushi-kun, get her legs!
My investigations have already revealed
that you are a non-combatant member.
Let's have you follow the noble
princess to the afterlife.
What?
You two-bit thug...
How dare you hurt Naomi!
Ability: Light Snow!
Snow at this time of year?
Atsushi-kun, stay far back.
This one... is mine to kill!
What?
My Light Snow ability
transforms the entire space
with snowfall into a screen.
What?
I have overlaid the background
scenery onto my image.
You can't see me anymore!
I may not be able to see you,
but bullets can still hit you!
Wrong.
Die!
Fear death.
Fear slaughter.
Those who desire death
have an equal desire to die.
Therefore...
Don't run into him!
If you do, run!
It's nice to meet you.
I am Akutagawa,
one the Port Mafia's dogs, as is she.
Akutagawa-senpai!
I can handle this myself.
I believe my orders were to
take the weretiger alive!
And yet here you are, gunning everyone down.
You useless bitch!
Stand down.
I'm sorry.
Take the weretiger alive?
What are you after?
My target has always been you
and you alone, weretiger.
Your fellow agents lying there
just got caught in the crossfire.
This is because of me?
Indeed.
That is your karma, weretiger.
You cause misfortune for everyone
around you, just by living.
Get out, you failure!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
You'll never find a place where you belong!
My karma?
Ability:
Rashoumon.
I missed on purpose that time, of course.
But my Rashoumon has poor taste.
It devours anything and everything.
I intend to capture you alive,
but if you continue to resist,
I'll take your leg next.
Why...
Why me?
Is this my fault, too?
Do I make everyone around me
suffer just by living?
A... Atsushi-kun.
Run, Atsushi-kun.
They're still alive.
Today you have joined the ranks
of our Armed Detective Agency.
Never be a burden to anyone,
nor shame the Agency's good name.
Choosing death over submission,
how tiresome.
That move wasn't half bad.
But in the end, it was a fool's last stand.
I told you.
My black beast is indiscriminate.
It devours anything and everything.
It consumed the very space bullets
were attempting to cross to reach me.
Neither spears nor flames can reach me
without a space to traverse.
How is anyone supposed to attack him, then?
And I am a man who keeps his word.
Quit crying, brat!
Only children who have parents
to care of them
are allowed to cry without reservation!
A child abandoned by his parents
has no license to cry!
That's right.
I've been abandoned countless
times over the course of my life.
I was never allowed to cry,
no one ever accepted me,
and I never had a place I could call home.
And yet, I...
What?
His right leg regenerated.
This is how it should be.
Akutagawa-senpai!
Stand down, Higuchi!
What?
Senpai!
You!
The bullets can't penetrate its skin.
Rashoumon:
Agito!
I was supposed to take you alive.
This is...
So I just ripped apart a mirage? Then,
Rashoumon:
Murakumo!
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
Okay, that's enough!
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
No
Longer
Human
What?
You're one of the detectives.
Why are you here?
I'm the type who can't stop thinking about
what a beautiful lady might be up to.
I decided to secretly listen in.
Impossible.
Back then...
You had already seen through
my plans then.
Come on, wake up, Atsushi-kun.
I don't want to carry three
people back at the same time.
You think we'll let you go alive?
Don't, Higuchi.
You can't win.
But, Akutagawa-senpai...
Dazai-san, we'll retreat for this round.
But the weretiger will be
the Port Mafia's someday.
Why?
Simple enough.
That weretiger has a bounty
on him from the black market.
The bounty sum is seven billion yen.
Now, that's very generous.
We'll pay a visit to your
Agency at a later time.
The Port Mafia will claim that seven billion.
Is that a declaration of war
on the Armed Detective Agency?
Try it... if you dare.
You're a small-scale operation,
whereas we are this city's
darkness made incarnate.
We have connections in this city's
politics and economy at every level.
An agency with a dozen or so operatives
will become ashes along with your
office in three days' time.
No one has opposed us and lived.
I know all that.
Indeed.
You know that better than anyone
being an ex-Port Mafia member, Dazai-san.
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
I heard, brat.
There's a bounty on your head to the tune
of seven billion on the black market.
Wh-Wh-What should I do?
Maybe the Port Mafia will
come raid the Agency.
But why me?
You caused this.
Think about what you can do.
What I can do?
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, episode 4:
The Tragedy of the Fatalist.
Episode 4
The Tragedy of the Fatalist