H-Block Captain: Maitel
Bo-bobo challenged Maitel, Captain of H-Block.
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
But then Maitel,
realizing he had forgotten about his important engagement,
headed straight to the party with Bo-bobo.
Maitel was irritated by
Bo-bobo's constant hajikeing.
However,
In the end...
He was overwhelmed by
innocence of youth.
The farewell party is at 5
o'clock at the karaoke bar!
Wait a minute! What about my role?
You remember what happened!
Don Patch
There, like that!
I did this too, all like, BAAANG!
That's when I shouted "Don Patch!"
I even got chased like that!
Here, I JUUUMped, with a BANG!
Not to mention my Porcupine Blowfish!
And this is where I turned into a ballad singer, and then a Shuriken!
Wait, what? Oh, right. The magic and miracles thing. I did that too.
And so on, wait for it... DoDoDoDON!
Purukogi? Oh, this is popular. I did this at school.
Well, hey there, look out for more of my
crazy antics this episode, so stay tuned!
Beauty
That boy who saved me...
I wonder who he was?
The mysterious boy
Man, I'm so hungry...
I want a hamburger...
I'm not totally sure why
but I really want a hamburger.
If only there was a huge hamburger just lying around...
I give up, I'll never find one.
Say, Beauty...
Uh-huh?
Look at me.
No.
How unusual.
Hajike Village's Hajike Festival
Bo-bobo and Beauty arrived
at the famous Hajike Village.
where everyone's insane.
Today was the village's annual
Hajike Village
Hajike Festival.
I was worried that it would flop this year!
The fish is great!
I can't take it anymore!
Anything's fine! I
realrly have to eat!
Come on, let's go get something to eat!
Huh?
What's the matter, Bo-bobo?
I just don't get it.
I've tried so hard, but...
I don't know if I'll ever
understand how a hamburger feels.
That's why...
Waaaaaah!
Don't be so hard on yourself!
"Burger"
You're...
Avocado Burger
I'm Avocado Burger.
Mister Avocado Burger!
You did your best.
That's what counts.
You're very brave.
Do you really think so?
Just kidding!
Oh, I'm sorry, Avocado Burger.
Did you think we were friends?
Bo-bobo is acting so odd today...
Now I have to slay the townsfolk!
I guess I'll start with these guys around me!
What the hell are you saying!?
Pudding!
Jelly!
What's the matter with you!?
You're acting so strange today!
Happiness! Joy!
Potato Butter!
That's not tickling!
Happiness! Joy!
Grilled octopus!
What's going on?
Don't ignore me!
Mont Blanc!
Honey!
Happiness! Joy!
What the hell is the matter with you?
What do you think you're doing?
The Townspeoples' Delegate
Freeze!
You will not escape!
How dare you!
I won't forgive you!
Calm down will ya!
- Let's go!
- But where?
Hey, hold it!
Don't let them get away!
I'll capture you! I'll capture you and get promoted!
Pawn
Hey!
Silence
Bastards!
Promoted Pawn
I got promoted!
But where are we going?
Listen to the wind.
I love you!
What's going on?
Chinese Man
Marry me! Marry me!
Beauty!
I'll avenge you, Beauty!
Bo-bobo!
You're finished!
We've got you surrounded!
There's no escape!
- Give up!
- What'll we do?
The legendary Hajike Village,
filled with such amazing Hajikelists...
Bring me your best hajikelist!
I'll take him on!
- He's gotta be crazy!
- What?
Stop screwing around!
That sounds like
a challenge!
That sounds like a challenge!
That... that voice!
The Three Dynamite Brothers
The Three Dynamite Brothers!
Sounds like fun! But we'll
decide the rules!
- As you wish.
- Okay!
Simply whoever hajikes
the best wins, got it?
Sure, why not.
Then I'll start.
A laptop?
With one simple click...
You can play the stock market!
Well, time to buy my
first ever stocks!
That's crazy for a beginner!
I'll start by randomly picking some...
Idiot! Slow down!
Stop now! Hey, bro! I've known so many
people who have lost at the stock market!
Stop!
You can never go back!
Collapse! Collapse! Collapse!
Already?
You're bankrupt...
So... how much did you invest?
500 million.
500 million!
That's hajikeing too far!
Piece of crap, you call that hajikeing?
It's my turn now!
Big bro!
No, you can't!
Certainly this is the only way I can win!
Stop!
Snap out of it, bro!
Moron, this is the only way!
If you explode, you'll
kill all the villagers!
I don't give a crap!
It's my turn!
Big Brother!
Bro!
Nobody can stop me now!
You guys are totally screwed!
Say, I've been thinking...
That guy's not dynamite, he's a firework!
Me? I'm a firework?
Hey! She's right!
You're really a firework?
Big brother!
Bro!
Parachute Fireworks
So he had a built-in parachute...
How dare you! You're screwed now!
This is unforgivable!
Everybody, may I have your attention!
Huh? Who...
Who said that?
Please quiet down.
Squash's vocalist: Kazutaka
This is our last concert together.
No, don't split up!
Shut up and listen!
You know them?
Here we go, our last number!
''Heart-pounding Animal Land!"
Squash
Amazing!
Rabbit, tiger, lion!
Sheep, deer, cow, monkey,
tiger and giraffe!
Hippos, seals, and otters!
Whale!
Salmon!
They're so into it...
For salmon!?
No, please don't split up...
Bo-bobo!
Squash!
So that's why Bo-bobo was
acting so weird today...
Duck, deer, pheasant, sealion, buffalo!
Their great producer?
The Great Producer
My job here is done.
Panda! Camel, bear, and rhinoceros!
You're gonna look for the next big star?
I'll move on.
Thanks for everything!
Nessie!
A convenience store?
Oh, yeah! I forgot I was hungry!
Great! I can finally grab a bite!
What?
Where am I? When did I get here?
Bo-bobo!
That's odd...
Where's Bo-bobo?
And-- cut! We're halfway done!
- Wow, that was fast.
- Dolts, where was I!?
Oh well, I'll be the star in the second half! Don't miss it!
Sorry for the wait!
Prepare for a bundle of fun with me in the second half!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo! Where are you?
I give up. I'm totally lost.
And plus, I'm still hungry as hell...
That made me jump... Don't scare me like that!
Woof.
It was a dream.
Oh?
A duck! How cute!
Oh, what happened to you?
Did you lose Mommy and Daddy?
Hey, little girl, you like ducks too?
You pervert!
No, you pervert!
That sounded like Beauty.
Triple!
You win again?
Let me go, you pervert!
I know you're with Bo-bobo.
Where is he?
It won't end well for you
if you don't tell me.
Stop it, you big pervert!
Bo-bobo!
Sorry I'm late, guys!
Beauty, you okay?
Where did the bad man touch you?
What did he do, Beauty?
Snap out of it, Beauty!
Don't touch me...
So it's you...
Okay, fine. Just give me a second to change.
So this guy is
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo.
Is this pervert really him?
Did this guy really beat
Hägen and Maitel, and destroy the
G and H-Block bases?
He just seems like an ordinary pervert to me...
But that might be part of his plan.
I do, however, know one thing about him...
He's a vegetarian!
Vegetarians love vegetables
Are you Bo-bobo?
Who wants to know?
Assassination Brigade: Kilaliino
Kilaliino of the Assassination Brigade.
I was hired to assassinate
the man who took out the G and H-Block bases...you!
I'm a trained assassin, don't take me for one of those pansy Hair Hunters!
You're dead meat!
As you wish. I will take you on.
I've put some flags on.
What country is that?
Stop screwing around!
I will show you the terror that is...
The Assassination Squad!
Bo-bobo, don't lose to the pervert with the stupid underwear!
Of course! I'd never lose to a
"Stupid Underwear"
guy wearing stupid underwear.
Shut up! I wouldn't wear this thing if it weren't our uniform!
What was that?
Wha...
Who you callin' stupid underwear?
Wha!
The underwear...
talked?
Takashi
Really, what the hell was that?
If I weren't in a good mood,
you'd all be dead by now.
You got that?
- Right?
- Yes...
Yo, you, girl!
Yes?
Tell me what I am.
I'm... not exactly sure...
Dumbass!
What the hell do I look like?
I'm a cute freaking duck!
You don't even understand that?
Idiot! I should kill you!
Forgive me.
Do I look like something other than a duck?
Well, yes, because you're not one.
Dad?
Hey! You look good, Takashi.
Takashi's Father
What the hell are you doing?
You'll understand when you're older.
But...
How am I not a duck!? Tell me now!
Well, fine, Takashi...
I guess it's time I gave you the whole truth.
Now...
I don't want to worry about this later.
I will tell you.
Bo-bobo Theater:
The storm of love is calling!
Back when I was your age,
Takeshi's Dad- 26 years old
26 years old,
There was a huge marriage boom,
and all the ducks around me
were marrying, one by one.
Man, this sucks!
I need to get married quick!
And that was when...
I met her.
Her name was Kaori.
Kaori
She was your mother.
Without a care in the world,
we started going out right away.
Two years later, against the
wishes of my family, I got married...
To panties...
I found a job.
About a year later, we had a beautiful baby boy.
That baby... was you, Takashi!
And we all lived happily ever after.
The End
So you were born of the union between a duck and panties.
That can't be true... I'm underwear?
No, you're definitely not underwear either.
So I'm not underwear or a duck?
Then what the hell am I!?
You're a swan.
A swan?
Actually, I knew it all along, that I was a swan...
Only... I couldn't accept it. I didn't want to accept it.
Chin up, Takashi!
It doesn't matter if you're a swan or not...
You are who you are!
You can be whatever you wish to be!
Dad!
- Kilaliino...!
- Yes, sir!
Can you... put me back on?
I have no more doubts!
I am... underwear!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
A Family of Glasses!
And bifocals, too!
Kilaliino of the assassination brigade...
In some way, he was a terrifying foe.
That's right!
Here we go, Beauty.
So that was the Fist of the Nose Hair, huh?
I'm starved!
I want a hamburger!
I don't know why, but I really want a hamburger.
If only there was a really big hamburger lying around somewhere...
Ah, I give up, It'd never happen...
- Hey, Beauty.
- Uh-huh?
Look at me.
No.
Bo-bobo defeated the cruel Kilaliino.
But what about this strange boy with a skull on his back?
What does destiny have in store for Bo-bobo?
Who gives a crap about his fate?
Screw this!
I didn't get any screentime today!
Here's a message to my 10 million fans:
I'll be the star next episode, so stay tuned!
Ah, look! A nose hair in Bo-bobo's nose!
It's always like that...
Ew! That thing's huge!
Oh, this must be that legendary nose hair that shows up once every 3000 years.
3000 years??
- Well, time to go to graduation.
- You're a student?
Next time on
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Bababa-ba Ba-baba, The Great King Nose Hair?
Who's Bababa-Ba Ba-Baba?