Take the weretiger alive?
What are you after?
My target has always been you,
and you alone, weretiger.
Your fellow agents lying there
just got caught in the crossfire.
This is because of me?
Indeed.
That is your karma, weretiger.
You cause misfortune for
everyone around you, just by living.
My karma?
Ability:
Rashoumon.
Where... am I?
I see you've come to, brat.
Kunikida... san?
Damn, I can't believe you pulled
this during such a busy time.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
I...
I was... attacked by the Mafia.
I remember now.
Kunikida-san, where are
Tanizaki-san and Naomi-san?!
Calm down.
They're both okay.
Are you... sure?
Yes.
Dr. Yosano is currently treating
Tanizaki next door.
What a nice big injury
you've racked up, huh, Tanizaki?
Do you like my treatment that much?
All right, I'll give you an extra
special treatment this time.
Ah.
That's... treatment?
I heard, brat.
Huh?
You've got a seven-billion-yen bounty
on your head on the black market.
What?
Seven billion, huh?
You've moved up in the world.
No wonder the Port Mafia is keen
to get its hands on you.
Seven billion?
My target has always been you,
and you alone, weretiger.
I see.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What should I do?
The Mafia might raid the Agency!
But why me?
Don't panic.
The Port Mafia is
certainly quite violent,
but stay calm.
Freaking out can kill even the best.
Ideal
That's what my mentor told me.
Um, it's upside down.
Your notebook.
I'm not freaking out!
I'm not going to panic over the Mafia!
I'd beat them back, even if
they attacked this very second!
I'll go like this, and this!
Kunikida-san's pretty wound up.
Slash and burn like a pro,
His explanation's all over the place!
stabbity-stab, and beat them all!
It must mean the Agency's
situation is pretty dire,
and it's all because of me.
He'll come for sure.
You caused this.
The worst case scenario may come to pass.
Think about what you can do.
What I can do?
By the way, brat.
I've been looking for something.
Have you seen my glasses?
Episode 4
The Tragedy of the Fatalist
It's time.
Stand back.
Sorry to bother you at work, folks.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
We're here for work, as well.
We'll be done soon enough.
We've heard rumors that an unruly bunch
have been selling Port Mafia
cargo on the black market.
They're supposedly based right here.
We're just looking for evidence.
Would you mind if I examined the cargo?
There's the evidence, right here.
That's impossible!
It's a steel pipe.
You've never seen an ability in action before?
Kill them all.
The best smokes are always
after a job well done.
An explosion?
What's going on?
I hear it's a massacre.
Damn.
The military police say the
Port Mafia's military squad did it.
The Black Lizard group,
the most violent of them all.
The Black Lizard?
They're as good as special ops,
and merciless to boot.
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard...
If they were to attack the Agency...
The worst case scenario.
Yes?
Who is this?
It's me.
Weretiger!
I see.
He saw the business card
I left at the Agency.
Your colleagues saved you the other day,
but that won't be the case next time.
What do you want?
I'm going to quit the Agency.
I'm going to quit, and run away alone.
Catch me if you can!
I see.
So you're telling us to call
off the war on the Agency?
Call the Black Lizard!
Oh, there you are, brat.
Thanks to you, it's a huge mess.
It's highly probable that this is the worst case scenario.
Come help me carry these—
Hey!
There's no need to worry.
The worst case scenario
won't happen anymore.
The agency is safe.
Huh?
Hey!
Come help me, brat!
Where are you running off to now?!
Get out, you failure!
No orphanage would welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place
if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
You're late.
Two minutes late.
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Don't be so uptight, gramps.
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
Black Lizard
Commander
Tachiwara
Michizou
What a glum place.
Where's Gin?
Is he late, too?
He's already here.
He's behind you.
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Black
Lizard
Com
man
der
Gin
Heh, a creep like always.
You get on my nerves.
Wanna fight?
Stop it, fools.
Would either of you like to be reported as KIA?
Leader of
Black Lizard
Hirotsu Ryuurou
Ability: Falling Camellia
Fine.
You're a hard one to read.
We're all here.
Well done.
And?
What's the target that takes
the three of us to crush?
The target
is the Armed Detective Agency's office.
The Agency?
Not the weretiger, then?
The previous attempt failed
because the Agency interfered.
We won't make the same mistake twice.
We'll annihilate the Agency first to
prevent them from protecting him.
No survivors?
Fine by me.
Understood.
I can't have Akutagawa-senpai
taking a back seat
to a mere detective agency!
Fear death.
Fear slaughter.
Those who desire killing
have an equal desire to die.
Worthless men
have no right to draw breath.
Your resolve is admirable.
I will give you a reason to live.
I have finally found a reason to live.
A reason to live?
No, a reason to keep on living until now.
That's right.
I've lived to this day so that I can
be in a double-suicide with you.
I'm sure of it.
Ah, bella donna.
Feel free to do it on your own.
A double-suicide isn't possible alone.
By the way, Dazai-san?
Do you have a proper life insurance policy?
Why would you ask that, bella donna?
Well,
because you've racked up quite a tab.
If you haven't gotten one yet,
I'd be happy to refer you one.
Ah, your vitality is blinding.
Aw, if that's the best you've
got for changing the subject,
I'm going to barge into your agency on the fourth floor.
Ah, your boldness is even more blinding.
Not even a sentry?
Talk about careless.
Who are you?
My apologies.
Even though you're a detective agency,
we forgot to make an appointment.
And we forgot to knock.
The Port Mafia's Black Lizard.
Well, I hope you'll overlook these mishaps.
Our errand will be over soon enough.
Get out, you failure!
No orphanage would welcome the likes of you!
The world would be a better place if
you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
They were right.
There's nowhere I could ever belong.
Gunshots?
But that's where...
Why's the Agency being attacked?!
Oh, sorry!
Why is this happening?
It's all because of me
that everyone's in danger again!
Stop!
What?
Huh?
There!
Hup.
So you're finally back, brat.
This is why I hate raids.
They really throw off
our budget projections.
How much do you think repairing the office
and replacing inventory will cost?!
Using machine guns for a raid
was a little over the top.
It's your turn to go
around the neighborhood
with apologies and gifts, Kunikida-kun.
So it is the worst case scenario!
Huh?
So this is the "worst case scenario"?
This is the Port Mafia military squad
said to be on par with special ops?
Huh?
Kunikida-san, what should we do with them?
Throw them out the window.
Roger!
Hup, hup.
One...
Two...
For the umpteenth time,
Three!
I wish they'd give up on raids.
So this is the "umpteenth" time?
The Agency's far more violent
than the Port Mafia.
Bye!
Hurry up and help clean, brat!
Have a nice trip!
I can't believe you wandered
off in the middle of it all!
I told you, you're a member
of the Agency now.
You should be thinking about
what you can do yourself.
Well, helping clean up
is about all you can do.
Think about what you can do.
I see.
Hey, if you've got time to laugh—
Wait, are you crying?
I—I'm not crying!
You are.
I said I'm not!
Just look at you.
You're so typical for your generation.
Even when given a job,
you run off and play without consent.
You cry if anyone gives even a word of criticism.
That's not it.
That's not what this is about.
But you're crying.
I am,
but that isn't what this is about!
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
The only reason they can call
themselves a detective agency
and function as one
is because of my ability, Ultra Deduction.
Oh, a murder case has
arrived on our doorstep.
Okay, Atsushi-kun,
help me with the case.
Uh, I'm not sure I'm up to the task.
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs,
Episode 5: Murder on D Street.
Episode 5
Is this going to be an
actual detective story?
All is well that is well by me.