After being separated from Bo-bobo,
Beauty was attacked by Killarino of the Pervert Brigade...
I mean the Assassin Brigade of the Margarita Empire.
However, Bo-bobo came to Beauty's rescue in the nick of time,
and saved her from danger.
After a long struggle, he beat Killarino,
Nonetheless, the mystery of the mysterious boy
watching Bo-bobo and Beauty remained just that... a mystery.
Hajike Village
Hajike Gang's Junior Boss
Don Patch's still missing...
Well, whatever!
Lil' Patch Army
But where's Don Patch?
As usual, it's Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Maybe he's dead?
As if you forgot ♥ Beauty
Some stuff should just be kept to yourself!
I'm sorry. Did I say something wrong?
- Not at all!
- Then don't act like it!
I'm hungry.
Excuse me!
Racoon Ping-Pong Delivery
- Package for you, sir.
- Thanks a lot!
Sign here, please..
Ah, yes. Just a moment! Hold on, hold on.
Thank you.
What could it be?
Don Patch!
"As you know," it's Don Patch!
Bon appetit!
Who would eat you?
- I'll eat him.
- Can you even eat him?
Is he a rice omelet?
Go ahead and eat. But listen to me.
Is he sushi?
You travel around fighting the Hair Hunters, right?
Here we go!
Is it good?
More like...
Put some soy sauce on, for Pete's sake!
Who would eat you?
Eat me! Eat me!
Boss Don Patch!
- Yo!
- What are you doing?!
Today's graduation day for Hajike School!
Dammit! That's right!
I'd better hurry or I'll be late!
Hop!
So Don Patch was a student...?
He was.
Hajike School Graduation Day
Made it just in time.
This is the last time I'll see the view from this window...
I'll miss it.
Don Patch!
You forgot your lunch box!
Why'd that idiot follow me here?
We got no choice but to go inside and bring it to him.
A'ight! Let's break in! Go!
That bastard! He's  trying to crash my graduation!
No! I can't let him do that!
Calm down! Look closely! They're just plush teddy bears!
What the hell are you doing?!
Bear A
The tea was quite nice.
Well, looks like it's my turn to break in.
The flower-viewing season... is all about the break-ins...
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Teacher A
Ah, Teacher!
Bear B
Bear C
Bear D
Wait!
Thank you, sir, for taking such good care of my Don Patch!
Ah, so you're his legal guardian?
It's not much,
but please accept this expired Mabo pork cutlet.
Cut it out! Cut it out!
You fool! Don't you get I'm doing this all for you?!
It's my precious expired Mabo pork cutlet that I carefully saved for three long years...
Do you even understand the trouble I went to to give it to him?
Ah... Um...
And yet... and yet...
Farewell!
Get to class.
'Kay.
Quiet in the hallways! And take off your shoes!
Really... What the hell were they thinking?
Purukogi
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
Kogipuru... Kogipuru...
Kogipuru
Purukogi
Hey, you!
Kogi
Bear E
You're not getting it at all!
I'm sorry! I was in bed with a cold until yesterday, so I couldn't practice...
So... so...
Forgive me... forgive me!
Are you feeling better now?
You've got bags under your eyes.
Don't force yourself.
Thank you so much!
Okay y'all, Purukogi training is done for today!
Tomorrow I'll be testing your "Bibimba", so make sure you practice!
What the heck?
More importantly, my desk's gotten pretty dirty...
Well, I guess I'd better clean it before I move on.
Madame, Madame.
We have a great detergent here.
Is that so?
Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
Will it make my skin look beautiful too?
Sure it will! Sure it will!
Go home!
It's an earthquake!
We will now begin the presentation of diplomas.
Student A
Student B
Student C
Student D
When I call your name, please
come to the front and pick up your diploma.
Student E
Principal
Student F
Student G
Student H
Student I
Student J
- Saito Masao!
- Yes!
It's finally going to be my turn.
- Don Patch!
- Yes!
Graduation Ceremony
L--Look out!
Hold it! You're not getting your diploma!
Water gun squad, take your aim!
Why?!
Don Patch!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
Fist of the Nose Hair:
Bababa-Ba Ba-Baba
Bababa-Ba Ba-Baba!
Diploma
Here.
Thank you... Thank you so much!
Thank Goodness
Thus began a warm friendship,
and the ceremony ended without a hitch.
Back at Hajike Village
What's that boy doing?
Hey!
Bo-bobo, you're back!
How'd it go, Boss?
I got my diploma.
Beauty, let's go.
Huh, already?
I hear the cries of hair tortured by the Corps.
Wait!
Take me with you.
Boss! What are you saying?!
Without you, what will become...
...of the Hajike gang?
Sorry...
But I want to Hajike more!
With them, I can hajike to my max!
That's why I must join them in their quest!
May I?
Whatever you want.
Bo-bobo!
Wait up!
Where's he aiming?
It sure is nice out, huh.
Yakkun
It's a perfect day for a stroll. Eh, Yakkun?
Hey, Bo-bobo is...
Shut up, idiot! You'll wake up Yakkun!
Jeez, it's just a doll...
I swear, you kids these days...
But that's not important right now...
Bo-bobo Tank
Could he... be aiming at me?
The General on his Head
Open fire!
Spare the child! Just spare the child!
Curry bread...
This is for my curry bread!
Dry... curry!
Stop! I'll just buy you some more curry bread!
No, no! I want THAT curry bread!
That curry bread was so tasty...
But that's nothing to turn into a tank about!
But, uh... But, uh...
Don Patch, are you alright?
'Course I am!
This is war!
You've been a bit naive lately.
Me?
Beauty thought about this awhile.
Elsewhere
So we're setting up camp here...?
You're good, you're good.
Bo-bobo's Maintenance Crew
Installing new earlobes. Bring parts G and F.
Verification, quickly!
Bo-bobo, stop goofing off and help us a sec, would you?
- We're under attack!
- To arms! To arms!
Protect the base!
Fire! Fire!
Stop screwing around and go find us some food to eat!
Okay, I get it.
Really, I swear...
Bo-bobo's sure taking his time...
It's already been an hour...
Vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom!
I'm back!
Ah, here he is!
I caught a huge fish!
A Hair Hunter!
It's a carp, isn't it?
CARP?
No, it's a snapper!
SNAPPER?
No way, that's a hair hunter!
- We got time. Wanna take a print?
- Good idea.
But it's a Hair Hunter!
Hair Hunter? What's she on?
It's clearly a snapper.
What are you doing?!
Hey girl, you saw through my disguise pretty quickly.
Anyone could've done it.
Exactly
Now that I'm unmasked, I have no choice...
- The snapper...
- stood up...
I'm the Captain of the River Block of the Hair Hunt Troops.
Kodebun
Kodebun!
Kodebun?
Bo-bobo, I came to defeat you.
Yay!
I'm getting stepped on!
- Let me tell you one thing...
- What?
I am...
not a fish!
What's he talking about?
Let's go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique: Nose Hair Revolution!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Revolution
He dodged it!
Your Fist of the Nose Hair is useless against me.
I can read peoples' hearts.
So I can foresee all of your moves.
That has nothing to do with anything.
It does!
Interesting!
Can you read my thoughts?
No way!
Impossible!!
Mind Reading!
Cucumber Field?
Cucumbers! It's cucumbers!
Yay, cucumbers!
So he...
So he likes cucumbers...?
Here!
Now you're the only one left!
So. What will you do, Bo-bobo?
Let's just see what's going on in your heart...
Mind Reading!
Bo-bobo Theater, Part 2:
Pun Pudding Pudding.
We already did this one!
Meeting Room
President
Vice-President
Executive Director
Vice-Director
Managing Director
President
Vice-President
Executive Director
Vice-Director
Managing Director
Section Chief
Section Director
Room Monitor
Chief Clerk
Official
Section Chief
Section Director
Room Monitor
Chief Clerk
Official
What's up with his heart?
Well, let me explain the new product idea.
We'll call it Nose Hair-chan.
Nose hair-chan Red
Nose hair-chan Black
Nose hair-chan White
These are special key rings for nose hair.
They come in white, black, or red,
so our customers can enjoy color variety.
It's clip-on, so it's easy to take on and off.
You can wear up to three per nostril.
According to the extrapolated data of our research division,
its popularity with teenage girls will exceed 70%.
This thing will really work!
Even the president loves them!
But...
That's way too many!
But can we handle the plan?
We'll have to work hard!
Quickly, prepare the production line!
Stop! It's not going to sell!
Wake up! Wake up!
But what's he thinking about?
I'm begging you, open your eyes!
At that moment, within Bo-bobo's nose...
Within Bo-bobo's Nose
King
Nose Hair!
Riah Eson!
Boogers
Nose Hair! Riah Eson!
Booger Elder
Today is the day King Nose Hair will awake from his 3000 year slumber.
Pray with all your hearts!
Oh, so you want one, eh? Which one do you want?
I don't want it!
Here you go.
Fine, it doesn't matter. Let's start with the girl!
But look again in Bo-bobo's nose...
King Nose Hair is awaking!
You okay, little miss?
Who are you?
King Nose Hair
I'm the famous King Nose Hair.
You shouldn't be rough to a lady. You better say your prayers!
You are screwed!
What is this huge nose hair? It's in the way.
P
U
L
Oh, what an unexpected twist!
I awoke from my 3000 year slumber.
I'm not gonna let this good-for-nothing ruin me!
So I will fulfill my dream before I die.
And that dream is... it is...
To go cycling!
Let's go!
Yahoo!
You were a good man and have my utmost respect, King Nose Hair.
I would like to convey my true feelings for you.
The Dream of a Nose Hair
To be quite frank,
you're disgusting!!!!
Come on, we're going!
Cycling, Cycling, Yahoo! ♪
Ah, the youthful feeling of cycling! Let's go!
What about me?
No one had any idea this was the bike path to hell.
Not Bo-bobo...
Not Don Patch...
Not even Beauty...
And the mystery of the mysterious boy still remains a mystery.
How long are you going to keep that up?
Well...
Of course I'm going to drag the mystery out!
So you have to watch next time!
Love Labyrinth? What's that?
Don't touch that!
I'm the heroine. But what if I put on the wrong costume?
Idiot! Do not fear failure!
Yes, director!
You said something nice for once!
Do your best for your role...
...as the dog.
The dog?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Sushi and a Bunny Girl? The Deadly Tea Soup Beam!!
Who's the bunny girl?