The Black Lizard...
The Armed Detective Agency
was attacked by the Port Mafia's
military squad, the Black Lizard.
But Kunikida-san, Yosano-san, and Kenji-kun
humiliated the entire team with ease.
Such is the might of the Armed Detective Agency.
Hey, hey, Harunocchi.
Can you take the marble out of this bottle?
Sure, right away.
A marble?
Is this what you wanted, Rampo-san?
Yes.
Marbles are nice, aren't they?
Yes, marbles are nice.
Um, isn't Rampo-san going to help?
Kunikida-kun.
I need to head off to a job soon.
Oh, to help with the murder case?
Indeed, the police in this city can't even nab a single criminal without my help.
Still,
my Ultra Deduction is the best
ability in this agency,
or even the whole nation.
I guess it's no wonder
that everyone depends on it.
We're indebted to you, Rampo-san.
Good, as long as you're aware.
That's right.
Though you call yourselves
a detective agency,
you all can't deduce better than a single monkey.
The only reason you can call yourselves
a detective agency and function as one
is because of my ability, Ultra Deduction.
Ultra Deduction is so amazing.
An ability that lets you see right to
the heart of any case instantly.
You're a role model for the Agency,
no, for all gifted people.
Of course.
Brat.
Y-Yes?
Never mind the mess here.
Go with Rampo-san.
The place is close by train.
M-Me as a detective's assistant?
That's a great responsibility.
Of course not.
I'm not some two-bit detective.
I don't need an assistant.
Then why am I going with you?
Well, see, I don't know
how to travel by train.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
Wow.
Honestly, I was surprised.
He knew absolutely nothing,
including how to buy a ticket,
how to get through the turnstile,
or how to find which
platform to go to.
I guess he really can't do anything
without his ability.
You're late, agents.
Oh, who are you?
Where is Yasui-san?
I'm Minoura.
I took over for Yasui.
This case has been reassigned
to our division.
So we no longer need you or your agency.
How foolish.
All difficult cases in the world should obviously be overseen by a great detective.
We won't need a
detective today.
Because the victim is my subordinate.
A lady.
She was discovered floating in the river this morning.
She was shot three times in the chest.
We don't know where or when she was killed.
We haven't even found the bullets.
Any suspects?
No.
As far as anyone at the office knew,
she wasn't in a relationship, either.
Does that mean you have no leads?
Which is exactly why
we can't let some amateur private eye handle this.
Hey!
The net caught something!
What's that?
We've strung a net across the river
to catch any evidence.
It's a man!
There's a man in the net!
What?!
Could there be a second victim?
Hey there, Atsushi-kun.
What a strange coincidence.
A-Another drowning attempt?
What, committing suicide alone?
That's so passé, Atsushi-kun.
I have come to realize
that if I shall die,
I must die with a beautiful lady!
Ah, double suicide.
What a sweet ring it has.
In comparison,
it feels so empty to bid this world
farewell all by my lonesome.
So,
I'm currently on the lookout for a
beautiful woman who'll die with me!
Huh?
Then what was all this about?
I was simply drifting along the river!
I see.
By the way, Atsushi-kun,
what are you doing out here?
I'm on a job.
A job?
What kind?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What a tragedy.
What a great tragedy this is,
that a young beautiful woman in
her prime has lost her life.
Sorrow is crushing my heart!
She may as well have committed
double suicide with me!
Who the hell is he?
A colleague at the Agency.
That's just how he is.
But rest in peace, milady.
An extraordinarily amazing
detective will avenge you.
Right, Rampo-san?
But I have yet to get the job itself.
What?
Why?
Ask this man.
We have no need for detectives.
In fact, all of my subordinates are far
superior to any private detective.
Oh?
What's your name?
What?
I am Sergeant Sugimoto.
The victim, Ms. Yamagiwa,
was my senior!
All right, Sugimoto-kun.
Solve this case in sixty
seconds, starting now.
60 Seconds
What?!
I can solve it in under a minute.
If you're as good as he says you are,
you should be able to do the same.
Okay, give it a try, Sugimoto-kun!
What?!
Um, okay, well...
Sixty seconds is a bit
overkill, isn't it?!
Okay, fifty seconds left.
What?!
This is what I must look like.
Oh, right.
Yamagiwa-senpai was pursuing
a political corruption case
and also investigating the Port Mafia.
I believe the murderer's M.O. is similar to
the Mafia's method of exacting retribution.
Maybe she was killed by the mafia
members she was investigating—
Incorrect.
What?
The Port Mafia's retaliatory methods are as
highly specific as a government-issued ID.
First, the traitor is forced
to bite the curb,
then they kick the back of
their head to shatter the jaw.
As their victim writhes in agony,
they flip him over,
then shoot them in the chest three times.
If we're being specific, yes, but...
So this M.O. is similar to the
Mafia's, but not the same.
That means...
An attempt at a cover-up?
Shooting two extra rounds
into the body just for that?
How cruel.
Beep!
Okay, time's up!
Too bad, you've got a ways to
go before you reach my level.
At the very least, this proved
that your subordinates
aren't all superior to me.
Cut the crap!
You've been going on and on about
deduction and great detectives.
You've been reading too much pulp fiction!
Cases are solved by thorough investigations,
interviewing persons of interest,
and analyzing the scene of the crime.
Huh?
When are you going to realize it?
Great detectives don't do "investigations."
My ability, Ultra Deduction,
can instantly identify the killer
and when and how the murder was committed.
Furthermore,
I can see in my mind's eye how
I can make the killer confess,
and where the evidence lies,
as if it's an epiphany.
I am gifted, after all.
Given my line of work,
I know about the gifted's existence.
But if you have such a convenient ability,
why do my colleagues and I still have a job?
Right on!
You've finally caught up.
You bastard!
Now, now, Detective.
Rampo-san's always like this.
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
After all, my motto is,
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
Motto:
All's well
that's well for me!
"All's well that's well for me!"
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
I've never heard a more convincing motto in my life.
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
What's better
than being alive?
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Well, well.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Motto:
Have a pure, cheerful,
and energetic suicide.
Since you praise it so much,
let's see this ability of yours.
Oh?
Are you asking if I can handle the case?
You should've just asked me from the start.
Heh, you have a lot of confidence
about this difficult case
despite the lack of any evidence.
Want me to count to sixty?
I don't need that long.
Watch closely, Atsushi-kun.
This is the ability that
keeps the Agency going.
Once he puts on those glasses,
Rampo-san's Ultra Deduction is active.
Rampo-san's ability reveals
the truth about a case.
Does such a gift really exist?
Ability: Ultra Deduction!
I see.
"I see," my ass.
You're trying to imply you
know who the killer is?
Of course.
Huh?
The killer
is you.
That's right.
The killer...
The killer is you,
Sergeant Sugimoto.
What?
Rampo-san?
Sergeant Sugimoto is my subordinate.
Sergeant Sugimoto is the one who killed her.
Don't be stupid!
It's impossible that the killer would appear nearby in the first place!
It's because he's the killer
that he wants to stay close to the case.
Besides, didn't I mention this?
I also know where the evidence lies.
Lend me your gun, will you?
Y-You've got to be kidding.
The punishment for handing a government-issued
firearm to a civilian
is far worse than a pay cut.
And here I was hoping you'd have a point.
Are you detectives just talk?
If we examine that gun and come up empty,
then sure, I'm just a dumbass running my mouth.
I've had enough of listening to you!
Show him, Sugimoto!
But...
He's dug himself a deep hole,
If we disprove him,
he'll shut up and go home.
We can't waste any more time.
Show him your gun!
Hey, what's the matter, Sugimoto?
Even in this city,
it's not easy for an amateur
to get spare ammo.
even harder if the firearm
was government-issued.
Why aren't you saying anything, Sugimoto?!
He's thinking hard right now
about the three bullets he used,
and how he'll explain their absence.
Sugimoto!
You can't be the killer!
Show us your gun, now!
That's right, Sugimoto.
Not good.
Sugimoto!
Atsushi-kun!
Go!
Stop!
Let me go!
I have nothing to do with this!
Running away won't help.
The murder took place
early yesterday morning
at the abandoned shipyard,
140 meters upstream from here.
How'd you know that?
If we go there, we should be able to
find yours and the victim's footprints,
as well as the bloodstains you
couldn't fully clean.
How?
No one could've known.
Let's hear the rest back at the station.
It may be the last time it's
your place of work.
I didn't intend to shoot her.
She...
She was going after a certain
politician for corruption.
What they didn't predict
was that she actually found evidence
of a major Diet member's crime.
However, the Diet member was savvy
and tried to use a mole inside the police
to get rid of the evidence.
And you're that spy.
I'd always wanted to
become a police officer.
After I failed the exam three times, I was depressed.
That was when a man reached out to me,
asking me if I was willing to
do anything to become a cop.
After joining the police force
with the Diet member's help,
I had to follow his orders in return.
So you killed Yamagiwa as one of his dogs!?
That's not it!
I was trying to warn her.
I told her she'd get herself killed
if she didn't give up the evidence.
But she...
Yamagiwa-san, he's taking
this very seriously.
Then I'll just have to take
him very seriously, too.
I've already made contact
with a prosecutor I know.
I just need to hand over the evidence.
Sugimoto-kun?
Please hand over the evidence.
If I fail in this,
he'll call a hit man.
Just stop here.
Hand over the gun, Sugimoto-kun.
You can't shoot me.
That's right.
That's why
I have another way to force you.
Don't!
Sugimoto-kun!
If you did nothing,
you'd be convicted
You'd be fired from your job.
In a panic, you could only think of one
person to go to for help. How ironic.
When you called the Diet member,
he told you how to destroy the evidence.
Just as you were told to, you fired
two more shots into her chest
to make it seem like the Mafia had done it.
You set her adrift in the
river to delay discovery.
Where is the evidence Yamagiwa obtained?
That Diet member's responsible
for Yamagiwa's death!
Tell me, Sugimoto!
Hey, Sugimoto-kun.
Want me to guess what her
final words to you were?
It was "I'm sorry." wasn't it?
I'm... sorry.
You really
see through everything, don't you.
The evidence is in my desk drawer.
Thanks, I guess.
Also, I'm sorry I doubted your capabilities.
If we run into another problematic case, we'll ask for your help.
If you need my abilities,
ask me any time.
I'll give you a discount next time.
That'd be helpful.
Rampo-san was amazing.
I had no idea he'd figure everything out.
His ability, Ultra Deduction, is amazing.
I might've figured out half of it, too.
Half of what?
About that case just now.
About how Rampo-san figured it out.
Oh, but he said his ability lets
him figure it out instantly.
That's right, you don't know yet.
Actually, Rampo-san isn't gifted.
Huh?!
Rampo-san is a very rare
ungifted civilian at the agency.
He himself seems to believe
he's using an ability, but...
Oh, and despite his appearance,
he's 26 years old.
What?
The reason why everyone at the
Agency respects Rampo-san
is because they know his
Ultra Deduction isn't an ability.
I'd heard of it, myself,
but I only witnessed its
power first-hand today.
To tell you the truth,
while he was "using" his
Ultra Deduction ability today,
I was secretly pinching his hair behind him.
As you well know,
I can neutralize anyone's ability if
I touch them. I'm anti-gifted.
No gifted can ever use their ability
while I'm touching any part of them,
no matter how strong their powers may be.
In other words,
his Ultra Deduction is not an ability.
It's not?
Then how'd he...
It's just deduction, pure and simple.
But how?
He figured out who the killer was
in such a short amount of time!
Is mere deduction enough to
make such a thing possible?
Right.
I could tell too, actually.
Remember what Sergeant Sugimoto said?
Shooting two extra rounds
into the body, just for that?
Anyone who saw a body
with three gunshot wounds
Illustration
would assume they were fired at the same time.
Oh.
In other words,
he knew that the victim had
perished from the first shot.
How could he have known
that before an autopsy?
Only if he was the killer.
But he also knew when it happened,
early yesterday morning.
That's because the body was
still in good condition.
So, at most, it'd only been
floating in the river for a day.
Yesterday was Tuesday, a weekday.
But the victim wasn't wearing any makeup.
A detective working long hours,
often late into the night,
would only be like that on a weekday
if the murder had occurred
in the early morning.
I see.
But how did he know the crime scene,
and that she was threatened with a gun?
That, I don't know.
Rampo-san probably caught a lot
more details than I could hope to.
That's true.
He even guessed her final words.
Oh, that.
She supposedly wasn't seeing anyone,
but her wristwatch was an
overseas brand-name item.
It's not something a single woman
would buy for herself.
And Sergeant Sugimoto's watch was the
men's version of the same model.
Then they were...
She went to meet him early when he called,
without bothering to put on makeup.
And their watches are of the same model.
They were dating.
That's why he couldn't curbstomp her,
even though he knew it wouldn't
look like the Mafia's work.
The ability to see through all that
would be par for the course if it
were an actual ability.
Nothing more, nothing less.
But if it's due to his personal powers
of deduction, that's a different story.
He's solved dozens of cases in the past.
In every case,
he was able to instantly determine the truth
of the matter with the slimmest of leads.
He's never been wrong, either.
What a great man.
Hey, guide!
I can't find my way back to the
Agency on my own, you know!
I think I kind of get it now.
Why everyone at the Agency
trusts Rampo-san so much.
All's well that's well for me!
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
What is the Ideal?
There are any number of
answers to that question.
It is words,
it is thought.
From a move scheduled
five years from now
to tonight's dinner menu,
this notebook has everything in life
written out in exacting detail.
It represents the entirety of my ideals!
But you should never show anyone
the page where you've written about
the ideal woman.
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 6:
The Azure Messenger.
Episode 6
The Azure Messenger
What's so bad about looking
for an ideal woman?!