Kodebun, an assassin for the Corps,
was a mind-reader.
Captain of the River Block
of the Hair Hunt Troops
Kodebun
Mind Reading
To counter him, Bo-bobo awoke King Nose Hair
from his 3000 year slumber.
King Nose Hair
NO!
So I will fulfill my dream before I die.
And that dream is... it is...
To go cycling!
Bo-bobo was moved by the
realization of a 3000 year dream,
The Dream of a Nose Hair
and he crushed Kodebun...
To be quite frank,
you're disgusting!!!!
Come on, we're going!
Cycling of youth!
Cycling on a Rhinocycle!
Note: It's pun on sai (rhino)
Cycling on a Rhinocycle!!
Cycling on a Rhinocycle!
But that's a hippo!
Note: More puns on "sai"
Rhinos are cool!
Excuse us!
Huh? I get one too?
Wait up!
Thus Bo-bobo's merry band
resumed their reckless journey.
What a pretty flower!
What was that for?
Jealousy
Little pest... I'll never let you be the heroine!
Never!
What are you talking about?
Never! Never! I'll never let you!
Sushi and a Bunny Girl? The Deadly Tea Soup Beam!!
I'll never let you!
Let me what?
Scene 3 Cut 2
Cut! Cut!
Director!
Director?
Base
ball
I said a squeeze play!
You mean coach!?
Director!
I'm the heroine, right?
And not this kid, right?
Idiot! Of course you're the heroine!
Director!
Your script. Break a leg.
Yes!
Love Labyrinth,
the Maze of Love.
Starring: Bo-bobo as the Prince,
Beauty as the Princess, Don Patch as the dog
The dog?
That piece of crap tricked me! You think I'm going to play a dog?!
Shake.
Sit.
I love home cooking!
Mama, gimme a bowl of rice with natto!
Wait, that's "seconds," isn't it?
"Sitting" and "Seconds" It's a pun...
Perfect.
See you at the Oscars.
For real?
That was close... did she see me?
I was getting the feeling someone was watching us...
But now I'm certain...!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo Theatre:
Love Labyrinth.
The Maze of Love:
Act 1.
It's starting!
Is this...
Is this Love Labyrinth,
the Maze of Love?
I think this is the end, woof.
Don't give up, you idiot!
Just eat my sushi!
Love Labyrinth
They even made pamphlets...
It was nice knowing you, woof.
Idiot! Just drink this and you'll be better!
Vinegar.
Vinegar
Start with some big gulps.
NO
No way.
NO WAY
You will never become the perfect sushi otherwise.
No way. No way.
NO WAY
Don't worry. It's apple vinegar!
In that case...
It's drinking him!
He drank it...
Come on, drink more!
Vengeance!
Vengeance for my little sister!
Vengeance for...
my little sis!
Standing Ovation
Those morons!
Seriously! Now's not the time for ths!
Dressing Room: Bo-bobo and Don Patch
Haven't you had enough?
Listen! Someone is...
No! I'll never make the cheerleading squad!
I just don't think I can do it!
Idiot!
What are you talking about, Ellie!? We've worked so hard for this...
We made it through the toughest of practices together!
Everyone gets scared at times like these.
But we'll do our best. Okay, Ellie?
Haruka, thank you... thanks, Haruka.
You're right... I can do it!
I will! Yes!
That's the spirit, Ellie!
Well, let's go!
Kabuki?!
I will Kabuki!!
Go, Ellie!
Dearest viewers, sorry for the wait.
Please enjoy the final act.
What about Kabuki!?
So, Sushi Saburo became the perfect sushi...
Huh?
It's show time!
Hey, no one told me about this!
Here you go, Sushi Saburo.
The stage is all yours now!
Blow them away!
Okay!
Hey, you!
Why'd you have to do that?
That felt-
Yes!
Bo-bobo!
Oh, Beauty?
This is no time to goof around!
There's someone following us right now!
What? That's terrible, could it be that...
It's definitely a hitman targeting us!
No, I don't think so.
Then who could it be?
The Tea Soup Aliens!
The Tea Soup Aliens!!
The Tea Soup Aliens?
Tea soup...
They thrive on Tea soup...
And intend to invade the Earth, and
force everyone to eat their favorite food.
So?
I was serious about it, too...
Tea soup...
It's him!
Bo-bobo was right!
Thank you, good sir...
You came for me, didn't you?
So I wouldn't be humiliated...
Don't you dare call me "good sir"!
Bo-bobo!
Hey, punks. You seen this kid?
But... that's...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Mama... there's someone
watching Bo-bobo's team...
Tea Soup Alien
And he himself is...
being chased by a Tea Soup Alien.
Don Patch
This is why...
Beauty
Foxes
The mysterious boy
He's...
He's the one who saved me!
I gotta get rid of this kid.
And I must do this because...
Bamboo-Tea soup! Plum-Tea soup!
Seaweed-Tea soup!
Tobacco-Tea Soup!
Another pursuer?
Isn't that guy working for the ducktail bastard?
Sea bream-Tea soup...
There you have it.
Tell me everything that you know.
And you'll get this great tea soup as a reward.
Huh?
French Bread... in my tea soup?
Who did that!?
I love bread
Down With Japanese Food!
Western Food Only!
Monsieur
We only eat western food.
Bonjour
We don't want you, so go home.
I'd rather die than eat your Tea soup!
You just ate the tea soup, didn't you!
No, I didn't.
I won't get mad at you, so be honest!
I didn't eat it.
More importantly, pour me more tea.
Phew, you had me worried.
Bo-bobo!
He's eating it!
That boy in the picture saved my life!
If he's after him, then this guy's bad!
Please defeat him!
That's right! I'm a bad guy!
Dumbass, don't judge people by their appearance!
Tea.
I guess not...
Of course I will.
Bo-bobo!
In return, you cook this week.
Jealousy
I beg of you, defeat him!
I'll do cleaning this week!
Whatever. I'm going to teach this guy to fear us Tea Soup Aliens!
Mr. Tea Soup Alien...
Tea-Tea-Tea Soup!
Tea Soup Alien!
Tea soup beam! Beam! Beam! Beam!
Anyone hit by this beam will
have a sudden craving for my Tea Soup!
What a pointless attack...
Don Patch!
T-Te-te-t-t-tea-t-tea...
I WANNA EAT PILAF!!
I
WANNA
EAT
TEA
SOUP!
Iwannaeatteasoup! Iwannaeatteasoup! Iwannaeatteasoup! Iwannaeatteasoup!
Pilaf!
Tea?
I want pilaf! I want pilaf!
Pilaf! Pilaf! Pilaf! Pilaf!
Why?
Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea-!
I WANNA EAT TEA SOUP!!!
Pilafpilafpilafpilaf pilaf!
Wait, Bo-bobo!
You're not goin' anywhere!
Bo-bobo!
Where'd he go?
Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea- Tea soup- Tea soup- Tea soup-
I WANNA EAT TEA SOUP!
This pilaf is amazing!
Exquisite!
What are you doing!?
Viva Pilaf!
Bo-bobo!
No, I could never eat all this pilaf!
Ciao. I've been waiting for you.
I am an expert of underwater combat!
You'll regret facing me down here!
You'll be the one to regret it. Here goes!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
Fist of the Nose Hair?
No way.
Old man...
Old man!
Piece of crap! How dare you do that to the old man!
Now I must call on the power of fish!
Fist of the Nose Hair Aquatic Secret Technique:
Aquatic Secret Technique?
I WANNA EAT TEA SOUP!
Fist of the Nose Hair Aquatic Secret Technique:
Fish Manipulation Dance!
Fish... Fish...
What's that noise? Fish?
Here's your miso soup!
What's that!?
Sorry about the wait.
Glad you've come, fishes.
Fishes!?
Nothing better than miso soup underwater.
Good stuff
That's good stuff.
You're not even eating it!
White miso is definitely the best!
Brother, you think he'll eat us?
The Clam Brothers
Of course! We won't end up like our parents!
We're not going to end up as just soup stock!
Here I go!
Forgive me for going first!
Idiot. Don't apologize, I'll be right after you!
To tell the truth, I'm kind of sad.
You've become quite the clam...
Before you were just a kid, but now...
you're a man...
Hold it?
I don't want soup stock.
I'm soup stock after all?!
Piece of crap! We're not soup stock!
We're garnishes!
You wanna fight?
You're losing?! I don't believe it!
Don't leave leftovers!
Tea soup!
I'm done screwing around!
Take this! Tea Soup Beam!
Fist of the Nose Hair Aquatic Secret Technique:
Fish Manipulation Dance...
2!
Fish? 2?
I've got a bad feeling about this....
These vibrations... no...
They're back!
What are you doing?
You looking for a fight?
Welcome to the Dragon Palace.
Hey! Stop, old men!
Wait!
Like hell I will!
Have a present. It's the Old Age Box. Open it,
and you'll become old.
I don't want it!
Bo-bobo...
Tea!
It's the Tea Soup Alien!
Those screwed up old men, trying to give me this box...
What about Bo-bobo?
What do you think you're doing!? Stupid pig!
Oh, no! I don't wanna be an old man!
Did you drop this gold pig or this silver pig?
Bo-bobo!
Umm... The Gold one...
No, there's no time for this! The smoke will...
I'm gonna become an old man!
Me too?
Bo-bobo!
It can't be true.
Bo-bobo... will become... a dirty old man!
Darn that nasty boss...
Okay, now come here. Kiss my ass!
Is that harassment?
Stop saying that all the time!
C'mon, Beauty, let's go!
No!
What the heck?!
The End
Thank you very much
for coming to see today's performance of Love Labyrinth.
You mean you were still doing that Love Labrynth?
Now let's have another round of applause for the star of the show!
Thank you!
Thank you! The same to you!
I love tea soup!
That's pilaf!!
Bravo.
The Tea Soup alien was in it too?
Thank you all! Thanks!
They drew in the Tea Soup Alien to their hajike...
I owe him one.
The applause drowned out this mysterious phone call that we just took note of.
Answer it! Answer it, Tea Soup Alien!
It may be an urgent call from your mother!
Incoming Call: Master Battleship
That's not it... huh? A call from Master Battleship?
Who is Master Battleship?
And what does he have to do with the mysterious boy?
Next time: a tempest of hair. Where will fate take Bo-bobo next?
And... Hurry up and answer the damn phone, Tea Soup Alien!
Let's all go on a trip!
I'm in! Let's go see the mountains! Where should we go?
I have to try for a technique. See ya!
A technique? Bo-bobo, where are you going?
Piece of crap! I won't let you take the spotlight!
But where are you going?
Next time on
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Terrible Ultimate Secret Technique of
the Fist of Somen! H.E.L.L.O!
What's the deal with "Hello?"