What is the Ideal?
There are any number of
answers to that question.
It is words,
it is thought.
It is the font of all meaning.
But if you were to ask me,
the answer is quite clear.
It is the word written on my notebook's cover.
The Ideal...
Everything about me is written in this notebook.
My schedule, my plans, my ambitions.
This notebook contains my entire future.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
I arrived a whole ten seconds early.
My name is Kunikida Doppo.
I am an idealist walking the earth,
and a realist in pursuit of ideals.
It's time.
Good morning.
Kunikida-san, please help us!
What's going on so early?
J-J-Just look at Dazai-san!
Oh!
Kunikida-kun, it's an emergency!
Just look!
Look at what?
At that!
I only see your moronic face!
I've finally arrived
in the afterlife!
At Yomotsu Hirasaka!
It's exactly as I imagined!
What's going on?
Blue smoke trailing the ground,
Kunikida-san.
moonlight dashing against the windows,
I think this may explain it.
and pink elephants dancing in the western sky!
I knew the Complete Guide to Suicide was a masterpiece!
Who knew I just needed mushrooms from the nearby hills
to have such an entertaining way out?!
So he ate shrooms?
Well, he thought he was eating lethal mushrooms, but...
Ah, I've finally caught you,
rainbow pillbug!
All right, let's eat you back home!
Kunikida-san!
I'm doing my routine paperwork after arriving at work.
Wait till I'm done.
What?!
Kunikida-kun.
You should come to the afterlife, too.
It's amazing.
There are rainbow pillbugs, too.
You can drink all you want!
You can eat all you want!
You can look at all the sleeping beauties you could possibly—
Shut up!
Why are two such incompatible people a team?
Kunikida-san, the president has your case for the day.
Dazai.
Quit dawdling.
Walk faster.
'Kay.
We only have two minutes and fifteen seconds until the appointment!
That's concerning.
Is it okay for me to tag along?
This is part of your rookie training.
This case involves solving a series of disappearances in Yokohama.
If I recall, it's the one where visitors to Yokohama
keep disappearing one after another, right?
We have an anonymous tip.
The victims have been kidnapped and imprisoned in a certain location.
An anonymous tip...
How suspicious and wonderful.
But we can't ignore it.
So we'll investigate that place?
No.
We will investigate the tip's source first.
How's it going, informant?
Hey, four-eyes. Are you being a slave to your notebook again?
You're speaking like that to a detective agent
when you're a hacker?
If you're arrested,
your deceased father will be rolling in his grave.
Don't mention my father.
More importantly, you're late.
Isn't that unusual for you?
Why?
Were you on a date with a beauty?
No!
Dates should be with a chosen woman,
followed by marriage six years later.
That's what's written in this notebook.
Huh?!
You have someone you've decided to marry?
I will in four years.
Is he a newbie?
I'm Nakajima Atsushi.
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
I'm Taguchi Rokuzou.
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
I'm an informant.
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
Cyber
Net
Warrior
Taguchi
Rokuzou
For the right price, I'll dig up dirt on anything.
And?
Did you find out who's behind the anonymous tip?
The Azure Messenger.
What?
There was data left on their server.
And pics of the kidnapped victims, I guess.
The mole's not a enemy though, is he?
He told you where they're holed up and all.
I wonder.
I hope we don't go there, just to find he's one of the kidnappers.
The Azure Messenger...
I want you to keep looking into it.
Sure, when I feel like it.
I'm busy looking after my tropical fish.
Episode 6
The Azure Messenger
Yeah.
Thanks.
I called a taxi.
We'll go to the abandoned hospital mentioned by the tipster now.
Kunikida-kun, why are you looking after the Rokuzou boy?
What do you mean?
It's not like you to give a job to a hacker.
You could've just spoke with him over the phone,
but you took the time to meet him face to face.
His father's deceased, isn't he?
Are you trying to be his dad?
We came here so that the brat
could meet our informant.
That's all it is.
Sure, let's leave it at that.
This driver's another informant of ours.
He was an actor in his former life.
I made no money,
so I switched careers.
It was the right decision.
He knows more about Yokohama than anyone I know.
He also saw two of the eleven victims right before they were kidnapped.
I just happened to drive them from the port to a hotel.
Is this case really about kidnapping, though?
There haven't been any requests for ransom.
Are you sure these two were the ones you saw?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
They even have the same clothes, too.
I see.
I have a hunch!
Look at these photos. They're both wearing glasses!
That means this is a serial glasses kidnapping case!
It's your time to shine, Kunikida-kun!
Some of the victims don't have glasses.
You can't say it's a pattern.
Oh.
Too bad. And here I thought it'd finally be your time to shine.
I can't let that comment slide.
Are you saying my glasses are the only reason why I'd be in the spotlight?!
Wh-What?!
We're here.
It's the abandoned hospital, as you requested.
What a nice atmosphere.
It may be haunted.
By what?
It is creepy, that's for sure.
It's kind of nice.
It revs you up.
You better not have eaten
another of those mushrooms.
Oh, are you scared, Kunikida-kun?
Are you afraid of ghosts or something?
I'm not afraid of ghosts!
Then keep up.
Fool!
In these kinds of movies, those who are thoughtless and oveconfident
are the first to die.
Look at these footprints.
They're still fresh.
Help!
That voice...
From the basement?!
What's this?!
Thank you.
You saved me.
I'm Sasaki Nobuko.
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
University
Professor
Sasaki
Nobuko
I'm a professor at a university in Tokyo.
So you're victim number twelve?
Did you see who kidnapped you?
I'm sorry.
I blacked out at the station.
When I regained consciousness,
I was drowning in the tank, as you just saw.
Dazai, what's your take on the situation?
Sasaki-san's looking damn sexy.
Be serious!
Oh, right.
There should be others who were kidnapped here.
I know I heard voices just as I began drowning in the tank.
What?
Kunikida-san!
I found them!
They're here!
Help us!
Please!
Are you alright!?
Get us out of here!
Get back, Atsushi-kun!
It's gas!
You too, Kunikida-kun.
Hey, hang in there!
Hey!
Kunikida-kun!
Let me go, Dazai!
People shouldn't die like this!
Let me go!
"Victims of Yokohama's serial kidnapping case were found,
but perished when a detective agency conducted an independent raid."
Series of Disappearances in Yokohama Ends in Tragic Deaths
Perished...
So this was the enemy's objective.
You're saying they were trying to frame the Agency?
That was their plan all along?
Maybe it wasn't my time to shine, despite what Dazai said.
Kunikida-san...
Where's Sasaki?
She should be in the infirmary.
Oh, that's great.
Thank you so much for saving me the other day.
If you hadn't come when you did,
I wouldn't be alive right now.
Not at all.
Not to mention, you even let me stay at your residence last night.
Huh?
Where did you stay?
My place!
What?!
I'm... deeply indebted to Dazai-sama.
See?
I-Is that something detectives are allowed to do?
It seems Sasaki-san didn't see who it was.
She apparently faints often due to anemia.
That's why she fainted on the day she was kidnapped, too.
I don't know how she was kidnapped afterward.
So she's your type?
I like all women.
But Sasaki-san seems like the type who'd commit suicide with me if I asked, which is nice.
But what about you, Kunikida-kun?
Is she your type?
She is a victim in the case and a witness. That's it.
Well, that's exactly how you would react.
Oh, Atsushi-kun, want to read it?
His ideal woman.
Ideal
You bastard!
When'd you swipe that?
Ideal
Read? You mean it's written down in here?
Kunikida-kun's notebook
has a wide range of schedules, plans, and ideals recorded in it.
See, like here.
Whoa!
Th-This is too much.
You have a problem with it?
No, I can sympathize with your vision of an ideal woman, but...
You probably shouldn't share that vision with women.
Forget about me!
We're discussing the kidnappings right now!
Have we picked up on anything?
Yeah.
In this newspaper photo,
you look pretty manly.
Is that your way of indicating that you want me to punch you?
What's regrettable is this.
You should've picked sexier glasses frames
if you were going to end up in the news.
They're so plain.
Hey!
Only a naturally flamboyant person like me could pull off wearing them.
What do you think, Atsushi-kun?
Not bad, actually.
They only scream "con man" to me.
Wait.
What's the matter?
Let's go, both of you.
I know who's behind this.
Sorry for the short notice.
You said on the phone that you figured out who's behind the murder case.
You're on your way to arrest the killer?
That's right.
Then let's hurry.
Where to?
Here.
Huh?
This is where the kidnapping took place,
and you are the kidnapper.
You dosed passengers with sleeping gas,
and kidnapped them after they fell unconscious.
You wore a gas mask.
What were his reasons?
I can think of one.
Cargo.
Cargo?
He'd sell them off.
There's a black market for organs in the underground.
The margin isn't great because of the exchange rate,
but if you're pulling it off alone, it's a decent payout.
That's horrible.
Wait a minute.
Hang on.
If I used this taxi to kidnap people,
the police would've found me when tracing the victims' last known locations.
No, no one looked twice at this taxi.
Because all the victims would vanish and become untraceable the following day.
When your targets boarded the taxi and you knocked them out,
you'd imprison them and take their clothes and luggage.
That's why all the victims at the hospital were in their underwear.
You would then wear their clothes
to disguise yourself as them,
then check into the hotels where they'd made reservations.
You showed up on security
cameras for that reason.
The victims were all of approximately the same height and build
because you were choosing passengers you could impersonate.
Many wore hats and glasses
because that made impersonating them easier.
If the security feeds show someone looking reasonably like the victim,
you could fool the police easily.
By the time the last known sighting of the "victim" was recorded,
the real victim had already been abducted.
Sasaki's abduction was even easier, wasn't it?
After she collapsed at the train station,
a certain someone paid for her cab ride.
It's faster to hail a cab than call an ambulance at a train station.
That's all circumstantial evidence.
I suppose.
You're right.
What now, Kunikida-kun?
Are you being serious?
Let's make a deal.
A deal?
If you agree to my conditions, I'll turn myself in.
Please protect me at the Armed Detective Agency!
I must be protected for 72 hours while the prosecution concludes their questioning
and arranges witness protection.
What's this about?
I was put up to this.
I was assured by a new-fangled organ smuggling organization
that this was a great deal I'd never get caught for, and yet...
So there's a group behind all this?
Where are they?!
I don't know.
I always meet them in the Central Harbor Building.
So that's the place.
And?
Why do you need our protection?
Well...
It appears one of the people I kidnapped
was with the Port Mafia.
Well, that's not good—
The Port Mafia?!
Help me!
Hey!
I don't want to die!
Wait!
Kunikida-san.
I can't get a signal.
They must be jamming it.
If we lose the driver,
the truth may never come to light.
Dazai, pursue the driver.
Brat, contact the police and request backup.
I'll distract them as a decoy.
Roger!
Let's go!
Ability: Doppo Poet!
Flash Bang!
Now!
Metal is fragile,
and so is the human psyche.
What about you all, Armed Detective Agency?
You...
Akutagawa of the Port Mafia!
Indeed.
If you can't shoot straight,
I don't have to to consume the space around your bullets.
My hobbies don't include murder.
Worthless words of a weakling.
Doppo Poet!
Stun gun!
Come to heel, you aberrant dog.
It appears the Armed Detective Agency isn't merely a group of entertainers.
You're worthy of being Dazai-san's cover.
Interference.
Very well.
Our paths will cross again in the future.
We'll continue this another time.
Don't ever come again.
I turned the driver over to the police.
So this is the building the organ traffickers used for their deals?
They already flew the coop.
The wall's scorched black.
This is where the Azure King blew himself up.
That's right.
What?
You mean, the one in the infamous Azure Flag bombings?
That Azure King?
That's right.
A terrorist who destroyed many national and corporate facilities.
From the time I heard the term "Azure Messenger,"
I've been wondering if they were connected to the Azure King.
I heard that the Azure King blew himself up in the end.
So this was the place.
He committed suicide after the police cornered him, right?
That's right.
I'd determined that this was his hideout
and reported it to the police.
You were the one who found the Azure King's hideout?
But on that day,
the military, homeland security, and the police were all working together,
so the chain of command was in utter chaos.
Only five detectives arrived at the hideout in a timely manner upon receiving the report.
To add further insult to injury,
the Azure King got wind of the police's actions,
so he holed himself up with a bomb.
After a conflicting set of orders,
the decision was made to raid.
But ordinary policemen without special training or abilities didn't stand a chance.
Cornered, the Azure King blew himself up and perished,
along with the five detectives.
I remember now, Kunikida-kun.
One of the detectives was that Rokuzou boy's father, wasn't he?
He was an excellent detective with a strong sense of justice.
I'm the one who reported the hideout's location to the police.
I may as well have set the bomb off myself.
That's not true!
It's the terrorist's fault for blowing himself up!
That's right, Atsushi-kun.
Yet Kunikida-kun can't stop trying to look out for the Rokuzou boy
in his deceased father's stead.
What is it?
Another job for the Agency.
The client
Regards, The Azure Messenger
is the Azure Messenger.
I see.
I'm starting to see who this Azure Messenger is.
So? What's the job?
Disarming a bomb.
A bomb?
If we don't disarm the bomb by sunset tomorrow,
hundreds of people will die.
A bomb capable of that can't be easy.
The equipment here is for building a bomb.
With this setup,
you could build a very advanced bomb.
But...
Don't worry. We won't let the bomb go off.
We'll stop it for sure this time!
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
What should we do?
If we don't find and disarm the bomb by sundown,
there'll be hundreds of casualties.
If we cannot find the bomb
and lives are lost,
we won't be able to call ourselves a detective agency.
Oh, President.
Think of this mission as a struggle for the Agency's existence and pride.
Begin the investigation!
Man, where'd Dazai-san run off to now, of all times?
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 7:
Love for the Disease Called Ideals.
Episode 7
Love for the Disease Called Ideals