A Tea Soup Alien came to invade the Earth!
Tea Soup Beam! Beam! Beam!
The Tea Soup Alien led a massive attack!
Did that actually happen?
For a moment, Bo-bobo felt crushed.
Idiot!
But the animals' cheering...
gave strength to Bo-bobo!
Thank you, everyone!
I shall protect the future of the Earth!
Justice Shall Prevail!!
I really don't think that happened!
Go! Bo-bobo!! Fight! Bo-bobo!!
I said, this never happened!
Thanks to Bo-bobo's efforts,
the Earth was saved!
Huh? What's going on? Lies! Lies! It's all lies!
It's all lies
Would you like to buy a lunch or juice?
I'd like a traditional-style meal! ❤
I'd like a soda meal!!
Here you are. Thank you very much.
They actually have it...
This looks great!
BURY IT
Welcome back!
That was filling! Train rides just aren't the same without the lunchboxes!
A hang glider!?
What are you doing, Bo-bobo?
More importantly, were we
actually riding a plane!?
I'm going on ahead.
That punk!
Aren't those windows supposed to be sealed?
I'm not letting you go on ahead by yourself!
Don't do it! You can't jump with just an umbrella!
I can't lose to him!
I'm not losing to him!
Looks like you won...
Sorry to disturb you, but could you close the window? It's freezing.
The Terrible Ultimate Secret Technique of
the Fist of Somen! H.E.L.L.O!
Demode City
No way! You serious?
What's with the big slide?
What could this be?
A slide?
There's water coming down,
is it a big pool?
No, this is flowing somen!
Flowing somen?
Is this for some special event?
What's going on?
How's this!?
Master Somen
This is Demode City's 4000-year-old Fist of Somen!
Terrible! Terrible!
'Somen'
Terrible!
Bo-bobo can't do a thing
against the Fist of Somen!
What's going to happen?
We used to be so poor...
We boiled our somen in bathhouse water...
Bo-bobo!
Who's this? Who's this? Who's this guy?
Stop playing around!
We've got to find Don Patch!
Hey!
I'm training.
I'M TRAINING FOR THE SECRET
TECHNIQUE OF THE FIST OF SOMEN!
Now if you'll excuse me, Master Ramen.
Fare thee well.
Aren't you going to train
for the Secret Technique?
But wait one minute.
There is one thing I must tell you...
I'M MASTER SOMEN!!
Terrible! Terrible!
Terrible!
Fine then. I'll find Don Patch on my own.
But where could he be?
Policeman B
Policeman A
What do you mean, "from the sky?"
We're asking you where you came from!
But... But... I really did come from the sky!
Policeman B
Policeman A
Stray
Child
Heh... I've got no choice.
Beauty, hurry and bring that
emergency meal back here.
Emergency meal!?
I really did! I really did!
Mama!
Mama?
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Is this your child?
No...
He's my emergency meal...
You'd better keep a better
eye on him from now on.
I will...
Okay, let's go.
That bitch!
You're wide open!
My spike! Gimme back my charm point!
Those spikes come off?
Where'd that bastard go?
Anger
He ain't getting away with this!
It's that time again, folks!
MC
It's time for everyone's favorite "Be brave
and say something to your mother" corner!
Here you go, Bo-bobo!
Say something for your mother!
There he is!
My... My mama is a big sleepyhead.
So I always have to wake her up.
My... that silly child...
I found him!
Mama
But whenever Papa's mad at me,
Mama comes to my rescue.
I... I like my mama.
I like her more than anyone in the world!
That silly child... That silly child...
I've got to make him some chou cremes when he gets back!
Since when are you a mama?
Kuma = Bear
Mama?
Oh, you're back!
Mama... I'm sorry for taking your spike.
It's fine. Mama doesn't care.
Mama... I... I...
What? I just told you it doesn't matter.
I want to be with you forever!
Mama!
My boy!
Is something weird gonna happen again?
My boy...
Mama
and
Me
Okay, my boy. This is our new home.
Oh. It's kind of shabby.
But if you're with me, Mama, I'll live with it.
Oh, you silly child...
The Rice Scoops' Residence
Okay, my boy. This is our room.
Okay!
The Rice Scoops' Rice Scoops
Mom, how many more boxes?
Only two more.
Rice Scoop Mother
Rice Scoop Child
I'm tired of making rice scoops!
I'm sorry I have to make you do this. Let's have dinner when we're done.
The rice scoops are making rice scoops!
Pineapples
The rain's not stopping...
Yeah...
Oh, Daddy!
Dear!
I'm home.
Daddy!? Weren't you the child?
Dear, where have you been?
You were out having fun, weren't you?
And who's the girl?
I'm one of his friends...
And I'm his mother, and...
That one's the emergency meal!
The emergency meal
Dear, please get a job!
We don't have any more money...
Shut up! You stink like a rice scoop!
Rice scoops have smells...!!
Mommy!
Are you alright?
Dear,
we are going back to the Toaster Kingdom.
Toaster Kingdom!!??
Toaster Kingdom!? But they're rice scoops!
This is a toaster I made. Please take it.
O-OK.
Take care of that man.
He may act tough, but he's weak on the inside.
Goodbye.
Well, we appreciate what you've done for us all these years.
Get out! Get out! Good riddance!
Bo-bobo! That was really insensitive!
Don't you feel sorry for the rice scoops?
Shut up.
It's just... It's just that I...
I eat bread, not rice...
You silly boy... You silly boy...
Bread, not rice...
Why are you crying, too?
Guess I'm left behind again.
Mommy!
What?
It stopped raining.
You're right.
The End
The Rice Scoops' Residence
Bread, not rice...
How long are you guys gonna keep crying?
You silly boy...
I found you, Bo-bobo...
There, there. It's alright.
Hey, comfort me, too!
Why do I have to?
Take this!
Okay. I get it.
Look out!
Shit!
Bo-bobo! Look out!
Beauty!
Beauty! Beauty!
That girl should've minded her own business.
Son of a... Wait!
Hang in there, Beauty!
Beauty! Beauty!
Beauty!
W-What's this?
Loss
Beauty...
Beauty!!!
Girls Gang Boss
Patchmi
This is bad, Bo-boko!
Calm down, Patchmi.
But...
Head of the Kanto Girl Gang Union "Ecstacy"
Bo-boko
Let's keep this just between the two of us.
If the secret's out, you'll be sorry!
This is real bad! Let's turn ourselves in!
Don't you dare object.
Or what? You wanna be my
cup-and-ball's next victim?
Well, no but...
Then don't object to me.
Got it?
Yeah...
Let's go.
Yes...
The head of the Kanto Girl Gang Union "Ecstasy," Bo-boko.
Having to follow along with her methods,
Patchmi was irritated with herself.
Patchmi's Room
This is really bad...
I have a bad feeling about this...
I hope... I hope that girl's spirit doesn't come to haunt us! I'm scared...
It's from Bo-boko!
Maybe she's inviting me to a meeting!
Hello? Hello?
Patchmi... Help me... Help me...
Bo-boko? What's wrong, Bo-boko?
What was with that phone call?
It can't be... is it that girl's spirit?
That's it! It must be her spirit!
What am I gonna do?
She's gonna come to my house, too!
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
Beauty's Spirit!?
I'm sorry! I'm the one that said we should turn ourselves in!
But... But... Bo-boko...
H-
H-E-
H-E-L-
H-E-L-L-
H-E-L-L-O
HIS HEAD IS SHINING!!
H-E-L-L-O...
Bo-boko, you're a robot?
I'll explain later! The Galats army is coming!
What did you say?
And so, the first crisis passed.
But Patchmi did not know that she had been dragged into a giant intergalactic war!
Patchmi, I'm going again!
Don't go, Bo-boko!
Bo-boko!
SF Robot Action Anime: Energy☆Busters!
Episode 2:
The Voice of the Stars
Energy Busters
Experience the Universe!
Stay tuned next time!
What are you guys doing?
Oh! You've come to, Beauty!
It's a ghost!
Excuse me, I'm still alive!
More importantly, Beauty, look at your forehead.
What's this?
Who did this?
It won't come off!
Who did it...
Could it be the Hair Hunters?
Correct!
Mr. Sakashita!
You know him?
Hair Hunters C-block Trooper Gechappi
I'm Hair Hunters C-block Trooper Gechappi.
M... Mister... Please accept these cookies I made just for you...
Hey! Are you stealing a march on me? That's not fair!
Not fair! Not fair! Not fair!
Cookies!?
It's moving by itself!
Hey, woman!
What you have just received was a Hair Loss Beam.
Those hit by this beam will
lose all
lose all their hair in 10 hours...
their hair
in 10 hours...
I'll lose my hair? No way!
Cookies!?
That's a great expression.
You butted in too far for your own good.
You're so mean! She worked
so hard to make them!
You're next, Bo-bobo!
Take this!
Hair Loss Beam!!
Bo-bobo, look out!
Don Patch!
Another intrusion...
Hang in there, Don Patch!
Don Patch! Hang in there!
T-This can't be...
Invincible Fortress Zygas
Invincible Fortress Zygas!?
You're awake?
Hey, what happens when it says "Invincible Fortress Zygas?"
No clue! That's what I want to know!
NO CLUE!
Are you alright?
You're so kind.
Oh well. At least it looks like
my attack worked on the girl.
How dare you do that to Beauty and the emergency meal!
THE EMERGENCY MEAL!
So I'm really the emergency meal?
Take this!
Nose Hair Serpent Fist!
Change Beauty back to normal!
What about me?
Don't get so worked up.
The only way to return her to normal is to use the medicine in C-block Base.
If you want the medicine, follow me!
Wait!
Zygas! Zygas!
There's no time to cry, Beauty!
We'll get the medicine for sure!
Alright!
Off to C-block Base!
To C-block
Three tickets to C-block.
We're going by train...
The train for C-block Base will leave shortly.
Oh, shit!
Wait for me!
That was close.
Huh? Where's Bo-bobo?
What are you doing, Bo-bobo?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kenichi. I can't go with you.
Garcia
I just can't leave my parents.
Why not? Didn't we decide we'd leave together?
Mr. Kenichi... please fulfill your dream.
I've found her! It's Garcia!
I will...
I will... fulfill my own dream.
You're not getting away!
I won't run or hide!
Farewell... Elsion.
Dammit! Who the hell is Elsion?
I've never heard of the guy! I don't get it!
Even Don Patch doesn't get it...
We're really on a train this time. Not a plane.
Umm... our seats are...
C12 and...
But this train's pretty empty.
C12...
Hey...
What?
Am I useless? Will you throw me away if you don't want me?
I don't know!
Let's see... C12... C12...
He's on the train!
You son of a bitch!
You'll pay for dissing us earlier!
Oh. It's you guys.
Alright, Beauty, get me my Don Patch Sword!
Eh? What's that?
Idiot! I said a Don Patch Sword!
Hurry and give me a Don Patch Sword!
I told you, I've never heard of it before! What is it?
Whatever. Just give me whatever you've got!
I have this green onion...
Oh! You DO have a Don Patch Sword!!!
Oh!
Don Patch
Sword!!!
Alright, now that I have this...
I can win!
But that's a green onion.
I lost.
Well, duh.
Is that all you got, small fry?
If only I had a Don Patch Hammer right now...
I have this green onion...
Oh!
Oh! You DO have a Don Patch Hammer!!!
Don Patch
Hammer!!!
Alright, now that I have this,
I can win!
But that's a green onion!
No way! They're fighting on equal terms!
Hi-yah!!
You're not bad!
But you're still no match for me!
Oh no! My Don Patch Hammer!
I'm burnt out...
He turned white...
That's how serious your challenge was.
The games are over!
I'm beat...
Don Patch! Look out!
That's...
Beauty!
Bo-bobo!
Dammit...
You're such a fool...
You came all this way to be defeated!
Take this! Hair Loss Beam!
Shit!
Bo-bobo!
Loss
Kaki... kuko... kako... kaki... kuko...
Kako... kaki... kuko... kako... kaki...
What's he doing!?
Kaki... kuko... kako... kaki... kuko... kako...
I get it! He's taking the "ke" out of all the words!
Raw wheat... Raw sesame... Raw egg...
You're right! He's taking the "ke" out of all the words!
Don't copy me. And those words don't have "ke" in them to begin with!
It's a bit different from what I wanted, but I've finally defeated Bo-bobo!
Mission Complete
What was that?
Bo-bobo? Wait a minute...
So who was...
Bo-bobo Doll (Large)
He turned into a doll!
What? You're right!
He really did turn into a doll!
Damn you! You bastards keep fucking with me!
I will defeat you with the Secret Technique of the Fist of Ramen!
Prepare yourself!
Tunnel
We're in a tunnel...
Welcome to the world of the Fist of Ramen!
What's this!?
Watch closely! This is Demode City's 4000-year-old Fist of Ramen!
Zygas! Zygas!
Here they come... Take this! Hair Loss Beam!
Shit! We're in trouble!
What? Already?
Emergency escape! I'll leave the rest to you...
Emergency meal!
So that's how it's gonna be? Here I go!
Damn those bastards...
Eat this! Fist of Ramen Secret Technique:
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your tea. Take your time.
Mmmm... 5 stars.
The Ramen Store of Tasty Tea!!!
Tunnel
Master Ramen, I have defeated the enemy
with the technique you taught me.
Magnificent. I have nothing left to teach you.
M... Master Ramen...
But there is one thing I must tell you...
I'M MASTER SOMEN!
Note: He's Master Somen
Terrible! Terrible!
Terrible!
Really terrible!
Mother and Son Hot Springs
I won again today!
Idiot, my hajike was in better shape.
Heh. I can't relax when you guys are around.
Right?
That's not something to laugh at.
But this water is great!
This is the best part of a trip!
Huh? We're on a trip...
but where were we going again?
Oh well!
The word "loss" remains on Beauty's forehead.
Beauty's hair only has a few hours left!
Will Bo-bobo and friends find the medicine
before it's too late?
Oh, and... what'll happen to Don Patch?
Whatever.
Zygas! Zygas!
I am proud to announce this
year's Miss Chicken Queen...
We're in the enemy base! Stop goofing off!
But this is really fun! I can turn into a cyborg and a monster cat!
Stop having fun by yourselves and look at reality!
You're right. Look at that guy with the really suspicious pink face!
Wow, it's really suspicious!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
10th Miss Chicken Queen Chickie and The Mysterious Guard Softon
He's too mysterious!