At present, we have an unknown mob
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
Azure Messenger Bomb Threat Incident
First Investigation Meeting
Armed Detective Agency
Conference Room
threatening to detonate a huge bomb in a crowded area
and launch a smear campaign
against the Agency.
I know the Agency's in a huge predicament.
Tell us about the bomb.
This is the message left behind by the perpetrator.
I'll read it.
"Greetings, I hope your
agency is faring well."
"Forgive my insolence, but I have placed a bomb
able to cause mass destruction in a certain location here in Yokohama City."
"To ensure public safety,
I request that you locate and defuse the bomb at your earliest convenience."
"You have until sundown."
"I have faith in your abilities."
"Respectfully, the Azure Messenger."
Who could the Azure Messenger be?
We have no idea yet.
So it's all rigged so that if the bomb detonates,
news of the Agency's failure will spread like wildfire.
The Agency can withstand sticks and stones,
but this type of attack would severely debilitate us.
Since yesterday, the office staff have been searching for plausible locations,
but there are too many possibilities.
Hey.
Are we still unable to reach Rampo-san?
It seems the case in Kyuushuu
is coming to a head.
I've requested he contact us as
soon as the criminal is caught, but...
Any other intel from the taxi driver?
He denies any knowledge of the bomb.
He wouldn't have the guts to blow up Yokohama itself.
Listen up!
This case is a dastardly act using intel to attack the Armed Detective Agency.
We have two objectives,
unveil the Azure Messenger, the instigator,
and defuse the bomb.
The bomb takes priority due
to its time-limited nature.
If we fail to find the
bomb and lives are lost,
we may no longer call ourselves a detective agency.
Think of this mission as a struggle for the Agency's existence and pride.
What time do you think it is, stupid four-eyes?!
You're the only one I know who's still sleeping at 9:00 a.m.
Are you able to find the Azure Messenger, the one who sent us that message?
Aren't you calling because you wanted to ask me something else?
So you know everything.
I only know what I actually know.
I want to ask you about tracing the bomb-making equipment.
I'll send you the shipping manifest.
A bomb?
Things are looking up for you.
Cut the chatter and get cracking.
Oh?
This is to save lives.
You may be regularly indulging in illicit activities,
but you should serve society sometimes.
Get off your high horse.
You're not my dad.
No.
Episode 7
Love for the Disease
Called Ideals
I'll never be your father.
Are you sure about this?
The Agency seemed chaotic due to the bomb threat.
Kunikida-sama seemed occupied, as well.
Kunikida-kun is a workhorse.
After all, he spends two hours before going to sleep
reviewing and editing his notes.
I doubt I could bare that for two minutes.
Maybe he's got some soldier ants working for him in his brain—
Oh, I didn't know you were here, Kunikida-kun.
How could you ditch the meeting during an emergency
and go on a fancy afternoon date?
Are you jealous of the fancy date?
I'm not!
So he is.
She's a victim who was nearly killed.
Ensuring her safety and tending to her psyche
is an important and urgent duty for the Agency, wouldn't you say?
Why are you, the poster child for sloth and irresponsibility, a good fit for the task?
Besides, given her charm,
I'd assume she has a lover at least.
Apparently, they broke up recently.
That's why, Kunikida-kun,
I say go for it!
Listen, Dazai!
I came here because you skipped out on the morning meeting
and I need to tell you what's going on.
I know what's going on.
The goal of the Azure Messenger who set the bomb
is to crush the Agency.
Um...
Are you sure an outsider like me should be hearing this?
Not really.
Sasaki-san's a person of interest in this case.
There's no issue here.
What?
Sasaki-san, what class do you teach at the university again?
Social psychology.
That's great.
I'd love to hear what you think about this case.
About the Azure Messenger,
it may be related to the Azure King
in the notorious Azure Flag Terrorist bombing.
So you think that, as well.
It may very well be the Azure King himself.
It's said that he blew himself up after being cornered by the police,
but it's possible he faked his death
and is still alive.
This world is incomplete.
One may grieve or pray,
but people still die from mishappenings,
and evil goes unpunished to flourish freely in this world.
A former official,
the Azure King set off a bomb in a government facility and issued a maxim.
His targets included killers whose cases were dropped due to inadequate prosecutors,
as well as diet members who were engaged in political corruption on a global scale.
All hazardous criminals invulnerable to law.
Thus I shall desire the ideal world.
It will be built not by the hand of God,
but by our own bloodied fingers.
But if the Azure King is alive,
why would he attack the Agency like this?
I have no idea.
Well, the one who backed the Azure King into a corner
is Kunikida-kun, who located his base.
I see.
Kunikida-kun is the target of vengeance here.
The terrorist's death was confirmed by the military police after forensic analysis.
There's no doubting it.
Either way,
you should stay cautious until you figure out who it is.
We'll need to hide Sasaki-san somewhere safe, as well.
That I will not allow, Dazai!
What do you mean?
You think you can keep a lady in your room
in the name of personal safety?
And day and night, do such and such unthinkable things?!
Nothing like what you're imagining is happening, though.
Shame on you!
Huh?
When I first let her stay,
I slept in the next room over
and didn't lay a finger on her, of course.
Well, I knew you misunderstood,
but I thought it was funny so I didn't correct you.
I really wonder why these two are partners.
Kunikida-kun seems to like Sasaki-san a lot.
Sasaki-san, what type of man do you like?
T-Type?
It would be presumptuous of me to even have such a thing in mind.
But, I do think it is wonderful when a man strongly believes in an ideal
and pours his heart and soul into it.
That's totally Kunikida-kun.
Okay, the two of you can pick up the rest.
Hey, Dazai!
D-Don't go making assumptions!
Kunikida-kun, you're an open book.
He really is.
He may be a bit misrepresented,
but as you can see, he is an intelligent individual who lives and breathes for his ideals.
Although, perhaps for that reason, his ideal woman is a bit of a challenge.
Care to take a look?
Bastard, not again! When did you—
Give it back!
Kunikida-sama...
Yes?
This goes too far.
Kunikida-san's crushed.
From:  Haruno Kirako
Subject: Received Word from Rampo-san
Atsushi-kun,
We heard back from
Rampo-san!
His case is finished, so
he has time to help us.
Haruno Kirako
We finally heard from Rampo-san.
So we know where the bomb is?
Edogawa Rampo
And here I was hoping to sightsee in Kyuushuu
and eat an egg treat since I solved my case.
You all disappoint me.
You can't conduct a single investigation properly without me.
We only have until sundown.
Please tell us the location.
A department store?
A school?
Or a train station?
Any one of these could produce casualties in the hundreds.
Where's the bomb?
The fishing shop.
Huh?
The bomb was set in a fishing shop in Negishi.
Oh, I see.
You're amazing, Rampo-san.
But why a fishing shop?
Do we have a map?
Behind the seat.
Page 97.
Page 97, okay.
Oh.
The terrorist's target is the petrochemical complex.
I see.
I don't know why I didn't realize it.
Yokohama is one of Japan's major port towns.
Here, there are many large facilities that store oil and gas.
If an explosion were to ignite nearby storage tanks,
the entire port would be engulfed in flames.
However, infiltrating a facility of that nature
will require getting past pretty good security.
The easiest approach would be to put a bomb in a car,
and leave the car near one of the facilities.
So, considering the range of a bomb that can be loaded into a car,
that fishing store is the one place that fits the bill.
Bingo.
The military police's bomb disposal squad has found the bomb,
but the bomb can't be moved
due to the timer device.
They say it'll be difficult to diffuse it by sundown.
We're having the nearby residents evacuate,
but we're not sure there's enough time.
No way.
However, the bomb's set to deactivate if we can transmit a stop signal.
We have to do something.
Wh-What's going on?!
A phone call.
Huh?
Hello?
Hey, Four-Eyes, is now a good time?
Rokuzou?
Um...
What is it?
I think we're causing a traffic jam.
Hello?
Hello, Atsushi-kun.
Rampo-san?
Okay.
Hello?
Dazai?
President?
Yes.
What?
The military police's...
I see.
Set a thief to catch a thief, I see.
That's quite...
Okay.
Understood.
Yes.
Right.
No, that's helpful.
Understood.
Understood, President.
I got a call from Rokuzou.
Someone recently ordered a transmitter and other equipment
to be delivered to a former police facility.
Rampo-san reached a similar conclusion.
That settles it, then.
My call was from the president.
He was informed by the military
police that the driver has died.
He's dead?
But I thought he was in the military police's isolation ward for protection.
He died after suddenly collapsing in pain in his cell.
No idea how he died,
but the numbers "00" were marked on his palm.
Numbers on his palm?
What?
What in the world's going on?
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
l
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
Former
Defense
Force
Facility
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
T-20
Minutes
Until
Detonation
Kunikida-kun!
Doppo Poet!
Flash Bang!
We're at the right place!
You two, go upstairs!
Find the transmitter and send the stop signal!
What the...
Give me your number.
How've you been?
You're looking great.
I'm sure you have a great number.
This is...
You sniffed out the place just like your reputation predicted.
The Armed Detective Agency's impressive.
Very impressive.
The sun's setting.
Can you figure it out?
It's easy!
But I can't do it.
What?
You have to insert the release key here and turn it,
but I don't have it.
What are we going to do?!
What are you doing here?
Wow, we've got quite a super heavy hitter here!
This one's ability can perform remote attacks!
What's your number now?
Number?
My ability cannot be evaded, you see.
I can send people who have numbers
in any direction I want.
Even if they're on the
other side of the earth.
And once their number becomes zero,
they'll die in agony.
No one can escape that fate.
No one.
Are you the boss of this group?
Your group poses a greater obstacle than the Mafia, for sure.
But the Armed Detective
Agency is now finished.
Here's the key.
It's the release key to stop the bomb.
Without it, you can't stop the bomb.
Do you want it?
Of course you do.
If you want it... here.
Now, there is no hope.
It's finished.
It's over, isn't it?
You fool!
Atsushi-kun!
You have really strong arms.
You should have gone into the bouncer business.
Kunikida-kun!
I know!
Don't think you can pull the same trick twice!
Dazai!
Here!
Will you be the next one to give me a number?
Impossible!
Why has no number marked you?!
Unfortunately, your ability will no longer have any effect.
Also, you should really have your partner switch careers and be a bouncer.
The weight difference doesn't seem to faze him at all.
Dazai-san.
Their partnership is amazing.
Oh, right!
Kunikida-san, the key?
He broke it.
What?!
Then what about the bomb?
We don't have time—
Calm down, brat.
Doppo Poet.
Release key.
My ability allows me to recreate anything I have laid eyes on
and understood its form and function.
However, the object's size is limited to that of a pocketbook.
So your notebook is really a tool that brings your ideals into reality.
You're visiting the graves of those who have lost their lives?
Yes.
When I first caused casualties during a job,
I cried so much I couldn't get up,
and I didn't go to work at times.
But now, I don't even shed a tear.
I just choose to visit their graves in exchange, or that's how I think of it.
Will the dead by comforted by tears?
I doubt they'd be comforted or redeemed by tears.
After all, their time stopped at the moment of their deaths.
I confess I told a lie earlier.
My significant other and I parted ways because he died.
I see.
What you said is true.
Time no longer has meaning for the dead.
No matter what I may do for him,
he cannot rejoice in it,
nor smile because of it.
I lost my composure without meaning to.
I have something I must attend to.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Kunikida-kun?
I need you for something.
What do you want here, of all places?
What do you think this is?
It's a survey of Yokohama we found on a computer in their base.
Surprisingly, it concludes that eradicating the Agency is the first priority
in order to take control of Yokohama.
And not the Port Mafia, who control the underworld?
They were being manipulated by false intel.
So there's another mastermind?
Actually, I've sent an email to the one I believe is truly behind this.
I said I have proof that they are the one truly responsible.
That person should be here any moment now.
It can't be you!
You're the one, Rokuzou?!
What are you talking about?
So it hasn't started yet?
I see.
You took a peek at my email by hacking into my account, didn't you?
So it's not really you!
I just wanted to take a look at the
one who's actually responsible.
So it's really, really not you, right—
Look out!
So you're the Azure Messenger,
Sasaki Nobuko-san.
It can't be.
I doubt this is the first time you used your intelligence
to execute a crime, either.
He was a man who lived for his ideals.
He was pure in his intentions to seek out the world of crime,
and that is why he got blood on his hands.
I just wanted to grant his desire and make his ideals come true.
Your significant other, the Azure King,
was an idealist who wanted to prosecute criminals who could not be judged by law
through illegal means.
This incident was meant to carry on his work.
Lower your gun!
What good will this accomplish?
Don't you understand?
You resemble him in a way.
Your plan was very sophisticated.
Without committing a single crime of your own,
you set up the Agency to take the fall,
and you destroyed both the kidnapper and the criminal organization behind him.
But you yourself have no convictions nor ideals.
You're just being swept along by the flow.
I'm just tired, now.
I want to be free from all this.
Will you shoot me, Dazai-san?
But I've lowered my gun.
If you were to shoot me now,
it'd be excessive use of force.
Kunikida-san's watching us.
You're right.
I can't shoot.
However...
The Azure King killed my dad.
Good riddance.
Why?!
Why does it have to end this way?!
What went wrong?!
Who was wrong?!
No one was wrong.
This was the only possible outcome.
Shut up!
You could've saved her!
Are you saying this is justice?!
Justice is a weapon.
It can be used to cause harm,
but it cannot protect or save others.
What killed Sasaki-san was, in the end, the justice of the Azure King
and of you.
Kunikida-kun,
as long as you pursue your ideals,
the flames that burned in the Azure King will one day take root in you
and raze everything around you.
Still!
I'll still push on until I push past it!
Don't underestimate my ideals!
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
Atsushi, aren't you hurt?
No, not in the slightest.
I'm in good health.
Oh, how boring.
Um, about your "treatment," Dr. Yosano.
How does it work, exactly?
Would you like to find out?
Why don't you ask Tanizaki since he was treated by me before?
Oh, but Tanizaki-san just shivers in fear
and won't tell me anything.
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 8:
Teaching Them To Kill; Then To Die.
Episode 8
Teaching Them To Kill; Then to Die
Ability: Thou Shalt Not Die.