After Bo-bobo reached Demode City,
Rice Scoop Mother and Son
his love for the Rice Scoop mother and son, who lived on despite being poor, deepened.
C-block Trooper Gechappi
But then...
Beauty was hit by Hair Hunters C-block Trooper,
Gechappi's Hair Loss Beam.
The word "Loss" mysteriously
appeared on Beauty's forehead.
In just 10 hours,
Beauty will lose all her hair!!
But I think I'd like to see Beauty like that...
You're mean...
Oh, whoops. Sorry.
Bo-bobo defeated Gechappi with his special move.
The Ramen Store of Tasty Tea!!!
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, and Beauty...
hurried to Hair Hunters C-block Base to get the medicine that will stop the hair loss!
Alright! I've recovered from
falling back in the first half!
Let's end this, Patchiki!
That brat... he's done it now.
Watch me, Father!
I will become the fastest in the world...
with this machine you made!
Arrest him! Arrest him!
Hells' Gate Curve
Here it is. The entrance to Hell: Hell's Gate Curve.
There are many who lost their lives because they failed this turn.
Here it is! This is the only place where I can beat Patchiki!
Arrest him! Arrest him! Arrest him!
I'm scared! But...
I don't want to lose anymore!
That idiot! He passed me at
full speed! He's gonna die!
That's too much. He's driving an FF Custom vehicle.
Not even my customized
SRM.VOX 23 R could make it safely,
not at that speed.
Turning this curve has nothing to do with the driver's skill!
The vehicle's capacity is all that matters!
That man... is dead!
Father! Father!!!
This is thrilling!
I'm gonna drive to the limits!
10th Miss Chicken Queen Chickie and The Mysterious Guard Softon
Hair Hunters C-block Base
Okay, everyone!
This is C-block Base!
All Smiles Tour
Imperial Steamed Buns
We have Imperial Steamed Buns, Hair Hunter Spicy Crackers,
Hair Hunter Spicy Crackers
and many other souvenir items available.
Guide
That's amazing.
It's pretty tall.
Now, please move to the middle! We'd like to take a group shot with the tower in the background!
Armor: Wind
Hair Hunters C-block Captain Geha the Tornado...
Hair Hunters C-block
Captain Geha the Tornado
Our plan has succeeded. Bo-bobo will arrive soon.
The rest is up to you, TesuiKatsu.
Yes, sir!
Gechappi... You did a good job on him.
Bo-bobo Action Figure (Limited Edition)
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
I, TesuiKatsu, guardian of the
Red Hot Room, will defeat you!
Guardian of the Red Hot Room
TesuiKatsu
It's an emergency! It's an emergency!
One, two, three, HEAVE!
Prep for operation!
Are you alright?
Please go ahead, Doctor!
Doctor
Doctor!?
I'm scared! I don't want an operation!
It hurts! I don't want an operation!
Anesthesia
Anesthesia.
P-U...
I don't want an operation...
I guess you could say that's a strong anesthesia...
I will now commence the operation.
Fork.
Not a scalpel!?
Are you going to help him?
Are you really gonna make him better?
Can you really fix him with that?
Eraser.
Eraser
Banana.
Banana
Battery.
Battery
Cucumber.
Cucumber
Hammer.
Hammer
Compass.
Compass
I...
I'm...
The operation was successful.
Doctor!
My propeller! Wait up, my propeller!
Propeller!
I'm gonna beat this guy up!
What is this great demonic energy?
You noticed it too?
Be careful. There's a superdreadnought demon hiding nearby!
Where could it be?
"How do I even make a comeback?" thought Beauty.
What's wrong?
I-It's here!
What? Where? Where is it?
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Toothbrush
Toothpaste Tube
Let's brush some teeth!
We'll work together!
How can this be?
Of all things, it's the Demon Toothbrush Set!
But it's a good thing it's just the toothbrush and toothpaste.
If there were a cup, we'd be done for!
There is!
Cup
Hello.
Shit!
It's perfect!
Brush! Brush!
They're cute!
In that case...
Thoughts and ideas are the source of existence...
Rid yourself of thought... Strengthen your ideas...
Rid yourself of halitosis...
Disperse the demons!!
This is fate.
Bro!
What is this familiar feeling?
When did I stop believing in others?
When did I stop loving others?
That doesn't matter anymore.
In this moment, I am a toothbrush!
Yes! I am a toothbrush!
I'll brush my shoes, too.
Bro!
Fine. Brush them.
The fun ends now!
Oh!
It spilled!
Look over here!
Don Patch!
I tried to catch him in a trap, but he trapped me instead, woof!
Be careful! He won't fall for bones!
Veggies! Veggies!
There's no way he won't fall for veggies!
Now, Bo-bobo. It's time to face off.
Prepare yourself, Bo-bobo!
This ends now!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The
Mayonnaise
War
The Mayonnaise War begins!!!
begins!!!
Don Patch!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
I thought so...
You're not getting away with this!
More coins! More coins!
What are you doing!? Get me out of here!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
DRIED-UP...
I'm pretty damn thirsty...
Don't get so cocky just coz you beat me.
I'm just an underling.
This C-block base is divided into five levels of Hell.
You
are
here
You
are
here
You
are
here
As you climb further up, more diabolical levels will await you.
Sorry, could you repeat that?
I hope it's not too late...
The hair loss is starting!
You're under arrest!
Don't worry, Beauty.
Trust me.
I've been caught...
Why does my blood boil so much?
Just what is this guy's head...
Wha... Wha... Wha... Wha... Wha...
I better stop.
The same old C-block Base
C-Climb these stairs to reach the second Hell.
Go and get defeated already.
Oh, look! An elevator!
You're right!
We can use this to get all the way to the top!
Yeah!
I'm sure the medicine for the Hair Loss Beam is there!
Hooray!
Uh... hello... excuse me...
Ignore it! Please ignore it!
We can't do that, can we?
Nope.
Please! I beg you!
Please! Please!
I guess we got no choice.
Just this once, 'kay?
Click.
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
Mama!
Chick
There, there. Don't you cry.
See, help has arrived.
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
I finally got them rounded up...
Take off those sunglasses!!
They aren't wearing any!
Fire in the hole!
They were wearing sunglasses.
Weren't they wearing sunglasses?
10th Miss Chicken Queen Contest
Judge
Well... now that the judging is finished, we will now announce the winner.
The most brilliant participant of the
10th Miss Chicken Queen Contest is...
Entry #3, Chickie!
Miss Chicken Queen
Chickie
Congratulations!
I will now present you with the Queen's gown and scepter. You look ex-scepter-nal.
Ex-scepter-nal... You were dazzling, Chickie!
Stop playing around! Let's just go!
If this elevator's not going anywhere, I'm gonna take the stairs!
Madam, here's some eggs I picked out myself.
FRESH-PICKED
Do you want to cook them?
I can have them? You're always doing favors for me...
Let's cook them sunny-side up for dinner!
But Madam, they're so fresh that you should cook eggs-on-rice.
Oh, I should?
Yes, you should. Eggs-on-rice.
Eggs-on-rice?
Eggs-on-rice!
Then should I cook eggs-on-rice?
Eggs-on-rice?
The Room of Thunder...
What traps could await us in here?
But we must continue!
Video Corner
Welcome!
IT'S A VIDEO RENTAL STORE!!!
Dammit! I'm late!
Good morning, manager!
You're five minutes late!
2nd Floor Guardian... I mean Manager
Man... this happens every time.
Break Room
Bobobo-bo Bo-bomi
This is terrible! This is the third time this week!
He's gonna fire me!
Bo-bomi.
Miss Spikette
Are you taking this part-time job lightly?
Miss Spikette...
Looks like you won't get it without some pain, ah?
Well I'll give it to you!
How's this? How's this? How's this?
Want more?
What the hell is going on?
Manager!
We've got a new part-timer starting today.
You guys show him the ropes.
Oh, no! Spikette's gonna bully the new guy again!
I wonder who's gonna get in this time...
Whoever it is, I'll bully him real good.
You! Get in here!
New Guy: Keselan Paseran
This is Keselan Paseran.
I don't have any experience, so I know I'll get in the way a lot...
but I'll do my best.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
Manager! There's trouble!
What's wrong?
There's 500 yen missing from the register!
What?
Damn! I forgot my makeup today, so I took
500 yen from the register to do my makeup!
That's the thief.
No doubt.
How did you know?
I'm sorry!
He made me steal it!
I didn't want to do it... But he said he'd wriggle more if I didn't...
I was scared... I was so scared, I...
Is this true, Keselan Paseran?
It's true.
He's covering for me!
Here you go.
Fuckin' idiot!
Take this! And this! And this! And this!
How dare you take the store's money!
Stop it! Stop it!
Somebody! Somebody save him!
Fist of the Nose Hair:
The man that ended
the Mayonnaise War, his name was...
the Mayonnaise War,
his name was...
Consort Ketchup!
Risumi, come back!!
Is he alright?
He's done for...
How despicable!
You too...
I won't forgive them! I'll never forgive them!
Hey, let's hurry and go to the third floor.
Absolutely.
Bo-bobo had defeated the 2nd floor guardian...
I mean, the manager,
and they continued to the third floor,
with Keselan Paseran in their hearts.
The Room of Rapids
The Room of Rapids...
What traps could await us in here?
Welcome!
Of course...
NOT AGAIN!!!
Mama!
I wanna see this one!
Didn't you watch it yesterday? Pick something else.
Okay. I got it.
For Pete's sake, that kid is such a hopeless idiot.
Which one, which one?
Which one?
New Arrivals
Ah!
"All About Youth" is checked out...
I'll just go with these two.
Eh!
That's...!
It's terrible!
What's wrong?
There was this guy...
And his head was all twirly and pink...
He shouldn't have been checking out videos but he was checking out videos!
Oh, please! Don't say things that
I can't understand, you stupid brat!
It's true! I saw it!
His head was twirtly... and it was pink...
and he was checking out videos!
If you keep acting stupid, we'll be going home!
But it's true! He liked dramas!
That'll be 600 yen for two videos.
I've got enough points, so I'll pay with this.
Thank you again for your patronage.
It's terrible!
What's wrong?
He was a regular!
That pink twirly guy was a regular!
Smarten up, will you?
No... It's true... It's true... It's true...
The pink guy rented a video
with the points he collected...
But he's not challenging us. Let's just move on.
It's true! It's really true!
Thank you very much!
Looks like this floor has no guardian...
Have at you.
3rd Floor Guard Bun-bun the Bunny
Have at you. Have at you.
Have at you.
Have at you. Hey. Have at you.
I'll beat the stuffing out of you.
Wait for me, Bo-bobo!
Wait up!
She beat me.
The Jet Black Room
The Jet Black Room...
It doesn't seem like a video rental store this time.
Dammit, where's the medicine?
I think it's on the top floor,
which is right after this one.
Can my hair hold out?
We don't have much time left. Let's hurry.
Glad you've come, thou angels
that have lost thy wings.
Let us begin the feast of our souls!
Who is this weird man with a pink, twirly head
that lay in wait in the Jet Black room?
Neither Bo-bobo...
nor Beauty...
nor Don Patch,
Nor I knew who he is!
Well... Stay tuned next time!
Time... time... time...
Bo-bobo, we're out of time!
My hair's gonna fall out!
I'm gonna turn into an invincible fortress!
You both stand back. This man is fearsome.
Who is he?
I know him, he's a famous fashion designer!
How!?
Zygas! Zygas!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Releasing your Soul: That means, Piropiropiropiro... Pirocchi!
That hairstyle's gonna be in!