What are you looking at?
What can you see?
Hey, Missy, are you waiting for someone?
Actually, I think I saw you here yesterday, too.
Have you been standing here the entire time?
Maybe she's a doll.
Oh, she blinked!
Woah!
She moved!
Huh?
Me?
Found you.
This can't be good.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
Dazai has disappeared?
He hasn't been answering his phone,
and he hasn't returned to the dorm, either.
He's just floating in some river again.
Or he could be in prison this time.
My guess is he left to flirt with a woman.
But it's true that he's targeted by the Port Mafia.
It could be that...
That man's ability to sense danger and stay alive approaches nightmarish proficiency.
Just think about how he's as healthy as can be
despite numerous suicide attempts.
I doubt the Mafia alone will be enough to get the better of him.
But...
I'll investigate it.
Are you all better now, Tanizaki-san?
Yes, thankfully.
I was really worried when it all happened.
I'm relieved you're fine.
I'm sorry I worried you.
So you've finally recovered.
It's all thanks to Dr. Yosano's treatment.
So, how many times did she get you?
F-F-Four times.
That many...
Atsushi-kun...
As long as you remain at the Agency,
remember to never get injured.
Okay.
If you think you're at any risk, run.
You should cultivate your ability to sense danger every day.
For example, ten seconds from now...
Oh, Dr. Yosano.
Good morning.
Oh, Atsushi.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh, I'm fine.
Damn.
Damn?
I was hoping to have someone accompany me on a shopping trip,
but I guess you're the only one available.
What?
Is this what he meant by the ability to sense danger?
D-Dr. Yosano, are you still not done?
Don't you dare drop anything.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You failure!
Hurry up and send my car over!
Ow...
U-Um, are you okay?
Why did you do that, you damn brat?
This is a custom suit from Europe.
S-Sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Were you hurt?
Don't touch me.
I'll file a complaint with your employer!
Hey, what's your job?
Are you a tea server?
A receptionist?
Or perhaps you're something more specialized?
Hmm.
Ow!
I'm a doctor, you pervert.
What's this?
You have two arms? That's too many.
Would you like me to remove one?
Episode 8
Teaching Them To Kill;
Then To Die
I'm sorry about... um... earlier.
The packages are in a sorry state, too.
Don't worry about it.
By the way...
What?
Is this punishment?
Hmm, nice leg.
I heard your leg was bitten off
by the Port Mafia when Tanizaki got injured.
No signs of scarring or fusion.
It's more restoration than regeneration.
The tiger did this instantly?
Um...
Is there a problem?
Oh, I'm just sad I couldn't treat you.
But there'll be no mercy from me next time.
What?
The Mafia is known for surprise attacks.
You should watch yourself at night.
You never know when they may strike next.
That's right.
I'm their prime target.
I should know how to defend myself.
Testing, testing. This is your train conductor.
We apologize for the discomfort, but we shall now conduct a minor physics experiment!
The topic: Evaluation of an Explosive Reaction and Sensory Response
in a Non-Inertial Reference Frame.
The test subjects will be our current passengers!
We greatly appreciate your cooperation!
So, without further ado,
please listen to this!
Maybe two or three of
you died from that one?
But that will pale in comparison to the next one!
We've rigged enough explosives
in the front and back cars
to blow everyone clear to the moon!
Now, test subject Atsushi-kun.
Unless you surrender yourself,
all passengers will go straight to heaven, maybe even the moon!
But...
Speak of the devil...
Wh-What should we do?
Option one, turn yourself in.
Option two, jump off this running train with several dozen passengers to escape.
Option three...
give them hell.
Excellent.
After all, we are the Armed Detective Agency.
Okay, Atsushi.
Let's split up and locate the bombs.
I'll take the front.
You take the rear.
What if we find the enemy?
Terminate with extreme prejudice.
Roger!
A bomb threat, on a train with civilians, in broad daylight,
that's essentially suicide.
Even for the Port Mafia, this plan's pretty bold.
Or, rather, obsessive.
I wonder who's behind this.
Our warmest welcome to the decisive lady from the Detective Agency
and our most regretful farewell!
Well, well,
if it isn't a celebrity we've got here.
Oh, you're still alive?
What a surprise.
Ladies are so resilient these days.
It is an era of equality for men and women.
From where I stand,
it's a greater surprise to find a wanted criminal like you in a place like this.
Kajii Motojirou!
While being a member of the secretive Port Mafia,
you're a surprisingly infamous terrorist bomber.
Port Mafia
Operative
Kajii
Motojirou
Port Mafia
Operative
Kajii
Motojirou
Ability:
Lemon Bomb
In the recent Marizen Building Bombing,
where you murdered 28 civilians.
That was most wondrous.
The slowing of the pulse,
the hypoxia of neurons!
Lactic acidosis...
Death is the collective music of infinite changes in states!
Ah, then comes irreversible death.
So you're saying death is an experiment?
Science, in its final form, is God and death.
Both exist and cannot be overcome by science.
That is why we are drawn to them.
So,
what color is your blood?
See for yourself.
If we can't remove the bombs, these people will die.
But can I do this?
Hey!
Don't go that way! There's a bomb!
Please go back to the central car.
There's a bomb in the rear car.
Um, you...
Your duty is to protect the bomb at any cost.
You're...
You're the one I saw.
Use your ability, Demon Snow,
to kill anyone who interferes.
What?
Port Mafia
Assassin
Izumi Kyouka
Port Mafia
Assassin
Izumi Kyouka
Ability:
Demon Snow
Shred your enemies, Demon Snow.
Sh... She's too strong!
Wh-Why?
Why would a girl like you...
My name is Kyouka,
an orphan like you.
I like bunny rabbits and tofu.
I hate dogs and lightning.
After the Port Mafia took me in,
I killed 35 people in six months.
Protect the bomb,
and kill anyone who interferes.
The Agency isn't as formidable as I've heard.
Oh, well.
So you're about to die, but tell me this before you do:
What does it mean to die?
What did you say?
Oh, it's just scholarly interest.
I'm an avid researcher, you see.
All the reasons for human death,
including hypoxia of neurons in the brain and telomere degradation,
are simple reversible
processes in laboratory settings.
Yet, why is death irreversible?
Why must all humans die?
You don't even know why?
So the Mafia isn't so formidable, after all.
You claim that someone who's a meddling private eye
would know something that I, a follower of science, do not?
Sure I would.
The reason for that is simple.
You're just an idiot.
Thank you for your precious opinion.
I think you would know this, being well-read and all,
but even after the body dies from blood loss,
the brain and your consciousness can survive for eight hours.
Afterwards, I'll ask your corpse this:
"You're dead now. How do you feel?"
Well, take your time.
It's impossible.
I can't win.
Will I die here?
Are people going to die again because of me?
Just because they boarded the same train as me?
Just for that simple reason, they'll all die.
That is your karma, weretiger.
You cause harm to everyone around you, just by existing.
Get out, you failure!
The world would be a better place if you'd just die in a ditch somewhere!
We don't need worthless louts!
Why are you alive?
You accomplish nothing,
and cause inconvenience and
misfortune for everyone around you.
Those who can save no one do not deserve to live.
Just then, an idea popped into my head.
It was a stupid idea.
But I couldn't shake it off.
If I...
If I could save them,
the passengers here...
If I could return them safe and sound to their homes,
wouldn't that mean
that I...
Wouldn't that mean it's okay for me to live?
Stay away.
Sorry.
I can't do this anymore!
She's too fast.
I guess I can't do this, after all.
If only I could use my ability...
All right.
I wonder if she's nice and cooked all the way through now.
Let's see.
Hmm, that was underwhelming.
I was hoping you'd go flying a bit farther.
H-How?
That little sparkler wouldn't kill me.
Which side did I punch you on just now?
I-I-If I had to choose, maybe this side?
Impossible!
You were just on the brink of death before!
I may not look like it, but I am a doctor.
I've seen at least a hundred times
more deaths than you.
What's death, you ask?
Let me tell you.
Death is the loss of life.
No matter how hard we doctors try,
our patients' lives just slip through our fingers.
Death, the ultimate form of science?
Bullshit!
I'll kill anyone who doesn't value life!
I... I remember now.
You're the Armed Detective Agency's physician,
Yosano Akiko.
My ability, Thou Shalt Not Die,
can cure any wounds.
Even my own wounds, as you can see.
But the necessary conditions are harsh.
It can only cure lethal injuries.
What an inconvenient ability.
If I want to cure moderate injuries,
I have to half kill my patients first.
Oh?
You're hurt, aren't you, boy?
Would you like me to treat you?
This is
finished.
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
Where's the bomb?
The last victims were a family of three,
a father, a mother, and a boy.
Demon Snow slit their throats.
What have you done?!
Who are you?
I can't feel any emotion in your words, nor even in you.
You're like a murder machine.
If you feel anything, you must put it into words.
Otherwise, a fool like me won't understand.
Do you really want to go through with this?!
This is the conductor's office.
Atsushi!
You still breathing?
Dr. Yosano?
According to this frail-ass bomber here,
your bomb has a remote detonator.
If you make one mistake trying to defuse it,
it'll explode in a matter of seconds.
You must press the detonator's stop button to defuse it.
The Mafia agent there should have it.
Do you have it?
Give it to me.
What?!
You pressed the button, Kyouka?
Defusing the bomb is unnecessary.
Die along with the passengers
and show the pathetic masses that the Port Mafia should be feared.
Take the bomb off!
How much time do we have left?!
There's no time!
What?
I am a fool, after all.
I only realized once her slender arms pushed me,
that her ability is always activated by a voice from her cell phone.
She's unable to control her own ability.
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
I don't want to kill anyone else!
Atsushi!
Um...
No matter how powerful it may be, a pawn is just a pawn.
What about you?
Are you a pawn or the master?
Or are you a pawn who is waiting to be crushed?
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
She didn't murder by her own free will.
Gifts don't necessarily bring happiness to their wielders.
I know that better than anyone!
But if I hand her over to the police,
she'll be put to death for sure.
Where are you taking me?
That's... um...
Oh, let's go on a date, for starters.
Huh?
A date with you?
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 9:
The Beauty Is Quiet Like a Stone Statue.
Episode 9
The Beauty is Quiet Like a Stone Statue
Boiled tofu is delicious.