Beauty has been hit by the Hair Loss Beam,
and she will lose all her hair in 10 hours!
Bo-bobo and friends broke into C-block base to find the medicine!
The Jet Black Room?
Dammit, where's the medicine?
I think it's on the top floor,
which is right after this one.
Can my hair hold out?
We don't have much time left. Let's hurry.
Glad you've come, thou angels
that have lost thy wings.
Let us begin the feast of our souls!
The man that lay in wait for Bo-bobo
did not match those pretentious phrases.
Not in the slightest...
He looked weird in every aspect, but you kinda want to know about him, don't you?
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Hey, hey, his face...
Beauty
It's soft-serve ice cream!
It's strawberry soft-serve ice cream!
No, there's no mistake. His face...
It's soft-serve ice cream, I said!
Strawberry, I said!
Beauty wished that it was.
Don Patch
You really think that you could settle it by saying...
IT'S SOFT-SERVE ICE CREAM!?
BUT IT REALLY IS!!!
Releasing your Soul: That means, Piropiropiropiro... Pirocchi!
Softon
My name is Softon. I run an ice-cream store.
You're really soft-serve ice cream?
Oh please! You should've said that sooner!
This is embarrassing! If there's a hole anywhere, I wanna get inside!
Get in.
Excuse me...
Now that the man's said it himself, forgive me.
Sure...
And to make up...
Start the mixer!
STEAMY
Go ahead and eat!
Here. Have some ice cream.
It's nice and fresh.
No thanks.
But it's fresh...
If that's ice cream, how come
there's steam coming out of it?
You're always like that! You're always so picky!
Would it hurt to eat me?
Would it hurt to try me out?
I'm sorry. Please eat it.
No.
Then I'll eat it.
Really?
LI
Lick.
CK
It tastes like shit!
Thought so.
Is this what you after?
It's the antidote to the Hair Loss Beam.
Hair-Gro
Alpha
Hair Loss Beam Antidote
Bo-bobo! It's the medicine!
Why? Aren't you a Hair Hunter?
I couldn't neglect you.
Because you and I have the same smell.
Same... Smell...
That 's just too much!!
No way!!!
Is that true?
It seems this medicine is the real deal.
Don't worry, Beauty.
Don Patch, you want some?
No thanks.
Now I can focus on our duel.
I've always wished...
to fight you!
I see. Ya wanted to fight my client Bo-bobo?
Ah sure. Ya helped us out. I guess we owe ya one.
Gimme three and you got a deal, capisce?
Yay! I got three candies!
You're no ordinary guy.
You also have no openings.
Looks like I'm gonna get a good fight!
Looks like it'll be an awesome fight!
Bo-bobo...
Here goes! Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Pursuit Fist!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Flow of Morocco.
Double!
Before the Fist of Babylon, all "exists"...
and is "naught"!
He stopped them!
What is the Fist of Babylon?
The Fist of Babylon?
Bo-bobo Instruction Manual (Vol. 1)
What is it?
What is the Fist of Babylon?
Uh...
Did you find anything? Tell me!
What is the Fist of Babylon?
It's...
It's what? What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
Tell me! I know you know what it is!
Tell me!!!
Bo-bobo...
I'll start this time.
I'll have you experience
my sorrowful Fist of Babylon!
Here I go!
I'll finish this in one blow!
Hello. My name is Square Jr.
Square Jr.
Ba
Babylon!
by
lon!
Bo-bobo!
Now, confess all in the name of Babylon!
I'm sorry. I lied.
I'm...
Triangle Jr.
I was born and raised a triangle.
But my sister's a square! My sister...
She's a perfect square!
Trust me!
Please believe me!!
Don't be hasty.
I am not the one to judge.
It is the God of Babylon.
God of Babylon
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
Your bliss shall never come.
It's gone!
What was that?
Hey, hey.
From now on,
we'll be his lovers!
What the hell?
Bo-bobo!
Oh! Is Contestant Bo-bobo down?
This is the Judgment of Babylon.
Then it's time for me to show you...
The deep secrets of the Fist of the Nose Hair.
What?
Va
rie
ty
Show!!
Today's Recommended Program!
Now it's time to judge your fashion!
Impossible! He's using my moves!
But I am not going to be the one judging you.
Don Patch will be!
Why is he going through this?
Let me down! I'll sue you!
Better be quick or I'll drop you!
Okay! I got it! I'll do it, okay? I'll do it!
Fashion Judgment Start!
Variety! Scrambobo
Our next segment is our most popular part of this program,
Miss Patchmi's Harsh Fashion Judgment!
Well then, Miss Patchmi, be as rough as you please.
Miss Patchmi's Harsh Fashion Judgment
Let's start with the feet.
These boots are this year's newest model,
and they're popular and suave.
And these denim jeans look like they're vintage,
but this man has good enough thighs that they fit well with the shoes.
It's striking.
Now the main problem is the jacket.
Souvenir jackets are so out of date! It looks silly!
But you know, the ice cream ornaments stitched on both breasts
does give it a bit of a fresh return.
This man's coordinated
a simple style without accessories,
but a light wool hat
might help accentuate it a bit.
That's all for my harsh fashion judgment!
Good work.
What a nice warm bath.
Does this man dare to mock Babylon?
Despicable.
You're open!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bad Hair Treatment Team Emergency Action!
by Bo-bobo!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
The Lost Red Treasure!
by Softon!
Bo-bobo!
Roaming and mastering the
bounds of light and shadow...
is the secret to the Fist of Babylon!
It can't be! Bo-bobo's
Fist of the Nose Hair didn't work!
I'll show you the true Fist of the Nose Hair!
It's gone! This medicine actually works!
You have some, Don Patch!
Invincible Fortress Zygas
Zygas
Siege!!!
I... Is this...
Is this the Invincible Fortress Zygas!?
We're too late!
King Nose Hair
Nothing to report.
Looks like rain.
King Nose Hair? But why?
You okay, little miss?
What is this huge nose hair?
It's in the way.
Oh, what an unexpected twist!
No! No! No!
So I will fulfill my dream before I die.
And that dream is... it is...
To go cycling!
Let's go!
Yahoo!
Didn't you go cycling?
More importantly, Bo-bobo's in danger!
Bo-bobo!
He's got a crew cut!!!
Here's a souvenir from my cycling trip.
Kyoto
Pennant
No thanks.
It's a pennant! A pennant!
Out of my face!
I'll show you the true Fist of the Nose Hair!
How interesting. I'd like to see it for myself.
Fist of the Nose Hair Top-Secret Technique:
Holy
Nose
Hair
Dom
ain
Holy Nose Hair Domain
Bo-bobo World!
B   O   -   B   O   B   O       W   O   R   L   D
Holy Nose
Hair Domain
B   O   -   B   O   B   O       W   O   R   L   D
Holy Nose
Hair Domain
B   O   -   B   O   B   O
W   O   R   L   D
What's going on?
What is this?
This is Nose Hair Space. It's a world I created.
Nose Hair Space
Nose Hair Space?
Those who enter this world can release their souls.
By doing this,
They can use the power hidden deep within their soul.
On the contrary, if they don't release their soul...
their minds will break and will die as a result!
Release their souls? What does that mean?
Jabaccha Galbarza!
Is this... releasing his soul?
Soul Release In Progress
Temna! Gor! Ralgacha!
Chitaani!
Hey, what's wrong?
Chitaani! Chitaani!
Natto—!
Natto—! Natto—!
Hurry! Hurry and put some natto on my rice! Put it on! Put it on and eat it!
Oh, natto! I guess not!
Hold on!
Why? Why are you a catfish? Why are you a catfish?
IT'S AN EEL—!
That happens all the time. That happens all the time.
This one's for the rice!
Fist of the Pennant!
Hey guys! It's time for the festival!
Here goes!
Bo-bobo Marching Song!
It sure feels like summer!
Yes!
Take a bite out of summer
Natsu wo maru kajiri
It's almost New Year's Eve
Mou sugu toshikoshi da
But it's summer!
Hold on tight, Hold on tight,
Sugari tsuke Sugari tsuke
Hold on tight to the quick end of the rainy season
Hayai tsuyu ake Sugari tsuke
Chululilala, Chululilala
Chululilala Chululilala
It's the school entrance ceremony for first grade
Nyuugakushiki dayo Ichinensei
Now it's spring!?
Purukogi-zui, Purukogi-zui
Purukogi zui Purukogi zui
When summer comes, it's the new year!
Natsu ga kurya Oshougatsu
Why?
Come, come, come at the same time
Koiyo Koiyo Issho ni Koiyo
Lantern Festival and New Year's, Lantern Festival and New Year's
Bon to Shougatsu Bon to Shougatsu
Come at the same time
Issho ni Koiyo
Lantern Festival and New Year's, Lantern Festival and New Year's,
Bon to Shougatsu Bon to Shougatsu
Lantern Festival and New Year's, Lantern Festival and New Year's
Come on!!!
Peep, peep, peep, peep!
But the Lantern Festival and New Year's...
don't come at the same time.
Look over here!
I'm a puzzle! Let's play!
It's a puzzle! A puzzle!
Look over here!
It's Knock Down the Don Patch! Now knock me down!
Bring it! Bring it!
I got it! Heave ho!
Look over here!
Can you tell where I'm standing?
Stab the right spot!
Where's the right spot?
You're right!
Hi-yah!
Police inspector! Police inspector!
Yes?
Pirocchi!
Piropiropiropiropiropiropiropiropiropiropiropiro...
Piro—!
Gadabon!
Somebody stop these three idiots right now!
What a fearsome technique.
Bo-bobo World...
It's working.
It really is a fearsome technique.
Against someone like me...
this world truly is Hell!
It's just as I suspected.
You would not release your soul.
If you release your soul, you would be showing your true self.
But there's a reason you don't want to show it.
A reason?
You are hiding something from us.
We're back to the real world.
You can't fight any more like that.
Our fight is on hold.
We don't need a rematch.
The fight's not over yet!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo!
Sashimi Farm!
I held back on him. Our fight's on hold.
It was a good fight.
Alright. I'm gonna go crush this base!
Let's do whatever the hell we want!
Thanks for the medicine!
C-block Base
5th Room: The Room of the Tornado
So Softon's been beaten...
Wind
It's finally my time to shine!
We're finally at the top floor!
Now that I think about it, it was a tough fight.
It didn't look like that!
I'm always serious.
That's what we call craziness!
But we're not worthless!
See, there's a boy chasing us!
Are you saying we're comedians?
Is someone there?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Mystery Kid's Identity and the
Fist of the Fart! Eat your asparagus!
Oh, you're...