My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people in 6 months.
Infirmary
My name is Kyouka.
I've killed 35 people.
I don't want to kill anyone else!
You've brought trouble back with you again.
She's a lost cause.
That girl's an infamous assassin.
She fools targets with her young appearance to lower their guard,
then decimates entire organizations.
She accomplished too much, too quickly.
It was only a matter of time before she was caught.
But,
whoever is taking advantage of her ability is the one to blame.
Gifts don't necessarily bring happiness to their wielders.
You know that better than most.
She's awake.
Do you think we can question her?
Yeah, no problem.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
Are you all right?
Um, this is the infirmary at the Agency.
How do you feel?
You remember me, right?
Girl, tell us who was behind this.
The Port Mafia forces are just like a snake.
Unless you cut off its head, it will persist.
Answer me.
Who's your superior?
K-Kunikida-san.
Tachibanadou's boiled tofu.
Boiled tofu?
It's really good.
You want us to get you some?
I'll talk after you do.
Oh.
Sure, that's easy enough.
Hey, you...
What?
Seconds!
Kunikida-san...
I'm not paying.
What would you like to order, sir?
Just water, please.
Well?
When my parents died and I became an orphan,
the Port Mafia took me in.
They wanted my ability, Demon Snow.
Demon Snow only follows orders given through a phone.
This is the cell phone.
The battery has been removed.
So the Port Mafia took advantage of your ability
and transformed you into a deadly assassin.
Why didn't you just toss the cell phone away?
If I put up any resistance, I would be dead.
Besides,
even if I'd left the Port Mafia, there would be nowhere else to go.
Who controlled Demon Snow through that phone?
A man named Akutagawa.
I see.
I'll head back to the Agency to report.
Brat.
Turn the girl over to the military police.
But if I do that...
With a kill count of 35,
she'll be sentenced to death.
Even if she went back to the Port Mafia,
she'd be killed as a traitor.
But...
What, are you going to save her?
A fugitive wanted for execution,
and a traitor to the Port Mafia.
Do you have the resolve to shoulder full responsibility of her?
That's...
Brat.
I'm not telling you to reject empathy for someone who's fallen into misfortune.
But misfortune of her sort is plentiful in our world.
You only have room for one on your boat.
If you try to save someone you can't save,
you'll both end up sinking.
But,
if that's true,
why did Dazai-san help me?
Episode 9
The Beauty Is Quiet
Like a Stone Statue
Episode 9
The Beauty Is Quiet
Like a Stone Statue
You can't do a double suicide alone...
But, but you can do it with two...
Oh, you were here?
I believe you know what manner of fate awaits those who are bound here.
This brings back memories.
I remember when you were a rookie.
You have committed grave sins.
You suddenly abandoned your mission,
vanished,
only to reappear as an enemy to the Port Mafia.
It's unbelievable, coming from a former executive.
And from your former superior?
Not even you are invincible.
As long as I don't use my ability,
I can hurt you.
I can kill you any time I want.
I see.
You've ascended the ranks.
I'll say this to you now,
but it was a challenge to train you.
You were a slow learner,
and you always disobeyed instructions.
Not to mention that useless ability of yours.
Your fake bravado will only last for a few more days.
In that time, we will obliterate the Agency
and seize the weretiger.
Your execution will then follow.
Look forward to the news of your organization
and your subordinate's demise
with clenched fists and teeth.
I wonder if you'll actually manage that.
My new subordinate is far superior to you.
I ate too much.
Y-You did.
I'm glad I had enough money.
You only have room for one on your boat.
If you try to save someone you can't save,
you'll both end up sinking.
Take her to a military police outpost.
Don't let her figure out what you're doing.
If we go there, she'll be
sentenced to death.
Let's go.
Go where?
Where are we going?
Huh?
Where are you taking me?
Wh-Where?
Well, so...
Um...
Wherever you want to go, of course.
Don't you have somewhere you want to check out?
You know, a place a girl your age would like to visit.
For example...
A date spot! Maybe?
S-See, I have the rest of the day off.
I doubt you've had many
opportunities to have fun outside.
A date?
Yeah.
A date with you?
Huh?
Oh! Um!
I didn't mean anything by it.
Um...
Er...
Let's go.
Oh.
Okay.
Whoa!
What a humongous baseball field!
This is Yokohama Stadium.
Oh, so this is it?
I've seen it on the map.
This is the Yokohama Port Opening Memorial Hall.
Huh.
Kanagawa Prefectural Museum of Cultural History.
Yokohama Customs Headquarters.
Huh.
You know everything, don't you?
I have the map and building layout memorized.
Oh, I know this one.
It's the Yokohama Red Brick Warehouse, isn't it?
The crêpe place here is great.
Let me have a bite!
Yum, delicious!
Oh yeah, it's popular.
Naomi-san said they make great crêpes.
It wasn't on the map.
I want to try one.
What?!
B-But you just ate so much boiled tofu.
There's always room.
I got the plushie I wanted.
There's just one more place I want to go to.
Okay, okay.
She's being really proactive.
Here.
I've had more than enough fun.
And it should've just ended
with the boiled tofu.
But if you're caught, you'll...
I'll probably be executed.
I've killed 35 people.
It's a sin that I'm still alive after that.
Besides, even if I return to the Port Mafia, I'll be executed.
Executed?
We wouldn't execute you.
You've fulfilled your mission.
Hey!
What're you—
"I got the plushie I wanted."
We implanted a transmitter into your body.
We know everywhere you go, and everything you do.
We're going home.
Where am I?
Atsushi-kun has been abducted.
The brat?
Now, of all times?
Yes.
The Agency's in a total uproar due to a recent ministry staff escort job.
We don't have enough hands on deck to look for him.
Do we know where he is?
Oh, yes.
Based on eyewitness statements,
he was assaulted on the street in broad daylight
and shoved into a truck.
Their destination remains unknown.
That's not good.
They have many dedicated smuggling routes.
Transporting an individual stealthily
would be child's play for them.
We must help him somehow, or he'll...
Help him? Why?
He was abducted because he's a weretiger and they want the reward, right?
So, it's not personal.
We're not his foster home.
He didn't join us looking for protection, either.
But Atsushi-kun is one of ours.
No.
Rampo-san is right.
We shouldn't be the ones to take action.
Kunikida-san...
Shouldn't we inform the police?
Atsushi is wanted as a designated major threat.
If his status with us becomes known,
the Agency will take a hit.
Um...
It sounded like you wouldn't make a decision in a million years
if you kept to your shoulds and coulds,
so I called him!
President!
I am so sorry.
As soon as our work is done,
I'll gather intel with Tanizaki, and—
That won't be necessary.
Listen up, all of you.
Our newest member has been abducted.
Everyone work on finding him.
I order the current task suspended
until he has been safely returned to us.
Suspended?
But what about the escort job?
I'll contact the client.
Don't worry.
They owe me enough that I can afford to let a minor official wait.
President, are you sure about this?
About what, Rampo?
Well, if you think about the rationale behind it—
One of our own is in danger.
We must help him.
What greater rationale do we need in this world?
Kunikida.
Sir.
Bring him back to us within three hours.
Understood!
If I predicted correctly, by now they should be...
It's about time.
Plotting as usual?
That voice...
Port Mafia
Executive
Nakahara
Chuuya
Port Mafia
Executive
Nakahara
Chuuya
This is nice.
This is a great view.
Ability:
For The
Tainted Sorrow
Ability:
For The
Tainted Sorrow
It rivals even a masterpiece
worth tens of billions.
Wouldn't you agree, Dazai?
The worst.
This is just the worst.
I love your reaction.
It makes me want to strangle you.
You haven't changed one bit, Chuuya.
Oh?!
What are you saying?!
I've always wondered about this,
but where do you get your embarrassing hats?
Say what you want, vagabond!
I bet you're still going on and on about suicide despite your age, aren't you?
Yeah.
At least pretend to deny that.
But now, you're just a sad little prisoner.
It's enough to make you cry, eh, Dazai?
No.
It's actually a little too convenient.
You may be able to deceive that apprentice, Akutagawa,
but not me.
After all, I'm your old partner.
What's your play?
Just what it looks like.
Get caught, and wait to be executed.
There's no way the Dazai I know would be caught through misfortune or sloppiness.
If you were that foolish,
I would've killed you long ago.
You're overthinking this.
Besides, why did you come here in the first place?
To harass you.
You toyed with me all you wanted back then.
But,
there's usually payback for it ten times over later.
I don't know what you're planning,
but fight me, Dazai.
I'll crush you right along with your schemes.
Chuuya.
Yeah?
So you could've escaped at any time?
You, stop my plans?
You must be joking.
I'm liking this turn of events!
Analyze the city's security camera footage!
Everything from the past six hours!
Oh, right!
Where's the Chamber of Commerce ledger?
Here.
Oh, this won't do.
This doesn't have any comic strips.
Kenji-kun!
Yes?
Can you look into whether there are any good homicide cases nearby?
Sure,
but the president won't be happy with you later.
Never mind, then.
Here!
This photo was provided by one of the
tourists who witnessed the abduction.
You can find trucks like that anywhere.
Yes.
The license plate was fake, as well.
But there are few places in Yokohama
that can work on this kind of vehicle.
After Kenji went around to all the repair shops we could think of,
they were more than happy to tell us more.
The truck's owned by Karma Transit.
They're mules who started off in the smuggling business.
So they can tell us where he was taken.
Yes.
They're the only ones outside of the Port Mafia
who might know anything about the abduction.
Tanizaki is on standby at the site.
He can go in at any time.
Understood.
I'll infiltrate the building now.
Status update.
It's quiet, like the bottom of a lake.
There are no signs of anyone.
No way!
We've been had.
They were one step ahead of us!
Hey, what's the matter?
They were silenced.
They're all dead.
It's Akutagawa.
What are we going to do?
Our only lead just went up in smoke.
Rampo.
It's your turn.
Do I have to?
Rampo-san!
Please, just this once!
Rampo, if you manage to bring the rookie back safe and sound...
Will I get a special bonus?
A promotion?
There's no need. After all...
I'll give you praise.
W-Well, if you're going that far, I guess I don't have a choice!
All right!
Ability: Ultra-Deduction!
Hmm, I see.
Atsushi-kun's location is
here!
The vessel's traveling at 20 knots towards the open sea.
He's still alive... at least for now.
The sea...
They're shipping him overseas, then.
That's not good.
Once he's out of the country,
we can't touch him.
Kunikida,
use this.
It's the Agency's high-speed vessel docked at port.
Bring him back, no matter what.
Understood.
I will now go rescue Nakajima Atsushi!
Don't die, brat.
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
Do you know what it's
like to be at rock-bottom?
It is an infinite darkness
where no light shines.
Weretiger, teach her what it's like.
To assist none,
to rely on none,
and to live in hiding, trembling like a worm.
This ends now, Akutagawa.
I can't forgive you for this!
Neither can I!
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 10:
Episode 10
Rashomon and the Tiger
Rashomon and the Tiger.