The C-block base...
The Jet Black Room
The fourth Hell...
The man from this fourth Hell
was Softon.
Softon
But who exactly is Softon?
That must never be known.
Never!
I'm pretty sure that's for your sake.
Through a violent fight
that broke out in Bo-bobo World,
Softon conceded to Bo-bobo.
Today's Recommended Program!
But now...
The fifth Hell was closing in on Bo-bobo!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
StitchOtaku626
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
StitchOtaku626
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Mystery Kid
"The Mystery Kid's Identity and the
Fist of the Fart! Eat your asparagus!"
's
Identity
and
the Fist of the Fart!
asparagus!
Eat your
C-block Base
C-block Base...
The three that headed towards the top floor...
did whatever the hell they wanted.
Let's hurry upwards!
That must be the top floor!
So this is the last door.
Alright! Let's smash this base!
With my Bo-bobo Custom Super Patch Car!
Bo-bobo Custom Super Patch Car
A remote-control car?
This Bo-bobo Custom Super Patch Car...
is a special machine equipped
with a Bo-bobo chassis.
Bo-bobo chassis?
I'm counting on you,
Bo-bobo Custom Super Patch Car!
Leave it to me! I'll take out
them C-block Hair Hunters!
Ready...
Go!
Go! Don't slow down!
Bo-bobo Custom Super Patch Car!
Ow!
What am I gonna do?
I broke Ta-kun's remote control car!
Don't ya worry.
Yer auntie will go with ya to make up for it.
That'll be fine, won't it?
Hey, hey, why're ya still cryin'?
Well then, I'm going.
But Auntie...
It's fine.
I understand.
You said we'd apologize together.
C-block Captain Geha the Tornado
So glad you've come, Bo-bobo.
You've somehow managed
to get all the way up here,
but that was all down to luck.
But you won't be so lucky now!
Sesame Salt
Sesame Salt! Sesame Salt! Sesame Salt!
Sesame! Sesame! Sesame! Sesame!
Sesame Salt
Why sesame salt!?
Sesame Salt!
Sesame! Sesame! Sesame! Sesame!
T-The sesame salt... is working?
Why does this have to happen to me?
Is he a slug?
Sesame! Sesame!
Cut it out!
Hey, Bo-bobo!
I told you sesame salt won't cut it!
Hammerspawn Shampoo
He who rules the shampoo, rules Japan!
I am the C-block Captain...
Shampoo! Shampoo!
This shampoo will make you all nice and clean.
Okay, I'll rinse it off for you.
Ah! It's clean now!
GEHA'S REVIVED!
What?
Vacuum Wind Cutter!
Vacuum Wind Cutter
Don Patch!
How was it?
How was my Vacuum Wind Cutter?
I ain't cut.
No, you are.
You are!
Giraffe
She's right! You are!
You get lost! I ain't cut!
Yeah you are!
I told you, I ain't cut!
Ya really look like you've been cut!
Shut up!
It's your turn now, Bo-bobo!
What?
If ya thought I couldn't shrink, yer a fool.
Who do ya take us giraffes for!?
Boy Giraffe
Ya got it, fool?
Girl Giraffe
Ya heard the man, fool!
Hey, Beauty...
You know, I've been thinking lately...
About what?
Don't you think I haven't been getting enough screentime these days?
You've gotten a lot!
I'm gonna go file a complaint.
A complaint? Where?
Bo-bobo Consultation Office
Bo-bobo Consultation Office?
Excuse me!
I have something I need to discuss...
I wanna be in the show!
Please let me be in the show!
The Weird Creature that
isn't in the Show
I wanna be in the show! I wanna be in the show!
W-What is this thing!?
Please!
Let me be in the show!
I can tell...
It's a character that hasn't been in "Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo"...
But why?
Look at me! Please let me in the show!
And why is Bo-bobo spaced out
and looking at the ceiling?
Why? Why!?
I wanna... I wanna be in the show!
What's going on!?
I wanna be in the show!
Bo-bobo Consultation Office
They're putting up more of a fight than I thought they would!
Shit! Now that it's come to this, it's time to play my last card!
Look out, Bo-bobo!
The Tornado's...
"Powerful Wind Twister Slash" !!!
"Powerful Wind Twister Slash"!!!
I WANNA BE IN THE SHOW!!!
Bo-bobo!
Heian the capital of yore, was founded in 794...
Heian 794
Let's see...
Kamakura Bakufu 1192
The Kamakura Bakufu started in 1192...
TL Note: 'Bakufu' is also known as 'Shogunate' in English
T-The Kamakura Bakufu...?
I wish I knew the root of two...
So now we strive to know the root of five...
Are you sure there's time to play around? We've been swallowed up...
by the Maelstrom of the Entrance Exam Hell!
Entrance Exams...?
I will now pass out the exam questions!
The Teacher In the Storm
There is only one correct paper!
Eh... whoever...
Examinee 1
Got it!
Examinee 2
Oh, no. It's the wrong one.
I got the wrong one, too.
Have I got it?
Examinee 3
Yes! It's the right one!
Correct
- Congratulations!
- Do your best for our sake too!
Now for the examinee's crucial item!
Who's gonna get it?
A magnifying glass?
Huh? This paper...
Correct
The writing's so small that I can't read the questions!
I get it! If I have that...
Alright... C'mon...
Got it!
"He who runs after two hares will catch neither."
So this is the Entrance Exam Hell?
But I'll ride it through...
On a unicycle!
Bravo, Bravo, Entrance Exam Hell!
Bravo, Bravo, Good work, everyone!
Bravo
Bravo, Bravo, Good work!
Sine, cosine, tangent...
"At the other end of the tunnel
was the Snow Country."
Bravo
Bravo, Bravo, Good work, everyone!
"Can you send up my
breakfast right now please?"
NO ONE'S LISTENING...
I can't ride it through!
University of Tokyo
Hey, stop it!
No, don't look at me!
You're so cunning, cunning, cunning!
Cunning!
Cun-cun-cun-cun-cunning!
It's like: "Grill it and eat it!"
What? What's your problem? Ow!
Meanwhile, Beauty was...
Will they be alright?
Now that they've been hit by my
Powerful Wind Twister Slash, it's all over.
No one can ever escape it.
Bo-bobo...
Brazilian Delegate Kimura Ichiro!
Coffee
Something else came out!
Now I can turn back to normal!
No way!
Well then, I'll be off.
Heave-ho!
What's going on in there?
Let's forget about the idiots. I'll start with you!
I get to hunt a girl's hair...
The games are over!
Hand over your hair...
Gimme your hair!
Stop it!
I'm taking it!
Who are you!?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Who do you think you are?
It's him...
Mystery Boy
He always saved me
He's the guy that always saved me.
Hey, who are you?
How dare you interrupt me!
You won't get away with this! Die!
Look out!
Don't think I'm letting you go! Damn it!
What? What just happened?
Fist of the Fart Secret Technique... May!
Fist of the Fart Secret Technique
"May"
"Fist of the Fart"?
"Fist of the Fart"...?
When Geha wrote his autobiography, he wrote...
"Yeah... I've never smelled
a fart this strong before..."
What's with that!?
We got hit by your fart and ended up like this.
What're ya gonna do about it?
Is that even possible?
What's with "Is that even possible?" Eh?
Look, Bo-bobo...
Happy Birthday
"Happy Birthday"...
Hold on... It's your birthday today!?
What're ya gonna do?
It's your fault that he's having his second birthday this year!
No, wait! That's not what my
Fist of the Fart is supposed to do!
Don't you try to play innocent on me! I'm not letting you off the hook!
Take some responsibility, man!
What is it?
If ya wanna say something, then say it!
What?
Spit it out!
I can't understand if you don't say anything!
Nervous Nervous Nervous Nervous
Don't be so nervous! Spit it out!
Asparagus
I got it...
If you're going this far to say it...
Okay!
Let's start the birthday party!
Funtime Birthday Party
Birthday party?
Hey, don't just stand there! You've got to manage the birthday party!
I do?
Of course you do, dammit! You!
Y-O-U!
But why me?
"Why me?" he says.
It's obvious! It's your fault!
Now take charge of the birthday party!
No way. Get real.
What was that for?
Are you alright, Bo-bobo?
Well, what's he saying?
I have absolutely no clue.
ABSOLUTELY NO CLUE
I should've known...
For now, just eat this asparagus.
Raw!?
Raw Asparagus
By the way... You!
Apologize! Apologize to Bo-bobo! Apologize!
I get it! I get it already!
Really? Do you really get it?
Shut up! I said I get it!
I'll apologize!
Will that be enough for you?
I'm sorry.
Dumbass!
What is it now?
Apologize better! Better, you dumbass!
I get it! I get it!
Apologize from your heart!
I am sorry, Mr. Bo-bobo. Forgive me.
I have done you wrong.
But why the hell do I have to?
Look, he's apologizing to you.
You should forgive him.
You don't want to?
How immature. Isn't it fine now?
Look, Buddy's gonna apologize again.
Right?
I am sorry.
∙
∙∙
∙∙∙
∙∙∙∙
∙∙∙∙∙
∙∙∙∙∙X!
"X"!?
That's my Bo-bobo! You're so kind!
I love you!
Oh, Bo-bobo...
Oh, please!
Stop looking, you lecher!
Huh?
Don't "huh" me!
Eh?
Don't "eh" me, you idiot!
I'll report you to the police, pervert!
What?
What is it? If you got
something to say, then say it!
I can't understand you if
you don't say something!
Macaroni
I get it. If you go that far to say it...
Then I'll ask him!
By the way, who are you?
What's your name?
Hey! Are you listening to me, punk?
I'm asking you what your name is!
Say it!
Are you listening? What's your name?
What's with him...
Is there a reason he can't say it?
Can you hear me now?
Alright already!
I can hear you just fine!
Then let's hear it! Say your name!
Your name!
Heppokomaru...
TL Note: Literally means "Farting Kid"
Heppokomaru
My name is Heppokomaru.
Sweet!
Cool!
- Sweet!
- Cool!
Gimme that!
Hooray for Heppokomaru! Hooray for Heppokomaru! Hooray for Heppokomaru!
Happy Birthday
It's... my birthday!
So your name's Heppokomaru?
You saved me again.
Thank you!
It was nothing...
What?
The wall! What the hell's that?
The young boy sought strength from Bo-bobo.
And the young girl
sought kindness from Bo-bobo.
Yes, from those lovable nose hairs.
And now a new enemy has come out of the wall!
Now that they have come to the fifth Hell,
what will become of Bo-bobo and friends?
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Hey, he looks pretty tough!
Mr. Fart, feed him a round.
Yes! I'll send him flying
with my Fist of the Fart!
Stop screwing around!
Oh, Beauty's gotten mad!
You two are clowning around too much!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Save the Environment!
"Save the Environment! The password is:
Farting Toot Toot! It doesn't stink!"
The password is:
Farting Toot Toot!
It doesn't stink!
Once you smell it, there's no going back!