Speed - 20 knots
Heading towards open sea
Don't die, brat!
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
You call that a punch?!
It doesn't even count as a massage.
Your martial arts skills are
below average for the Port Mafia.
Your ability to neutralize
gifts is a nuisance,
but I don't even need to
use mine at this point.
Get up.
The party's just getting started.
You're not the Port Mafia's
top martial artist for nothing.
Whoops.
I thought my blocking arm'd get torn off.
He blocked my hit with
his arm at the last second?
He's predicting my attacks.
We've known each other for a long time.
I already know your
moves, pacing, and habits.
I wouldn't have been a proper
partner otherwise, right?
He's fast!
Then I bet you saw this coming, too!
This is how you throw a punch!
You thought you could beat me just by predicting my moves?
Tell me before you die.
Why did you let yourself get caught?
What were you waiting for here?
Heh, the silent treatment?
Fine.
I'll just have more fun torturing you.
The main reason
is Atsushi-kun.
Atsushi?
The weretiger you're all obsessed with.
I wanted to know who put the seven
billion yen price tag on his head.
You wanted to know so bad
you put your life on the line?
I'd like to say that's heartwarming,
but look where you ended up.
I guess even geniuses can
end up less than average, eh,
youngest executive in the Mafia's history?
Well, you've been deserted by lady luck.
After all, you got caught
the very day I got back
from suppressing uprisings in the West.
From my perspective, it was a stroke of luck.
What's so funny?
Let me tell you something that's good to know.
There will be a meeting between
the top five executives tomorrow.
Impossible.
That's a meeting of critical importance
that only occurs once every several years,
to determine what direction
to take as an organization.
If there were going to be one,
I would've been notified.
The reason it's happening is
a certain  letter I sent the other day to
the upper echelons of the organization.
So, I'm going to predict this now.
You're not going to kill me.
Moreover, you'll tell me where to
find information on who's paying
the weretiger bounty
before leaving this room.
And when you leave, you'll walk
and talk like a little rich girl.
What?
My predictions always come true.
I think you know that.
What can you even hope for right
A letter?
You mentioned a letter?
The letter said this:
"Should Dazai fall,
all of your secrets will come to light."
You bastard! You didn't...
So now you've caught a former
executive turned traitor.
But the package included a
letter to the upper echelons
that if I die, all of the
organization's secrets will be disclosed.
If the public prosecutor's office
gets a hold of those secrets,
all the Port Mafia executives can
be executed a hundred times over.
That's more than enough of a
threat to trigger the meeting.
The Port Mafia aren't so feeble that a threat like that would make them hesitate.
You'll die!
There will be an execution!
Probably.
But that'll be the council's decision.
If you execute me before that
decision without permission,
your unsanctioned act will be
considered an act of betrayal.
You'll be discharged or, at worst, executed.
And even if I look past all of
those factors and kill you,
you'll just be happy because
you managed to die.
So yeah, go ahead if you want.
Come on, hurry.
Come on.
Oh?
You're not going to?
"Chuuya driven out of the
organization because of me"
had a nice ring to it, too.
Don't tell me...
The main reason
is Atsushi-kun.
So your second reason was to force me
to make that impossible decision just now?
Besides, why did you
come here in the first place?
To harass you.
In actuality, you were waiting to harass me.
It's a reunion long in the making.
A surprise of this caliber is only fair.
I'll have you killed.
I'll have you killed someday, I swear.
By the way,
you're the one who broke
my chains and freed me.
If I just run away now,
you'd be suspected of aiding my escape.
You bastard!
If you do as I say,
I could make it look like someone
from the Agency came to rescue me.
Why should I believe you?!
I don't lie in these kinds of negotiations.
I think you know that.
Bastard!
What do you want?
I said it earlier.
If it's about that weretiger,
Akutagawa's leading the operation.
He should have records in the communications
storage room on the second floor.
I see.
Well, I had my guesses about that.
Oh?!
Just finish what you came here
for and get outta here, you ass.
Why, thank you.
But I have one correction:
my dream right now is to commit
double-suicide with a beautiful woman,
so being kicked to death by you wouldn't
make me happy in the slightest.
Sorry.
Uh-huh.
I'll try to find a beautiful woman
willing to kill herself next time.
Chuuya.
I had no idea you were a good person!
It's my way of saying go to hell, idiot!
Let me tell you this, Dazai.
Don't think this is the end of it!
I won't  give you a second chance!
No, wrong!
Don't you think you're forgetting something?
Don't-you-think-you're-forgetting-something?
I won't  give you a second chance!
N-No second ch-chance.
You're supposed to laugh!
Huh?
Did you... come to rescue me?
I struck to kill,
but it seems the tiger's healing power
is in effect, if in incomplete form.
Where am I?
Am I at sea?
You're on a smuggling ship that
carries weapons and munitions,
though it's been reserved
solely for you today.
Enjoy your last voyage for the next
few hours before we hand you over.
There's no point, I can't beat him.
I'll have to find an opening
and make a run for it.
The weak will die.
Die, and make way for others.
Why does he have so much hatred for me?
Did you find yourself moved
by being in the outside world,
Kyouka?
Let him go.
Do you know what it's
like to be at the nadir?
There is only the mire,
a foul stench, and self-pity.
At times, someone will look
in from an opening far above,
but no one will notice you.
With every breath, your
wretchedness burns your lungs.
That's what's waiting for
you out there, Kyouka.
Demon Snow is slaughter made flesh.
Yet you think you can live a normal
life outside of the Port Mafia?
Weretiger, teach her what it's like.
To help no one,
to be counted on by no one,
and to live in hiding,
trembling like a worm.
Continue killing, Kyouka,
as the Port Mafia's assassin.
If not, stop breathing.
Worthless human beings don't
have the right to breathe.
You may be right,
but
the crpes were delicious.
Where are you, brat?!
Brat!
Kunikida-san?
So the Agency's found us already?
Run while you still can.
This ship isn't going to
reach the meeting spot.
Where else is it going?
The nadir.
Hey!
Run!
Weretiger!
You set explosives in the armory?
You're trying to die, aren't you?
Is that man worth saving
at the cost of your life?
Brat!
Over here, brat!
I can't come any closer
with those explosions!
Jump!
I'm making it out alive.
I'm safe now.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
The ship's going to sink!
You idiot!
How much more trouble are you
going to cause the Agency?
Everyone's working unpaid right now!
What about her?
Let that girl go!
Not all innocent people can be saved.
I've failed many times, too!
That's the kind of city we're in,
and the job we have!
She can't be saved?
That's right.
We're not heroes.
I've wished so many times that we were.
But we're not!
Brat!
She...
She said the crpe she
had with me tasted great.
She was told worthless human
beings have no right to breathe,
and she thought maybe that was true.
I don't think so.
Because Dazai-san... the Agency...
didn't give up on me!
I'm going!
Hey!
Run!
Run, Atsushi!
Kyouka, is this the path you've chosen?
Out of appreciation for your hard work thus far,
I'll lay you to rest.
Die.
Face me, Akutagawa!
Episode 10
Rashoumon
and the Tiger
It now seems curious to me,
but I felt things between us
would end up like this eventually.
You'll miss out on the bounty.
Don't worry.
I had no intentions of handing
you over to them alive.
I can't forgive you.
The same goes for me.
Rashoumon!
It's the same devoured space
that stopped bullets before.
As long as it's there,
my attacks can't get through.
How futile.
Is this the best you can do, weretiger?
Slow torture is not one of my hobbies.
If you must, curse your own weakness.
You are a weakling who deluded
himself into thinking he was strong
for having joined an armed
organization like the Agency.
Your membership was merely
due to coincidence and luck.
You're quite the talker today.
I don't recall ever
identifying myself as a mute.
It's just like you say.
I am weak.
But I do have one advantage.
And what's that?
I can defeat you!
You reversed your tiger paws
to free your arms?!
I thought so.
It takes time to activate
the devoured space barrier.
I'll just use my speed
to push my attacks, then!
What?!
I don't have the time to play
along with childish fistfight
Sorry, but I'll just observe
your efforts from up here!
Having this distance between
us works to his advantage.
I have to close the gap somehow.
Shit!
There's less than five minutes left
before the ship is completely submerged.
He leapt using a fragment
blown from the explosion?
Your ability's slow to activate.
The enemy won't wait for you to get up.
Now, get up.
Retaliate with your ability.
That's not enough to
survive in the Port Mafia!
Or perhaps you want to return to
being a stray dog in the slums?
Good.
Again.
I have to take her to
Kunikida-san before the ship sinks!
Why?
Why is it you?!
Your ability is only newly
learned, a crude addition.
It's full of flaws, and you're not using it right!
And yet,
why is it you?!
There it is again.
His hatred for me.
Where does such hatred come from?
I wonder if you can.
My new subordinate is much better than you.
I won't let him say that.
I won't let him say such things ever again!
Rashoumon!
Higanzakura!
Even if I've defeated him..
Wait.
Why?
My attack was a direct hit.
He can't possibly move.
You're so powerful.
Why'd you have to use her?
I didn't use her.
Demon Snow is an ability to kill.
Only when killing someone does
Kyouka's existence have meaning.
If she does not kill, she is worthless.
I merely gave her value.
To make her worthy to live.
That's the thing.
You don't get to decide whether
someone is worthy of being alive!
Why couldn't you tell
her something different?
People need to be told they're worthy
of being alive by someone else
or they can't go on.
Why can't you understand
such a simple thing?!
He tore Rashoumon apart?
The tiger's ultra-regeneration!
I can't let him get close!
I'll take him out at this distance!
Rashoumon!
Sawarabi!
Akutagawa!
Rashoumon!
Goku Mon
Agito!
Just fall.
The tiger's tail
Devoured Space!
My new subordinate is
much better than you.
You big idiot.
Well done.
So,
who in the world wanted to spend
seven billion to buy a tiger?
They're...
It's time.
It seems the bounty approach has failed.
Leader
of
The Guild,
A
Gifted
Organization
Francis F.
Leader
of
The Guild,
A
Gifted
Organization
Francis F.
The island mafia are such a half-baked lot.
Ability:
The Great Gatsby
The Promised Land will be
The Guild's for certain.
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
A challenging task even the police passed on
has come to our Agency.
Atsushi, give it a try.
Okay, I'll do my best!
What?
Kenji's the one going to
the job site with Atsushi?
I can't believe we already have a lead!
Kenji-kun, you're amazing!
Episode 11
...............................................................
l
An Unsuitable Profession for Her
An Ecstatic Detective Agency
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 11:
First, An Unsuitable Profession for Her.
Second, An Ecstatic Detective Agency.
Shit...
It's the best and worst team ever.