Bo-bobo and company
have finally arrived at C-block Base.
Waiting for them was Geha the Tornado,
who trapped them in the harsh
Maelstrom of Entrance Exam Hell.
However, the one who saved the day,
was that kid we've kept a mystery for so long, Master of the Fist of the Fart,
Heppokomaru!
And so, while Don Patch was celebrating
"Happy Birthday"
Bo-bobo's second birthday this year...
Someone came through the wall.
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
StitchOtaku626
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
StitchOtaku626
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Save the Environment!
"Save the Environment! The password is:
Farting Toot Toot! It doesn't stink!"
The password is:
Farting Toot Toot!
It doesn't stink!
Wallman
I found you, Heppokomaru!
Wh-What is he?
Did you think you could get away from me?
From me, the Great Wallman?
It's my birthday!
Dammit, why'd a pursuer have to come now?
Celebrate! Celebrate!
Heppokomaru!
- You got me angry now.
- Yay yay...
So is the asparagus?
Asparagus?
The boss thinks highly of your strength.
Where's the next camera angle?
I'm not asking for much.
I just want you to join us.
Here!
Next one...
Over my dead body.
Right here!
Who would join you monsters?
- I'll give you asparagus if you join us.
- Not over yet!
Where's the next one? Where is it?
Crap! It's over there! I lost...
Game Pig
Hey!
What do you think you're doing in my base?
Geha the Tornado
Idiot! Don't touch him!
Too late!
Time to eat you up!
What's going on?
H-Hel...
That was delicious.
No way! Did he just eat that guy?
No way! This isn't asparagus!
It's macaroni!
What was that? This guy could only control wind?
I can't use this. I don't even need it.
Heppokomaru!
What I really want is your Fist of the Fart...
You monster!
No way... He eats people...
No! Please, no!
He's scary... He's too scary...
Don't worry about a thing!
I'm sure we passed!
"Hajike University Announcement of Successful Applicants"
Come on! Be brave and come look!
Um... my exam number is...
My exam number is...
Found it!
It's "Medium Blessing!"
Fortune Slip
Medium Blessing
Medium Blessing... Medium Blessing...
Let's see...
"Medium Blessing"
There it is!
I passed! I actually passed!
"Hajike University Announcement of Successful Applicants"
I drew a fortune and I passed!
Thank you, Mama and Papa
from the countryside!
Yay! Yay! I passed!
How are we supposed to fight
against a people-eating monster?
This is the worst situation
we've ever been in!
Beauty!
Bo-bobo!
Cheer up.
What the hell!?
"Instructor"
Begin the cheering!
Please cheer up, Beauty!
Go for it, Beauty!
Go for it, Beauty! Go for it, Beauty!
You're too quiet!
You think that'll make Beauty cheer up?
It's fine!
I've cheered up a lot now.
Really...?
Cheerfulness is most important.
Cameo Actor Frailman
I'm Cameo Actor Frailman.
"THE END"
I don't get it. Now I'm not cheerful anymore.
If you won't join us, then I'll
just have to consume you.
I'll take your Fist of the Fart by force!
This is gonna be good.
You just try it, ya freakin' wall!
That's my line!
He stole it, eh?
Ya know what...?
I'm angry at ya.
I am truly sorry.
Earth Bo-bobo
If ya keep farting this much yerself...
ya don't care if the Earth's
atmosphere gets polluted?
Yes, sir! It is as you say, Mr. Earth!
Heppokomaru... was it?
Yes!
Don't ya think yer not bein' nice ta me?
Whaddya think o' the environment, Heppokomaru?
Yes, you ♥
M-Me!?
Well, what?
Ya'll cause abnormal weather.
Ya don't care if El Niño
or somethin' happens?
No, I do care! I repent in
place of the person himself!
Well, ya know... the person himself...
I'm being invaded!!
The Aliens
Commence the invasion on Earth!
Hey, can't we just start over?
Risuo
Risumi
I'm sorry. But... I...
I can't...
Run! We're closed for the day!
The Old Man in Bo-bobo's Nose
Hiro's underwear...
The Housewife in Bo-bobo's Nose
Purukogi!
What's happening? What's happening?
Mr. Earth!
Earth Defence Force HQ
Sector 204 has been suppressed!
No response from Sector 14!
We have lost contact with Sector 707!
Earth Defence Force Captain
We have no choice but to use our ultimate weapon!
Earth Defence Force Ultimate Weapon
XAAP-120-A Mk4 #2
No! Don't be hasty!
Please don't be so hasty!
Fire!
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ouch!
Retreat at once!
We did it! We won!
My birthplace... peace on Earth...
forever...
GASP
Mr. Earth! Mr. Earth!
Setting that aside...
What's wrong, Heppokomaru?
Ya not gonna come at me?
Fist of the Fart...
October!
Fist of the Fart: October
October! October! October!
May!
Fist of the Fart Secret Technique:
Fist of the Fart Secret
Technique: May
I'd like to hit him with a combo...
but he'll eat me if I get too close.
I'd better keep my distance and take this slow...
Papa!
Kenny
Take me to the amusement
park! Amusement park!
Amusement park?
Take me to the amusement park!
- Let's go!
- Stop it, moron! Let me go!
Let me go! Let me
go now, you stupid...
Over here...
- Let me go!
- Over here!
Over here!
Over here! Over here!
- I said let me go!
- Over here!
Over here! Over here!
Oh won't you please take him, Father?
Mother
I'm just as surprised as you are!
Hey now, Kenny. Your nose is running!
How long were you in there for?
Just get lost already!
Seaweed!!!
"Seaweed"
Me too.
Then let's go together!
Let's go!
Yeah!
But what was with the seaweed?
Heppokomaru is no longer a mystery,
but we have another mystery on our hands.
Heppokomaru!
What is it, Wallman?
Honestly, you're a very weak boy.
What?
You haven't even mastered the Fist of the Fart.
What do you know about the Fist of the Fart?
More than you think.
You liar!
The reason the boss wants you,
is because he wants his hands on the hidden power of the Fist of the Fart.
The hidden power of the Fist of the Fart?
Whatever the case, you can't use the hidden power of the Fist of the Fart.
But if I eat you, I'll be able
to use the Fist of the Fart!
Now feed me the Fist of the Fart!
You've gotta be kidding!
Bo-bobo!
I-It's strong...
Did he beat you, as well?
Be careful. He's coming up here,
to finish us off.
Dammit!
It's here!
Old World Swallowtail
Class Insecta
Order Lepidoptera
Family Papilionidae
Signature Attack:
Drinking Nectar
A butterfly!?
- Mercy! Mercy!
- Please forgive us!
That's one tough butterfly...
Well, have fun with that...
No, no!
Have mercy!
No!
- Mercy! Mercy! Have mercy!
- Congratulations, Don Patch!
Quit getting in my way all the time!
Give it up. You can't beat
him the way you are now.
What?
You got that right.
Who are you anyway?
Me?
I am...
My name is...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Take my Fist of the Fart!
Why the hell are you wearing my clothes?
And you can call me...
Don Patch!
So you've come, Don Patch!
I'll defeat you with my Fist of the Fart!
I'll eat you! I'll eat you!
Toot toot! Toot toot!
It smells good! It smells good!
Now, all of you watching the TV, join in!
Toot toot! Toot toot! ♦ Puppu Puppu
-
It smells good! It smells good! ♠ Ii nioi Ii nioi
Toot toot! Toot toot! ♦ Puppu Puppu
-
It smells good! It smells good! ♠ Ii nioi Ii nioi
- Toot toot! Toot toot!
- It smells good! It smells good!
Everyone thinks I'm some kind of joke...
Quit making fun of me!
Calm down, Boy A.
Let me go!
That must be the Fist of the Nose Hair!
How could this be?
To think that someone besides the boss could use the Fist of the Nose Hair!
I have to return and report this to the boss.
Hello, I'd like to hail a taxi.
Yes. #813 will arrive in about 3 seconds.
Some urgent business has come
up, so I getting out of here.
The hell!?
Thank you for waiting.
Our fight is on our tea soup...
I mean... on hold, Heppokomaru!
"Hajike"
Excuse me, could you take
me to Shinjuku Station?
Got it.
"Hajike"
So, Mr. Driver, how's business?
Alright, I guess.
"Hajike"
"Patch"
This vehicle is turning left.
Please be cautious.
Um... aren't we going in circles?
We're almost at Shinjuku, sir.
How is that taxi going to get anywhere?
Beauty!
Hey, Beauty!
Wake up, Beauty!
Huh? When did I...
Right. I remember now.
I got bored of Bo-bobo and Don Patch...
and I fell asleep.
Wallman's left.
Let's leave too.
We can leave?
Wait!
I have a request for you!
Wait! I really need your help!
Please listen to me!
Hey, Bo-bobo, are you listening?
Okay. Let's finish it.
Click.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Aren't we shaking?
Could be.
Iwasaki Household
Meanwhile, at Mr. Iwasaki's house...
Father: Iwasaki Yoshio
Mother: Iwasaki Masako
Hiroki!
Eldest Child: Iwasaki Hiroki
What is it?
You had a test today, didn't you?
How did it go?
Whaddya mean?
Your grades!
Who cares?
I do.
Seconds.
60%. I got 60%.
How can you be satisfied with those grades? You've been watching too much TV...
Seconds, mother.
Get them yourself.
Okay.
Doesn't it feel like we're falling?
Could be.
So they've finally found me.
I don't know who they are,
but they must be very good at this.
I can't stay in this town any longer.
Sir.
We've reached Shinjuku.
That'll be 1280 yen.
Here...
Sir!
You're ten yen short!
And thus... The Hair Hunters C-block Base...
was destroyed.
Let's go, Beauty.
Yeah.
Hey! Wait up!
Softon
If she's with him, then I don't have to worry.
I'm not sure it's much of a relief myself...
But this man named Softon has felt something about Bo-bobo
that only those who have fought Bo-bobo themselves can know.
Is Softon a friend or foe?
And what mysteries are those eyes that look from behind that meaningful face hiding?
Looks like we've got another
mystery on our hands!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Mr. Bo-bobo, please make me your student!
Very well. But the path of Hajike is very harsh.
Why are you trying to
make him a Hajike student?
I will submit to Mr. Bo-bobo's teaching.
Then come with me to the Nose Hair Dojo!
Oh! Looks like this dojo
will make me stronger!
Hold it! You're making a big mistake!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
""The Crane Maiden" of Betrayal
and Greed. Thanks for the verse!"
"The Crane Maiden"
of Betrayal and Greed
Thanks
for the
verse!
The master is an old lady?