We made it back alive.
But,
can the Agency look past the
thirty-five people she murdered?
What am I going to do if the
Agency doesn't accept her?
Good morning.
Can you turn around for me?
So cute!
What's going on?
Well, she looks good in anything.
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
Kunikida-san...
Don't look at me like that.
I tried to stop them, too.
I wonder if this is going to work out.
Maybe it's not such a good idea.
Even if everyone else is okay with it,
Rampo-san might be a
stickler about the rules.
Oh, don't worry about that.
I'm back!
I bought some!
Rampo-san's into it the most.
This is the snack I told you about earlier.
It changes color when you mix it.
Go ahead, mix it.
First, open the bag,
then put the two powders in the container,
They're like siblings
in elementary school.
and add some water.
Next, mix really well.
It's important to put your feelings into it.
Okay? Mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
And look, how strange!
But I'm the one who gets to eat it.
How childish.
Rampo-san, you're a terrible person!
Well, it's just like him to do that.
So, who called her over to the Agency?
It was me.
President!
Any movement from the police?
Thanks to the Port Mafia's
attempts to erase her identity,
they haven't tracked down who she is yet.
But she'll be a wanted fugitive soon.
Please let me stay here.
What?
I'll do anything.
I don't recommend it.
It's not because you were
with the Port Mafia,
or because we don't have work.
But don't do it.
It's not easy, the world we live in.
Besides, if you stay here,
the Mafia will find you eventually.
Shouldn't you run somewhere far away?
He said
that I could do nothing
else but kill people.
I want to prove to myself that he's wrong.
President.
I would also like to ask on her behalf.
Please.
Please...
Very well.
What?!
I'll take her in.
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
Slight fracture of the lower jaw,
avulsion of the pedicles
and the T2 thoracic vertebrae,
damage to the jugular ligament,
rupture of the brachial
and femoral muscles,
and first-degree burns over the entire body.
To top it off, he's in a coma.
He's suffered serious damage.
It is the price he paid
for failing his mission.
I'm sorry.
He may not regain consciousness.
But...
Don't feel so disappointed.
You all did your best.
You did fail in attacking the Agency and
capturing the weretiger,
and you sank the transport ship.
But you did your best, didn't you?
Effort is what's important.
Results come second.
Isn't that right?
Oh, that reminds me.
The remnants of Karma Transit,
the group Akutagawa-kun crushed
during the operation,
are apparently coming together.
I presume they want
vengeance on Akutagawa-kun.
Listen, Higuchi-kun.
The Mafia are, in the end,
an act of commerce that
employs violence as its currency.
It is allowed to desire and
kill anything and anyone.
Retaliation in kind is a matter
of expenditure and liability.
But, liability?
Akutagawa-senpai has accomplished
much in his missions thus far.
Indeed, Akutagawa-kun is competent.
His propensity for violence is high,
even for our organization.
But what about you?
Higuchi-kun,
have you ever felt that you were
actually suited for this job?
Episode 11 Part 1
An Unsuitable
Profession for Her
I look horrible.
That's quite enough for rehearsals, Gin.
The Black Lizard!
Gin's often stuck with dark jobs like
infiltration and assassination.
It's not unusual for him to have
to slit the throat of one of our own
by a higher-up's command.
When it's for real, you won't
even have time to be surprised.
You're saying the boss will terminate me?
Not at the moment.
But I don't know about tomorrow.
Are you here to mock me?
If I were in your situation,
I'd rethink my current position before
an assassin arrives at my doorstep.
You, along with Akutagawa-kun,
are a strike force under the
boss's direct supervision.
As such, you have the authority to give
orders to us in the combat squad.
In that sense, you are our superior.
But what makes us obey is not your authority,
but fear and respect for the
ability Akutagawa-kun wields.
Higuchi-kun,
for the time while
Akutagawa-kun is incapacitated,
do you possess anything
that motivates us to obey?
I don't need your help!
Akutagawa-senpai!
Even for you, this would be suicide!
You're walking right into a
building full of security guards!
You didn't even give us subordinates
any orders about how to support you—
Shut up!
What would you know about any of this?
That's a sign.
A sign visible from anywhere in the city.
It is a powerful sign that
will be seen by the one
who left without a word,
and without acknowledging my power.
But it's my job to help you, senpai!
I don't need your help!
I don't need anyone's help!
I'm back.
Have you ever felt that you were
actually suited for this job?
Of course not, there's no way.
Yes? This is Higuchi.
What?!
I urge you to reconsider.
Your actions are contrary to
what the brass would want.
Are you insane?
That's suicide!
Akutagawa was abducted by foreign mercs
hired by Karma Transit's remnants!
Not only do they have numbers on their side,
they're armed to the teeth!
The boss will eventually issue orders
to conduct a retrieval operation.
Wait until that happens!
There will be no order!
If we retaliate as an
organization against smugglers
who targeted
Akutagawa-senpai as an individual,
the fallout will trigger
conflicts with other organizations.
To avoid that,
the brass will turn a blind eye to a
personal dispute between individual members.
Akutagawa-senpai has been cut off.
But what can you hope
to do by yourself?
Nothing.
Still!
I can't stand by and do nothing!
I knew...
I knew I wasn't suited for this job.
I knew I didn't have my
subordinates' respect.
If I were in your situation,
I'd rethink my current position before
an assassin arrives at my doorstep.
It's not easy to leave the Port Mafia,
but it's not impossible.
I've thought about it many times.
Yet I didn't, because...
Crap.
I can't rescue
Akutagawa-senpai with this injury.
Yet I didn't, because...
Kill everyone you don't recognize!
Why is the Black Lizard here?
You are our superior officer.
If our superior officer is in danger,
we must act.
I guess we're about done here.
Akutagawa-senpai...
Senpai...
Senpai!
Higuchi?
Senpai, you're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
It's not easy to leave the Port Mafia,
but it's not impossible.
Yet I didn't, because...
It's my job.
You look after the girl.
What, me?
Of course.
You saved her.
Okay.
Excuse me.
We're from the city police.
Oh, welcome.
Oh?
Oh Minoura-kun, your subordinate
was arrested a little while ago, right?
We're here today on a
different matter, detective.
We have a case.
Episode 11 Part 2
An Ecstatic
Detective Agency
They left as soon as they
were done talking business,
without even sitting down for tea.
I guess policemen in cities are busy.
Where you're from, do the
police have lots of free time?
Everyone knows each other in my village.
A policeman's job would
be fixing the well's pump,
rescuing cats from chimneys,
and tasting the year's first watermelon.
What the...
What happens if anyone commits a crime?
The perpertrator'd get tied up
and thrown off a cliff.
Um, Kenji-san...
You can call me Kenji-kun.
Until two months ago, I was living
in a village called Ihatov
where we don't have
electricity or telephones.
I was scouted by the president
and came to the city.
The city's full of new concepts.
I'm having a lot of fun.
New? Like what?
First, I don't really understand
the concept of money.
Isn't
bartering
good
enough?
Isn't
bartering
good
enough?
I see.
Kunikida-san,
what should we about the request
from the city police earlier?
A moving car blew up
for unknown reasons.
It'll be a challenge.
The police have given up on it.
Atsushi, want to give this one a try?
Shadow another agent
and learn the ropes?
You can do this.
Got it.
What's going on?
What's that?
I heard a car was just going along
when it suddenly flew over there.
Another explosion?
I'm not sure I'm up for this.
The driver died on impact
and he hasn't been identified.
Why not?
Can't we identify people if their
fingerprints or teeth are intact?
Yes.
If they were intact.
What?!
Then,
everything inside that car turned to mush?
All right,
Rampo-san would be able to solve
the case right away here,
but our task right now is
to gather information.
Oh, Ken-chan.
Oh hello, Miss Maeda.
Thank you for the boar meat the other day.
It was delicious.
It was extra sent from my home.
It was nothing.
"Miss"?
She'd be one of the
younger ladies at my village.
Hey, boy.
The vegetable garden I told you about,
it doesn't drain very well.
The soil might be too dry.
I'll come take a look tomorrow.
Thanks.
You're really popular.
Hey, Ken-chan.
You on a job?
We're investigating the car explosion
that happened earlier today.
Do you know anything?
Oh, that.
There are... rumors.
I'm not really supposed to talk about it,
but the young'uns were saying
that before it happened,
backstreet folks from the factory
district bought a load of fertilizer.
Fertilizer...
I wonder if they realized
the beauty of farming.
No, they were apparently talking
about manufacturing something.
Then it was probably nitrogen fertilizer.
Nitrogen fertilizer?
It's an ingredient for building bombs.
What?!
Thank you as always.
It was very helpful.
I'd do anything for you, Ken-chan.
We already have a lead.
Let's stay in touch.
Kenji-kun's amazing.
The same goes for me.
I'll be counting on you.
Speaking of the back streets
of the factory district,
there's a meeting hall for the
Gojo Youth Association there.
Youth Association?
Put in city terms... a gang?
A g—gang?!
I wonder if they're the ones
who built the bomb.
Well, let's go ask them face to face.
Wait a minute!
Even if they were responsible,
I doubt they'd admit to it.
Won't it be risky?
If we are sincere in our
inquiries, they'll respond.
It's how things are.
I-It's how things are?
Is it?
It's...
I guess that is how things are!
Hey, Tanizaki.
Aren't you with Atsushi?
Oh, Kenji-kun went with him.
Was Off
Purchasing
Eggs on a
Limited-
Time
Only Sale
Was Off
Purchasing
Eggs on a
Limited-
Time
Only Sale
What, with Kenji?!
Yes, they went to the crime scene together.
Kenji-kun's very competent.
He's solved many difficult cases,
so I doubt there'll be problems—
It's a huge problem!
Kenji's methods are too unique.
He's not a good role model!
Given how simplistic
and naïve Atsushi is,
he may easily take Kenji's
methods at face value
and believe them to be the gold standard!
Best and
Worst Team
This isn't good.
Huh?!
Did you all build the bomb that
made the car go flying?
You're funny!
You guys cops?
Not at all. We're with the
Armed Detective Agency.
Oh, nice chain!
You must be keeping one on you
to use when you need to herd cows.
Don't touch me!
What's your angle?!
Oh, I just wanted you all to tell me
if you're responsible for what happened.
Huh?
Don't know anything about it.
Right?
I see!
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Huh?!
Thank you for your help.
What?
H-Hey, Kenji-kun?
They were lying, no matter
how you try to look at it.
They're the ones responsible!
They might've used the bomb to kill someone
in an opposing gang, or something.
But they said they didn't know anything.
Well, sure, but...
Be it with a cow or a person,
be it in a village or a city,
if you are sincere, you can
communicate with others.
I've never failed using this method.
R-Really?
Really.
I guess I can see that.
Shall we head back for now?
Yeah.
Let's go by a beef bowl
place on our way back.
I'm starving.
Kenji-kun, you can eat beef
even though you keep cows?
I love cows!
I love having cows, communing
with cows, and eating cows.
The bomb was used to kill
an enemy gang member.
Who knew private
investigators would sniff us out?
Since you left without
really questioning us,
does that mean you found conclusive proof?
You're gonna tell the cops, aren't you?
We won't let you.
I see.
I'm glad you went through the
trouble to tell us the truth.
Huh?
I knew sincere conversation
would lead to understanding.
In all of my cases, everyone
confesses to me like this.
Oh, I see—
One down.
Crap!
We're surrounded.
What have I been doing?
Get 'em!
Ow...
Huh?
Phew.
Oops.
Ouch...
Oh, don't mind me.
This happens sometimes.
Out in the countryside,
cows often get in a temper
and refuse to listen to you.
In times like that...
Be not defeated by the rain.
Be not defeated by the wind.
Nor by the iron pipe.
Nor by the knife.
Nor by the metal bat.
Be of sound body.
Be without desire.
Never be angered.
Always have a quiet smile.
That is whom I wish to be.
Miyazawa
Family
Motto
Miyazawa
Family
Motto
Should
Cows
Act Up,
Hit Them
With
Whatever's
Close
At Hand
Should
Cows
Act Up,
Hit Them
With
Whatever's
Close
At Hand
This won't work.
I can't do things like this, Kunikida-san!
Calm down, idiot!
I commend you for
realizing that on your own.
Kenji is gifted with superhuman strength,
but he isn't invincible.
He can only manifest that
strength when he's hungry.
Huh?
Beef Bowl
Then what happens when he's full?
I can't eat any more.
He goes to sleep.
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
Meanwhile,
Dazai...
I'll say I got away from
the Port Mafia tomorrow.
Episode 12
Borne Back Ceaselessly into the Past