The assassin Wallman
Wallman
was after Heppokomaru's Fist of the Fart.
Astonished by Bo-bobo's Fist of the Nose Hair,
he fled to report to his boss.
But what's this!?
C-block Base is...
It's...!!!
It crashed on the Iwasaki's house!
Iwasaki Household
And so, the Hair Hunters
C-block Base was annihilated.
Heppokomaru follows after Bo-bobo.
Softon
If she's with him, I won't have to worry.
As Softon watches them leave,
he mutters something inconceivable.
What can those words mean?
Softon... Could it be that you're...
In love with Heppokomaru?
There was a slight error
in the narration there,
and for that I deeply apologize.
And now it's time for today's story!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
StitchOtaku626
SpiritofHokuto20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Destroyer Ring
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
StitchOtaku626
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
"The Crane Maiden"
""The Crane Maiden" of Betrayal and Greed
Thanks for the verse!"
of Betrayal and Greed
Thanks
for the
verse!
Bo-bobo, he's trying to tell you something.
So stop stuffing your face and listen to him.
Alright then.
I've come seeking your help, Bo-bobo. I need you to save my hometown that was attacked.
Your hometown?
Bo-bobo, I've been observing your fights for the past few days.
You're a lot stronger than I'd ever anticipate.
You did horseplay a lot, though...
So you're the one who's been
following us all this time, Hekkun?
Hekkun?
Heppokomaru's too long, so I'll call you Hekkun.
Hekkun...
Huh?
Are you listening, Bo-bobo?
What's with that costume!?
Now, everyone!
It's feeding time!
Feeding? But that's a battery!
Eat it all up!
It's a battery. Don't you want it?
What's wrong? Aren't you feeling well?
Hey, are you listening?
Where does it hurt? Where?
Alright. We're taking them as we planned.
Employee A
Employee B
OK!
I'll distract the parent! You take the young ones!
OK.
I'll protect them with my life!
With my life!
I've analyzed your data!
And this is what you're after!
They're...
Alkaline batteries!
Alkaline batteries! Alkaline batteries!
Mission accomplished.
We did it!
Now that we have these...
We can do better calculations!
Now our company's IT will be revolutionized!
We will now return...
To our company.
Best of luck!
You fiends! You demons!
Hey, are you going to listen...?
My daughter and two sons...
Daughter and two
sons...!
So they were boys and girls?
Your children are saving a company.
Now will you listen to me?
Come.
Hey, come on! I need your help!
Wait a minute!
Crane?
Don't you peek. Don't open the door, either.
I guess I've gotta wait here until Mr. Bo-bobo feels better...
Fever!
Let's forget all our problems
and dance the night away!
Fever!
Yeah!
Wow!
Hey!
Fever!
Yeah!
Wow!
This is about saving lives here! Listen to me!
Just wait here, Hekkun.
I'll just ask them for you.
Bo-bobo! Listen to what Hekkun has to say!
I thought they were having fever time!
I am sorry, Crane.
I've been causing you so much trouble.
What are you talking about?
Don't be such a stranger.
Just close your eyes.
I'll be working now, so don't worry.
Tribute
I've got to pay my tribute soon...
Oh, I completely forgot!
The bank closes at three!
There, there. If you're in too much of a hurry, it'll cost us more.
So you pay tributes at the bank?
Of course you don't.
Are you not the Crane that I saved back then?
I told you not to peek inside this room!
Hey! I'm sorry!
Why don't you ever listen to me?
I didn't mean to...!
Could this be "The Crane..."
TL Note: "The Crane Maiden" is a very well-known Japanese folktale
The Crane...
Dung Beetle!!
Get away from us!
Don't come any closer!
And they all lived happily ever after.
No we didn't!
Someone's there!
Hair Hunters L-block Trooper: Puppetman
I'm Hair Hunters L-block Trooper, Puppetman!
I've found you, Bo-bobo!
Prepare yourself.
At last your time has come.
I will now... defeat you.
H... He's cute ♥
I never back down from a challenge.
I'll beat you up, Bo-bobo. I'll beat you to a pulp.
He's coming!
Heppokomaru.
I understand how you feel.
I'll help you out. If you can defeat him, that is.
Really? Don't go forgetting your promise!
Right then, I'll show you what I can do!
However, you must not use the Fist of the Fart!
Out of my way!
Why? Why can't I use the Fist of the Fart?
Hekkun!
He...he's strong.
At this rate, he'll be done for!
Bo-bobo!
Come down this instant! What are your demands?
I can't wait! I wanna eat cup noodles, but I ain't gonna wait for three lousy minutes!
I'm gonna eat it one minute after I add the water!
But if you eat it, it'll be hard!
You just leave this to me!
Raw
It's...
The raw noodles you can eat
one minute after adding water!
(One Minute After Adding Water!!)
Raw Noodles
My, my.
What an impatient guy we have here.
Now allow me talk to him.
Please do what you can.
Hey, boy! Listen to me! I'm Raw Noodles!
You're Raw Noodles?
What flavor?
Sugar and Soy Sauce.
Does that even exist?
Your mother didn't raise you
to threaten cup noodles!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Remember!
You used to put the powder,
on dry noodles and eat them!
If you eat ramen...
Do six situps!
Hear that, boy?
We noodles sweat all day to
keep our backs in shape!
But situps don't work the
back, they work the abs!
Back
Abs
If you eat ramen, do six situps!
If you eat ramen, do six...
Situps! If you eat ramen...
If you eat ramen...
Do six sit-ups!
If you stretch tanmen...
You have six stories of rebars!
THE END
Shit! I can't read his movements!
If only I could use the Fist of the Fart...
But why?
Why can't I use it?
You depend too much on the Fist of the Fart.
Bo-bobo!
I could easily beat someone like him,
without even using the Fist of the Nose Hair.
What?
Fist of Clap-Clapping a CD Case!
Clap-clap! Clap-clap! Clap-clap!
Let's go!
My CD...
It won't clap.
Fist of Not Clap-Clapping a CD Case!!
No clap-clap! No clap-clap!
Take this!
Oh, no! It closed!
Thank goodness.
Who does he think he is?
You're just as weak if you don't use the Fist of the Nose Hair.
Idiot. Take a good look at his feet.
Tissue
Tissues!?
Fist of the Tissue Secret
Technique: Box-Wearing Fist
That's the Fist of the Tissue Secret Technique: Box-Wearing Fist.
Box-Wearing Fist?
It's a legendary secret technique that triples the user's speed.
To think that he's mastered it...
Wait, that secret technique...
Box Dash!
I didn't know! I didn't know...
I didn't know that tissues were this devastating!
Wow! Bo-bobo is really astonishing!
You're still feeble, Heppokomaru.
Join me, and I'll train you myself.
Really?
At the Nose Hair Dojo.
Nose Hair Dojo?
Heppokomaru felt like a storm was brewing.
You sure got it rough, eh, Hekkun?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Nose Hair...
Dojo?
Nose Hair Dojo
Bo-bobo has arrived at the Nose Hair Dojo,
to train Heppokomaru.
So this must be the Nose Hair Dojo.
A lukewarm wind.
Here comes the storm...
No!
What's that!?
Now here's your bean paste bread. Put it on.
Huh?
I feel kind of stupid wearing it... Like this?
Put it on! Put it on! Put it on!
Alright, dammit! I'll put it on!
Awesome.
The bean paste bread is consuming me!
I didn't take it seriously!
I didn't take the bean paste bread seriously!
Am I at fault for not taking
bean paste bread seriously?
Behold! Bean paste bread is sweet as sugar!
Glory to the bean paste bread!
'Scuse me.
What's this?
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
They're giant killifish!
Killifish #1
Killifish #2
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
That's...
Bean paste bread!
What?
Step 1: Protect the bean
paste bread with your life!
Bean paste bread!
That hurt!
Hekkun!
Killifish #10
I'll be eating that!
Killifish #10! What's wrong?
This is a jelly donut!
Jelly Donut
You're barbaric... You knew we killifish are vulnerable to jelly, didn't ya?
And yet you fed me a jelly donut?
Fiend!
Demon!
Are killifish really vulnerable to jelly?
That's obviously not true!
Bo-bobo, these are jelly donuts.
Strawberry
Kiwi
Marmalade
He's spreading it on them!
There, ma'am. Now your skin is all smooth and shiny.
I'll put some on your lips to make them glossy.
Eye shadow's in style so I'll put some on your eye... See? You're all sparkly!
Excellent!
Spread some jelly on me!
You're...
Tomorrow's Bread!
Spread it on me! Please spread some on me!
None for you.
Why won't you spread some on me?
Cut that out!
Let me go! I need to be spreaded!
Let me go!
Bo-bobo, spread some on him.
I only put butter on my bread.
Only put butter
on my bread
Butter...!?
The beat-up bread...
slumped to the mat with a BUTTER.
- One... Two...
- Tomorrow's Bread!
Three... Four...
It's alright... It's alright now.
You've done well.
Tomorrow's Bread was burnt to a toast.
I'm sorry, okay?
I won't sneak any more bites, so don't eat me.
Are you alright?
You're...
I have drifted 3000 miles from the southern isles.
I'm the drifting Coconut Man.
Coconut Man ♥
I shake my thighs under the starry skies.
And I'll make my ukulele sing for you tonight.
Aloha 'Oe!
Now rest up and drink from my husk!
No way... You'll let me drink you too?
Do I taste good? Are you refreshed?
The south! You're from the south!
Northern Man
A northern man is invading the area!
This is bad! This is bad!
Somebody please notice him!
What's with you?
The southern guy noticed!
Southern Man
It's cold! It's cold!
Get out! Get out of here!
That's the spirit, southern guy!
Get that northern guy out of here!
Wanna fight?
What!?
That's it! Go southern guy! Go southern guy! Go southern guy! Go southern guy!
Go southern guy!
Victory!
What!?
As a result, the world entered a five hundred year ice age.
The Northern Men conquered the world.
What a load of bullhonky!
I can't fight any more of these guys.
Alright. That's the first step cleared.
Hey, Bo-bobo, how about me?
Beauty, you've graduated as well.
I did it! Hooray! Hooray!
How did she pass...?
What's that...
Bloodlust?
Schedule Book
Do you want to know the schedule?
Now it's time to move on to step 2.
Alright...
What're y'all doin'?
Mother!
Mother! Don't get mad at us!
Mother?
Master!
Master!?
Old Lady
(Master!?)
Stop horseplayin' and do ya homework!
Yes!
Ah, Master!
The hell ya doin' here?
No way. There's no way she's the master.
Alright, Heppokomaru.
Step 2: Defeat the master.
Defeat her!?
Are you sure? She's just an old lady!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique...
She uses the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Nose Hair Clone!!
What the...!?
Three old ladies...
Four old ladies...
Five old ladies...
One old man...
Six old ladies...
Can ya see through this technique?
I'm surrounded!
Now, can ya keep up with our speed?
Just who is that old lady? She's using the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Didn't you just call her master!?
I can't see them through all
this smoke! What should I...?
They all turned into sake!
I see now. That old lady became sake of her own free will...
So we could drink the spoils of victory.
Is that sake safe to drink?
It can't be!
It's poisoned!?
Congratulations!
Of course it's not! Of course it's not!
Wait!
You celebrate too soon. I'm still here!
Bo-bobo...
Bo-bobo!
Yay! We did it!
It was a croquet battle!?
Not at all.
What was the deal with that old guy anyway. And this dojo...
It seems that you have learned
a valuable lesson, Heppokomaru.
Alright. You've cleared the second step.
He cleared it!?
But isn't that the best, Hekkun?
Hey, I'm going on ahead!
And so, they left the Nose Hair Dojo.
What kind of trial awaits Heppokomaru next?
And will it really be a trial?
Only the twilight-colored nose hairs really know.
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Hey, hey, hey, hey, look at that.
Look at that blue guy.
What? What is it?
I don't believe it! His body's all square!
It's too weird!
Right? Right? Right? Right? That's impossible.
That's really impossible!
I don't think you guys have
any right to say that...
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
"A wobbly foe appears!
His name is Tokoro Tennosuke!"
A wobbly
A
wob
A wo
A wobb
A wobbly
foe appears!
His name is
Tokoro Tennosuke!
He said he's Tokoroten!
That's hilarious!
Don't laugh at him like that!
You're hurting his feelings!