Bo-bobo and friends paid
a visit to the Nose Hair Dojo.
Nose Hair Dojo
Within the dojo,
the hellish training began.
Brave men showed up one after another,
until finally this mysterious old woman showed up.
Nose Hair Clone!
What?
Three old ladies...
Four old ladies...
Five old ladies...
One old man...
Six old ladies...
Can you see through our technique?
Heppokomaru's in danger! What's going to happen?
But all of a sudden...
Purukogi! Purukogi!
Oh! It's almost time for Bo-bobo! Let's go home!
Wait, what?
For the love of God...
This isn't the time for a recap!
Gotta go home! I can't miss this!
- Wait for me, old ladies!
- Huh? They all left?
I gotta see this too! You guys take over, okay?
Take over? What do you...?
Is he leaving too?
A-Anyway, it's time to start the show!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
StitchOtaku626
tare9
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
StitchOtaku626
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
A wobbly
"A wobbly foe appears!
His name is Tokoro Tennosuke!"
A
wob
A wo
A wobb
A wobbly
foe appears!
His name is
Tokoro Tennosuke!
Bo-bobo and company have
settled in the countryside.
Sir Bo-bobo
Sir Don Patch
Happy, Happy,
I'm always happy...
What a great day t'day!
Mah back's all worn-out.
Ey! Sir Bo-bobo!
Whatcha doin' t'day?
Ah, if't ain't Sir Don Patch!
T'day's such a fine day, I thought I'd plant me some disposable chopsticks!
Oh is that so?
By the way, I chilled a watermelon in the stream, ya fancy some?
Ah! Of course I'd like some!
Huh?
Pencil Box
Pencils... Pencils... Pencils... Pencils...
Hey! It's that no-good pencil box again! Get off mah property!
Pencils!
I told ya those there ain't even pencils!
Hey Bo-bobo!
What is it?
I can't seem to find Hekkun anywhere!
Do you know where he went?
I... reckon he's out by that there stream training.
What's that sound?
It's the signal to start.
Perfect Perfect
Do your best! Do your best!
What's that? What are you doing?
What? What? What is this thing?
What is this? What are they doing?
Perfect Perfect
Perfect Jealousy
There it is!
Is it over?
Congratulations! You've reached 3 meters!
Well, that's that.
Now... This should do it.
What's this for?
Just watch.
Alright.
Pencils! Pencils! Pencils!
Here he comes!
Pencils! Pencils! Pencils! Pencils!
This is...
No... There's no way...
It can't be...
Hey, what's he doing?
Just be quiet and watch.
Perfect Perfect
It's... It's...
My mother's handwriting...
No... No way...
You're... Are you... Are you...
Mother!?
Smear smear smeeeeeear smear!
It's a lie! It's a lie!
It's all a lie!
It's no use!
I can't keep dodging it!
At least we'll die together!
They are good friends ♥
There!
SUKIYAKI
I wonder what Hekkun's doing?
No! You gotta put your whole body into it!
Hey you! You better listen to me!
Fish Master
Mr. Bo-bobo has asked me
to forcefully train you here!
What kind of training is this?
Hey! Stop playing with yourself
and move those hands!
That hurt, you fish bastard!
Foolish boy! Don't talk back to me!
I get it already.
Shit... Young people these days...
They don't do any work!
All they do is talk, talk, talk!
But... Lately... These days...
I've always liked that about you!
What are these feelings I'm having?
Could this... Could this be...
No... No, I can't...
I'm his master and he's my student!
That's right! I have to keep it in!
I can't... I just can't...
I have to keep it in!
Keep it in...
I can't keep it in!
I'm gonna eat you! I'm gonna eat you up!
What the hell are you doing?
Help me!
Somebody help me! I can't swim!
Oh, no!
Today, I met a weird fish. It was a really lousy day.
Hey, I got a bingo!
Don... PATCH!
Well, tomorrow's the chopstick harvest, so I'm going to bed.
You guys should get to bed soon, too.
Okay, I'm going to bed too. Good night.
Okay, good night.
Sweet dreams!
I got a bingo too!
Don... PATCH!
The hell's wrong with you?
Idiot!
"This guy was also really lousy.''
Mother...
I know not where you are.
But I will find you one day!
Wha...
What's...
That?
Hey, are you alright?
Yeah...
Mother!
Splendid!
I'll make this my base.
Bo-bobo, it's morning!
I'm coming in!
Bo-bobo! It's morn...
My head feels like it's gonna split!
That's a huge head!
It's splitting. ♥
It's closing. ♥
The Pencil Household
Pencil (Mother)
Pencil (Father)
How is it? It's a big house, isn't it?
Yes. It's very big.
Eraser (Dog)
Pencil (Child)
I never thought we'd find another house so soon.
It's all thanks to Mr. Bo-bobo.
Alright, I'm off to the chopstick field.
We're here!
This is...
Märchentic Amusement Park
Someone built an amusement park here!
There is no reason to be so surprised.
Since ancient times, this village has always grown amusement parks
Elder Patch
from disposable chopsticks.
Now what?
Elder!
If the other villages know about this...
Sorry, sorry.
Now, let us wake the villagers! Wake the villagers!
Hi, everybody!
Welcome to the paradise of dreams,
Tour Guide of Dreams
Kegirl
Märchentic Amusement Park!
Who are you?
I'm the Tour Guide of Dreams, Kegirl.
Amusement Park! Amusement park!
Hey, hey, calm yourself down.
But you know... You know...
Darling, you're always at work, so we haven't gone on a date in so long...
I'm so happy... So happy...
So I just spontaneously...
Transform into a beastman!
Me too!
Now before you enter
Märchentic Amusement Park...
Please have a look at this.
Welcome, la...
Please pay attention.
Yeah, sure.
Welcome ladies and gentlemen, to Hair Hunters A-block Base, Märchentic Amusement Park.
I am Hair Hunters A-block Captain, Tok...
Darling!
W-Who did this to you?
They'll pay for this, I swear!
Please pay attention!
Oh, right.
Excuse me...
I am Hair Hunters A-block Captain, Tokoro Tennosuke.
What? Captain?
Don't leave without me!
Didn't you... Didn't you say we'd fulfill our dream together?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am A-block Captain Tokoro Tennosuke.
What? A-block Captain?
First, I must thank you for
creating this base for me.
Thank you.
Thank you so very much!
I'm made of tokoroten...
so whenever I tried to make an A-block base, my budget was always so much smaller than the other bases.
And on top of that, we took shortcuts in construction and got reported for not having permits...
And everyone made fun of me...
It was harsh... It was so harsh...
Captain.
But that ends today!
I've got a wonderful base now!
Yay! Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Uh, Captain...
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Please calm down, Capta- Stop it...
Sorry about this.
Our captain is a bit of a lunatic.
You moron, I ain't tofu!
I'm joking! Sorry!
Now let me get straight to the point.
Take a look at this guy.
I'm sorry guys. I screwed up big time.
Tomohiro
Tomohiro!!!
Who's that!?
Here, have some spaghetti!
Spaghetti! Spaghetti!
I'll never give in to your spaghetti!
We have curry! We have curry!
Come on, it's spaghetti! Spaghetti!
You better hurry and take the spaghetti!
We have curry!
Look... Spaghetti...
Hurry and take the spaghetti!
It's my curry.
That's it, Tomohiro! Indian! Indian!
Très bien! Très bien!
You...!
Son of a...
Hold on a sec! What is this?
There aren't enough potatoes in this curry!
What's the meaning of this?
I'm really sorry.
What the fuck are ya doin'!?
Ya think that's the kind of attitude for an apology? I will not accept it!
Take off your mask and apologize!
Finish your studies!
It's her! It's the amusement park specialty Education Mom!
You have to get into a prestigious school!
I'm hidden somewhere in this amusement park.
If you want this guy back,
you better come and find me.
Here. Spa-spa!
Spa-spa!
I'll never give in to spaghetti!
Tomohiro!
Do you think you can find me?
Anyhow... Good luck finding me!
He won't get away with this.
How dare he do that to Tomohiro...
But who the hell is Tomohiro?
Heppokomaru,
from here on out, this is my battle of destiny with the Hair Hunters.
You can go home now.
Get real. This is what I've been waiting for.
Alright then. If you insist, then come along.
Isn't that great, Hekkun?
Yeah.
Perfect. I've been training all this time.
This is a great opportunity to test my strength.
Okay. Let's go!
Yep!
OK!
Hey, mom, can I go too?
No, you cannot!
Monkey Train
It's huge!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hekkun!
What is it?
What should we ride first?
If we're at an amusement park...
Don Patch!
Bo-bobo, where are you going?
If we're at an amusement park...
We gotta ride the roller coaster!
Roller coaster!
Wait up, you two!
There it is!
It's the roller coaster!!!
This is a Hair Hunters base,
so we should be more cautious!
And besides...
THAT'S A FERRIS WHEEL!!!
It appears that... We made it on.
I know, right?
I am the Guardian of the Ferris Wheel, Fair Riswiel.
Guardian of the Ferris Wheel
Fair Riswiel
I       I       I       I       I       I       I       I       I
Bo-bobo: You're a Hair Hunter, aren't you...
Fair Riswiel: Now that you're here,
I'll beat you up!
That's what I'd like to say...
I       I       I       I       I       I       I       I       I
Fair Riswiel: But it's so cramped
that we can't fight... What should we do... ...
Bo-bobo: ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...
There's someone else on that ferris wheel.
You've got good eyes, Hekkun.
It must be an enemy.
I know what you mean!
So she dumped you!?
Idiot! I was serious about her!
Ayumi...
My bad. Here, have some gum. Sooner or later, something good's bound to happen!
You're so kind...
Huh? What's wrong, Hekkun?
Well... You see... Thing is...
You're weird, Hekkun.
They're back!
You're not serious!
It's true, you know!
For real? I so wanna go!
Huh? They're having a heart-to-heart talk!
So, you wanna go together sometime?
Sure! Let's trade phone numbers!
You son of a bitch!
How dare you kill Don Patch!
But you were the one that finished him off!
Don Patch! I promise that I will avenge you!
Beauty!
Take care of Don Patch for me!
What about you, Bo-bobo?
I cannot leave this roller coaster until I've defeated this man!
Now, let's finish off our battle, shall we?
Just what I wanted to hear.
Bo-bobo! Wait a second!
I leave Don Patch in your hands now!
But Bo-bobo, that's a ferris wheel!
Hey! You alright? Hey!
So, picking up where we left off...
Yeah, and?
They're still having
a heart-to-heart conversation.
Hey! Hey, you alright? Hey!
Really? You're a fan too?
Yeah! We have so much in common!
Huh? What's wrong, Hekkun?
Well... You see... Thing is...
You're weird, Hekkun.
They're back again!
So then, what did you think he said?
What? How should I know!?
Heh... You'll never believe this, but he...
What? Stop building it up and just tell me!
Not again!
You son of a bitch!
How dare you kill Don Patch!
But you were the one that finished him off!
Don Patch! I promise that...
W-Wait a sec!
Hekkun, weren't you with Don Patch just now?
He melted.
What a relief!
Oh, what a relief!
That's no excuse.
Get a life.
I was worried for a second!
Excuse me, can I buy a balloon?
Here you go.
Thanks.
I'm so happy!
You like it?
Now I'm bored of the roller coaster.
But it was a ferris wheel!
Alright gang. Let's roll out.
Wait a sec!
Aren't you guys forgetting
something important?
No, not really.
Fair enough, guess it was nothing then.
If that's the case, then it's alright.
Of course there's something!
What is it now?
We're kind of in a hurry, so if you got something to say, just say it!
I'm the guardian of this ferris wheel! Do you think I'll just let you go?
Right. I forgot about that.
Whatever. Now's the best time
to catch you off-guard.
Now behold,
the potential of my true power!
Are you astonished?
Each of these ferris wheel cars have become giant balls of energy!
Now, let's see how many of these you can dodge!
Eat this!
It's coming!
Run for it!
Looks like you've dodged the first one.
But how about this one?
Here it comes!
Take this!
It didn't work! Get back!
They dare to dodge it again!?
Thanks, Hekkun!
So it's you two? What are you trying to do?
Well, whatever. Have some of this!
Alright, Don Patch!
We're doing this like we planned!
Gotcha.
What are you trying to pull?
It's not like that'll help you.
What's that? Is that my phone?
Let's see...
Found it.
Incoming Call
Number Withheld
Unknown number? Who could it be?
Well, whatever.
Hello?
One serving of buckwheat noodles?
Um...
Who is this calling me?
Yes... No, you've got the wrong number.
Y-Yes.
That's right.
Yes... Yes... No, goodbye.
Seriously! Now of all times, a wrong number?
You're open!
Oh shit!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Am I getting hit too!?
Send your scenic views on a postcard!
We do not supply postcards.
So he failed his mission?
You're quite good, Bo-bobo.
But...
It appears that they've set up one guardian per attraction here.
But we don't have the time to go through them one by one.
Then how about this...
How about we each split up to find him?
Good thinking, Hekkun! Let's do that, Bo-bobo!
Who's gonna find him first?
Sounds fun. Let's do that.
I'm in on this too you know.
Come on.
Alright, gang! Now that we've decided on that, let's roll out!
Yeah! I'm gonna find him before you do!
Good luck, you two!
They've somehow managed
to defeat the first guardian Fair Riswiel.
But the battle starts now!
And where is Tokoro Tennosuke hiding!?
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
We've all split up, but was that a good idea?
Now let's ride that one!
I knew it! He's just playing around!
You're being really inconsiderate!
I'm the one fighting the hard fight here!
Really now?
An amusement park, huh?
Yu... What are you doing now?
Who's Yu? Do we even care
about Tomohiro anymore?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
"Intense Snapshot! 24-Hour Amusement Park!
The Hippo Mastermind Revealed!"
Intense Snapshot!
24-Hour Amusement Park!
The           Mastermind Revealed!
Hippo
Are you saying he's a hippo?