Hair Hunters A-block Base
The Märchentic Amusement Park
W...Was actually...
Hair Hunters A-block Base!!
A-block Captain Tokoro Tennosuke
Huh? You already knew that? Alright then.
After a harsh fight on the ferris wheel,
Bo-bobo defeated the guardian of the ferris wheel, Fair Riswiel.
Guardian of the Ferris Wheel
Fair Riswiel
Send your scenic views on a postcard!
And now, to save Tomohiro...
Tomohiro
Who's Tomohiro again?
To save Tomohiro...
Bo-bobo,
Heppokomaru,
Don Patch,
And Beauty split up,
to look for A-block Captain Tokoro Tennosuke.
By the way, do you eat your tokoroten
with mustard or with no mustard?
In case you were wondering, I don't.
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
angel_of_chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Intense Snapshot!
"Intense Snapshot! 24-Hour Amusement Park!
The Hippo Mastermind Revealed!"
24-Hour Amusement Park!
The           Mastermind Revealed!
Hippo
Now, where has everyone gone?
I know we did say to split up, but they all left in a hurry...
Come on...
Hey! Get your balloons here!
Don't push! Don't push! Here you go.
Thank you!
Yokoseyo! Yokoseyo! Yokoseyo!
TL Note: Hand it over! Hand it over!
Yokoseyo! Yokoseyo!
Jumbo Department Store in Shibuya, Yokoseyo!
Papa, Mama and me.
We're all happy! We're all happy!
Yoko-Yoko-Yoko-Yoko-Yokoseyo Department Store!
Our 2583rd Anniversary Sale is now on!
President Yokoseyo!
President Yokoseyo
The people's champion, President Yokoseyo!
President Yokoseyo! Three cheers for Yokoseyo!
Thou dog.
Didst thou know that I doth be a warrior when thou started this riot?
Are you serious?
Then you must be the samurai of Greater Edo...
Hajike Dojo
Indeed. I hath mastered my skills at the Hajike Dojo in Edo...
And my name doth be Patchyama Patchzaemon.
On this occasion,
I hath been given a secret mission from my lord Tokugawa of Edo,
And I hath hastened to Echizen.
And the secret mission I hath spoken of...
There doth be a man who hath secretly kept his eye on my lord Tokugawa.
Bo-bobo! Don't run off on me without telling me anything!
I found lots of rides over there. You wanna take a look?
Sure. Let's go.
Okay.
For I hath been ordered to subjugate the villain.
And so, I doth be headed for Echizen
Doth thou understand?
That's terrible, huh?
Such a hackneyed thing is well once in a while.
Ah! A gourd sushi roll!
It looks so delicious! I'mma eat it!
Oh. Couldst thou refrain from eating my topknot?
I ask this because that doth be my dinner.
But I'mma dyin' of hunger here!
Whatcha talkin' about? Ya stupid or something?
If ya eat it, you'll be sorry!
Ya get it? Ya get it, moron?
Wait, wait. What are you doing?
Athletics on the Water
Alright. Let's start with this one.
Monkey Train
The monkey train? Do we really have to?
Wait for me!
Rabbits
Man. Those monkeys weren't anything special.
Alright. Let's go beat up the hippos.
Bro, those hippos are real dangerous!
Ya chicken?
I hear they keep goldfish in their sacks.
What? Goldfish?
Whatcha lookin' at?
N... Nothing...
Is that so? Well then, excuse me.
Hey guys! Wait up, will ya!?
Okay, Beauty. Let's get on.
That's okay. I'll just watch from over here.
You're not gonna ride it?
No.
Ride with me! Come on!
Ride with me! Ride with me!
No, I'm fine!
Ride with me! Beauty! Ride with me!
The Monkey Train will be leaving shortly.
Well then, I'll just ride it alone.
OK, sure.
I shall be your guide for today,
My name is Ukiki, Guardian of the Monkey Train.
Ukiuki... (Happy)
And now, we shall be departing to the wonderful world...
Of monkeys!!!
Such a hackneyed thing is well once in a while.
Young lady, would you like to have a cup of tea with me?
No!
Then how about a movie?
Stop.
I really suck at flirting...
That driver sure did look like a Hair Hunter...
Is Bo-bobo gonna be alright?
Everyone hold on tight!
Y...your right! Everyone look to your right!
Monkeys.
Everyone look to your left!
This is no fun!
We're approaching a tunnel!
Tunnel
Huh?
They're not coming out... Why not?
Bo-bobo...
Where is Tomohiro?
Why would I tell you?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Turtle Village Submerged!
So he's not here, either...
Meanwhile, Don Patch was...
Here, darling. Eat as many as you'd like!
Yakkun
Huh? You don't want any?
But I made them just for you!
Fine then. I'll just eat them all myself.
If only Yu was here, he'd be happy to eat them.
Yu
That's mine and Yu's keepsake mug!
Yu!
It's so full...
So full of memories with Yu...
Yu...
Yu... What's your dream?
U
To Become an S
I want to become an S.
It's stupid for a U like me to say that, isn't it?
No, it's not! It's not stupid at all!
You can do it, U! I know you can become an S!
Thank you! That really makes me happy.
U...
I miss you... I miss you so much...
Hey!
Who's that screamin' in my mug!
T...that voice!
U!
You've become a number, U...
Maybe you're not an S, but you still changed.
U!
6 Attack!
You! How dare you wear shoes in my house!
Don't you know that
I'm the guardian of the teacups, 6?
U...
And so, the love triangle started to turn.
Yes... Just like the teacups.
Tune in to the second half
for the exciting conclusion!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
Here's a recap of the first half...
U became 6...
Yes... Like a caterpillar
transforming into a butterfly.
You're Patchmi, aren't you?
U...
What's going on, Patchmi?
Were you trying to go back
to the way things were?
Don't be so stupid! Why would I even think that?
It's fine, you know.
We can go back to the way things were.
Thud!
Oh no... I'm wavering...
I know he's deceiving me...
But...
Six!
Thud!
No! What did he just do? What was that?
Seven!
Thud!
6 and 7... 6 and 7...
I'm sorry, teacher!
I can't figure out this problem!
Now, together with me, Patchmi...
Eight.
This is perfect.
Yakkun!
Stop it, you perv!
What's wrong, Patchmi?
Now, let's do it together.
Eight.
What the...!?
S...she turned into a goat!
Goatkichi
Eight!
Eight! Eight! Eight!
N...no way! My charms aren't working on her!
"Oh! If it isn't Goatkichi!
What's wrong? What happened?"
"What was that? Patchmi's in trouble?"
"Alright, Goatkichi! Lead me to Patchmi!"
"Patchmi! Where are you, Patchmi?"
Yakkun! I'm right here!
"Hey, Patchmi! You alright?"
"You bastard! How dare you try to deceive me, Patchmi!"
"You'll pay for this! Prepare yourself!"
JOHNNY!!!
He flew! Johnny flew!
Hey... 6 is our answer, right?
Of course it is! You should be more confident.
Bo-bobo will deliver our answer soon.
Thanks for waiting!
There he is!
Here is your answer.
7?
That's a load of bull! Our answer's 6!
You moron!
Equals!
Three plus three is eight!
But I'm 7.
Six!
Six! Six! Six!
Six! Six!
Fist of the Nose Hair:
...Equals 8!
Eight! Eight! Eight!
Never underestimate the power of math.
Seems like you're having an awfully hard time, Bo-bobo.
If you don't find us soon...
It'll be a horrific day for your friend!
Right, Captain?
That's right.
What a nice bath...
What are you doing, Captain?
Oil-bathing.
Don't be stupid! You're made of tokoroten!
Please stop fooling around
and get out this instant!
No! You perv!
Bo-bobo! Please, hurry up!
But where on Earth is...
Tomohiro?
I've become much stronger.
Idiot! You're wide open!
Gun
Prepare yourself!
It's cheap.
It's cheap. It's cheap.
Goddammit!
I can clearly see his movements. Is it because of my training?
Athletics on the Water
So he wasn't here either?
Where should I go next?
Meanwhile, Beauty was...
At today's special event...
The Refined Kitty.
Thank you all for coming.
This cat is very refined and delicate...
So please be quiet during the performance.
And now, introducing... The Refined Kitty!
It's refined...
Haunted House
Here will do.
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo and Don Patch...
Guardian of the Roller Coaster:
Hagechaz Telno
Defeated the guardian of the
roller coaster, Hagechatz Telno,
And were riding the roller coaster.
All you bros and sistas walkin' down the road!
Soko no michi iku niichan neechan
We're doing this with style, standing firm, standing free
Tsukisusumu style kakuritsu, dokuritsu
This age echoes from one man's scream
Jidai no hankyo hitori no zekkyo
We're the youth born in this turtle company
Kono kame shakai ni umareta oretachi wakamono
But we'll make it through with our spirit, our demerit
Soredemo taenuku ore no spirit, demerit
Is this devotion? Emotion? The turtles are in motion!
Korette junjou? Seijou? Kame sanjou
We've been livin' in contradiction and we've got an irritation
Kono mujun no naka de ikiteru bokutachi no iradachi
With the unforgivable, miserable, turtle-saving life
Yurusenaku yarusenaku kamedasuke jinsei
So now's the time to stand up!
Saa tachiagaru nara ima
Now's the time to get walking!
Michi susumu nara ima
Is this devotion? Emotion? The turtles are in motion!
Korette junjou? Seijou? Kame sanjou
A burgeoning virgin engine in full-throttle...
Rifujinna kifujinna enjinna joutai zenkai
Why a turtle rap? Why a turtle rap?
Why do you think?
Why is it?
Well you see...
It's because...
YA SERIOUS!?
No way, no way, no way, no way. The truth is... The truth is...
The truth is... The truth is...
Expel the demons!
Spinny-spin!
That actually hurt!
Forget your troubles! Forget your troubles!
Now's my chance!
Pervert sighted! Pervert sighted!
Has a pervert been here lately?
Not one.
Effort
Thank you! I've become confident!
Party's over
Party's over!
Don't wanna! Don't wanna!
What am I gonna do about you...
Then I guess I'll play with you
until the end! It's a special deal!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
We're parallel! We're parallel!
We're parallel!
This time the
party's over
Oh yeah!
I was so busy watching the cat show that I lost Bo-bobo again.
Beauty!
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
It's a good thing you're safe.
This base is dangerous.
Don't wander off on your own
That's the deal. Let's roll out.
Both of you are covered in scars...
There must have been a fierce battle when I was gone.
Haunted House
Alright. We'll go here next.
Alright.
I don't like haunted houses...
Do we really have to?
What are you doing? Stop pushing me!
Don't be such a goody-two-shoes!
We didn't come here to have fun!
Take this more seriously!
I'm sorry...
Here.
Don't let go! Please don't let go!
Whatever you do, don't let go! Don't let go!
So he is scared.
HEKKUN!!!
Oh, no! Hekkun...
I mean, Heppokomaru...
Has been defeated!
What happened in this haunted house?
And who is this man who
defeated Heppokomaru?
Actually, I already know what happened!
But you'll have to wait until the next episode!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
Eien nii
...forever!
It's terrible! Hekkun's in trouble!
Hekkun! Congratulations on your wedding!
Say what!?
I'm your bride, Bo-boko!
Wow, you're pretty!
NOT!
And now we pledge our eternal love...
Just look at Hekkun!
You do not look. You feel.
Honestly, you guys...
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
"Wedding at the Haunted House! Papa, Mama, I will be happy."
Wedding at the
Haunted House
Papa, Mama,
I will be happy
But Hekkun's in real trouble here!