Haunted House
Alright, let's go here next.
Sounds good.
I don't like haunted houses... Do we have to?
What the hell are you doing? Stop pushing me!
Watch who you're talking to!
We didn't come here for a good time!
Let's be serious here!
I'm sorry...
Here.
Don't let go! Don't let go!
Whatever you do, don't let go! Don't let go!
Is he scared?
HEKKUN!!!
Bo-bobo and friends have arrived at the haunted house
of A-block Captain: Tokoro Tennosuke's new base, Märchentic Amusement Park.
There, Beauty saw none other than Heppokomaru...
banged up like a dust rag.
Who is this mysterious man that banged up Heppokomaru?
The mystery will soon be revealed!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Translation:
SystematicChaos
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
angel_of_chaotix
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
denshousha
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Guess what? We were, like, in the haunted house,
And, you know, Heppokomaru got totally banged up! Isn't that hilarious?
And there was this guy that was like... White Kick... Rebad Reblue... MK5...
and is kinda like he's Chirami-ing! Yeah, kinda like that!
Gal-talk Analysis Mode
Allow me to explain this.
White Kick
Apathetic.
Rebad Reblue
Really Bad, Really Blue.
Man, he's gonna flip out in 5 seconds
Is kinda like he's Chirami-ing!
Yeah, kinda like that!
Um, this one says...
Is kinda like he's Chirami-ing!
Yeah, kinda like that!
Yeah, kinda like that! It means Yeah, kinda like that!
That's oldschool gal-talk!
More importantly...
What happened to... Hekkun?
On top of that...
Just who is he?
Wedding at the
Haunted House
Papa, Mama,
I will be happy
It all happened, a bit before Beauty came to the Haunted House.
Some haunted house this is.
There aren't even any ghosts.
Do you see anything?
Stop! You pervert!
You scoundrel.
It's already started.
So they were all here?
The star's finally here!
We've been waiting for you!
Huh?
Congratulations on your wedding!
You've done it, you lady-killer!
Wedding?
Hekkun, I wish you happiness in your life!
I'm gonna be married?
And now that the groom is here, the bride will now be entering!
Bride?
Hekkun!
She's gonna come out of here?
What do you think you're doing!?
Hekkun, do I look beautiful?
Why the hell are you asking me?
Go to her.
Tell her she's more beautiful, than anything in the world.
Hekkun...
Do I look beautiful?
Yes.
Really?
Oh man, it's getting hot in here.
I think I'm gonna burn.
And now we will begin Heppokomaru and Bo-bobo's wedding reception!
I'm your host, Don Patch! Now let's start this!
Who just attacked me from out of nowhere?
Hair Hunters A-block Deputy Captain Katsu
I'm A-Block Deputy Captain Katsu.
I'll be taking my revenge on you,
for beating up all my lackeys.
Damn you!
But how? My attack should have connected there!
So how is he unharmed?
Heppokomaru!
Could you tell us a bit about how you proposed?
Outta my way!
Thank you very much!
Now Bo-bobo, when he confessed,
"Outta my way! Ow! Ooh!," how did you answer him?
I said "Give me back my money..." and...
Oh, it's so embarrassing! I can't finish!
That's a very common pattern for a proposal, folks!
Now we will hear a congratulatory message, from their mutual friend!
OK, go right ahead with your message, Tea Soup Alien!
Tea Soup Alien
What on Earth is he doing here!?
I... It is a-an... h-h-onor to b-b-b-b-be h-here...
But isn't he
an evil alien!?
He's got stage fright!
Tea Soup Beam!
Allow me to explain.
Once someone is hit by the
Tea Soup Alien's Tea Soup Beam,
they have a sudden irresistible
urge to eat tea soup.
Tea... Tea...
I WANNA EAT TEA SOUP!
Here you go.
Bo-bobo... Heppokomaru... Congratulations!
Aren't you our enemy?
You finished yet?
Son of a...
Two!
What just happened?
That face just swallowed up my attack!
He...
He said those fishes were his lackeys...
It can't be! He's on a whole other level!
This is great. I've become much stronger through my training.
I'm not gonna stick around just to play wedding games!
Time to cut the cake!
Cu...Cut the cake... Cu...Cut the cake...
Cut the cake!
Fifth Prize
Mini Patches
Hekkun's! Hekkun's!
It's too dangerous! Get out of here!
I'm scared! I'm scared!
But, we can't give up now!
Nothing will happen if we run like cowards and hide!
We can't give up! We can't give up!
Eat the strawberry first! Eat the strawberry first!
This is too scary!
Help me, Mother! Mother!
You're not going to help them?
It's fine, honestly.
It's fine if they bite the dust.
All they kept doing was multiplying...
You should be more honest to yourself.
My children were 5th prize, dammit! 5th prize!
Don't you understand how I feel?
I do.
Goto
The name's Goto.
But something happened,
and next week he's gonna be Sato.
I was spoiled! I was too spoiled!
Children! Children!
Mother!
Children! I'm sorry, my children!
You don't need to worry anymore!
I'll promise that I'll never run away, anymore!
Mother!
Let's become one!
Children!
Combine!
God of Destruction, Zarbios!
God of Destruction, Zarbios
Zarbios is a lone hero, that was resurrected from the ancient ruins of Trinidad and Tobago...
And without anyone noticing, he fights against evil...
Politicians
For the peace and prosperity of the human race.
Monsters
Door-to-Door Salesmen
God of Destruction
ZARBIOS
Deep-fried Kabobs
Excuse me, sir! Double-dipping is not allowed!
Sorry! Sorry, sorry, so sorry, sorry, sorry, so sorry...
God of Destruction
ZARBIOS
Cut the cake!
Route 16 Turbo
Route 16...
Turbo!?
Let's stop playing around, and pick Beauty up.
Oh sorry, my bad.
So you didn't like my Route 16 Turbo?
Three!
I'll send it all back to you.
Three times over!
This guy ain't shit.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
And now the second half begins!
As you can see, Heppokomaru
got pretty banged up
by Katsu, the Deputy Captain of A-Block.
Yeah, this guy's Katsu.
Oh! You're that guy!
So why were you so scared of him?
What are you think you're doing?
I'll claim this as booty.
Hekkun!
What... What do you want?
These look nice.
Gimme them!
Ow! Ow!
Let me go!
You won't get away with this, bastard!
You damn fashion freak!
Hey, it's connected!
Gotcha!
Noodle House
I'm catering here!
Three plates of dry buckwheat noodles coming through!
Hey! Hey! Let me through!
Move it! I'm catering here!
We've been making buckwheat noodles for 38 years, 4 months and 65 days...
Have a taste of the buckwheat noodles,
hand-made with our burning booger souls.
This is... This is...
This is for you.
You've got some nice sunglasses there.
Gimme them.
I'll be taking those sunglasses.
Fist of the Nose Hair!
I am Kanagawa Prefecture's
Sakurayama Vocational School Senior
Defense Club Captain, Kaneda Tatsuji!
Bo-bobo, now that the
Sakurayama Defense Club is here
you don't need to worry.
We'll show you the top defense of the nation!
Sakurayama Vocational! Sakurayama Vocational!
Kaneda... Do your best!
Bring it on then!
Sakurayama Defense Club...
You have much to learn, young one.
You do not see...
You feel.
Ikeda!
Ouch!
Miyamae! Oshida!
That's quite a useful technique.
It's 5-0...
If I can pull off a back stretch one side step from the back corner...
We may be able to turn the tables!
Sakurayama Vocational! Sakurayama Vocational!
Sakurayama Vocational!
Ikeda and Miyamae have both
been accepted into university...
Oshida has found a job...
But this is all I have!
As this will be my last summer!
Trash Can
Now bring it!
I won't lose! I'll never lose!
As long as I have this victory charm my manager gave me...
Traffic Safety
I'll never be hurt by cars!
Wait... Traffic Safety!?
He went along with the joke...
And so, my summer was finally over.
Hello?
Congratulations! It's a boy!
Is it... Because of my charm?
Hurry up and help him...
Hurry up and take him to the hospital!
I got 'em!
Hey, hey!
What just happened? Was that his aura?
I can't get the goldfish!
Let's go home, Dad!
Too late!
Out of my way!
Dad! Dad!
Don't get carried away!
Goldfish! Goldfish!
Dad!
I'm going to go all out.
Come and get it!
You're dead!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Stress-Relieving Fist!
That's it!
Harder than that! Much harder than that!
That hurts! That hurts!
Stop it! Stop it!
Alright! Stress relieved!
Hey! Don Patch, you fool, take a look at this!
What are you doing, Bo-bobo?
Don Patch will get really mad at you!
You're not getting mad?
Beauty was thinking,
"This Don Patch is ticking me off."
It hit me.
It sure did.
Fist of the Nose Hair!
Bo-bobo!
That's...
my afro!
Hey, that was dangerous!
You're not giving up, are you?
Hekkun!
Hekkun... What's going on, Hekkun?
A rose?
Babu?
What's this!? This is a very sudden transformation!
Just what has happened to Heppokomaru after rising from the ashes?
Could he be...
The legendary Rose Warrior...
That only comes to the World once every 15 billion years?
Is Heppokomaru that very same warrior?
Hekkun...
U...uh... The Rose Warrior that saved the World...
From a galactic wave...
Is Heppokomaru that very same warrior?
That legend doesn't exist!
In the language of flowers, roses mean "Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo."
What's going on, Hekkun!?
That's not what roses mean!
You see, I snapped back for you.
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
Eien nii
...forever!
What's happened to Hekkun?
He's a bit different from normal.
Has Heppokomaru finally awakened?
Huh?
As a Hajikelist?
That's not possible!
By the way, where's Tokoro Tennosuke?
We gotta find him soon!
You're gonna keep him to yourself?
That's mean, Beauty. He's a snack for all of us!
He's no snack!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique!
Tokoroten Gun Explodes!
But I don't taste anything
I don't even care!