Son of a...
That's two!
That's three!
Hair Hunters A-block: Deputy Captain Katsu
Heppokomaru was in a predicament,
as his new enemy Katsu kept
absorbing all of his attacks.
Meanwhile, Beauty was starting to worry about him.
You're not giving up, are you?
However...
With the scent of a beautiful red rose blooming in the fields,
Heppokomaru stood up again!
A rose?
Time to cut the cake!
Cu...Cut the cake... Cu...Cut the cake...
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo was
cutting a cake at Don Patch.
Even after everything
that had happened in this journey,
she had never anticipated anything like this...
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
NyKaMuRa
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
GonbeFAN
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble
Secret Technique!
Tokoroten Gun Explodes!
But I don't taste anything
Hekkun!
Hekkun...
A rose?
What? What is it?
Hekkun, what's got into you?
SKID!
Don Patch!
No, I don't want that thing!
I told you, I don't want it!
Ya dirty brat!
D
R
I
P
Water?
Don Patch!
Please plant me.
When the spring wind blows,
a new life is born.
When the summer sun shines,
a red flower blooms.
A fruit in the color of the earth will grow in autumn.
And in winter, a new Don Patch will be born.
SPLAT
Save me over here, Bo-bobo!
Leave this one to me.
He's opening up!
Afro Unit, roll out!!
Go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Attack!
Pencils?
Fall back!
Attack!
Bo-bobo's the engineer!
Who's the conductor around here?
Well, Bo-bobo sure likes his trains...
Hekkun! Behind you!
Hekkun! Look behind you!
Wh-What's going on?
That was incredible, Hekkun! You're amazing!
Over here, my little boy!
Come over here, Hekkun!
Come on, come on...
That's it! Just like that! One foot at a time!
Look, you're walking! Look, you're walking!
Look, you're walking!
There, there. Good boy.
Are you alright there, Don Patch?
CRUNCH CRUNCH
I'm perfectly fine. Don't raise your voice.
He's just a little frightened.
Now that he knows I'm here, he'll settle down, and it'll all be fine.
You don't have to be afraid. I'm on your side.
There's nothing to be scared of.
Attack!
What do you think you're playing at, Bo-bobo?
Oh crap, I'm outta here!
What's happened to Hekkun?
And what's making him act like this?
Hey, over here.
Yo!
What are you meant to be?
Who, me? I'm a collar.
A collar?
Maybe he's my collar.
Not on your damn life!
That was uncalled for...
So... what are you doing?
Heppokomaru's Collar
It's all my fault that Heppokomaru's been acting this way.
What do you mean?
Here, I'll explain it all to you.
Heppokomaru's techniques,
are so powerful, that it can take a huge toll on himself.
You mean like a double-edged sword?
When he releases his full strength...
his personality changes into something completely different.
Yeah, that might explain why his techniques are so powerful.
And so, I'm there to make sure that his full power is sealed off.
So that means, he'll turn back to his normal self
if you're returned back to his neck!
So it's all cause and effect.
You see the word "seal" on my back?
Not really.
By the word "seal" written on my back,
I must ensure that I seal his power within him.
But it doesn't say "seal" anywhere.
Missie...
You better make sure that you do not tell Heppokomaru about me.
Alright!
Now I can seal him without any more worries or concerns!
Attack!
Hey! You attackin' bastard! I finally found ya!
Oh, goddammit!
I have you now!
Yogurt
But what if I give you this?
No deal!
Hey, hold it! Hold it, you attackin' bastard!
You won't get away from me!
This time...
I'll kill you!
December!
This is nothing! I'll absorb it all!
That was... too much...
Hey! Stop right there, you bastard!
He just won't stop!
You're never gonna catch us!
I said halt this instant!
Glad to see you safe, missie!
Are you ready?
We'll make sure that we seal his power this time!
Go for it!
He's back to normal!
But he had quite the expression back there...
What just... happened to me?
It's alright now, Hekkun.
You're the Hekkun you're supposed to be.
The me I'm supposed to be...
I see.
Yo!
You seen Don Patch anywhere?
He went to the bathroom.
Oh. I see.
It's an emergency! It's an emergency! It's an emergency!
It's an emergency! It's an emergency!
It's non-stop... It's non-stop kitties...
I beg of you...
Stop this madness and let me eat my spaghetti in peace...
AHHHHHHHHHHHH!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
AHHHHHHHHHHHH!
That sounded like, Don Patch!
What do you think happened?
Alright! Let's roll out!
Is Bo-bobo still acting like a car?
Is everything alright, Don Patch?
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
They're doing Purukogi !
Move it! Move it! Move it! Move it!
Move it!
MOVE IT!
Move it! Move it! Move it! Move it!
What was that for!?
Why the hell were you in the men's room!?
You little peeping tom!
Well, who was the one dressed like a princess?
Leave me! Just leave me alone!
And you just turned into a girl, again!?
Why you...
I know that! You think I didn't know that!?
Why'd you bring it up?
There are times that I don't want to hear it!
Why can't you understand a simple thing like that?
Okay, okay... If leaving will make you happy...
That's right! Leaving will make me happy! Leaving will make me happy!
Memorie
Manor
Hmph!
If Tomohiro's here with us, that must mean that Tokoro Tennosuke is nearby.
It won't stop raining cats...
Where is Tokoro Tennosuke hiding!?
Alright! Let's search the washroom together!
Okay!
Not here...
Where could he be?
Maybe he's here?
Stop standing around, and help us find Tokoro Tennosuke.
He's right.
You better start listening to Tokoro Tennosuke.
That's right, get going!
But aren't you... Tokoro Tennosuke?
Why'd you have to say that?
I know that I'm Tokoro Tennosuke...
But can't we all look for
Tokoro Tennosuke together?
We don't need to look,
because you're right there.
That was low! How could you doubt Tokoro Tennosuke?
Eh!?
But isn't he the Tokoro Tennosuke?
Multivitamin...
C! C! C!
So are you Tokoro Tennosuke?
Multivitamin...
C! C! C! C!
And what are you going to do about it?
Multivitamin...
C! C! C! C! C! C! C! C! C! C!
Keep
the
Toilets
Clean
I'm taking you down!
You guys need your calcium too!
What an amazing aura! I've never seen Bo-bobo like this before!
How much stronger can he really be?
Oh? So you say you'll take me, Tokoro Tennosuke, down?
Sounds great. I'll have some entertainment.
Time to dig in!
Help yourself to ginger and horseradish!
That's a fine texture! You're tasty!
YOU'RE TASTY!!!
Isn't that right? Can you taste it?
What an amazing battle!
There's no room for both of them to jump!
It was in the middle of this fierce clash, that Tokoro Tennosuke
realised something very important.
"I'm... being eaten!"
Bo-bobo also realised something else that was very important.
"Tokoroten tastes a lot better with citrus sauce than with soy sauce."
I left my citrus sauce at home...
I don't feel anything here... Did he eat that part?
Bo-bobo is regretting leaving his citrus sauce at home!
Is that so?
I can tell. I know at least this much.
Citrus Sauce
That's right. I can tell too.
Is that so, my fellow understander?
Take the citrus sauce!
Alright, Don Patch!
Citrus sauce? Is this some kind of joke?
Time to retreat!
Citrus Sauce
You're no citrus sauce!
Maybe, I should open up a pet store.
What a cute kitty-cat.
Hold your jellies!
Now you can't do a damn thing to me!
You fiend!
How dare she keep it all for herself!
Yeah, what you said!
Not on my watch!
I'll put an end to your hoarding!
Now I'm in the tokoroten! Suckers!
That's it! Good work! Leave the rest to me!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Soy Sauce Injection Fist!
Alright, Don Patch! Indulge in the sauce!
It stings! The soy sauce stings!
Don Patch!
Is this high quality soy sauce, by any chance?
Oh, how did you know?
It stings! It sti-sti-sti-sti-
I don't care!
Oh, don't care!
Don't care, don't care!
Huh?
What are you  talking about?
You really are retarded, aren't you?
The games are over!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Gun!
Have a taste of that!
How does my tokoroten taste?
Like lychee.
L-L-L-L-Lychee!?
No way! That can't be true!
It's true. You taste of lychee.
You're right! I do  taste like lychee!
Lychee! Lychee! Ly-Lychee!
Lychee!
Okay! Daddy's gonna go look for lychees!
Take care! Take care!
Good luck, Daddy!
Shut up, ya dumb brat!
I never said ya were allowed to talk casually to me!
What was that? Ya lookin' fer a fight, ya geezer?
Who do ya think yer talkin' to, ya good-for-nothin' punk?
Want a pummeling?
Let's see you can even try that on me...
Senior!
Please stop fighting!
Please stop fighting... over me!
Eight-headed Serpent!
Sounds great! Bring it on!
It's already been brought to the table!
Oh, is that so?
Hello?
I'll kick your ass!
Well, go on then!
Stop it, you two! No more snacks for you!
NO MORE SNACKS
What's this meant to be? An old movie?
Father...
Your head's in the way and I can't see the TV...
Trust your dreams to the blue sky. Coming soon:
"No More Snacks."
FIN
We're so sorry!
We're sorry! Just please don't
take our snacks away!
Well, kids will always be kids.
Okay! Have some tokoroten for a snack!
What? Again?
Don't be so picky!
I'm... being eaten!
You guys are so cruel! Why are you ganging up on me together?
I'm one serving! I'm only one serving!
I won't be enough for you both to eat me!
I'm insufficient! I'm so insufficient!
You're a fool.
I can make you complete.
You're not Byoune, by any chance, are you?
SPLAT
Here. Have some konjac.
AHHH
Don't move around too much, otherwise it'll fall.
T-Thank you...
Wriggle Wriggle
But... but... but... but...
But, what?
Wriggle Wriggle
I know you just made me complete and all, but...
I'm... actually...
What? Go ahead and say it.
I'm...
I'm not konjac!
You're not konjac?
I'm not. I'm sorry for not telling you this.
So you're... not konjac?
Then...
What are you?
I'm...
I'm actually...
A GODDAMN TOKOROTEN!!!
Not only that, but I'm also your sworn enemy!
ENEMY
What!?
Eat this!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Eight-Headed Serpent Fist!
Tokoro Tennosuke
was indeed Bo-bobo's enemy!
But we already knew that from the beginning!
By the way, is tokoroten tastier
with citrus sauce, or horseradish and soy sauce? Or how about mustard and soy sauce?
Frankly, that depends on personal taste!
And by the way...
I prefer it with brown sugar syrup!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Eat this! Fist of the Wobble Wobble: Eight-headed Serpent Fist!
In that case... Ma-ma Defence!
Bo-bobo! This is a fearsome foe!
You should be serious about this!
Alright, Don Patch! We're gonna combine!
I said, stop playing around!
Sounds great.
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Fusion!
F-F-F-Fusion!?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Farewell to our foe
Tokoro Tennosuke!
Good evening to our new foe
Dengakuman!
Just what is a "Bobopatch"!?