Bo-bobo and friends had been searching for Hair Hunters' A-block Captain, Tokoro Tennosuke.
Heppokomaru had been revived, bearing a rose in his mouth.
But he was Hajike-ing more than usual.
Beauty had managed to risk her life...
to re-attach Heppokomaru's sealing collar back on him.
And now the two Fist users are locked down in a harsh amusement park showdown!
Bo-bobo and Don Patch began their battle with their fated rival, Tokoro Tennosuke.
Only God knows how this showdown will end!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Translation:
SystematicChaos
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
angel_of_chaotix
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
(Like a Phatman)
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Farewell to our foe
Tokoro Tennosuke!
Good evening to our new foe
Dengakuman!
Not only that, but I'm also your sworn enemy!
You're what!?
We already know that... you dummy!
Eat this!
Eight-Headed Serpent Fist!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
That's nothing! Fist of the Nose Hair: Ma-ma Defense!
Ma-Ma Defense
Ma! Ma! Ma!
Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma!
Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma!
He's moving too quickly AND he's starting to annoy me!
Get lost!
Alright, I'll start with you!
Ca! Ca! Ca!
Ca! Ca! Ca! Ca!
Ca! Ca! Ca! Ca! Ca! Ca! Ca!
Copycat! Stop copying me!
Ma
But after ''Ma'' comes ''Ca''!
Ca
Ro! Ro! Ro!
Ro
And after ''Ca'' comes ''Ro''!
Ma! Ma!
Ca! Ca!
Ro! Ro!
Just one more letter and the word's complete!
Ma
Ca
Ro
Now it's Beauty's turn! It's your turn!
Huh? My turn?
Say the last letter! The last letter!
Ma... Ca... Ro...
What comes after that?
The next letter! The next letter!
''N''?
Macaron
It's Macaron!
I am Macaron!
Now I'm satisfied. I don't care if I die anymore.
I'm really really, happy!
I think I might just...
melt...
I'm so happy!
Bo-bobo! Now's your perfect chance!
The enemy's melted! Get him while he's down!
Fine... if it makes you happy...
You weren't wrong at all, Hekkun! Trust me, you really weren't!
Tokoro Tennosuke!
It's time I show you the only fusion technique in the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Fusion Technique?
F-F-F-F-F-F-F-
F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-Fusion!!?
Fusion!!?
Let's do this, Don Patch!
O.K.!
Transform!
Impressive mechanics!
Candy ball
Candy ball!
Candy ball!?
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique
Bo-bobo Fusion!!!!!
Bo-bobo Fusion!
It's happening! It's happening! It's happening!
Somegoro! Somegoro!
What's he doing? What's he gonna do?
Somegoro! Somegoro! Somegoro!
Fusion complete.
Who is that?
My name is Bobopatch.
BOBOPATCH
And I can only remain in this form for one minute.
So let's get this battle over with.
That's Bo-bobo and Don Patch fused together?
He feels kinda different...
Alright then, bring it on!
Eat this! Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique:
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble
Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Rocket!!!!
Tokoroten Rocket!
He's not bad.
Incredible!
He's actually pretty cool!
Be on your guard, Beauty!
We have a strong enemy here.
But you're the enemy, here!
I can't let fight go on forever.
Now that it's come to this, I'll use that technique to bring him to my pace!
Now... Follow along! Follow along!
What an intense battle! It's so intense!
Quit screwing around. Be serious about this fight.
Ow! I broke my leg! It hurts so bad!
C-Call an ambulance! I'm dying! I'm gonna die!
Now, Bo-bobo, make a comeback! Say "There's no way a tokoroten can break its leg!"
It'll be over once you say that and you'll be stuck at my pace!
Now, fall for my trap!
Fall for it!
Now, fall for it!
What the heck?
There's no way a tokoroten can break its leg.
He didn't fall for it!!!
You son of a bitch!
What do you think you're doing to my boy?
Mom!
As my consciousness faded away...
I saw an image of myself...
Prime Minister
I saw myself as prime minister,
TOKOROTENISM
as I declared tokoroten to be the staple dish.
Tokorotenism!
Are you quite finished? Then it's time I take the lead.
He's acting much more different than the other two...
What kind of attack will he use?
Don Patch Sword!
That's a leek!
You're kidding me! I never imagined I'd see it here!
That's the legendary Don Patch Sword!
It all ends now!
It's a radish!
Your luck has ran out!
The Evil Radish Blade!
The Evil Radish Blade is a mythical sword,
said to be wielded long ago by the legendary swordsman Garius...
Why are you even explaining it?
I won't lose! I can't lose to him!
If I do, I'll have to go back to the way things were!
Hey! Come on in!
Supermarket
Today we have our big monthly sale!
So come on in, folks!
Mama! I want that one!
Sure thing.
Yay!
Now I just need to grab some tokoroten.
Tokoroten
Found it! I'll just take one...
Tokoro Tennosuke
So, you cooking some tokoroten tonight, ma'am?
N-No, not really.
You know, right now I'm at half price...
No thanks, I'm fine.
Ma'am...
I said, no thank you!
Tokoro Tennosuke
Maybe I should've dropped it to 50...
Tennosuke...
you still haven't been sold yet?
Well, I guess not.
You messed up the counter yet again...
Tokoro Tennosuke
You do realize that I have to clean up the mess?
Well, isn't that what part-timers are for?
Oh, that reminds me.
The manager said he wanted to see you.
He said that?
I'm sure you already know this, but I'm not doing volunteer work here.
Our customers are having a hard time buying tokoroten, and that's driving them away.
I hate to say this, but you're fired.
fired... fired... fired...
What am I even... doing?
I'll never... I'll never go back to the way things were!
If I lose...
If I lose to you...
I'll be a dead weight to our business!
You can't take my position away from me!
Chemistry!
Chemistry
I don't want to go back to the way things were...
Mama! There's something stuck on the window!
Do not avert your eyes.
That is the way of a man. You must live by it!
It's over.
They're back to normal!
And then, the Radish Blade, now evil,
was sealed with the Carrot Sword in the Demonic Realm.
Why are you still explaining that!?
Great, my makeup's messed up!
You've been acting real weird lately, Hekkun!
Weird?
Yeah, weird!
I was acting weird?
Bo-bobo, you're so strong, I'm really jealous of you.
That's cause you're a small fry, Tenjiro.
Tokoro Tenjiro
I want to be a policeman when I grow up!
Young Bo-bobo
That'll never happen.
I hate bad people!
I can't excuse them!
So if I ever become a bad guy in the future,
I want you to stop me, Bo-bobo!
Yeah, sure. I'll plaster you onto a ferris wheel or something.
You promise?
I've fulfilled my promise, Tenjiro!
You got the wrong Tokoroten!
Now that A-Block Base has fallen...
Hair Hunters Z-block Base
We can't just ignore this Bo bo bobo bo...
Damn, what a stupid name to pronounce!
Z-block Trooper A
But, no matter how hard he tries,
we still have the man with the ducktail.
Z-block Trooper B
Right, Captain?
Hair Hunters Z-block Captain Dengakuman
TL Note: Dengaku is grilled tofu dipped in miso on a stick
Let's make them eat dengaku, nah-la!
He's so cute...
That's why everybody loves Dengakuman!
Nah-la-la-la!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
Family Restaurant
After changing Tokoro Tennosuke's life forever,
Bo-bobo and friends decided to think about their own future, and started job hunting.
You find anything yet?
Get your own copy.
By the way, I heard that Tanaka was laid off recently.
Seriously?
Hey, find anything good yet?
Nope, not yet.
Damn, it's hard to find a good job these days...
Did you find something?
Here we go!
Hair Hunters
Now Recruiting!!
for you!
We're waiting
let's crush
together!
Bo-bobo
It looks like the Hair Hunters are recruiting!
The Hair Hunters...
This is it! This is perfect! You even get two days off per week!
But that's from the Hair Hunters!
Plus, you get a year's paid vacation if you crush Bo-bobo!
But YOU'RE Bo-bobo!
Alright. This will do.
Well, good for you.
Hold up!
How long... do you think you're gonna keep up this lifestyle?
Why don't you just settle down for once?
Hey, hey!
Again with the preaching? Gimme a fuckin' break, man.
Why, you...
I'm worried about you, man.
That hurts! Get off me, asshole!
Take your feelings and shove it!
You may be fine with it, but if this keeps up,
then what's gonna happen to poor Bo-bomi?
You need to rethink this...
Sorry, but...
You're really boring the hell outta me.
Smell ya later!
Don Patch!
Don Patch...
What's going on? Just what's going on?
I'm home.
Welcome home, Patchie!
Bo-bomi
Just wait a little bit longer.
I'll have dinner ready in no time.
Oh...
by the way, I met up with Bo-bobo today.
Who might thou be?
Saturday Night is the Bo-bobo Movie
No more talk!
Oh, did he say anything?
He mentioned that I should find some work!
Isn't that hilarious?
What's wrong? It's funny, right?
Patchie, do you really want to marry me?
W-Where'd that come from?
I mean, of course I do!
Stop lying!
You're nothing but talk, Patchie!
If you really want to marry me, at least find a job!
But haven't I already told you?
I'm gonna be a guitarist!
You're lying! I've never seen you play the guitar!
Besides, that thing in your room you keep calling a guitar...
That's not a guitar
That's not a guitar... That's butter!!!!
That's butter!!!!
And that butter's gonna melt in the summer and make a mess!
You should just throw it out!
What the hell is your problem, huh?
I can't trust you. I can't trust you anymore, Patchie!
Bo-bomi!
Goodbye!
How long are you gonna keep this up?
Just a bit longer...
This episode's getting way too long.
I know...
It's still going on...
Bo-bomi...
I was just finished talking to Bo-bomi.
It sounds like you guys broke up.
Now that she's gone, I've got nothing else in my life.
Aren't I a joke?
You can laugh at me if you want.
I won't laugh.
Really now...
You're probably laughing at me on the inside anyway...
Just go away! Why did you come here anyway?
I made you a resume.
I came so that you can change, today.
I'll give you a helping hand with all this.
Isn't that what friends are for?
Can I change? Can I really change?
Can I really change?
N-O!
N!
N
O!
O
He's going down...
So what about the Hair Hunters?
Just let them go at it until they're tired.
And so, the day of the Hair Hunters Entrance Exam arrived.
You're looking pretty sharp, Don Patch.
Keep your cool.
Today, I'm officially a new man.
Alright. Let's go!
O.K.!
There they go.
Entrance Hall
This
way
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
Mysterious Person
It's that bastard!
You know him?
So he's still alive...
National Youth Shogi Tournament
I was once a genius Shogi player...
with great hopes for the future...
Everyone expected my name to go down in legend.
That is... until HE showed up.
So, let's begin this game.
One-move... checkmate!
I concede defeat!
And so, my life as a Shogi player was over.
I wanna get my driver's license...
Even though I already have one...
Your door's open.
It really is. Thanks for that.
We will now move on to the interviews.
Those whose names have been called out, please head to the next room.
Empoyment Interviews
The first thing we'll ask you, will be about your current skills.
Novice Examiner Pagiya
Mr. Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo, we'll start with you.
Yes, sir.
Um... my skill is...
Saying "Ahhh!" in front of a fan.
I practice three times a week in summer, and twice a week in winter.
And by the way, in last year's contest...
57th Annual Saying "Ahhh" in Front of a Fan Contest Second Place
I got second place!
There's even a contest?
Yes, it normally happens once a year at the beach during summer time.
But you know... I wouldn't exactly call that a useful skill, Bo-bobo.
Right, Senior Examiner?
Senior Examiner
Grand Prize
He got the GRAND PRIZE!?
Junior Examiner
Oh also, I came in third place.
Not you, too!
Third Place
To be honest, I did too...
57th Place
57th Place?
That's really lame!
You're worthless!
You guys are mean!
Sorry about that. But you don't have to cry.
Let's move on to Don Patch.
Please tell us what your current skills are.
I am an expert guitarist.
Could you play us a tune?
Of course.
Bo-bomi... No matter what I told you...
Butter
This is all I have.
Just watch me, Bo-bomi! See how I've changed!
What will you be playing, today?
I will sing "Wild Challenger".
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Come and fly away!
Step on it!
He's still tone-deaf.
Bomb it!
Go! Go! Tricky style!
Hurry and hit the gong!
Wild! Wild! Wild! Wild challenger!
Don't stop! Don't stop! Don't stop!
Let my feelings reach them.
That is all.
Clean this mess up.
They didn't reach them...
They reached him!
I got trash in my eye!
He's old... But he's still a child.
Moving right along, please tell us your current skills.
Yes. I'm currently skillful at...
this!
I'm under orders to eliminate the Hair Hunters.
If you bastards wanna live, you better take me to the top brass.
Put down your gun. If you don't, I'll kill you with this butter.
Not so fast, Don Patch!
Watch this!
That's a lot of canned food...
Grilled Chicken
Take one more step, and they'll all go BOOM!
Oh, no!
Take whatever you were reaching for, and put it on the fuckin' desk!
I still haven't finished it...
The Tortoise and the Hare
And I was so desperate to know how the race would end that I...
He killed him!
Didn't I tell you not to move? Dumbass!
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to eat all these cans of grilled chicken!
Idiot! If you do that...
If you do that...
Grilled Chicken
You'll want some rice, won't you?
Give Me Carbohydrates!!!!!
Come on! Turn the page! Turn the page!
Just a second.
You gotta wake up, Mr. Rabbit!
What's with that door?
Hair Hunters Management Room
Is this the big shot's room?
Please knock
What was that sound?
Excuse me.
Hold it, solid fuel.
Did you just call me solid fuel?
If we just barge in, we could be in big trouble. We'll get more than just burned.
Burned?
Oh I get it, I'm solid fuel, so that's why you said burned.
If my intuition serves me right, there's a man waiting in that room.
The real reason I came here was to meet that man.
In here?
What the...
What's wrong?
What's this?
T-There's someone on his ducktail!!
That's way too long!
Is this the guy Bo-bobo was talking about?
T... That's...
Who is this mysterious ducktailed man
who's acting all important?
And what is his relationship to Bo-bobo?
Long time no see, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
What is he doing here?
No way! He uses his nose hairs too! Who is he?
He's a cute little octopus!
No way, that's disgusting!
Nice-chu!
I can't depend on you two anymore!
Then should I call them?
Twirly-twirl and Wobbly-wobble, right?
You don't mean...
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Ducktail
Ducktail vs Afro! Eternal Rival of the Purest Sect
Afro!
Eternal Rival of the
Purest Sect!
And I'm of the innocent sect!