Tokoro Tennosuke had been fired by the manager of the supermarket.
And his rage clashed with Bobopatch.
Chemistry
Bo-bobo and Don Patch began thinking of their own future and were looking for work.
Yes, sir.
Um... my skill is...
Saying "Ahhh!" in front of a fan.
Hurry and hit the gong!
Wild! Wild! Wild! Wild challenger!
Don't stop! Don't stop! Don't stop!
Let my feelings reach them...
That is all.
You're the best, Patchie!
As he played his heart out for Bo-bomi, Don Patch's full-house concert
was a big hit!
A full-house concert? When did this happen?
Mr. Patch
Dressing Room
However, in the dressing room,
a man was patiently waiting for Bo-bobo!
Long time no see, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Just who on earth is this ducktailed guy?
And what is his relationship to Bo-bobo?
A new fated battle is about to begin!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
It's morning...?
I gotta get to work or else...
What the hell's this?
Oh, right! I guess I fell asleep on a ducktail! That scared me for a second.
Hey! Let's get to work!
My bad. I fell asleep on a ducktail again.
How many times has this happened to you now?
The wife's gonna be real mad at me!
Bo-bobo... Or maybe I should say,
my eternal rival,
Heir of the Fist of the Nose Hair, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
That's the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Who is this guy, Bo-bobo?
His name is Battleship.
Just like me, he also uses the Fist of the Nose Hair.
However, because he uses the Fist of the Nose Hair for the sake of evil,
he was eternally exiled from the Nose Hair Dojo.
I never thought he'd still be alive...
Long time no see, Bo-bobo.
Or maybe I should say, my eternal lover,
of the purest sect from birth, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
He stuck jump ropes in his nose!
Who is that guy, Bo-bobo?
I have absolutely no idea!
Take this! Fist of the Nose Hair!
What the hell are you doing?
Fist of the Nose Hair?
Alright you dumb brat, hold it right there!
What were the odds of me seeing you here?
Looks like fate has guided us to fight to the death.
Ducktail
Afro
Eternal Rival of the
Purest Sect!
Bo-bobo...
If I remember correctly, this was the day we first met.
Ducktails
Afros
The Ducktails are already down to their boss.
Let's beat the shit outta him!
Goddamn you, Afros...
Ducktail Attack!
Are you OK there?
I'm alright... I don't know who you are or where you're from, but you saved my life.
Thanks for that.
THAT'S JUST RIDICULOUS!!!
W... What are you...?
Who, me? I'm just a passing ducktail.
Think of me as a hardcore ducktail through and through.
And I can't stand afros or any other hairstyles.
They're just not cool enough.
Is that so...?
Huh? Who's this guy you found?
Dunno, I've only just met him.
Another one?
That's a pretty fine ducktail you got there!
It really is!
I'm surrounded by ducktails!
Lemme get a closer look!
Me too!
I-I can't breathe...
Hey, how do you treat it?
What shampoo? Which conditioner?
How long does it take to set?
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna be crushed by ducktails!
It's the master!
Ducktail! Ducktail!
Oh, good boys!
That must be...
I knew by the shape of your hair that you were the Afro boss.
Pardon me. I believe that my ducktails were bothering you, weren't they?
I take it that you're the Afro boss?
Who do you think you're fucking with, keeping ducktails as pets?
Compared to the Afros, Ducktails are nothing but dogs.
How much can you, a Ducktail, struggle these days?
He also uses the Fist of the Nose Hair!
The heavens must have decided to let this happen.
Then you must be the 7th rightful successor to the Fist of the Nose Hair.
Take this! Fist of the Nose Hair: Ducktail Attack!
Fist of the Nose Hair: Ducktail Attack
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair:            Mermaid Lagoon
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair: Mermaid Lagoon!
You better understand that you aren't the only one who knows the Fist of the Nose Hair.
What's this?
Risuo and
Risumi
Three months after Risuo and Risumi broke up...
Risukichi
Risuo's senior
Risuo, you should get out there and grab yourself a girlfriend!
Do you still have that other girl in your head?
Risuo
Not really, I'm completely over her now.
You were so sad when she dumped you. You were like... "Risumi!"
I was young and foolish back then.
Besides, real men don't cry when their girl dumps them!
Risuo, you've really have matured!
Risumi...
Risujiro
Risumi
Risujiro...
RISUMI!!!!
So you're also a master of the Fist of the Nose Hair?
Since I've been expelled from the Nose Hair Dojo,
I've developed my own style of the Fist of the Nose Hair.
I'll just tell you, that my Fist of the Nose Hair
isn't as easygoing as yours.
I'll crush you!
And so, Bo-bobo and I fought for three days and three nights straight.
You're pretty good.
So are you.
My name's Battleship. What's yours?
Battleship
It's Flowerman.
Flowerman
And so, after Bo-bobo and I gave it our all,
a friendship bloomed between us.
Wait, is that Bo-bobo?
Soon, we became best friends and did everything together.
That looks good on you!
But one morning...
It's already morning?
Flowerman!
I've made a big mistake...
I've been dragged into the Flower Wars without even realizing it.
Flower Wars
I have a request for you, Battleship...
Please... Please plant this for me...
I'll leave it... to you...
Flowerman!!!
Flowerman's dead at last!
Now the Flower Kingdom is ours for the taking!
Blue-eyed Lambda!
You fiends...
Now that you've laid your hands on us, you're done for!
The Dark Flower King will soon eventually kill you...
Ever since then, the Dark Flower King has been after my life.
But who's Flowerman?
Dammit! We failed!
Shit!
Run for it!
God damn!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique: Jump Rope
Tango down!
Now that's been explained, why are you fighting the Hair Hunters?
That's a long story. But in short, I'm crushing the Hair Hunters in the name of justice.
You're not fooling anybody!
He's one of the Four Lords of Margarita!
What?
Four Lords of Margarita
Four Lords of Margarita?
No. I'm just an octopus!
Quit making stuff up, asshole!
There's no way he's anything but an octopus!
It's true! It's really true!
I know this because...
He's the guy that destroyed my hometown!
Wait, what? Did you really do that?
No, no. I'm still an octopus.
Quit making shit up, fuckin' brat!
That octopus' story doesn't match up to yours!
You wanna go back to being the Mystery Boy or something?
I'm telling you the truth!
Bo-bobo!
Hekkun wouldn't lie to us! You should listen to him!
The fuck did you say!?
You can't fuckin' tell us what to do!
What's with you guys?
They're really being hard on her today...
That loincloth...
You recognized it, Heppokomaru?
What have you done to my friend?
It all happened half a year ago.
Half a Year Ago
Heppokomaru's hometown Puppuu City, was all but devastated.
Puppuu City
It seems like we're the only ones left.
I know.
That ducktail guy is no laughing matter.
Heppokomaru!
Loincloth Taro
At this rate, Puppuu city will be no more!
You must find someone who can save the city!
Get a move on!
But Taro...
There they are!
We've been found!
I accept your challenge!
Now go, Heppokomaru!
The splendorous Loincloth Assassination Art...
Helicopter!
Loincloth Assassination Art: Helicopter
Now get going, Heppokomaru!
Let this red loincloth dance bid you farewell!
Taro... You'd even do the red loincloth dance for my sake?
Thank you for everything!
Did you... Did you do Taro in!?
Well, he did refuse to become one of us.
Or rather, we got rid of him cause he pissed us off.
If I remember correctly, you did refuse to join us as well.
You bastard!
Suzu
Lord Battleship,
I have destroyed Hair Hunters B-block as you ordered.
Dollman
No way! That girl destroyed B-block base all by herself?
Nice-chu! Nice-chu! Nice-chu!
Thank you for the kind words.
Now the Hair Hunters are almost all destroyed.
The day my dreams come true draws ever closer...
Battleship, I've been wanting to ask you this:
Aren't you one of the Four Lords of Margarita?
So why are you crushing the Hair Hunters?
Sure. I'll tell you the reason why.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
It's true that I became one of the Four Lords of Margarita.
But that was no more than the first step of my plan.
My real plan was to sneak in and usurp the Margarita Empire!
Thankfully, the Margarita Empire only requires the Hair Hunters to be bald.
Which made the infiltration a peace of cake!
After I became one of the Four Lords,
my next step was to get rid of the Hair Hunters.
But then I heard you were destroying the Hair Hunters too.
I then thought that would be my big break!
So if I destroyed a few Hair Hunter blocks, you would've taken all the blame.
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
Hey, young lady...
DON'T YOU DARE LOOK DOWN ON ME!!!
Look out!
S... Sorry...
Thank you!
You're really are kind, Hekkun.
He's completely worthless.
Beauty
That dumb girl! She's so annoying!
Grudge
Why is she getting so lovestruck?
Look at me! I want you to look at me!
Heppokomaru... Could it be that you're in love with that girl?
W-What are you talking about?
You're in love with her, aren't you?
You're in love!
Shut up! She has nothing to do with this!
Go right ahead, Dollman.
That's so evil of you, Lord Battleship!
You just love disrupting peoples' love!
Chips
Man, these chips are salty.
My, talk about a premium doll!
Well, if the original is cheap, so is the doll!
Get... Get... Get off me...
Change her back this instant!
Fine! I get it! Don't get so mad! I'll change her back!
Don't trust him, Heppokomaru!
Grab Beauty's doll before he does!
Sorry about that, Heppokomaru!
But he doesn't have the power to change her back!
Bo-bobo, Heppokomaru.
If you want her back, come to my Pomade Ring fortress.
Fortress?
Pomade Ring?
You should be glad, Bo-bobo.
I've already prepared a place where the Fist of the Nose Hair's battle of destiny will happen.
Teleport!
Battleship commands the fearsome Battleship Quintet!
You can try all you want, but you'll never win!
Fist of the Nose Hair: That's Gorou! That's Gorou!
That's Gorou!
Dammit, it's all my fault... All my fault...
Don't worry. It wasn't your fault.
Bo-bobo...
It's Heppokomaru's
Fault!
We know it's your fault!
The Battleship Quintet... In that case, we'll need to bring him along!
That silhouette! You don't mean...
After Beauty was kidnapped by Battleship,
Bo-bobo and friends went to the mountains to seek a certain man's help.
Is there really someone in these mountains who will be our ally?
Beauty's not so sure! Hey, are you two listening to Beauty?
I'm really sorry about this, Bo-bobo... It's all my fault...
Don't let it get to you.
Beauty's being ignored!
I love you, Hekkun!
Cut it out!
Quit fooling around. This is no time for games!
Beauty's not fooling around! Beauty's being serious over here!
Of course I'm acting serious.
I'm getting like, totally real serious over here.
Ya got a problem with that? Huh?
Let's go, Bo-bobo.
Well, you see...
I'm not called Bo-bobo, I'm Beauty.
How can you get me confused with him?
Now what?
Beauty's gotta go!
What!? Then go by yourself!
You're being cold today, Hekkun!
Let's get a move on.
Ahh! That felt good!
Can we just quit fooling around for once?
You're quite the noisy customers.
Can you take it down a notch?
The ice cream talked!
This guy must be...
The man that fought Bo-bobo to the death in Hair Hunters C-block Base...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bad Hair Treatment Team Emergency Action!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
The Lost Red Treasure!
Softon!
What's he doing in a store in the middle of nowhere?
Yo! Selling soft-serve as usual, I see?
Yeah, heard this shop pays pretty well.
I see. It pays pretty well.
Hey! What do you think you're doing, trainee?
Softon's Shift Manager Empty Can
Orange
I told you to start selling soft-serve!
You wanna get paid or not?
He was a juice vendor from the mountains.
Know that I'm a veteran at selling juice for 30 years.
Let me show you how business works 'round here.
Alright! Here come some potential customers!
Welcome, would you like some juice?
Shoot!
Put your Trash in the Trash Can
Are you alright, manager?
This ain't enough to do me in...
He was a changed man.
But, we didn't come here for this!
Softon, we have a request for you.
A request?
We need you to help us defeat Battleship, one of the Four Lords of Margarita,
so that I may finish my fated battle with him.
Please help us!
I decline.
Don't forget that I was once a Hair Hunter.
I can't help you.
Beauty's been kidnapped!
What?
We have no time to waste.
Is she safe? Is Beauty safe?
We don't know...
Please? I'll give you candy if you help us!
But...
Softon! Softon!
Softon! Softon! Softon!
Softon Soul
But I...
Heppokomaru, you join in too!
Wait, me!?
This is for Beauty, and for your hometown, Puppuu City!
Softon! Softon! Softon! Softon!
BABYLON!!!
And so, Softon had joined up with Bo-bobo's party.
A Supermarket Called Supermarket
Meanwhile, at a supermarket called Supermarket...
Tokoro Tennosuke:                 10 yen
I'm forced to return back to this lifestyle after losing to Bo-bobo.
My, Tennie, you're shaking more than ever today.
Here, have some refreshments.
Oh! Fish store lady!
I really hope you get sold soon, Tennie.
It's fine. I actually like this lifestyle.
I can tell that you don't really mean that.
But I really do like this place.
It's so strange that a good boy like you wouldn't get sold to any customer.
Then will you please buy me?
No, can't do that. Don't press your luck, Tennie.
Well, good luck selling yourself.
It's all Bo-bobo's fault that I have to endure this humiliation!
If it weren't for that bastard... Dammit!
I hate him! I hate him!
Dammit, I hate him...!
Excuse me.
The hell do you want?
I'd like one Tennosuke, please.
Huh? That's weird.
Why am I tearing up all of a sudden? This isn't supposed to...
Here. Dry your tears.
Thank you! Thank you ever so much!
Grade 1 Class 2 Don Patch
You pervert!
What's with all the commotion back there?
Hi, can I help you?
I would like this, please.
That head...
It can't be...
Breath-Clean
This customer's worried about his breath!
Sorry to make you wait.
Oh, you're back, Softon.
Heppokomaru has something he'd like to say.
Everyone, listen to me carefully!
Everyone, please put these on!
I believe Battleship
is in his fortress, Pomade Ring, which he built in my hometown Puppuu City.
So I will lead you all to Puppuu City.
I know it will be a rough battle,
but I know we'll do our best!
Alright! Let's go save Beauty!
Whatever the case, this week's episode was rather indecent.
It's your fault, isn't it?
This is all your fault, isn't it?
I'm sure it's your fault, isn't it?
Great, it's your fault, isn't it?
Now assembled, the five warriors head to the city of battle!
Bear with it a bit longer, Beauty!
They will surely come to rescue you,
and their names will go down in history!
Probably!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
We made it! Is that Battleship's fortress?
Beauty, where are you?
I'm right here!
You better come out quick or we'll go home without you!
But I'm a doll? How can I "come out"?
She's not saying anything. Let's go home.
She must be trying to avoid being found.
That's cause I'm sour!
Now's not the time for stand-up!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Battleship's fortress!
Infiltrating
Infiltrating Battleship's fortress! The Great Spy Mission!
The
Great
Spy
Mission!
!
I may be a doll, but I can still make comebacks!