Shut up! She has nothing to do with this!
Ignoring Heppokomaru's pleas,
Beauty was magically transformed into a small doll.
Bo-bobo, Heppokomaru.
If you want to save this girl, show up at my fortress, Pomade Ring.
And that was Battleship's challenge.
Furthermore, Battleship was in command of a group called the Battleship Quintet.
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, and Heppokomaru headed towards the mountains.
That's where...
Ahh... That was amazing!
And at the supermarket...
One Tennosuke, please.
With Softon and Tennosuke joining them,
they are now a five-man unit!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
NyKaMuRa
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Rescue Beauty!!! Attack Love
Number One, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo.
Let me gift you a...
rainbow-colored nose hair!
Wow!
Number two, Softon.
It's a pleasure.
Wow, his head's all twirly!
Number Three, Tokoro Tennosuke.
He's wobbling!
Number Four, Don Patch.
And today, I'm hajike-ing!
Patch, patch. Patch, patch.
Don Patch is Don Patch...
N-Number Five, Heppokomaru.
I-I-I-I-I-I-It's a pleasure.
How cute of him!
What stupid act are you pulling? We even gave you the Number Five spot!
You're supposed to be the idiot character, so do something stupid!
That's easier said than done...
It's clear as day now that Heppokomaru doesn't have what it takes to be Number Five.
What a shame.
So, who really has what it takes to capture the cute girls' hearts,
and rescue the damsel in distress, Beauty?
What are you...? I don't even care about all that!
Anyone will do, just change me back to normal!
Puppuu City
Bo-bobo and friends have made it to Puppuu City...
But Battleship's fortress, Pomade Ring, was nowhere to be found.
Hey, are you sure you know where it is?
You said it was here, didn't you?
Well then, I'm sure the five of us can split up to find Pomade Ring.
Tennosuke has passed away.
What!? We're down to four already!?
Infiltrating
Battleship's fortress!
The
Great
Spy
Mission!
!
Tennosuke...
How did he...?
He was another who fallen victim in his duty as a modern-day crusader.
You're still wearing that outfit!?
Tennosuke!
You've been FOOLED
I can see that!
Tennosuke!
Tennosuke! Tennosuke!
He's watching my reactions...
I have no choice. I'll just have to play along with them.
Really? So Tennosuke's dead, I guess...
You moron!
We tricked you!
You've been FOOLED!
You've been FOOLED
You're not fooling anyone, bastard!
It really...
It really happened!
It really happened? Am I really dead?
Ah, I see now. I'm really am dead.
So...
Is this real too?
Huh? Where did Bo-bobo run off to?
Where did that guy go?
He's not here...
They're totally ignoring me...
That's weird...
What's that sound!?
Robot Yamada's Face
W-What is...!?
WHAT IS HE DOING!?
Wait, don't abandon me!
Don't leave me, Robot Yamada's Face! Please don't leave me!
Come back!
Is this what you wanted?
Yes, I'm sure.
I know that body was insufficient to support myself.
I will now search for someone who can give that support to me.
Robot Yamada's Face!
I'll be terminated...
I'll be terminated from the robotics institute!
Want some oden?
TL Note: Oden is a popular Japanese dish consisting of various ingredients stewed in soy-based broth
No, I don't want your oden!
Hey, can I have a word?
I've been wondering about this for a while now...
but...
I haven't seen or heard
a single sign of anyone in this town.
What's going on here?
I've got no idea.
Where did everyone go?
Just the other day...
I went and met...
Is someone here?
A whole lot of bears...
The hell are ya doin', idiot?
I was born in Edo, now eat your sushi!
Stop acting like an idiot and start acting more serious for once!
Press play... Press play...
Please press play!
Seriously... Let's get going.
OK!
Battleship's Special Forces Captain
We have you now, Heppokomaru.
This town is already under the control of Battleship's special forces.
So that explains why there was no sign of anyone...
Evil
Those who dare oppose Lord Battleship...
deserve a fate worse than death!
Attack them!
Softon!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Grief of Sweden
Heppokomaru.
Leave this group to me.
Carry on searching for the Pomade Ring.
You got it!
Heppokomaru's running in that direction!
I should expect no less from someone who's fought evenly with Bo-bobo. I can count on him.
The only opponent you're facing will be...
myself!
I'll take you all on at once.
Let me in on this.
Tennosuke!
It's been a long time since my jelly's boiled like this.
Now watch! Fist of the Wobble Wobble Secret Technique:
Nice and round...
First-rate cooking!
First-rate cooking!!!!
Be nice when you eat me, OK?
I'm...
NOT GONNA BE EATEN!!
So that's all you got, huh?
Shock!
Got him!
Stop... treating this as a joke...
Slaughter them all!
Don't you die on me now, guys!
If I don't find Pomade Ring soon...
Pomade Ring
It's that small...
Don't let that one fool you.
That's only a decoy.
So where's the real one at?
The real one...
The real one?
The real Pomade Ring...
is right here!
Pomade Ring
I tried it, but it kind of tasted like oil-free salad dressing.
Just where the hell is the real Pomade Ring?
By the way...
I've been wondering about this for a while, but...
What's that thing flying over the city?
Pomade Ring
Pomade Ring!
So Pomade Ring's a flying fortress?
And that's the face Bo-bobo was riding on!
Heppokomaru!
What's that thing in the sky?
Apparently, it's Pomade Ring.
So that's it?
How are we supposed to get up there?
We fly.
We need to fly!
Don Paatchi
Because we...
We have wings!
Forgive me, Don Paatchi!
But I don't have any wings to fly!
Of course you do.
They were always...
in your heart!
Now let's go!
To the never-ending sky!
Open your eyes, idiot!
Uh...
My eyes are open.
Why are you joining in, Softon?
And all this time I thought you were a serious person...
Meanwhile...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Where have I just crashed?
Welcome to the Pomade Ring.
We've been expecting your arrival.
Y-You must be...
My name is Suzu.
Suzu
I'm under orders from Lord Battleship...
to defeat you!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
Battleship's lackey now stands before Bo-bobo.
Her name is Suzu.
What will you do, Bo-bobo?
I'm gonna make a Slam Dunk!
Squid!
Dammit! Let's swim outta here!
Stop right there!
I'm a squid! I'm just a squid!
You moron! That's a dead end!
Oh, hi there...
If you're looking for Bo-bobo, he ran that way.
Who are you fooling!?
Please, come sit down over here.
And please eat...
my delicious cooking!
Fried Fish Special
Now, commence eating!
Don't mind if I do!
This girl's more than meets the eye...
Bravo!
Keep going! Keep going!
Keep eating it! Keep eating it!
Flap, flap! Flap, flap!
Don't come in! Don't come any closer!
Especially Heppokomaru.
It's too late! I'll shoot them down!
Round and round, round and round...
Flap, flap! Round and round!
These guys are starting to piss me off.
Don't leave leftovers on the table, dammit!
Meanwhile, Tennosuke was...
No matter how hard I try... I just can't fly...
It's alright. I'm sure you can fly.
It's really easy. See, you just do this.
He still wasn't flapping.
Seems that your father's coming home late today...
Don Patch!
Shit, I forgot!
Bo-bobo, I've come to rescue you!
Don Patch...
I told you not...
to come!
So, who's next in line?
That'll be me.
I'm L Foodstuffs Stock Co.'s Third Sales Department Manager, Suzuki Hiroshi.
L Foodstuffs Stock Co.'s Third Sales Department Manager, Suzuki Hiroshi
Also, by the way, I was laid off yesterday.
L Foodstuffs Stock Co.'s FORMER Third Sales Department Manager, Suzuki Hiroshi
I've got no choice but to jump...
You don't have to jump!
There's no reason for you to jump!
You didn't do anything wrong!
You gotta be strong, old man!
Thank you... Thank you so much...
Get away from the ledge and don't jump!
Serviceman
Think of this as a service.
Alright, we made it to Pomade Ring.
Don't let your guard down. Things are gonna get tougher.
Seems like Heppokomaru and Softon have safely broken in.
Now then, the only problem left at hand...
is trying to find how to deal with this gir-
See, I finished it all!
Good girl! She's such a good girl!
Squid
A squid!
Suzu!
I would never have thought he would be passionate.
Bo-bobo, you came to rescue me!
Lord Battleship.
Oh, it's you guys.
The Battleship Quintet.
The Battleship Quintet
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
There's six of them!!!
He dropped all of them!
Just what do you think you're doing?
I counted them and there were six!
It's supposed to be a quintet, but there were six of them!
But Bo-bobo's gonna charge through that door any second! What are we supposed to do now!?
Uh... Uh... Uh... Uh...
Where are they!?
Lord Battleship!!!
Wh-What just happened!?
Meanwhile...
We've finally made it.
Man, you guys are slow!
I'm sure glad I have wings too.
Tennosuke was getting extremely sentimental.
Meanwhile, back to Heppokomaru and Softon...
Where do you think Battleship is?
Flap, flap. Flap, flap.
Don't let your guard down, Heppokomaru.
We don't know what kind of traps he's laid out for us.
That's a lot of special forces...
If they see us, it's all over. We better take a different route.
You're right.
I just hope Don Patch and Tennosuke haven't been caught yet.
Hey, are you sure they haven't figured us out yet?
You moron, we're spies! There's no way they could figure us out!
But it just feels like everyone's watching us...
That's just your imagination.
Besides, even if they catch us, all we gotta say is...
"Hey, we're spies."
Spy
And it'll be smooth sailing!
Nice thinking!
Breaking in is mad easy!
Get them!
Shit!
I suppose I have only one choice...
I... am... sour! I'm sour!
TL Note: This is a pun on "spy" and "sour"
You're not sour!
I'm sour! I'm sour!
Is there anyone in here?
Man, that's just awful!
Oinkton
That bald manager really ticks me off!
Not only does he keep staring at me all the time,
he actually has the nerve to touch me! That's sexual harassment! Sexual harassment, I say!
We gotta report him, oink! Report him, oink!
By the way, who are you?
That's the one thing I can't tell you, oink.
Who are you and what are you doing?
Oh, it's the manager!
Oh, no! Did you hear everything I said?
Did you?!
Oh, no!
Stop! Just what do you think you're doing?
Manager, this is sexual harassment!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Every Rose
Has Its Thorn!
That night, they say that Oinkton was aroused and couldn't sleep.
So we ended up having to enter through the front door.
If we don't meet up with Bo-bobo soon...
Serviceman...
Revenge Service!
What do you mean "revenge"?
Revenge!
I will regain my lost pride,
and continue this pure fight!
Have a look!
Another look!
And here's another look!
The finish!
Oinkton's sleepless nights continued.
Yo, Heppokomaru.
Oh, Bo-bobo!
That freak really showed off his skills to you, didn't he?
Hey! So you're the guy who took down Heppokomaru, right?
That's a great pose! Let me take a few pictures of you!
I'd rather you didn't.
Otherwise I'll break your face!
Sorry.
Seriously... guys like you...
Well that was a shame, Oinkton...
For a fortress, this place wasn't much of challenge.
It feels like we'll take out Battleship without even breaking a sweat.
You really shouldn't underestimate him!
He's probably scheming...
some huge, indescribable trap of some kind that would put fear into the hearts of men!
Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday!
They're having a birthday party!?
Thank you!
Lord Battleship! We're in a crisis!
Bo-bobo and his friends
have taken out half of our forces!
What was that?
Start making your way to the battle stage, and get ready to take them all out!
But we're in the middle of a birthday party...
There's no need to worry about me.
We can always celebrate... next year...
Apologize to him at once!
Now he's crying, thanks to you!
He's CRYING!?
I'm sorry.
YOU'RE sorry!?
What's done is done. Now go and get rid of this Bo-bobo!
Will do.
Soon, Bo-bobo and company reached a certain room in the depths of Pomade Ring.
Battleship's not in this room either...
Welcome, Bo-bobo and company.
That voice...
It's Battleship!
Now in order to defeat you five,
I have prepared for you five battle stages.
Look outside the window.
Give me milk! Give me milk!
Give me milk!
You can see it from out here!
There are giant faces in the middle of Pomade Ring...
What are those faces?
It's Kiichiko's.
Kiichiko
Ever since he was young, Kiichiko was a very large guy.
To think that he would become a battle stage someday...
And five of him!
Now look down at the floor.
There are warp panels numbered from 1 to 5.
If you step on one of those panels, you'll warp to the corresponding stage.
At every battle stage, there is a guardian.
As Heppokomaru should know by now, they'll be one of the Battleship Quintet!
You will be able to see what is going on in the battle stage on this giant screen.
Now let's start the game.
Let's start with Battle Stage 1!
Who will be the first challenger?
Alright, I'll go first.
You're going!?
Listen to me, guys.
The Battleship Quintet are very brutal and ruthless.
We don't know what kinds of tricks they'll play.
Plus, each of them are as strong as us.
Not only that, they could possibly be even stronger.
That's why...
I'll choose to fight first.
Heppokomaru!
Are you saying you don't trust us!?
I'm not saying that, but rather...
I trust you guys enough to sort out the remaining four.
Heppokomaru,
we'll leave it to you.
Battleship has set up the fearsome Battle Stages.
Heppokomaru jumped in, knowing fully well that it would be a trap!
As for his destiny...
He has been brought into the heroic fight
with the Battleship Quintet!
I'm here already?
So, who's gonna be my opponent?
Let's see... looking here, Heppokomaru's opponent is...
Huh? Really? This is a joke! This has to be a mistake!
It's him!!!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Just you wait, Beauty! We're coming to save you!
Don't let your guard down, Bo-bobo! We don't know who we're up against yet!
I don't care who I'm up against! I'll win for Beauty's sake!
No! Don't go so far to save Beauty!
No!
Hold it, hold it!
That was a horrible comeback!
If Beauty were here, she would've gone along with the joke.
I'm sorry.
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Tangled
Nose Hairs of
Destiny!
This'll be
on the test!
I'll make a comeback for Beauty's sake!