Tsuru Tsururiina IV
The year is AD 300X.
The dreadful Margarita Empire is using the Hair Hunters to rule all of mankind.
To protect the peace and freedom of hair,
Four Lords of Margarita
the man opposing the Margarita Empire...
our hero Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
and his company, continue on with their quest.
Battleship of the Four Lords of Margarita, Bo-bobo's eternal rival,
Battleship
had transformed Beauty into a doll. His fortress, Pomade Ring,
floats in the sky.
Pomade Ring
Don Patch, Heppokomaru, Tokoro Tennosuke, and Softon
ascended into the sky with the wings of their hearts.
Meanwhile, L Foodstuffs Stock Co.'s
L Foodstuffs Stock Co.'s FORMER Third Sales Department Manager, Suzuki Hiroshi
former Third Sales Department Manager, Suzuki Hiroshi,
was encouraged by Bo-bobo and company to keep flying.
Bo-bobo had engaged in a harsh battle
Suzu
with Battleship's female assassin, Suzu.
Suzu devoured Bo-bobo's magnificent cooking, a giant roast fish,
with an intensity that didn't seem to suit her,
and she was defeated.
Serviceman
Amidst all this,
the mysterious Serviceman stood before Heppokomaru,
and Oinkton's restless nights continued.
Oinkton
And lastly, Battleship sent the Battleship Quintet after Bo-bobo.
Battleship Quintet
But did I just count six of them!?
In order to save Beauty,
the first challenger on Bo-bobo's team,
Heppokomaru, has stepped forward!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
StitchOtaku626
angel_of_chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Right then, who's gonna be my opponent?
Glad you could make it!
I'm facing all of them!?
Also they're a quintet, so why do I see six of them!?
Why did all you decide to show up?
Isn't this supposed to be a one-on-one battle?
Huh? Are you sure?
Didn't any of you know?
No one told me.
But even Battleship himself told us about the rule!
Sorry about that.
We'll go back and take it from the top.
Please wait outside for a moment.
The Tangled
Nose Hairs of
The Entangled Nosehair of Destiny: It'll be on the test!
Destiny!
This'll be
on the test!
Okay, we're ready now!
So who am I... gonna face... as my opponent...?
How many am I looking at!? And they're all in class!?
You're late yet again, Heppokomaru.
You'll never pass if you're always late like this.
Alright, which one of you ate my curry bread!?
This'll probably be on the test.
This is not the time to be writing notes!
Who am I facing out of you lot?
Let's get this over and done with!
Drop the big guy talk, alright!?
We're trying to study for an exam here!
If you want to be loud, that's up to you, but stop disturbing the others who are trying to study!
Dammit! He found me out!
What the hell is wrong with you, Bo-bobo?
Warp!
Seriously, he never lets his guard down for a second.
Honestly.
Go home.
Warp!
Why don't you shut up over there!?
I can't concentrate in this environment!
I'm heading home!
Class president...
What happened to her?
Dunno.
Heppokomaru,
Go and apologize to her immediately.
You're screwing around now!? I said let's get...
I said get out there and apologize!!
You lardass...
Don't you ever take the class president for a fool!
Heppokomaru...
I'm not done yet! One more time!
Move it... Move it...
You're getting... insistent!
I lost again!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shut the hell up! Stop singing already...
you fat sumo bastard!
I wish...
She's really mad.
Hands off.
What's with this treatment I'm getting today?
What did I ever do to them?
What are we fighting for?
I don't get it...
Hold up...
Welcome!
Now it's changed into a rotating sushi bar!
Alright, sir, you can sit here!
We've got some good stuff lined up here!
Don't put it on me!
Don't put soy sauce on me!
Don't... don't put soy sauce...
What the hell is going on with this place?
Who's supposed to be my real opponent?
Loincloth...
Old man, fill 'er up with your High-Octane!
Yes, sir!
One plate of High-Octane, coming right up!
Now she's full of High-Octane!
Alright!
It's time to put the pedal to the... metal!
What did you just do? She won't even move an inch!
I suppose you just can't run on sushi...
That's nothing to say lightly!
I suppose...
I just can't run on sushi...
Give me an answer, Mr. Sushi!
You can't!
Isn't that right?
Loincloth.
I thought you were defeated by Battleship. So what are you doing here?
Yo, Heppokomaru!
It's because... I'm one of the Battleship Quintet now!
Loincloth Taro,
one of the Battleship Quintet
Haven't seen you in ages, Heppokomaru...
I still remember what happened to us that day.
What do you mean?
Looking back, those were good times.
When did I ever do that to you?
Don't just make stuff up!
Now that I think about it... this happened too.
How about you listen to me first!?
It's a loincloth festival! Hooray! Hooray!
Grow up, Heppokomaru!
I'm never gonna grow up!
I'm sorry for slapping you back then.
When did that ever happen?
In all honesty...
I bet you'd still look good with a loincloth.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Who would have known that Heppokomaru had such a sad past?
He's the type of fighter who carries his burdens by himself...
Alright, then!
From now on, let's all call him Loinclothmaru!
Loincloth! Loincloth! Loinclothmaru!
Mother...
look that the friends that I've made.
It's alright. I have such wonderful friends by my side now!
Pomade Ring Battle 1
Heppokomaru vs Loincloth Taro
Pomade Ring Battle 1:
Loincloth,
there's something I need to know...
Why have you become one of the Quintet?
That's none... of your business!
Eat it!
Red Loincloth Festival
Red Loincloth Festival!
Heppokomaru!
Your attacks will always be futile against my Loincloth Assassination Art!
Red Loincloth Festival!
He wasn't joking when he said that.
I know that his Red Loincloth Typhoon...
is capable of totally canceling out my attacks.
May
May!
Red Loincloth Typhoon!
October
October!
As long as he keeps using the Red Loincloth Typhoon, he'll just cancel out my attacks.
And on top of that, he's superior to me at hand-to-hand combat.
What should I do...? What can I do!?
See what I have to put up with?
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
I'm gonna lose if I don't do anything!
It's time that I handled things from here!
Allow me to explain.
Once Heppokomaru's collar comes off, the seal breaks
and his true power is fully released.
December!
Babu!
At the same time, his personality is changed to that of a baby,
but he's totally unaware of that.
Your seal's going to come off now, Heppokomaru!
Let's show him your true power!
I thought I'd loosen up, but turns out I strangled him instead...
Oh, my...
Heppokomaru vs. Loincloth Taro: Loincloth Taro is the victor!
Nah, la!
Eat dengaku, na-la!
Eat...
I lost...
Out of curiosity, how many times did you snap back?
Lemme count...
One.
I'm facing all of them!?
Two.
How many am I looking at!?
Three.
Four.
Five.
Now it's changed into a rotating sushi bar!
Six.
Seven.
Seven times!
Heppokomaru
You trying to take Beauty's place, you son of a bitch!?
That goddamn brat...
Z-block Trooper A
Captain, you need to think before acting like that!
Z-block Trooper B
Why did you warp to them so carelessly?
I just wanted to make them eat dengaku, nah-la!
Hair Hunter Z-block Captain Dengakuman
He's such a cutie...
And that's why everyone loves Dengakuman!
Flap, flap! Flap, flap! Flap, flap!
Flap, flap! Flap, flap!
So, who's following up after that loser?
I'll go next.
I'll let you handle this, Bo-bobo.
Don't let us down.
S.S. Don Patch
Go for it, Bo-bobo!
Warp!
January 1st
Calendar,
one of the Battleship quintet
I'm gonna enjoy beating the hell out of my next victim, whoever it is!
Where is that watermelon cooling? It's Calendar!
Allow me to explain.
He just shouted "cooling there!" to make it sound like his name "Calendar!"
That's a stretch...
Yeah, seriously.
So, for Pomade Ring Battle 2:
Pomade Ring Battle 2: Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo vs Calendar
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo vs Calendar
The beach is open to the public!
What?
It's open!
Son of a...!
The perfect dive!
Alright!
Time to go swimming!
Crawl! Crawl! Crawl!
Stop it! Stop it!
Front stroke! Front stroke! Front stroke!
Crawl! Crawl! Crawl!
Do I look like the ocean to you!?
Of course you don't!
You're open!
Why don't you show me, what's after January 1st?
No! You can't! I beg you, don't look!
You ready for it?
You can't! I've never shown it to anyone before!
January *th
It's January *th!
I should just kill myself...
Now that you've seen it...
Stop talking about killing yourself, idiot!
But I can't live life knowing that you've looked at it!
You should have confidence in yourself!
February *th
He powered up!!
Hey, you wanna show me March?
OK!
March *th
It's a hitman!!!
Calendar! Quickly, April!
Yes, Commodore!
April *th
He got married!
June 7th
Look what you just did, you bastard!
Now I'm completely worthless until June 7th!
Then take a good long look at me!
If you're just a stub of a calendar,
why don't you tear me apart, too!?
I'm gonna rip you to shreds!
Alright! Start tearing me apart!
Where should I start ripping him from?
Flip.
Dammit! There's nothing to rip!
Alright, this should make us even.
Talk about being unfair!
You're just picking random things to laugh at, just because...
You're the main character of this show!
Stop bitching!
Arrrggh! This is why grown-ups are...
Attack!
You OK there?
Who did this to you?
It was probably you...
Don't worry!
I can't go on...
Calendar!
I lost all my pages in this fight.
Farewell...
Calendar!
You really sent him to the grave!
For my father!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Splitting the Fried Chicken Gang
Splitting the Fried Chicken Gang!
You managed to dodge my Fist of the Nose Hair!
Does that mean you're one of the Battleship Quintet?
Got that right.
June 7th
Member of the Battleship Quintet
I'm June 7th, the actual member of the Battleship Quintet.
Let's drink milk on June 7th!
Losers
Or instead, let's eat a bowl of Tokoroten!
You guys,
don't turn away from the screen now.
He's eating soft-serve ice cream. Figures.
It's about to start.
You may have dodged my attack, but don't let that get to your head.
Pay close attention to the true Fist of the Nose Hair.
The true Fist of the Nose Hair?
Bo-bobo World!
It's here!
Now in Bo-bobo World, with the recurring King Nose Hair...
how will this fight turn out?
Can Bo-bobo's team win against the Quintet
and bring Beauty back to safety?
Bo-bobo, whatever happens now you must win!
Crap!
We forgot to do a "Bo-bobo Theater" this week!
Well then,
since I didn't have enough screen time...
let's do a "Don Patch Theater" as a special presentation!
Yay!
Life Consultation
Don Patch:
Don Patch: Life Consultation
What would you like to eat, Yakkun?
I'm taking a break from work today, so what should we eat?
Don Patch Consultation Booth
No way... That pig's been waiting on this snowy night...
to tell me about his troubles?
But I took a break from work to go on a date...
Without even taking the pig's feelings into account...
That's it, you're not getting any food from me!
Get off! Get off me!
Let go! Drop it!
I mean it! Let go! Stop holding me! Stop it!
Just get off me already!
I'm sorry, Mr. Pig. I'm coming to hear your troubles now!
Okay, Porky Boy.
Please tell me all about your troubles...
Get lost...
Happy, happy, I'm always happy...
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
Where does happiness come from?
Shiawase wa dokokara Yattekuru darou yo
I will go to you again today.
Kyou mo kimi no toko made iku yo
Aaaaaa
Happiness comes suddenly when I'm sleeping.
Shiawase wa neteru toki Totsuzen yattekuru
If you're happy,
Ryoute wo agete karada de arawase yo
show everyone by raising your arms into the air!
Happy, happy, I'm always happy.
Shiawase shiawase Itsumademo shiawase
I wish that it would never end.
De aru koto wo sukunakarazu negatte
Shiawase shiawase Bokutachi wa shiawase
Happy, happy, We are happy!
Because I am loved...
Soshite aisareru kara
...forever!
Eien nii
Bo-bobo, I've noticed that you have a fatal weakness.
You mean he gets anxious around people?
No, I don't think that's it.
You must confront your weakness in the World of Babylon!
You're right! I can't grow bigger if I don't eat my green peppers!
He's not talking about what foods to eat!
This will make Bo-bobo more powerful.
Softon, help me out here!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
New World Travel Guide!!
Bo-bobo's
I saw
weakness
backwoods
in the
of
Babylon!
Will somebody please guide us?