Tsuru Tsururiina IV
The year is AD 300X.
The dreadful Margarita Empire is using the Hair Hunt to rule all of mankind.
To protect the peace and freedom of hair,
Four Lords of Margarita
the man opposing the Margarita Empire...
Our hero Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
and his company continue on with their quest.
Let's rescue Beauty, Loinclothmaru!
There's no time for fun and games.
The same can be said to you.
Come on, everyone, take this seriously!
The first from Bo-bobo's crew that fought Loincloth Taro,
the first member of the Battleship Quintet, was Loinclothmaru...
I mean... Heppokomaru...
His collar tried to break the seal, but...
He took him out.
The next battle was
between Bo-bobo and Calendar.
For my father!
Splitting the Fried Chicken Gang!
I'm June 7th, the actual member of the Battleship Quintet.
Pay close attention to the true Fist of the Nose Hair.
Bo-bobo World!
It's here!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
(Get up!) Stand up.
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Come and fly away!
Step on it!
Bomb it!
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHoktuo20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
We can't be stopped!
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Really hard
Like a starving wild challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Where are we...?
Bo-bobo World.
Once you step into my world, you must release your inner soul.
However, if you're incapable of doing that...
Your soul will be destroyed, and you will surely die!
Got it, baby?
New World Travel Guide!
Bo-bobo's
I saw
weakness
backwoods
of
Babylon!
in the
Medanichiyo!
Kyoto
Ta-da!
Zedagalni! Zedagalni!
Piscachiracchels Sumerashika...
Detaa!
Well look at that, we haven't had any guests for a while!
Let's all give him a big warm welcome!
Hey! You're in MY zone!
Gamra Twist, Gamra Twist...
Is that the...?
Let's see, let's see...
Bingo!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Rareness Level:
You never
know what
is going to
come out
of his afro
at any time
He runs
around on
these legs
at amazing
high speeds
His left punch is
decent, as well
Has a decently
powered punch
It's all mine! I'm gonna capture that super-rare character and train it!
What the hell's going on here!? Why's there a weird old man showing up for class!?
Well, whatever! Class is now in session!
Turn to page 36 in your textbooks!
Natto
But sir! Your student's in grave danger!
Damn, I missed! Beanzawa Beanzawason got away!
Beanzawa Beanzawason!
Who the hell is Beanzawa!?
Alright, you morons!
Beanzawa
If you know the answer this, raise your hands!
Like natto can answer that question!
6x+8y, remainder 4.
Oh, by the way...
That pack of natto is Beanzawa!
I feel like crap!
If that's the case...
Try to solve this equation if you can!
Full Marks
Well,
from 6x*4y,
you raise it by 8,
then use the circle equation,
and it simplifies to four times
the
square
root
of
over
which
leaves
you
with
the
answer..
of...
Shut your mouth!!!
Bo-bobo! There's something I've been wanting to tell you!
Something I've been wanting to tell you!
But I won't tell you.
Then go take these thoughts back!
I got it!
But you don't get anything!
The c-c-c-c-c-c-c-corn stew...
corn stew's stew lid...
it's totally different from this cream stew...
The cream's lid is a corn stew lid... cream's...
Finish your sentence already!
Check me out!
Yo!
I transformed into this! I transformed into this!
And then I kind of transformed into this...
Mature Girl
And finally I guess I sorta transformed into this...
Alley-oop!
Police inspector! Police inspector!
Yes?
Docking system ready!
Yes, sir, Colonel!
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti...
Docking!
Yes, yes, yes!
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-ti...
Docking!
Oh, good!
Happy New Year!
Good Luck
That looks nothing like the character!
My heart...
So in the end, he couldn't release his soul.
This fight's over.
Pomade Ring Second Fight,
Bo-bobo
June 7th
Pomade Ring Second Fight,
Bo-bobo versus June 7th:
Bo-bobo wins!
He did it! Now it's one to one!
Man, that was tiring...
Bo-bobo was seriously amazing back there!
He's someone you can totally depend on!
One of these days, I'm going to be just like him!
Shut your mouth!
Shut your mouth, and know your role!
Yes, sir.
Losers
Why is he sitting here with me?
Alright, guess I'm up next.
This'll clinch our second victory.
What's going on? You actually won that match! You don't need to sit here!
Shut up! You underdogs just shut your traps!
Yes, sir.
Honestly... You brats... Just shut your mouth and watch my fight.
Good luck, Don Patch!
So, who do I get to smack down?
Pomade Ring third fight,
Don Patch
Tough-looking Guy
Pomade Ring third fight:
Don Patch vs Tough-looking Guy.
I'll beat you up in one second.
Bring it, Jabroni! Come and get some of the Great One!
Come on! Come on!
Don Patch
Pomade Ring third fight,
Tough-looking Guy.
Pomade Ring third fight:
Don Patch vs Tough-looking Guy:
Tough-looking Guy wins!
I'll make sure none of them will return alive.
I can't take the suffering anymore...
I can't stand watching my friends get hurt anymore!
Beauty!
Who said that? Where are you?
Don't cry.
Beauty, there's no need for you to worry.
It'll all be over soon.
No! Stay away from me!
Please don't get close to me!
For the time being,
I can only enter your soul like this.
You're in my face!
But I'll come to save you soon.
Hey, what's that twirly-head trying to do?
No clue...
Here we go, I'll put an end to this losing streak.
Tennosuke!
We all believe in you!
Sorry for being so useless...
Don't talk to me, underdog.
He didn't lose. He didn't lose.
That's right, he didn't lose!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
Hello? Is there anyone home?
Pomade Ring fourth fight,
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Gum.
Pomade Ring fourth fight:
Tokoro Tennosuke vs Gum
This... is my opponent.
I'm pretty hungry, bro.
Of course! I know what to do!
Whoever can satisfy that dog's appetite is the winner!
This makes everything so simple! I've got this in the bag!
Now, let's start this showdown!
That's right. Come here, boy.
Come over here, boy.
That's right. Here, boy.
Pomade Ring fourth fight,
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Gum.
Pomade Ring fourth fight:
Tokoro Tennosuke vs Gum:
Gum wins!
You gotta love that yogurt flavor.
That's so true... Yogurt flavor is the best...
We won this fight too.
That gives us three victories, Lord Battleship!
Is that so?
Alright, gentlemen...
here's a toast to our three victories!
Cheers!
Tasty!
Alright! I'm gonna party all day and all night!
You gotta fight for your right to party! Yeah! Yeah!
Party hard!
Sorry, I spilled it on you.
It's all good!
This is how you do it! This is how you do it!
Look at this! I was partying too hard and broke the monitor!
It's all good!
South Central does it like nobody does! What!? What!?
Do not press
Check this! I partied so hard I pressed Pomade Ring's self-destruct button!
It's all good!
I guess I partied too hard...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Talk about a lucky break in staying alive!
But what the hell just happened?
Wait, Tennosuke! Where's Tennosuke?
Ah, don't worry about that schmuck.
He can handle himself.
You're right, he sure can.
Moving on to more important things, look what I found!
Look, I found Beauty's doll here!
Oh, Beauty! You're safe!
Right then, leave this bit to me!
As I'll now turn Beauty back to normal like magic!
You can really change her back?
Mixer start!
Are you sure she's safe in there?
Yeeeeeeessss...
What the hell did you do to her? Don't try to hide it!
Calm down! Calm down!
Calm down!
CALM DOWN!
Where am I?
Huh? You're all here?
Oh, Beauty's back to normal!
We did it! Beauty's back to normal!
Back...
to normal!
Did I party too hard?
Yes, you did.
Well...
I was partying too hard... and I...
Beauty had made it back safely.
OK, fine, I hear you. Now let's starting acting a bit more serious.
Sorry.
What? Sorry?
Five packs of noodles
TL Note: This is a pun on "sorry"
Five of them?
I can't do that! There's no way I can eat all those on my own!
This is great, since we're all here now...
all that's left to do is take out Battleship!
Let's go and mess up his day!
We can't just yet.
I hate to say this, but as we are now, he'd take us all out.
W-Why not?
Wait a second. I'll explain it all right now.
He's right. As we are, we'd all get...
You're forgetting someone. You're forgetting someone.
Bo-bobo,
when I watched your last fight, I discovered your weakness.
Bo-bobo has a weakness?
If you were to fight Battleship now, he'd definitely take you out.
And then he will be reborn as a terrible evil spirit and haunt people.
That's not gonna happen.
But...
there's only one way to overcome your weakness.
I'm going to summon the Gate of Babylon.
Go to the World of Babylon, and overcome your weakness.
Now, show yourself, Holy Gate of Babylon!
Reveal to us all the realm of discovery!
I-Is that supposed to be a...!?
Softon!
Are you alright?
The Gate of Babylon can't stay in this world for very long.
Behold! The gate's open!
Enter it! Now!
But Bo-bobo and Don Patch went that way...
Those guys...
Just where...
Could they be?
Now get in there!
Young lady.
Y-Yeah?
I'm worried about leaving those two on their own,
so I want you to go with them.
No worries, I'll keep an eye on them!
Be careful.
Well then, away I go!
She'll be safer with those two than staying here with us.
By the way, what kind of place is the World of Babylon?
I wanted to tell him "Hekkun, that has to be wrong."
Finally! Now I can take a dump!
Final Member of the
Battleship
Quintet
This is perfect! I was just about to explode in my pants!
'Scuse me!
Softon! He's-
Jumping in!
Hey, play it cool in the toilet.
Sorry, Mr. Twirly-head!
Goddammit! That was one of the Battleship Quintet!
And I just let him go in right under my eyes!
This is bad. This is really bad.
When did you...
So you're Battleship?
You're going to pay for the sins you've committed against Beauty!
It's only natural, but...
Here's our new corner!
The Bo-boroscope!
Everyone get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your horoscope will be revealed at the end of the show!
We made it!
Is this the World of Babylon?
Dammit!
What is that thing...?
My little brother ate my pudding!
I'm not much, but... I'm not much, but...
Oh, you're Inspector Soy Sauce!!!!
Inspector Soy Sauce!!!!
He's a policeman?
Incorrect, madam, I'm the Guide to the World of Babylon.
Guide to the World of Babylon
Hey, can I have some mayonnaise?
Hiroshi's mother
Hiroshi!
Mom!
Why are you romping around the house?
And what's with that outfit? Take it off now!
Stop it, woman! I'm the Guide to the World of Babylon! I'm not your Hiroshi!
Exactly!
Babylon Guide Squad
There's a whole bunch of them now!
We are the guides to the World of Babylon.
We're all trained to guide those who come from the real world.
Just what we needed! Now we don't have to worry about getting lost in this world!
It looks like someone doesn't want to be guided!
OK then, we need one of you to guide us through the World of Babylon.
Very well, then allow me to be your guide.
And with their helping guide, they all set out to find Bo-bobo's weakness.
Okay, let's all get out there and find Bo-bobo's weakness!
Hey, where should we...
How many did we ask for!?
Teacher, I can't find Sato anywhere!
Don't know him.
Teacher, I gotta go!
Then just go.
Don't do it!
Stay back!
Fruit Yogurt
Taste Revolution
Did you know, that fish yogurt is becoming ever so popular in France right now!?
That's not true! That's not true!
Fruits
Stop it, Bo-bobo! If you harm those talking fruits, they'll get ruined!
Well, let's find out!
As you can see, I didn't ruin them.
Yes, you did.
The Aristocrat Pigs
So, you left over some pork from your lunch, oink, right?
Don't screw with the Aristocrat Pigs, oink.
I'm sorry.
He's in the custody of pigs!
The Aristocrat Pigs!
Nice collaboration!
If this keeps up, we'll never find Bo-bobo's weakness.
Does Bo-bobo even have a weakness?
Bo-bobo's Weakness
Dammit, I've been found out!
Gotta run!
Beauty didn't follow it.
"Well, who would follow that?" she thought.
Teacher! I managed to find Sato!
I'm sorry, teacher!
I see. Look, I want to have a word with you guys, so follow me.
Yes, teacher!
I've found you at last, Bo-bobo.
Come on everyone...
let's stop screwing around and get this done already!
While we've been screwing around, Hekkun and Softon have been fighting Battleship!
I'm sorry.
It was an impulse.
It was an impulse!
An im-im-im-im-im-im-im-im-im-
And that was "It Was an Impulse" by Bo-bobo.
We'll be right back after a word from our sponsors.
No we won't!
Look, I'm begging you, take this more seriously!
OK.
Alright, let's go!
They've somehow multiplied!!!!
What's with these guys? Why do they keep multiplying?
Come to think of it, they haven't even guided us anywhere!
They're being born!
That's disgusting!
See, there's your mama! Now let's all follow Mama!
Mama! Mama!
Look, I already told you, stop screwing around!
I hate all of you!
Boei Productions
The love of two lovers...
The throbbing of intertwined hearts...
Sayuri Yoshikawa as
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
We are two as one... two as one...
Mayumi Kawasaki as
Patchmi
Love Romance Teacher...
Koji Yamada as the
Battleship Quintet member
I'm in this too?
The feelings of two dreamers...
Episode 1:
Throbbing Premonitions
It was the Late Tokugawa era.
Edo
This is a historical play?
It's your fault she hates us now, right?
It's your fault, isn't it?
It's your fault, right?
Mr. Bobobo, the preparations for the coffee have been finished.
Oh, it's that time already.
Alright, the two of us will go apologize tomorrow.
Yes. That will be good.
But there are three of us.
Sorrree.
OK, that's nice. Now let's be more serious.
That's our Miss Beauty, you're so kind!
Miss Beauty!
Miss... Beauty!
Miss...
Beauty!
Our very own Miss Beauty!
I hate the World of Babylon.
I don't have time for this crap!
Run away!
Bo-bobo! Prepare yourself!
I, the final member of the Battleship Quintet,
Death Mask,
Final Member of the Battleship Quintet
Death Mask
will crush you!
He's a cute enemy!
En garde!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
You missed!
He managed to dodge it!
I can already predict where your Fist of the Nose Hair will strike!
I cleverly watched all your moves in the Battle of Pomade Ring!
And because I've seen how you fight, it won't work on me!
That's it!
I know it! I know what Bo-bobo's weakness is!
Weakness...
I've figured out what my weakness is.
You know your weakness? What is it?
You're a bed-wetter?
I never asked you.
My weakness... is that I don't have enough techniques.
So if it's been used once, I run out of moves to use in battle.
It's too late to realize that you don't have any moves left!
And even better, you still don't know what to do!
Let's end this!
Fist of the
Nose Hair
Secret Technique:
Armpit Chop! ♥
Armpit Chop!
That's so pathetic!
But it still managed to defeat me.
It's not that I don't have any moves.
The Fist of the Nose Hair's secret techniques are sacred.
I don't use them recklessly.
But if Battleship's my opponent,
I have no choice but to use the Fist of the Nose Hair Final Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Alley.
All done. Now that I've overcome my weakness, let's go back.
Bo-bobo, let's hurry back!
I'm worried about Hekkun!
Yeah! I'm worried! He must be a bed-wetter!
Is not!
Exit
That must be the exit.
Let's jump!
Are Heppokomaru and Softon safe?
And what is the Fist of the Nose Hair Final Secret Technique: Nose Hair Alley?
You're forgetting something. You're forgetting something.
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Sakura saku koro omou yo
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
I lost things and broke things,
Nakushite kowashite
I understood so many things
Ironna koto wakattetta
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
What was I drawing again
Kirai bakkari motteita
that had so much hate in it?
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
How many times will I go in circles
Guruguru omotte nandome no
before I understand what weakness is?
Yowasa wakatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mogaite mata naitatte
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
To the future ahead of us
Mukou no mirai he
Take this! Final Secret Technique!
What an amazing fight!
Those nose hairs are a little too amazing...
Battleship, the time to come to blows has finally arrived!
What happened between you two?
Could it be? That legend?
Yes, that's it. When we were three,
we were the protectors of the universe.
I thought so.
That can't be true!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Farewell,
Bo-bobo!
The Final Nose Hair Battle!!
But this isn't the end!
The Galat's attack...
Hekkun, get a grip!
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, going all-out hajike will
make you super-popular at school!
If you tied or lost, do ten Purukogis!