Tsuru Tsururiina IV
The year is AD 300X.
The dreadful Margarita Empire is using the Hair Hunt to rule all of mankind.
To protect the peace and freedom of hair,
Four Lords of Margarita
the man opposing the Margarita Empire...
our hero Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
and his company, continue on with their quest.
We're like gonna so totally save Beauty!
Yeah!
Previously, Team Bo-bobo finished an intense fight
with Battleship's forces.
Pomade Ring First Battle: Heppokomaru loses, Loincloth Taro wins
Pomade Ring Second Battle: Bo-bobo wins, June 7th loses
Pomade Ring Third Battle: Don Patch loses, Tough-looking Guy wins
Pomade Ring Fourth Battle: Tokoro Tennosuke loses, Gum wins
Battleship's fortress,
Pomade Ring, was annihilated, and Beauty had finally been rescued.
But how!? We lost 3 to 1!
Alright, all that's left to do is take out Battleship!
Th... The pain...
We can't just yet.
I hate to say this, but as we are now, he'd take us all out.
Bo-bobo. Go to the World of Babylon, and overcome your weakness!
Help me...
Anyhow, Bo-bobo,
Don Patch, and Beauty all went to the World of Babylon.
And meanwhile,
who should appear before Softon and Heppokomaru was none other than...
So you're Battleship?
You're going to pay for the sins you've committed against Beauty!
Don't tell me they... forgot?
But somehow, Bo-bobo overcame his weakness.
Bo-bobo, let's hurry back!
I'm worried about Hekkun!
They definitely forgot.
That must be the exit.
Let's jump!
Get moving, Bo-bobo!
Help Heppokomaru and Softon take down Battleship!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Hey, we're back.
Where did Hekkun and Softon go?
Alright, that's that. We've finished the frame.
How's about we take a break, Heppokomaru?
Sure thing!
They're building a house together!
Farewell,
Bo-bobo!
The Final Nose Hair Battle!!
But this isn't the end!
Two hours after Bo-bobo returned from the World of Babylon,
the house was finally complete.
Hey, that's a nice looking house we made.
You're right!
Check it out, it's the house I've always wanted!
Alright then, how about I show you inside?
Oh, that reminds me. I wonder where Softon is?
He got built in...
He got built in!
He got built in!!
HE GOT BUILT IN!!!
This is the Self-Taught Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Construction Fist.
Self-Taught Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
That twirly-headed friend of yours isn't going anywhere.
You bastard! What have you done to Softon!?
You do realize you built it with him?
If only I had realized it was him...
Wow, this brick is perfect for the house.
But I'm, Softon.
Battleship, I've finished up with the front wall.
But I'm still Softon.
Did you just hear that brick talking to us?
You're just hearing things.
Please tell me that's not true!
I'll never let you get away with this!
Patch
Is this supposed to be my home? Is this it?
Here's your food.
October!
October
Patch
Although looking at it from another angle, it does actually look homely.
Why don't you try... this!?
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Law of the West!
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Not so tough anymore now, huh, Heppokomaru?
You're way too green to fight against me.
Take a chill-pill and lie down for a while.
Battleship...
It appears that fate would have us fight regardless of our circumstances.
You are the only one...
that I will defeat using my fully released nose hairs!
I've been waiting for this moment to come.
The moment where I finally end your life!
It's feeding time! Feeding time!
Alright!
You got it!
Hekkun!
Dammit... Damn him...
I've been revived!
Here I come!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Super-sized!
How'd you like that?
Whoa, he's huge!
Now you're going to get it!
Imbecile!
Are you alright?
Ow...
Are you alright!?
I said are you alright!?
Being kind means everything to me.
So I promise not to hurt anyone.
Battleship remembered like the time the fish stick said:
Fish Stick
"I really despise hollow stuff."
That was exactly how he was feeling now.
Have it your way. I'll show you my power, for a limited time only.
Don't let him, Bo-bobo!
You can't let him use it!
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair Top-Secret Technique:
Skeleton Fist!
Wh-What technique is he doing?
It's too late...
Once this attack hits you, it's all over.
It sucks out all the life from your body, leaving only your skeleton behind.
I'm being drained... I'm being drained!
Now become a skeleton!
I'm becoming a skeleton...
Bo-bobo!
It's an archaeological discovery!
Bones, bones... An ancient romance, an ancient romance...
It truly is a romance.
Bo-bobo!
But this...
This is nothing compared to my scars from back then.
W-What happened between... the both of you?
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
A long time ago...
The Earth was pressed in
from the East and West by the Galat Army,
North
West
East
South
Galaxy
and faced a life-or-death crisis...
Captain...
Your friend's platoon
went missing in action after that last battle.
But no need to fear.
It's time to play our trump cards that have been under secret development
for three long years.
You mean these newly modeled robots...
...that will change history forever!
3-year-old Bo-bobo
3-year-old Battleship
Enemy sighted! Enemy sighted!
All personnel to battle stations!
It's the Galat Army!
Alright, time to show them the full power of our new robots!
With that, Bo-bobo and I were launched into battle.
We were both equal in ability,
But because I had the Ducktail Bazooka,
I was more suited for combat.
But in reality...
In reality, he stood alone.
He destroyed every enemy after enemy...
And all because I had a bad pilot.
Battleship's pilot Jennifer
Huh? Something's not right here...
At the end of the day, we were robots.
We had to trust everything to our pilots.
What kind of pilot does he have? Whoever it is, he's no pushover.
It opened!
A dragon!
Roar, Dragon!!!
Once that dragon flew into space,
the battle was all over.
How am I expected to forget that humiliation!?
You're acting pathetic!
Are you still dwelling on the past?
Bo-bobo!
Do you remember this scar?
That scar...
I hurt myself a few seconds ago.
Twenty years ago
Fist of the Nose Hair!
7-year-old Bo-bobo
Exhausted already?
7-year-old Battleship
You're such a wimp, Bo-bobo.
Good job, both of you.
Master!
Juice
Master
You have both defeated the 500 men and passed the final test!
So now, I will announce the successor of the Fist of the Nose Hair.
Finally, the time's come!
After so long, I will be the 7th successor to the Fist of the Nose Hair.
I know that I'm far more skilled than Bo-bobo.
Now all the years of harsh training
will finally pay off!
The 7th successor...
to the Fist of the Nose Hair will be...
Bo-bobo!
You for real?
And just like that, my pride was shattered.
I don't understand!
Why Bo-bobo over me?
I'm more fit to be the successor!
You for real?
Please explain yourself!
It's all so simple, my boy.
You for real?
It's because you aren't from the Hair Kingdom!
Cans / Bottles
You for real?
The successor must hail from the Hair Kingdom,
And only from the Hair Kingdom!
Do you understand, Battleship?
It was always that way.
No matter how much I worked...
No matter how hard I tried...
I could never be accepted.
I wasn't from the Hair Kingdom.
And just because of that, no one would accept me.
Battleship...
Back off me.
What an anticlimax...
I don't have enough screentime!
Neither do I!
But at least we've got more than...
This guy!
Here's my screentime.
You've really done it, Bo-bobo.
Now I'll show you my super-secret technique.
What? Your super-secret technique?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock! Paper Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Eat it! Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair Super-secret Technique:
Self-taught Fist of the Nose Hair
Super-Secret Technique
Armageddon!
Hello? Is this the Planetary Defense Commander?
Yes, hello, my name is Battleship...
And I've got a guy I'd like you to beat up...
Yes... yes... so could you do something to...
You can't call that a technique!
10 minutes later
Fire!
Presently under attack ♥
by the Planetary Defense Force
It's over!
Bo-bobo!
Ow...
That attack only bruised him once!?
Don Patch Sword!
New Year's Day.
That was supposed to be an attack!?
Alright! Now let's transform into Bobopatch!
You mean we're gonna do a Bo-bobo Fusion!?
You really think I'd let you!?
Beat it!
What the...?
And I've been smacked to the ground again!
Just how did he get behind me so quick...?
An abacus!
No wonder he's so fast! That can only make him super speedy!
I am now six times faster than normal to be exact.
58932 minus 237362
equals negative 178430!
And by the way, Bo-bobo,
you're not the only one who can pull off a Fusion.
My Don Patch Sword!
Once I've fused with the Don Patch Sword, no one will be able to stop me!
Don Patch Sword!
Don Patch Sword?
That's a leek...
Beauty snapped back silently to herself.
Battleship Fusion!
What's gonna happen? What's gonna happen?
One order of onion-topped Battleship sushi wrap!
Can I change back?
Go ahead.
That was close.
I was getting worried for a second there.
Me too.
Self-taught Serpent Fist of the Nose Hair!
Now you can't move a muscle.
Take this! Final Secret Technique:
Ducktail Attack!
Now this is the end!
Crap! I can't dodge this attack!
Bo-bobo!
Three of them?
Did I just see three of you?
No, you didn't.
Now it's my turn to reveal my secrets!
Fist of the Nose Hair Super-Super-Super Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Armor!
Aomori Mandarin Oranges
You're finished, Battleship!
Now!
Don't get arrogant on me!
I don't feel a thing.
Aomori mandarin oranges...
Oranges...
Aomori Mandarin Oranges
Aomori mandarin oranges!
Aomori Apple
It was Don Patch all along!
Oh, is that so?
I did it! I finally did it!
Good, now go home.
I won't allow you to mess with me... any longer!
It's alright.
It was revenge for Don Patch.
You must atone for killing Don Patch!
It's not like Don Patch was anyone worth making a fuss over!
Take him down, Bo-bobo!
Take revenge for what he did to Don Patch!
What's going on?
Battleship, this ends now.
Fist of the Nose Hair Final Secret Technique:
Nose HaIr Alley!
This was the one secret move that I wasn't able to pull off!
I wanted to be accepted...
Goddamn you Hair Hunters!
Look what they did to the Hair Kingdom!
I'm glad that it's gone.
I'm content that this country's no more.
You're "glad" about this!?
Because any country that can't accept me
is better off destroyed.
No...
I'll take over the world...
and make everyone accept me!
But it wasn't that... I didn't really care about ruling the world.
In reality...
Bo-bobo, I only wanted you to accept me.
What're you doing? Why are you holding back on me?
Give it up. The fight's over.
Shut the fuck up!
There's no way it's over!
Battleship, you really are an idiot.
You're an idiot, a blockhead, even a single-celled organism,
and have one messed up beard!
Bo-bobo, you son of a bitch!
But you're also a hard worker.
In order for people to accept you,
you've worked many times harder than anyone else.
But you didn't know how to get people
to accept you without using force.
Shut up...
So one by one, people drew away from you.
It's only natural.
Shut up! Shut up already!
But even though people may hate you,
Even though people don't accept you,
you're still the best friend that I've had.
You've become a lot stronger, Battleship.
Bo-bobo...
Bo-bobo!
Battleship!
Stop whining!!!
We aren't...
We aren't men if we whine about everything!
Battleship Arc: End
Everyone, thank you for cheering Bo-bobo on.
Next time...
What? Are we...? This must be Hair Hunter A-block Base.
A-Block Base
Oh yeah, I've seen those guys before.
But something's happened to all of them. What's going on here?
So after all that...
He wasn't here...
Just where is... Bo-bobo?
It's a... It's a new character!
There's no way we can end the series now!
If that's the case, we'll move on to a new arc!
It's the start of a new adventure!
What will become of Bo-bobo?
And is this new character friend or foe?
We'll see about that.
Don't you dare miss it!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
Ahhh! He stole my spotlight! Who's that guy?
He's the only normal person I've seen since the series began!
Looks can always be deceiving.
Hang on Don Patch, do you know him?
He's my twin brother!
No wonder why he looks just like you.
You're lying, how do they look alike?
Yo-You don't have to go that far...
I-I'm sorry. But is it true?
Of course not!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Enter the
Mys
te
Enter the
ri
ous
Cool Guy!
He'll
LOCK
Up Your Heart!!
So just who is he?
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, tokoroten is your lucky food tomorrow!
If you tied or lost, you better not leave leftovers!