Their shocking past is finally revealed!!
We have the testimony of one of their acquaintances.
Friend of subjects, P-mi
I really didn't know, either.
Who would've thought they would have such a deep connection?
Re-enactment
Battleship's hatred for Bo-bobo...
was all because of his wounded heart.
3-year-old Bo-bobo
3-year-old Battleship
7-year-old Bo-bobo
7-year-old Battleship
Master
The 7th Successor to the fist of the Nose Hair is...
Aomori Mandarin Oranges!
The successor to the Fist of the Nose Hair is an Aomori Mandarin Oranges? You're kidding, right?
It was always that way.
No matter how much I worked...
No matter how hard I tried...
I could never be accepted.
It's because you've only drunk apple juice your entire life.
That's not it! That wasn't the reason!
After 20 years have passed...
Bo-bobo and Battleship's final battle began.
Fist of the Nose Hair Final Secret Technique:
Nose HaIr Alley!
But it wasn't that... I didn't really care about ruling the world.
In reality...
Bo-bobo...
I only wanted you to accept me.
After understanding Battleship's heart...
Bo-bobo stopped the onslaught.
Shut the fuck up!
You're still the best friend that I've had.
Bo-bobo...
And when you think it's over...
Stop whining!!!
It's all because you were a 100%...
Apple juice drinker!
Apples or oranges: That is the important question.
And that was today's story!
Come on, can you act serious about this!?
We have got some new development for this episode!
The new development
Hair Hunters A-block Base
Just where is... Bo-bobo?
Hair Hunters A-Block Deputy Captain Katsu
Oh, look! There's a mysterious figure looking for Bo-bobo!
Just who is he?
There's something written on his back. It's visible, but you can't really see it...
Who is this mysterious man acting so mysterious?
We will continue this next time!
And by that I mean...
Right now!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Angel_of_Chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Enter the
Mys
te
Enter the
ri
ous
Cool Guy!
He'll
LOCK
Up Your Heart!!
Where is that Bo-bobo?
I'm right here.
You're rubbish at finding me!
Please let me go!
Don't shoot me! Please, don't!
Human nature is nothing but pure evil.
They're up to something stupid again.
Even if that was by nature...
I can't die!
I can't die and leave the children without their parents!
That's right, that's what mother birds are supposed to do.
Wait... That has absolutely nothing to do with human nature!
Alright, cut! Cut!
Give me more screentime!
This just won't do!
I've been thinking about this for a while now...
But I haven't even had enough screentime lately!
With that said, I will now read the precious written opinions of our fans.
You better be listening, producers!
And now, I want everyone to put this around your neck!
Bronze Prize
Silver Prize
Gold Prize
What do we do with these boxes?
And so, let's get this started with pen-named Kitty-Cat...
Age 6, from Osaka.
"Don Patch hasn't had enough screentime lately."
"Please show him more on screen."
Bronze?
Badge
Bronze Prize
Towel
Silver Prize
Gold Prize
Watch
Oh, so the prize is a badge!
Gold prize is a watch... How thrilling.
Silver prize is... a towel?
This next one comes from pen-named Bororott...
Age 10, from Tokyo.
"Don Patch is an irritating thing with legs. Please give him less screentime."
"Whenever I see Don Patch, it makes me want to vomit."
Well, this guy's got a strong case.
How does he!?
Guess this was Bronze Prize, too.
Moving on, this next postcard
is from pen-named Poo-taro, age 13, from Yamanashi.
"To sum up this anime in one word, it's gratin."
GRATIN
That's all.
This is exciting...
That's gold!?
Will it be a gold prize watch?
It's bronze prize.
I think so too.
The judging is pretty strict here.
And for the next postcard we have...
What's the meaning of this shit!?
Did you do that?
Did you really have to go that far?
What are you trying to say?
Hey, stop it!
You back off, Heppoko-moron!
You only came with us to save Pupuu City, right?
Guess what, you done it, whoop-de-doo!
So why are you still tagging along with us?
You're absolutely right.
But I'm still far too weak to face the world.
That's why I decided to travel with Bo-bobo to train myself and get stronger.
My goodness... This little boy... He's grown up to say something so eloquent...
Mama's so happy to hear this!
And this week's winner of the spur-of-the-moment Don Patch Present...
is this anonymous contestant from Kyoto!
Congratulations!
No such prize actually exists.
Alright, now that the idiot's finally gone, let's move out!
Bobsled
A bobsled? What's this doing here?
I've found you at last, Bo-bobo.
Who's there?
You had me looking everywhere for you.
Who are you?
Ready and...
Hang on, have you really forgotten about me?
It's me, remember? From the Hair Kingdom...
Oh, did you say from the Hair Kingdom?
I don't know anything about the Hair Kingdom...
However, I don't talk to people who aren't riding a bobsled!
I don't think I'll ever understand how you act...
Hey Bo-bobo, there can't be anyone else on this mountain who's riding a bobsled!
Don't be so quick to make assumptions. Now move aside!
Hair Hunters M-block Captain Hisashi
Are you brothers?
No, we're not.
So, Bo-bobo, we meet at last.
Today, I will have that yellow head of yours.
We've been having a plethora of weird guests today.
Hey, you serious? Don't count me as your weird guest!
Alright, I'll start things off with you.
That sounds more like it.
You really have forgotten me, haven't you?
Alright, fine.
Could it be...
He keeps a weapon there?
A key?
This should help you remember!
You're mine, Bo-bobo!
I have no grudge against you, but forgive me for this.
You're...
Fist of the Key!
Fist of the Key
LOCK!
Sorry 'bout that, but I've LOCKed your body in place.
Now you won't be able to move.
But you can relax. The LOCK will wear off after a day. Just grin and bear it.
What was that technique?
He locked his body with a key?
That's the Fist of the Key...
You must be... Hatenko!
Hatenko
That took you long enough, Bo-bobo.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
Long time no see, Bo-bobo.
You know this guy?
His name is Hatenko.
A master of the Fist of the Key,
and a fellow survivor of the Hair Kingdom.
What have we here, Bo-bobo?
You changed your job to babysitting since we last met?
He's pretty rude.
Wanna see if we're kids or not, old man?
Hey, and what's this?
We have a boy that doesn't know when to keep his goddamn mouth shut.
So Hatenko, what brings you all the way out here?
Ah, right.
There's something important I need to tell you.
Although to tell you the truth...
What happened?
What happened to you?
I was delivering the Don Patch present to the anonymous contestant from Kyoto, and then...
I've been waiting for your arrival.
Boss!
Boss!?
What's going on here? Why'd you call him boss?
The fatal meeting between Don Patch and Hatenko...
happened five years ago.
Five years ago...
Hatenko, at the time, had given up on life.
There was no other way he could run from his pointless love.
Now I've finally been hit by that terrible weapon...
The Blown Kiss.
Death? It doesn't sound so bad.
He had no regrets in his life.
However...
Hey, this guy's still breathing.
You're right.
Boss! This guy's alive!
Boss!
He was frying in a red-hot frying pan...
and blowing a whistle with a really cool face.
Is the ketchup ready?
Ready and waiting, Boss!
And then, after being fried...
he then followed up by asking for ketchup.
This exceeded my imagination.
I then thought, "This guy's truly amazing."
Boss, I'm so glad to see you again.
It's your faithful lackey, Hatenko!
Boss?
Lackey?
What's happened, Boss?
Why are you hiding from me?
Get away from me!
Get! Away! From! Me!
Boss...
I'm sorry, Hatenko.
But we can't go back to the way things used to be.
Because! Because!
Because!  Because!
I'll turn out like this!
You're the best! You'll always be the best, boss!
You mean the worst, don't you?
I don't get any of this, but how come Don Patch's lackey is so strong?
Now what?
There's something coming our way.
Is it them?
What is the strange object coming towards them?
Is it a bird? Is it a plane?
No, it's...
A-And there they go.
Who were those guys?
That guy riding on that weird hovercraft...
is on an entirely different power level!
Looks like they've started moving out.
Dammit, and they're headed straight towards Iguana Town!
Wait up, Hatenko!
Iguana Town
Purr-poo of the Four Lords of Margarita
Choco Chocotto
Soda Pop
Lord Purr-poo, I finally got the rat.
What're you doing, spark?
Let me go, spark!
Stop moving!
He's absolutely the guy we're looking for.
No, that's someone completely different...
Sparkman
Let me go, spark! You've got the wrong guy, spark!
Well, well. Now that we've caught you, you're trying to play ignorant?
How unsightly of you.
Spark!
He's saying "No, you're wrong."
Well, if you look at it that way, he does seem different.
Oh, you're right. They look alike, but they're not the same.
No, they look absolutely different!
Spark...
Hey, you blind? Can't you tell it's not him!?
Get lost!
Spark!
Meanwhile...
Bo-bobo and company have arrived at the village.
How cruel.
What on earth happened here?
I'll explain this all later.
In the meantime, if you see those three we saw earlier, let me know.
Wait a sec. Where did Don Patch go?
Sounds like you don't understand the Boss at all.
Have a look up there.
Up where?
Hot, hot, hot...
He's become the sun!
Oh, it looks like I've become the sun.
And he's just calm about it!
Hat, hit, het...
Boss...
You're always like that.
You're always exceeding my imagination.
Hatenko, I am so happy.
I finally get to see you happy.
The same for me, Boss!
What's wrong, Boss?
The night's coming... The jet-black world of darkness, night...
After this break...
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
The night's coming... The jet-black world of darkness, night...
Hi.
The darkness prevails... Such is life...
Boss!
And so, Don Patch's ever-changing life continued.
Wow, those two are pretty good at tennis.
Who are they supposed to be?
That stings. Who smacked me?
The tennis players who hit Purr-poo were angry.
Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah!
The angry tennis players thought...
What's all the fuss about?
Aren't we just... extras for one scene?
Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah! Blah!
"Hey, if you get so angry, you'll build up stress."
"Have one of these."
"It only has 500 milligrams of polyphenol..."
he explained to Purr-poo.
No thanks.
Eat me, you son of a bitch bastard!
No, eat me!
Please eat me.
You'll do.
Thank you!
What'd you take him, you son of a bitch?
I'll kill you for that!
Talk about your annoying chocolate bars!
But this one looks the most preferable.
Solid Curry
I tricked you, you cretin! You'll be expecting something sweet.
When I'm actually super-spicy!
Even among super-spicy stuff I'm the hardest to wash out!
Hey, this chocolate's old.
It's a weird color.
And it smells like curry!
What's wrong with this chocolate? It's the worst I've ever smelled!
I've been found out?
But I've come so far...
Mother... Father...
I'm sorry!
After his tragedy, Solid Curry released a new single showcasing his pain...
Entitled "Expiration Date Blues."
Yesterday I tasted just fine...
So why can't you eat me today?
But it never made it to the shelves.
All that aside, I've been watching you this whole time sneaking around.
Care to identify yourself?
I'm a love burglar.
What exactly is in that vault?
Wait... Why his head!?
Something's peeking out.
I think I know what it is...
When he says "love"...
He really means he's a carp burglar!
It's not what you think.
That's what I thought.
I won't let you steal it!
Uh-oh, he put an alarm on it!
Just stop it!
That one's Bo-bobo.
It's alright, young lady.
Oh, stop! Stop it!
No, young lady, I'm Santa, not the Love Hunter...
Well...
Whatever you call yourself...
Ow! Ooh! Merry Christmas! Ow! Merry Crueltymas! Eeow!
Boss, that wasn't the way it was!
I must overcome this! By the name of the one who's treaded the path of stealing love for 30 years...
Love Hunter Y, I will overcome this!
Love Hunter Y:
To Be Continued
What do you mean, "To Be Continued?"
Kids, don't try this at home!
People who do bad things will end up like...
Love Hunter Y!
End
I tried...
What does the "Y" in "Love Hunter Y" mean anyway?
I think it has something to do with Yakkun...
Should've guessed.
I am Purr-poo of the Four Lords of Margarita.
And to think that we'd meet in a small village like this.
I've heard about your epic bravado.
Like how you won against Battleship.
I'll admit that I'm impressed...
But don't get your hopes up all because of one person.
He was more of the runt of the Four Lords.
So it's only natural that you didn't know.
But to make myself clear...
my two lackeys here are far more stronger than Battleship will ever be!
"Give me back Volume 5 of Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo that I lent you a year ago."
Your nose hairs are showing.
Huh? Who said that? What're you talking about?
See, two of them.
That's exactly how it feels.
Should you judge a man by his face?
Should you judge his face?
This is turning out real bad.
Bo-bobo, I hope you were listening to what he said.
Because it's true, their strength is way out of our league.
As we are now, we can't take them on!
What a malicious aura...
Standing up's the least I can do!
Are you alright?
All of you... Get lost!
They're coming, Hatenko!
Let's show them all we got from the start!
Prepare yourselves!
Transform!
You again?
One down.
Wow!
He's so strong... Boss is so strong!
You're kiddin' me!? Was Don Patch really this strong?
"Damn! He's really done it now!"...
And he dashes towards Don Patch.
Give up on the glory, criminal.
"H... He's..."
Said the completely startled Choco Chocotto.
He felt like he was reliving his youth.
It happened ten years ago.
There has been someone eating in class lately.
Would the criminal please step forward?
Choco Chocotto thought that he wouldn't be found out.
No one in the class suspected him...
And no one would find out if he kept his mouth shut.
Who else was it going to be!?
"Like I'll forget that grudge!"
And his rage reached its maximum.
"Gwahhh!" said the beaten-up Choco Chocotto.
Two down...
T-That was not a fluke.
It must be the sunglasses.
T-That's...
Boss is the best! Boss is the best!
Whack-a-Gameboy Pig
What the hell's wrong with you?
What do you think you're doing?
A comeback!
Yay, me! I beat two baddies up!
He took off the sunglasses?
Hmm, guess you're pretty strong.
I never thought you'd take down those two.
Well, whatever.
You get lost, too!
Come on! Have at you!
Here I come!
I felt that...
That's nothing to write home about.
I never thought Don Patch was hiding so much power...
I can't believe it!
And those sunglasses had nothing to do with it!
Don Patch, you have to tell me...
Where did all that strength come from?
Alright, I'll let you in on everything I know.
But first I have to explain...
this scar on my left eye.
I knew it, I've been wondering about that since Episode 1!
You liar, he didn't even have that in Episode 1!
Don Patch was hiding tremendous amounts of strength!
But is this scar a memoir of battle,
or a souvenir of a matrimonial quarrel?
You old men, I hope you don't forget this!
Always remember to stretch before swimming!
Huh? What will become of Bo-bobo?
Just ask your nosehairs!
They probably know something about what's going on!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
He's getting married?
Who? Could it be me?
That guy! THAT guy!
I'm excited for the party!
I think it's a trap...
Oh, no! I don't have any good clothes to wear!
Are you listening? It's gotta be a trap!
Come to think of it, Don Patch doesn't actually wear clothes.
No, I want to go to the party!
It's a TRAP, I say!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Welcome
to the Evil Blood Mansion!
The
re
turn
of
the
Duck Underwear
!!
Don't tell me he's coming back!?
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your lucky color is Don Patch-color!
If you had a tie or lost, look out for Serviceman!