The man who holds the key to the scandal
is finally revealed!
We hear from Miss B-ko, the victim who he was stalking.
Miss B-ko, The Victim Who He Was Stalking
That man's been following me around...
Even though he's one of my good friends! It's too painful!
That's not protecting your identity!!!
That guy you've been wondering about
who's looking for Bo-bobo is named Hatenko.
He was a master of the Fist of the Key.
With the Fist of the Key, Hatenko LOCKED
Hair Hunter M Block Captain Hisashi
for twenty-four hours.
Fist of the Key
LOCK!
Sorry about that...
but I've LOCKed your body in place.
And somehow, Hatenko
turned out to be a lackey
of the Hajike gang's boss, Don Patch.
Meanwhile, Purr-poo, one of the Four Lords of Margarita...
came to Iguana Town with Soda Pop and Choco Chocotto.
Also, Don Patch turned into the sun.
He's so calm about it!
Boss!
Bo-bobo and Don Patch fought a vicious battle against Purr-Poo...
and were victorious.
Beauty and Heppokomaru were totally dumbfounded
at Don Patch's power.
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Welcome
to the Evil Blood Mansion!
The
re
turn
of
the
Duck Underwear
!!
Don Patch, you have to tell me...
where did all that strength come from?
Alright, I'll let you in on everything I know.
But I first need to explain...
this scar on my left eye.
I've been wondering about that since Episode 1!
You liar, he didn't even have that in Episode 1!!!
Let's go.
Hey, don't go!
Why don't you want to hear it?
Don't you want to know about the super-cool scar on my left eye? Please hear me out!
I mean, you seemed like you were really psyched to hear about it!
Stop being so cold to me!
I don't really care.
Bo-bobo.
The real reason why I've been looking for you...
was to deliver this letter.
Tsuru Tsururiina IV requested me to do this.
What? Tsuru Tsururiina IV?
Come on! You know, this scar...
It's actually a sticker!
It's probably part of a scheme to get me in some kind of trap.
It's a sticker. See, it's a sticker.
That's pretty sweet, huh?
"We've gotten married."
---Tsuru Tsururiina IV and Mako.
No way! What's going on here!?
He sent a wedding announcement? This guy's too polite!
She's sucking him!!!!
And today's the wedding reception...
So I've been cordially asked to guide you there.
Oh, no!
I don't have a dress that I can wear to the party!!
OK, Patcherella...
We're off to the party, so you can stay and watch the house.
Sister!
And while we're gone, you can separate the male and female chicks.
Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi... Purukogi...
You can't be serious!?
You better not screw this up!
If only I had a dress...
This one's male... This one's female...
Well, let me do something about that!
The Magical Fairy Godmother!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
Oh, my! What a pretty dress I'm wearing!
What's a dress without the accessories!?
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
Wow! these are some beautiful accessories! They make me look just like a princess!
And of course, the magical carriage!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo!
Now, hurry along, my dear! The party's just about to start!
I'm on my way!
Smell ya later!
Just wait, Masatora. I'm gonna avenge you no matter what.
Yo! There's a motorbike headin' our way!
The fuck's that?
That's Boss Patcherella!
The boss didn't abandon us after all!
Alright! Let's get this party started!
Margarita Empire
Here's the latest report as requested.
Bo-bobo and friends are headed towards the Evil Blood Mansion...
Hatenko did his job perfectly.
Alright...
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Send Gurin and Guran to the Evil Blood Mansion.
You want to send them out?
Bo-bobo, this will be your undoing.
Hey, Hatenko...
What's the ETA to the reception hall?
We're almost there.
Is it really in the middle of the woods?
We've arrived.
This is the Evil Blood Mansion.
Evil Blood Mansion
Alright, let's go join the party!
It looks too suspicious for a party! I'm pretty sure it's a trap!
- It's a cute ducky!
- Cold... Cold...
What's wrong, ducky? Did you get stuck?
Cold... Cold...
Assassin Corps Trooper Killalino
Hey, little girl. You like ducks too?
That weirdo duck-guy is back again!
Godammi-
Let g-
You're stran-
Calm down, Beauty. Let go of that door.
Bo-bobo?
Are you alright there?
What is she, the devil's daughter!? That was totally uncalled for.
Takashi
She didn't seem to care that I hadn't been in the show for so long.
And she just brutally attacked me at first sight!
Yeah, sorry about that.
I'm going to open the door for you now, so you should forgive her.
Well, make yourselves at home.
You fell right into our trap!
Shoot! The door's shoot!
You guys are totally finished!
So this was a trap after all...
I think we're the best at falling for traps every time.
They've already fallen for it. Everything has gone to plan.
So you've been an enemy all along?
I was right to suspect you from the very beginning.
There are all kinds of traps set up and rigged in the Evil Blood Mansion!
Once you set foot inside the Evil Blood Mansion, there's no escaping!
Not even a single mouse can crawl out alive!
Oh, there's a mouse.
It's great to be in the outdoors!
You may have been clever enough to deceive Bo-bobo by joining us...
But you're not fooling me!
You trapped us in a corner to fight those three...
And this is the next part of your plan.
No matter how you look at it, you're on their side.
And you'll never be able to understand anything.
What?
Whoever's on whose side...
doesn't make any difference to me.
I'm just bored...
Can you make it out of this house alive?
Good luck with that!
The lights went out!
It's pages of liver stir-fry!
Bo-bobo?
The low sodium soy sauce!!!
Don Patch?
The lights are on!
Huh? Didn't you guys get caught in the traps?
I got caught... in the traps.
Let's go home.
And... they're just walking out.
Don't forget that Gurin and Guran are heading our way.
How about I report to them about your failures?
To Gurin and Guran?
Don't tell them! Please don't tell them about this!
Tsuru Tsururiina's Greatest Assassin Gurin
We've finally arrived.
Now to get rid of Bo-bobo!
You ready, Guran?
Guran!!!
Guran
Hang in there, man!
I'm done for... That impact broke me in half...
Bastard! You've got no legit excuse to complain just cause you're a newer model!
I can't fold in half anymore...
Sending Message...
Message Sent
Alright,
I've just sent you a text message!
Read it and be happy!
Receiving Message
I got your text...
Do your best! From Gurin.
Thank you... Brother...
I'll do my best...
That's the spirit, Guran! Do your best!
Do your best! Do your best!
Idiot! Idiot!
Guran!
I've had enough...
Guran!!!
Don't press so hard! Don't press my buttons so hard!
I'm g-gonna break!
Why the hell did you break!?
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Meanwhile, back with Bo-bobo and company...
Why did we decide to go back inside?
This Evil Blood Mansion reeks of blood.
I've got a bad feeling about this place.
Rustle, rustle, rustle, rustle...
Is anyone in here?
Umbrella, umbrella, umbrella, umbrella, umbrella...
Kappa!
Are you alright, little boy?
Rainy days are for raincoats... Not umbrellas, raincoats!
Kappa
Of course they're for raincoats. Rainy days are for raincoats!
TL Note: The Kappa, a Japanese water sprite, is also a word that means "raincoat"
Kappa Fashion Show
The whole-body design...
The form that accentuates the body's lines...
The material that's made to work...
Kappa will be in this spring.
No, they won't.
Now, young lady, try it on!
No... I don't want to!
It's alright! Nothing to fear!
If you wear a raincoat... If you wear a raincoat...
You'll be an... idol...
An alien!
Just like us!
Huh, where did Bo-bobo run off to?
I finally have achieved it.
This is the ultimate research material!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo!
My research is finally complete.
Don Patch!
Nooo! Let me go! Don't do your research on me!
Don't do it... Don't do it... Don't do it...
Trash
Hair Hunters' Evil Scientist MAX Kiyokawa
I have immersed Bo-bobo in a special bio-fluid!
Now Bo-bobo has become the Hair Hunters' ultimate battle machine!
Bath chemicals! Bath chemicals! Bath chemicals!
Bath Chemicals
Bath chemicals! Bath chemicals!
What do you buffoons think you're doing?
Making it nice and warm!
What are you doing to Bo-bobo?
There's another intruder in the lab...
I won't let you lay your filthy hands on my research equipment any longer!
Now, come out of your tube, Bo-bobo!
Protect the research equipment!
I don't remember putting in this much water...
I put in too much bath chemicals!
It doesn't matter.
At least I have succeeded in controlling Bo-bobo.
And as proof, the insignia of the Hair Hunters will appear on his forehead!
The insignia of the Hair Hunters?
Hakata
Hakata...
Hakata!?
That's Kyoto.
Good morning, Professor MAX Kiyokawa.
Well, at least I succeeded.
Bo-bobo?
Alright, now teach that girl a lesson!
Yes, my Master, understood...
Wait, Bo-bobo... It isn't true, is it?
This be truly what that Hakata's like, ain't it!!!
That says Nagoya!
Beauty!
Don Patch...
And now I just...
Go for a slam-dunk!
Bo-bobo, how dare you harm Beauty like that! You won't get away with this, you bastard!
Those who oppose the Hair Hunters...
shall perish!
How could you go so far to attack Beauty? You've really hit rock bottom!
Shut the hell up! Give me your best shot!
Bo-bobo!
You villain!
You are too green.
Buy a Kappa lunchbox! Buy a Kappa lunchbox!
Kappa Lunchboxes: Once a year, on the banks of the river...
The Kappa make these legendary, mysterious lunchboxes.
It is said that the Kappa make their living off these Kappa lunchboxes.
So as we see the Kappa casually working...
the Kappa Lunchboxes are their only lifeline.
That's why the Kappa are so desperate.
If this keeps up, then none of us will last the winter!
We Won't Last the Winter
CD single "We Won't Last the Winter" - Now on sale.
(Not actually on sale.)
The lives of the Kappa are in your hands.
Please, both you, stop fighting each other!
This isn't supposed to happen!
Bo-bobo's just being controlled by that mad-reptile!
I know that. Then I'll solve this problem peacefully!
Vitamins.
Calcium.
The discussion breaks down.
It didn't work!
No way...
I shall annihilate all those who oppose the Hair Hunters!
Now that I've fought him, I know how strong he is...
I cannot afford to fight in close combat.
If I get near him, he'll attack me with his nose hairs!
I have to watch my distance!
Come over here everyone, all you lovely children!
Alright! Alright! Alright! Alright! Alright!
Don't get near him!
You've fallen for it, you evil demon!!
It was a fluke!
Don Patch!
You'd better think of your own situation before worrying about others!
What're you trying to do, jackass?
Hekkun!
Young man... Young man...
Is it power that you seek?
Who's that?
After this break...
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Young man... Young man...
Is it power that you seek?
Who's that?
If you wish for power...
If you wish for power... then you shall have it!
Oh, he managed to power up.
Then I believe that I too, will...
Power Up!!!
Who are you? Who are you guys supposed to be?
W-What happened to me? Is this... my body?
How did all this happen to me?
I don't understand... I don't understand... I don't understand...
I don't, I don't, I don't understand!
Teacher!
I don't understand!
You total bird-brain.
There's... no way that's true!
It's all true, you blockhead.
That's so mean...
Wanna go for a drink?
It was bad enough calling me a bird-brain...
But he called me a blockhead, too... That's going too far!
That's really mean of him to say.
But I feel better about it after talking to you. Thank for this!
"If there is someone hurt, comfort them."
This is the Gals' Unbreakable Rule.
Alright, let's get back to the Evil Blood Mansion.
"Whoever drinks more pays the bill."
This is the Gals' Unbreakable Rule.
"You don't have to pay if you're the one being comforted."
"Expect that coming and have money ready."
This is the Gals' Unbreakable Rule.
You're pretty good.
Same to you.
You're short on the bill.
The Gals' Unbreakable Rules:
To gals, these are what's known as the absolute laws.
We're back!
We finally got back to the Evil Blood Mansion.
I'll make you come to your senses!
Come and get some!
Well then, who are we supposed to be?
Don't drink and drive! Don't drive and drink!
But I wasn't even drinking!
Good job, Bo-bobo! Only those two brats are left! Get them!
Roger!
Will I be able to stop him?
Do something to stop him...
Hatenko!
Hey, Boss!
W-Why did he decide to show up?
Isn't he our enemy?
Man, oh, man. Babysitting ain't easy work.
Fist of the Key!
LOCK!
Fist of the Key
Boss...
My Fist of the Key will only work on Bo-bobo for a minute.
That's plenty of time.
Alright, let's use that attack for old times' sake!
Here, Boss!
It's going to the center!
Good morning!
What a turn of events!
The goalkeeper has finally woken up!
Come on!
Let's go!
Double Hurricane!
Attack!
Is this volleyball?!
GOAL!!!
GOAL!!!!
GOAL!!!!!
GOAL!!!!!!!!!!!!
S-Shit!
What were all of you doing?
It's the whistle!
Alright, Bo-bobo! Playtime's over.
Take them all down!
Huh? Take who down?
Get a move on, Bo-bobo!
That's an order! Beat them all down!
Do you know what he's saying?
No clue.
No way... He wasn't under my control?
Then what's he been doing this whole time?
You didn't notice?
There's no way Bo-bobo can be controlled.
Fools! I knew that! I knew that all along!
There's no way I wouldn't know that!
Okay, I lied...
Gurin and Guran died because of that lie!
That's right! That's right!
You guys are still here?
Genius Researcher's Pitiful Path
Bobobo News
The next day
And so, Bo-bobo and friends left the Evil Blood Mansion behind them.
Why are you still tagging along?
I can do what I like.
Well, I still don't think of you as one of us.
Suit yourself.
Check it out, everyone! Look at the Evil Blood Mansion.
This means it truly was the Evil Blood Mansion.
That's true.
That doesn't make any sense.
Sometimes these endings are alright.
Is this kind of ending really alright?
Will Hatenko decide to become their ally or not?
In any case, what dangers and peril wlll await Bo-bobo and his faithful comrades next?
No one knows!
Whatever happens, we wish them all... the very best of luck!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
So this is the ultimate Z-block base!
Yeah, we've got to stay on our toes.
Things seem to be more serious than usual.
Wait, isn't this the ocean?
Right, let's go swimming!
I'm getting an audience!
Don't be so serious about playing!
Don't let your guard down! The enemy's here!
Alright, let's have a showdown! With beach volleyball!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Arrival at the fearsome
Z-block base!
It's the ocean!
It's a quiz!
It's Forgive Me Mask!
Is this base a leisure land?
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your efforts will pay off on your test!
If you tied or lost, don't
forget to brush your teeth!