It's feeding time!
It's mine! It's all mine! Gimme all the food!
Stop fighting, you guys!
Listen to her!
Let's all get along!
My bad, my bad!
It's time for Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
What's with this opening!?
I wanted something new for this part!
I just... think we should try something new sometimes...
Didn't I tell you to drop that act?
A new opening... A new opening, you say...
But what's wrong with the old one!?
After clearing all sorts of traps...
Bo-bobo and friends left the Evil Blood Mansion.
The user of the Fist of the Key, Hatenko
became one of of their traveling companions.
But it wasn't a wholehearted decision.
Besides, Hatenko still remains mysterious
and smells of danger...
Well, whatever!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20xx
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
What's wrong with the old one?
Something new...
This isn't going anywhere.
Arrival at the fearsome
Z-block base!
It's the ocean!
It's a quiz!
It's Forgive Me Mask!
Bo-bobo!
Hair Hunters Z-Block Base
So this is Z-Block Base?
Yup, let's bring it down.
Bo-bobo's arrived. Just as Lord Tsururiina had anticipated.
Those hopeless fools.
They're just digging their own graves.
And they don't yet know the secret of our Z-Block Base.
What's our plan of action, Captain?
Should we give them a frontal assault?
Hair Hunters Z-Block Captain Dengakuman
Let's give them dengaku, nah-la!
H-How cute!
And that's why everyone loves Dengakuman!
Shower Room
Changerooms
Hey, Bo-bobo... What's going on here?
It's the ocean, Beauty! Come along now! Don't dawdle!
Boss, we should go watermelon bashing!
Don't be impatient. The ocean isn't going anywhere.
He's especially patient!
Right, Hekkun...?
Now you're joining them, Beauty!?
Finally this day has come...
It's so cold...
Looks like I arrived a bit early for summer...
But just you wait!
This summer a really cool guy's going to pick me up!
I'll make a boyfriend for sure!
Hey! Pretty lady!
He's already made his move!
If you don't mind, I can spread this here oil on you.
He looks like he's good with spreading oil!
What should I do?
Bo-bobo...
I wanna be a pop star!!!
A pop star!!! I wanna be a pop star!!!
Hey, you. Super-famous music producer!
I'm gonna be the next big star! It's gonna be me!
He's sure enjoying himself.
Well then, maybe I'll go in, too.
Is she wearing a swimsuit?
Ba-Dump... Ba-Dump... Ba-Dump... Ba-Dump... Ba-Dump...
Oh, but I didn't bring my swimsuit with me.
Amazing, Hekkun! You know how to make earthenware!
Yeah, I can make Jomon style.
But I can't make Yayoi style, though.
Where'd you run off to, Boss?
What the hell are you doing, you bastard?
Boss, you don't have to beat around the bush.
I can spread the oil on you.
Tha-That hurts...
I-I'm sorry!
A man, jealous? How disgraceful of you.
What's that?
This chick belongs to me. Now, get lost.
You goddamn robot...
Don't feed me your bullshit!
I say let's have a watermelon-bashing showdown over Boss!
You're on!
I'm getting stepped on. This hurts.
You're going down!
This is killing me. Can't feel my back. My back's gone. I have no bones now...
No, you're going down!
Well, let's find out!
I'm sorry, Boss! I'm sorry! I'm truly sorry!
Hey, this isn't watermelon bashing.
Like I said, I'm not gonna hand the Boss over.
You fools. You're trying to beat skilled watermelon bashers at our own game!
But this isn't even watermelon bashing...
We'll let you bitches serve first.
They're dissing me...
You're from the Hair Hunters, aren't you?
Robot #1
Welcome to Z-Block Base's special branch, Robot Block.
Base? But we're next to the ocean.
Robot #2
It's all over for you now!
You'll never make it to our headquarters!
The match has begun! Bo-bobo will serve!
Referee Seagull
Apparently, that's a seagull that was just flying around here now.
Bo-bobo, do your best!
Think fast, Hatenko!
Nice! Good one, me got it!
You stupid son of a...
Let's be serious about this!
The daybreak of rebellion is near.
Bo-bobo's second serve!
They came from behind!!!
Two points to Bo-bobo and Hatenko!
To them!?
I have done it, my lord.
Bravo, bravo!
I shall take your life!
I'm glad to know you're doing well, my lord.
How can you call that "doing well"?
Serve change: Robot Team's first serve.
Take this! Special...
RoboServe!
What was that!?
I was going to save this move for the nationals, but...
No points!
Why not!?
Until three years ago, my parents and I...
lived peacefully by the ocean.
Until you guys showed up!
"I want to return to the sky..."
That's what my parents would cry every day.
So I'm getting my chance to avenge them!
There will be no second serve for you!
Serve change: Bo-bobo and Hatenko Team!
Damn...
Since it's come to this, we'll be using our trump card!
You better not pull off any more of your jokes, you're doing my head in.
Got you covered.
Look who we invited over!
Nooooooooo!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Robot #3
Robot #4
Nooooooooo!
How about we set these fans all the way up to high?
Stop doing that!
What's supposed to be happening here?
Boss!
Boss!!!
Stop right there!
If you want to stop those fans, you have to do as we say.
You cowards...
That's our cue to set them high!
Boss!
Please, don't worry about me anymore!
You got to focus on winning your beach volleyball game!
How can I? How am I supposed to focus with you suffering like that, Boss!?
You idiot! If you're really thinking about me, then win!
Win the match!!!
The sun's going to set today...
It will set. Yes, it will set.
I hear you, Boss.
I'll quickly dispose of them, and then I'll come save you!
I say that... But I can't win with this dumbo as my teammate.
I have to swap him for someone else.
But I know those two will be good for nothing...
Go for it!
That one has pure potential!!!
With that helicopter, the nationals will be in my grasp!
Go for it!
You're the best!
You can do it!
Player change: Bo-bobo will be replaced by Helicopter.
I have to ask,
but you got experience in beach volleyball?
On and off for about three months.
Good enough for me.
Then we're gonna give it all we got!
Combine!
What?
Folding fan!
They're great!
Looks pretty!
W-W-We were just lying! We can't really combine!
They're up against some formidable foes.
It's about time for me to shine!
I know, right?
We, the Robot Team, are robots made with the Hair Hunters' high-spec computers.
Against us, who have accumulated the best technologies of the Margarita Empire,
you'll never win no matter how hard you try!
Bring it on! Then let's have a baseball showdown, bastards!
Let's do it!
Bo-shien Baseball Stadium
Right then, let's move out!
Yeah!
You guys are on the same team!?
Ahhh... Missed it!
Overwhelming Defeat
T-They totally suck.
This is great... Just what I wanted.
Right you tin-men, I'll get serious now!
Now let's have a showdown with beach flags!
That's pretty good!
Now let's have an exclusive news showdown to see who has the most shocking news photos!
Bugs Swarming to a Flower
We win, you lose!
Here.
Refresh
They're short-circuiting in a hot tub!
We risked our lives for this shot.
The Robot Team... They're capable of anything! They're far from normal!
How's that for you? Do you give up?
Are you freaking kiddin' me?
These guys are robots, right?
We just cut off their power supply...
and they won't be able to do anything.
Oh shit!!!
Right then. let's see where your power supply is!
Open sesame!
If I don't work hard I'll end up getting downsized...
Go back home!!!
I'm finally free!
That was my power supply!
Do you realize what you just did?
Without my power supply, I'll just freeze up and hang!
You have...
The V3 Engine!!
It's the legendary state-of-the-art engine model!
Why does this man have such an amazing engine?
We've got no hope in winning!
With all our powers combined, we still can't beat him!
Wait, look closer at his engine...
So, why are these guys still running?
For fun.
We can't win!!!
Looks like you've lost this battle.
We don't stand a chance...
Time to finish you off.
W-Wait just a moment!
We'll change our ways!
We won't do bad things anymore!
Like I'm going to trust you.
But we've really changed!
Please witness this combination technique!
Combine!
Forgive Me Mask!!!!!
Forgive me... Forgive me... Forgive me...
You dumb robots! You think that combination's enough to make us forgive you?
We'll show you a real combination!
Combine!
Forgive Me Mask!!!!
Forgive Me Mask.
Forgiven!
However, #3, you're not forgiven!!!!
#3!!!
Didn't you just say you forgave us!?
I never said it!
Cool idol style!!
Grown-ups are so filthy...
We don't want to become filthy grown-ups like them...
Roscal!!!
So Robot Block's been shut down?
It wouldn't have been any fun if they couldn't get that far. Right, captain?
Let's give them dengaku, nah-LA!
H-How cute...
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Hey Bo-bobo! Look over there!
That's...
the enemy's stronghold...
Hair Hunters Z-Block Base (Front Gate)
There's so much to make fun of!
Let's head in now.
Time to hajike it up in this base!
Is this really alright?
Quiz! Hair Hunter...
Pong!
Hello, ladies and gentlemen!
It's that time again for the quiz show, Hair Hunter Pong!
What's... What's...?
Huh? What's going on here?!
Host: Pong-taro
I'm your host for the quiz, Pong-taro!
Now, we'll select some contestants from the audience!
Everyone give our contestants a big hand!
Quiz
Why are you two joining this quiz!?
Thank you, thank you!
And before we begin...
Kappa! You're not allowed in here!!!
And now for the first question:
It's a silhouette problem! So go ahead and give your guesses!
A really big egg! A really big egg!
A really big egg!
A really big boiled egg! A really big boiled egg!
A really big boiled egg!
Mercator's projection.
And the answer is...
Too bad.
Indeed... Indeed...
And now, question two:
What noise does this animal make?
Squeal! Squeal! Squeal! Squeal!
Oink! Oink! Oink! Oink! Oink!
6x+3y=7.
Look at that! We have three different answers!
Well then, let's see which one them has got it!
Should've gone with that answer.
What's wrong with you two?
This isn't any fun to watch!
You guys are even worse than Hekkun!
Worse than Hekkun... Worse than Hekkun...
Worse than Hekkun...
It's fine. It's fine. I mean, I'm just...
And now, question 3:
It's the charades quiz!
In this humble world we live in, please demonstrate "humility"!
Right, let's do this!
You're on!
I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira!
TL Note: A Mappira is a dog-like Japanese monster, but the word is also used to express humility and is used as a greeting in some areas
I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira!
I'm a Mappira! I'm a Mappira!
It's a Mappira! It's a Mappira!
Howdy!
No way....
That wasn't good enough?
Sorry... I... screwed up.
I remember seeing that question on a prestigious university's entrance exam.
Now onto question 4!
Eat your box of natto!
What the hell is with this quiz? I'm gonna... Do it!
What the heck do you mean!?
And now for the final question!
The final question is setting out on a trip.
Everyone, please set out!
There they go...
Now that I've got rid of Bo-bobo...
All that's left is to take care of you kids.
Dammit! It was all a trap!
You son of a...
Here I go!
Bo-bobo!
Show host! Show host!
This is the final station, Show Host.
Please take all your baggage with you off the train.
Yeah! Samba! Samba! Yo! Rhumba!
What did you see in your aimless voyage?
Please tell me, as a man who can only live as a station.
Tell me!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
This voyage was a pure story that cannot be told!
You guys had a good trip!
So Pong-taro's down, too.
We can't let them get ahead of themselves.
They don't yet know Z-block's true fearsome secret.
Enter Radioman!
What now? An earthquake?
Radio!
Radioman
So what is Z-Block's true fearsome secret?
And wait... isn't Radioman a TV?
And yet still, Dengakuman's so cute!
I want him! I want to take him home! Seriously!
Eat it, nah-la!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
There's too many of them!
Help me, Bo-bobo!
Hey, Beauty!
Who are you?
Are you Bo-bobo?
Oh yeah, I am.
Why are you speaking English?
What's with that form? Have you powered up?
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Enter Battle Armor!
But... you're not saying that in English?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
New Bo-bobo is born!
With fishcakes!
Dad's doing his best!
Is that really Bo-bobo?
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you may have a
love-love love-love meeting!
If you tied or lost, wash your own dishes!