The Seven Rare Wonders of the World!
As Bo-bobo and friends were trying out a new opening...
They saw something.
Hey, Bo-bobo!
I've found the Hair Hunters' base!
It turned out to be the Hair Hunters Z-Block's base.
They were attacked by dangerous foes...
And a deadly... plus fearsome trap.
How is this a trap?
Congratulations!
You all got every question right!
No, that buzzer means "incorrect"!
Would you like to say a few words to anyone?
I'd like to say something to everyone watching this show!
Hi, everyone! Thanks for cheering me on!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Angel_of_Chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
denshousha
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Radioman
Radio!
I'm radioman, but I'm...
a TV!
My name's Radioman but I'm a TV!?
No way!
Oh, joy.
New Bo-bobo is born!
With fishcakes!
Dad's doing his best!
You're so surprised you're speechless, huh?
Well then, I'll pull you all, into the TV!
Can't move him...
What're you trying to do?
Get your filthy hands off me!
What's your favorite CD?
Wild Challenger, stuff like that...
Won't you come inside? We have snacks!
We have toys too!
And I'll give you 100 yen!
How cool does that sound?
Who would fall for that dumb offer!?
100 yen? You serious?
You'll really give me 100 yen?
We have comics too!
Really? You do?
Boss!
Right, one down!
Beauty!
Hatenko and I will go into the TV to save Don Patch.
If we're not back in half an hour...
call the police.
Whatever...
You bastard... Look what you've done to Bo-bobo!
I'll break you for that!
Try damaging me in the slightest, and you'll hurt your precious friends inside!
What?
Watch this!
Hair Hunter News Super
Is this the Hair Hunters' news program?
Good evening everyone. It's time for today's news.
And now for our first news item:
We're in trouble.
They're showing up on TV!!!
Zero!
It's time for Bo-bobo and Don Patch's
News News News!
And for our top story...
Today, two wanted criminals were at last caught and arrested.
Hey, that's us!
That's us!
That's us, us,
rock, paper, scissors!
I won.
And I lost.
And now, for our next news item.
What's with this news program?
Today, we have an image of the latest car that has hit the market.
Really? What kind? What kind?
This kind.
And also this kind!
Good gas mileage!!
Next we have out sports corner. Over to you, Patchmi.
Yes! Thank you, Bo!
Here are your latest sports news for today!
Sports Newspaper
And that was Patchmi's sports news corner!
Now back to you in the studio!
We can't read that!
I must say Patchmi, your sports corner is getting more popular by the day.
Why thank you, I'm so glad to hear that! I research it every day!
I'm getting pissed off just watching these clowns.
Huh? Have you seen Hatenko yet?
That's true, he hasn't made an appearance yet.
Next we have a shocking image sent in from our viewers.
I love this corner!
Today it's a
ghost photo collection!
Shocking Images!
Ghost Photo Collection
And here's the first photo.
Are you COOL with that, Hatenko!?
That's all the news we have for you today.
Let's finish up by giving you the forecast for tomorrow's weather.
Tomorrow's Weather
Bye-bye!
Yuriko! You watching?
You're in the way!
I can't see!
It's even worse when you realize that this is being broadcast throughout the entire world!
You've really done as you pleased!
It's too bright!
They found a bad guy!
Shou Mei
I'm Radioman's core, Shou Mei!
Enemy target has been sighted.
I don't think either one of you know nothing about Z-Block's secret.
It'll be a shocking truth for your ears...
What's the secret? I want to know.
Right then...
Allow me to show you!
A-Block
Strong
Hair Hunters are ranked in strength in alphabetical order.
A-Block
Strong
G-Block
H-Block
Weak
G-Block
Etc.
H-Block
Weak
Etc.
But in reality, Z-Block is the strongest.
Z-Block
Strongest
Even A-Block Captain Tokoro Tennosuke
is only as strong as one of our troopers.
What's more, we're 2,000 strong!
A-What did you say?
Ahhh... He got tangled.
That means that it's not us inside the TV,
but the two outside that are in even greater danger.
What's gonna happen to them!?
Let's get this over with!
OK!
Flash of Penitence!
Before the Flash of Penitence, there can be no lies!
You will confess everything!
I confess.
That I, Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
Bo-bobo Popularity
Poll 1. Character you Like:
Bo-bobo
2. Character you Hate:
Don Patch
tried putting down my friend.
You son of a bitch! That's real low of you!
And now, it's your turn... to confess!
I confess.
That I, Don Patch...
reported my friend as a lost child.
Oh, you are such a douchebag!
You want some, bitch!?
FrIends no more!
Now they're squabbling. It's all going to plan.
While they do that...
Did he just say they're all as strong as Tennosuke?
Captain, it won't be long before they're annihilated.
What shall we do?
Let's give them dengaku, nah-la!
Such a cutie...
Everyone really loves Dengakuman!
Nah-la-la!
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Don't assume we're generic, ordinary troopers.
The hell?
We're actually, in fact...
The First-Rate Chef Army
First-Rate Chefs!
Chefs...?
Chefs?
Now let's commence our cooking!
I'm stuck...
Should've guessed they'd be just as dumb as Tennosuke as well.
Help me, Bo-bobo!
Beauty! Heppokomaru!
End of your line for you two!
Bo-bobo, you're...
I'm sorry, Don Patch.
I've been hiding it for so long, but...
truth is that I'm...
a vampire!
He's a what now!? That's a big scoop!
We vampires can't live in the light. I cannot go on.
I've already been exposed to his light for too long.
So that's why...
you always had a parasol on sunny days.
Dammit, if only I knew beforehand...
No, I didn't! I didn't hold a parasol!
If only I knew...
Stop! I beg of you! Please don't hurt this vampire!
Nooooo! I'm turning into ashes!
Just kidding.
What!?
You dumbass! You were just watching an act!
Now let's counterattack, Bo-bobo!
He's really gone!
Hey, please tell me this is a joke?
Right? Someone tell me this was a prank.
Bo-bobo!
Now some weird guy decided to show up!
I can tell who you are.
You're... Bo-bobo, aren't you?
Thanks to the Don Patch Keyholder you gave me...
I was able to revive myself.
I am he who has been resurrected from the depths of hell, the incarnation of the Grim Reaper...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Double Twin
MK-II
Second!
That's such a redundant name!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo Double Twin MK-II Second
Shou Mei, watch as I will defeat you and leave this place.
And Don Patch RX Turbo K will lend a hand!
Hopeless fools! Even if you defeat me you still can't go outside.
You're stuck in this TV for the rest of your lives!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
I wanna go outside! Please, I just wanna go outside!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo Double Twin MK-II Second
is worthless at doing anything.
Stop acting like a baby!
Do something like pulling something out of your afro like you always do!
What the hell? You only have fishcakes in here!
This means... This means...
I have no choice but to sell oden!
So what would you like, sir?
I'll take a fish roll and a fishcake.
That sounds real tasty! Hope you get your fill!
Oden!
Loyalty
I-I-It's moving...
What's going on here?
My fishcake's gone!
I'm going to crash!
Loyalty
Assembled!
Battle Armor of Loyalty:
Chaos of Oden!
Chaos = Confused
I never thought you would wear the legendary armor, Chaos of Oden...
Now I feel better about you...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo Double Twin MK-II Second
Shou Mei, you may as well give up!
Like I'm gonna do that!
3 days ago
Dear, you said you found a new job?
Yeah, it's a full-time position as armor.
Wow! Daddy's gonna be armor!
That's nice...
But I hear there are lots of people being laid off in the armor business.
No need to worry. I'm still as tough as a youngster!
Taeko, Yoshie...
Dad's doing his best!
He's doing his best!
Truth
That customer's awoken his true powers?
Right! Time for me to lend you my power!
Truth
Assembled!
Battle Armor of Truth:
Stardust Mossfire!
Now, let's get this started.
The dance lesson of death, that is.
I don't think I can win.
At that moment,
Beauty and Heppokomaru were...
T-The pain...
It's only a matter of time before you guys suffocate!
Help me...
Help me, Brother!
Did you call me, Jiro?
I didn't call you, brother.
Z-Block Base Women's Toilet
That'll be the end of them.
And we didn't even have to make an appearance.
Phew... made it...
No!!
No, please wait Miss... It's not what you think...
It is what I think!
What do you want? What do you think you're doing here?
Wait... Please... Listen to me for just a second...
What was with that twirly-head, anyway?
Service!
Are you alright?
Yeah. Let's get moving.
But that was too close of a call.
That's why I said we should break in from somewhere else.
I have one thing to say to you.
This way I am workaholic.
Even if you want to make me happy...
We've got the sunset on the beach.
As soon as I screamed,
the chicken boy compromised me so greatest hits
I think you are the most variable trouble maker, you know?
You must go ahead!
OK?
How was that one thing?!
And did that actually mean anything...?
Whatever...
I'll take you down first!
After this break...
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
I'll take you down first!
O wind, in the name of the spirit of the forest Jennifer, blow for me!
Reveal your true power to us!
Battle Armor Secret Technique:
Perfect Hajike Block!
Alright! Leave it to me!
You dodged it...?
Where are you looking?
I'm not gonna let you lay one finger on my master!
Dad's...
done his best...
For the old man! Eat it!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Field Trip!
What is this? A technique?
And is it just the two of us?
It's not just the two of you!
The Oden Friends
We're with you too!
Don't count us out!
And this is how our field trip started.
What the hell is going on?
He's gonna break!
Isn't anyone gonna help him!?
He ate my pointy top.
That's why we keep telling you...
Take this, radish!
Can everyone shut the hell up!?
Quiet!
It's way past your bedtime!
Teacher, Shou Mei was being loud and we couldn't sleep.
Radish!
That's not fair, guys!
Shou Mei!
I'll have you atone for all the sins you've committed!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Burning Hand Hell Fire!
Was that really a sin I committed!?
Captain Dengakuman!
My left hand is like fire, slices through darkness...
And halts evil!
It even has a catchphrase!
Don't get your hopes up. You still can't get out of the TV.
What should we do?
Leave it to me.
I will use a move...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo Double Twin MK-II Second
That I can only use as Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo Double Twin MK-II Second...
Fist of the Nose Hair Legendary Reverse Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Metamorphose!
This move will break the TV and let us outside!
What kind of move is it? Will it really let us outside?
We have no other choice.
There's no time! Let's get going!
He's focusing all of his energy into those horns!
Does that mean this move needs those horns to work?
Nope!
You don't need them?
Fist of the Nose Hair Reverse Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Metamorphose!
What's happening!?
What is that!?
That's Bo-bobo.
Let this scene be burned in my eyes.
Victory achieved!
An egg...
What does that mean!? What are you trying to say!?
It's starting to hatch!
Hair Hunters Z-Block Deputy Captain Kibahage has arrived.
Hair Hunters Z-Block Deputy Captain Kibahage
An enemy hatched out!
Congratulations! I'm so happy that you were born!
What's wrong with you!?
I'm so happy! I'm really happy to see this!
This is usually the time when you snap back!
Shut up. I can do what I want, idiot.
Something's wrong with Beauty...
Right now, Beauty's head was having a hard time
keeping up with all the rapid changes of the journey, and was in confusion.
I can't keep up!
It's party time!
Please open your eyes!
Don't  hesitate.
Just go ahead,
and do it.
What was that, you bitch!?
You better not mess with me!
Sorry... Sorry... Sorry... Sorry...
I'm sorry!
Those are the feathers of the legendary immortal phoenix, Phoenifalco!
Is it possible, that he's going to transform!?
Phoenifalco!
Enter the Immortal Phoenix Phoenifalco!!
And the Phoenix just died!
How come you're dead!?
Aren't you the immortal phoenix!?
Just let me die...
Stop acting like a dead bird! Just take this seriously!
Fine, then. I'll be serious...
I'll be serious...
Section Manager
Phoenifalco
Episode 1: The serious section manager arrives.
Mr. Kimura, this print has three calculation errors.
I've corrected it now, so make 30 copies of this...
And take them to the sales department...
Who the hell is Kimura!?
I'm a phoenix, so no damage for me!
Ceiling!
Ground!
I don't get it!!!
Beauty, get a hold of yourself!
I don't get it at all!
I don't get what's happening, either...
Huh?
Hekkun, what happened?
Beauty!
The fight's about to start!
It's been five years since you ate me...
But finally I have my chance to defeat you!
Let's do this!
So you're tough enough to be inside me for five years...
Then take this attack!!
Five Glasses!!
In that case...
Disposable Chopsticks!!
He used a feint...
That means I can't use this pollock roe...
And with this oolong tea...
my combo is complete!
Damn! That's a dark combo!
Then I have no choice...
I activate this dustcloth!
And... you used two of them!?
It's your turn to choose the stage!
Give me the receipt!
I can't hand it over! I don't know how to use it!
I don't get what's going on...
If Bo-bobo hadn't used the dustcloth...
We'd be dead by now...
You understood that!?
You're digging your own grave...
Am I really?
What?
As long as I have these spectacles, that's enough.
Y-You don't mean...
Spectacles...
Taclesspec!!
He used it! The final magical communication, Taclesspec!
This means all of us will get damaged, too!
I have to go and buy some taclesspec...
Taclesspec Shop
Taclesspec!
It's all over...
The technical combo, Imperial Purveyor Taclesspec!
What kind of communication is that?
Drop it.
And clutch!
You're not using the spectacles?
You're not actually going to use it?
Taclesspec!
Taclesspec is no more than a simple word.
Does this mean your taclesspec is higher than my taclesspec?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hell Shrike Drop!!
It's a draw!!!
She's back!
That's as far as you'll get!
We'll end this with Z-Block's newest tank model, the P365!
A tank?
There's someone weird riding it, though!
No!
They're in deep fear of the tank, Captain.
Let's give them dengaku, nah-la!
But before that...
We kill 'em!!!
Z-Block's secret weapon...
has arrived without warning.
Do Bo-bobo and his friends stand a chance?
Is service time already over?
And where is Hatenko hiding!?
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
Now we meet, Captain of the Z-Block!!
Dengakuman's so cute!
Watch out! He's a hajikelist!
Then we'll have a hajike showdown...
So then it's going to turn out like it always does...
But this guy has some kind of secret!
Is it that he's something from somewhere?
Yes, yes. He's something from somewhere.
Hey, don't be so cryptic! Tell me already!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Our                  foe yet again!
strongest
Dengakuman!!
How many friends
can we make?
This guy's...
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, tea soup will fit right in with your meal, even a Western meal!
If you tied or lost, keep your desk clean!