A new hero is born!!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Double Twin
MK-II
Second!
The rebirth of Bo-bobo...
Oden!
Loyalty
met a father who was the President of the Eating Oden in Midsummer Society...
Was he really?
And they both combined.
Assembled!
Battle Armor of Loyalty:
Chaos of Oden!
However...
One egg won't be enough to fill anyone!
Bo-bobo?
Put that in the Oden.
Is that why he laid it?
Hair Hunters Z-Block Deputy Captain Kibahage has arrived.
Hair Hunters Z-Block Deputy Captain Kibahage
It's an enemy!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hell Shrike Drop!
And finally...
Z-Block's secret lethal weapon, Dengakuman, has made it into the arena!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Angel_of_Chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Our                  foe yet again!
strongest
Dengakuman!!
How many friends
can we make?
Service!
Let's give them dengaku, nah-la!
But before that...
We kill 'em!
Service over.
What's that!?
No clue...
I-I want friends...
Right then, without further ado, as you all know, it's me again, Dengakuman!
This time, I entered in from some yam paste...
So you see, I'm a bit nervous, but...
I got something to say to ya, so listen up!
Honey
Let's all eat honey together!
Let's eat, oink! Let's eat, oink!
Let's eat the yam paste too!
The yam paste, too!
Then let's mix them both and eat up!
OK.
The yam paste and honey made a little love...
Kids, please don't try this at home.
Hey, we get the point, so just start fighting already.
You fool! The fight's already started!
Just take a good look at your bodies!
O-Our what!?
Nothing's happened to us!
Right. You've both got completely healthy bodies.
And you should thank your parents.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Father!
Mother!
Your teacher's so happy you understand!
Well then...
Let's all sing along!
Ahh, Papan, Maman!
Yai!      Yai!
Ahh, we're so thankful!
Hai!     Hai!
You've loved us
with all you have...
Thank You!!
What the hell do you think you're doing!?
Hekkun, that was a very fine move!
I'll start with you then, spiky boy!
What?!
You meanie... You meanie... You meanie... You meanie... You meanie...
You meanie... You-
That will be enough for today.
I feel like I've seen that somewhere before!
Fooled you, didn't I...?
Here I go!
This always happens to me!
Always!?
Got ya!
I fooled you! I fooled you!
You stupid idiot! Now's my chance to finish you off!
Oh no! What should I do?
Owie! Owie!
What should I... What should I...
These guys...
are useless at everything!
This battle's way to high-level for me!
Hey, I've been wondering about this for a while, but...
Do you really mean it when you say that?
I gotta quickly find something to attack them with... I gotta find something...
Hurry! Gotta hurry! I gotta find something!
No way... What type of purse is that? It's really cute!
What is this? Let me see! Can I see this purse, please?
Give me back my purse! Give it back! Belongs to me!
Don't bullshit me!
My Dengakuman purse! Dammit!
What is this?
Dammit! Dammit!
"Dengakuman's Secret Notebook?"
If we read this we may learn about his weaknesses!
Dengakuman
He's practicing his signature!?
Man, I'm feeling way too sweaty after that fight.
Shall we go take a bath?
Sure thing!
Hey! We're nowhere near finishing this yet!
Baths
Two tickets, please.
That'll be 8,000,000 yen.
Talk about expensive.
Well, here you go...
That's the right change. Thanks for visiting us.
Hey, stop this screwing around! Just fight me already!
Hey, you listening to me up there?
Well, let's head in.
Yay!
It's a really tall bath!
Wash yourself off well, okay?
Yep.
...I get it. This isn't a bath. It's a waterfall.
All three of them were complete idiots.
Now it comes to this, I'll show you my true power!
What!?
I've lost. Forgive me.
I surrender!
Don't give up until it's over!
He's showing me such kindness!
Well then let's have a showdown with my specialty, the Flag-Raising game!
Let's do the FLAG-RAISING game!
Yeah!
Raise the RED flag!
Goddammit!
My left leg!
I broke a bone!
Okay now, raise the WHITE flag!
Dammit, I wanna win!
Ow! Now both of my legs are in deep pain!
But left leg still in pain!
Good night, mama.
He fell asleep!
Now's not the time to be sleeping.
No.
It's past your bedtime.
Who's that supposed to be!?
Good night, boy.
These are really nice blankets. I can sleep so peacefully...
It's too heavy!
I can't be complaining about the little things.
Because today is...
A beautiful day!
Hey, if you're gonna be like that, at least rain some arrows!
Okay! Gladly!
See? This happened to your mother because of you guys!
And you can't even apologize to me!?
But then... You won't be able to do anything when you go into the world...
Just like mommy!
I'm sorry, mother!
Wha-t are you talking abo-ut?
A lu-xury cruise aro-und the world fo-r 304 da-ys...
Lunch included!
A special deal!
Is he a...
a Hajikelist!?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Watch out for him, Bo-bobo!
We've got ourselves a Hajikelist!
What!?
That's right! Have a taste of my Hajike!
I'm so hungry.
Dumplings
Dumplings?
Warm
Cold
I guess I'll try one.
Thy Lady Dumpling hath arrived!
I-I'm Dumpling.
I wish I could've eaten you... Dumpling...
Well? Did you enjoy my Hajike?
That went right to my heart... Dumpling...
Don Patch!
That's real low!
Dumplings are not allowed!
You're asking for it.
I'll show you my Hajike!
Satomi...
You've been pretty cold to me lately.
Satomi Ramen
You were a lot hotter when we first met!
Let's go back to the way things were, Satomi!
Why won't you say anything to me?
I'll eat your roast pork!
I got to control myself. Violence won't solve anything.
Satomi...
Let's go back to where we met.
Let's remember how I felt back then.
Welcome!
We're here, Satomi. This is where we met.
This is just like old times, right, Satomi?
You really were a hard woman back then.
Don't get so mad. You really were.
Kiyomi Tonkotsu-flavored
Kiyomi!
What are you doing here?
N-No! It's not that I'm cheating on you!
There's a reason for...
There is a reason for all things.
Therefore there will be war. Learn this well.
By Nin Patch.
He was a ninja?
That really got to me. What amazing Hajike...
But now it's my turn to show you.
Bo-bobo Burger
You're kidding! That's so...
Trespassers will be prosecuted.
Dammit! That was Heppokomaru's weak point!
In that case...
We'll go with a double Hajike!
Let's go, you stupid dog!
Table Manners Golf
You spilled two drops. Disqualified!
Man, these rules are so strict...
in Table Manners Golf...
I don't get it!!!
Then don't do it.
I can't... There's no way I'm gonna die just yet!
Not until... I can look my brothers in the eye...
Ten years ago, I was born...
as the runt of seven brothers.
You're supposed to be a dog!?
I am, woof.
It's a little late to add "woof" to everything you say!
And you're walking on two legs! How are you a dog!?
It's because I look like this...
that my brothers always bullied me.
Are you meant to be a dog?
Are you really our brother?
I wasn't loved by my family... I couldn't make any friends...
It's all because I wasn't dog-like enough!
I decided to act more like a dog.
So I did that...
by taking up tennis.
How does playing tennis make you a dog!?
No one's gonna play you in tennis!
You'll be alone for the rest of your life!
I just wanted friends!
I just wanted friends so I could look my brothers in the eye!
Captain Dengakuman...
Captain Dengakuman!
Take a look! You have friends all around you!
All the Z-Block Troopers are your friends!
Dengakuman, go home!
That's right, go home!
Go home!
This kid's got nothing...
Shut up! Will everyone just pipe it down already!?
That's nice of you, Don Patch!
You're gonna wake the baby!
C-Cheer up, little guy! You'll make some friends for sure!
Like I said, it'll be fine.
This one's pretty strong.
After this break...
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Shall I introduce you to some new friends?
Huh? Really?
Bo-bobo's "Let's Make Friends!"
For our first guest...
we have Mr. Yamashita from Osaka!
Come right in!
Mr. Yamashita
Mr. Yamashita is first and foremost, a carpenter foreman.
Gross!
Now come over and become friends!
W-Will you be my friend?
I want to raise... I want to raise beetle eggs...
He's scary!
What's wrong with him? He's so scary! Don't you have anyone normal?
Someone plain and quiet?
What a picky guy...
Well... How about this guy?
He looks normal this time!
Except he looks like a lion!
My name's Wolf Gorou.
Wolf Gorou.
And I like to collect toilet paper tubes.
Go back to your cage!
And now for the last guest!
I beg you! Make this one a normal guy!
Come in!
Mr. Rubber Band!
It's Mr. Rubber Band!
He's normal!
You're stupid, aren't you?
And now we'd like to introduce the ladies team!
Lady Raisin
Little Girl
And now it's free talk time!
Nice to meet you, I'm Patchmi.
Nice to meet you. I'm Yamashita.
And now, I, Bo-bobo, will play the background music.
Um... I'm Captain Dengakuman of Hair Hunters Z-Block Base...
Asia!
Asia, Asia, Asia, Asia!
Shut up!
Apologies.
Let's all go for a drive!
Sure.
Let's go, let's go!
C-Can I come too?
No! No! And double no!
Let's quickly go.
Don't you get it? You're just a dog.
That's right... I'm a dog... I'm so pathetic...
And cute, nah-la!
Okay! Now it's game time!
We'll play a balloon-bursting game! Everyone get into pairs quickly!
Want to pair up together?
Sure.
Let's do our best!
OK.
Um...
Will you be my partner?
I'm not the fan of these vulgar games...
Pretty please?
The rules are simple.
The people with the balloons have to run around.
While the other people have to burst the other teams' balloons.
Ready...
Go!
Time to burst it!
Already after me!?
Raisin!
Nod bad, tough girl.
But all you've managed to do is push me over the edge!
May I suggest you look down?
Why?!
The raisins made some kind of pattern...
Raisin Mandala
You're standing on the Raisin Mandala.
Once you step in, it's all over. You can no longer move on your own will.
It all ends now.
Raisin!
Raisins summon the raisins! Raisins are for raisins!
She's too scary!
And so, Team Dengakuman won.
I can't accept that! Let's have a rematch!
Stop this at once!
Who said that?
Every one of us here are all equally small...
Mr. Rubber Band!
when compared to the universe.
Also, don't you understand that all this fighting...
is meaningless?
Now that we've gotten everyone pumped up, it's confession time!
Once you found someone you like in the group,
all you have to do, is go up to them and confess!
Can I finally make some friends?
Beauty! Come with me!
And Mr. Yamashita has confessed to Beauty!
Let's collect beetle eggs!
Let's watch them come out of their pupae!
Let's feed them cucumbers every day!
I hate bugs.
That's too bad, Mr. Yamashita.
Oh, look! We have the first couple already!
It's Wolf Gorou and Little Girl! Congratulations!
And now those two will move in to their love nest!
Please go forth with your love!
Stop showing off, you two!
But you're the one that suggested it!
Um... So do you want to be friends with me?
Please?
You will? You will?
The Raisins
We don't want to be your friend.
Dengakuman...
He's become a sports fan!
Go Japan!
Japan!
I couldn't make any friends again...
I'll never make any friends...
You can't let yourself think that!
I'll be your friend.
Thank you...
I've always wanted friends...
Not just so I can look my brothers in the eye...
But I was really just lonely for so long...
Thank you... Thank...
He annihilated himself!
What an amazing hajike!
I won't accept you!
Even if Beauty and Don Patch accept you...
there's no way would I ever accept you!
Why not, Bo-bobo? Explain yourself!
Of course. I'll explain why I said that.
Dengakuman, from what I saw before...
You just fawned on people and kept saying "I want friends".
But is it wrong to ask someone to be their friend?
Listen up, Dengakuman. A friendship only in name is meaningless.
Let us clash our opinions together!
Let us have a heart-to-heart competition!
If you can do that, only then will you be my friend.
Heart-to-heart competition?
Now, let us have
a one-on-one clash of hearts!
Come attack me with your burning passion!
This is pretty much a hajike duel, isn't it?
Yeah. It's a serious one, though.
I want to have friends!!!
This is my hajike, Bo-bobo!
I want to have...
friends!!!
Power of Friendship!!
Dengakuman.
Your hajike was as good as mine.
It was good, but you lost because you were alone.
There's no way you could win against the power of friendship.
Power of friendship?
Until we meet again, think upon the meaning of friendship.
But...
isn't six-on-one, a little unfair?
He's talking like a high school girl!
Alright, let's go home.
I guess I was more anxious than I needed to be.
And so, Z-Block base...
The strongest base of them all, was destroyed.
In their grueling battle...
Bo-bobo's team has proved their friendship.
However...
Damn you, Bo-bobo! This is unacceptable!
I won't forget this!
Stay tuned next time, nah-la!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
Hajike Block Base?
It's a legendary base filled only with Hajikelists.
That's actually really scary...
Alright, let's go!
Don Patch and I can win this alone!
Wait, what about me?
You can't.
Yeah, honestly, you really can't.
You think so, too, Beauty?
Mr. Don Patch, I'll come with you!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Hair-raising!
The Legendary Hajike Base!!
Wipe your tears with the
"Nu"
Handkerchief...
kerchief...
I'm going in first!
Don't push yourself, Hekkun!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, take a nice warm bath
and you'll stay healthy!
If you tied or lost, be careful of the shower temperature!