It's so great to have friends...
Friends no more!
Bo-bobo and friends were engaged in a tough battle
against the Z-Block Captain, Dengakuman.
Amidst the tough Hajike battle...
Dengakuman told us of his sorrowful past.
He revealed that he had no friends.
Out of sympathy, Bo-bobo decided to introduce him to some new friends,
but no one wanted to be friends with him.
With the power of friendship, Bo-bobo defeated Dengakuman,
and they became friends in the end!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Curses...
Bo-bobo's gone and destroyed Z-Block, the strongest of the Hair Hunters!
If this continues on, the glory of the Margarita Empire will collapse!
Now it is time! Open up the Hajike Block immediately!
Oink?
Hajike Block Base
There is a legendary base in the Margarita Empire comprised only of Hajikelists!
Now that the greatest warriors of the Hair Hunters have shown up...
what will become of Bo-bobo and friends?
Hair-raising!
The Legendary Hajike Base!!
Wipe your tears with the
Nu
Handkerchief...
kerchief...
Japan!
Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
Japan! Japan!
Gasoline Stand
Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
Let's charge ourselves up at the gasoline stand, Japan!
Yes, Sir!
Welcome!
Fill it up with Japan.
That's the first time I've ever heard that in my whole time working at this gasoline stand!
And is this even a car?
Is it... supposed to be a car?
It's a car!
I haven't got all day.
Got it.
But where's the tank filler?
Tank filler... Tank filler... Tank filler...
Tire
Tank Filler
Bear #6
Bring it!
Is he... for real?
I said bring it!!
Here comes the Japan!
Ten minutes later...
Man... Boss still hasn't brought us our lunch yet...
They're finally back!
Bear #6!
What happened?
The Hair Hunters killed him!
They'll pay for this...
You'll pay for this, Hair Hunters!
Right, guys?
Right, right, right, right, right!
Absolutely...
Positively...
Undeniably...
Unquestionably...
Without a doubt...
In my mind...
Unforgivable!
Alright!
Time to avenge Bear #6!
Let's crush those damn Hair Hunters!
Boss...
I'm afraid I can't go with you.
Why not?
My friends have come for me.
I must go back with them.
Friends?
You don't mean...
That's right.
The breeding season has begun!
That's a whole lot...
of flying Hatenkos!
The Hatenkos all gather together in the summer...
to lay their eggs.
As a Hatenko myself, I must take part in this process.
So the season's already begun...
But this doesn't add up! You're not even a bird!
It's impossible for you to lay eggs!
Now he's chirping all of a sudden!
Goodbye for now, Bo-bobo.
I'll come back in the winter!
Alright!
Take care!
I will!
One of them's got humongous sunglasses!
But what's with him, anyway?
Is he really another Hatenko?
Did he evolve?
Is that an evolved Hatenko?
Hello. Hiroshi speaking.
That's not even a Hatenko!
OK, I got it.
Ow!
We're having Hiroshi for dinner tonight.
He was wearing his helmet?
Who the hell are you?
I want... some ice cream...
I want some ice cream...
I want some ice cream!
Don't touch me!
I have soft-serve if you want it.
Ice cream!
Ice cream! Ice cream! Ice cream! Ice cream!
I have another one.
Ice cream!
Teacher! I won't play hooky anymore!
Hey, that's foul play!
But I can do better!
No tardies, no absences!
Here you go, Don Patch!
Yaaaaaay!
Ice! Ice! I-Ice!
Ice... Ice... I-Ice...
Ice... Ice... I...
What the hell are you playing at?
This is embarrassing!
Ha
That's the badge of Hajike Block!
I heard that there's a Hair Hunter Block...
comprised only of Hajikelists...
I never thought it actually existed...
C Attack!
Can Don Patch and I scale up to them, and still be victorious?
I wanna Hajike!
If he's with us, we can win!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Hair Hunters Hajike Block Base
is a legendary base comprised solely of Hajikelists.
It's a little-known fact, that only those who are Hajike-ing may enter.
However, they already knew about this fact!
Yes! They already knew!
The battle has already begun!
It's officially begun!
But we did our best...
Good morning, dolphins! It's practice time!
Synchronized Attack!
I would expect that from Hajike Block.
They don't let their guards down for a second!
What do you guys think you're doing?
Get a move on!
Return to the spaceship!
We're all saved!
We're heading through the atmosphere!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Now we can't do anything to them!
You saved our skin back there!  Who are you supposed to be?
My name is N & Ns, and I'm just a space traveller.
N & Ns
No need to repay me, by the way.
I just rescued you on a whim.
We would've been done for if you hadn't come along!
As long as you're on my ship, you don't need to worry about a thing!
The steering's broken!
Damn machine! Work, will ya?
What a sad little man.
Our only choice is to disconnect the main engine!
That way, your lives will be spared!
I regret nothing!
Ow!
Wall
We already know.
Come on, the show's about to start!
Bo-bobo!
Dolphin Show
Thank you for waiting patiently, everyone!
The dolphin show is about to begin!
Let's all call for the dolphins to come out!
Come out dolphins!
They drowned!
How'd they recover so fast?
It's time for the show to start!
We'll start with...
The Ring of Fire!
Good job, guys!
Here.
And for the final act...
It's already over?
Heigh-ho.
Fireworks!
Fireworks! Fireworks!
I don't get the joke.
It was a tough battle, but at least we won.
Hold it right there!
You can't call yourself dolphins!
And who are you?
I'm...
That thing that draws the lines that you find in schools and stuff!
Okay, let's go!
Ahh, wait! Can you at least listen to me?
Make it short, alright?
Sure.
I made a promise that I would one day see the dolphins...
In a physical education storehouse in a certain school...
I'm gonna go see the dolphin show today!
No way! Really? I wanna go too!
But I don't have tires like you do... So I can't!
15th Level of the Vaulting Box
This was the 15th Level of the Vaulting Box...
my only friend in the world.
And he was the most unused thing in the storehouse!
No one can jump this high!
They can't! And they're going to throw me out tomorrow!
Please see them for my sake, too!
I'll take a video of it!
But silly me, I forgot my video camera!
Then why did you come here?
To swim.
Well, here's your first lesson!
We sure helped him out.
Help me! Help! Help!
Yeah.
I'm getting water inside! I won't be able to draw lines!
That thing that draws lines went on to represent Japan in swimming...
and played a major part in the world championships!
World Swimming Championships
That's not possible! Not for a line-drawing thing!
But in this day and age...
TL Note: This is a pun on the word for "It's Possible"
Ant!
L!
Intruders...
Intruders! Intruders!
Crush the intruders!
Let me tell you your fortune!
Your fortune! I'm gonna tell you your fortune!
Hajike Fortune Teller
I'm gonna find out this, and that, and those,
and everything about you!
Please stop! Don't read my fortune out!
It's already too late!
Where shall I start from?
Let's see... let's see... let's see...
Fortunes for July
I can't read Chinese!
I can't read it! I can't read it!
I'm so scared...!
I can't read it, stupid! I can't read it!
Hey, save some for me, okay?
Oh, hey, Mr. Goat!
See ya!
Now you're gonna face your real opponents!
String Man...
And Paper Man!
Crush them! Crush them! Crush them!
There's too many of them!
What do you think you're doing?
Get a move on!
Return to the spaceship!
N & Ns!
But don't you want a better ship?
Aren't you that Apollo!?
Apollo
Wait... Don't let him fool you!
He's a space policeman!
He's here to send you back to Mars!
But don't you worry! Your savior is here!
I'll make sure to protect all of you!
All aboard.
It's nice and soft!
N & Ns!
Was that good enough?
Yeah. Thanks, gramps. You really helped me out.
If you hadn't done that, I wouldn't have been able to look at Boss in the eyes ever again.
What's wrong?
There's no more time!
I have to find the survivors of the Hair Kingdom, and fast!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Tea Ceremony Room
Bo-bobo and friends have arrived at the Tea Ceremony Room.
Tea Ceremony Room?
It seems a little out of place, doesn't it?
All Hajikelists have a taste for the tea ceremony.
As we drink the tea, it allows us to calm our minds.
This is probably the rest area for this base.
Is that so?
That's great!
Now we'll be able to take a bit of a break in here!
You traitor! You traitor!
You're a teacup! Who said you could put coffee in you!?
No, we can't take a break in here, either.
What's with the world these days?
He looks so cute!
Glad you could make it!
I've been waiting for you!
The Teacup
My name is The Teacup.
I've been expecting this battle so much that my tea stalk is standing straight up!
Not really, just chilling here.
Well? How about a tea ceremony showdown?
You're on! You've got me as your opponent!
Tea Ceremony Showdown Round 1
Excuse me.
Please come in.
Tea, please!
Gotta keep my cool!
Yes. Right away.
Tea
Here you are.
Bottled tea!?
That was great! Gimme another!
Well then, please wait a moment as I buy one from the vending machine.
A vending machine!?
I've returned.
Orange Juice
Here you go.
That's juice!
How much sugar would you like?
Two, please.
More sugar!?
Why are you drinking that!?
It tasted very good.
You don't know that!
Now I shall give you something...
Here.
But that's food you're giving him!
It can't be! I'm chewing my tea!?
Of course. It's ramen.
You're quite good.
But now it's your turn to make the tea!
You're on!
You dumb fool!
The guest always has the advantage in a Tea Ceremony Showdown!
Once I enter this room, prepare yourself for the battle of a lifetime!
I'll make a real shocking entrance!
Tea Ceremony Showdown Round 2
A real shocking entrance...
He's not coming, is he?
Nope.
He came in from above!
I don't have enough rope!
Why is he so proud of that?
Forget that ever happened!
So, The Teacup took that back
and demanded a rematch.
Excuse me.
Please come in.
Not again!
Give me tea!
You meanie...
Oh, no...
Alright! Let's get a move on!
Stairs
Hey! There are some stairs over there!
But there's only one stair!
This is the second floor
How is he climbing that?
This is amazing!
There are so many animals I've never seen before in my life!
Looks who's talking...
Unpleasant Beckoning Cats
Unpleasant beckoning cats?
What are they?
Lovely Journal
Business is prospering.
Customers are roaring in.
They're more unpleasant than I imagined!
It's time for breakfast!
That's unpleasant!
Didn't think I'd find these here.
Hey guys, check this out!
This is a Hajike bird.
When you hold this bird hard enough, depending on your Hajike level,
it can transform into many things.
That's godamn amazing!
The stronger your Hajike...
The Hajike Bird transforms into something bigger and more complex.
Can I give it a try?
If your Hajike is too weak, it turns into Captain Ishida.
Wait, who?
Captain Ishida
HQ! Please respond!
This is really fun!
Hey, how about you give it a try, Don Patch?
What a drag...
It disappeared...
Humbug. Let's move.
It disappeared...?
But it looks like there's only a bunch of strange animals here...
Now I wouldn't say that!
Tokoro Tennosuke!
You're alive somehow!
But how did you end up here, anyway?
It's too sad to hear or to tell the story...
Nu
What's with that weird handkerchief?
After the battle with Battleship was over...
I went back to the supermarket.
Until he bought me!
And he's been working me to the bone ever since...
Who worked you to the bone?
This guy did!
Captain Ishida?
I sent Tennosuke to the front lines in all my battles with the Galats.
He's keeping a cool face, but that is working him to the bone.
I am Tokoro Tennosuke of the Planet Earth!
And I fight in space on weekends.
I can't handle this lifestyle anymore!
I can't take you seriously with that handkerchief...
And by the way, I am the guardian of this floor.
Intruders will be eliminated!
That makes everything so much easier!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Cool MEN!
You got hurt! Are you alright, Bo-bobo?
It was a close call, but thankfully it just grazed me.
Are Nu handkerchiefs in these days or something?
I'm gonna be destroying this base now.
Tennosuke,
you wanna come with?
That's not a cute face!
Lookie here, I found some stairs!
Hooray!
What could be on the next level?
Let's go!
What a shock!
That must be the Hajike Bird that Don Patch had!
It was so big that no one noticed!
This is the first time I've ever seen a Hajike Bird transform into something so big and complex!
Who on earth are you, Don Patch?
Come on over and don't keep me waiting, Don Patch!
What is this man who's waiting at the top of Hajike Block Base planning?
And what is his relationship to Don Patch?
And what will become of Bo-bobo and Don Patch, who know nothing of this?
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
Don Patch! Let's cut him off over there!
Alright!
Oh, he's gone that way, Bo-bobo!
Huh? What's going on?
Don't just stand there! You help too, Beauty!
What are you chasing, anyway?
Piranhas! We're chasing piranhas!
It's a mouse! We're chasing a mouse!
No! It's a Hajikelist! And he's the King!
Just pick one of them already!
Isn't it obvious? All of them!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Death Match!
Fist of the Nose Hair
Fist of Rice!!
Let's fight nicely, okay?
Is he the King of Hajikelists?
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, make up with a friend you've been fighting with and Mamaslappie!
If you tied or lost, don't forget to groom your nose hairs!