The battle has begun!!
Oink?
Hajike Block Base
The legendary base comprised solely of Hajikelists,
Hajike Block Base.
All sorts of Hajikelists
were waiting there for Bo-bobo...
Everyone's really hajike-ing up in this place!
But at the top of the base...
What's taking you so long, Don Patch?
Just forget the rest of the base and come up here!
So that I can take you down...
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Angel_of_Chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: StitchOtaku626, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
Katatonia
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Death Match!
Fist of the Nose Hair
Fist of Rice!!
Let's fight nicely, okay?
Hunt
Alright! Now that I made my comeback...
let's give this our all!
Our new adventure together with yours truly has officially begun!
So, are you doing anything tonight, oink?
Ah, sorry, I'm getting a makeover tonight, oink.
I've got an English class, oink.
Then let's do something on another day.
Sure, oink!
The Adventures of Tokoro Tennosuke
Begin Game
New Game
Continue
A     Quit    a
Chapter 1
A New Journey Begins
This is gonna be an adventure!
You were peeping, weren't you!?
He's an enemy of women, oink!
What's your problem, oink?
END
No! Please! It's all just a big misunderstanding!
Bad Ending No. 4058
The Moral: Peeping Toms are the Enemies of Women
Continue?     a
Yes    a
No    a
There's another door over here!
Okay! Let's open it up!
Huh? Is anyone there?
W-What's that?
W-Who's there?
I shall take thy lives!
Dammit...
Surprise attacks are unfair!
Thou art quite skilled to dodgeth my blade.
That kind of attack won't work on us!
But you're really cut-up!
There doth be a full moon tonight.
Mine sword Shadowfang doth thirst for blood!
Where are you?
Come out at once!
It doth be a perfect day for visitors.
The one who shall make it rain blood shall be me...
Squeaknosuke!
Mouse Samurai: Squeaknosuke
He's way, way too cute!
O Bo-bobo, enemy of the Hair Hunters...
I shall take thy life in an instant!
I can be way cuter than you!
Too easy!
Here I go!
I can see... through your attack!
Don Patch!
I shall not lose to the likes of thee.
And the reason being is that I liveth by three tenets...
What?
Three tenets?
First: Follow thine own path.
Second: Know what is good and what is evil, and rid the world of evil.
And third:
Never flush the toilet.
That's just gross!
Squeak Films
The Tenets of a Man
Starring Squeaknosuke
Squeaknosuke!
You must flush after you use the toilet!
Don't wanna!
You don't want to?
I must abide by this tenet!
What's gotten into you?
I'm not gonna let you leave till you flush!
Never! I can't break the tenets!
End
I hath lived like this all mine life.
Thus I can no longer break the tenets!
Those are some messed-up tenets.
If we have to face a nimble mouse...
Bo-bobo...
we gotta become cats, meow!
Disguise complete!
You look nothing like cats!
Have at thee!
You goddamn mouse!
We'll catch you now!
Catch me if thou canst!
What did you say, bastard?
Hold it right there!
Thou cannot followeth me inside here.
We'll see about that!
He's out!
Hold it!
You're not getting away with this!
That's a totally mismatched shape!
He's doing it again!
Heppokomaru! Beauty! Let's use a pincer!
You take the other side!
Sure. Got it.
Now, come out!
Come on out!
Huh? That's weird. He isn't coming out.
Don't disturb my nap!
There was a warrior spirit inside!
How am I supposed to sleep with all this racket?
Keep it down!
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Damn that mouse...
Where did he scurry off to?
Hey, there he is! No, he's over there...?
Wait up!
It's no use.
Art thou done already?
If thou art ashamed then catcheth me!
What amazing speed.
We can't catch him if we just keep running around!
What a hopeless group I've got!
Leave this one to the professional!
Chapter 2
Full Speed! Tokoroten Jet!!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique: Tokoroten Jet!
I can now move at 300 kilometers per hour!
Try and catcheth me!
There's no getting away from me!
Over here!
Got him!
Letteth me go!
END
Bad Ending No. 9960
The Moral: Jets can't make sudden stops
Continue?     a
YES     a
NO  a
Tennosuke! Hey, Tennosuke!
He's awake!
Heppokomaru...
You OK there?
Were you worried for me? Just a piece of tokoroten?
Of course! You're our friend!
Friend...?
What are you imagining?
Thank you!
It's the "Nu" handkerchief again!
Letteth me go! Letteth me go now!
He got away!
Try and followeth me here!
He's gone in the hole...
Alright, I have the perfect plan.
We'll use the cheese to draw him out, and then it goes SNAP!
But this is a pretty smart mouse. I don't think he'll fall for it.
Hey, get walking!
The cheese was completely pointless!
You're under arrest for violating the Sword and Firearms Control Law!
Okay, let's go.
Sure.
So the mouse society is doing pretty good!
And that doth be just an act!
You simpleton!
Beauty!
Are you alright?
Ow, ow...
I'm fine. My clothes just got a little cut up, that's all.
Thank goodness.
Squeaknosuke!
For harming a woman, you've truly hit rock bottom!
I'll smack some honor back into ya!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
What canst one so slow as thou do to me?
Humans doth be no match for me!
Gourmet
Then I shall use my dried bonito!
How was that...?
Hold it!
Mine only option doth be to run!
You're not getting away from me!
Alright! Now that Bo-bobo's here we can hit him with a pincer!
But we can't let him in on our plan.
That's it! I can use gestures!
Bo-bobo! I'll go on ahead!
Let's hit him with a pincer!
Wow... What a clumsy cat...
Alright! Time to start!
Oh no! They've got me trapped!
Eat it!
You're both punished for fighting!!!!
Fight nicely, okay?
Bo-bobo!
Alright, let's move on up.
OK.
Huh? By the way, where'd Don Patch go?
Well I was kinda hungry over here...
Man, you're such a glutton aren't you, Don Patch!?
You just can't help it!
There we go, you're free!
Sorry.
That punchline was too goddamn light-hearted!
You're really taking your time...
But you finally made it...
Don Patch.
Captain's Room
This must be the Captain's room...
Be on your guard!
The Captain must be an amazing Hajikelist!
I've been through so much already that nothing can surprise me.
There's someone in the rice!
No! I'm not a topping!
Please! Believe me! Don't eat me!
I can tell already.
You guys took your sweet time.
You're so late that I had to come down to meet and greet you!
Who are you supposed to be?
Are you the Captain around here?
Oh no! It couldn't be me!
In fact, he's the captain.
Hajike Block Captain Rocker
No! I'm not a pickle!
Don't eat me!
I have been hired by the Hair Hunters to dispose of you.
But rest assured.
I have no intentions of fighting you whatsoever.
Well? How about we share a meal instead?
Thanks a lot!
Yay! Yay! This is great!
Thank goodness! I'm so hungry!
Wow! It looks really good!
You're right! It looks great!
They're looking for a fight...
It's full of piranhas...
It's yummy, so yummy!
Seconds, please!
Talk about the tastiest fish ever, right?
You said it!
They're biting you, you know!
I'll just drink it all at once!
That's not the problem here!
I had a feeling you wouldn't fall for a meager trap like this.
Of course not!
But you really fell for it!
You're such a fun guy, Senior Don Patch!
Senior? I don't even know who you are!
Of course you don't, because this is our first meeting.
How much rice does he have?
You son of a...
Name yourself!
My name is Rice. I've taken the title
Rice, King of Hajikelists
of "King of Hajikelists" that you refused, Don Patch.
King of Hajikelists?
What's that?
What's this King of Hajikelists thingy?
What? You don't even know?
You really are a pleasant one!
I ain't eating your rice!
Bo-bobo, why did you turn into bread?
Idiot! Why wouldn't I turn into bread?
How could I not turn into bread?
People aren't eating bread...
He got soggy!
People aren't eating bread as much as they're eating rice!
We bread are the leaders!
We can't afford to let rice be so popular over bread!
What's with you? What are you talking about?
Let's decide now which should be the staple dish: bread or rice!
Fine then...
Hold it!
Candidate Tokoro Tennosuke
Let's include Tokoroten in this battle for the staple dish!
Don't do it! You're not gonna win!
Now ladies and gentlemen, should the staple dish be rice, bread, or tokoroten?
Staple Food King Showdown
Who will
be No. 1
Staple
Food
King
Rice
Bread
Tokoroten
All those in the audience, please press your button to vote!
Staple Food King Showdown
Who will
be No. 1
Staple
Food
King
Rice
Bread
Tokoroten
Here's the results! Rice has 55 votes, bread has 42 votes,
and tokoroten has 2 votes!
Rice is the winner! It's rice!
Dammit! I would've won if the poll was limited to breakfast...
There were two!
There were two people who wanted tokoroten!
We thought it would be pathetic if you had no votes.
Cheer up.
You guys...
You guys!
Good! Then you better eat the tokoroten! You better!
Eat it for every meal! You better!
So this is what I get for showing sympathy...
Well, whatever.
I'm only interested in fighting Don Patch.
You guys on the other hand, I couldn't care less about. So would you mind going home?
You're getting on my nerves!
We can't leave without Don Patch!
Anyone who would go home now is not a man.
You guys...
Are you scared? Are you scared?
But... But... He has a short temper!
Here's Mr. Don Patch! Now no need to be afraid of him!
Why?
Fair enough. Since you're all so eager, I'll take you all out.
I won't let you do as you please!
To protect the powers of love and smooth skin...
The kinda tomboyish fresh girls...
The magical vitamin warriors...
The Gastric Juice Girls have arrived!!!
With a kiss that tastes like the scent of lemon... Lemon Princess!
With the sweet moment of love... Strawberry Princess!
The savory Melonette.
Take this! Lemon Prism!
Fools...
Strawberry Strike!
In the language of flowers, a strawberry means "retirement on marriage"!
Dammit!
I wanted to be grapes...
I'm so spineless!
Why can I never voice my opinion?
Melonette!
Strawberry Princess!
Quit bitching!!!!
How dare all three of you to beat me down!
You won't get away with this!
Can you let us off with this?
Like hell I will!
You're all...
W-What's that?
It's a giant bowl of rice!
You're all gonna get mixed in the rice!
After this break...
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Take this!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Gusto Burst!!
Here it comes!
Run away!
Running won't do you any good.
Don Patch!
Whaddya want?
I'll never forget you!
Help me!
What?
The rice is eating me! The rice is eating me!
Now's the time for...
those piranhas!
Nice work, Patchzaemon!
If we put the piranhas in, they'll make the rice tastier!
This is pretty great!
Now I can chow down!
This is the good stuff!
More! More! More! More!
We're safe and sound!
Beauty!
The piranhas are eating us!
What's going on? I can't move!
It's no use! It's too hard!
Beauty!
That's one down.
I can't free myself!
Why you bastard...
Beauty!
Once she enters the rice bowl,
she can't get out until I stop the technique.
And if she stays in that rice bowl for over an hour...
No! I can't get out!
What'll happen?
She'll be terminated just like the captain was...
by turning into a panda!
But he hasn't been terminated!
And he doesn't even look like he's troubled!
No! I'm not dried sprinklings! Don't eat me!
She'll turn into an ugly panda!
Son of a bitch...
Then I want everyone to come at me!
And I'll promise to defeat you all!
Sure! We'll come all at once!
They're charging at me in a paper clip!
Idiots!
Eat this!
Run!
I'm the one who got hurt!
Let me go!
Fist of Rice
Help me!
OK, great! Just let go!
Secret Technique:
Rice Strike!!
Shit, I missed...
So you singled me out...
Are you that afraid that I'll take the spot of the staple dish!?
I don't think so.
You moron!
You're full of holes!
I'll show you how different my power is from yours!
Ricesplosion!!!
Right in the face! The fight's over now!
Oh really, now?
My name is Ri-cerebrum!
Ri-cerebrum?
Everyone's
Ricerebrum
Episode 1 The Sharing Heart
It's time to start!
What's wrong, children?
Why are you crying?
I'm hungry!
I want to eat rice!
I see.
The End
See you next time!
It's already over?
Give them some rice then!
Why me!?
Now release Beauty from the rice!
Too bad for you. Because once that technique's been used...
there's no way to undo it!
GA
SP
GASP
What did you say!?
What kind of acting is that?
I can't budge!
Beauty!
We're coming to save you!
That girl has another 40 minutes before she turns into a panda!
What!?
Beauty
Panda
That's not what a panda looks like!
Bo-bobo, we can't let him deceive us.
Remember that the rice is part of his technique.
If we defeat him, the rice will be gone!
You're the smart one, aren't you?
But that's assuming can defeat me, which you can't!
Let's test that, shall we?
Get him now! Don't worry about me!
Let me go, goddammit!
Good job, Tennosuke!
We'll take care of the rest!
They really don't care about what happens to Tennosuke!
Tennosuke!
There's still a survivor!
Are you alright?
Have this as a keepsake from me...
It's the "Nu" handkerchief!
So this is how it ends...
Right, then! Let's end this!
Yeah!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Rice Tsunami!
Followed by...
Then with a...
Bo-bobo!
Don Patch! Tennosuke!
What's with them? They're way into their Hajike!
I've never taken this much damage before...
This guy's especially dangerous! He's no pushover!
To think that such a man exists...
They're back!
It hurts!
I'm feeling pain all over!
You're safe!
Rice!
I don't care how many injuries I take!
But...
I'll never forgive anyone who hurts my friends!
Bo-bobo!
Shut the hell up!
You're all gonna get mixed in the rice!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Gusto Burst!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Guard!!!
That was a close one...
You fool! Look behind you!
Don Patch Guard!!!
You bastard! Now you've really done it!
Survival of the Fittest!
I've managed to survive somehow!
Friends are everything!
He-He's amazingly persuasive!
Wait, how?
Rice!
Do you really call yourself the King of Hajikelists?
You're hardly Hajike-ing at all!
Of course I haven't, that's because I've yet to even begin Hajike-ing.
It's still only snacktime.
But it's getting close to dinner time! That's when my Hajike peaks!
Allow me to show you the greatest dinner show ever!
What did you say?
Just how much is he gonna hajike when it's dinner time?
Was Rice's Hajike up until now...
only snacktime-level?
If snacktime was that great...
how great will dinner be?
Bo-bobo is facing...
his greatest foe yet!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
If this keeps up, I'll totally turn into a panda!
Don't worry! I'll defeat Rice for sure!
Leave the Hajike showdown to me! I'll put him to shame!
You two are so dependable!
Hey! I'm the king!
No, I am!
Wanna fight, bastard?
Now's not the time to be fighting!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Bo-bobo
Rice's
30-minute Cooking!
Ma'am,
how do you like tonight's menu?
Who will take the seat of King?
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, all your plans will go without a hitch if you eat sweet-and-sour pork!
If you tied or lost, be sure you enjoy your meals!