30-minute Cooking with Rice!!
It's time for 30-minute Cooking with Rice!!
Alright, so what shall we be cooking today?
Let's make some Pretty-Boy style rice!
First we wash the rice.
And next, we're gonna steam the rice...
But here's the important point!
We'll add a subtle flavor by putting in about three watermelons!
It's in season right now!
How is that a "subtle" flavor!?
Dear, please don't read the paper at the dinner table.
So, what shall we do while we wait for the rice to cook?
Let's see...
How about I tell you... my secret?
His secret!?
The Pretty-Boy's Surprising Secret Revealed!... After this!
My name is Rice. I've taken the title
Rice, King of Hajikelists
of "King of Hajikelists" that you refused, Don Patch.
It turns out...
that Rice is a pretty-boy Hajikelist
that's out to defeat Don Patch!
I'll mix you in with my rice!
Eat this! Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Gusto Burst!!
Followed by...
Then with a...
This is not the time for swimming lessons!
She was exactly correct, of course.
After being trapped in the rice, Beauty only has one hour left!
If she remains in the rice for an hour...
No! I can't get out!
she'll be terminated...
by turning into a panda!
The time limit draws ever closer!
Can Bo-bobo defeat the Hajike King Rice, and rescue Beauty from the huge bowl of rice?
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Angel_of_Chaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: SweetDevilStitch, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Bo-bobo
Rice's
30-minute Cooking!
Ma'am,
how do you like tonight's menu?
Do you really call yourself the King of Hajikelists?
You're hardly Hajike-ing at all.
Of course I'm not. I haven't even started Hajike-ing yet.
Dinnertime starts at six.
And dinnertime is when my Hajike peaks!
Allow me to show you the greatest dinner show ever!
What the...!?
Just how much will he Hajike at six?
Take a look at that clock behind me.
Man
Soft
Hard
Ippon
Waza-Ari
Yuko
What's the deal with that clock!?
It's 5:55!
There's only five minutes left till dinnertime!
Where do they sell that?
"King of Hajikelists" is a title given to the greatest of all Hajikelists.
And you'll get to see me Hajike in five minutes.
Then let's smack you down in those five minutes!
Bo-bobo Punch!
Don Patch Kick!
I ♥ Tokoroten
Tokoroten Promotion.
Bo-bobo Chop!
Don Patch Headbutt!
I ♥ Tokoroten
Tokoroten Promotion.
Now, say it with me!
A tokoroten a day...
Come on, take this seriously!
He split into pieces!
No need to fret, my boy!
My head and body are of one body and soul!
Assemble, body!
Combine!
That's the ticket!
Tennosuke's back in action!
How's that? Impressed yet?
And you are...?
Dammit!
It's almost 6:00!
One point for wearing black tights!
Black tights means it's 6:00!
What the hell!? Seriously, where do they sell clocks like that!?
Dammit! It just turned 6:00!
He's gonna become the King of Hajikelists!
Respect your parents ! ! !
He's such a good guy...
Is that your response?
I want to massage... someone's shoulders or back...
What's the deal with that vigor?
Now I want to respect my parents too!
What do you want?
I did peepee on me...
What is he, a baby?
Well, don't just sit there, moron! Take this and wipe it off...
Tea
I lied.
They're quite stiff aren't they, Mother!?
That's one down.
Respect your parents...
He's our demographic target!
This is bad! He's an unbelievable Hajikelist!
It appears that my bangs are in the way. Perhaps I should use a hairband...
You ready? Dinnertime has just begun!
But that's a shower cap!
I hate to admit it, but that looks cool...
Seriously!?
Papa!
Fine with me, Rice! I'll take you on!
Wow! He's all wobbly!
I feel it...
You're quite good, sonny...
More! Massage me more!
What the hell is this?
It's tokoroten.
That's two down.
Hekkun!
Tennosuke!
Hang in there, guys!
Come here, you bastard! I'll take you down!
Thank you ever so much, Rice.
Don't mention it, mother.
That was a close on!
He was just about to respect his parents on me!
Damn you, Rice-Boy!
Let me challenge you to a four-panel duel!
Battle 1
Here we go!!!!
TL Note: This is a reference to the manga Tsurupika Hagemaru
Lucky me! Now I don't have to buy a rug-beater!
Cheapskate!!!
Battle 2
It's my turn now!!!!
Slip on this!
The banana was pointless!!!
He's sharp!
He's got Bo-bobo on the ropes!
What intense concentration...
Rice!
If you really are the King of Hajikelists...
then I must surpass you, not matter what!
Hajike
Now is the time to overcome him!
I'd like to see you try!
But you still don't understand a single thing!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
There is no love like a father's!
Respecting your parents is no excuse to hurt others!
Your mother is grieving over you!
That felt... so good...
The way... you showed respect to your parents...
I could get used to it.
Fine then. Let me show my respect for your attack...
by getting deadly serious on you!
Rice
Now, show me what you got!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Y-You're a pervert!
A pervert?
Why are you calling my special Hajike King outfit perverted?
Oh, no!
I put my pajamas on by mistake!
Those are your pajamas!?
Wait, just a minute!
I've got a King outfit which is so much better!
Here we go.
Incredible!
An outfit fit for a King, is it not?
It really is! I could tell you're a King at first glance!
It's the King!
The King?
When I wear this around town, everyone knows that I'm the king!
You wear that around town!?
Splendid, is it not?
It's great!
Yeah, it's great!
Upsy-daisy!
You're mine!
Take this!
King Flash!
My eyes!
M-M-M-M-My eyes!
Oh! It's fantastic!
Bo-bobo!
We're alone at last, Don Patch.
Because you spurned the title of King of Hajikelists...
no one has accepted me as the true King of Hajikelists.
Get ready to face me, Don Patch!
Let us decide who is the true King of Hajikelists!
I'm not out of this fight just yet!
Bo-bobo!
Then I'll take you both on at once!
Hajike Secret Technique 1:
Stance of the Anemone!
Look! It's an anemone!
Were you born yesterday or something? That won't fool me!
It'll never even fool anyone!
And it'll never fool me...
But your face just turned into a fish!
You clownfish!
Silly Don Patch...
I won't be fooled by him twice!
Then how about this?
Hajike Secret Technique 2:
Stance of the Automated Telling Machine!
Now withdraw all you'd like.
Just five hundred dollars...
He fell for it again!
Out of service!
And finally, Hajike Secret Technique 3:
Stance of the Witch!
Now have this delicious, tasty apple, Snow White!
Apple...
He just became the woodcutter from Princess Kaguya by mistake!
That was a new low!
You just gave him a poisoned apple!
I-I didn't!
You're talking to a Hajikelist!
I fight purely with Hajike and nothing else!
No cheap tricks from me!
That means the murderer is still nearby...
Inspector Nose Hair and the Case of the Steam Murder
"You cat burglar..." The housekeeper saw
A mysterious parental health handbook!
The Demon Bride that Disappeared in the All-you-can-eat Crab Restaurant at Night
Part 36 Conclusions Episode Three Chapter 1
And so...
we reconsidered who could have poisoned the apple.
The crime took place at 6:15.
There's no question that the murderer poisoned an apple...
in order to frame Rice.
But who could have done that?
The way I see it, this narrows down our suspects to these three.
More like...
It's 100% gotta be Tokoro Tennosuke!
It wasn't me!
This can't be happening...
Then, just when we all thought the case was closed...
Don Patch!
How are you alive!?
It's so sweet!
Quit making those confusing reactions!
Fin
You're as good as they say.
You're fighting on equal grounds with me at dinner time.
He hid inside the rice!
Don't get the wrong idea, please.
This bowl of rice allows me to greatly increase my Hajike power!
Damn him!
Is he gonna power up again?
It's full of piranhas!
What the hell!?
I almost got turned into fish food.
But now I've managed to power up myself!
You moron!
I'll just power up myself!
Oh, crap!
What's gonna happen?
Whatever it is, it's gonna be terrifying!
It's a dog!
Or is it...
Beauty?
A dog? Or is it...
Beauty? Or is it...
Beauty!
It's Beauty!
Hooray! It's Beauty!
Just kidding!
It's a dog!
The horror!
Power-up complete!
Impressive, Don Patch.
Rice...
what do you say we end this?
Can't agree more...
Don Patch!
What's the deal with their aura?
You better stay outta this one, Bo-bobo.
Alright!
Limit Break!!!
Don Patch!
That's quite the expression!
Now I can declare myself the true King of Hajikelists!
Don Patch!
Now, time for the grand finale!
I've already achieved my goal,
so I don't need this base any longer!
Those three in the rice will die, too!
A beautiful finale, don't you agree!?
Bo-bobo!
And this time... Scissors!
You can relax now. It's my dinnertime now.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
It has been almost one hour since Bo-bobo's battle with Rice began.
What am I gonna do? The time limit's almost up!
It's almost an hour since I've been stuck in the rice!
Please no, I don't wanna turn into a panda!
It's too late to save the girl now.
An hour has already passed.
What!?
No one can stop it now.
Now... change into a panda!
No!!
After an hour passes, change into this.
So I do it myself!?
I've turned into a cuddly panda!
Is that what you expected!?
She played along for a second!
How dare you do that to Beauty!
You will pay for your evil deeds!
Too slow!
Nice job, Bo-bobo!
Now beat him down with your best move!
Leave it to me, Heppokomaru!
I'll do that attack you've been looking forward to...
Secret Technique:
I can't escape him!
Knee-Bend!
I haven't been looking forward to that...
Was that from that attack!?
Bo-bobo Hospital
This is a serious injury! I gotta hurry to the hospital...
Perfect! There's a hospital over there!
Am I ever gonna get better, Doctor?
Just give it to me straight!
I took an X-ray of you, but...
there don't seem to be any injuries.
There's a tumor on the ear!
Is that the problem!?
Now I'll have you eat my attack!
Fist of Rice:
Rice Cyclone!
Alright, then how about this?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The Three Little Bo-bobo Pigs!
Let's all build a house that can stand the typhoon!
Yeah!
House of Straw
The oldest Bo-bobo pig built a house of straw.
House of Sticks
The second Bo-bobo pig built a house of sticks.
St. Michael's Cleopatra Palace
The youngest Bo-bobo pig built St. Michael's Cleopatra Palace.
That's some amazing architecture!
What the...!?
You bastard!
For our lost brother!
Secret Technique: Piggy Bank!
I-It's no use.
We can't do anything... to harm it!
Brother!
Not even the Bo-bobo pigs could stop it!
Is that all you can Hajike?
If that's all, you can never compare to me, the King of Hajikelists!
After all, I am the King!
What's going on? I-I suddenly felt faint!
What's the meaning of this?
It can't be...
Has my...
Why didn't you tell me we're filming?
Has my body been unable to keep up with his Hajike?
That's not possible! It's ridiculous!
Is he...
Is he Hajike-ing way more than the King could ever Hajike!?
It's time for your punishment!
This one's for Beauty!
Bo-bobo!
This one's for Heppokomaru!
This one's for Tennosuke!
Bo-bobo!
This one's for Don Patch!
Bo-bobo.
And this one's...
for all the animals that are suffering from the effects of global warming!
Bo-bobo...
And now to finish you off!
I am the King of Hajikelists!
I'll never lose to the likes of you!
Hajike Ultimate Secret Technique:
Stance of the Mud Puppy!
Alright!
I'm now the super-popular mud puppy!
How about that? I'm so cute you can't even attack me!
Uppa!
That's played out!
That was way too close.
I wouldn't have been able to attack if he were a frill-necked lizard.
Well in that case...
Stance of the Frill-Necked Lizard!
He attacked me anyway!
It all ends now, Rice!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Festival!
Show yourself, boogers!
Yes! Finally some screentime!
Let's go wild!
What's going on?
Gentlemen, let's get some results and show Bo-bobo...
what we're really made of!
Due to their few appearances, the boogers were on fire!
It's raining...
We're rained out!
Stop it! You're going up my nose!
After this day, 20% of Bo-bobo's boogers lived in Rice's nose.
It's almost the lantern festival.
I know.
We gotta set the welcoming fires.
Please get out of there!
Rice!
I will surpass you, no matter what!
Don't get ahead of yourself! I'm still the King!
Pinappudding!
That's my style of finale. Can't say it's that beautiful, though.
You did it, Bo-bobo!
Glad to see you safe, Don Patch.
He did it!
Bo-bobo's the victorious champion!
Now that makes him the King!
Hey! You guys are heavy!
Wait, what's going on here?
And so, the Hajike Block Base was destroyed.
The Hajike showdown ended in Bo-bobo's victory!
Farewell, former King of Hajikelists...
our young idol, Rice!
Not so fast!
I'll still be there in the next episode!
While you wait, remember to respect your parents, all you Hajikelists of the nation!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
We just managed to get out of Hajike Block Base, but now we're at OVER's castle?
If it's a castle, doesn't that make the boss a king?
Then that makes me the queen!
I think it's a different kind of castle.
There are ninjas and stuff.
Then I doth be the feudal lord.
And I doth be the princess!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Stormy Ninja Castle!
Lips and Rubies and a Pig's Butt...
What the hell kind of anime is this anyway!!
Don't ask me...
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, go Hajike at the beach for good times!
If you tied or lost, watch out for bug bites!