Shocking Footage!
The Rising Star
Pretty-Boy Character Hajiked Too Far!!
Oh, no!
I put my pajamas on by mistake!
Those are your pajamas!?
On the top floor of the Hair Hunters Hajike Block Base...
Bo-bobo and Rice engaged in a fierce Hajike battle...
over the title of the true King of Hajikelists.
And the one who stood up against Rice was...
Who was it? Bo-bobo? Don Patch?
Or was it...
Beauty!
I've turned into a panda!
Well you see... that was...
Don't get ahead of yourself! I'm still the King!
Pinappudding!
Lies! It's all lies!
You did it, Beauty!
Glad to see you safe, Don Patch.
He's lying!
Don't believe a word he says!
Thanks to Beauty, the Hajike Block Base was destroyed.
No! I said no!
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: SweetDevilStitch, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
I never imagined that such a great Hajikelist existed...
I shall admit defeat.
I truly have lost.
This is the insignia of the King of Hajikelists.
Only you are truly worthy of wearing this pendant.
Please accept it.
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo, the New King of Hajikelists, is born!
So not fair...
In return for your kindness, allow me to give you this.
I ♥ Tokoroten
Tokoroten Promotion Goods.
Thank you kindly!
He actually put them on! And he even thanked him!
That was a very fine battle.
Who's there?
The walls have ears, the doors have eyes...
Where is that coming from?
And also...
the ceilings have mouths!
That's not a part of the expression!
And who are you, anyway!?
Who the hell are you?
I am merely a ninja who serves OVER,
one of the Four Lords of Margarita.
Puckered Lips
My name is Puckered Lips!
The Four Lords of Margarita!?
Phew
Oh good, he didn't comment on my name...
The Stormy Ninja Castle!
Lips and Rubies and a Pig's Butt...
What the hell kind of anime is this anyway!!
You ought to know how grave your situation is!
Know that I am classed as a first-rate ninja!
I'm only sent out for highly important missions!
What kinds of important missions do you do?
Don't be surprised at this, now.
Stuff like watching girls' tennis.
How is that a mission?
That's so amazing of you!
So how did it turn out?
But of course,
I didn't get a glimpse! Something got in my eyes!
Wait, wasn't it the match you were watching?
That's oh so amazing!
I was indeed a third-born child.
Nobody cares.
Bo-bobo.
My reason for approaching you
is to see if you are worthy of fighting Lord OVER.
What's wrong?
It appears it has activated.
That's Lord OVER's Murder Seal.
The insignia on his jacket moved to his neck!
The Murder Seal drains out all the power from his body...
until there is no more, thus ending his life!
I believe he placed it on you when he hired you.
Rice never really wanted to defeat us to begin with!
He just wanted a fair Hajike showdown!
You big lip son of a bitch!
I'll shut that damn mouth of yours!
Then we'll help you out!
Let's have a battle of ninja arts!
I'll take you on all at once!
Ninja Arts: Concealment Technique!
They're gone!
Where could they be hiding?
Prepare yourself for a surprise attack!
Go on, get out there.
But I don't wanna!
I'll let you borrow my video games...
Huh? You will? Alright!
Blunt-Edge Slash!
As for the other one hiding, come out!
Game Console
Whatever! Just get out!
Blunt-Edge Slash!
That leaves one left...
but where could he be?
Is this happening!?
1 Hour Later
Where is he?
Right behind you, dumbass!
What? That's where you were hiding?
Rub those eyes of yours...
Take this!
Ninja Arts: Energy Bullet Technique!
Ninja Arts: Barrier Technique!
You're quite skillful with the arts!
Barrier!
It's not even ninja arts anymore...
Okay, Beauty! Then I'll show you some real ninja arts!
Ninja Arts: Camel Clutch!
But that's a pro wrestling move!
You're far better than I anticipated.
I haven't been so thrilled...
ever since I snatched some taros before supper when my mom wasn't looking!
Are you really even a ninja?
And now to finish you off!
Dammit!
Ninja Arts: Concealment Technique!
POOF
He disappeared!
My concealment technique makes me completely invisible!
Now you'll never be able to sense my presence!
But how?
How did he find out where I was?
You were talking and all.
He's right.
Then I won't be so bold with my speech... I won't be bold with my speech...
I won't be bold with my speech...
It's a boulder!
But I still won't be bold!
I've never been cornered like this before...
since I was doing my summer homework in elementary school!
Research projects are time-consuming, aren't they?
This is great!
I couldn't be more pleased, Bo-bobo!
Never have I fought such a perfect opponent!
How will you attack me now?
He's spouting fish sticks from his head!
It's a bonus stage.
What? A bonus stage, you say?
Yay!
Be extra careful.
Because one of them is a dumbbell.
Fish sticks and dumbbells...
You couldn't tell the difference between the two.
Damn you!
Don't forget I am a first-rate ninja!
Squidopotamian Civilization!
This is real bad, Bo-bobo!
His condition's getting worse!
What should we do?
I never thought Bo-bobo would be this strong...
It seems like you are worthy of fighting OVER.
Ninja Arts!
Mouth Vacuum Technique!
I'm being sucked in!
My mouth can surpass space-time!
I shall gladly send you all to Lord OVER's domain!
Fine by me!
And I'll beat that OVER guy to a pulp!
This is it...
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Bo-bobo and friends have been warped to the castle of OVER...
one of the Four Lords of Margarita.
So this is where OVER of the Four Lords is?
And right below us is the castle...
of OVER of the Four Lords of Margarita!
Who's that...?
He's here!
It's our idol, Serviceman!
He's gotten up!
Here it comes...
Serviceman!
This has happened once before.
Hey! Do your service!
Do your service!
What's wrong with you, Serviceman?
Don't you always do your service for us?
You promised that you'd always do your service no matter what!
You fat liar! I hate you!
That got to me real deep.
I don't want to feel so helpless...
ever again!
As long as there are those who wish for service...
I will continue to service!
Service!
I failed...
Let's see what's over there!
Sure!
There's a pond!
These old-style ponds are so chic!
Come on in! The water's great!
Yeah, that looks pretty nice.
No comebacks, huh?
Hup...
I am the guardian of the castle lawn, Gump!
Gump
I am under direct orders from Lord OVER to test your strength.
So, if you want to fight Lord OVER...
then allow me to test your strength, Bo-bobo!
Fine then! Let's get started!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Principal's Speech!
It is the middle of summer.
Thank you for taking the trouble to come to assembly out here in the hot, hot sun.
I'd like you all to follow my example and work hard every day.
But you probably won't turn out like me.
The speech before summer break is so rough!
I can't go on.
Now that it's come to this,
allow me to take it to the skies!
How's this? You can't reach me up here!
Alright, Tennosuke!
Let's use that attack we practiced!
Wait, what are we doing?
Go forth!
Tokoroten Magnum!
This can't be happening! It didn't work!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Transform: Ball!
Now throw me right into him!
OK!
What are you doing!?
Hey, Beauty! Forget about that, look at the lake!
Huh? What happened?
Isn't that chic?
It's not chic, and I don't get it.
Complete fools! What's wrong?
You gonna come at me?
So what's the plan?
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble New Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Trampoline!!
Alright you two, bounce on me to reach him!
No thanks. We're good.
You can fly!?
New secret technique.
He is playing on me now.
Boingy-boingy-boing.
Tennosuke's Haiku of the Heart
Wait up, guys!
He's fitting in quite well with the team...
Alright, Don Patch! Pluck his wings off!
OK, Bo-bobo!
Think I'll let you?
My wings!
Is that a wing?
I'm falling!
Human Pyramid!
Why'd you hurt Don Patch, too!?
You're taking it too far!
These guys are strong!
On an entirely different level!
But unless I defeat them,
the Five Ultimate Assassins will kill me!
I'll take at least one down with me!
October!
They've got no openings!
What's up with them!?
What the hell's with you all!?
We are...
Kung-fu B-movie characters!
And now...
Human Pyramid!
Not again!
We did it, Tennosuke!
Yeah!
Come over here, Bo-bobo!
What's up over there?
They've been Hair Hunted!
What a cruel thing to do!
And there's so many of them...
This is an outrage!
How could he do something so horrible?
You'll pay for this, OVER!
Seems like he liked our welcome.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Are we just gonna go through the front door?
Of course.
This could be a trap.
This enemy is on a different level from those we've fought before!
But this atrocity they pulled is unacceptable!
Yeah, and I'm going to crush this castle for good!
Alright! Let's do this!
Yeah!
Just you wait, OVER. I'm coming for you.
So glad you've come, Bo-bobo.
You can call me Ruby.
Five Ultimate Assassins
Ruby
And I'll judge you in the name of the heavens!
Go Ruby!
Trash
What was that for!?
You're making me so mad!
Second Floor
What kind of door is that?
I-It's not opening...
Only I can open that door.
I can open it if you want.
I know they told me to defeat you,
but I hate fighting.
And it's been so long since I've talked to someone,
or really enjoyed myself.
So if you can help me have fun, I'll let you pass!
So what's the plan?
We can't exactly fight her.
I guess we've got no choice but to have some fun with her.
It's time for a picture story show!
Don Patch's
Picture Story Show for Children
Yay!
Tales of Unemployment
That's too dark!
That's not gonna make a girl happy!
Girls love to play with beads!
Now let's make some fun accessories!
I don't have fingers...
You idiot!
Try putting yourself in the girl's shoes!
What girls love to do is...
It's so fun!
How is that even remotely fun!?
Stop drooling on my face!
Okay Heppokomaru, you give it a try!
Who, me?
You can do it, Hekkun!
Uhh... Uhh... Uhh... Uhh...
You're a scoundrel, Honey!
A scoundrel!
Are you still going on about that!?
Booooring!
This is complicated! How do you entertain a child?
I guess I have no choice.
Since you're out of practice, let me be the child.
Oh! Nice idea! Thanks a ton!
Now, let's practice.
Crusher Ball!
I'm so bored!
So bored! So bored! So bored! So bored! So bored! So bored!
We hear you, loud and clear!
Just be quiet and I'll get you some snacks.
Snacks?
What are you gonna give me?
Hmm, how about I give you a hint?
Does that mean a caramel candy?
Dried Fish
It's actually dried fish.
That's too hard!
There's nothing more to do!
Hey, Bo-bobo...
I don't know if this will work or not...
but when I was a little girl...
I loved playing dolls with my friends.
No one asked for your opinion!
Playing with dolls, huh?
Bit of a long shot, but it's worth a try.
Ruby! Ruby!
It's Daddy!
Don't you have any other dolls?
I have dollies too!
Let me play!
I'll be the mommy.
Sure.
This worked better than I thought.
Thank goodness!
I'm home, mommy!
Welcome home!
How'd your test go?
So Don Patch has a doll, too?
Mustard
I failed!
You can't use that! That's mustard!
Hi, I'm home, too!
I got hit by a car on my way home and now I'm as flat as a pancake!
That backstory's way too far-fetched!
Thank goodness! It looks like they're all having fun!
And so, an hour passed.
This is weird. How long are they gonna play, anyway?
A little slow on the uptake, aren't we?
They've already fallen under my spell.
Her mood suddenly changed!
I am Ruby. I am one of Lord OVER's Five Ultimate Assassins.
And I have the power to gain full control over anyone that plays with me.
You could call it brainwashing.
Bo-bobo!
Don't waste your breath.
They're incapable of hearing you.
And they'll be playing for the rest of their lives.
Just one look at their face...
and you can tell they're being controlled.
Bo-bobo!
Don't worry, Beauty!
We're not being controlled by her!
Yes, you are!
So all that was just an act?
You tricked us!
Well, whose fault is it for being so gullible?
It's the grandpa!
Just shut up for a sec.
Anyone under my control
will be utterly defenseless.
I can finish them off without breaking a sweat.
Y-You don't mean...
So, which one of your friends should I get rid of first?
What's wrong with this guy?
He's got his guard up!
But why?
He should be under my control by now!
Of course! Don Patch always wants to play around for the rest of his life, anyway...
so he's no different when he's under her spell!
You rotten brat!
How dare you trick us!
I'm totally stuck!
I'll be killed if I can't get out of here!
Here you go.
Why did you spare me?
You made that pitfall, didn't you?
Enough with the jokes!
I was about to finish you all off!
I don't need your help!
Finish me off! I don't need your sympathy!
I've prepared myself! Finish me off!
Bo-bobo...
You buffoon!
Now, let's all run off into the sunset!
Yes, Coach Rugby!
Yeah! There's nothing between us and the sunset!
Nothing at all!
Why?
Why... are you all sparing me?
Don't be so quick to throw your life away.
No man is an island.
If you're gone, there will be someone that will miss you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Tokoroten...
I was wrong about everything.
Well, I guess all's well that ends well.
For some reason, Tennosuke had the last word.
I shall declare my loss to you all.
Your first trial is over.
This is the key to that door.
Take it.
Why do I have to...?
I'm waiting, oink!
But I've got no choice but to do it!
But the stairs to the second floor are over there...
Let's get a move on, Beauty.
And so, Bo-bobo and friends...
arrived at the second floor, the Jungle Stage.
Our next opponent's gonna be a ninja too, right?
Well they are the Five Ultimate Assassins. Of course they're ninjas.
Exactly! I'm totally a ninja!
Who's there? An Ultimate Assassin?
Nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin nin...
The second member of the Five Ultimate Assassins
stands before Bo-bobo and friends!
But who's this guy supposed to be!?
I don't think he qualifies as a ninja!
Hey, which one of you thought ninjas equals soccer players?
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
Are we gonna fight over here?
Could this be...
No! It's the legendary coliseum!
What'll happen if you fall?
Don't flush it!
I don't want to fall in!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Five Ultimate Assassins
Bo-bobo All Stars!
Baby Hekkun Goes
Wild Too!!
Babu ♥
Hekkun's gonna finally Hajike again!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, wake up early and let the Hajike thoughts fill you!
If you tied or lost, finish your homework early!