A New King
is Born!!
You got that outfit, too!?
Our hero Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo became the new King of Hajikelists!
It's so fun!
Is this all the new King's got to offer!?
Stop drooling on me!
Suddenly, Puckered Lips...
a ninja serving one of the Four Lords of Margarita, OVER, stood before them.
Puckered Lips
After a fierce ninja battle...
Bo-bobo and friends were warped to OVER's castle.
It was there that Serviceman...
and the guardian of the courtyard, Gump, were waiting for them.
Gump
But he was no match for the mighty Bo-bobo.
The true enemies were the Five Ultimate Assassins.
They encountered the first member, Ruby, and engaged her in a fierce battle.
Five Ultimate Assassins
Ruby
And so, Bo-bobo and friends
came to the Jungle Stage on the second floor.
Our next opponent's gonna be a ninja too, right?
Well they are the Five Ultimate Assassins. Of course they're ninjas.
And the one waiting for them was some creepy soccer kid under the waterfall!
What will become of Bo-bobo?
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
AngelofChaotix
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: SweetDevilStitch, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Five Ultimate Assassins
Bo-bobo All Stars!
Baby Hekkun Goes
Wild Too!!
Babu ♥
Nin nin nin nin
nin nin nin nin
nin nin nin NIN!
What is up with this kid?
He's the furthest thing on Earth from a ninja!
You thought I was practicing?
Well, we thought you were working on some special kick.
I am the second member of the Five Ultimate Assassins...
Five Ultimate Assassins
Infinite Shoot
Infinite Shoot!
I'll be more than happy to take you all on at once!
He stole my ball!
I'm gonna pop your precious ball! You cool with that?
This ball's just like a friend to you, isn't it?
Isn't it like a girlfriend to you?
No. A ball's just a ball.
Give it back.
O-OK.
He's more sane than he seemed at first!
I was born and raised in this castle!
So I will never let you destroy this castle!
Now, let us fight!
Baseball!
He's actually catching on fire!
I will defend this castle to the very end!
Actually, I think you're burning down the castle!
Ten minutes later...
You burned the entire stage!
Didn't know I could do that!
This ain't good! The foothold's breaking apart!
Alright! Now's the time for our new secret technique!
Gojo Bridge!
Gojo Bridge? But we're not in Kyoto!
And no one would walk over that weird bridge anyways!
And it looks like it'll break any second!
And besides, you obviously don't look like a bridge!
And there's no time to be messing around like this! And I think my comeback is way too long!
Heppokomaru! If you take too long, we're gonna fall!
You gotta walk over us and take him down!
No! I could never step on Bo-bobo or Tennosuke!
Then why don't you just step on Don Patch?
Good idea!
He agreed to that!?
Wait, that didn't even make any sense!
Too hot!!!
Courthouse
Plaintiff
Judge
Dismissed
Now, why don't we start the battle already?
Tennosuke!
The pain... and the humiliation...
Cut it out, you fresh bastard. You've gotta deal with me now.
Fine by me! I'll take you on!
Help me!
Hang in there, Tennosuke! I'm coming to save you!
Release the princess!
Year 34 of Tokoroten... I've never been treated so nicely before!
June!
And I've never felt so much pain before, either!
You're quite good!
Now it's my turn to take the lead!
I bet his weapon's gonna be his ball. That's easy enough to deflect!
I was totally wrong!
Take this!
Isn't that ball your weapon?
No, it's just an accessory!
He admits it!
But there's actually a purpose for this ball beyond a mere accessory.
Because this ball is my...
lunchbox!
And it's gotten all messy...
Well what did you expect after kicking it around?
Heppokomaru's fighting this battle all on his own...
Isn't there anything we can do for him?
Let's sing him a song!
Stop dropping dead all the time...
Kutabatte bakkainna
Buttonde ikou janai
Come and fly away!
Funbatte
Step on it! Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Who hath disturbed my slumber?
You awakened some weird creature!
Don't panic! This is exactly what we've been practicing our new song for!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember...
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn
that will never come back...
He decided to leave!
Time to resume our battle!
I used to wish I would be hurt...
Because I thought being hurt would make me happy!
That's hot!!!
Courthouse
Plaintiffs
Judge
Dismissed
What's up with him? He looks like another person altogether!
His collar came off, which means he's in Baby Mode!
He's gone into invincible mode!
Alright, Heppokomaru! Get out there and take him down!
Courthouse
Plaintiffs
Heppoko!
RAGE
Wanted
Judge
Dismissed
What was I expecting...?
Your attacks are far too slow!
I can easily keep up with them thanks to my years of ping-pong training!
Now it's ping-pong!?
So try as hard as you like, you can't land a hit on me!
Hekkun...
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Hekkun...
March
Dammit! I never expected that from him!
Where is he? Where's he gonna attack from?
What kind of attack will he use!?
He used a race car!
Heppokomach's tires are almost worn out!
Pit
Get back to pit as soon as possible!
You keep worrying me sick...
Please come back alive, Heppokomach!
He made it back!
We've got to put his collar back on soon...
Let me deal with with our farting friend.
Hekkun, let's play!
Let's play!
He's coming this way!
Tennosuke, he's all yours!
I can't run!
I won't run!
I will not run!
I shall not run!
This isn't working! He's gone out of control!
We can't put the collar back on!
Huh? Is something up, Bo-bobo?
He put it back on himself!
Infinite Shoot
Out of Commission
Alright! We can go up these stairs!
Perfect! Let's get a move on!
Yeah!
Now that your precious ducktail is gone, you're done for, Battleship!
You think you're a disgrace to us? Hardly.
As if you ever were an equal to me...
One of the Four Lords of Margarita
If we don't hurry up and defeat OVER, Rice's life will be in danger!
But where is OVER hiding?
What kind of room is this!?
My traps have left them speechless!
Only three people in the world have been able to make it through this gauntlet!
And two of them were mice...
Your Heart
Damn it to hell, I can't lift this!
I wanna give him a hug.
I can't lift it!
You see all the traps, Patchmi? Like, I don't think we can get through if we don't clear them...
Oh really, Tenko? Don't you think we should, like, send someone to test it out?
Okay, then.
You can do the honors!
It's coming back!
How's this?
Tennosuke!
I'm alright. Thankfully, this "Nu" handkerchief cushioned the blow.
How lucky of me!
Good for you.
Alright, it's on!
And as a veteran of innumerable galactic wars...
these traps are a piece of cake to me!
Tag me! Tag me in!
Tag...
Good! Now go back out there!
No way!
What was the point of the tag?
He fell right in!
Rock 'n' roll!
Alright. I'll go next.
It's too dangerous, Bo-bobo! You'll turn into a rock star!
Every body has a presence...
so when I erase my presence and become naught,
nothing can harm me.
That's amazing!
He just might be able to pull it off!
It didn't work!
It's only a matter of time before they bite the dust...
I'll finish them off with my special trap...
Something's pouring in!
It's gasoline!
You're all finished! Take a look in front of you!
Is he planning to set the gasoline on fire!?
Exactly. But that's not gasoline you're standing in!
It's something way more lethal!
More lethal? So what's this liquid?
It's coffee!
Please stand back!
So you can't substitute gasoline for coffee?
I wanna give him a hug...
Time for my last resort...
Let me cook you up with my greatest weapon!
Take this!
Death Cyclone!
This wind's too strong!
What are those? What are you trying to do with us?
I'll hand you over to the Java Men!
All covered in feathers!
I'm sure those cavemen will be so pleased...
I don't understand what you're doing or why you're doing it...
And you've still got coffee below you! There's nothing you can do!
Should I ask him out tonight?
This trap's more dangerous than I thought!
If we swallow the feathers, we'll choke on them!
We got a problem!
It's Don Patch!
What about him?
He's turned Visual Kei!
I couldn't even care less!
He fell for it! Bingo!
You can't have a flurry of feathers without Visual Kei!
And you can't have Visual Kei without singing!
And once he starts singing, the feathers will clog his throat and kill him!
Now start the music!
No! It's a trap!
Here's your mic!
Don Patch! Don't sing! It's a trap!
That's no mic, it's a bike!
My kindred spirit...
My "Nu" handkerchief is flying out of the cage!
"Nu" handkerchief!!
Whatever the case, this cage is bad news!
We've got to get out of here somehow!
It's no use! This cage won't even budge!
If only Hatenko were here now...
Good grief. You guys really are useless without me.
Hatenko!
After this break...
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boboscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Hatenko!
It's me.
We've been waiting for you, Dengakuman...
Dengakuman!
What are you doing here?
Did you forget that we're friends now?
Friends help each other when they're in need!
Super Dengaku Punch!
I once used that attack to cause you pain...
but now it's helping you!
Is your wound from Z-Block Base all better now?
He never used that attack on you, remember?
There's no time to spare! Let's climb to the fourth floor!
OK!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Shake it up, baby!
That weird guy is following us...
We're here!
Yeah!
Toilet Coliseum
But what's the deal with this place!?
This is the legendary arena that has won innumerable awards...
the Toilet Coliseum!
Totally Awesome Spot Ranking #1
First Date Spot #1
Arena with the Prettiest Night View #1
Arena You'd Like to Fight In #1
7th Annual Best Arena Ranking #1
Best Jeanist Award #1
Who in their right mind would vote for this?
Wake the hell up!!!
She's really feisty there!
So you finally decided to show up, Bo-bobo! Take a look at this!
What?
I'm sorry, guys. I've been kidnapped!
Are you just gonna let us have our way with him?
OK, baby.
The rock star answered!
Not like it matters, though...
My plan failed!
But why? Is it because I'm an enemy?
No, it's because you're a child.
Why do you always treat me like a child?
Bo-bobo! This Toilet Coliseum before you
is a death match arena where the losers meet their demise in the middle.
So, choose your three representatives!
And the three of us will take you on!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Rock Star!
The three of us will challenge you!
Yes! Come at me! Let's start the 3-on-3 death match!
It wasn't until much later that I realized...
that this wasn't a 3-on-3.
Take the card already!
Just wait one second!
They have eleven!
No, it's six. Good grief.
I guess I'll take out the tokoroten first.
He's coming for me!
What do I do?
I'll do this!
That was close...
Nice decision.
You're always saving me, "Nu" handkerchief.
Now prepare yourself, Rock Star!
Yes, yes, yes, yes! Shakin' it, baby! Hey!
Bye! Baby! Hey!
Dammit...
I guess I'll take you on instead!
I'll be your opponent!
How about that? You know the twin-sword style?
But two swords are not enough to defeat me!
If only I had one more sword...
Bo-bobo!
I'll let you use my sword!
Bo-bobo has three swords!
Three-sword style!
He's wrecking the entire restaurant!
May I take your order?
One Egypt, please.
One Egypt coming up!
Urgh!
And flop!
It's time to finish you off! I'll throw you in now!
Long-held grudge!
Now for Tennosuke!
Right, let's drop him in!
Sure!
Bo-bobo! I'll use my Super Dengaku Punch to save you!
You meanie, you meanie, you meanie,
you meanie, you meanie, you meanie, you meanie...
I surrender!
That's as far as you'll go!
Combined Secret Technique:
Wobble-Wobble May Jet!!
Let's go for one more run!
Next time, stop wobbling so much! I accidentally hit Bo-bobo back there!
What a fearsome technique!
And where do you think you're looking?
That's nothing! Combined Secret Technique:
Nosehair Dengaku Shot!!
Accidental Double Super Dengaku Punch!!!
Not so fast, Bo-bobo!
Look over here. Don't you care about what happens to him?
Be my guest!
We'll have to fight back with a combination attack of our own.
But we don't have any of those! We'll have to improvise one!
Combination attacks have to be carefully planned out.
Improvised combination attacks can't compare to ours!
Mouth Kick!!!
That's an amazing technique!
How was that?
I didn't feel a thing.
Because your attacks lack care for one another!
You can't call that a combination attack!
Allow us to show you how a true combination attack works!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Combination Secret Technique:
Our Friendship Lasts Forever!!!!
You made me get dizzy!
He's just having fun at our expense!
Dengakuman,
because you pulled off that combination move, I consider you a friend.
Take this as a symbol of our friendship.
I don't want it!
It's a play-dough sculpture I made of you.
That's supposed to be me!?
Fools! You turned your backs on us!
Die, Bo-bobo!
Take that!
Now that we're together, we're invincible!
Invincible!
He's scary!
Tennosuke and Heppokomaru fell inside.
What's going on? My body suddenly bloated up!
Am I giving birth? But I'm supposed to be a guy...
What's going on?
That's right. I forgot to explain this stage.
This is a special kind of water.
Whoever's soaked in it will start to inflate.
And if they're in there for ten minutes...
their bodies will explode and be blown to pieces!
That happened way too quick!
This is scary! This is really frightening!
Can anything so terrifying ever be legal?
Will it be the end for Heppokomaru?
And what happened to Tennosuke?
Huh?
I see he's back already!
Anyway, my heart's swelling for the next episode!
No, my entire body!
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
The Five Ultimate Assassins sure are strong.
We have no choice. We have to...
Is he serious!?
He's going to do that!?
What's he gonna do?
Combination! Bo-bobo Fusion!
Bobopatch is gonna come back again!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Go!
Bobopatchnosuke!!
On a granny bike!!!
Seriously!?
That's not Bobopatch!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, play soccer with your friends and you do a soccerful job!
If you tied or lost, don't waste stuff or you'll regret it!