The Legendary Battle Finally Begins!
Bo-bobo and friends have beaten two of the Five Ultimate Assassins...
And have made it to the legendary arena...
The Toilet Coliseum.
Toilet Coliseum
But what's the deal with this place!?
Now the three of us will take you on!
Nosehair Dengaku Shot!!
Mouth Kick!!!
Amidst the fierce battle,
Heppokomaru and Tokoro Tennosuke
fell inside the toilet!
It was filled with a special kind of water
that bloats anyone who enters it!
Am I giving birth? But I'm supposed to be a guy...
And if they're in there for ten minutes...
their bodies will explode and be blown to pieces!
This is scary!
This is really frightening!
Can they really be saved
from the toilet of terror?
Say what? Bo-bobo!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Say what? Bo-bobo!
(Get up!) Stand up.
(Get up!) Stand up
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Stop dropping dead all the time,
Kutabatte bakkainna
Come and fly away!
Buttonde ikou janai
Step on it!
Funbatte
Bomb it!
Bomber tte
Go! Go! Tricky Style!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Hurry and hit the gong!
Hayaku narase gongu
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20XX
That's the kind of era we're in,
Konna jidai da ze
We can't be stopped!
Oretachi wa tomerarenai
Karaoke: SweetDevilStitch, SystematicChaos,
Walker Prescott
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Get out!
1,2, Blow! Megaton Puncher!
「1, 2, Blow」 Megaton kyuu puncher
Fighting Soul! Explosive Power!
「Fighting Soul」 Yo! Hajikeru power
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Punch a dent into logic!
Bukkowashiteenda joushikitte yatsu wo
Yes come on!
Crash Bomb! C'mon, Block Buster!
「Crash Bomb」 ittoke Block Buster
Let's jet go! Straight down our path!
「Let's Jet Go」 Waga michi masshigura
Quality Checking:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
I'm an up and coming fighter!
Kakeagare faitaa!
(Like a Phatman)
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Like a macho man
Binbin macho de
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Push ahead
Gangan ittoke!
Really hard
Banban hard na
Like a starving wild challenger!
Ueta Wild Challenger!
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
By the way, you still haven't given us your names.
What a perfect time to ask that question.
We ninjas have never had names of our own.
But now, we have finally been given names!
Behold! These are our names!
Indus Civilization
Mesopotamian Civilization
Yellow River Civilization
Those are the civilizations of the ancient world!
What kind of godawful names are these?
This sure takes me back to middle school.
I can't take this!
Hey, where's Egypt?
Go!
Bobopatchnosuke!!
On a granny bike!!!
Seriously!?
You're dead meat!
Right back at you!
Go right ahead!
Help us! We're getting flushed!
Help us! Get us out!
Oh, no!
Bo-bobo!
Yeah! Have at you, bastards!
He's ignoring them!?
I gotta help them out somehow!
Try and grab onto this!
Somen
Somen!?
Of course that won't work!
Noodle Sauce
Those bastards...
What's your problem? Don't throw my noodle sauce like that!
Got you now, Bo-bobo!
What!?
You fell for it!
Look down at your feet!
What the...?
You've entered the Trap Zone!
A little late on the uptake!
Activate the trap!
Zero!
We have you now, Bo-bobo!
Well, that worked.
That wasn't supposed to happen! Release Trap button!
Zero!
Now to finish you off!
Not on my watch!
Damn you, Yellow River Civilization!
I won't let you lay a finger on Mesopotamian Civilization!
But you two are laying feet on me, like, really hard!
I must assist them!
Hold up, punk.
I'm gonna take care o' you.
Ya know who yer pickin' a fight with?
Why don't ya tell me then, bro?
Now you're asking for it! I'll beat ya to a pulp!
Don't go off cryin' to mommy now!
What the fu...?
Go do that somewhere else!
Now you've done it. Allow me to show you my legendary top-secret technique...
that took me an entire year to learn!
What's that? A legendary top-secret technique?
Here goes!
Fist of the Nose Hair
Top-Secret Technique!!
Roly-Poly Attack!!
It took you a year to learn how to roll!?
We have to go save Heppokomaru!
Leave it to me!
I'm going in and saving them!
The minute I give you the signal...
pull up on the rope!
Nice idea!
Alright! I'm trusting you on this!
If he pulls up the rope at the wrong time, all hope is lost!
Not yet...
Alright! Now! Pull me up, Bo-bobo!
I got the Old Maid!
Don Patch!
Wait for me, Don Patch!
I'm on my way to save you!
Why me!?
Dengakuman!
How dare you do that to my precious friends...
You're not getting away with this!
You're not getting away with it!
You're never getting away with it!
But you were the one who chucked them in!
So quick to resort to violence?
How self-indulgent of you.
Is he actually saying what I think he's saying?
Say whatever you want, but you're the only one left!
This fight is as good as won!
Only one? Don't you mean three?
What?
This is something I found in Tennosuke's desk the other day...
Tennosuke's Embarassing Poem Anthology
Tennosuke's Embarrassing Poem Anthology.
"Flowers," by Tokoro Tennosuke.
Flowers are pretty. Why are they so pretty?
Red flowers are pretty.
They make me burn with passion.
Yellow flowers are pretty.
Please, no more!
Don't read any more of that!
They're my one regret!
He came out!?
He came back out of the toilet?
This makes two!
Yakkun!
And this makes three!
Check it out!
Our bloated bodies are back to normal!
Right you are.
Who are these guys? I don't believe my eyes!
Is this a joke!? There's never been anyone
who's made it out of that toilet alive!
But they still were weak enough to fall in, in the first place!
We couldn't care less if they come back!
What's with the fist, Bo-bobo?
Time to bring back the Tokoroten Magnum!!!
What just happened there?
I don't think I would've survived a direct hit!
But look! You had to sacrifice your partner's life to use that move!
Which means you can't use it anymore!
Let's move!
Repeater! Six shots per second!
Now that it's come to this... Activate Trap!
Zero!
Now to finish you off!
Yeah!
This is our finishing move of friendship!
Finishing Move of Friendship
Bo-bobo Torpedo!
Dump the trash!
They dropped him!
Alright, fine...
I'll take you down with me!
You just don't give up, do you?
Fall! Just fall already! Why don't you fall?
Just fall! Fall already! Fall down, you bastard!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Just fall! Fall already! Fall down, you bastard!
You know what, we'll let you off this time.
Don't get your hopes up, though!
Fools!
You've made yourselves open to me!
Love you ♥
Not that kind of open!
Okay, Bo-bobo!
You can land safely on this mini-mat!
Thank you kindly!
The games are over!
Take this!
Yellow River Ninja Arts: Freezing Sweat!!
What?
My sweat freezes all that it touches!
You'll be frozen solid in a matter of seconds!
They're completely speechless.
Now! Freeze up!
What a stupid kid!
Wait, that attack just froze the entire ground!
Here they come!
Let's go, Don Patch!
Yeah!
We'll show you
what our combination can do!
You nutjob!
Why'd you have to use an annoying technique like that?
Is he going to be alright!?
Alright! Clone Technique!
Is it this one?
It's this one!
He just threw around some octopus wieners!
Leave this one to me!
Heavenly Dog Style Secret Technique:
Heavenly Dog Style Secret Technique
Chop Breaker!!
The hell!?
I surrender.
That's as far as you'll go!
Now what?
Oh, he's okay, after all.
Say whaaa? Bo-bobo!
Get up!
Stand up!
No way!
What a cute little thing...
Fine, then! I'll show you our special move that makes use of this frozen ground!
Take this! Yellow River Ninja Arts:
Yellow River Ninja Arts:
Curling Attack!
Outta my way!
We're sorry, Yellow River Civilization.
But this bomb's gonna win us the gold!
8.95 meters!
We did it!
That was a dreadful technique!
But I can do it just as well!
Doubt that, moron! You can't pull it off without a curling stone!
Sorry to disappoint you, but I found a very nice and suitable...
curling stone, right here!
Go on ahead!
But why me!?
Don't fret, Dengakuman.
We'll lead you in a safe direction!
You guys...
You better fall in line, freshie.
Ya think you can get by just by being cute?
Whaddya think you're doing?
Sorry!
So they're having a falling-out! Perfect! Don't stop now!
Dammit! I'm stuck in the seat!
Well, at least he's stuck too, so he's in no position to attack me anyway.
Bo-bobo Fire!
He breathed fire!
He's looking this way!
Medium-rare! Make me medium-rare, please!
Fire!
That's not medium!
My precious slick hair...
I'm out! Prepare yourself, Bo-bobo!
Shut the hell up!
Bo-bobo! Look at Hekkun! He's...
What?
He's clogged the toilet!
Dengakuman's in trouble, too!
This is bad, Bo-bobo! You've gotta hurry!
What kind of attack can take care of these three quickly?
Not a chance! You'd better not think of us as small fry!
Bo-bobo! Tennosuke!
We'll have to pull off that move!
Yeah. It seems like that...
That move...
That's the only move we can do!
You're not thinking the same thing!
Bo-bobo Fusion!
Let's go, Don Patch!
OK!
Transform!
CANDY BALL!
Open wide!
Here it comes!
No one's looking.
Everyone saw that!
A fusion technique? With the three of them?
What's gonna happen?
What's gonna happen!?
Fusion complete.
Who's that!?
After this break,
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
My name is Bobopatchnosuke.
Bobopatchnosuke
And I can only remain in this form for one minute.
So let's get this over with!
Is that really those three guys?
They seem a little different than normal...
What power! Even the atmosphere feels heavy!
He's not normal!
There's no time. Here I come.
Not another Don Patch Sword!
Oh good. It's just a normal sword...
I spoke too soon...
Prepare yourselves.
The Tanaka Sword shows no quarter.
Tanaka Sword
I'll show you the true power of Bobopatchnosuke!
You moron! What do you think you can do with that sword?
First Flash
Tanaka Slash!!
And on the back...
Mesopotamian Civilization!
What kind of slash was that?
This is really bad! We're in real trouble!
I can't get him angry. If he gets angry, it's all over!
He looks super angry!
I will never forgive the likes of you. I'll hit you with all I have.
Beauty... Heppokomaru... Dengakuman...
For my three friends who've passed on!!!
But we're still alive.
I can only remain in this form
for another fifty seconds.
I'll give you the instakill treatment.
Are you retarded?
You'll defeat us in fifty seconds?
It'll never happen!
Here goes! Ultimate Secret Technique:
SE
RIOUS
LY
SERIOUSLY TIME!
What's going on?
We're in space!
Seriously Time is a spatial dimension.
Seriously!!?
will be your worst nightmare.
You'd better get hyped up, or you'll suffocate!
Seriously!!?
Quit making those stupid reactions!
Great. They've detected that reaction of yours.
They're coming...
Seriously...
The Seriously Meteor Swarm.
Seriously Meteor Swarm
Seriously!!?
Seriously!
In Seriously Time, all is Seriously.
Seriously!!?
They're gone.
Here, everything is Seriously.
All words aside from "Seriously" have no meaning.
That didn't make any sense!
We'll crush you!
Seriously
Seriously!!?
I have struck you with a Seriously Wave.
Soon, you will encounter...
Seriously!!?
of your own making...
What's that supposed to mean?
This is what he means.
Seriously!!?
Bro!
Kojiro!
Seriously!!?
To tell the truth...
I'm a woman!
Seriously!!?
I've loved you for the past three years.
We're getting married!
Seriously!!?
Congratulations!
Seriously?!
We're going to Hawaii for our honeymoon!
Seriously!?
I'm home!
Hawaiian Treats
Hot Spring Steamed Buns
I brought back some hot spring steamed buns!
Seriously?!
The spaceship is here!
You're all taking off!
To where?
Istanbul.
U.S.S. Seriously
Seriously!!?
Now, we will fire upon the Earth.
How much firepower does this ship have!?
Well-done
Seriously!!?
Engine room
And now we be like, "Seriously"!!?
It seems you've had enough of Seriously Time.
Then allow me the pleasure of finishing you off.
S-
Se-
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-
That's so uncool!!!
Seriously?
Seriously? That's so uncool!!!
But at least the pedals look decent!
Here I go!
He's coming this way!
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-...
Fist of the Eyelash...
Forever!
Seriously!!?
They're back!
Get on.
No questions. Just get on.
FIN
Hold it right there!
You didn't wrap anything up!
Or what, did they forget about us?
What's with the sunset!?
And so...
Bo-bobo and friends saved Heppokomaru and Dengakuman.
Let's bounce.
Help me out here, guys!
And finally...
they reached the top floor of OVER's Castle!
Alright! Let's charge in!
Prepare yourself, OVER!
Battleship!
Who could've done this atrocity to him?
It has to be OVER!
Hey! Come on out, OVER!
Shut the fuck up.
I am one of the Four Lords of Margarita...
Four Lords of Margarita
OVER!
He looks scary...
He is scary! He's seriously scary!
What's with those giant scissors?
Does Bo-bobo even stand a chance
against the evil foe known as OVER!?
Sakura saku koro omou yo
When the cherry blossoms bloom, I remember
Modoru koto no nai yawarakana yoake
The gentle dawn that will never come back
Itsuka kizutsuketamitai ni
I used to wish I would be hurt,
Kizutsukeba raku ni nareru to omotteta
because I thought being hurt would make me happy
Nakushite kowashite
I lost things and broke things,
Ironna koto wakattetta
I understood so many things
Kotoshi mo sakura yurete
This year the cherry blossoms will sway too
Kasundeku youna omoi ha kaze ni tokashite
My hazy feelings will disappear with the wind.
Kirai bakkari motteita
What was I drawing again
Nani wo mata egaiteita?
that had so much hate in it?
Guruguru omotte nandome no
How many times will I go in circles
Yowasa wakatte
before I understand what weakness is?
Mogaite mata naitatte
I'm struggling and crying again,
Mada genkai nanka janai yo
But that doesn't mean I can't keep going
Mukou no mirai he
To the future ahead of us
It's our first midair battle!
It sounds like fun!
Now's not the time to be saying that!
But OVER's really scary!
Don't worry, Beauty! Leave it to us two to save the day!
No, it's not just two of us.
Tennosuke's our friend, too!
Well said, Bo-bobo!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
I'll
take you
down!!
Tennosuke
said it!!!
Some friends you are!
Here's the results of the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, eat some dengaku and watch your dreams get bigger!
If you tied or lost, recite the Four Ancient Civilizations right now!