Now then, let's start by reviewing what we learned last week.
Third Period
World History
The Four Civilizations of the Ancient World are...
Indus Civilization
Mesopotamian Civilization
Yellow River Civilization
And what was the fourth one?
Raise your hand if you remember.
Here.
Go ahead, Bobopatchnosuke.
Seriously Time.
Seriously!!?
Note: The correct answer is
"Egyptian Civilization"
Bobopatchnosuke stood before the Four Civilizations of the Ancient World.
Seriously
Seriously!!?
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-...
Ha!!!
That wasn't the move you used!
Seriously!!?
With the Four Civilizations defeated, our heroes reached the top floor.
It was there, that they saw...
Prepare yourself, OVER!
Battleship!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Battleship!
His glorious ducktail's been hunted!
Who could've done this atrocity!?
It has to be OVER!
Battleship!
I'll
take you
down!!
Tennosuke
said it!!!
First he took Rice, and now Battleship too...
Over, you bastard... I'll never, ever...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Episode 1033: Battleship and Bo-bobo
Hey, hey. Take a chill pill, man.
Try to relax and don't let your shoulders get so tense.
I will!
Bo-bobo (OFF)
Ggh... First he took Rice, and now Battleship, too...
Thank you for helping! I'll do my best!
Hey, you were reading my lines!
Hey, OVER! Get yo' ass out here!
We're gonna beat the crap out of you!
You hiding or something, chicken?
Shut the fuck up, bitches.
Who said that?
If you want OVER, you're looking at him.
One of the Four Lords of Margarita
So who's gonna beat the crap out of who?
Huh?
He's scary...
Super scary...
So you're OVER?
I'll beat the living crap out of you!
That's what he said!
Box!
Ride on!
Stray Dog
And what?
He doesn't look pleased!
I'm a stray dog, but I can make it just fine on my own!
I'm sorry for being so sentimental!
Fuck off.
I'll beat you to a pulp, OVER!
He said that as well!
You too?
I never said that!
Set up!
It wasn't me that said it!
See, I even made soup for you, OVER!
It's all yours. Go right ahead and eat it, if you please!
Well, eat up then, bastard!
Dammit all to hell!
I couldn't help myself!
You son of a...
No, please! My hand just slipped like that!
You bad hand! You bad hand!
Bad hand! Bad hand!
Bad hand! Bad hand...!
So you wanna ruin my castle too, bastard!?
Fine, then.
Instead of just Bo-bobo...
I'll cut all you fuckers up into pieces!
What's up with him?
He's more dangerous than anyone we've ever encountered!
Such an enormous pressure!
I can barely stay on my feet!
I feel like I'll get blown away any second!
What are you trying to do?
And I have the perfect place for all your bodies to rot.
Show yourself!
Deathperado Killoseum!
Deathperado Killoseum
Where are we?
Is this...?
This must be the legendary dueling ground that goes all the way back to the ancient Romans...
I should've guessed that you'd know it!
The Deathperado Killoseum,
a death match in which two contestants launch themselves from cannons and duel in midair.
And if you don't land back in a cannon...
this happens.
And there's your rules.
Very well! I accept your challenge!
So let's begin the pre-battle ceremony!
Go, Dengaku Fireworks!
I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't! I can't!
I can't! I can't!
I can't
No, you just did...
How dare you use Dengakuman as fireworks!
You're not getting away with this!
Well then, come at me!
Not me, this guy said it!
You again!?
I never said that!
I just wanted to give you this handkerchief as a gift!
Fist of Bloody Murder Secret Technique: Pomegranate!!!!
Tennosuke!
Use this Scotch tape to put yourself back together!
Nice one, Bo-bobo!
How's this supposed to work!?
He's venting!
This always seems to happen to me...
That's one down.
Keep it coming, you fucking maggots!
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to call him over!
Call who?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
We've been waiting for you, Master!
He brought out the ultimate weapon!
Go do your thing, Master!
Service!
It is only Service if I do the exposing myself!
I will not take handouts!
As I expected of Serviceman.
A forced Service goes against his convictions.
Really now?
That's nothing!
Now we'll send in the Deadly Don Patch!
Go, Don Patch!
Let's show him what we're made of!
Don't wanna.
Why not!?
Well, I'll get beat up if I do, so what's the point?
You won't know 'til you try!
Yeah, I do, actually.
See?
Yep, like I said. Predictable.
Don Patch!
Get yo' lazy ass up there!
Again?
I'm really sorry, Bo-bobo...
What are you trying to do?
Farewell, Bo-bobo!
Please don't die!
It can't be... Are you...
Get off me, you little shit!
Don't do it!
Don Patch!
Man, that sure startled me.
Why are you the only survivor!?
Out of my way, fucker!
And there we go again. Predictable.
You're weak! You're all so goddamn weak!
Is this all you fucking shits have to offer?
Now you got me as your opponent, OVER!
Bring it, Bo-bobo!
Why'd the cannon go with him!?
I'm stuck in the cannon!
That was amazing, Bo-bobo!
Yes! Did we get him?
He's scary!
Are you supposed to be a character?
Meanwhile, far from the Hajike showdown...
in a certain village...
So he's not in this village, either...
Bo-bobo, until I get there, don't...
Don't lay a hand on OVER...
You don't stand a chance against OVER!
The countdown of death draws closer and closer for Hatenko and Rice!
Will Bo-bobo and friends make it in time?
Now you've gone and done it.
Let me have some fun, bitches!
Sure thing!
You're all dead!
I wouldn't jump ahead if I were you!
Eat this!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Amoeba Airspace!!!!
Alright!
He's swallowing him!
Now just to wait till he's suffocated.
Sorry.
I don't have enough volume.
Then leave the rest to me, Tennosuke!
Secret Technique: Tickle Attack!!!
Why am I the target?
Ultimate...
No! Tickle me! Tickle me harder!
New evil spirits sighted!
This is bad! If they don't recover, they'll all die by those bear traps!
Nimbus!
You have one?
Sup! I'm Nimbus!
Let us on too! Let us on! Let us on!
Yeah! I'm pretty sure OVER had to have taken some damage from that attack!
No way! No damage!?
Hooray for No Damage
Yay!
And why are you celebrating?
Now I see it!
Those scissors he's using are nullifying our attacks!
No, definitely not.
We gotta do something about those scissors!
Yeah!
But I said that's not the case!
Here he comes!
Okay, leave it to me!
Take this! Tokoroten Magnum!
Afro Magnum!
Whoa!
What kind of plan was that?
You won't get anywhere with a frontal approach.
You gotta use your head in this situation.
Mr. OVER... I see that your scissors look pretty beat-up.
Want me to fix them up for you?
The fuck's your deal?
Oh, sorry to introduce myself so late.
Scissors Specialist
Patcho Patchyama
Here's my card.
But I don't have anywhere to put it.
Sure you do!
It's right here, see?
What the fuck are you doing!?
I'm the new employee, Chikachi!
What's going on here!?
Allow me to explain.
So after Dengakuman transformed into fireworks...
he fell and got tangled up in OVER's hair...
and he's still stuck in there.
That's all.
We can't link our attacks in this type of fight!
Our time in midair is too short!
Dammit, don't we have a bigger cannon that can shoot us higher?
Super-Extra-Large-Ultra-Super-Gorgeous Cannon
Airborne
There it is! And it's enormous!
We're gonna rock you, OVER!
Piece of crap!
Why me?
How dare you do that to Heppokomaru!
I'll take you down, OVER!
I ain't flying!
What's with that tiny thing?
Go right ahead!
Nice shot!
Rabbit Attack!
So that's where you've been, Dengakuman!?
I missed you, Dengakuman!
Bo-bobo!
Dengaku Shot!!!!
So that's why...?
I did it!
That attack made him drop his scissors!
I can do it!
Just one blow...
Well?
This is bad!
He has two pairs of scissors now!
Okay then! Let's use weapons, as well!
Take these, Bo-bobo!
Hang on, isn't that a bit dangerous?
Are you trying to kill me?
He's venting again!
Bo-bobo! Another weapon's coming your way!
But that's a two-story house!
You muppet!
Well?
Damn you...
You're gonna pay for this.
How dare you make a fucking spectacle out of me!
You're gonna pay...
This is bad, Bo-bobo!
Man, you guys have problems.
I'll dice you up!
I'll slice you to bits... Tennosuke!
Why did... Why did he pick me?
He even remembered my name!
Don't care.
Monsieur,
could you get that guy with the white hair, a cocktail? It's on me.
OK!
Tennosuke declares war!
When did I say that!?
Hey, hey, ain't ya gonna drink Tennosuke's special booze?
Stop doing that!
Sorry about those idiots!
I'm truly sorry they made you all wet!
Have one more drink!
Fist of Bloody Murder Secret Technique: Kabosu!
And there I go getting sliced and diced again!
Whoa, there!
A little heat...
A little shake...
And pour.
Here we are! One serving of Tennosuke!
Yuck!
She's gone psycho!
OVER! I will destroy you with my next attack!
The Secret Technique I am about to use
is a legendary technique long forbidden and sealed within the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Here goes!
Secret Technique:
Ringaling Heaven!!
Some weird things just popped up!
I set this up three days ago.
Number 56, you go here!
Really?
They're all ringing at once!
This ringing causes damage to the eardrums of whoever is designated as the enemy.
It's just a matter of time until your eardrums explode!
What a horrid sound... My eardrums are about to burst!
Shit, I'm in real trouble!
Quit making that noise!
You're saying that!?
What the fuck's wrong with you!?
You bastard...
Give it to him Don Patch!
THAT HURT, DUMBASS!!!!
Good job, guys! Now, time for my phone attack!
Hey honey, do you like Tokoroten?
Quit fucking around!
Sorry for disturbing you!
He wasn't talking to you!
Now that ghastly noise is gone...
Bastards!
Alright, who fuckin' did that!?
Who's the clever punk that put the phone on my head!?
Hey, it wasn't us, I swear! See?
He's right! It wasn't us!
That's right! Our phones are still on our heads!
It was you, you bitch!
He found out!
You're wide open, OVER!
Somehow Nata de Coco is still alive!!!
He did it!
It's been so long...
since anyone's made my stomach churn like this!
Same here!
Yes, yes. Your stomach is churning, alright.
Allow me to congratulate you...
for pissing me off a total of four times!
Commentator      Announcer
What do we have here, folks!?
There's a coat of arms on OVER's chest!
What could this all mean?
Your thoughts on the situation, Commentator Beauty?
Shut up.
Only two more times!
If you piss me off two more times...
I'll have gathered enough infuriating power...
to revert to my true form!
What!?
My present form is nothing compared to my true form.
You will all be left as corpses in an instant.
This is bad! We can't get him any angrier!
We have to defeat him before he can get angry twice...
Okay, okay, let's wrap it up, Little Miss Over!
Stop it, idiot!
I'm so sorry! I swear, that boy of mine...
I'm so sorry!
Take these Natto as an apology!
He's full of rage!
That's why I said you should've gone with the fish sticks!
Shut up! Natto is where it's at!
That's a strong gust of wind!
It's full! Now it's GAME OVER!
Now I can revert to my true form!
Oh, crap! He's reverting to his true form!
What's gonna happen!?
Has it begun...?
Have they just...
Dammit...
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah.
O-Owie!
Torpedo Girl
Uhhh... Who is she supposed to be?
Is that really OVER's true form?
Her unbelievable Hajike will explode next week!
Oh, dear, a blister...
Good gracious...
Well?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Is that really OVER's true form, Torpedo Girl?
What's going on!?
Our attacks aren't even doing anything to her!
What do we do, Bo-bobo?
Gimme a sec, I'm thinking!
So just wait till next time!
W-Well hurry it up as soon as possible!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience!
FINALLY!
Torpedo Girl is here!!
Have people really been waiting?