Tantalizing!
Oh! That Dynamite Body!
The Super Beauty
Ranked First in the Popularity Polls
Finally Appears!!
Bo-bobo and friends have been engaged in a deathly battle
with the third of the Four Lords of Margarita, OVER.
Somehow Nata de Coco is still alive!!!
Only two more times!
If you piss me off two more times...
I'll have gathered enough infuriating power...
to revert to my true form!
This is bad! We can't get him any angrier!
Okay, okay, let's wrap it up, Little Miss Over!
I'm so sorry! I swear, that boy of mine...
I'm so sorry...
Take these Natto as an apology!
He's full of rage!
Oh, crap! He's reverting to his true form!
What's gonna happen!?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
AngelofChaotix
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
TORPEDO GIRL
Oh, dear, I've got a blister...
The hell is this all about?
I'm going home.
Ten
O
The number you are trying to reach is currently unavailable.
Guess I can't blame them...
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience!
Finally!
Torpedo Girl is here!!
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience!
Finally!
Torpedo Girl is here!!
Your attention, please!
Eyes up here, everybody!
She's annoying...
Guys, don't let her set the pace!
Take the initiative!
Let's go!
Ringaling Heaven!
Not again!
Outta my way!
Stop this act of foolishness!
Tennosuke!
I will not tolerate even the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Could she be one of the legendary Idiot Killers?
What do you mean by Idiot Killers?
I've heard about them.
They say that there are warriors in the world,
who can't tolerate any acts of foolishness.
They were known as the Idiot Killers...
and they suppressed all types of foolishness that they saw.
Then...
Judging by her speech, intense brutality, and direct actions,
I fear she is one of the Idiot Killers.
What a fearsome... battle nerd!
But I thought the Idiot Killers were annihilated ages ago!
So how can you be here?
I'm the only one that survived.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
I couldn't give care less about the Idiot Killers,
but you're gonna pay for attacking Tennosuke!
Take this!
Don Patch Sword!
That is a green onion!
Someone finally noticed!
No, we knew that for a while now.
I will not tolerate even the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
That attack was so fast I couldn't even see it!
How's anyone supposed to even dodge that?
Guys, don't make a fool of yourselves!
Nailed it!
But why? Why was Bo-bobo knocked out just then?
What are you, an imbecile!?
No, he really isn't! He was actually being serious there!
I will bring the hammer of justice on all those who act foolish!
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Not so fast, OVER!
For I, Dengakuman,
challenge you, nah-na-la!
She just ignored me...
Torpedo
Communications
It's been too long since I was last in this form.
This really brings back memories of the good old days...
We object!
Abolish Weapons!!
I was such a rebel back then...
You actually were an anti-weapon protester?
But you're a torpedo!
Oh, I feel so sheepish, torpedo!
Oh, how far I've come since then...
Now I'm a commercial queen!
You never can tell how things will turn out...
A commercial queen!?
It's the truth.
As proof, I'll show you the commercial I starred in.
PNN News
End
I just moved into this house today.
And the girl next door...
Kamato
Bore through it...
is a torpedo.
For the best meetings in life...
Torpedo Moving Center
Torpedo Moving Center.
Who's this trying to market to!?
I feel so sheepish, torpedo!
Be careful, guys!
If you act foolish like she wants you to, you'll be in big trouble!
She's right, everyone! We can't act foolish!
Your mere existence is foolish!
Well, if that's the case, then we're all doomed!
I don't mind that...
Commercial Queen
because I'm a torpedo!
She's accurate and bold...
Oh, no! She's really strong!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
So her Idiot Killer title isn't just for show...
One...
Two.
Torpedo Girl is strong! She's extremely strong!
One...
Two.
How is she capable of attacking like that?
It's all so simple.
Torpedoes are outfitted
with a high-level N-3 automatic tracking sensor
which ensures that they reach their targets.
When the sensor's electric reactor reaches 380 kilowatts,
it locks out the main engine and ignites,
allowing the engine to produce its maximum output.
You just made that up, didn't you?
Yep, mee-ow!
I will not tolerate even the slightest act of foolishness!
In the name of the torpedo!
Okay, then...
Kitty 1080 degree Midair Revolution!
Alright, now that I have a break...
Torpedo
Crossword
Puzzles
I seriously need to complete these crossword puzzles I've been working on.
These are getting hard...
Let's see... "A weapon used for sinking ships"...
You morons! You're letting her control the fight!
I'm not gonna let her lead me around!
Never!
I will crush those who fool around!
We're in trouble!
This means that Bo-bobo can't attack her, either!
Who do you take me for, Heppokomaru?
I'm not fooling around here!
Let's fight!
He'll be fine like that!
In my swimming trunks!
You moron!
Out!
Hold it, OVER!
I, Dengakuman, challenge you to a duel, nah-na-la!
She just ignored me again...
How is she so strong!?
She's nothing like she was before she transformed!
I will tolerate no foolishness
while I still draw breath!
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
How are we supposed to defeat her?
What? Defeat the sole survivor of the legendary Idiot Killers?
There's no way you can pull it off.
Torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo...
Is that how you really laugh!?
Oh, no! I feel like I'm gonna sneeze!
Anti-aircraft missile!
That had to be a forced sneeze!
She's extremely dangerous! We should just survey the situation for now without doing anything!
That sounds good.
What's the matter? No one wants to act foolish?
Nobody, yeah!
Found you!
Bo-bobo, you idiot!
My apologies!
Alright! I got her now!
Now's your chance, boys! Beat her down!
Alright!
I may be a cute torpedo,
but we live in a civilized society!
This is a serious crime, you know.
But I'll let you go this time.
You may leave.
Okay...
Good luck, boy!
Annoying...
The foolishness ends right now!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The Afro that Dances and the Afro that Watches!!
He used a Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique! Now the battle's as good as won!
H-How did she...?
What the...?
She stopped it?
She managed to block my Fist of the Nose Hair with her toes!?
I knew I shouldn't have expected much
from someone from the Hair Kingdom.
I can't win this.
Now I hope now you realize.
There is no one in the world who can defeat me.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
I'm Tokoroten!
I ♥ Tokoroten
This is hopeless...
She's suppressed every attack we have!
We'll never win at this rate!
As one who does not tolerate foolishness...
I cannot tolerate your existences.
And that is because... I'm a torpedo!
But we can't just give up!
There must be some way to attack her!
Think...
Think.
He turned into the Thinking Man!
Stop this foolishness!
Bo-bobo's been taken out!
We have to think of another way to defeat her!
Think...
They turned into the Birth of Venus!
And why are you the Thinking Man?
Why am I the Thinking Man!?
But you did that yourself!
Think...
What's with that dumb face!?
Is that your epiphany face or something!?
That face is out!
Not so fast, OVER!
Prepare to get terminated by your opponent, Dengakuman, nah-na la!
Smash! Torpedo.
Why is she treating me this way, nah-na-la!?
I've got an idea!
What is it?
A single arrow may snap, but three arrows together cannot be broken!
I hear ya!
We may be able to do something if all three of us combine our powers!
Perfect! Then let's give it a shot!
Alright! Everyone get out your arrows!
Yeah!
But those aren't arrows!
With these three arrows combined, we are invincible!
They snapped anyway!
What's the deal? We weren't acting goofy at all!
You're acting pretty goofy to me!
You guys!
I'll send you all flying to the ends of the Earth!
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
You half-wit! You're right where we want you to be!
You're up against the three of us!
We can stop your reckless charge now!
Right, guys?
Where did everybody go!?
That wasn't even our plan.
Nope, nope. Not at all.
Just do it! Put me out of my misery!
Don Patch!
But you both deserted him.
I will not tolerate even the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Torpedo
I think I gained some weight...
We will not allow your evil deeds to continue, either!
And that is because he too is a torpedo!
Stop your stupidity!
Offset Failed
Torpedo, torpedo, torpedo...
How dare you harm Tennosuke!
But you threw him into her!
Now I'll just have to use my nose hairs to keep her from moving!
But don't you remember, Bo-bobo?
She made short work of that Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique!
After this break...
Is the super-fun...
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
No! Do fishnet stockings turn you on or something!?
They don't.
Then...
what's going on here!?
It worked! This is the Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Torpedo Angling!
He did it!
How can it be angling if it doesn't have any angles?
I've stopped you dead in your tracks!
You can't fly anywhere, anymore!
Now he's got her!
Oh, dear... I don't want to be bound by a man...
But I guess it doesn't hurt to try it just once...
What am I talking about? I feel so sheepish, torpedo!
Bo-bobo!
What's going on? How could Bo-bobo's Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Techniques
be defeated twice in a row?
Bo-bobo!
Hang in there!
Please... That was far too kinky for our first time.
Remember, I'm a torpedo, so you have to be gentle with me...
Otherwise... I... will... explode!
I don't know if this is a joke or for real.
Now that it's come to this, we'll attack from three directions!
Yeah!
Alright! We've got a hold of her!
Take care of her now, Bo-bobo!
Stop! Let me go, you perverts!
No!
How dare you gang up on a frail woman like me!
Cowards, cowards, cowards, cowards...
Cowards get my...
Torpedo Whirlwind Kick !!!
Why must men be ever so violent?
You're beasts! You're all nothing but beasts!
All of you kneel down!
Seriously... How far do you have to drive me up the wall? I can't take it any more!
Why can't you just cut it out? You're all uncontrollable!
It's about time you learned
what's right and what's wrong!
Because you're all my precious students...
I don't understand how this torpedo thinks...
Now, what's done is done.
You should all apologize to your teacher.
We're sorry.
Who said I was a teacher?
Really now... I can't even take my eyes off you for a second!
You bitch! That was a scam!
Where are you touching, pervert?
You've let your guard down!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Violent Nose Hair Fist
He got her!
That should settle it this time.
More! Give me more!
Are you serious!? I can't believe it didn't work!
What is she, invincible!?
That felt too good.
The least I can do is to thank you.
Torpedo Folk Tales
The Torpedo Maiden
Episode 1: Thanks
What the crap!? She's doing something weird!
I'm sorry to disturb you at this hour.
I'm the torpedo to whom you did a favor for this afternoon.
I have come to thank you.
You can't come in. Go home.
I understand. In that case...
Excuse my intrusion!
Torpedoing
My Way
Here. It's my signature.
You're acting extremely foolish!
Bo-bobo's flying!
And now, I'll head towards Tennosuke...
Why!?
He's headed right for us!
And he's holding that weird signature!
You're quite good, I see.
But I cannot tolerate this.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
I cannot tolerate you either!
And that is because...
I'm Bo-bobo!
I don't think her poses were that disturbing!
Are you serious?
Torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo, torpedo...
If he uses a foolish attack, she launches at him...
If he uses a normal attack, she blocks it...
The Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Techniques don't work either...
So...
Why is Bo-bobo so confident?
I've finally found...
the only way to defeat you once and for all!
That's not possible. And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Bo-bobo World!
What's going on!? What's happening!?
Bo-bobo has begun his counterattack in Bo-bobo World!
But can Bo-bobo win
against such a terrifying foe as Torpedo Girl!?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll meet Hajike-ing people if you go out on your holiday!
Your lucky item is a highlighter the color of my afro!
If you tied, you'll have peaceful days after a week of ups and downs.
And if you lost, if you eat too much of your favorite food, it'll harm your health and your wallet!
We'll lose to Torpedo Girl at this rate!
Now we'll have to use our trump card, Bo-bobo!
Yeah! Let's go! Eat this!
We don't have any trump card!
Huh? You don't?
Well, now that you mention it...
We do... I guess we do...
Which is it?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Torpedo Girl!!
I'll judge you
in the name
of the Earth♪
But it'll be a lot of work....
Whatever! Just do it already!