It's time for Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
I'm the heroine here!
Don't just take over my role like that!
It's time for Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Bo-bobo and company had a tough battle with the legendary Idiot Killer Torpedo Girl.
I will bring the hammer of justice on all those who act foolish.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
I've finally found...
the only way to defeat you once and for all!
Here it goes! Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Planet Judge
Judgment of Mercury
Judgment of Earth
The infinite galaxies that unify the powers of these nine great planets...
Judgment of Mars
Judgment of Jupiter
Judgment of Saturn
and reign over the solar systems of distant galaxies...
Judgment of Uranus
Judgment of Neptune
is the Universe!
I don't get it at all!
Bo-bobo won with the powers of Bo-bobo World and the Judgment of the Cosmos!
However, they had little time to celebrate, for their next foe, Halekulani, lay in wait for them!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Halekulani has returned to the Hair Hunters under orders to eliminate Bo-bobo.
He is the last of the Four Lords of Margarita,
and also the strongest.
The strongest, you say?
Let's save that talk for after dinner!
Now take your seats everyone, it's dinner time!
I really don't think we should be eating at a time like this...
Dig in!
I don't have any appetite.
Yay! It's dinner, nah-na-la!
Time to eat!
Dig in, guys!
Dinner's over!
He's just indulging himself!
To Hallelujah Land!
Full Speed
Ahead!
Next Stop:
Hell!?
Lord Halekulani!
Reporting in!
Lord OVER has been defeated by Bo-bobo!
Your point?
Well... How should we deal with this matter?
Can't you do anything without my orders?
My apologies!
I will send assassins right away!
I couldn't care less about the likes of Bo-bobo.
He's no more than a worm compared to me.
Alright, let's get out there and defeat Halekulani, Bo-bobo!
But I can't.
I'm just a worm..
The hell!?
You chicken or something?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop hitting me!
Stop it! Stop it! Please stop it!
Leave me alone!
I don't wanna go!
Pupated.
How dare you hide in your shell!
So where can we find him?
His base is Hallelujah Land, the world's biggest theme park.
Theme park?
I'm going!
He became a butterfly!
Halekulani of the Four Lords of Margarita...
He's a worthy opponent, indeed!
Yeah!
Yeah, but you guys aren't worthy!
Then again, I've always wanted to visit Hallelujah Land...
Shut up! You too?
We all do!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
What kinds of rides do you want to go on?
Well... I...
Don't get so excited!
Why me!?
But how do we get there?
It's simple.
We just have to board the train at this station behind me...
Now departing for Hallelujah Land Station!
Meadow
Station
Since when was there a station here?
And I have six boarding passes with me!
Six passes?
One... Two... Three... Four... Five... Six... Seven...
Hey, aren't we one short?
Don't worry. We've got it sorted.
Good to hear.
And so, they all boarded the train without a hitch.
Nice Idea!
It sure is fancy inside!
It's so nice, nah-la!
We'll arrive tomorrow morning.
Take it easy and rest for today.
So fancy!
Turncoat!
This bed's reserved only for me, the heroine!
What's your deal? You're a bunch of... A bunch of...
I'm the heroine! Get that through your heads!
I don't understand...
But we've got this big room all to ourselves...
Don Patch!
Is Tennosuke really gonna be alright?
I told you, you don't need to worry!
I'm gonna go check on him to make sure!
Tennosuke!
You OK over there?
The Words I'd Like to Say
He's completely relaxed!
I feel stupid for worrying about him.
Right?
Look at them, all fast asleep with unsuspecting faces...
They don't even realize that their lives are in danger...
But honestly...
Who would imagine that anyone would be riding on top of the train?
Check. I've captured your rook.
Oh, so that's how you're gonna play?
What's with these guys up here?
In that case... I'll use my lance skewer!
Just kidding...
Warp!
Then I'll use my spinning tactics!
You've really done it, haven't you?
Then I'll promote my piece!
Wait...
How can we play it here!?
Hey, who are you?
You were peeking in on our game...
Are you a Shogi maniac?
Of course not!
I am one of Halekulani's men...
Kanemaru
Kanemaru!
I have come to claim your lives!
What!?
The wind's so strong that I can barely stand!
How is he standing!?
It's simple!
I'm the greatest man at fighting on top of trains in the world!
The Greatest Man on Trains!
Is that why you're standing?
That makes sense!
How does it?
But...
I don't need to stand on top of the train...
to attack you!
What?
Fly for me, Tennosuke!
Tennosuke! Grab on!
Nice, Bo-bobo!
It burns! It burns! I smell like burnt jelly!
Dammit! I lengthened them too much!
I'll pull you back up right away!
Here we have our main dish of the day.
I wonder what it is?
It's tokoroten!
What!?
He's the devil...
That's enough fooling around!
Extend!
Extensible Spear!
Hey, Mr. Suzuki!! How are you doing?
Oh, that sounds rough!
Kenny, you've gotta eat your green peppers!
What's going on?
How am I supposed to sleep with all this noise?
What's... going on?
You're getting ahead of yourself...
Now let me use a secret technique that makes use of this air pressure!
What?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
When you think of Kyoto,
this comes to mind!
That's got nothing to do with air pressure!
Stop messing about!
Get a grip!
Bo-bobo!
That's one down.
You're next!
What the hell!?
Achieve Your Dream!
Good luck...
Good luck in Tokyo!
Sis!
What's the sister doing here?
That was the Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique: Encouragement Fist!
Encouragement Fist!
Was that supposed to be a technique?
Fine then!
I'll fight with my spear from now on!
Spear? You mean me?
He sure is a flexible companion...
Let's go!
Nose Hair Wobble-Wobble
Double Secret Technique:
Tokoro Spear!
Help!
Tennosuke!
What?
You can cut and cut, but it's still Tennosuke!
This is the Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Tokoro Candy!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique: Tokoro Candy
I dare you to defeat this secret technique if you can!
Gross!
The games are over!
Here goes!
They just won't stop moving!
I caught something weird!
I'm the tragic heroine, Don Patch!
I'll never hand over the position of the heroine to anyone!
Did I say I was the heroine?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
I hold the title of "Greatest Man on Trains!"
There is no one who can defeat me on top of a train!
If you hold the title of "Greatest Man on Trains..."
then we'll win with teamwork!
I'm gonna fall!
What a bunch of fools!
Die!
Spear Beam
Look out!
Teamwork!
This is teamwork!
What amazing teamwork!
But that's not teamwork...
Beauty made that remark in her sleep.
Alright!
I'll use my teamwork to defeat you here and now!
Hell yeah.
Tunnel
Ow! Ow! Ow! My head! My head!
Hang on! We're almost at the exit!
Alright! Let's pull ourselves together and try it again!
Not another tunnel!
Ow! Ow! Ow! My head! My head!
My head! My head! My head!
Tunnel
Now you know what a train battle is like.
It seems like we're heading into a forest.
The trees are closing in!
You're right!
I dodged it!
Here!
D-Did you just see a little old man in the trees!?
What are you talking about?
I said there was a little old man...
There are little old men! I'm sure of it!
And plus this big old man, too!
Tennosuke!
Sup?
It's a Nu car!
You guys fall in with him!
Fools! You may be able to keep up, but you can't get back on!
From Tchaikovsky's...
"Swan Lake"...
Four Swans Jump!
But there's only three of you!
Now, give back the last swan!
What the hell!?
The sun's starting to rise...
Hey, look over there!
Hallelujah Land
It's Hallelujah Land!
That's it?
Move it!
What are you doing, Bo-bobo?
Look ahead of him!
There's a puppy on the tracks!
Is he doing all this just to save a puppy?
Outta my way, you dumb mutt!
Now, which car were Beauty and the others riding in...?
That one!
Alright!
Let's make our way into Hallelujah Land's first area...
Space World
Space World!
Excuse us!
"Run away!"  "Run away!"
Space World is an area where people get to meet real aliens.
It is one of the most popular attractions in Hallelujah Land.
It's morning already?
Have we reached Hallelujah Land yet?
Help!    Help!
We're on a different planet!
Hold it right there!
We haven't settled this yet!
Let's duel!
That's so cruel! How could you do this to the aliens?
The poor things!
Help!    Help!
How about a car chase?
Just what I wanted, you horrible man!
Alright! First to the UFO wins!
Whaaaat!?
Get away!
What did we do to deserve this!!!?
What was that for, asshole!!?
Now we can't go back to space anymore!!
You gonna pay for that, huh!?
We don't wanna stay on Earth for the rest of our lives!!
Quit your damn chirping!
I don't get why you're making these weird accusations at me...
You're wide open, Bo-bobo.
Take this! Triple Strike!
First Strike!!
Second Strike!!
That's nothing!
Third Strike!!
Guard up!
Okay! That's twice for me!
Dammit...
You bastard!
How dare you harm him like that!
You're gonna pay!
That's him in the middle? No way!
Now it's my turn to fight back!
Let's go, Tennosuke!
What? What do I do?
Tokoroten Trampoline!
Don Patch! Let's use that attack!
Which attack?
That attack!
Double Desk Pad Set!
Rub, rub, scrub, scrub,
Rub, rub, scrub, scrub...
Static Electricity On!
Take this! Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Lightning NoseHair Ball!
Lightning NoseHair Ball
I admit defeat.
From this day forth, you're the "Greatest Man on Trains."
This sash is yours now.
Looks like we've made it to Hallelujah Land.
Yeah! I'm so happy! I've always wanted to go here!
Hey!
Hey! Take a good look at this!
Check it out, Beauty!
We're the greatest on trains!
Greatest on trains! Hear that? Greatest on trains!
There's no one who can defeat me atop a train!
Is that supposed to impress me or something?
Anyway, let's go!
What attraction should we see first?
Bo-bobo and company have broken into Halekulani's base, Hallelujah Land.
What kinds of traps await them in the greatest theme park of all time?
What will become of Bo-bobo?
Trash
in
the Trash Can
Greatest on Trains
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, wake up early and go to the waterfront and you'll be hajike-ing all day!
Your lucky item is a train the color of Heppokomaru's hair!
If you tied, don't play cards outside on a windy day or you may lose your cards.
And if you lost, you may lose your chance this week!
If you meet an alien, make sure to take a picture!
This is Hallelujah Land?
Just you wait, Halekulani!
I'll defeat you at once!
But before all that...
Let's ride the roller coaster!
I wanna see the goldfish old man show!
They just wanna have fun!
I'm always a child at heart!
What are you talking about?
Huh? How am I shrinking!?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Hallelujah Land
RIOT!
We all
turned
into kids
♪
Here come the Pure-heart Boys!