Aesthetic Salon
Today, we'll take a look at the next big thing, the Aesthetic Salon.
So what's the people's choice here?
That would have to be this one...
It makes your skin and everything else look gorgeous!
The Money Bath!
What unthinkable gorgeousness!
But they say there is a man who takes a money bath every day!
Who is this gorgeous man?
I couldn't care less about the likes of Bo-bobo.
Four Lords of Margarita
Halekulani
He's no more than a worm compared to me.
Alright, let's get out there and defeat Halekulani, Bo-bobo!
But I can't.
I'm just a worm...
Bo-bobo and company made their way into Halekulani's territory...
That's the biggest theme park in the world...
Hallelujah Land!
Hallelujah Land
Mama!
We're flying!
And so, the train became a star.
No, it did not!
I hold the title of "Greatest Man on Trains!"
Kanemaru
There is no one who can defeat me on top of a train!
If you hold the title of "Greatest Man on Trains..."
then we'll win with teamwork!
Die!
Spear Beam
Look out!
Teamwork!
This is teamwork!
What amazing teamwork!
Teamwork!
But that's not teamwork...
Space World
This was Space World, a very popular area
where you could meet real aliens.
Excuse us!
"Run away!" "Run away!"
"Whaaaat!?"
Get away!
"What did we do to deserve this!!!?"
This marked the outbreak of the great galactic war.
Now! Return fire!
Are we hit?
No options left! Turn 90 degrees starboard!
We'll charge right at those UFOs!
Let's go!
For victory!
That's not how it happened!
Take this! Triple Strike!
First Strike!!
Second Strike!!
Third Strike!!
Heave-ho!
Okay! That's twice for me!
Take this! Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Lightning NoseHair Ball
To commemorate his victory,
Bo-bobo attained the sash of "Strongest on Trains."
He caused an intergalactic war and that's all he gets for it?
That can't be right!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
AngelofChaotix
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
At last, Bo-bobo and company have arrived at heaven on Earth, Hallelujah Land.
So where should we head first?
Well, that's an easy map to follow!
Hallelujah Land
Map
Who would follow it?
So where should we...
Whatever!
Let's just start with wherever looks the most fun!
Yes, sir!
Is that really alright with you?
This one!
The Old Goldfish Guy Show
It's fun!
But that looks really boring!
The Hallelujah Land
RIOT!
We all
turned
into kids
♪
The Goldfish Old Guy Show
This is the Nanking bamboo screen!
Money Castle
Meanwhile, back at Halekulani...
Lord Halekulani! Here are this month's proceeds!
I can see one that's going into the red...
We don't need any attractions that don't bring in money.
The Old Goldfish Guy Show
It's fun!
I wonder what they're doing in there?
This must be Halekulani's doing!
Is he alright?
That explosion just now...
turned my raw egg into a boiled egg!
Now I can't make raw egg on rice anymore!
Raw egg on rice?
Why do you even care?
Halekulani...
He destroys any attraction that doesn't make profits!
Even if there are customers inside...
That can't be...
What a bastard!
You won't get away with this, Halekulani!
You're stepping on me! You're stepping on me!
Oh, were you there?
Yes I was, nah-la!
Halekulani, you goddamn bastard!
Kappa Forest
You're going down!
They just wanna have fun!
That's nothing...
We're not done yet...
Kiddy Area
Are you really that desperate to have fun?
Wait up, Bo-bobo!
This place is full of children!
Where are they?
Welcome to the Kiddy Area!
What was that?
What's going on? I just shrunk!
It's alright! This is a place where anyone can become a child!
It's a popular attraction where anyone can return to their childhood and play!
Does that mean Bo-bobo and the other guys did, too?
Yes!
Those three guys as kids?
I can't afford to miss this!
I see Don Patch!
I'm five years old!
He's so not cute!
What's going on?
Is this candy?
I want friends...
Just say that then!
Bo-bobo!
The revolution is nigh.
He was a samurai?
Is that Tennosuke?
How beautiful!
He was a narcissist!
All three of them had messed-up childhoods!
What's gonna happen if they meet?
That kid looks friendly...
That kid will understand...
Let us talk...
Yes, let's talk...
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
They formed a band!
Pure-heart BOYS Live
Hey, hey, once I'm done my language drills...
we'll have a party at the school!
Oh, no!
Pure-heart! Pure-heart!
Pure-heart BOYS!
But they're not selling well!
Okay, now...
Yeah!
Let's play tag over there!
And they got over it so quickly!
Okay, so Tennosuke's It!
Sure!
Alright! Let's start!
OK, I'm over here!
Wait up!
Look out, Beauty!
Wait for me!
I shall slay thee, It!
What do you think you're doing to him!?
Come here, you!
Are you okay? You're getting picked on just for being It...
I'm not being It! I'm being a pretty-boy It!
This is fun!
Wouldn't it be really bad if an enemy showed up now?
Enemy
No enemies here!
You're just a scaredy-cat!
If there was one, I'd beat them up!
An enemy!
What, me!?
It's the enemy!
No, stop! I'm not an enemy!
But it says "enemy" right on your head.
It really does!
This is bad! We're still children!
Things can't get any worse!
I have you now, Bo-bobo!
I'm one of Halekulani's men, Nightmare!
Nightmare
And now that you're a kid, taking you down will be a piece of cake!
Take us down!?
Give it up!
You can't use any Fists in your current state.
You're all...
deat meat!
What do you take me for?
I may be a kid, but that doesn't mean I can't fight!
It didn't work!
Hey! Let go of me!
Three-point Shot!
And it's in!
He pulled ahead!
I did it! I did it!
You're being ridiculous!
You're next, Bo-bobo!
Take this!
Narcissist Guard!
What have you done with my beautiful face!?
My sincerest apologies.
Just watch the face.
Fine! Then this time...
I'll cut him in half!
Sure, as long as you don't touch my face.
Dodge it! Tennosuke!
My face...
Why don't you drop that kid already!?
Because a samurai does not abandon his comrades!
Hold up!
Man, you guys owe me one!
Don Patch!
That's amazing! They're in perfect sync, even with their childhood personalities!
But if he can't use the Fist of the Nose Hair...
That's right! You are no match for me if you cannot use the Fist of the Nose Hair!
But I can use the Fist of the Nose Hair!
What!?
Fist of the Nose Hair!
He can!?
Hey, those aren't nose hairs!
Gotta study, gotta study...
Temple School
How the hell are these guys so strong?
Are they even kids?
Meanwhile...
in the remains of the Old Goldfish Guy Show...
This is the Nanking bamboo screen!
This is just like Broadway! It's magical!
It's nothing like Broadway, nah-na-la.
Now you've crossed the line...
But you're still kids! You're no match for me!
I'll show you how much more powerful grown-ups are.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
I'll show you how much more powerful grown-ups are.
You can't escape me!
See, they're kids, after all. They've gotten so bored of the fight, they're playing fishing!
Yay!
It worked!
Great idea putting a shark in the sandbox!
Isn't that a little dangerous? What about the other kids playing in there?
I couldn't care less!
How can you say that, you villain?
Aren't you the villain here!?
Let's run to the swings!
Okay! He can't attack us while we're on the swings!
You seen Don Patch around?
What's he doing there?
Franco #2
I am Franco #2.
He got on Franco instead of the swings!
I am afraid.
My eyes are spinning.
Now it's your turn!
Yay!
He fell for it!
A trapdoor, is it? Just the kind of thing a child would...
It's so deep! This doesn't even count as a trapdoor!
Impertinent brats...
I've had enough of you! Time to bring out my pitching machine!
Take this!
Don Patch Guard!
You ready?
Of course!
Then go!
Narcissist Magnum!
Here I come!
Handsome Block!
My face!
Are you alright, Tennosuke?
I'm fine.
Don't laugh at me!
Now time for me to use this!
Pipe Maze
Let's show the grown-up how we kids fight!
How kids fight?
Sounds fun. Please show me!
Where'd he run off to?
Flamethrower!
How is this kids' fighting!?
You brat! Stay still!
Where'd he go?
Children...
Children!
How is this children's fighting!?
How? How do they know where I am?
Is that a...?
It's a transmitter, baby!
How'd you learn this stuff?
Mission accomplished... Major Beauty.
What's with those words on the side of the screen?
I never gave any such orders!
Now you're asking for it! I went easy on you because you were kids, but not anymore!
Now, I'll use my signature technique to send you all to Hell!
You'll be defeated by your own nightmares!
Nightmares?
Have a taste of the fatal phantasm...
Death Nightmare
The Death Nightmare has the power to make your nightmares come real!
Now, let's see your nightmares!
Tofu
Just hurry up and admit it!
You're tofu, aren't you?
Your friends Konjac and Jelly have given in already.
Tofu
Now just give in and join the tofu!
I'll never give in! I'll never give in to tofu!
I'm sorry, what?
This is the most pointless nightmare ever.
So let's see what the others are like.
What!?
This is a nightmare.
That is not a nightmare! What kind of dream is that anyway?
How should I know?
Oh well.
How's your nightmare going, Bo-bobo?
Um... we want to play basketball.
I don't get it in the slightest!
Hey. It went in my pocket.
What kind of dream is that!?
I should be asking that!
Now it's our turn! Let's go!
Yeah!
Are they...?
Transform!
CANDY BALL
So long for now!
They're gonna turn into Bobopatch!
Can they turn into him as kids?
Fusion complete.
He's incomplete!
You are mistaken. I am not incomplete at all.
You're pretty clearly incomplete! Because I'm pretty sure Bobopatch looked a little more like...
BOBOPATCH
Who drew this anyway?
Now let us begin this holy battle.
Sacred Sword Excalibur!
No! No way! You won't even cut paper with that! It looks bent and crooked!
I'll show you my true power.
back
His back's even worse!
Here I go!
He's gone...
What can a scribble like you do against me?
Advent of the Holy Guardian
He actually won!
Justice always prevails.
Meanwhile, Halekulani was relaxing in his money bath in Money Castle...
Lord Halekulani!
Bo-bobo has broken into Hallelujah Land!
His strength is first-class!
Fist of Gorgeous
You're worth no more than small change.
W-W-What a fearsome technique!
Halekulani's can convert anything and anyone into money!
Will Bo-bobo and company stand a chance?
Wait!
Boys, play to your hearts' content.
At least until the next battle...
Don't miss the next episode, nah-la!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll explode with talent at your recital and get really popular!
Your lucky food is raw egg on rice with fresh eggs!
If you tied, be sure to ask for an encore at the Old Goldfish Guy show.
And if you lost, when you ride the slide, make sure there aren't any dangerous creatures at the bottom!
We're at Hallelujah Land and all
but we can't have any fun!
There's no time to have fun!
Aren't we here to defeat Halekulani?
That's right! Alright! Time to pull myself together!
Let's charge in without any distractions!
Oh look! The snack house!
Charge!
These guys are hopeless...
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Money Castle!
Break In to
But let's take
a bit of a detour
♥
Can I go home now?