The New Foe is an
Army of Terror!
Not all of them look that terrifying, though...
The last and strongest of the Four Lords of Margarita,
Halekulani!
Bo-bobo and company have come to Hallelujah Land to defeat Halekulani.
It may seem like an amusement park, but it's the enemy base.
That's right.
The Old Goldfish Guy Show
It's fun!
That's nothing...
We're not done yet...
Why are these three so desperate to have fun?
Kiddy Area
And so,
they came to a super-popular spot in Hallelujah Land
where anyone can return to their childhood, called the Kiddy Area!
Y-You guys aren't children!
I have you now, Bo-bobo!
Now that you've become a kid, taking you down will be a piece of cake!
But they're not even kids!
Oh, really?
What?
Here I go!
Bo-bobo Fusion!
My name is Urashima's Casket.
I know this trick! Some smoke will come out, and I'll turn into an old man, right?
But I came prepared.
It's a Don Patch-in-the-Box!
This never happened! That's not how it went!
Are you sure?
Really? My memory's not what it used to be...
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
We're back to normal!
Kiddy Area
We didn't get a chance to play because of that dumb enemy!
I'm blaming you, Suzu!
It wasn't my fault!
Idiot!
What?
Tell us where Halekulani is, now!
Right.
Halekulani is in the building in the center
of Hallelujah Land's 500 attractions...
Money Castle!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
They're not listening!
everybody say HOhoooo!!
But be on your toes!
Halekulani is protected
Hell Killers
by three terrible assassins known as the Hell Killers.
I say bring it on!
Playtime's over! Let's go kick Halekulani's ass!
Oh yeah!
That's the spirit, Bo-bobo!
Let's kick some ass!
Hell yeah!
Money Castle!
Break In to
But let's take
a bit of a detour
♥
What's happening to him?
They're withdrawal symptoms.
He's gone insane from the shock of learning he can't play anymore.
He's run off with Hekkun!
Let him have his way!
The poor boy just can't take it anymore!
Snack House
I sense an enemy in there!
We're gonna take you down!
Liar! You just sense the snacks!
I'm most impressed, Bo-bobo...
I congratulate you for noticing my bloodlust.
There really is one here...
Bo-bobo!
Another one of Halekulani's lackeys?
He's Garbel the Bloody.
What's one of the Hell Killers doing here?
It's the Snack House, nah-na-la!
It's not as though I chose to be here.
Garbel the Bloody
These nails just want a taste of blood.
Take this! Hunting Claws!
Hunting Claws
Everyone run for it!
Hang in there!
I can't last much longer, Bo-bobo!
Leave this one to me!
Thanks!
Secret Technique:
Tokoro Shield!
Forget him, you're my real enemy!
Now, I suppose it's time we tried out our new technique.
A present for me?
Tennosuke!
I will never forget about you!
Yay, yay, yay!
Nose Hair Wobble-Wobble Double Secret Technique:
De-Ten-nation!!
Is everyone alright?
Beauty! That wound...
Don't worry, I'm fine.
It must've been those nails.
That was a pretty disgusting technique.
How about I cut you all to shreds!
Don't you mess with me.
You've harmed Beauty...
You are absolutely... positively...
Despicable!
He turned into a beastman!
Super Sacred Mighty Claw Beast Smash Bullet!
And now he's using a really weird technique!
My favorite food is 100% tuna with a hint of bonito.
No one cares.
Damn it all! Who do you take me for!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Coating!!
Okay, coating-ish.
Wobble-Wobble Nose Hair Double Secret Technique:
Mobius Wall!!
How amazing! They're just toying around with Garbel the Bloody!
But Bo-bobo seems a little bit off of his game.
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Ikinokore
Stay alive!
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby
Baby!
Is it just my imagination?
Have you figured it out yet, young lady?
It's because Don Patch isn't here!
If he's not here, Bo-bobo can't unlock his true power!
I have to do something about it...
Damn you!
Patch! Patch!
Don Patch!
Counterattack-patch! Counterattack-patch!
Alright! It's working!
Now Bo-bobo can unlock his true power!
Me thinks mine is better-patch!
He saw right through me!
Never do that again.
Am I useless to them?
Oh hey, it's Don Patch.
Something wrong?
Garbel, was it? My next attack will seal your claws!
That's quite the bold declaration there.
But don't think I'll be using the same attack!
Howl!
Darkness Serpent
It all ends now!
Bo-bobo!
Manicurist
I have five years experience in nail art.
Nail Artist Yasuko
I am Yasuko. Have at you.
Beautiful Nail Life!!
Oh my goodness! Is this really me?
What a lovely design.
I feel at least three years younger!
We have been awakened to beauty.
We will fight no longer.
What the hell!? What's have you done to my snake nails?
Now that you have lost your nails, you will never harm anyone again.
Tennosuke! Let's use that technique!
Okay!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Drink
Alright!
Here goes! The coup de grace!
Wobble-Wobble Nose Hair Double Secret Technique:
Tokoro Nose Hairs!!
Tokoro Nose Hairsl!!
I'll bring the smack-down on anyone who lays a finger on Beauty! You got that!?
Y-Yes!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Hero Show
Fashion Sentai
Oldschool Rangers
With burning passion, and the impact of battle... Oldschool Red!
With the thrill of love, and a maiden's prayer... Oldschool Pink!
The cool Oldschool Blue!
Fashion Sentai Oldschool Rangers!
Ow, ow, ow!
Was I unconscious or something?
I'm all played out now.
What the hell are you doing? Where are the others?
Shh! The enemy's on his way!
What? Is it the Hell Killers?
Evil
Oldschool Rangers! It's time to meet your end!
Isn't that just the bad guy of the hero show?
Quiet during the performance!
Just let me watch this! Please!
Now who should I kidnap here?
Candidate
What is that guy? Raw food!?
He's getting closer...
I can't make eye contact!
I must not make eye contact!
He kidnapped me...
He came on his own!
The show must go on.
Stand back!
Don't you care about what happens to the kid?
Keep that child out of this!
The Oldschool Rangers are in trouble!
Oldschool Rangers...
You coward!
Fight us on even grounds!
Oldschool Rangers! Oldschool Rangers!
Forget about me! Defeat the evil!
He self-destructed!
Hey kid, are you alright?
Yeah, are you okay?
Hell yeah! Cause I drink my milk!
There are cows everywhere!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Stop it!
Milk
Moo-moo
Oldschool Rangers
Hero Show
Moo-Moo
Milk Sales Event
Let's drink milk, moo! Milk, moo! Milk, moo!
He's gone and done something weird again!
Milk, moo! Milk, moo!
You're already amoosing if you drink your milk!
Let's all sing together and buy some milk!
Who is he? Could he be one of the Hell Killers that Suzu was talking about?
Get off the stage, Don Patch!
Hair sprouts moo! Hair growth moo! Let's drink milk, moo!
Mil-mil-milk...
This is sick!
This song won't get people buying milk!
You there.
Aren't you one of Bo-bobo's comrades?
Who said anything about comrades?
I'm the main character!
Anywhere and anytime, we got milk!
Are you one of the Hell Killers?
Affirmative.
I am one of the Hell Killers...
My directive is to terminate every member of Bo-bobo's party.
I repeat, aren't you Bo-bobo's comrades?
You heard that, right?
He actually said "Bo-bobo's party!"
Yeah, so?
Don't you mean Don Patch's party!?
Don't mistake me for Bo-bobo! Listen up, I'll tell you how it is!
Bo-bobo
Equals
Me!
I
Equal
Fist of the Nose Hair
Got it!?
Does that mean...
That you're Bo-bobo?
I said I'm Don Patch!
Am I Bo-bobo? Am I not Bo-bobo?
That stuff doesn't matter!
It doesn't matter!
As long as I have him, it doesn't matter.
Oh no! This performance is more emotional than I thought!
Tragedy!
I will crush every last one of you.
Just like I did that doll!
Just like that doll...
Do you mean Yakkun?
Do you mean Yakkun!?
Die!
Death Cannon Revolvers
I have recorded all of your battle data.
In other words, I can predict every move you make!
Now I have to put on poultices...
Poultice
That was unpredictable!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
What!?
Allow me to explain.
When Don Patch wears the Protectors from the Poultice Star,
and draws the shape of the Poultice Constellation with his hands,
he transforms into a cool and tough nice guy, the Poultice Hero!
Poultice! Poultice!
It's stuck!
Stop it! Don't put them on!
Poultice!
I said don't put them on!
What's he doing? I'm scared, Mommy.
Don't try this at home, children.
Make sure you read the instructions and use them correctly.
OK.
Damn it all...
Bring it on, bitch! I, Don Patch, am gonna take you down!
Alright, take this!
Don Patch!
Didn't feel a thing!
Cause I'm an idiot!
He really is an idiot!
What on earth is he?
That was a direct hit!
So why didn't it harm him?
Why? Why not?!
Nonstop Idiot
'Cause I'm an idiot!
THE Idiot
'Cause I'm an idiot! 'Cause I'm an idiot!
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot,
'Cause I'm an idiot!
I may be an idiot, but that still hurts!
He's flying!
It hurts!
I'm an idiot... I'm an idiot, but it still hurts!
My heart hurts...
It hurts...
John...
John! Come back!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Ouch! That hurts! What's his problem? Who's this John, anyway?
What's with this target?
My battle data is entirely unusable!
What's his next move going to be?
It's a piano.
I can't do it! I'm in a slump today!
Slump! Slump! Slump! Slump! Slump!
Slump!
Slump! Slump!
Now what the hell?
Okay, then...
Gotta ship off the canned goods!
Why me?
Canned Goods
Get out!
We don't need so many in stock.
I'll ship half of them back.
OK.
Blah blah blah. Blah blah blah.
Why didn't you sell yourself better?
What the hell just happened?
Damn it all...
I'll never be beaten by the likes of you!
You small-fry! You still don't know who I am?
I'm the main character!!!
Is this the power of a main character?
Secret Technique: Cheapskate Blues.
He's strong! I guess Don Patch's power really is limitless!
He's not Bo-bobo's tag team partner for nothing.
Not that he's the main character...
Hekkun! Patchmi was so scared!
Let's go back and find Bo-bobo.
Just one more attraction!
I said we're going back!
No! Why are you so cold, Hekkun?
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo and company...
Wait up, you jerks!
were headed to Money Castle to find Halekulani.
Suzu! Are we there yet?
Just a bit more!
Suzu!
What?
How much longer?
About five minutes.
Let's get a move on, Tennosuke!
What's wrong, Tennosuke?
His soul's left him.
What's with this structure?
You monster! You're a monster!
Help me, Bo-bobo!
Beauty! Suzu!
An enemy? When did you get here?
Don't you dare lay a finger on those two, or you'll have to answer to me!
Even Dengakuman! This is going from bad to worse!
Beauty! Suzu! Are you alright?
Dengakuman, I'm gonna save you now!
Am I gonna be...
Among Men
That happens a lot.
Yes, it certainly does!
Bo-bobo!
Who are you bastards?
We are the core of the Hell Killers...
The Three Murder Brothers!
We are at our strongest when all three of us are together.
So as three-in-one,
we form the core.
And so that Lord Halekulani may smile upon us...
We will now claim your life!
Bo-bobo and company are but one step away
from reaching Halekulani, the last of the Four Lords of Margarita!
But now that Beauty and the others have been taken hostage...
even Bo-bobo is powerless!
Is this the end? Is it all over for our hero?
It looks like you could use some help.
That voice belongs to...
That's...
Professor Grunty-grunt!
It's Softon.
Isn't that... uh... it's got to be that... how should I say it... It's that, isn't it...
Softon!
Softon! What are you doing here?
Just doing a little part-time job.
Oh, a part-timer?
I'd like a roe-flavored soft-serve please!
This looks like the worst-case scenario.
Please don't ignore me.
Hey, you!
We're busy here, so move along!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Sunlight Through the Trees in Saint Lucia!
That's amazing!
Impressive.
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
Impressive, nah-la!
Now, you foolish fallen angels...
Shall we play the tune of terror?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won,
the moo-re popular you get, you'll really have a cow!
Your lucky items are snacks and fresh-squeezed milk!
If you tied,
leaving your nails long is unlucky!
Keep them nice and short!
And if you lost,
don't trespass into a hero show, or you may be booed off!
What's that weird smell?
I feel like I'm gonna die!
Bo-bobo! Hurry up and save me!
The Three Murder Brothers sure are fearsome! Then we'll face them as the Hajike Trio!
Then I'll be the heroine!
And I'll be the hero!
And what about Tennosuke?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Showdown!
Three Murder Brothers
Hajike Trio!
Who has the better teamwork!?
Does it really matter?