Here we have Money Castle,
the castle of Halekulani, last of the Four Lords of Margarita!
They say if you throw your change at this castle,
you'll receive a blessing!
Okay everyone, let's make our way to the bus.
Huh?
At the Snack House of Hallelujah Land,
Halekulani's lackey, Garbel the Bloody, stood before Bo-bobo and company!
He's a scary guy that attacked us with his fingernails!
But seriously, what's with those long nails!?
Nose Hair Wobble-Wobble Double Secret Technique:
De-Ten-nation!!
Damn it all! Who do you take me for?
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Coating!!
Okay, coating-ish.
Wobble-Wobble Nose Hair Double Secret Technique:
Mobius Wall!!
Meanwhile,
Don Patch and Heppokomaru were at the hero show, fighting with the T-500.
He's hurting the cows too MOOch!
Very clever, Beauty.
Die!
Death Cannon Revolvers
Poultice!
I'll never be beaten by the likes of you!
You small-fry! You still don't know who I am?
I'm the main character!!!
Here goes! The coup de grace!
Wobble-Wobble Nose Hair Double Secret Technique:
Tokoro Nose Hairs!!
Bo-bobo and friends defeated Garbel the Bloody.
But who should stand before our heroes...
but the Three Murder Brothers!
The Three Murder Brothers
With Beauty and Suzu kidnapped, Bo-bobo was in a dilemma!
Help me!
But just then, who should show up but...
It's Professor Grunty-grunt!
It's Softon...
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Sunlight Through the Trees in Saint Lucia!
That's amazing!
Impressive.
Now, you foolish fallen angels...
Shall we play the tune of terror?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
What just happened?
Not so fast!
Look up here!
Beauty!
Suzu!
When did you...?
We have ourselves some precious hostages.
Stop it! What do you think you're doing?
Hell's Gum!
It smells!
Hell's Gum is spoiled milk-flavored.
It stinks!
The stench!
All those on the receiving end of this attack suffer a terrible fate.
In 30 minutes, this smell...
This smell...
What'll happen?
will kill them!
Kill us? Just from the smell?
Is that even physically possible?
What!?
Showdown!
Three Murder Brothers
Hajike Trio!
Who has the better teamwork!?
Three Murder Brothers
Middle Child: Megafan
I'm the middle child of the Three Murder Brothers: Megafan!
Now, let's see if you can make your way up the Climb High Tower!
You son of a bitch... You're playing dirty!
Release Beauty and Suzu!
And if you don't...
What'll you do if I don't?
I'm gonna make him...
Big Brother!
touch this guy!
Little Brother!
Bro!
L-Little Brother!
Little Brother!
No! No! No! No! No!
What the hell were you thinking, bastard!?
How could you think up something so horrible!?
Everything alright, little brother?
I was so scared...
I'll act flustered so I can appeal to his conscience!
Look, look!
You scared him so much, you broke his mind!
Dumbass!
Just play along, alright?
The wind... The wind stopped...
Then buy a fan!!!
He doesn't have a shred of a conscience!
Alright, leave this to me.
You two go rescue Beauty and Suzu.
Got it!
We're counting on you!
Three Murder Brothers
Youngest Child: Beep
I, the youngest, Beep, will defeat you!
Sai
For being a pink twirly-head, he's stronger than he looks!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Passion of Jamaica
Way to go, Softon!
Yeah!
So we have to jump from plate to plate to get to the top...
Seems so.
What's with this plate?
It's a hot plate!
I'll melt cause I'm tokoroten!
I'm gonna melt, I'm melting!
T-This is all...
Seaweed!
It's a trap!
Exactly!
We've set up a third of these plates with traps.
Just like this seaweed plate.
How about it? The seaweed's restricting your movements!
Then I'll use this technique...
Seaweed
Seaweed!
What kind of attack is that!?
Don't ask me, you're the one who used it!
Fried Tokoroten
10 yen
Three Murder Brothers
Eldest Child Haoh
Fried Tokoroten
10 yen
Release Beauty and Suzu this instant.
You cannot defeat me.
You keep getting on my nerves...
you pink twirly-head!
I'll kick your pink ass!
Nazca
Now receive your judgment as the God of Babylon wills!
Trying to scare me, huh?
Nothing happened at all!
You can't stop me when I'm angry!
Take it!
How'd you like them apples?
You pink twirly-head!
Have you had your fill?
What's going on?
You are in the hands of the God of Babylon.
How though?
I thought I defeated you!
You defeated nothing but the product of your own delusion.
Look carefully.
What?
Love And Peace
Love and Peace!
What in the hell?
Did I really think this up?
You were merely dancing on the palm of the God of Babylon.
Now receive your judgment, along with your foolish ideals!
Judgment of Babylon
Perish with your wicked thoughts.
Also, Love and Peace!
What was that attack about?
Hey, hey!
I've finished the seaweed miso soup!
Does seaweed not work on this bastard?
Seaweed...
Just kidding!
Beautiful Nurse Squad
Now receive your judgment, as the God of Nose Hair wills!
T-This can't be right!
You can use the same technique?
Everything but the face is different!
Of course.
He came out of a really weird place!
There's more of them!
This is nothing but your own fantasy.
You are merely dancing on the ass of some weird thing!
No, those things are doing the dancing!
Judgment of Some Weird Thing
Now perish along with this seaweed!
Next patient, please!
This man's impressive.
You asshole! Don't just sell me off like that!
You're awake, bastard?
Tokoro...
Ten!
Dammit! I don't have any fingers!
Look who finally decided to show up.
Lost
Child
What's with him!?
Don Patch!
Bo-bobo! Bo-bobo!
Don Patch! Don Patch!
You piece of shit!
But I love you just the way you are!
Same with me!
What kind of soap opera is this?
It stinks...
I really want a bath...
Well in any case, it seems we're all here.
Alright! Let's dial the hajike up to eleven!
Yeah! Let's do it like we always do!
OK!
Go! Don Patch!
How was that?
He's smiling!
But why!?
This is bad, Big Brother!
They're all together!
What do we do? What do we do?
What do we do? What do we do? What do we do?
What do we do? What do we do? What do we do? What do we do?
Why are you acting nervous, too?
What do we do? What do we do? What do we do?
What do we do? What do we do? What do we do? What do we do?
What the hell's wrong with you?
I accidentally used the Secret Technique: Nervous Typhoon!
Secret Technique: Nervous Typhoon
What kind of dumb attack is that?
But this works for us.
Now they can't go rescue the girls!
Beauty Rescue Squad
There they go! In a hot air balloon, no less!
Now I'll just have to eliminate them all at once!
Little Brother!
Okay, Big Brother!
Poison Gum set!
Take this!
Brotherly Secret Technique:
Poison Bubble Flower
That's nothing!
It's my turn now!
Saury set!
Secret Technique: Fried Saury Hour
What? Ugh, that stinks!
Dammit, there's smoke in my eyes!
Are you trying to block my eyesight while you attack me?
But you can't reach me with the Poison Gum in the air...
Ow! Owowowowowow....
To think that the wind would lift me this high...
That was a lot of damage taken!
Now we'll have to use that technique!
Yeah!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Now we'll have to use that technique!
Yeah!
Big Brother!
Little Brother!
Brotherly Secret Technique:
Healing from Brotherly Love
I can't let you do that!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Tickle Attack!
That's real disgusting!
And now...
Dengaku Shot!!
Alright! Now just fall to the bottom!
You fool!
We know the positions of all the plates!
This is no problem for us!
What was that?
What's this house doing here?
And what are those weird handkerchiefs?
Who the hell built a house here!?
They're the yellow nu handkerchiefs of joy!
Was it you?
And on closer inspection, he's kidnapped our big brother!
Back Strike
Tennosuke!
I never expected less of Big Brother Haoh!
Now that he's here, we can use that secret technique!
Brotherly Secret Technique: Big Brother Cannon!
Our footing!
We destroyed their plate!
Now they'll just fall to the bottom and they're done for!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Legacy of Mu
You goddamn pink twirly-head!
Seriously, what the hell is your fucking problem?
No matter.
We've destroyed all the plates around them.
Now they can't move upwards.
The hell!?
Don Patch! You climbed up to save us!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm the heroine here!
Bo-bobo!
Oh... And there he goes...
Patchmi was so scared!
Patchmi! Patchmi!
Bo-bobo!
Don Patch Attack!
Everything has gone according to plan.
As always.
And now...
For Don Patch!
You sucker!
We have the ultimate defense!
Take this!
Brotherly Secret Technique:
Beautiful Appeal
Please, stop fighting.
How's that? Now you can't attack!
He just attacked anyway!
You bastard! How dare you harm Beep!
Dumbass!
We have an ultimate defense too!
Secret Technique: Cuteness Guard!
Nah-la!
You piss me off!
They're too strong!
Now we have no choice but to combine our power!
Here goes! Brotherly Secret Technique:
Brotherly Secret Technique
We'll leave it all to the laser beams!
That's got nothing to do with brothers!
And that's no secret technique, you're using weapons!
Don't we have any weapons of our own?
We have some scrub-brush sponges.
That's not a weapon!
Now that I think about it,
they say that scrub-brush sponges soaked in water become a weapon that can match a gun!
No one says that!
Sorry, but I only brought dry scrub-brush sponges.
Why!?
It's worth a shot.
It's not!
Start throwing!
Sponge
Those are some tough scrub-brush sponges!
I'm out of scrub-brush sponges!
I need to reload!
There aren't any more!
We still have a scrub-brush sponge!
Where? Where is it? You seen it?
Where's the scrub-brush sponge?
I don't see any scrub-brush sponges!
Well, where? Where is it?
Here it is!
Oh, you're right. It's a spitting image!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Scrub-brush Sponge Bomb
Sponge!
Oh, no!
How did he get so high?
Now that it's come to this...
We've got to transfer our power into Big Brother!
OK!
Brotherly Final Secret Technique:
What are they gonna do?
Power Transfer from Little Brothers
Now Big Brother Haoh is unstoppable!
Now become the cornerstone of my conviction.
Bring it on!
I'll defeat you and save Beauty and Suzu!
The Three Murder Brothers' power just keeps on escalating!
How will Bo-bobo and company fight them?
Good luck, Bo-bobo!
Don't lose, Bo-bobo!
We believe in you, Bo-bobo!
Probably!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your brothers or those close to you will save you from trouble!
Your lucky item is miso soup with lots of seaweed!
If you tied, shout "Love and Peace" three times to calm down those around you.
And if you lost, be careful not to step on gum at the top of a tower!
We're finally facing Halekulani.
No! I wanna play more of this roulette!
What are you talking about?
Let's start running towards that golden sunset!
Yes, teacher!
They've charged straight into Money Castle!
What is this place?
There's money waiting for us!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Down with
Halekulani!
But more importantly,
money!
Let's get some
♪
More importantly, let's fight...