Ahh! Beautiful Brotherly Love!!
Eldest Child
Middle Child
Youngest Child
Big Brother!
Little Brother!
Big Brother Bo-bobo!
We'll go you wherever you go, Big Brother!
How beautiful.
You think so?
Big Brother!
Little Brother!
Brotherly Final Secret Technique:
What are they gonna do?
Power Transfer from Little Brothers
Finally, the legendary Haoh has awoken his true powers.
Can Bo-bobo defeat Haoh,
and rescue Beauty and Suzu?
I need a bath...
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
AngelofChaotix
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Now become the cornerstone of my tenacity!
Bring it on!
I'll defeat you, and save Beauty and Suzu!
Bo-bobo...
Down with
Halekulani!
But more importantly,
money!
Let's get some
♪
Now our Big Brother is unstoppable!
What kind of moves will he bust out?
Looks like things are getting rough...
Let me demonstrate.
Big Brother! What are you trying to do?
Big Brother... you can't be serious...
Now that I have transformed...
This...
It's too risky! You can't hold tofu in one hand!
Don't do it, Big Brother!
...will be your fate.
Is your hand alright, Big Brother!
T-This is... made from purely domestic, organic,
genetic engineering-free ultimate soy beans...
The Ultimate Tofu!
Purely Domestic
Organic
Genetic Engineering-Free
He's invincible! He's the strongest!
Big Brother's the strongest!
You guys are all stupid.
Then allow me to show you...
Are you insane!? Two tubes of wasabi?
He's just bluffing! There's no way he could do it!
Let me show you what happens to those who lay their hands on Beauty...
Wasabi!
Non-burnable Garbage
It burns! My mouth burns!
That will be your fate!
And those who incur my wrath...
Spicy Mustard
You too?
Are you for real!?
This will be your fate!
Kids... don't... try this... at home...
Kids,
don't try this at home ❤
Kids... don't... try this... at home...
Fine, then...
Let's let our fists do the talking!
Sure thing! I'll show you the essence of the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Las Vegas!
Bo-bobo Roulette!
How's he gonna attack us?
What's gonna happen?
The Bo-bobo Roulette will judge everything by random chance!
Not even I can predict what fate will bring!
With that said, let's list the perps!
Don Patch
Beep
Tennosuke
Megafan
Haoh
Wait, what? We're on the board, too!
And I'm on there twice!
Roulette Start!
Who will have the honor to be judged first?
Don't land on me...
Don't land on me... Don't land on me...
Who will it be, who will it be, who will it be,
Who will it be, who will it be...
Uhh, this guy...
Huh? Me?
And he's got motion sickness!
Congratulations!
Now receive your judgment!
And this is the method of judgment!
What'll it be? What'll it be?
Meteors falling within 10 kilometers of Beep!
That's pretty drastic!
What the hell is up with this roulette!?
Show time!
So who'll it be the second time?
Who will it be, who will it be,
who will it be, who will it be...
This guy!
He has two arrows now!
And the method of judgment...
1000 Bees!
Run away!
We'll be stung!
My beautiful face!
Show time!
Dammit! Doesn't seem to be landing on Haoh...
I'll get him this time!
Roulette Start!
Who will it be, who will it be,
who will it be, who will it be, who will it be...
Don Patch
Who will it be, who will it be,
who will it be, who will it be, who will it be...
Stop right there, will ya!? What's up with the wheel?
Don't you think my space is way too big compared to the others?
You're making stuff up.
The answer is you!
Yes! It's no more than probability!
Finally! It's Haoh! And here's the judgment!
Bo-bobo Squished You Flat!
Big Brother!
Too weak.
He did it!
That's Big Brother for ya!
Big Brother!
Too weak!
What kind of pose is that?
Big Brother!
So who's gonna be next?
Who will it be?
This is one dangerous roulette we're playing here!
Who's next? Who is he choosing next?!
Uh, this guy, I guess.
He doesn't even care!
Oh, and his friends, too.
How can you even call that fair?
And the method of judgment is...
enter the Bo-ninjas!
Bo-ninjas? Who are they?
Clone Technique!
Flame Technique!
Poison Gas Technique!
Bo-ninja Beam!
That's not ninjutsu!
Nice work, guys!
More! Give 'em more!
Oh, look at the time.
Retreat!
Good work, guys!
Alright, let's jump back in there too.
What the...?
Now for the next perp...
Who will it be, who will it be,
who will it be, who will it be...
This bastard, you fucking morons!
He just snapped!
Why was he so angry?
And I just realized,
I've been almost attacked every time!
Like anyone cares, moron!
Take a good look up at the slot!
Your method of judgment is coming!
Don Patch is going down!!
Not even I know what will happen! That's the Bo-bobo Roulette!
Come to think of it...
What's the point of the roulette anyway?
And now for the last round!
Who will be that lucky last criminal?
Who will it be?
Don Patch
Haoh
Tennosuke
Small-fry
Haoh! It's you!
He used a ladder lottery!
And it's pretty obvious it would land on me!
And the final method of judgment...
Fancy-chan!
What the hell? I don't get what it's supposed to be!
I don't understand...
What is this...
Just what...
What will happen?
Big Brother!
The fight is settled.
Those who land on Fancy-chan will become fancy, no matter what kind of guy they are!
It's your loss!
I couldn't care less!
No matter what happens, you cannot crush my tenacity!
Very well! Then let's finish this once and for all!
Here goes, Haoh!
Big Brother!
That was nothing! That won't work on me!
I survived! And now that I'm back to normal, I win!
Why don't you take a closer look at the roulette?
The three
idiot brothers
The three idiot brothers.
I won't let you do it! I'll defeat you all and crush your roulette!
Sentimental Nose Hairs
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Graduation!
Now I need to check on Beauty and Suzu...
Bo-bobo!
We're both alright!
Softon managed to saved us!
I'm so glad you're safe.
Lord Halekulani!
And just what is the matter, exactly?
With all due respect, Bo-bobo and his friends...
have just destroyed the Climb High Tower...
As a result, Hallelujah Land's losses have just exceeded one billion!
So that means I have to squeeze a billion out of them.
Do Not Enter
Meanwhile, elsewhere...
Heppokomaru was looking around Hallelujah Land.
What is this place?
Hey, hey!
Work it!
You guys won't get off easy if you slack off!
What's this all about?
Some Hallelujah Land this is! This is Hell!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
It's finally time for the final battle.
Alright! I don't need any halfhearted punks from here on out!
I'll leave them all behind!
Hey, moron! I'm putting my whole heart into it!
Then show me your wholeheartedness!
Just what I wanted to hear!
Down with Halekulani!
Tennosuke 100T
Halikulini...
Hariyakulani...
Down with Halekulani!
Cut it out, guys!
What are you three doing, anyway?
I wouldn't worry.
This is how they psych each other up
to prepare for the final battle.
Oh, that's how it is!
Okay, let's... roll out.
But you're all practically dead!
Hey! Halekulani!
Come on out, will ya?
We'll kick your ass, bastard!
They're suddenly better...
Bring it on!
Hey, hey, hey!
Here it is.
The entrance...
Halekulani! Where are you hiding? Show yourself!
What's happening? There's money falling from the sky!
Where is he?
Welcome to Money Castle.
I waited far too long for you, pests.
Halekulani!
Bo-bobo!
The money in the air is infused with Halekulani's will!
You mustn't touch it!
What the hell are you two doing?
I just told you not to touch it!
Moneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoney...
Hey! Weren't you just shouting "Down with Halekulani" just a minute ago?
Halekulani! I'm gonna come up there and kick your rich ass!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo's
Share
Have at you!
He's only saying it!
Now I can die happy.
Why!?
Moneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoneymoney...
I said stop it already!
Drop the money! It's dangerous!
I worked for 35 years to make this money! I'm not letting you cheat me out of it!
What the...?
Get away!
Suzu!
Did she just...?
Suzu...
Halekulani! You goddamn bastard!
He can turn people into money? What a terrible technique!
At this rate, Beauty will be in danger, too!
We gotta blow the money away first!
How do we do that? Hey, tell me! How do we do that?
Bo-bobo Typhoon!
It's working! The money's blowing away!
They're getting hit on purpose!
You're too heavy!
Money's nothing more than paper!
If we feed them all to a goat, who loves eating paper, we'll be fine!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Summon Goat!
But that's obviously a giraffe!
Eat all the paper you like!
Don't mind if I do.
Is that how you eat it?
You see... when we were young...
We goats couldn't even afford to eat paper...
But you're a giraffe.
Now he's sending coins! Let's go, Don Patch!
Yeah!
Allow me to use this coin!
Grand Prize!
Coin Beauty
What the hell is this?
That's a lot of weird me's!
Beauty Flash!
The weird me actually does something important!
This money just keeps on coming, no matter how much we blow away!
We'll never reach him at this rate!
Bo-bobo!
Even if his money touches us, it still takes two or three seconds to wrap us up!
How about we make a mad dash straight to him, instead?
That's a good idea!
Alright! We'll go with that plan, Dengakuman!
OK!
Go!
So why did you do this to me?
Alright! At this speed, we can shake off the money before it wraps us up!
Now we can throw a punch into that damn face!
What!?
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique:
Limb Ex-Ten-sion!
Nice idea, Tennosuke!
But Bo-bobo... We can't go any further now!
Good point.
No way... There's money floating above them...
And there's a huge pool of money below them...
How are they supposed to get to Halekulani now?
We've made it out of every crisis so far.
Bo-bobo's sure to think of something!
Bo-bobo!
I can't see him anywhere! Could he have fallen?
What?
No...
Bo-bobo!
Yeah?
Softon! Over there!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique: Gondola Tour!
Gondola?
Did you have that all along?
Take this!
He did it!
Consider that my hello, snob.
That was quite good.
I never thought you'd clear the Money Trap.
Money Trap?
It was nothing.
It was not nothing!
The final battle has finally begun!
Will Bo-bobo defeat Halekulani,
and rescue Suzu who was turned into a coin?
Somebody help me!
Help me, too!
Thanks for the meal.
Huh? You were still eating? Help me out here!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll be lucky if you expand your field of activities!
Your lucky item is a gondola the color of Softon's twirl!
If you tied, be sure you check an encyclopedia so you don't get animals' names wrong.
And if you lost, be careful not to squeeze wasabi tubes too hard!
How do we deal with someone who uses money as a weapon?
This is looking bad! What do we do?
We have a gorgeous guy of our own, remember!
Who's that?
Anyone want some tokoroten?
Tennosuke for 10 yen!
That's cheap! We can't win with that!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Halekulani!
with
Gorgeous
Showdown
Behold
Illusion!!
the Super
His eyes got big!