Hello everyone, from inside a dice! Nah-na-la!
It's me again, Dengakuman!
This is a board game invented
by the strongest man of the Four Lords of Margarita, Halekulani...
Fist of Gorgeous
Dark Secret Technique
Death Money Board Game
Fist of Gorgeous Dark Secret Technique: Death Money Board Game, nah-na-la!
Let's try rolling the dice!
It stopped, na-la!
And it's now coming back!
Two.
Fun Time Board Game
Bo-bobo destroyed the Death Money Board Game with the Fun Time Board Game!
Put the board games away!
He got stuck!
But the persistent Halekulani transformed into a money monger.
Moneymoneymoneymoneymoney...
He's gotten scary!
Money is power! Money is everything!
Bo-bobo also fought for the sake of money.
Pretty sure he didn't!
I mean he's the hero and everything!
That's right! Our hero Bo-bobo...
was about to teach Halekulani what is more important than money!
Contract
I leave all my wealth to Bo-bobo.
Signed, Halekulani
I leave all my wealth to Bo-bobo...
Over my dead body!
Just forget this hero stuff, okay?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
VigorousJammer
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Halekulani! I'll show you what's greater than money!
There's no such thing.
What's greater than money...
Is this foot!
Git 'im, Bo-bobo! Git 'im real good!
That was basically how it went.
Hang on! This pro wrestling thing never happened the last time!
These guys are trying to screw up the recap! But why?
What do they have to gain from doing this?
Absolutely nothing.
Yay! Nothing at all!
Then don't do it at all!
Final Battle
with Halekulani
Finally
Concluded!
...But now there's a new
enemy
!?
Something greater than money?
There's nothing greater than money!
Exactly.
No, there is.
It is...
Eggplants!
OK, no. Not a chance.
What was that just now?
Did he think "eggplants" would be a good answer?
What's greater than money is...
Love and friendship or something like that...
He's gone really sloppy!
Even his art style!
That was such a moving speech!
It was?
He's such an actor...
How? Which part of it?
His words...
touched the enameled wires of our hearts!
They ascended!
Halekulani! Let me tell you then!
What's greater than money? It's Ordinary Everyday Life!
Ordinary Everyday Life
Ordinary everyday life?
That's total bullshit!
How is that greater than money?
You tragic money monger...
Allow me to demonstrate the greatness of ordinary everyday life!
Here we go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Superior Secret Technique:
Wonderful Nose Hair 7 Days!
Halekulani, you will now experience the wonder of everyday life
over a period of seven days!
First comes Monday!
Wonderful Nose Hair
A Peaceful Morning
Shut up!
That's way too many alarm clocks!
My mother gently wakes me up.
It's morning, dammit!
Our dog hears the ruckus and comes in.
And then all together...
Canned Crab Time!
What's happening? I'm scared!
This Monday is...
Perfect!
How?
And now the Merry-Go-Round...
explodes!
But why?
Next up, on Tuesday...
A Police Barricade
You are completely surrounded!
What did you do?
Followed by hibernation!
Hibernation
I'm a Gecko
I'm a gecko.
Our dog hears the ruckus and comes in.
There he is again!
And now for our traditional...
Canned Crab Time!
It's become a tradition!
Mackerel
Hey wait a minute, this is canned mackerel!
I'm so sorry! I wasn't looking!
What were you thinking?
Eat up, then.
It's a crab bowl.
But I'm sick of crab!
And now the roller coaster...
But what's the point of this?
Next up, next up, it's Wednesday...
His face is huge!
A Battle
He's gone back in time!
Onward, everyone!
We must reclaim those idol CDs I bought!
Yeah!
That's a lame reason to start a battle!
Buy a new one!
We must reclaim them!
He actually unified Japan!
Just a dream...
A dream ending? Wait, how come you're a wrestler?
This Wednesday is...
What the...? What are you gonna do?
Rolling-rolling-rolling!
He fell!
We gotta help Bo-bobo!
Quit it!
That ain't cool, bro!
That guy, yo, he wants to go!
Oh my God!
No thanks!
Yo!
You can't!
Yeah!
That guy's just gotta go!
Yo!
Rolling and falling is how he lives, so he gonna roll and fall...
Upside-down, yo!
Once he starts poppin', then he ain't stoppin' for
ANYBODAYY!
Let him go, let him go, let him go, bro!
Let him go, baby!
Yeah!
He looked like he was calling for help!
You didn't see anything! There's nothing for you to see!
What kind of secret technique is this!? This doesn't look good!
Let's move on to Thursday!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is what happens on Thursday!
O the Xth
It's a diary!
And it's reallly crazy, too!
Bo-bobo went to go shopping at a fish shop in outer space.
Bo-bobo: Hey, got any good fish?
Alien: Well, we do have some fresh Andromedafish in today.
You know, because we're in space. (Laughs)
Bo-bobo then destroyed a planet.
Bo-bobo: Give it over!
Alien: You can't be serious! Oh, wait... you're that guy from five years...
Nu Person: Nununununu.
Bo-bobo: Yep. I'm that guy from three years ago.
Nu Person: Nunununununu.
Nu Person: Nunununununununununununununu
nunununununununununununununununu
Who wrote this rubbish? Was it Tennosuke?
Bingo!
This Thursday is...
Three Peace!
That's oldschool!
You bastard!
How dare you destroy my Hallelujah Land!
Don't look at me!
Hey hey hey! Don't get sidetracked now! Let's move on to Friday!
Friday is...
Chocolate Pies
A box of chocolate pies with a squirrel inside ❤
It looks super cute! But I don't get it!
Isn't it adorable?
There, there.
Adorable enough for a quick kick to the neck!
What did he have to do with it?
And now it's Saturday!
Monster Wars
Monster Wars!
Wow, you guys really could pass as actual monsters!
There's a bunch of other monsters stampeding at us!
Sword of Light!
Fire of Light!
Ice Storm of Light!
Destroy the Monsters of Darkness!
You guys are on the side of light?
Today's Trivia
Monster No. 65
Mercedes
And here's today's trivia!
Today's Trivia
Monster No. 65
Mercedes
Monster No. 65, Mercedes.
A French monster that likes the shade.
He stabs people with toothpicks.
He was promoted to manager last April.
A French monster that likes the shade.
He stabs people with toothpicks.
He was promoted to manager last April.
A French monster that likes the shade.
He stabs people with toothpicks.
He was promoted to manager last April.
Nobody cares!
And last of all is Sunday!
On Sunday...
We're in Alice's Wonderland...
doing covert ops!
That's quite the mission!
Alright, everyone! Follow me!
Everyone from Monday to Saturday is following them!
Who's the guy at the front?
Halekulani...
How about it? Ordinary everyday life wasn't too bad, was it?
There wasn't a single ordinary day in this whole week!
What a load of crap!
In this world...
Money is everything!
You still don't understand?
How thick are you?
Everything that happens in everyday life...
is my power!
All these precious meetings and experiences that money can't buy...
bring forth the greatest power of all!
Before that power,
money is no more than slips of paper!
The most precious thing in the world? The strongest thing?
That should be obvious!
It's money!!
What? Which one is it?
Weren't you just talking about how the most precious things in the world
Are meetings... And experiences... And friends?
I wanted to teach him a lesson.
Now the hideous one has been destroyed.
You guys!
Suzu! You're back to normal!
However, the hideous ones...
had not been destroyed yet.
Hideous Ones
Money...
Hallelujah Land destroyed.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
May!
That's the last of them.
Thank you so much!
Now we're free from that evil Halekulani!
Not bad, kiddo.
You're Heppokomaru, aren't you?
How do they know my name?
No doubt about it. He's on our list.
What do you guys want?
You're a Fist User, aren't you?
So what if I am?
We came to bug Halekulani for some cash...
but I think we've got us a bigger catch!
Commence the Fist Hunt!
Let's start by kidnapping this brat.
Okay!
Meanwhile, now that Bo-bobo and his friends had defeated Halekulani...
they were drawing up plans for rebuilding Hallelujah Land.
Why are you guys doing it?
Well...
Tokoroten Land
we could always change it to "Tokoroten Land".
Nope, that plan will never work!
Okay...
Then let's plant a bunch of rubber gloves!
Why? I don't get the point of that!
Both of those ideas...
Tokoroten Land
have already been put into action.
It's too late!
The more I look at it, the better it seems!
It'll be a big hit!
Wait...!
30 minutes later
It flopped...
We haven't got a single customer...
I should think so.
More importantly, anyone know where Hekkun is?
I'm starting to worry...
Don't worry, Beauty.
There he is. Perfectly alive and well.
See how spunky he is?
Let me out! Let me out of here!
He's being kidnapped!
You call that spunky? Get up there and save him!
We can't do that. I mean he's in the sky and everything.
How about I just kill you?
Why do you have to be so scary today?
I'll save you now, Heppokomaru!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Spring!
I'm begging you! Please take this seriously!
And they're gone!
I don't believe it... Hekkun's been kidnapped!
I'm sorry.
We did everything we could, but...
You didn't do a damn thing!
Well, this is Heppokomaru we're talking about, so I'm sure he'll be fine.
I wouldn't be so sure.
From the looks of their uniforms,
they come from Cyber City.
It's the most atrocious city in the entire Margarita Empire.
I doubt he'll come back in one piece.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
So we have to save Hekkun before he reaches the city!
Cyber City is a giant city floating in the middle of the ocean.
We can't head them off.
No way...
You useless pink twirly-head!
So what's gonna happen to Hekkun?
Everyone must die sometime.
Get back here, you little...
I can at least teleport you to the docks.
Yes, please do.
Cyber City
Bo-bobo has even managed to take down Halekulani.
So I need you... Or rather, all of you to help me.
Lame!
Never imagined that Mr. Moneybags was so pathetic.
Giga, this is an order. Bo-bobo must be...
Quit ordering me around, Tsururiina.
Aren't we supposed to be equals?
Son of a...
Those were the conditions upon which I agreed to remain in the empire.
But more importantly...
I've been getting into this Fist Hunt.
I just can't stop making Objets d'Art out of my targets.
Emperor of Cyber Empire
Giga
Teleport!
We made it!
Alright! We're at the docks! Let's board a ship!
Board! Board!
That's just a car!
Set sail!
That joke went flat.
Now's not the time to mess around!
I have a ship! Let's set sail immediately!
Softon!
Now get on!
What's wrong?
Hop aboard!
I don't wanna! Nobody would ever want to ride on that!
Except him!!
Good grief.
What a picky little lady we have today.
Why don't you ride my nu ship instead?
Isn't there any more decent ship?
Let's go, Softon.
The shock!
I lost to that pink twirly ship!?
And so, Bo-bobo and company set sail on the pink twirly boat.
Take care!
This ship's narrower than it looks, isn't it?
Not really. It's just wide enough...
for having a field day!
We're not doing that in here!
On your marks...
Not you too, Softon!
The first contest!
The Dengaku-put!
The second contest! The Don Patch Dunk!
Red team wins.
But he didn't even do anything!
What was that crash?
Let's look outside!
Who are those guys?
You're entering Cyber City waters.
Cyber City Coast Guard
We have orders to destroy any trespassing vessel.
Those two look dangerous! Who are they?
This doesn't look good. They're the coast guard!
Who are you trespassers?
We are known as...
The Strawberry Au Lait Speed Drinking Club!
No we're not! What are you talking about?
Speed Drinking Club
Here's your T-shirt, Beauty.
I drink mine nice and slow!
Sink!
We're sinking!
We're sinking! We're sinking!
The pink twirl is sinking!
The pink twirl...! It's...!
The pink twirl is...! It's...!
It's... it's... it's...!
Oh, shut up!
Leave this to me!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Iceburn!!
So the other day...
I got mistaken for some Hollywood star at a party.
The ocean froze!
Sure, that joke was cold, but come on!
Alright! Now the ship won't sink!
Now let's cross the ice and kick their asses!
Okay!
It's freezing! It's freezing!
I'll save you!
I thought that was the life preserver!
Lies! All lies!
Those are some pretty stupid techniques.
They're hardly worth the effort, but whatever. It's a living.
Shut up!
We will bring back Heppokomaru!
And we'll crush anyone who gets in our way!
Eliminating trespassers at Sector 306 South.
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hondorapoy and Hogehogepo ♪
What are they doing?
I will not tolerate any foolishness!
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Our nemesis showed up now, of all times!
She really came!
She came from the sea, too!
But I don't like her...
Dengakuman may not like her,
but Torpedo Girl has made her re-appearance!
But why has Bo-bobo called for Torpedo Girl,
last of the Idiot Killers?
Does Bo-bobo have some kind of plan?
Ugh. Another blister.
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the rock-paper-
scissors fortune, nah-na-la!
If you won, sing a rap parody at a party and you'll be a big hit!
Your lucky food is anything with canned crab!
If you tied, make sure you plan out your week and follow it, and you'll be lucky.
And if you lost, if you buy Strawberry Au Lait, make sure you drink it slowly and savor it!
Torpedo Girl is here! What do we do?
Don't worry, Beauty. Calm down, balm down.
If we act foolish in front of the Teacher, she'll kill us!
Everyone do your parasol spinning practice seriously!
You guys are both too foolish!
Then Don Patch...
Yeah?
We'll just have to entrance her with our graceful dance!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Enter
the Six Cyber Knights!
You'll get charmed
by a male ballerina, too.
♥
I can't take this anymore...