Daddy...
Dengaku, nah-na-la!
I really owe you one, don't I?
But Daddy would rather have tokoroten than dengaku.
You promised you wouldn't be so picky, nah-na-la.
Hey Pops, we'll be takin' back that money we lent you!
P-Please have mercy...
Then we'll be takin' yer daughter instead!
Daddy!
Denko!
Why would I want her?
Well that was pointless!
Halekulani! I'll show you...
What's greater than money? It's Ordinary Everyday Life!
Ordinary Everyday Life
That's total bullshit!
How is that greater than money?
You tragic money monger...
Allow me to demonstrate the greatness of ordinary everyday life!
Here we go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Superior Secret Technique:
Wonderful Nose Hair 7 Days!
With this attack
that proved that a week in ordinary everyday life is greater than money...
What part of is this ordinary?
The last of the Four Lords of Margarita...
the terrifying miser Halekulani,
was finally defeated by our hero Bo-bobo!
If only I had taken that money... Just imagine what I could've done with it...
H-However...
Heppokomaru had saved those imprisoned in Hallelujah Land,
but he was kidnapped by a new foe!
In order to save Heppokomaru,
Bo-bobo and company set out to sea.
I lost to the pink twirly ship...
The pink twirly ship... The pink twirly ship...
OK, we hear you already!
Will they be able
to defeat the coast guard blocking their way and make it to Cyber City?
Hondorapoy and Hogehogepo ♪
I will not tolerate any foolishness!
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Our nemesis showed up now, of all times!
She really came!
She came from the sea, too!
But I don't like her...
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Oh, dear. Not another blister.
We have another weird thing on our hands.
Shouldn't be a problem.
Enter
the Six Cyber Knights!
You'll get charmed
by a male ballerina, too.
♥
So tell me, have you guys been fooling around again?
No! We're innocent!
It was them!
They were the ones fooling around!
They're actually scapegoating!
Also this guy.
So, care to explain this foolish boat?
Anti-Foolishness!!
That's theirs, too!
You guys are pretty desperate. I guess you must be really scared.
But that plan will never...
Then let's give them their punishment!
Yes, Teacher!
How gullible is that torpedo?
All trespassers will be eliminated!
I will not allow...
Any foolishness!!!
Torpedo! Look up! Look, they're being pretty foolish if you ask me!
What just happened...? They're strong...
You were far too foolish!
Say your prayers, punks!
You guys really do amaze me.
But what's our next move? Our boat broke mid-fight.
Torpedo!
I spy something dreamy!
She locked on him! Is she gonna attack him or something?
I shall carry you for love!
I can see the city, na-la.
That must be Cyber City.
Cyber City
Hekkun... We're coming for you.
Miss Torpedo, we'd like to infiltrate as quietly as possible so we don't get noticed.
Leave it all to me, torpedo.
Farewell, torpedo!
That goddamn torpedo...
This is bad. We're sticking out like a sore thumb!
There's still time left! Quick, hide yourselves!
Yeah.
You're way too late!
And now, today's Aerial Hair Hunt Stadium match
is finally reaching its climax!
Only one fool who tried to escape Cyber City remains!
Please spare me! I'll never run away again!
What is this? All the monitors are showing gruesome videos!
Origami Class
Today, we'll learn how to fold a crane!
I spoke too soon! One of them is showing some weird TV show!
I can't do it!
And you can't even do it?
We wanna see some anime!
That's a pathetic reason to throw a tantrum!
I'm back, people!
Man, making a real crane was the best I could do...
That's actually way more impressive!
More to the point, what's going on...?
It's a public Hair Hunt.
All those who try to run away, seeking freedom of hair...
are Hair Hunted up there to set an example.
We don't want to see those videos... but they're broadcast day after day all through the city!
Sucks to be you.
That's terrible...
We can't stand this life anymore!
And?
Bo-bobo, let's go take them out!
Sure. There's a chance Heppokomaru may even be up there.
But how do we get in there?
Secret Technique: Bo-bobo Spring!
They're doing that stupid move again!
And they're flying!?
So why couldn't you fly when you tried to save Hekkun!?
Aerial Hair Hunt Stadium
Spare me! Please, I beg of you!
Come now, don't be a wet blanket.
You'll disappoint those who bet on you.
Anyone will do, just please save me!
Sure, I said anyone, but I didn't expect these weirdos!
Heppokomaru!
We meet again!
Wrong guy! That's someone completely different!
Phoenix Twirl!
I take it you must be outsiders?
What's with him?
I am one of the Six Cyber Knights, Pana.
Six Cyber Knights
Pana
I can't have you interrupting my Hair Hunt Game.
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Where are Bo-bobo and the others?
Over there!
Bo-bobo!
I don't know what brings you here,
but I'll let you join in my Hair Hunt Game.
Take this! Phoenix Twirl!
Are you alright?
He's way too fast!
He's coming back around!
In that case...
They've started spinning!
And I don't have a clue what they're saying!
Spin Attack!
There they go!
White Tiger Twirl
He blocked Bo-bobo's attack! This guy's powerful!
I'll have you taste the true terror of the ultimate Hair Hunt Stadium!
He's coming this way, Bo-bobo!
They've gotten dizzy from all that spinning!
In that case...
Reverse Secret Technique:
Party Trick
Hey! Good job!
You're the star of the party!
What kind of attack is this?
But nobody invited me to the party!
Well, I didn't see that coming.
However...
Reverse Speed Electric Wheel
You can't hope to keep up with my Reverse Speed Electric Wheel!
Here
What the hell!?
Goal!
Where!?
What was that all about?
Because this race had such a close finish, we will determine the winner by stop-motion camera.
Stop-motion Camera
It's a completely different picture!
You've let your guard down! Go! Killing Rings!
Killing Rings
Friendship Guard!
The usual!
Now you've really done it! This one's for my friends!
Bo-bobo Wave!
Take my Secret Technique: Bo-bobo Wave!
He called it a secret technique but he's just using a gun!
Bo-bobo Wave!
I'll finish him off with my New Ultimate Attack!
Driving!
New Ultimate Attack:
Driving
Nonononononono...
Phoenix Twirl!
This next attack is my ultimate, unparalleled move!
What?
Take this! Mach 6...
360 Degree Cyclone!!
How do you like this indiscriminate attack from all directions?
Dammit! He's moving too fast for me to see!
There is no way to get out of this technique alive!
But I'm the only one actually getting hit each time!
I can break through this attack without a sweat!
What?
Let's go, you dumb dog!
Secret Technique: Blowfish!!!
Blowfish!!!
They're all getting hurt!
They're strong! Could they all be Fist Users?
Now to finish you off!
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique: Tokoroten Press!
Tokoroten Press!!
I found one! I knew there was a Fist User hiding among you!
No! I'm not! I was faking it the whole time!
Psychoball!
Psychoball
What's with that ball?
Tennosuke!
Those who touch the Psychoball
will have all the power drained out of them!
It's sucking me up!
That's a funny face.
Manga
No one cares about him!
I'm turning into a skeleton! It'll suck everything out and turn me into a skeleton!
But you don't have a skeleton!
That tokoroten Fist User must've been their strongest fighter.
All that's left is the small fry! This'll be easy!
Those two weirdos are spinning too!
Ballerina Attack!
Ballerina Men
Coming Soon
I really don't wanna see that.
Bastards!
My leg's cramping up!
He's coming back!
This move will cut anything it touches in a second...
Rising Dragon Twirl!
Just kidding.
His hand's huge!
Impossible! He's so strong! Who are these guys?
We are...
Building Code Violation
Prevention
Corps
The Building Code Violation Prevention Corps!
What the hell? Weren't you just the Strawberry Au Lait Speed Drinking Club?
Here.
Here's your t-shirt, Beauty.
She put it on!
You can't prevent that!
She ripped it!
She made a comeback at herself, nah-na-la!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Just kidding!
Amazing! They're overpowering Pana of the Six Cyber Knights!
They are our only ray of hope!
Amazing, squid! Amazing, squid!
Come to think of it, what about Tennosuke?
We're too late!
He's had too much power sucked out by the ball...
And he turned into a sausage!
A jelly sausage? How would that even taste?
My Psychoball is impossible to escape!
You can no longer save that tokoroten of yours!
I got your back, Tennosuke!
Leave it to me!
You're so cool, Bo-bobo!
Secret Technique:
The Legendary Hustler Shot!
What do you think you're doing?
Now I can take you along with me!
I'll bounce off the sides of the sphere until I hit you!
I couldn't bounce...
That takes care of that nuisance.
What a guy!
I'm not giving in...
Approval Rating
We're being bet on?
This Hair Hunt is essentially a game!
It's a life-or-death game where they bet on who will survive!
They're playing with our lives...
So how popular am I in this?
Approval Rating
I'm lower than Beauty!
Why is mine lower than hers?
Oww! Oww! Oww!
I'm strong! I'm so strong! Bet more on me, shitheads!
I'll use this opportunity to make another Psychoball.
Then I'll do it too.
Stupid Ball
I'll make a Stupid Ball!
That's a really stupid ball!
Those who are hit by the Stupid Ball...
will be at the top of their class on their test!
Isn't it supposed to make you stupid?
Purukogi... Purukogi...
But all your classmates are bears.
Purukogi
Purukogi...
I knew it! It makes you stupid!
Purukogi
Alright! Approval rating is up!
Now my approval rating's sure to go up now!
Hellbound
I've lost all my popularity!
Quit your stupidity!
Then take this!
360 Degree Cyclone!!
Dammit! Not this attack again!
Beauty!
Calm down...
Don't rely on your eyes...
Use his sound and his aura to pinpoint his location!
There he is!
Heroine
What the hell are you doing?
You can't possibly hope to break through this attack!
I have plenty of ways to break through it!
What?
Secret Technique:
Banana Field!!
He fell for a really cliched joke!
Incredible! He's just playing around with Pana of the Six Cyber Knights!
Just who is new combatant?
I can't say just what he is...
But when he has the choice to do or do not...
He does it.
Approval
Rating
Oh! The pink twirly-head's approval rating's shot up!
Just for that one line?
Approval Rating
Hellbound
Now this is getting good!
Enough of this foolishness!
You won't get away with this!
Well then, allow me to use your attack!
You can't do it if you don't have this wheel!
Yes, I can!
It's the Bo-bobo Car again!
And it powered up!
Here goes! Bo-bobo style 360 Degree Typhoon!!
360 Degree Typhoon!!
Impossible!
Fool! I can still use the Rising Dragon Twirl!
How's this? Now you can't touch me!
Music Recital!
Now it's time for the performance! Put all you got into it!
Yes, Teacher!
Flow of the Ganges river! Flow of the Ganges river!
I see that you've completely mastered Beethoven's "Destiny."
That grating noise was supposed to be Beethoven's Fifth!?
This can't be right!
Incredible! He's far too strong!
Amazing! He just might be able to win!
Way to go, Building Code Violation Prevention Corps!
Amazing, squid! Amazing, squid!
Now I've had enough of this stupid game.
Don't fuck with me! I'm one of the Six Cyber Knights! There's no way I could lose!
How about taking a good look at yourself?
What? What the hell is this? When did he...
Those are my nose hairs!
Your nose hairs!?
Since this battle began...
I've been laying out my nose hairs throughout the stadium as I fought!
Dammit! They're not coming off!
I will never forgive anyone like you...
who plays around with human life!
Now to finish you off!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Wait! If you harm me, Lord Giga will...
Nose Hair Spider Hold!!!
The flow of the Ganges... The flow of the Ganges...
He's still performing!
Impossible... He's... a Fist User...
Lord Giga...
The flow of the Ganges... The flow of the Ganges...
Please shut up!
That was a rough battle.
Who are you supposed to be?
Now you've gone and done it.
This fight has been broadcast throughout Cyber City!
The other Cyber Knights will come after you!
You can count on it...
Bo-bobo!
Perfect. Let's send out a message to Heppokomaru through the TV.
You're right!
Missing
Heppokomaru
Age 3 (not really)
Heppokomaru! I'll give you back your snacks if you come back!
That's not why he's gone!
Heppokomaru! Heppokomaru!
I'll give you your snacks! Your yummy snacks!
I'll give you your snacks! I won't be mad at you, I promise!
Come back, Heppokomaru!
I beg you, call him like a normal person!
Bo-bobo has defeated one of the Six Cyber Knights, Pana!
Can they defeat the other five
and save Heppokomaru?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won,
be a ballerina at a talent show and your approval rating will go up!
Your lucky item is a t-shirt that matches your friends'!
If you tied,
practice your origami cranes so you can make them nicely.
And if you lost,
don't act too foolishly or there'll be no snacks for you!
What kind of fearsome battle is next?
I'm ready for anything!
Strings on our legs? Could this be...
A bungee jump?
Hooray! Bungee sounds like fun!
No! Of all days to wear a skirt!
I don't think you're wearing one.
Sorry, Patchmi!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Invitation to
the Abyss!?
Aerial
Showdown!
Bungee Battle
Begins!!
The blood is rushing to my head...