Bungee Time!!
MC
And now for the last question of the Bungee Time Quiz!
This will be a buzzer question with a video!
Once you get the answer, press the buzzer in your hand!
However, please be careful!
If you press too soon or get it wrong,
you'll fall straight into the abyss!
Bungee Time!!
MC
Alright, let's get going!
Start the video!
In order to save their kidnapped friend...
Heppokomaru!
Heppokomaru, our heroes came to...
Cyber City!
And the next guy too!
Why me?
Cyber City.
It was there that they fought the first of the Six Cyber Knights, Pana.
Six Cyber Knights
Pana
White Tiger Twirl
While Bo-bobo and company had a hard time against him...
360 Degree Cyclone!!
they finally defeated Pana!
Nose Hair Spider Hold!!!
Lord Giga...
And now, here's the question!
MC
Question:
How do you read this upside-down?
"Bobo-bo Bo-bobobo"
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Correct! And Beauty wins!
Oh, yeah!
Bungee Time!!
MC
And now for your prize, Beauty...
I present to you this strawberry soft-serve ice cream!
Torpedo!
That prize is mine!
It's time for Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
That guy cracks me up!
I know, right!? He's so lame!
Impossible... My Fist of the Carrot's been defeated?
Well then...
I think it's time to make some creative art!
There we go.
It's a doll of me!
What the hell is going on?
Invitation
Invitation to
the Abyss!?
Aerial
Showdown!
Bungee Battle
Begins!!
Well, that was a flop. Five points.
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo and company
had just defeated one of the Six Cyber Knights, Pana...
in exchange for Tennosuke's life.
In exchange for
Tennosuke's life
No! Still alive over here!
So Heppokomaru isn't here...
Why, you little...
Don't get so cocky just because you beat Pana.
Those giant monitors just appeared in the sky!
And one of them's a completely ridiculous-looking monitor!
Who are you?
We are the Six Cyber Knights.
Six Cyber Knights
How convenient that you who disturbed our Hair Hunt turned out to be Fist Users.
Now we're going to hunt your Fists, felons!
This doesn't sound good, Bo-bobo!
Who's a good boy?
They're not even listening!
These monitors are connected to our Hair Hunt Stadiums.
Now choose your final resting place!
You're cruel!
I say bring it on!
Yakkun got a hole in one into the fly!
You bastards! Here we come!
Yeah!
But before all that, let's share some natto!
As a sign of our new friendship!
They're opening with natto!
We have you now!
Allow me to hunt you!
We're being drawn in!
Y-You guys!
Now, get over here!
I wanna read rom-coms!
That's a really ugly robot!
We made it.
They came out of its cheek!
That's one messed-up robot!
What kind of place is this? There's a cave below us!
We're being pulled down!
It's a bungee cord!
Welcome to the Bungee Hair Hunt Stadium!
Who's there?
I am one of the Six Cyber Knights, Sonic.
Six Cyber Knights
Sonic
His blood's all gone to his head! In fact, his face is all red!
The pain...
I can't... go on...
I wanna go home...
Preemptive Strike!
Energy Drink
Bottles
How dare you raise your hand against me!
You'll have to answer to my two lackeys now!
Your two lackeys?
Allow me to introduce you!
First up we have...
Super Rabbit!
Super Rabbit
He's not living up to his name!
And he even spelled "super" wrong!
And my second lackey is...
Despair Kid
Despair Kid!
I don't care if I fall.
What's wrong with you?
You can't fall! Have some more hope!
There's nothing good about him!
Whatever the case, these guys are dangerous in a totally different sense of the word!
Now listen... It's a three-on-four bungee battle!
And there's nothing but the abyss below us.
Once you fall, it's all over.
Let's do this then!
I'll give you a taste of my chain scythe!
He's falling with a really sad face!
Don Patch!
Catch!
You saved me, Bo-bobo!
And now I move right into...
What?
Secret Technique:
Idiot Bomb!!
That's all I need you for.
You son of a bitch!
Now you've done it! But I can use the cord's recoil...
He sprouted wings!
Take this! Killer Rocket Attack!
I missed!
You missed by a country mile!
That was close shave!
Alright! Let's kick his ass as he falls!
Back me up here, lackeys!
They're totally demotivated!
Dammit!
Now, Tennosuke!
OK!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Wrecking Ball Bullet!!!!
He did it!
Nice one!
Dammit...
Wing Cutter!
I'm gonna fall!
It's not cut through! I'm hanging on by a thread!
Now that was close.
But now there's a pair of naughty swallows pecking at it!
Tennie's in trouble again!
Please stop it, swallows! That string is not edible!
Stop it!
They bit down hard on it!
Oh no! I'm falling!
Of course! I must rely on the Nu for help!
Oh, Nu handkerchief... Become a magic carpet and save my life!
Become a magic carpet and save my life!
That's not gonna happen!
Nu handkerchief!
Tennosuke!
Well, that's one down!
How dare you kill our friend Tennosuke!
But I'll tell you what, you won't be able to cut our strings so easily!
What?
Because I just switched my rope...
With spaghetti with meat sauce!
This
What the...
Now it's down to just the two of you!
So, what's your next move?
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Now it's down to just the two of you!
You're no match for the three of us!
But one of you already fell!
Who cares if I fall...?
Die! Long-distance Wing Cutter!
Watch out!
I missed!
Now it's my turn!
Take this! Bo-bobo Cutter!
Bo-bobo Cutter? I threw that piece of junk out.
Okay...
Then you go instead!
Now you're messing with me!
I'll show you the true terror of the Six Cyber Knights!
Change!
Change complete!
Cyber Cross Jet Form!!!
His armor turned into a rocket!
Alright! I'll transform, too!
You can do that?
Transformation complete!
He transformed into a nugget!
Look out!
Cyber Jet 100mph Slicing Fist!!!
Bo-bobo!
That shock sent Bo-bobo flying towards Super Rabbit!
Boing-boing Signature Technique:
Bungee Karate!!!
Super Rabbit's showing off some amazing moves!
Oh! Superb, Super Rabbit!
Bo-bobo!
Help Me Mask
Yes?
He's undamaged!
He's even reading manga!
But you can't move in that position!
It's time to taste the terror of the Bungee Hair Hunt Stadium!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Take this!
Bagworm Defense!!
What?!
Followed by...
Bagworm Laser!!
Laser?
How strange.
Where could they have gotten to?
Amazing! They're overwhelming Sonic!
They're incredible!
Well, I can't see them around here.
You rotten bastard!
Bo-bobo! What about Don Patch?
I suppose it's time to call them back.
Wait, you can do that?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Snacktime!
Okay, everybody gather around!
Snacktime
Yeah, no way! This won't bring them back!
Snacks!
They're back! And they're swimming upwards!?
Even that weird guy is joining their snacktime!
Snacks!
Um... Didn't you fall down just a minute ago?
I just...
I just want snacks! Is that too much to ask?
What are you guys doing?
Snacks!
Come on! Fight me like men!
OK, snack time's over!
Man, I'm full!
Huh? But I want more!
He fell again! Was it that much of a shock?
That aside, these cookies look pretty expensive!
I'd say about 20,000 yen each!
I guess I did splurge a bit...
But I had just enough money...
in Tennosuke's wallet.
My life savings!
He's falling like an autumn leaf!
Sonic! Our pointless battle ends now!
I'll show you the essence of the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Just what I wanted to hear!
Here goes!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
You get a red card!!
Red Card? And what's with those annoying motions?
Introducing the Bo-bobo Mystery Box!
A weird box just appeared out of thin air!
What's that box for?
Not even I know what will happen to those who enter the Mystery Box.
You'll just have to find out for yourselves!
That's a pretty reckless secret technique!
Winner
Also, that's not even a red card!
Tennosuke fell inside!
There was boiling-hot ramen inside!
That ramen was so hot, he's on fire!
Damn. He came back.
I get it!
Now that the box is there,
at least we can't fall to the abyss!
We won't lose Despair Kid now!
He managed to avoid it!
What do you think you're doing?
If there aren't any cookies, I may as well fall.
Are cookies all you're living for?
Cookies? Hang on, I think there are a few left...
Cookies!
He's coming back! On a surfboard, too!
Oh wait... those aren't cookies...
Just dengaku!
Eat dengaku, nah-la!
No thanks.
What was that, nah-la?
He fell in the box this time! What's gonna happen?
Dreams do come true! Life is beautiful!
Life is beautiful!
He's overflowing with hope!
That's one dangerous box!
Anything really can happen!
That's even more reason not to fall...
It's a wonderful life!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
What kind of box is this?
Anything really can happen!
This is dangerous! We can't afford any risks!
This is even more reason not to fall...
But then again, the same goes for them! This battle is going to be good!
Is it just me, or are there are angels floating around us all of a sudden?
Secret Technique:
Angel Flight
What's going on? What are you trying to do?
First we trick you with a pretty face, then...
What's going on?
It's a hornet's nest!
But our innocent smiles make you forgive us!
It's just a playful prank by us naughty angels!
That's way more than just naughty!
I'm falling!
And the box is below me! What's going to happen now?
Now it's time for you to taste my bungee karate!
Survival of the Fittest!!
This is a grim reminder of the harshness of Mother Nature!
Damn those punks!
Bring it on, assholes!!!
He's more bullish than he's acting!
I have you now! Rocket Attack!
Try and come up here if you can!
Alright, how's this?
What?
Here we go!
Jump out!
Wow, that's annoying! And where's that splash coming from?
Here they come!
Now fall into the box!
Secret Technique:
Synchronized Frenzy
Why, you...
This one's for those two guys!
Dammit!
They both fell in the box!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
He's turned into a ridiculous shape!
Spike Roller of Hell!!!
He's already mastered a new move!
Super Rabbit!
Oh, yeah! Tennosuke also fell in with Don Patch! What happened to him?
There he is!
Ne
He's fighting some kind of weird battle!
That's scary! That box is seriously scary!
But I still have my lackeys!
Go, Super Rabbit!
He's gone back to tame right when he needed him most!
I don't have any decent lackeys!
You finally noticed? A little slow on the uptake there!
Shut up!
Beauty!
Beauty...
He's...
You're...
Don't throw your life away!
Speak for yourself!
It's the Spike Roller of Hell again!
Are you alright, Beauty?
I dunno, are you?
How dare you harm Beauty!
Now tastee my special bungee attack!
What? Your special bungee attack?
Here goes!
Here he comes!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Push 'Em Out Bungee!!
That's got nothing to do with bungee!
In fact, it's probably the furthest you can get!
Can't let you do that!
Bo-bobo! Let's use that technique!
Secret Technique:
20-Ton Press of Hell!!
This kind of brutality would put the devil to shame!
Tennosuke!
They're all yours!
This is one strong Ne!
Tennosuke!
I've got my hands full over here!
I can at least take him down with me...
You leave me no choice!
Nu!
Amubosatsu meiekiteikai
kuushokuzeshoku shikijinhoren!
What the hell? Tennosuke's playing a bigger part than ever before!
Onkutenmitsu harakaisha...
He sealed them away!
We did it!
Now the Six Cyber Knights are down to four.
Bang!
They're so strong! They've even defeated Sonic!
I don't believe it! They defeated two of the invincible Six Cyber Knights!
Way to go!
Meanwhile, elsewhere...
Hey you! Keep walking!
Damn you...
Seriously?
Yeah, totally!
Here we are.
Where are we?
Who are you?
Heppokomaru has been brought before Giga!
What's going to happen to him?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, stand on your head and you'll come up with great ideas!
Your lucky snack is a fresh-baked chocolate chip cookie!
If you tied, if you want to make peace with someone, tell them how you feel now!
And if you lost, at least remember how to spell "super" right!
Where are we? The Driving School of Hell?
It's filled with lots of cursed cars!
Bo-bobo's nose hairs have been cursed and they've disappeared!
What should I do? Now I can't get married!
Right, right.
More importantly, somehow we've been surrounded by demons!
Don't worry, Beauty.
I'm sure our teacher will come to our aid.
Teacher?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
A Hero
of Justice from the Darkness !?
Torpedo Teacher Torpe-be!!
Enter
Is she coming back?