In order to save Heppokomaru, who had been kidnapped,
Bo-bobo and company broke into Cyber City.
That goddamn torpedo...
We told her to make a quiet entrance...
Everyone here has been Hair Hunted!
At the Aerial Hair Hunt Stadium,
Bo-bobo and company defeated one of the Six Cyber Knights, Pana, after a harsh battle.
Nose Hair Spider Hold!!!
But just then, they were dragged
into one of the five giant monitors that appeared in the sky!
I wish I could've gone inside that weird-shaped monitor!
Me too!
But why?
Their next foe, Sonic of the Six Cyber Knights...
challenged in the Bungee Hair Hunt Stadium.
Bungee
Hair Hunt Stadium
Who said anything about chimpanzees?
I turned into one, too?
Bo-bobo and company fought against Sonic's lackeys,
Despair Kid and Super Rabbit, in a battle that would just not abate.
Who said anything about chestnuts?
I'm picking them up, too?
Guys! I said "just not", not "chestnuts"!
Thanks to Tennosuke playing a surprisingly major role,
Sonic was defeated,
and Bo-bobo's team won the bungee battle!
The blood is rushing to your heads!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
VigorousJammer
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
of Justice from the Darkness !?
A Hero
Torpedo Teacher Torpe-be!!
Enter
It's the Chimes of Death!
Chimes of Death?
That means Giga's monitor is about to show up!
Monitor?
Where? Where's the monitor gonna appear?
It appeared in the weirdest of all places!
Heppokomaru's shown up in the weirdest of all places!
What do you want with me, you son of a bitch?
Oh, nothing. Just doing a little Fist Hunt.
Fist Hunt?
It's just a simple process of capturing every single Fist User out there, like yourself.
What?
And he's quite the artist,
so he turns them into sculptures and collects them.
Collects them?
What am I looking at?
You goddamn asshole!
What the hell is your goal?
You wanna take a guess?
Fist of Objets!
My body... feels like clay...
What a beautiful work of art!
Heppokomaru!
No!
Damn you to hell!
Hey, wait, what are you- Stop! Stop! Stop!
How dare you turn Heppokomaru into a sculpture!
You guys!
That voice...
Marriage, marriage!
Are you alright?
Are you!?
We're here, torpedo!
Bo-bobo...
You saw that video, didn't you?
That man was Giga, emperor of Cyber City!
He's equal in power to Tsuru Tsururiina IV!
What? Equal in power to Tsuru Tsururiina IV?
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Who is this?
It's on now!
I'm gonna kick Giga's ass!
Now come out here! Come out and face me like a man!
He came out!
See? The "I Came Out" Old Guy actually came out!
It's another freaky thing!
And today's story is...
You guys are too foolish!
Bo-bobo! Softon!
Welcome.
He got the jump on me.
Torpedo! What's with that bizarre monitor?
It's too foolish!
Tennosuke!
That is obviously a challenge to us.
Let's go punish him.
But I don't wanna.
I'm not feeling it, either...
What's going on?
Then we're agreed! We're breaking in!
Oh, dear. What's going to happen now?
We're finally here!
Huh? Since when did we become "Donna Donna"?
You idiot, this is Chona Chona.
Chona Chona?
We go from place to place and Chona Chona.
What does that mean? I don't get any of this!
Okay, guys! Let's go Chona it up!
Chona!
But what does it mean? Is it some kind of code?
Hey! Beauty, you say it too!
No thanks, I'm good.
Come on, just once! Say "Let's Chona it up", just for the heck of it!
Well, okay... Let's Chona it up!
Huh? What're you talkin' about? Are ya retarded or somethin'?
I don't understand you! Nobody here understands you!
Bo-bobo... please help me...
Jokes aside, where are we? It's full of books!
Welcome to the Written Hell Hair Hunt Stadium.
Written Hell Hair Hunt Stadium
Who's there?
Chair
I am the Secretary-General of the Six Cyber Knights, The Poet.
And it looks like you've got the short end of the stick, seeing as how you're here.
Wind
Secretary-General of the Six Cyber Knights
The Poet
At long last, I have a chance to exhibit my Fist of Gothic...
He's a Fist User?
Is that moving word part of his power?
I know! How about you start by telling me your names?
Sure! We'll tell you!
My name is Dragon Knight Galzack!
Dragon Knight Galzack
And my name is Sacred Swordsman Gaiya!
Sacred Swordsman Gaiya
What the hell?
I'll be borrowing those names for a moment.
Fist of Gothic!
Dragon Knight Galzack
Sacred Swordsman Gaiya
What!?
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique:
Projection of Names
My Fist of Gothic can draw on the power dwelling within words.
So, how does it feel to be attacked by your own names?
And I was just about to say
Toothless Warrior Herohyoron...
I knew I should've gone with Busty Warrior Boobalina...
You guys actually thought that?
Flame! Lightning! Blizzard!
Let's see if you can approach me now.
That pathetic attack can't work on us!
Exactly!
Because we...
Because you...?
We can't read Chinese!
Too bad for you!
That doesn't make a bit of difference!
You guys!
Well-Done
No way!
Now then... Time for the coup de grace.
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Now then... Time for the coup de grace.
That's quite enough, torpedo!
Miss!
Miss Torpedo!
And who are you?
I am the one who has come from the depths of Hell...
to destroy the evil spirits!
Hell Torpedo Teacher Torpe-be!
Hell Torpedo Teacher
Torpe-be
Torpe-be? That doesn't roll off the tongue at all!
Evil spirits, begone! Hand of the Kappa!
Don Patch!
Evil
Curse you, Torpe-be! I'll get you next time!
What kind of character are you supposed to be?
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique:
Six Word Ropes
Rope
I will protect my students, even if it costs my life!
Miss Torpedo!
On closer inspection, she isn't protecting anyone!
Miss Torpedo! Don't die on us!
Why did you do something so reckless?
Wait, why is the torpedo half-dead? You didn't even get hit!
Because you students mean just as much to me...
as those black beans in my lunch boxes that I always leave uneaten!
You don't eat them?
Let me tell you one last thing before I die...
Miss Torpedo!
Peace to my boring Torpedoing My Way, morons!
You're not gonna die, are you?
That brat's really gone and done it now!
Let's bring the fight to him! Follow me!
Yes!
Here we go!
You're dragging them!
Idiot Bombs!
To think she would damage me not once, but twice...
Who exactly are they?
What if we told you we're the Pretty Secret Agent Girls?
Pretty Secret Agent Girls
I don't think so! Besides, that's a really weird name!
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique:
Cage
Prison Enclosure
Now you're mine. That cage has a hardness of 200.
Once you're inside, you can never get out.
Nice try, but there's no cage that can hold me.
What?
And that is because... I'm a torpedo!
But torpedoes and cages have nothing to do with each other!
And we, too, are...
Torpedoes!
Since when?
Now, can you win against us four torpedoes?
Is she including me in the group?
Then again, I feel like we can trust the torpedo for once!
Meanwhile, back with Bo-bobo and Softon...
I've managed to drag Bo-bobo in. Now time to pound him to the ground!
Here he is!
They came in with figurine poses!
And that one's coming out like one of those erasers
that you could win in the stationary store lottery!
I've no time to mess with you! Lead me straight to Giga!
He... He's stepping on me!
I assure you that you will never reach Giga.
And that's because you will die here...
at the hands of the most car out of the Six Cyber Knights...
Six Cyber Knights
Carman
Carman, at your service!
Alright. Then I'll just have to beat it out of you.
Now pray, before you wander to the end of oblivion.
This is getting entertaining.
Hey, what do you think you're doing, driving me?
Alright, let's take this baby for a spin to Hakone.
Not happening! Get out!
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique:
Unparalleled Shield!
Shield
Where a torpedo goes, chaos follows!
Alright! Now it's our turn to strike back! Take this!
Sweet sigh...
And now we act needy!
Won't you buy me a brand name handbag?
I want a Jueline!
Now that's what I call a pleading attack!
Get off!
Lightning
That torpedo's a tough customer!
I'd better use a super secret
technique to disrupt her vision!
Fist of Gothic Super Secret Technique:
Illusion
Illusory Word Vision!
Everything's turned into words!
Poet
This secret technique completely dominates your vision.
Now everything besides yourselves looks like words.
What's going on? Everything turned into words!
Beauty Vision
What about the others?
Yo, Beauty!
Ten★nosuke
What's with that old-school idol-like word?
It's me.
Tennosuke, right? What's with the stupid-looking star?
No touching the star!
Will you guys keep it down, torpedo?
Miyabi Girl
Torpedo Girl turned into Miyabi Girl!
Allow me to explain. "Miyabi" is a word that means refined or elegant.
Over here, Beauty!
That sounds like Don Patch!
Ball
Nose
Mouth
Eye
Spike
Hand
Foot
Pointy Hat
Are you alright?
What is this creepy thing?
And on closer look...
Pointy Hat
One of those spikes is actually a pointy hat!
Torpedo Vision
So what is this about?
Have you forgotten? I can create words at will.
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique:
Homonym Mirror!
Poet
Beauty
Tennosuke
Don Patch
Now you have no way of telling which one is the real one!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Now you have no way of telling which one is the real one!
Is this your attempt at blinding me? Too easy.
What?
Fist of Bloody Murder:
Torpedo Lock!
She's making a lot of weird markings!
Fist of Bloody Murder Secret Technique:
Falling Torpedoes 2005!
Impossible... She only attacked me and the words I made?
My Torpedo Radar
can precisely lock on to any targets identified as hostile.
Bang!
Miss Torpedo's really powerful!
Huh?
I guess I must be a hostile, too...
But thank goodness! Now our eyes are back to...
Wait, what? He looks a little weird!
Alright, everyone! Now get him!
Okay, teacher!
But I really don't want to fight, either!
What character is he doing now?
Lightning
Stay back!
He got beaten so quickly!
Flora... I loved you...
Time for round two!
What is this annoying thing?
Damn it all!
I refuse to lose to this torpedo!
Well, sorry for being a torpedo.
Secret Technique: Raging Dragon, Triumphant Storm!!!
Lightning
Flame
Blizzard
However, The Poet's attack had absolutely no effect on the torpedo.
And that is only natural, because she was...
She was...?
She was Napoleon!
Huh? Now you've really lost me!
Bravo, Napoleon! Viva Napoleon!
So you're the one writing this weird stuff?
Alright! Let's do that attack, just like Napoleon!
Revolution!
Secret Technique: Napoleon's Neapolitan!!!
Taste the revolution!
Ketchup is the revolution!
What kind of attack is this? It's just a play on words!
Those words aren't even related at all!
Enouf meffin arounff!
Don't you dare rip off my catchphrase!
What? That was a ripoff?
Alright! Let's fold it once and for all!
Yes, Teacher!
Fold! Fold!
Wait, fold laundry?
The torpedo's bugging me to do the laundry...
And now he's singing some weird song!
Ready, and...
Enough of this foolishness!
Those three are made for each other!
You are no match for us!
And that is because...
We are torpedoes!
This torpedo is too strong!
I have no choice but to use my Greatest Secret Technique!
Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique: Memory Destruction Array!
Memory Destruction
Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique
Memory Destruction Array
Memory Destruction
Hold on. What am I doing here?
Snacks!
What happened to you?
The Memory Destruction Array destroys peoples' memories.
Their memories have already been wiped!
They don't even know why they're here anymore.
No way...
I'm not selling...
Now, there's no one left to protect you.
Kill
Time to die!
What?
I don't have those things called "memory" thingies! I'm an idiot, I am!
Don Patch!
Well, this is no matter. He's no more than small fry, after all!
What're you, dense?
Beauty, tell this egghead who the main character of this show is!
Bo-bobo!
Meanwhile, back with Bo-bobo...
You damn stupid brat! Get out!
Get outta my head already!
Alright, he's on my side  now.
Wh-Wh-What did he say?
Bo-bobo, you're already finished!
Help!
Because this is the most brutal of the six Hair Hunter Stadiums...
The Driving School of Hell!
We're going to suck your blood dry!
What's going on?
At this driving school, you'll be assaulted by the spirits of cars possessed by speed...
Then the road signs of death will rob you of your free movement...
and toy around with your life!
And finally, the evil spirits that possess the driving school...
will drag you down to Hell!
Stupid fools! Why are you trying to drag me down?
Let's get this over with!
Fist of Babylon: Passion of Jamaica!
My face... You're rearranging my face...
Look what you've done to me...
You've ruined my beautiful form!
Wait... No, you haven't....
You've made me a super car!
I'm so happy! I'm off to the dealership!
That's what you get for jumping like that, nah-na-la.
He made a mess on the seats!
Now I'll never sell!
Goddammit...
Go, Vengeful Cars!
With just his bare hands
This man has stopped both the cars!!
The cars have both stopped!!!
Crap! I was so shocked that I accidentally wrote a haiku!
No matter! Go, Road Signs of Death!
He cut right through them!!
This freaking twirly-head guy
He cut right through them!!!
There's more where that came from!
Go, evil spirits!
Could this be a dream?
All the evil spirits are
Flying through the air!!!
Damn it all! It's time for an all-out assault!
Now time to mail in those haikus I just wrote.
Have you had enough?
H-How are they so strong?
It's not possible! They're so strong that I my haikus just might win the prize!
With the morning sun,
Rays of light shine brightly on
The water's surface.
And you get off already!
Yes, Bo-bobo and Softon are too strong!
But is this really all that Carman has to offer?
Bo-bobo and Softon's composure
is starting to worry me now.
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, expand your knowledge at the library and your luck will rise!
Your superior top-secret item is a homemade present!
If you tied, folding the laundry might turn out to be a good change of pace.
And if you lost, be careful you don't dirty your clothes when you eat Neapolitan spaghetti!
Huh? It looks like we've warped somewhere.
Looks like it's finally time to take on the final member of the Six Cyber Knights!
I'll bet he's really strong, if he's the last one!
Hey, what's with the glum face, Bo-bobo?
I can't tell if he is an onion or garlic!
Wow! I really can't tell!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
A Fierce Battle of
Sink
or Swim!!
There's an onion guy too.
guy too.
♪
An onion guy?