I got one!
Torpedo Girl!
Don Patch Girl!
Tennosuke Girl!
And that is because...
We're torpedoes!
A new trio is born!?
Cyber City
Fierce battles are underway at two Hair Hunt Stadiums
between Bo-bobo and the Six Cyber Knights.
Lucky him! I want one of those wheels on my head too!
White Tiger Twirl
Nose Hair Spider Hold!!!
They're all hanging like I always do!
Amubosatsu meiekiteikai
kuushokuzeshoku shikijinhouren!
Go! Vengeful cars!
With just his bare hands
This man has stopped both the cars!!
The cars have both stopped!!!
Crap! I was so shocked that I accidentally wrote a haiku!
Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique: Memory Destruction Array!
Memory Destruction
Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique
Memory Destruction Array
Snacks!
What's going on?
The Memory Destructor Array destroys peoples' memories.
Their memories have already been wiped.
No way...
Now, there's no one left to protect you.
Kill
He made a bunch of really complicated characters!
What?
I don't have those things called "memory" thingies! I'm an idiot, I am!
Don Patch!
Thank goodness, he's an idiot!
Thank goodness, nah-la!
Now, Don Patch! It's finally time to reveal your true power!
What're you, dense?
Beauty, tell this egghead who the main character of this show is!
Is it me?
Bo-bobo!
Figures...
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Oh, yeah! What happened to Tennosuke?
Tennosuke?
He turned into some kind of rodent!
W-W-What's wrong? Why are you eating sunflower seeds?
You're a tokoroten, not a hamster!
He's ticking me off.
What about Miss Torpedo?
What's she doing?
They're doing some kind of weird battle!
A Fierce Battle of
Sink
or Swim!!
There's an onion guy too.
guy too.
♪
Memory
Destruction
Looks like your Secret Technique didn't affect me at all!
Then I'll just turn you into words.
What?
WO
RD
What the...
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique: Textualization!
Now, time to turn into words!
Don Patch!
Pork Patch
Pork Patch?
Pork Patch's Tales of Pork Cutlets
Tales of Pork Cutlets
Pork Patch's
Episode 1: The Downtown Pork Cutlet Shop
What the hell? He's doing something goofy!
Pork, pork, Pork Patch!
Pork Patch
Pork, pork, pork cutlet Pork Patch!
Alrighty! I'm off to get some of that pork from those pesky pigs!
We're open!
Pork Patch
Jump, oink!
B-But I can't...
They're the ones in charge!
Pork Patch's
Tales of Pork Cutlets
FIN
What the...? He reverted on his own accord!
Screw you!
Could all the damage that I took from that torpedo
be preventing me from turning him completely into words?
You were protecting me...
Miss Torpedo!
My precious students...
Who on earth is that?
But that reminds me, what happened to Miss Torpedo?
Big Brother? Are you my Big Brother?
Friends from outer space...
What are they even doing?
Whatever. I can still beat the living daylights out of you, even if I can't turn you into words.
Take this!
Secret Technique
Raging Dragon, Triumphant Storm !!!
Blizzard
Flame
Lightning
Blizzard
Flame
Lightning
Nice try, but I've already figured out a workaround!
What?
Get off me!
You just drank my Extract.
But I haven't changed at all!
Come forth, Lightning!
Take this!
Secret Technique
Thunderstrike Strike !!!
Inspector
Kappa
Pure-heart
He made some kooky words!
I will protect Akemi no matter what!
What the hell did I do? I never created those words!
Enough foolishness!
Relax. The Extract of Don Patch isn't gonna kill you.
All it'll do is make your thoughts like mine.
Like mine...
That's one fearsome technique...
At this moment, Beauty felt more afraid than she'd ever been in her life.
My thoughts will become like yours? Don't give me that. I'm still normal.
Take this!
Secret Technique
Super Raging Triumphant Storm !!!
Pollock
Roe
Stupid
Prince
Madonna
That's obviously not normal!
No!
They all went and attacked Tennosuke!
Dammit! But I can still defeat you in a fistfight!
However, The Poet's attack did not work.
And that is no surprise, and that is because...
He was Ashikaga Takauji.
First Napoleon and now this?
My hand's going out of control!
I knew it was you! You still have your memories!
Fine, then! Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique:
Fist of Gothic Greatest Secret Technique
Super Giant Word Dragon !!
Are those giant words?
His thoughts can't possibly have affected my Greatest Secret Technique!
It's sink or swim! I bet it all on this technique!
Heart-throbbing Delinquent High School
It sunk...
Heart-throbbing
Heart-throbbing Delinquent High School!
Delinquent
High School
Are they doing another one?
Heart-Throbbing
So who gets this question?
Heart
Throbbing
Yes! It's "Heart-Throbbing!"
Teacher! Please teach us the "Heart-Throbbing" equation!
Pay attention! Come on, how come you've got nothing but "Heart-Throbbing" in your heads!
You're disrupting my class!
All "Heart-Throbbing" students stand out in the hall!
Heart-Throbbing
To Be Continued
You're the best students ever...
They're all out in the hall! What's with this high school? It's creeping me out!
Heart-throbbing
Delinquent
High School
Next time
There's gonna be a "next time"?
A transfer student has come to Heart-Throbbing High School! Her name is Sally!
The whole school will be swept up in a storm of love!
Teach!
Dammit! We'll take revenge for Teach!
The narration doesn't match up with the video!
Dammit! How dare he make me stand in the hall!
You were standing in the hall?
I never expected this! Was this spiky brat really that strong?
Memory Destruction
Oh, no! Now that he's blocked my Fist of Gothic, the Memory Destruction Array is weakening!
I'm remembering something...
Her memory's returning!
Alright! Time for a Torpedo Chant!
Torpedo!
She melted! But why?
Are you feeling better, Miss Torpedo?
Oh, it's you guys. Has the enemy been defeated?
Yes! Her memory's back!
I'm remembering something...
Tennosuke too!
OK, let's do it again!
Wake the fuck up already!
Chanting Squad
He's real harsh on Tennosuke!
You goddamn brat!
How dare you play around with my memory!
You'll pay for this!
I'll blast you to pieces!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
I'll blast you to pieces!
Torpedo vs The Poet Concluded!!!
She got me!
Chanting Squad
Tokoroten
Riot of Rage!!!
Why me? Why? Why me? Why?
What just happened?
No way... How could I lose to these guys?
The Poet is defeated!!!
Memory
Destruction
Good job, boys.
Thank you, Teacher!
This team works out better than I imagined.
Come to think of it, are Bo-bobo and the others alright?
Driving School of Hell
Meanwhile, back to Bo-bobo...
I took too many of their attacks.
They've rearranged my face...
Never mind that, they turned me into a plane!
Time to finish you off.
Okay, fine! Let's settle this with a haiku battle instead!
We refuse.
OK, how about this? If you win, I'll tell you where Giga is!
Does that sound better?
If that's the case, then I guess so.
We accept.
Fools! I'll take you down while you're distracted!
I'm done.
So am I.
That was fast! Let me see, let me see!
I'm gonna kill you!
Kill you kill you kill you kill
I'm gonna kill you!!!
O Great Babylon!
Bring your holy judgment on
This accursed fool!!
Spit it out!!!
Where is he?!!
Accursed fool.
Accursed fool, Accursed fool!!!
You morons!
A haiku has to have 5, 7, and 7 syllables, and a seasonal word!
You mean like... The gleaming silver
The gleaming silver
New fresh leaves are breathing out
A scene of winter
There! Now you got it!
Like I can do that!!!
But you just did!
So you're the Bo-bobo that Tsururiina told me about.
Are you Giga?
Gigigigigi
Gigigigi Summer Gi
Is that Lord Giga?
Seasonal
Word
Lord Giga! Why are you watching us?
Just killing some time.
I have no more time for crazy games!
I can't embarrass myself in front of Lord Giga!
It's time to end this!
Giga! I swear I'm gonna kill you!
Oh, it's on.
Sir Poet and Sir Carman have been defeated!
Strengthen the guard!
Hey, talk to me, what's going on here?
Pana
Poet
Sonic
Carman
Even The Poet and Carman have been defeated.
Looks like everything's gone to shit while I was away.
Six Cyber Knights
Wang Longya
Let us out!
If it weren't for these cages...
I'll break this damn cage!
Let me out!
Quit your shitty tweeting!
No matter how hard you struggle,
you can't escape from my Fist of the Prison.
What the...?
Man, that was a good nap.
Did I really fall asleep in this crappy position?
Well, whatever.
You bastard!
How did you escape my prison?
And who the hell are you?
Meanwhile, back at the Driving School of Hell...
What're you getting so strung-up about?
You're no more than time killers to me.
You'll pay for what you've done
You'll pay for...
Huh? Since when have you been wearing that hat?
What you've done!!
A scrub brush
Here's your consolation prize.
...what you've done!!!
What was the point of the hat, nah-na-la?
You dare treat us like time killers? Who do you take us for?
Giga... What a screwed-up man.
Oh, it's on.
It's time we showed him just what we can do.
Huh? They're gone!
What's going on? Have we warped or something?
Looks like we've been taken straight to the next foe.
I sense an evil presence.
Are you the one who called us here?
Mama
Okay, little man! It's time for your milk!
Drink it all up!
Huh? Don't be picky now. You have to drink it.
What do you think you're doing?
Bo-bobo!
Oh my, torpedo!
Oh, it's you guys! What are you doing here?
We finally meet again! Thank goodness!
I have brought you all here with my Fist of the Black Sun.
Who goes there?
I am the last general of the Six Cyber Knights,
and the Emissary of the Black Sun.
Is that man...
What?
Is he an onion or is he garlic?
That's just what I wanted to know!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
This is most unexpected.
It would appear that I am the last of the Six Cyber Knights.
This onion-head is surprisingly gentlemanly.
But I thought we've only defeated four...
Forget about that, where are we?
This is the core of Cyber City.
The core?
All the energy in Cyber City
is generated by my Fist of the Black Sun.
Cyber City Core
I am incapable of departing from this core.
Thus, I had to invite you here.
Impossible! He can generate enough power for a city all by himself!?
But then... if what this onion-head says is true...
Alright. I'll take you on.
Wait.
Let me do it.
You must save your strength for when you face Giga.
Unkichi...
Do you mind if I face you?
No problem whatsoever.
You appear to be quite skilled. May I ask for your name?
Six Cyber Knights
J.
Wait... your name is J?
That does not suit you!
Good name.
He complimented him!
Then may I ask you a question in return?
What, exactly, is it that you preach with your fists?
Love.
Love
Love...?
Is that true? Does Softon preach love with his fists?
Sure he does. He's done so all along.
But why?
Because of love, you put your ego and desire to rest,
and restore your mind to its pristine state. How deep.
What are you talking about?
And those to whom Softon's preached love with his fists...
They travel the world on the Softon Wagon...
In search of love!
What the hell are you doing?
Where is the love!?
Softon
And there they go!
Very well.
Then receive the purification of the flame!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Electra of Sorrow!!
Full Speed Into Summer!
Why the hell are you trying to surf?
This guy's super strong!
Yeah! If we hadn't turned into summer old dudes, we'd be dead by now!
Was that actually serious?
But now we've seen through your attack!
Yeah!
I'm afraid not.
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Eternal Blue!!
That's nothing!
Double Summer Old Dude Punch!!!
J Guard!!
D-Did you say J guard?
This is bad! He's ridiculously strong!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Factoria of Youth!!
Are you two alright?
Deathly
Faces
Those are some deathly faces, alright...
Boss Pink Twirly-head... Ya gotta get us satisfaction!
We don't wanna be the losers!
You guys are scary!
But you should be grateful.
We put ourselves on the line for your sake!
Yeah, that's right! Whaddya think of that? Touching, isn't it?
Outta my way.
At this moment, Don Patch felt like the time when everyone went to a raffle...
First Prize: Hawaii
and everyone else won a trip to Hawaii...
and all he got was a tissue.
What kind of analogy is that? It's too hard to understand!
And Tennosuke felt like the time he bought a new game,
but his friend beat it before him.
Clear
That's not any better!
My Fist of the Black Sun is a modern mystery.
It is a burning-hot cornerstone that can never be solved.
What's this onion-head talking about?
Come on, you ungrateful pink twirly-head!
Yeah! Go on and slice and dice and smash and mash him!
What are you guys even talking about?
Biding your time will do you no good.
Now have at you!
Then don't mind if I do.
There it is!
Babylon
Our idol, the God of Babylon!
Idol?
Jugement of Babylon!
May God have mercy...
On your soul.
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Sin-colored Catharsis
Softon!
What happened? He defeated Softon in one blow!
He's strong! This onion-head is real strong!
Wait, is it an onion? Or garlic? Onion? Garlic? Well, whatever!
What will become of Bo-bobo?
Softon!
Pink Twirly-head!
Darling!
You guys!
Were you left behind?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won,
write a haiku in nature and it'll be a masterpiece!
Your lucky food is fresh-fried pork cutlet!
If you tied,
make sure you can tell the difference between onion and garlic.
And if you lost,
double check to make sure you locked your doors or your bike!
He beat Softon in just one blow?
This onion-head is strong! Okay, Don Patch...
Let's go for the Bo-bobo Fusion!
Okay, Bo-bobo! Transform! Candy Ball!
Is Bobopatch gonna show up again? Or maybe Bobopatchnosuke?
Here we...
Oh no. Fusion failed.
Who's that?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Magical Girl
Denbo-chan
Arrives!
The spell of love is
Gabapabitch!?
Wait, Magical Girl?