Quiz
Bo-bobo
And now, for our winner Tokoro Tennosuke...
Here's your chance to get the grand prize, a free trip!
Gardening Set
Trip to Hawaii
Scrub Brush
Me
Tofu
Too bad. You get a scrub brush...
Trip to Hawaii
Scrub Brush
Tofu
Me
Scrub Brush
It's "me!"
It's me! Me!
No, I'm the heroine!
It's me! It's me!
No, it's me!
The final member of the Six Cyber Knights... was a leek.
No, he wasn't!
Is he an onion or garlic...?
That's more like it.
I am the emissary of the Black Sun...
J!
Eeeny-meeny-miney...
mo!
Let's just say he's an onion!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Sin-colored Catharsis
J's attacks were so dreadful...
that even Softon has fallen!
Darling!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
Ninjacloud
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
I-It can't be possible...
This isn't happening...
Mr. Ant!
I just got stepped on.
It's the ant you care about?
Don't die on me, Softon!
I don't want to be widowed so soon after our wedding!
Don't just leave me and our cute children!
Shut up! You never got married!
And are these supposed to be your children?
Okay, okay. I'll see myself out.
He defeated Softon in one blow...
This guy called J...
is strong!
He is the pinnacle of infinity!!!
Why did you have to put that pompous tagline on the screen, you onion-head?
Magical Girl
Denbo-chan
Arrives!
The spell of love is
Gabapabitch!?
Softon's not looking so good...
You have to rub herbs on his wound!
That sounds like Granny's old wives' tales!
Bag of Patience
Nope, it's Obana's bag of patience.
What the hell!?
Obana's...
That's no medicinal herb!
Bag of Patience!
What the hell are you playing at?
Are you alright, Softon?
Don't worry about me.
OK, don't say another word. I'll treat your wounds.
Alright. I've managed to save his life.
You buried him? You just buried him, didn't you?
So who might be next?
You'd better know your role, onion-head.
I'm gonna mince you into a thousand pieces and throw you into a pot with radishes!
Cooking Mom
Careful! If you don't boil the radishes ten minutes ahead of time,
it'll become a real mess!
I'd love to see you try.
Cooking Mom
Try? Don't even joke about it! Cooking with a low flame is impossible for an amateur!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Half Calories!!!
Night Bewilderment Fortissimo!!!
I can't watch anymore!!
The weirdo's joining in too!
Bo-bobo!
Me too!
Figures.
This can't be right! I thought I had predicted his attack...
I guess this J really is... powerful!
Is it transience that makes the heat haze so beautiful?
He's made another weird tagline!
This is strange. I'm sure I dodged his attack just now!
And my nose hairs definitely hit him!
Why? There must be a trick to it!
Think...
I figured it out!
I know the secret of the Fist of the Black Sun!
Listen, Bo-bobo! That guy there is no more than an illusion created by refraction!
A what?
We were trapped in his secret technique from the moment we arrived!
You are the first to have caught on to the truth of the Black Sun...
The truth of the Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique: The Five Slumbering Suns!
Five black suns just appeared in the sky!
Huh? What's that?
Figure 1
Don't let him fool you!
He uses the refraction from those five suns
to make illusions!
Doesn't stick to your teeth
I get it! Kind of like this, right?
Wrong and wrong.
Figure 2
Bo-bobo! What we need is a strong light!
Strong Light
We need a light brighter than the black sun to get rid of the illusions!
I'm afraid you can't do that. There is no light brighter than the Black Sun!
No, there is one!
What?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Super Flash!!
That's just an ordinary desk lamp!
They disappeared! The Black Sun must be pretty pathetic!
Now we've finally found the real one!
Here goes! Super Secret Technique:
March of the 300 Schoolgirls!
What kind of attack is this?
Stay on your toes! Let's transform to Bobopatch while we stil can!
OK!
Transform!
CANDY BALL!
Bo-bobo Fusion!
I can't let you do that!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
No Screentime
Black Flame Teleportation!
Dengakuman!
Fusion failed!
Dengakuman's headed straight for Bo-bobo!
Nice one! He shifted his weight to avoid him!
'Scuse me!
He entered in his butt!
Venice!
He fused with Dengakuman! What's gonna happen?
Could this mean... the birth of a new great warrior?
Fusion complete!
They became a girl!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Denbo
I'm Denbo.
D-Denbo?
I can only remain in this form for five hours.
That's a lot longer than usual!
But are you really Bo-bobo?
You're hurting me...
This is getting worse and worse...
Hey, you! You got any neat signature techniques?
I'm talking skills! You gotta have some decent skills, right?
I can sing!
She's going down...
Hold your horses! It may be a special kind of song!
Like maybe she's so tone-deaf, she can destroy the enemy's ears!
Good point.
Alright, go ahead and sing for us.
Okay.
In this endless world...
What have we here? I guess she's just a good singer.
You and I...
We're screwed...
Oh, crap! J's coming!
He came to hear me sing!
Thank you!
No, you dumb broad!
Don't forget she's still Bo-bobo! We have to protect her!
It'll be alright! That onion-head looks like a gentleman, so he shouldn't attack a woman!
Exactly. No matter what I do to others, I would never lay a finger on a lady!
Thank goodness he's so stupid!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Humiliation of Vanessa!
I guess Denbo doesn't count as a lady!
That hurt! Why is this happening to me?
Denbo...
That voice...
Don't cry anymore, Denbo...
It's my papa in heaven!
What's with this backstory?
I will give you a charm passed down through the Ijutarl line.
Thank you, Papa!
This charm will always protect you.
Nunchucks? Your charm is a pair of nunchucks?
Now fight! If you're really my heir, then you'll get up and fight!
His personality changed!
No... I'm not your heir... I can't use those!
Quit your whining, you pig!
I can't use nunchucks!
Your tears are in vain! Let's end this!
Here he comes!
Denbo-chan!
She's suddenly mastered them!
Hachoo~!
She said "Hachoo~"!
She actually yelled "Hachoo~"!
You guys... Are you okay?
This is a work of fiction.
I jagpumeun fiksheon imnida!
Teungjanginmur mij tanchemeongeun
Any similarity to real persons, living or dead, places, and events
shirjeoa amureon noangega apsseumnida!
is coincidental and not intended by the author.
And now she's started speaking in Korean!
What's going on? Did the nunchucks change her personality?
I suppose I could compare you to a beautiful rose that blossoms with the dawn.
What are you going on about?
Now let me show you my Superior Secret Technique!
This is starting to seem like some kind of kung-fu movie...
It's Chinese!
That can't be right. I must've misjudged it.
I'd better take a closer look...
A
I didn't misjudge it! She's doing some impressive stuntwork!
Haiyaa! Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
What's this all about? Is this the outtakes? This should've been an outtake from the get-go!
It would appear your fusion has failed you.
Failed? Hardly. It was a great success!
Allow me to show you...
Fist of the Nose Hair Superior Top-Secret Technique:
One Song Museum ❤
Where are we?
This is the world of song and sensation.
My song is in control of everything in this world.
To put an end to this meaningless battle,
and to bring peace to everyone's hearts... I will sing!
Go for it, Denbo-chan!
Magical ★ Girl
Denbo-chan
Music and Lyrics by
Takeda Shingen
What's with this song?
What was that about peace?
And why are the music and lyrics by Takeda Shingen?
Who's that running through the sunlight in the glade?
There she goes...
It's him!
Ka
re
What? You?
My body moved against my will!
My heart beats out for him...
What kind of song is this?
Everything she sings actually happens!
This is amazing! Her song really does control everything!
Magical Girl Denbo is always...
...ready to go!
Gen
ki
na
no
That's a little too ready!
But sometimes there are nights when I feel sad...
An ant's nest?
At times like that...
Wait, isn't this your theme song? You can't be doing this!
I get through them with a great big smile!
Denbo, Denbo, Denbo-chan...
Den
bo
chan
What just happened?
I'm not the biggest fan of carrots...
I've figured you out! I only have to take away your mike to stop your secret technique!
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Syndrome of Destiny!
Oh, no! If the song stops, we'll be forced back to our world!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Somebody has to sing in my place!
All you have to do is trust your feelings...
and just sing whatever phrase comes naturally to mind!
OK! I got this one!
Here we go!
Tokyo Tokoroten Communication!
Tokyo Tokoroten Communication
That's the first phrase that comes to mind?
Tokyo Tokoroten Communication!
And the National Diet...
Kokkai gijidou wo Kokkai gijidou wo
What'll you do with it?
Drown it in tokoroten!
Tokoroten de umetsukuse
What the hell are you talking about?
He's taking damage, even from such a pointless song!
Tokoro 10 Tokoro10 10
Tokoro10 Tokoro10 10
What's that?
Rave Meter
I'm the rave meter!
It talked! The fact that it exists is annoying enough!
Eat Tokoroten!!!
Tokoroten kue
Do you know the secret
Tokoroten no oishisa no
Himitsu wo shitteru kai
To why tokoroten tastes so good?
Shut up!
Bitou dakara sa
It's because it's low-sugar...
Low-sugar!
Bitou desu
Bitou bitou bitou desu
Low- Low- Low-sugar!
He's seriously annoying.
Don Patch! It's your turn to sing!
Why do you have to put me on the spot?
I...
I can't sing!
Diva
Liar!
I can't do it! I can't think of anything to sing!
I have no talent!
You can do it!
Don't give up!
Just sing already.
The onion head's coming!
Anything will do! Just sing it!
I can't... This one word just won't leave my head!
That's it! Sing it as loud as you can!
Be...
Beta-Carotine!!!
Carotine! Carotine!
Carotine Carotine
Carotine sesshu
Carotine intake!
Carotine! Carotine!
Carotine Carotine
Carotine intake!
Carotine sesshu
The most important nutrition your body needs is...
Mottomo karada ni hitsuyou na eiyou sore wa
The Venice International Film Festival?
Venezia kokusai?
Venice International Film Festival!
Full Marathon! Full Marathon!
Full Marathon Full Marathon
Okay, now I don't even know what he's doing anymore!
Hey, look! Don Patch's song made the rave meter...
Seaweed
go into seaweed mode!
Rave! Rave!
That's annoying!
And once the meter hits max...
Screw this!
What's gonna happen now?
What happened to the scenery?
We've gone into Fever Time!
Fever Time is the time for everyone to express their heartfelt feelings!
From now on, we'll all sing together!
My very own secret magic...
It's a very special spell of love.
I'll tell it to you, and you alone.
I chant this before I go to sleep...
Gabapabitch!!!
That's harsh!
And without further ado, I took that spell...
Down to City Hall...
shite
To make it his name!
Gabapabitch
That's awful!
But someone with that name...
Is 100% unacceptable!
Gabapabitch
I won't waste another second on bringing him down.
chan
That's right, Denbo-chan!
It's time, it's time for my signature...
Eggplants fried in spicy miso!
Na
su
no
Eggplants fried in spicy miso!
Is this even an attack?
Is that onion-head gonna be alright?
Eggplants are yummy!
Oh! My Seaweed!
What kind of power is this?
They're in a different league!
Yes ano ko wa
Yes, that girl
lives next door to me.
Tonari ni sunde iru
Yes, she's always close to me.
Yes itsumo bokura no chikaku ni iru yo
She's a little naughty, and her name is...
Chotto ochame na ano ko no namae wa
Kinoshita Daihachi
Age 49
Yonjuu kyuu sai
Who is that!?
He looks totally different from the back!
Daihachi gets mad when you lie to him...
Daihachi wa uso wo tsuku to okoru
Piece of crap!
He gets mad when his favorite team loses...
Gohiiki team ga maketemo okoru
That was rigged!
And that same Daihachi...
Sonna Daihachi wa
For a brighter Japan
Kinoshita Daihachi
is running for prime minister!
Jiki Shushou Kouhou nano
No way!
But let's forget about him for now, cause Denbo-chan...
Nice! She's brought it back on track!
Has something on her mind.
And it's about Daihachi again!
Sore wa Daihachi ga
Will the US President like him or not?
Daitouryou ni ki ni irareru ka doukatte koto
You want a fight?
It's on, bitch!
Oh, dearie me, they're fighting! Oh, dearie me!
Ara yada tairitsu Ara yada
What's gonna happen to the rest of this song?
Kono uta no tsuzuki dou nacchau no
Please tell us, please tell us, Softon!
Oshiete Oshiete Softon san
Yo-Y-Y-Yo-Y-Yo
Yo, don't put me-put me-put-
Put me on the spo-
On the spot, bro!
He's DJ-ing?
You've left yourselves vulnerable.
Now slumber for all eternity!
Tricked you!
What?
Denbo-chan...
will draw on the powers of love and friendship...
to unleash her super signature move!
Chou
And its name is... And its name is...
Holy Radical Ceremony!
Saint
She used her nose hairs!
I saved it just for you!
How beautiful... is the world of song...
And so, J fainted from Denbo's musical attack.
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to hear us sing!
That was a pretty nice concert! I should come again!
The fools!
Seems like they're just asking to be turned into sculptures.
The next foe awaiting them is their strongest enemy yet, Giga!
Will Bo-bobo and the others make it out of this tower alive?
What's with this picture?
Something's out of place!
See you next time!
Gabapabitch!!!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, those things your grandma told you will come in handy!
You'll be more healthy if you watch kung-fu movies!
If you tied, keep your toenails short so you don't rip a hole in your socks.
And if you lost, if you hog the mike at karaoke, your friends won't like you!
He's predicting all of Bo-bobo's attacks!
Just how high is Giga's IQ?
Don't worry, Beauty! We're pretty confident in our own IQ!
1+1=2! 1+2=3! 1+3=4!
2x2=4! 2x3=6! 2x4=8!
In your face, Giga!
You can't keep up with our high-level mathematics!
They're not high-level! You're totally useless!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Super
Unintelligible?
IQ Battle
Begins!
Giga,
Bring it On!!
We might actually be in trouble this time...