Giga Station
We're here live at Cyber City!
Wouldn't it be funny if I opened with that?
So where are you going to show us first?
Do you really want to see it?
I wanna see! Of course I wanna see!
Okay, go right ahead.
So... what am I looking at?
This is Lord Giga's collection.
See, this one is the master of the Fist of the Carrot.
And this one...
Huh? What was he again? I forget.
Oh well!
More importantly...
Can you ladies show me your room? Or not?
Oh, you're getting mad? My bad, my bad.
But you know, you're really cute when you're mad! Know what I mean?
We'll have you turned into a sculpture!
Hell yes!
No! Please! Stop!
The Story So Far
Okay, let's move straight on to the recap!
Bo-bobo and company came to Cyber City
Nose Hair Spider Hold!!!
in order to save their kidnapped friend Heppokomaru,
Tokoroten
Riot of Rage!!!
where they crushed the Six Cyber Knights one after another.
And their next opponent was the self-proclaimed Last General of the Six Cyber Knights,
His name was J.
I guess we never found out if he was an onion or garlic.
I don't think he was a garlic head.
Jugement of Babylon!
Softon challenged J...
Fist of the Black Sun Secret Technique:
Sin-colored Catharsis
but was defeated in one blow!
Bo-bobo attempted a Bo-bobo Fusion with Don Patch...
No Screentime
but ended up fusing with Dengakuman instead.
I'm Denbo.
One Song Museum ❤
And its name is... And its name is...
Saint
Holy Radical Ceremony!
She used her nose hairs!
I saved it just for you!
Den
bo!
Everyone!
Thank you so much for coming to hear us sing!
Encore!
We present you the idol trio... The Nose Hair Girls!
How mean! Am I out of the group?
What are you doing? You'd better turn around before I get mad.
But I'm...
It's time to start, meow!
I'm the heroine!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
VigorousJammer
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Black Sun vanished!
It must be because we defeated J.
Does this mean the city's gonna fall apart?
Oh no...
Don't let that distract you!
We gotta think about what we should do next!
Which way now?
Just over there.
What made you think that?
We'll all die if this keeps up!
Please wake up, you onion-head!
Die, beautifully and ephemerally...
Well, whatever... Wake up! Please!
Beauty!
What is it, Bo-bobo?
Did you eat my eclair?
I don't know what you're talking about!
That doesn't matter right now!
My eclair!
I'll buy you another one.
There is only one way to keep this place from falling apart.
You must make a replacement for the Black Sun!
A replacement for something that can power a city?
That's impossible!
Impossible! Impossible! Impossible!
It's impossible.
Don't worry.
Because...
That's way too illegible! Just use your words!
I will create a holy power in the name of the God of Babylon!
Babylon!
And of course, it has a shape that takes away its impact!
How about here?
Left.
The destruction is stopping! Amazing!
How much power is this man hiding?
Hooray! We're saved!
And we beat the game at the same time!
Finally the endgame!
Were you still doing that?
Our sweat and blood!
Super
Unintelligible?
IQ Battle
Begins!
Giga,
Bring it On!!
The shock...
What happened? A coffin fell from the sky!
That is a sculpture created by Lord Giga.
Lord Giga is inviting you to him!
What?
He resides at the top of this tower.
Now, get in that coffin!
It will take you straight to him!
Combine!
Tokoden!
Shut up!
You're on!
Let's do this!
It's so cramped in here!
Let's move, Softon!
Me can't. Me make energy here.
Just you guys go. This best plan.
Wait, why is he only talking in one-syllable words now?
Don't worry about me! Just go!
Softon! We'll leave this to you!
It's finally time for the final battle!
Taking us to him in a coffin? Who does he take us for?
Giga...
Giga!
That never happened!
I love you...
Giga...
Did you have to sneak that thought in there?
We're gonna... We're gonna smash his face in!
OK!
Wait for me!
The fools! They're pretty much begging to be turned into sculptures!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
There it is! That's the top floor!
Alright! We gotta start off on the right foot!
So let's bust him up right from the get-go!
The hell!?
Here's your welcome party, scumbags.
Look out, Beauty!
Softon...
And here comes the direct hit.
Huh? Where's Tennosuke?
Most impressive, Lord Giga! Now they're finished!
What do you think you're doing?
And you too! Who do you think you're supposed to be?
Rub rub rub...
So, who are you?
Well you see... I'm a door-to-door salesman...
And I'd like to present to you our new line of swimsuits...
Here, Missy, would you like to try it on?
Look! It fits!
Just kidding!
Very funny.
Get lost.
Don Patch, are you alright?
I'm fine! I'm perfectly fine!
Of course I'm not, you bastard!
He's put on his mean face!
It's on now, you son of a bitch!
I'll show you what happens when you take me for a fool!
Cyber City Arc
Fin
No! I didn't mean to do that! I swear!
You gotta believe me! I'm actually just an ordinary karaoke staff...
That was just a sculpture, you idiot.
Since when did he replace himself with a sculpture?
Damn it all! How are we supposed to smash his face in?
Softon...
Alright! This calls for...
Plan Seduction!
I can't do it!
I can't ad lib like that!
Didn't we practice it together?
Yes, but...
Then it's not ad lib.
If you're a sculpture...
then so am I!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo
Now you can't tell which of us is the real one!
What the hell? It's completely obvious!
Bo-bobo!
What? That one was a sculpture, too?
Huh? Then where's the real one?
Where could the real Bo-bobo be?
Where is he? Where is he? Where could he be?
Right here!
Ther'es a murder in my stomach!
That's... another sculpture!
No way! What's his deal?
Where is he?
Where's he hiding?
I'm right here!
He's outside!? And he's in a mascot costume!?
Saurus Kick!
Saurus Kick!!
Lord Giga!
Even a dinosaur's foot is too good for you!
Alright! He smashed his face in!
That's Bo-bobo for you!
You're gonna pay for that!
Bo-bobo...
Lord Giga...
Lawd Geega...
Are you still doing that?
What the hell are you doing?
Now turn Heppokomaru back to normal!
Heppokomaru, you say?
Which one was he again?
Are those all people he turned into sculptures?
I'm scared...
How terrible...
Isn't it a nice collection?
It's a distastefull collection, that's what it is!
That can't hope to compare...
Wasabi
With my Wasabi doll collection!
He brought out something weird! That's just as distasteful!
And my... Bug collection!
Bugs
The bugs are revolting!
Which one is Hekkun?
Giga!
I'll take you down and get Heppokomaru back!
If you want your little friend back, you'd better bring it!
I'll play with you!
You'll play with us?
Huh? What happened to your rage?
Clay Hand!!!
What the...? A bunch of hands came out of the ground!
We're being pulled under!
Bo-bobo!
Oh, come on, is that really all you got?
Fresh Vegetable Attack!!!
And now it's off to the supermarket!
Yen
Nu
You're not getting away!
Homing Sculptures!!
That's nothing!
Secret Technique:
School Curtain Guard!!!
Incredible! I never knew school curtains had that kind of power!
Now it's my turn!
Homing Blackboard Erasers!!!
There's more where that came from!
Vice-Principal Chop for people who waste school supplies!!!
Wha...?
Get lost.
Bo-bobo!
I'll let you have a taste of my greatest sculpture!
Your sculptures...
aren't even a match for this clay sculpture I'm about to make!
How amusing.
Well, why don't you show it to me?
If you have time to make it!
Tofu!!!
Lord Giga!
This masterpiece has gotten me through more art projects than I can count.
You got through them!? With that!?
Giga! I can never forgive you!
Let's start the countdown to hell!
Yeah.
But your faces are still lumpy! Are you guys alright?
Don't get ahead of yourselves, morons!
If Lord Giga gets serious, you'll all be dead in seconds!
Me? Get serious? No need for that.
You'll all writhe in pain on my sculptures!
No!
Bo-bobo!
What do you think you're doing?
And now we charge straight at Giga!
Huh? Your vehicles changed!
Future Police
Bobobo Team
Episode 1:
Emergency Dispatch OK?
And now they're doing something really weird!
Scramble! Scramble! Enemy in sight!
Dispatch immediately!
Roger, OK?
We've got a big fish to fry! Let's keep it cool, OK?
Attack!
Roger, OK?
They're using primitive weapons!
Outta my way!
Very well. I'll show you the power gap between us!
Imperial Intuition
What is this?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
What is this?
That's the calculation grid that activates Giga's ultimate IQ!
It's a godly power that can decipher anything!
This is the intuition of an emperor, only accessible to a true genius!
Tokoro Tennosuke
Don Patch
What's the matter?
Too scared to move?
Scared? I'm not even fazed!
Here we go!
Safety
They're being pretty cautious!
Allow me to calculate your moves.
This seems really bad!
I have no idea what you're gonna do...
But I have no idea what I'm gonna do either!
Ad Lib!
Good point!
Calculation complete.
Yakkun!
No, it's not him!
You're wide open!
Bastard!
I don't even have to move anymore.
For Don Patch!
I'm still here, numbskull!
How dare you step on me!
What the hell are you doing, Yoshio?
Just as I calculated.
No way... Does that mean he calculated everything that would happen in a second?
How high is his IQ?
I can calculate all your movements.
I never thought he'd have a secret technique like this...
Now that it's come to this...
I'll eat all these weird markings!
Nice idea!
You can eat those?
Now you've become smart!
Dammit, what do we do now?
Leave it to me.
There is only one method...
that can equal the Imperial Intuition...
Nu Intuition!
This guy has an amazing intuition too!
Nu!!!
Now do you understand? This is the gap between an emperor and a peasant!
Don't get ahead of yourself, Giga!
I'll calculate what's beyond your calculations!
You're just adding? That's not so great!
Huh? Some difficult-looking graphs came up!
Just from addition?
The move that can surpass Giga's calculations is... This!
No way!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Woof Woof Super Spin!!!
I've already calculated that.
My next punch will pierce right through your throat!
Wang Tanmen!
What the...?
My calculations were way off!
Impossible! My calculations can't have been off!
This has never happened before!
Why? Why were they off?
Why...
What the hell is this?
Looks like your calculations didn't factor in that extra weight.
Extra weight?
How long have I had this extra weight...?
So that's how it is.
My calculations win.
Alright! We overcame his Secret Technique!
Secret Technique?
I haven't even used any yet!
What a coincidence.
Neither have I!
No, you've used quite a few...
It turns out that Giga's been fighting without using a single Secret Technique!
Just how powerful are Giga's Secret Techniques?
How will Bo-bobo face this foe more powerful than any he's fought before?
Stay tuned...
Next time, nah-la!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, ride your bike and you'll keep healthy!
Your lucky item is a Dengakuman doll made of clay!
If you tied, don't get too into your collection or you'll lose your money luck.
And if you lost, be careful of which way the wind is blowing when you dust the blackboard erasers!
Giga's drawing power from those sculptures!
Hekkun's sculpture is in danger!
This is really bad...
Giga powered up!
Let's go, Don Patch!
Oh yeah! I'm ready for this!
Ready, and...
Lord Giga!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The seal is broken!
Super Giga
is here!
We're switching to
your side ❤
Then who's gonna fight?