We have to find Hekkun's sculpture while we have the chance!
Beauty, leave it all to us!
Let's go!
Please, take this seriously for once!
After Bo-bobo and company had defeated J of the Six Cyber Knights,
Holy Radical Ceremony!
they challenged Giga, who was equal in power to Tsuru Tsururiina, ruler of the Margarita Empire!
It looks like Giga's got an astoundingly high IQ!
Watch out, guys!
What's an IQ? Can you eat it?
I'm the staple food, dammit! I won't let anyone else take that from me!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Woof Woof Super Spin!!!
These guys are hopeless...
Wang Tanmen!
Alright! We overcame his Secret Technique!
Secret Technique?
I haven't even used any yet!
What a coincidence.
Neither have I!
No, you've used quite a few...
I'm right here... You guys... I'm right here...
I'm Heppokomaru...
Just kidding! It's actually Dengakuman, nah-la!
Oh, Softon...
She ignored me again!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SweetDevilStitch
VigorousJammer
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Secret Technique?
I haven't even used a single Secret Technique yet.
Th-That's not possible...
Then what about all of the attacks he's used so far?
Clay Hand!!!
We're being pulled under!
You're not getting away!
Homing Sculptures!!
Imperial Intuition
You mean all of those were just normal attacks?
He's a monster...
Don't worry, Beauty.
I haven't used any Secret Techniques worth mentioning, either!
Bo-bobo!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Woof Woof Super Spin!!!
Turn into a dog and deliver a spinning attack against the enemy
Secret Technique
Fresh Vegetable Attack!!!
Turn into fresh vegetables and attack the enemy
Don't be picky with your vegetables
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
School Curtain Guard!!!
Wrap yourself in a school curtain to defend against attacks
Don't try this at home, kids
Active Volcano Burst Hundred Kicks
Infinite Cannon Battery Throw
Fang Mountain Dragon Tiger Thunderstrike
Spiral Soldier Attack
You sure look like you've run out of techniques!
The seal is broken!
Super Giga
is here!
We're switching to
your side ❤
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo, we still haven't used the Secret Technique: Slipper Sole Slap-Slap!
Secret Technique: Slipper Sole Slap-Slap.
Take a slipper and slap the enemy with it.
That's obviously a leftover!
They're doing it!?
Eat it!
Secret Technique:
Slipper Sole Slap-Slap!
It's working! Turns out it's a really amazing Secret Technique!
Dammit!
Outta my sight!
Why? Why did he hit me out of nowhere?
Now allow me to show you my Secret Technique!
Behold!
He's finally gonna use his Fist!
For this is...
The power...
Of an emperor!
Fist of Objets!
Huh? They're hardly reacting!
So, you know what an Objet is?
I think it's the name of a plane!
Not at all!
An Objet d'Art is a general term for sculptures that depicts
everyday objects fantastically or symbolically.
I never expected him to answer it!
Not it matters much though...
Let's get this going!
Here comes his Secret Technique!
Mega Chandelier
What the hell is that?
Take this!
Oh, crap
Run away!
Look out!
So, how do you like my technique?
It's on a whole other level from all his other attacks!
Now that it's come to this...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Love-love Umbrella of Love!!!
He's protecting against it with the power of love!
Alright! Time for our counterattack!
Roger!
Secret Technique: UMBRLA-36X!!!
Wow! Where do they sell that umbrella?
And now...
Mommy brought me my umbrella! I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
Oh, you silly child...
Wait! Where are you both going?
Now you've gone and done it.
Just kidding!
Angry Long-leg Old Guy Kick!
Time to get real!
That's the attack he used to turn Hekkun into a sculpture!
Hold it... Look at me over there...
Doesn't my doll look a little worse for wear?
Something's coming!
I'll sculpt you all like clay!
What's going on? My body feels like clay!
No way! I'm all squishy like jelly!
I thought that was the norm for you.
I'm turning into a sculpture!
Nu
Well, at least I ended up with this design.
Good for you.
I've figured this Secret Technique out!
We just have to beat down these weird creatures before we get sculpted!
And mine is freaking huge!
Don Patch
Hold it! What's this for?
Hold it, Don Patch!
You jerk! You jerk! You jerk! You jerk!
This one's for Yakkun!
Don Patch!
I turned into this.
That's disgusting!
You're up next, Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo!
His sunglasses are huge!
Now you're a perfect sculpture!
It can't be... Bo-bobo's...
He's been turned into a sculpture...
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
It can't be... Bo-bobo's...
He's a sculpture now!
Huh? One of them looks really weird!
Now he's kneading the two weird creatures! Is he turning them into sculptures?
What?
He made noodles out of them!
Thanks for waiting!
Alright!
Bo-bobo!
Lord Giga!
Damn it all...
Giga! Your Secret Technique has been defeated!
Since when did you turn into dolls?
Huh?
Did you think I was using any Secret Techniques?
What?
Why are you taking a bath?
That's it! Those are the faces I wanted to see!
You thought those were Secret Techniques! That's hilarious!
You guys are funny...
How much does he have to screw with us?
You see, the Fist of Objets' Secret Techniques are quite a pain to perform.
His hair...
First I'll start with these guys.
I have to absorb energy from Fist Users for them to work.
No way! He's absorbing power from the sculptures!
Is that how powerful his Fist is?
This is bad! Heppokomaru's somewhere on that shelf!
Become my flesh and blood!
They broke!
Now let's begin!
Fist of Objets Secret Technique:
Giga Sound!
What's going on? My body's moving against my will!
Those who hear the Giga Sound naturally assume a pose of respect for the Emperor.
Now, bow down!
On your knees!
No way... What about the others?
What kind of pose is that?
Are you trying to prostrate yourself?
Now, now.
Calm down, calm down.
A sushi boat?
You're prostrating yourself a bit too much!
So, what about Bo-bobo?
Let's all bow down.
He's high and mighty! He's not respecting Giga at all!
It doesn't matter what your pose is.
The fact remains that you can't move!
So what do you think of my Secret Technique?
Stop the damn noise!
We've been waiting for you, Miss Torpedo!
They're actually bowing down!
Now what do you think you're doing?
Thanks to your cacophony...
I knitted the design on this scarf all wrong!
Softon
Design
That's not possible! She's obviously just venting at him!
Miss Torpedo!
We understand the pain of your heart!
Eww! Perverts!
Alright! I'll follow Miss Torpedo's lead!!
Hold it, Bo-bobo!
You can't let Giga use his Secret Techniques!
Or he'll break Hekkun's sculpture!
Don't worry, I got this!
What's with that gesture?
Workbook
Miss Torpedo!
There's a problem I don't understand!
Oh, what is it?
Workbook
You're not even my teacher!
What the hell was that for?
Babylon!
Oh, my, Softon! You were here all along?
Impossible!
Is the Giga Sound ineffective against them?
Softon!
Alright then... MAX VOLUME!
Now kneel!
This is bad! My body's naturally assuming a pose of submission!
No, it's not! If anything, that's rebellious!
Now let's run him over!
You scratched my car!
She really is acting imperial!
For goodness sake...
Those goddamn speakers!
Something came out of her mouth!
Fist of Bloody Murder Secret Technique:
Torpedo Takedown!
That's a really drastic move!
She did it!
Collateral Damage!
Impossible... Is she... She...
She's a Fist User strong enough to destroy my Secret Technique?
Giga!
Fist of the Wobble-wobble...
Super Bloody...
Holy Nose Hair...
Stupid...
Murder...
Nu...
Secret Technique:
Southern Cross!!!
Lord Giga!
That was amazing! So amazing!
Those four are way too strong!
Bo-bobo! I believed in you all along, nah-la!
That's right! We still have to look for Hekkun!
We won because of me!
No, it was all because of my Nu!
Lord Giga!
Bo-bobo!
I did more than you!
It was all my Nu!
You goddamn brats! I'll fucking kill you all!
I'll fucking kill you all!
What a plain, old-fashioned line.
You said it.
What a plain, old-fashioned donut!
Can I have it?
Okay, now...
Lawd Geega!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
You goddamn brats! I'll fucking kill you all!
I'll fucking kill you all!
He's more intimidating than ever! But bo-bobo can't lose to him!
So, my son, what do you want for snacks today?
Umm... Umm...
Dried persimmons! And soy powder-covered mochi!
What are you, an old man!?
That's right...
I'm impressed you figured it out... Perfect...
Fuck off!
Stop messing around with me!
Fist of Objets Artistic Secret Technique:
Death Rondo!!!
W-What is this spiral?
There's some weird thing coming from down there!
We gotta run up to the top!
This stairway is a highway to Hell!
Let's see if you can make it up here alive!
You're on! I'll break out of this Secret Technique!
Here goes!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Cinderella Story!
What kind of secret technique is this?
That can't be easy to run in!
When you think of stairs, you think of Cinderella.
Tonight, I will become Cinderella.
What are you talking about? No, you won't!
And at the top of the stairs...
Softon is waiting for me.
He's not! It's Giga's who's up there!
Derella
Cinderella! Cinderella!
What the hell? That's not even 1% Cinderella!
Tokoro Pizza
Pizza coming through!
Okay, okay.
Allow me to show you the true terror of the Death Rondo!
Fist of Objets Secret Technique:
Mega Objet Eggs!
Wait for me, Prince Charming!
Something's coming!
This must be a test to see if we're the real Cinderella!
Fine by me! We'll prove to them that we're Cinderella!
Shinsengumi-style Secret Technique:
Shin Dere Ra!!!
Nope, I'm sure Cinderella never used that attack!
Alright, how about
Fist of Objets Secret Technique:
Killer Pole!!!
A giant sculpture just appeared in the middle of the staircase!
It's attacking us!
Look out!
The Killer Pole attacks indiscriminately!
If you don't get a move on, the entire staircase is gonna be destroyed!
Oh, no! The stairs! What do we do?
No matter!
Leave this job to us!
It's all in a day's work.
They turned into carpenters! Is this gonna work?
This is our way of life!
Amazing! They're building a staircase with houses!
Alright! Let's head straight up to Giga!
Fools! Speeding up will be your downfall!
I can bend these stairs to my will!
This ends now!
Fall!
He bent the staircase! They can't turn all those corners!
Double Drift!
There it is!
The super high-speed technique Super Duratech!
What? They turned the curves?
The thing about racers is that we can't stand losing.
What the...
That sculpture in the middle is a big pain!
Then I'd better summon a giant sculpture of my own!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Summon Super-Aesthetic Sculpture!
That's the ugliest sculpture possible!
What kind of messed-up sculpture is that?
Super-Super-Size Service!
He broke it!
You sons of bitches! Get out of my sight!
Fist of Objets Secret Technique: Thousand Trace!
What? A bunch of Gigas popped up!
Go forth, my sculptures!
Then I have no choice but to use that Secret Technique!
Super-Secret Technique:
Manager's Chair Spinning Attack!!!
That's some incredible power!
My chair's bolted to the floor and won't budge!
Tennosuke!
I can keep making sculptures till the end of time! So what now?
Dammit! I've used up all my attacks that are effective on a stairway!
Now we have to use our last resort!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Elevator!
You should've used this to begin with!
What?
Alright! All aboard! Now let's head straight to Giga!
Giga
Elevator Takeoff!
Huh? Is this how we're going?
Then what's the point of the elevator?
Here they come!
Last stop!
Giga! Even if the Heavens forgive...
a villain like you...
This cherry emblem will never forgive you!
You're a policeman now?
Police Line - Do Not Cross
W-What the... What's going on?
Take this!
Raging Policeman Drop!!!
It's the glorious strike of a policeman!
We did it! We're back to the real world!
L-Lord Giga!
It can't be! No!
Did you see Bo-bobo's awesome power?
Now we gotta find Hekkun's sculpture, and fast!
Umm... Um...
What's going on?
The sculptures are breaking on their own!
What did you say?
Failure! Failure!
What the hell are you doing?
What's going on? What does this mean?
At this rate, Hekkun's sculpture will break, too!
And so will our butts!
Shut up!
Got it!
Look, Bo-bobo!
All the power of the broken sculptures are entering Giga!
This is bad! He's powering up!
Then we gotta hurry and swallow these raw eggs!
Quickly, now!
Not bad.
Is that... Is that our Lord Giga?
I've never seen him like that before!
Mandarin Oranges
Is that... Is that our Tennosuke?
I've never seen him like that before!
Why are you smiling?
Interesting. I couldn't ask for anything else.
Bo-bobo!
Though they thought they had defeated Giga, he revived, powered up, and more evil!
Does Bo-bobo have a shot against him?
"No way," they say...
Wait... You guys?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll be seeing a light as bright as a chandelier soon!
Your lucky item is a Don Patch-colored slipper!
If you tied, make sure you don't turn your music up too loud.
And if you lost, you'll get weaker if you use the elevator too much! Take the stairs!
Giga! There's no way I will never forgive you!
Bo-bobo seems different from normal...
We'll show you the heat of the Hajike Trio!
Even Don Patch!
Even if this body is broken, I will defeat you...
and save our friend!
It seems we're having a serious episode next time!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Power of Art
Nose Hair Soul!
Take this!
The Hajike Trio's
Burning
Iron Fist
!!
Now it's time to break the seal of the Fist of the Nose Hair!