Previously on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo...
Oh no! I'm late! I'm late for school!
Look both ways before you cross!! Nah-na-la
Oh, sorry about that. You okay there?
No!
Bo-bobo is my childhood friend!
That's pretty much how it happened.
No, no! You're not even close!
Oh, you didn't like that?
Fine, fine. I get it. I hear you loud and clear.
Fist of Objets Artistic Secret Technique:
Death Rondo!!!
You're on! I'll break out of this Secret Technique!
Here goes!
Shinsengumi-style Secret Technique:
Shin Dere Ra!!!
You could've just run up to the top like a normal person!
Elevator Takeoff!
Raging Policeman Drop!!!
Give it to 'im, Bo-bobo!
Giga has transformed into a form befitting a tyrannical emperor!
Oh! Hero Mode! Très bien!
I'm not handing over the position of the heroine!
How is he even close to being a heroine?
How will Bo-bobo stand against this form of Giga
that no one has ever seen before!?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Giga Station
Now that I have assumed this form...
Do you have any idea what's about to happen to you?
Well, do you?
No way...
It can't be!
How terrible!
Allow me to introduce our new transfer student. This is Gigette.
I'm Gigette. Nice to meet you.
Thud!
You're...
You're that guy...
Oh, so you've already met?
No!
None of those are possible!
Come to think of it, was that a continuation of the intro?
Power of Art
Nose Hair Soul!
Take this!
The Hajike Trio's
Burning
Iron Fist
!!
I'll give you all an artistic despair!
Oh, that reminds me. It's time to take a group photo!
Hey, did he say a group photo!?
Shut up! Now's not the time for a photo shoot!
Okay, here I go!
I gotta strike a good pose for the group photo!
Good pose!
Okay! Say cheese!
Buy up all the stocks in OX Industries!
We've bought them.
One billion yen worth of shares under Tennosuke's name.
Oh, no! You actually bought them?
What do I do? Hey, what do I do?
I'll let you see your friend again one last time before you die!
What's going on? The wall's crystallizing!
Heppokomaru's up there in a crystal!
Bo-bobo! You guys!
Hekkun!
Witness what is my greatest art!
Oh, you're on.
We'll bring back Heppokomaru!
Secret Technique:
Retrieve the Love!!
What's with the post-apocalyptic attack?
It's all Art!
Art
What was that scene just now? Was that the Fist of Objets?
No, it wasn't! It was the power of another dimension!
Mom! Dad!
They're smiling like they were caught peeping into their daughter's room!
So you noticed?
Oh, please! I hate you guys so much!
I'm never talking to you ever again!
I don't know what that bastard's gonna do, but we're not gonna lose to him!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Fairy Tales:
The Monkey and the Crab 2005
You're all mortars!
What about the monkey and the crab?
Let's go!
And now they're attacking by Pegasus! That's pretty noble!
Art is the harmony of the mind dyed in refrain!
Before the Power of Art, all else is meaningless!
Power of Art
New-Wave Suprematism!!!
Illusory Art
What kind of power was that?
He practically erased our attack!
It's hopeless! We can't win!
If direct attacks don't work...
we'll have to give him a direct mental attack!
Yeah!
Today may seem pointless, but try hard and tomorrow will come.
Bobopatch
What the hell!?
Bo-bobo's Message
That went right to my heart!
It hit the torpedo instead!
Now's our chance! You're exposed!
That was too soothing!
Such an unartistic attack can never overcome the Power of Art!
I get it!
When Giga transformed, he gained power from a different vector called "art!"
So if you don't hit him artistically, he won't take any damage!
Impossible! For I am the greatest artist of all!
Now show me...
your pathetic attempts at art! I'll even score them for you!
You're on! Then let me show you my art!
The Nu Supper
This painting is disgusting!
Twelve points!
Now take my attack!
Amazing! He's using the contrast of black on white to make modern art!
Lights up!
And he ruined it!
35 points!
That's questionable!
Now it's my turn!
I haven't done anything yet!
Does this mean I'm perfect?
I got 100 points without doing anything!
I got 100 points... without doing anything?
My very existence is an art!
Master Art!
Please let us study you for the sake of modern art.
Go right ahead.
Thank you!
What do you think you're doing, Don Patch?
That's Master Don Art Patch to you, young lady!
Isn't art great?
Couldn't agree more!
We can't underestimate the power of art!
Then we'll show you the art that surpasses art!
Let's go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Art of The Tanakas!!
This has nothing to do with art!
Presented to you by
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
This is a FREE fansub.
Not for Sale, Rent or Auction.
http://www.hokutonogun.com/
Art of The Tanakas!!
Give it up!
That is no more than a Romanesque illusion inspired by Byzantine art!
I'll show you what real art looks like!
Passionate Landscape Painting:
Thousand Knocks 2005!!
Impossible! How did his attack hit me!?
Amazing!
It's a fusion of Secret Techniques and art!
Then take this!
Finest Sculpture:
Gold Fish
Take this!
Alright, tonight's dinner will be...
Fish soup.
What?!
How dare you make soup of Ancient Europe's finest art!
Yuck!
Mattress Beating Stress Relief!
That's a harsh concept!
How come their attacks have become super effective?
Are you telling me this is art?
Where am I now?
Upperclassman...
I-I've always...
Upperclassman... I've...
I've...
L-L-
Loved you!
Some ink-and-wash ghosts came out!
Go out with me!
That's far too scary!
You're one to say it!
Huh? What's wrong, Tennosuke?
I got it...
OX Industries
I actually got it!
The OX stocks that I bought for the group photo!
What kind of attack is this?
I'm not even sure I can call it an attack!
And finally, it's time for my walk, nah-na-la!
He's so cute!
The Dengakuman wallpaper fell on him!
Damn you all!
I don't accept any of this as art!
Okay, let's head back to our homeland.
Onward to Italy!
That's Egyptian!
OX Industries
It's a crash...
Why?
Why is my art inferior to yours?
What is your art that surpasses art?
I'll explain it to you!
Your art is no more than a representation of ideals and illusions!
True art is the aesthetic concept that only exists in the reality of everyday life!
I get it!
Through the everyday life of the Tanaka family,
Bo-bobo found the true art dwelling reality!
So you mean...
You've started a new movement of art out of Orientalism?
Exactly!
Then let me ask you this...
What of the balance in the harmonization
of the Romantic and Neoclassical movements brought about by rapid social changes?
Art is...
Back Drop!
Is this supposed to be the pinnacle of art?
That's what you get for underestimating art.
Thank goodness!
Now Hekkun will turn back to normal!
You're kidding me!
We've defeated Giga and everything, so why?
Everything in the crystal is at my whim!
Stop it!
Destruction is the truest form of art!
Please stop it!
I'll never forgive you for this!
It's time to break the seal of the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Meanwhile, Hatenko had escaped from Wang Longya's prison...
Fist of the Prison Secret Technique:
Slave Ring!!
What, this attack again?
These are a real pain to take off!
That's a strange key you have.
To think that it can even unlock my rings.
But even given that, I've still got the advantage over you.
I've measured your skill during our fight.
Quit your yapping, bitch.
Seal Unlocked!
You're a monster!
I don't really need to do this...
I just don't like that mouth of yours.
Fist of the Key Secret Technique: Eternal Lock!!
Stay there for the rest of your life.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
I'll break the seal of the Fist of the Nose Hair!
Fist of the Nose Hair:
Release the Seal!
That nose hair transformed into a dragon and rose to the heavens.
No way!
It awoke the raging gods slumbering in the heavens.
They look pretty raging to me!
Now the power of nose hairs is unleashed!
Nose Hairs!
What are these dragons? What's gonna happen?
What is this power? It's like the whole earth is shaking!
Nose Hair Soul Unleashed!!!
One, two, one, two...
What the hell are you doing?
This is getting really serious!
The earth really is shaking!
It's over, Giga!
Go forth, Dragons!
They breathed fire on Bo-bobo!
What a joke! They killed themselves!
The flame turned into a phoenix!
Giga!
I'll have you feel the true heat of our burning soul of rage!
Let's go!
First of the Three Great Secrets of the Nose Hairs:
Blazing Manly Romance!
They're hot... I can feel Bo-bobo's heat from here!
Blazing Manly Romance... What are they going to do?
Wind, forest, fire, mountain!
What a blazing charge!
What's going on?
They're so hot that I feel like I'm burning up!
I will defeat you, even if it means burning to ash!
He's suddenly steeled himself for an honorable feat!
And now...
Even if my fist shatters...
We'll put our all into it!
Go!
It really did shatter!
That was all the power we had...
Seems like Bo-bobo's right arm couldn't handle it...
They're all half-dead!
My body's burning!
What is this?
The Burning Manly Romance is a secret that passes on the heat of your soul!
We're making direct attacks on your soul!
Now let's go to Hell together!
He can't be thinking...
Never thought I'd be going with you...
Now, Bo-bobo! Don't worry about me! Just burn him up!
I shall accept your spirit!
But listen...
I won't let you suffer alone!
You truly are the man I believed you were...
Are you alright, Tennosuke?
Yeah. Never been better.
Do you have any last requests?
I want to see the sunset...
Enough with the hot stuff!
It's hot!
Incredible! Bo-bobo and the others are at the top of their game today!
This Burning Manly Romance is far too hot!
What the hell is this giant rock doing here? When did they...?
It's me!
Hot!
That's really hot, Don Patch!
Hurry up... You gotta defeat Giga in one blow...
That's not possible!
There is no Secret Technique that can defeat him in one blow!
Wait! There is one!
It's an attack that lets you defeat your enemy at the cost of your own fist:
The Manly Fist!
Teach me this Manly Fist!
There's no time! You'll have to get a feel for it!
Man!
Secret Technique initiated!
Farewell... My right fist...
I've got a feel for it.
Quit the hot stuff!
But my right fist alone isn't enough to defeat Giga!
In that case...
Quadruple Manly Fist!
A soulful strike that sacrifices his arms and legs...
That's hot!
We've used up all our power.
Bo-bobo?
Bring us back to life, dammit!
King of the Underworld? Big deal!
Yama
They're picking a fight with Lord Yama!
They're hot even when they're dead!
Charge!
Bo-bobo's Iron Fist
Hell Conquest Arc
Episode 1: A Man's Bonds
Now they're having an all-out war with Hell!
That's hot!
Dokugan-Death!
I don't get what's going on, but it's real hot!
What the...?
We've come back from the depths of Hell!
This ends now!
Time for you to taste the hottest strike of all!
What?
That's too dangerous!
If you do this with your wounded bodies...
Fly like the mighty Pegasus!
Everything they're doing is super hot!
What fools!
You sent him flying in the wrong direction!
Giga!
The wait is over!
Burn to ashes, Giga!
It's hot...
This heat... The heat of the Sun, the hottest thing on Earth...
The Sun that gives light to all life...
The Sun that has a burning soul...
It's the heat of my fist that is even hotter than that!
He surpassed the sun!
It's over.
Yeah.
And so, the men went home by train.
What a mundane way to end it!
Hooray! We finally defeated Giga!
I knew it. Breaking the seal consumes a lot of energy.
I can't use it haphazardly.
I'm back to normal!
Hekkun!
Hekkun! Hekkun!
What are you...?
Director
You followed my instructions well!
Now return to your homes and rest!
That is all!
Tsuru Tsururiina IV's Castle
It can't be...
They've defeated Giga...?
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Bad news!
Octopascal
The Cold Sleep Chamber that housed your predecessor is now empty!
Empty!? Have they finally awakened?
But this may work out in our favor...
Finally, Bo-bobo has defeated Giga!
But who is Tsuru Tsururiina IV's predecessor that has awoken from his cold sleep?
What fate awaits them now?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your luck will rise when you appreciate art at the art museum!
Your lucky food is fresh fish soup!
If you tied, watch the sunset over the ocean whenever you're stressed, and you'll settle down.
And if you lost, don't stare at your computer for too long or it'll hurt your eyes!
We did it!
We finally defeated Giga!
Now there's nothing to fear!
It's all thanks to me!
Better be grateful now!
Yeah, yeah.
This show's gonna power up next episode!
Yeah! And the main character is...
Me!
Hey Bo-bobo, is that true?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Welcome Back, Hekkun and A New Enemy Arrives!
Welcome Back, Hekkun ♪
A New Journey Begins!
A New Enemy Arrives!
Death Match on the Bridge!!
In two parts!
We've got a two-part format now!