The New Enemy!!
It is...
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Who?
Isn't it Giga?
We just defeated him last week.
You're too foolish!
Who?
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Don Patch!
Wait, that's me!
Alright, alright.
Who?
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
The new enemy... The answer to that...
will be revealed in this week's episode of Bo-bobo!
Well, you're technically right.
Margarita Empire
Emperor
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Four Lords of Margarita
Battleship
Purr-Poo
OVER
Halekulani
At Hallelujah Land, Bo-bobo and his friends defeated Halekulani,
It's money!!
last of the Four Lords of Margarita...
Now that I think about it,
Miss Torpedo joined us, and she's actually OVER of the Four Lords.
Torpedo Girl
Margarita Empire
Emperor
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Four Lords of Margarita
Battleship
Purr-Poo
OVER
Halekulani
That's right, she is!
Bo-bobo and friends went to save their kidnapped friend Heppokomaru
Margarita Empire
Emperor
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Four Lords of Margarita
Battleship
Purr-Poo
OVER
Halekulani
Cyber City
Giga
Six Cyber Knights
Pana
Sonic
Poet
Carman
Wang Longya
and headed for Cyber City.
It was there
that they challenged the man equal in power to Tsururiina IV,
the greatest warrior of the Hair Hunt, Giga!
What the hell's wrong with this picture?
Cyber City
Giga
Six Cyber Knights
Pana
Sonic
Poet
Carman
Wang Longya
Bo-bobo and friends defeated Giga's henchmen, the Six Cyber Knights, one after another,
and after a long, hard, final battle,
they finally defeated Giga once and for all!
Cyber City
Giga
Six Cyber Knights
Pana
Sonic
Poet
Carman
Wang Longya
Hold on.
Didn't the sun get destroyed in that battle?
Then what's that shining in the sky?
Hot, hot...
Let's get this shit on the road!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
I'm back to normal!
Hekkun!
Thank God you're safe!
That's disgusting!
What wrong with you idiots?
It's stuck on me!
Isn't there anything I can wipe it off with? Um...
Thank you very much, all of you.
What the...? He ignored me!
I'm just glad you're okay.
Thank goodness for that!
How dare you follow Giga and put up with all his evil and demonic deeds!?
Repent this instant!
Just look at me!
I wasn't sucking up to Giga, now was I?
Let's just go.
Huh? Where did Softon go?
Oh, shit! I completely forgot all about him!
We wouldn't have defeated Giga...
if Softon hadn't prevented Cyber City's collapse.
That's Softon for you!
Alright! Let's go back to him!
Look! There he is!
They're worshiping him!
And what's with that pose?
Welcome Back,
Hekkun
♪
A New Journey
Begins!
What are you two doing here?
Have mercy upon us...
Mercy? What mercy?
I'm afraid that he cannot leave.
Onion-man!
If he were to vacate that spot...
The city would collapse once more!
No way! That means Softon has to...
Let's go to the beach!
Cut it out!
We'll make happy memories!
T-T-T-T-T-T-This is real bad!
July 29, Sunny.
Summer Vacation started today.
I asked Daddy Softon to take us to the ocean.
Period.
Get away from him, you two!
The fate of a city rests on him!
August 31, Sunny.
We finally convinced him today!
And we went to the beach.
School starts tomorrow!!
I caved...
He caved in after a whole summer of persuasion!
Now that Softon is gone,
the place is starting to collapse!
Can't anyone take Softon's place?
Here's a replacement!
Kii Plum
That's a dried plum!
I don't even care anymore...
That takes care of everything.
But where's Miss Torpedo?
She's rolling right at us really fast!
But why?
Guess who's back!
Oh, Softon...
I'm afraid this is where we must part ways.
For I must go to an anti-war protest
as a representative of weapons.
I see.
That's too bad.
Miss Torpedo!
Please let us see you off!
Thank you, boys.
I'm sure I'll be back.
We'll give you a grand farewell!
Farewell Ritual
What kind of ritual is this?
It's freaky!
Well, that's it for the exorcism.
Let's go take a rest.
Exorcism!?
Cyber Hotel
I can't go on like this. I can't always be relying on Bo-bobo to protect me.
I have to start closing the gap while everyone else is resting!
Hey, pick up the pace! The tournament's tomorrow!
Yes, Coach!
I'll master that spike, no matter what!
I won't lose!
I'll never lose!
Margarita Empire
Fourth! Bad news! Bad news!
What is it?
Octopascal
The Cold Sleep Chamber that housed your predecessor is now empty!
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Empty? Have they finally awakened?
The ones who built the Margarita Empire into the greatest and strongest empire of all time...
The Evil Tsururiina III's Generation!
I heard that he subjugated nations with such cruelty...
that he was said to be the devil incarnate!
And now his seal has been broken...
But...
This may work out in our favor.
Because my predecessor's target...
was the remnants of the Hair Kingdom.
Bo-bobo's new journey had begun!
We shall found...
A great nation...
Hey! Kamakura Shogunate! Kamakura Shogunate! Kamakura Shogunate!
TL Note: First military dictatorship of Japan, 1192-1333
1192! 1192! Kamakura Shogunate!
TL Note: The pronunciation of "1192" sounds like "Great Nation"
How can they be so hyper this early in the morning?
Fish stick, fish stick, fish stick!
Cheers.
All this meaningless energy...
Guess it's the same as ever.
I'm home again.
Ono-no-Imoko!
Kamakura rules!
Welcome Home, Heppokomaru!
Commemorative Song "Shogunate"
Ono-no-Imoko!
Kamakura rules!
Hang on! This noise is actually a song for me?
Enough with the singing!
Just keep quiet for once!
Okay, fine.
Sparkle, sparkle!
Hey, we can't see!
What the hell? That car just crashed into us!
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
How on earth did that happen!?
Bo-bobo! Hang in there!
Hooray!
It's a bumper crop!
My precious car...
Who do you think you are?
Hello, I'd like to call a tow truck...
We have reason to believe
Gorgon
that there is a remnant of the Hair Nation among you. Now who is it?
Nihil
Otter
You can't hide from us, otter!
These guys look dangerous.
We can't let them know that Bo-bobo's a remnant of the Hair Kingdom!
The Hair Kingdom?
And what if there is?
We'll do something real nice to them.
Something nice?
You mean they'll give us ten yen?
Here you go.
Yay!
The Hair Kingdom is too sweet!
Are you guys Hair Hunters?
Yeah.
But we're not like the softies from this era.
We're the strongest Hair Hunters in history...
from 100 years ago!
Hair Kingdom
There.
Now the ten yen is all mine!
What are you trying to do!?
Bargain Sale
And what do you guys from 100 years ago
want with the remnants of the Hair Kingdom?
You'll do something real nice, right?
Just sacrifice them.
What!?
Not give them ten yen?
He looks like a remnant to me, otter!
No! I'm not! You've got it wrong!
Madam
I'm one of those fuzzy things that madams put on their outfits!
This
That's an amazing excuse!
Well, in any case,
You're bound to confess if we put you through some pain.
This is not good!
If we find a remnant of the Hair Kingdom, we'll take him alive.
Those who we deem are not...
will be eliminated!
Here they come!
Get ready!
I'll start with you!
Me again?
This calls for...
Self-Styled Fist of the Wobble Wobble
Secret Technique:
Wriggling Around!
Tennosuke's
Lesson of the Day
Simply wriggling around
does not a Secret Technique make.
I'll take this one, otter!
Loincloth festival!
Oh! You pervert!
If you're a remnant of the Hair Kingdom, you better fess up quick!
I'll... I'll take on the fight!
What a lame age this is.
Here he comes!
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Thunder of Luxembourg
He did it!
Looks like some people in this era are still worth their salt.
We can't let these three find out
that Bo-bobo is a remnant of the Hair Kingdom.
We still don't know their full strength.
It's too dangerous to let them focus their attacks on him.
We should keep them in the dark
and force them to disperse their strength.
OK!
Jubei
You look like you're having fun.
Shaina
Why don't you let us join in?
They've got allies? Since when?
That makes five of them... This is horrible!
Looks like you're in for it now.
Oh! We have allies too!
Despair Guy
Super Rabbit
The most useless allies we could ask for!
So what are you up to?
Just treasure hunting.
That woman looks suspicious to me, otter.
Go home!
Let's take her, otter!
Scallop!
Who was that?
I'm a remnant of the Hair Kingdom, scumbags!
Bo-bobo...
That's the Fist of the Nose Hair...
That's definitely a Hair Kingdom art...
You saved us the trouble of looking for you.
Why did he tell them?
By revealing his identity,
he means to draw their attention away from us
and draw all of the enemy attacks to himself.
He never changes.
But...
I'll back you up, Bo-bobo!
Mars!
Sounds fun. We'll take you alive.
I see your legs are shaking, boy.
Don't let him provoke you!
We're after the remnant of the Hair Kingdom!
We're after the scallop!
Fight!
Let's go!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock Paper Scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Bo-bobo and company had defeated Giga and saved Heppokomaru,
and they have gone back on their journey to defeat the Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina IV,
for the peace and freedom of hair.
1192! 1192! Kamakura Shogunate!
Bo-bobo and his friends enjoyed a brief moment of peace.
However, no sooner had it begun,
than Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago stood before him!
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
A New Enemy
Arrives!
Bridge!!
on the
Death Match
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Train!!
Stop it, you idiot!
We're still in your way!
Charge!
I'm not stopping now!
I couldn't ask for more!
What? Her hair turned into a spider!
Spider's Net!
Spider's Net!!
Yahoo!
You're mine!
Scales Attack!!
We're going back to the forest now!
Damn brats!
He got me!
Don Patch! I'm coming to save you!
May!!
Thanks, but I never asked for that!
You damn small fry!
Check. Captured your rook.
What the hell are you playing?
Now's my chance!
It's my chance to use my greatest Secret Technique!
Here goes my Final Secret Technique!
Hot Spring Bananas
Brown-nosing!
That did it!
A perfect execution!
Stuff it, trash!
That's hot.
That idiot.
Is he trying to burn us along with them?
This looks bad! We have to block off the bridge somehow!
Right, leave this to me!
What the hell is that?
Set up!
That takes care of it!
Secret Technique:
Extinguisher Attack!!
Pour!
Hooray!
It looks like Hell on Earth!
But somehow it put out the fire!
How?
Hooray!
Alright!
Rainclouds, be gone!
Bo-bobo! I've captured the enemy's otter! What should we do with it?
Good question.
Chona chona chona chona...
The otter is riding off...
The wagon is shaking...
The cold front's brought me back!
Bo-bobo!
You're the one they're after! You better stand back!
Then I guess I'll be the backup this time.
Heppokomaru! It's time to use our power of friendship!
Alright!
Let's show them what our friendship's made of!
Combined Secret Technique:
Wobble-Wobble May Jet!!
Wobble!
There it is!
It's their ruthless indiscriminate attack!
This move is intense!
I can tell.
You're more powerful than the others.
I couldn't be any happier to know that there are still warriors worth their salt left in this era.
Have at you!
With the sun reflected in an owl's eye in my left hand...
And the moon sunk in the crimson sea in my right hand...
Draping on the vestments of a fallen angel clad in wings of desire...
I open the door of the silent hellfire!
Babylon!
Jubei!
Impossible!
What just happened?
Go, Tennosuke!
I'm really sorry about this! He just hasn't seen any action in a while!
Washed-out Teabag Attack!
Washed-out Teabag Attack!!!
That's a really weird way to fight!
Alright!
Time to take them all out at once!
Here goes my Final Secret Technique:
Raise the bridge.
What the hell are you doing?
We're falling!
Shaina!
I get it alreayd.
Spider's Territory!!!
That move sure comes in handy.
Look at the others, falling like idiots.
I'm far better at fighting underwater!
I'll take these chumps underwater with me!
Gulp, otter!
Bearkichi and Bearie
Congratulations on your Wedding!
Bearkichi!
Our lovely wedding...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bear Dance of Rage!!
I'm drowning! I can't swim!
I know I'm an otter, but I can't swim!
Slice 'em up!
Supersonic Nihil Fist!!!
That's a huge attack!
Softon! Grab on to this!
Is this actually tangible?
Die!
Your attacks won't reach us up here!
We'll see about that!
May!
What in the...?!
That's some bizarre combination!
Combined Secret Technique:
Babyfart!!!
You two OK?
This can't be happening!
How are they so powerful?
I see your legs are shaking.
You damn brat!
Papylon!
You bastards!
Enough of this bullshit!
Mama's made... this tasty, tasty...
lunchbox!
Rice balls go...
outside the lunchbox!
What just happened?
I couldn't see it...
Now then...
How about I show you...
the power of the main character of this anime?
You think you're the main character?
But Bo-bobo's the main character!
Hair Hunter
Meanwhile...
It's morning!
The evils from a hundred years ago have begun to awaken!
But this is getting crazier and crazier!
What's gonna happen now?
What will happen to Bo-bobo, the remnant of the Hair Kingdom,
and his friends?
You saved my life...
But why did you save your enemy?
Because you have the same smell as me.
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll get lots of compliments if you cooperate with your friends!
Your lucky food is a rice ball with a dried plum inside!
If you tied, you may meet someone new on top of a big bridge.
And if you lost, next time you're in a dark woods, make sure you don't bump into any spider webs!
These new foes seem pretty strong!
We have to do some training and power up!
Then I'm going to train in this boutique!
Boutique?
Then I'm going to that supermarket!
Supermarket?
Wait, isn't this a shopping mall?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Let's All Power Up! and The Enemy is our Strongest Ancestors? In two parts!
Let's All Power Up!
The New Costume is 582 Yen?
The Enemy is our Evil Ancestors? The Power Up is Useless!!
You can't power up like that!