Nose Hair Masterpiece Theater
The Tale of the Otter
Mother...
Where am I going?
Don't cry, my boy.
I will come and find you... one day...
Mother...
My boy!
Mother?
Mother!
My boy!
Mama!
That's the boy?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
To protect the peace and freedom of mankind's hair,
Bo-bobo and his friends have set out on their journey once again.
Hooray! A hot spring!
That'll warm me up!
But you'll melt!
But before them
stood Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago,
the strongest in the history of the Margarita Empire.
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
Their target: The remnants of the Hair Kingdom.
Let's take her, otter!
Scallop!
Who was that?
I'm a remnant of the Hair Kingdom, scumbags!
Have at you
Babylon!
Rice balls go...
outside the lunchbox!
Bo-bobo and friends have defeated Jubei and Gorgon.
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
But unbeknownst to Bo-bobo,
the evils from 100 years ago
are waking up one after another!
This place is worth the money!
We've got beach bodies now, nah-na-la!
Wait, this isn't a tanning salon!
Let's All
Power Up!
The New Costume
is
Yen?
That leaves two to go.
These guys...
are strong!
Not you, though...
Now, why don't I show you my main character powers?
Main Character
Show us!
Alright!
Let's take them down all in one blow, Softon!
No, not you...
Son of a...
They stepped on the main character!
Let's go, Heppokomaru!
OK!
Grief of Sweden And May!
No!
You're not needed here.
Sorry!
We avoided a direct hit.
The same attack won't work on us twice.
Papylon Returns!
Now's your chance, main character Don Patch!
Lend us your power!
Main character?
Guess I have no choice.
That's our main character!
You're so cool! You're our hero!
Dynamite
Hey... That's going a bit too far, Bo-bobo!
Stand aside, lady.
You could get hurt.
Here we go, main character!
It's hard being the main character.
Fire!
Idiot Cannon
Fool!
Now, I'll...
All your dreams will come true!
Main Character
Alright!
Time for me to finish you off!
Back me up, supporting characters!
Okay! You're gonna use that attack, aren't you?
Olé!
What? What? What are you going to do to me?
Café Olé!
And now time for our signature pose!
Wait for it, wait for it...
Olé!
It's tough dealing with that idiot.
He's way too strong...
It's over.
Heppokomaru.
Your fight out there wasn't half bad.
Thank you very much!
But you can't let that get to your head.
You're still no more than a baby chick.
Yeah, yeah.
Guys!
You forgot about this guy, na-la!
No!
Please listen to me!
I'm actually just an ordinary otter!
See, I was just going along for the ride!
I was hitchhiking...
Tokyo
Is that so?
Otters never lie.
Alright!
Let's sell him off to the aquarium!
You brute!
Why me?
But why do you suppose hair hunters from a hundred years ago
are after Bo-bobo?
I can't accept this! He defeated us all?
I have to fall back for now!
He's making a run for it!
Stop right there.
Look... If you're heading out,
can you hand this to your boss for me?
Tokoroten
Gift Set
Make sure he knows that the tokoroten is a good guy!
Fools!
You'll regret this!
Why the hell did you let him go!?
You piece of shit!
This can't be good.
They must have been just ordinary troopers.
If the other Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago are awakening,
this could spell trouble.
The battle could get even rougher from here on out.
Then I guess that place will have to be our next destination.
Where are we going?
And didn't our car break down?
We have a car.
Not a decent car!
Let's move, Softon.
I lost to the pink twirly car yet again!
And so, the Pink Twirly Car set off with Bo-bobo and his friends inside.
Divine Drift!
Move it, move it, move it!
Wanna fight, punks?
The place we are headed to now is called the Holy Land of Eternal.
It is a sacred place that can raise the powers of Fist users.
Eternal... The holy land that can power up Fist users...
What kind of place is it?
Three hours later...
We're here.
Holy Land
Eternal
Wait, this is just a shopping mall!
All the shops here in Eternal are training grounds.
By training in a shop that befits your powers, you can power up.
That's not true! It can't possibly be true!
Alright! I'm going to power up in that store over there!
Bakery
Hekkun! Please wake up already! That's just a bakery!
Heppokomaru
leveled upllll
a whole lot.lllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllll
He's actually powering up in here!
Mysterious land, isn't it?
Alright, let's go too!
Let's go power up!
Yeah!
Wobble-Wobble
Area Map: Eternal
I can only power up in a Nu store.
And there should be a Nu store somewhere around here...
Nu Store
Ne Store
The Nu Store went out of business, but the Ne Store is booming!
Damn you, Ne!
Damn you to hell!
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Tennosuke's anger
against Ne gave
him a limit break.
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Alright. This should do it.
Awaken, Babylon!
What the hell!?
I shall bestow my power unto you.
Softon attained
sacred power
by the gracelllllll
of Babylon.lllllllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
As for Don Patch...
What's that?
I gotta power up too!
And...
I can only power up in that store!
Jewelry Store
He's coming straight for us!
And feint!
He went into the clothes store!
Fish! Fish!
I'm a fish!
What the hell is with him?
Now...
It's time for me to deck myself out!
Changing Room
He's trying them on?
This skirt is sooo cute!
Oh, but this camisole is pretty, too!
I can't decide!
I buy them all, ooga.
Well, how much, ooga? How much, ooga?
What the hell is his problem?
Majjimo
Don Patchlllllll
gained 60lllll
majjimo.llll
llllllllllllllll
Majjimo
Those lights...
I guess they all managed to power up!
All that's left is Bo-bobo...
Supermarket
Bo-bobo!
Hey, Beauty!
My training was extreme like you'd never imagine.
H-He's powered up incredibly!
What could have happened here?
That'll be 582 yen.
Beauty. Pay for me.
So which one is this impudent sacrifice?
I'm sure he's in this town...
Lost
What the hell are you looking at? I ain't on display!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Alright, let's go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
In their fight with the Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago...
Grief of Sweden And May!
Papylon Returns!
Olé!
Café Olé!
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
Bo-bobo defeated the last survivors of the team of five,
Nihil, Shaina, and Otter,
and in preparation for the battle to come,
they headed for the Holy Land of Eternal
where they say Fist users can power up.
There, Heppokomaru leveled up...
Heppokomaru
leveled upllll
a whole lot.lllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Nu Store
Ne Store
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Tennosuke's anger
against Ne gave
him a limit break.
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
as did Tokoro Tennosuke...
Softon attained
sacred power
by the gracelllllll
of Babylon.lllllllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
and Softon...
Majjimo
Don Patchlllllll
gained 60lllll
majjimo.llll
llllllllllllllll
Majjimo
and Don Patch...
Supermarket
and finally...
Bo-bobo.
That'll be 582 yen.
Beauty. Pay for me.
But just then...
Nihil returned with a creepy-looking man!
What the hell are you looking at? I ain't on display!
The Enemy is our Evil
Ancestors?
The Power-Up
is Useless!!
So which one of them is from the Hair Kingdom?
I'm sorry. I can't find him in this crowd...
Then why don't we draw him out...
with a little Hair Hunt?
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Cherry Blossom Slash
My hair!
What just happend!?
This is...
A woman's...
Blizzard of Love...
What the hell are you doing?
So they're here already.
What are these flower petals?
So he's brought an ally back with him, after all.
Which one of them is from the Hair Kingdom?
Neither of them. They're just his comrades.
Meanwhile, back to Bo-bobo...
Let's move, Bo-bobo!
What could that whirlwind be?
Could it be another Hair Hunter from a hundred years ago?
We have to hurry!
That telephone pole looks nice!
Beauty!
We can't even get close to him!
Sorry to keep you all waiting!
Ne
The headliner is here.
He's wearing Ne! What happened to him?
I went to the Nu store but it was out of business, and the Ne store salesmen talked me into a sale...
That's good!
It looks good on you!
You think so?
I can't take it anymore!
Oh, really?
You're getting wet.
Guys!
Beauty!
Enough of this bullshit!
Where is the man from the Hair Kingdom?
I'm right over here!
What?
What the hell is he doing?
That's him!
Wait just a second, Your Highness!
During the war a hundred years ago...
The Margarita Empire was a minor power.
But through power and violence,
Tsuru Tsururiina III and the Third's Generation turned it into the greatest empire in the world,
in just four days..
Their power and atrocity matched the devil himself.
Modern
Third
Generation
Tsururiina IV
Tsururiina III
Tennosuke
Tsurun
Geha
Kitemasu
Mask
Hägen
¥800/hr
Part-Timers
Dengakuman
With the former emperor Tsururiina III at their head,
the 26 captains from A to Z-block
were said to each be able to hunt five million heads in just a few hours!
The past generation was cruel!
Having conquered this world, my predecessors entered cold sleep chambers for some reason
and entered their long slumber.
That's right.
And to make sure they never woke up again, I sealed them with packing tape...
Packing tape?
But...
Why has the Third's generation of Hair Hunters awakened now?
Well, never mind.
I'll use the Third's generation.
Who do you think you are?
H-How did he...?
I couldn't sense him coming!
Is this the power of the Third's Generation?
We're having fried octopus tonight!
Octopascal!
Wait a moment!
I take it that you're my predecessor's captains.
I'm Tsururiina IV!
I've come to pay my greetings to the Third who has returned to this world!
Fourth?
Oh, the reigning emperor?
My apologies.
Octopascal!
Are you alright?
At least they didn't pickle me...
You gotta pay your greetings, don't ya?
Come with me, Fourth.
By the way, I'm no captain. Just an ordinary trooper.
Amazing! This is really amazing!
Even he is but an ordinary trooper!
With the Third's Generation's power, I can surely defeat Bo-bobo!
We're here.
This is the resting place of Tsururiina III
and the A to G-block captains directly under his command.
One of them's open!
Kikunojo, Captain of G-block,
has already headed to the front line to find the remnant of the Hair Kingdom.
This is perfect!
It's just what I wished for!
Now, Bo-bobo will finally meet his match...
So the sacrifice is finally here.
And who do you think you are?
You guys look weird together!
I am the man of the falling cherry blossoms,
G-block Captain of the Former Margarita Empire,
Roselily Kikunojo.
Former G-block Captain
Roselily Kikunojo
My mission is to claim the remnant of the Hair Kingdom.
You've come to take me away?
I've been waiting for you, Kenji!
Me?
Don't leave me, Bo-bomi!
Pork Chop!!
Patchya!
Bo-bomi!
Pork Chop!!
What are you even trying to do?
I'm going to disprose of you, trash.
DispROSE
He's so intimidating!
This man is a former captain from a hundred years ago!
Hey, you.
Thought I told you to give it to him.
Tokoroten
Gift Set
You know, the Tokoroten Gift Set!
Yeah, course I gave it to him...
Yeah, I got your expired tokoroten.
I take it that was your challenge to me?
Now I've gone and done it...
Now, in this blizzard of cherry blossoms,
what do you think will become of you?
A party!
No way!
Party time! Party time!
What the hell? This is real scary!
A Hair Hunting party!
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Rosacuda!
That's...
His indiscriminate attack that hurts friend and foe alike!
Captain! What should I do?
I have no further use for you.
Get out of here, you disgrace!
That's cruel!
What do you take your friends for?
Right?
Flower
Nothing more than minor diversions.
I'm going to give the impudent sacrifice a little beating.
And the rest of you will all die!
You bastard!
I won't let you lay a finger on my friends!
Never!
The roses are following me!
Everyone, spread out!
Roger!
What the hell are you doing to me?
I'm gonna kill them later.
And now...
Finish!
I'm Number One!
What do you think you're doing?
That's one down.
Hekkun!
It's too dangerous! Stay back!
That son of a bitch!
Our attacks won't reach him up there!
Leave it to me!
Transform!
Spike Ball
Now, throw me right into his face!
Got it!
Slam Dunk!
That felt great.
Why are you playing basketball?
You must not understand the situation you're in.
Five Times the Roses!
There's more of them!
This is dangerous!
Softon! Take Beauty somewhere safe!
Got it.
Bo-bobo!
We'd better go somewhere safe as well.
I have a job for you two.
Bait!
You do this to us all the time!
They're coming for us!
It's no use! There's too many of them!
We'd better split!
Okay!
Here!
With only half of them following me...
I can use my Fist of the Wobble-wobble...
They're all following me!?
Nu! Nu! Nu!
Now I'll have to call for help with the cry of my soul, Nu Telepathy!
Help me...
No, I am not a cat burglar.
I am a love burglar.
They won't follow us this far.
You're not half bad, Hair Man.
But it looks like I can't say the same for your friends.
What?
Bo-bobo!
You guys!
By the way, my roses emit a liquid strong enough to dissolve the human body.
In about ten minutes, they'll have dissolved to the bone.
Bo-bobo! Please!
Bo-bobo!
Now, it's time for your punishment!
I have to teach you your place, foolish sacrifice.
I'm glad I could face a brute like you.
Because now I can test the full power of my power up!
Me, too.
Don Pa...
No...
Love Hunter Y!
The cruel and smug man that can control roses...
Can Bo-bobo save his friends from him?
And...
Now that the former Hair Hunters have awakened...
What are they after?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll have a happy encounter at the shopping mall!
Your lucky drink is a Café Au Lait with lots of milk!
If you tied, you'll have good luck if you give a gift to someone who's taken care of you.
And if you lost, Tennosuke might jump out at you from a manhole!
What's that?
It's coming for us at an amazing speed!
A bird?
A plane?
That yellow afro... It can only mean...
Super Bo-bobo is here!
Super? How are you different from before?
You'll know when you see it!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Go! Super Bo-bobo! and Happy Battle in the Flower Field! In two parts!
Go! Super Bo-bobo!
Activating the Power of Love ♪
Happy Battle in the Flower Field!
The Scent of Flowers is the Scent of Death?
What's different? I wanna know!
Patchmi wants to know too!