Pre-Show Private Time
Supermarket
No! Please, stop!
Oh, come on, it'll be fine!
Let me put these Groucho glasses on you!
D-D-Don't do it! I'll become a boss!
Don't do it!
There you go!
I'm a boss!
Oh God, no!
When Ms. Don Patch screams "Oh God, no",
she transforms into Ohgodno Mask!
Oh God, no!
Oh, my.
How dare you!
Prepare yourself for my Serious Mode!
Oh God, no!
He put them on!
Get out!
It's cold! It's really cold!
Then have a taste of Double Boss!
Oh God, no!
By the way, the show started a whole minute ago
Oh God, no! That was supposed to be private!
We were on full display!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
After defeating the Hair Hunter troops from a hundred years ago,
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
Bo-bobo and friends headed to the Holy Land Eternal to power up for the upcoming battle.
Heppokomaru
leveled upllll
a whole lot.lllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllll
It was there,
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Tennosuke's anger
against Ne gave
him a limit break.
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
that they powered up at the shops that corresponded to their abilities.
Softon attained
sacred power
by the gracelllllll
of Babylon.lllllllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Majjimo
Don Patchlllllll
gained 60lllll
majjimo.llll
llllllllllllllll
Majjimo
However...
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Rosacuda!
Softon and Beauty,
Tennosuke,
and Heppokomaru were captured.
And that was when Bo-bobo's rage reached its peak!
Go!
Super Bo-bobo!
Activating
the Power of Love ♪
Dammit!
Yeeeow!
Flower Flower Flower
It's time to dole out your punishment!
We'll be putting civilians at risk if we fight here!
Let's take this to somewhere less crowded!
Alright!
Just kidding!
We'll fight you in the crowd anyway!
That's how we do things!
Getting a bit gung-ho are we?
Stop it, you two! You'll get everyone hurt!
Just save me already!
Hey, is it just me, or does my rose have more fluid than the rest of you?
Know your place.
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Rosacuda!
Leave these flowers to me!
I've been stealing love for 30 years.
I live freely, and master the path of impossible love.
And my name is Love Hunter...
Y! Y! Y!
What the hell even is a Love Hunter?
That was pretty good!
Then how about this?
Seeds
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Lily Demons!!!
Some weird things came out of the ground! Well then...
Hey, what are you doing?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Spike Crop!
Grade 1 Class 2
Grade 1 Class 3
Wait, that's the true nature of those spikes?
Let us do battle!
Couldn't ask for anything better!
Those spikes are weak!
But we could've beat them at cards...
Who has the Six of Spades?
They're useless!
You useless piece of shit!
What? Why me?
Very well. It's my turn to take you on.
Is this...
Is this the powered-up Bo-bobo?
What an intense aura! It's nothing like it was before!
This power is the real deal!
Here we go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Take this!
Thousand Nose Hair Wave!!!
I can do it!
Oh, no! That's it!
That's my limit!
I gotta sleep!
Come on! Save me now!
He's gotten weaker!
What's happened to me?
Secret Technique: Bo-bobo Wave!
Secret Technique: Bo-bobo Beam!
It's hopeless!
I'm making nothing but clams!
How about some clam chowder?
Is that all you've got?
That's not even worth mentioning.
Secret Technique: Thorns!!!
He spit out some more clams!
Now!
My loyal lilies!
Hunt the hairs of the villagers!
That bastard!
He's Hair Hunting in the middle of a battle!
N-No!
Is it just me, or is my flower wiggling around?
Why me? What did I ever do to you?
Hunting while fighting.
That was common practice a hundred years ago.
Why now?
Why can't I use my powered-up strength?
Let's hide ourselves for the moment!
A smokescreen?
Come out! Where are you hiding?
We are this city's public art pieces.
"A Passing Wrestler"
and "Man Fighting Bear".
What the hell are you doing here, trash?
Jewelry Store
He figured it out!
They're headed right for the jewelry store!
Now you've gone and done it!
They're coming back as celebrities! In this recession?
Thieves!
Rosacuda!
Oh, my! Let's take cover in that house!
Got it!
Not you, though.
You son of a bitch! You betrayed me!
Come on! Say something to me!
They're coming!
You can't hide from me!
Fist of the Myriad Blossom Secret Technique:
Spring Glory!!!
These tulips you see here
can detect anything that moves!
Whatever you two do, don't move!
It's a flower garden!
This idiot came out on his own!
Harvest time, harvest time!
But why are you guys showing yourselves now?
It's a flower garden!
You saved me the trouble of finding you!
Thorns!!!
Bo-bobo!
Now then...
It's about time I finished you off.
But why?
Forget using the power-ups...
I can't even use regular Secret Techniques!
Then what was all that rigorous training for?
Supermarket
Several hours ago...
Master Tuna Fillet
Thirty more laps!
Yes, Master!
Idiot!
Your pace is slowing!
Yes, Master!
My training was hard and strict.
And five hours later...
Past-Expiry Sale:
Cheap Tuna!!!
Tuna Half Off
You have done well.
You have successfully passed.
Thank you very much!
Manager! Come take a look!
Tuna Half Off
The secret password: Open Sardines!
What's going on?
The seafood corner is reconstructing itself!
Is the tuna fillet doing that?
This jacket that you see before you is proof of your mastery.
Those who wear this jacket will gain mysterious powers.
Tuna Half Off
This is the only jacket of its kind.
Take good care of it.
Master!
What!?
Snacks Corner
Thank you so much!
Wait, why!?
Okay then, time to go!
Hey!
Farewell!
Hey! Put me back in the seafood corner!
I'm gonna go bad!
My vision is going black...
I'm a blackfin tuna, but my now my vision is going black...
Quit making fillet jokes!
What the hell is he talking about?
Look out, Bo-bobo! Get out of there!
Die!
I... can't afford to lose!
Not until... I've saved my friends!
Yes. That mindset of yours is... love.
Love...
Love
Die!
Those who know love will gain power.
What?
The most important thing for supermarket employees
is the love that wishes that their customers enjoy their shopping.
You, who know love, are the successor.
The infinite power of all the supermarkets of Japan...
Supermarket
Love
is yours!
Supermarket
Super Bo-bobo has been born!
I now have the power of love!
Wait, is that what you meant by Super?
Well whatever the case,
my power-up is complete!
Don't get ahead of yourself, trash!
Take this!
What?
Concentrated Fire!!!
His afro split twice!
That's never happened before!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
W-What was that?
Amazing! Those nose hairs were amazing!
Wait, those aren't quite nose hairs!
We put them out wrong.
And there are three old men now!
Dammit...
Nose Hair Sword!!!
Wow! He's got a new weapon!
What's that? What are you gonna do?
Take this!
Slice
Blade Testing!!!
Tennosuke!
Wait... What's with that expression?
It can't be!
He really has...
I can power up even further.
P-Power up further!?
He sprouted...
wings!
But why there?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Flap-Flap Wind Slicer!!!
He's powered up?
To be continued!
He's so annoying!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
The fight with Roselily Kikunojo continued.
Bo-bobo challenged Kikunojo with his powered up strength,
but he had been powered down instead.
But Bo-bobo's heart awakened with love,
and he finally activated the power of Super Bo-bobo!
Concentrated Fire!!!
Fist of the Nose Hair!
Happy Battle
in
the Flower Field!
The Scent of Flowers is
the Scent of Death?
What's with that confident face you're making?
A mere remnant of the Hair Kingdom
could never match the Hair Hunters!
Are you stupid?
A mere Hair Hunter could never defeat me.
Know your place!
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Iron Cosmos
In that case...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
They're really hard!
Maerchen
Four Maerchen Sisters!
What!?
Yay! It's a flower!
How cute!
Let's make flower decorations!
How the hell!? Those flowers are made of steel!
You're so cruel, sisters!
No! I can't do it!
Just think about how the flowers feel!
What's that monster doing here?
Where is it? Where is it? Where's the monster?
Seed-planting!
He planted seeds on him!
Bo-bobo!
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Man-eating Flowers!!!
What!?
Eat him up, Man-eating Flowers!
No! Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo!
They ate him right down to the bone!
Stop the bullshit!
Dammit! That was a decoy!
Where's the real one?
I'm back!
You gotta be kidding me!
Bo-bobo!
Seed-planting Counter!
Trying to copy my attack? That's not possible!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Flowers!!!
America!
Shut up!
America's the best!
They're uncontrollable!
America's... the best!
How is this America?
And now...
Fukui Spike-planting!
You can plant flowers too?
What the hell?
What the hell is this!?
They're staring at you!
The Ms. Don Patches love young men!
They're staring at you! They're staring at you!
They'll stare at you till kingdom come!
That's annoying!
So the Former Hair Hunters don't have much to offer.
Time to take you back to the past where you belong!
What!?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
What is this capsule?
A time capsule?
Get in!
Space Rocket Liftoff!
But what about the past?
Planet Bobobo
Ow, ow, ow...
What kind of planet is this?
Dammit! This planet is the worst!
U.S.S. Patch
Damn you, Bo-bobo!
They're back already!
Take this!
Amazing!
Bo-bobo's controlling the fight!
I'm melting! I'm melting here!
Tennosuke!
Damn, you're so irritating!
The Hair Kingdom are still as irritating as they were a hundred years ago!
The Hair Kingdom a hundred years ago?
My distant ancestors...
What the hell kind of image is that?
You're romanticizing it way too much!
It actually... was more like this!
Time for breakfast!
That's irritating!
Hey! Hey!
So what about my ancestors?
Hey! Hey! C'mon!
Huh?
Hey!
Probably confeito or something.
Confeito or something...
This revelation
deeply wounded Patchie's heart.
Drama:
Weekend Wife
She could not tell her husband Bo-bobo about this.
Patchie could only tremble through the weekend.
To Be Continued
I have nothing more to say to you fools!
Fist of the Myriad Blossom Secret Technique:
Myriad Scattershot Machine Gun!!!
You can't dodge these ten thousand poisoned seeds!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Wandering Crow Caw-taro
What was that?
It can't be!
He dodged my Myriad Scattershot Machine Gun!
Not only that...
He's hitting them back!
Hey, it's hard to eat these without tea!
But that's poisoned!
I have you now!
Dammit!
Where are you taking me, piece of shit?
To find what there is beyond the sound barrier.
W-What!?
They found me!
You're speeding!
Bo-bobo!
Tennosuke's...
Tennosuke's in danger!
Bo-bobo!
Huh?
What's with your indifferent attitude?
Dammit!
Tennosuke!
Yes?
He's eating smelt!
He's okay!
What's with his techniques?
They're all complete rubbish!
How could someone like this have shown up after a hundred years?
It's impossible... It's impossible!
Fist of the Myriad Blossom Final Secret Technique:
Multitudinous Man-eating Flower Hell!!!
Bo-bobo!
Eat him down to the bone!
You're being eaten, too!
Now I'll have to become the sun and dry out all the flowers!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Sun Flash!!
That "Sun"? No way!
They're dried up!
This can't be happening...
That was my Final Secret Technique...
Now time to finish you off!
You must atone for three things.
First!
You hunted the hair of innocents!
Second!
You insulted my homeland, the Hair Kingdom!
Third!
You hurt my friends!
Dammit! Put me down! Put me down!
And to atone for those sins...
You will become the lone flower that blooms in the desert!
He did it!
Bo-bobo won!
Good grief.
Feels like mayonnaise.
What's going on?
This can't be happening!
He was the captain of G-block!
Meanwhile...
Is this the Third's cold sleep chamber?
What a massive aura!
The Third will awaken shortly.
What?
But what an impressive one he is!
He has such an aura even when sealed!
After a long, hard battle,
Bo-bobo defeated Kikunojo, captain of Former G-block.
But no one knew that they were about
to face even greater foes than ever before!
No one... no one...
Aquarium
Meanwhile...
Hey, Mama...
What's that?
Hmm... Perhaps a new species of otter?
You guys...
To be continued!
Tune in next time!
Next time!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, planting seeds now will make them grow big in the future!
And something lucky will happen next time you go to the supermarket!
If you tied, make sure you can de-bone your fish yourself!
And if you lost, if you see Dengakuman at the aquarium, be sure to cheer him on!
Beauty! That man will finally return!
Who's "that man"?
Yakkun? It's Yakkun, right?
Not at all, idiot!
Then who? Who is it?
The answer is a hundred Hair Hunters.
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Hatenko's Back ♪ and Onwards, Rampaging Gadget! In two parts!
Hatenko's Back ♪
Forming Factions and Breaking Friendships!?
Onwards, Rampaging Gadget!
Blast Aside Friends and Foe Alike!!
Oh, it's just Hatenko.