Hajike TV
Bo-bobo
Shopping
It's time for Hajike TV's Bo-bobo Shopping!
And here we have our special product of the day!
It's the Bo-bobo Costume Set!
Product No.001
Bo-bobo Costume Set
Special!!
Hajike
It's amazing! It's super trendy!
But wait, there's more! Order now...
and you'll get the 5-Color Nose Hair Set for absolutely free!
Free
5-Color Nose Hair Set
(Red, Blue, Yellow, Green, Pink)
You just can't pass up a deal like this!
It's the perfect product!
You can't buy nose hairs...
with money!
We're ever so sorry!
We both lied!
They lied?
I really wanted that, nah-la...
You actually wanted it?
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
A hundred years ago,
the Margarita Empire became the greatest empire in the world in just four days
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
thanks to Tsururiina III and his generation.
And now, the Third's generation was awakening.
DispROSE
Heppokomaru
leveled upllll
a whole lot.lllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllll
In the Holy Land of Eternal, said to be capable of powering up Fist users,
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Tennosuke's anger
against Ne gave
him a limit break.
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Softon attained
sacred power
by the gracelllllll
of Babylon.lllllllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Don Patchlllllll
gained 60lllll
majjimo.llll
llllllllllllllll
Majjimo
Bo-bobo and his friends engaged in combat
Fist of the Myriad Blossoms Secret Technique:
Rosacuda!!
against Roselily Kikunojo, captain of G-block a hundred years ago.
Help us, Bo-bobo!
I'm melting! I'm melting! I'm gonna melt away!
Rosacuda!
Supermarket
Super Bo-bobo has been born!
Wait, is that what you meant by Super?
Don't get ahead of yourself, trash!
Take this!
What?
Concentrated Fire!!!
And to atone for those sins...
You will become the lone flower that blooms in the desert!!!
After a long, hard battle, Bo-bobo defeated Kikunojo with the power-up of love.
Emperor from 100 Years Ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Hair Hunters from
100 Years Ago
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
llllHair Hunters fromllllllll
100 Years Agollllllllllllllllll
Shaina
Jubei
Kikunojo
Otter
Gorgon
Nihil
But Bo-bobo had no idea that the tremendously powerful Tsururiina III
was about to awaken.
Hatenko's
Back
♪
Forming
Factions
and Breaking Friendships!?
Alright, guys!
Time to crush those pathetic Hair Hunters!
Hell yeah!
But we don't know where they are located!
Well, I do.
Who's there?
Want me to tell you?
Hatenko?
Good grief.
You guys are totally useless without me.
Boss!
I missed you so much!
Hey, stop! Not in public!
You're one to call us useless.
What's happening now?
The Top Brass, the captains from A to F-block, are awakening.
You'd better stand back if you value your life!
We've lost contact with Kikunojo, who left to find the remnant of the Hair Kingdom.
Former E-block Captain Combat Blues
It's possible he was defeated.
Former B-block Captain Lambada
What in tarnation?
Former F-block Captain Ujikin TOKIO
Kikunojo got defeated? That ain't possible!
How sad.
So there are still losers in the world that defy the Hair Hunters?
Former C-block Captain Jeda the Wind God
The Third will awaken shortly.
We must capture the man from the Hair Kingdom before his awakening, at all costs!
Former A-block Captain Fishcake
I now invoke the Triple Hunters Formation!
Triple Hunters.
Triple Hunters
It is the ultimate Hair Hunter Captain formation, consisting of a team of three captains.
The three captains' powers combined can wreak terror thousands of times over.
You really sure we have to use the Triple Hunters?
I'll execute my mission with those two.
I'm fine on my own.
Getting stubborn I see, Lambada!?
And as for you guys, get moving already!
He suddenly snapped at us!
Captains.
Allow me to lure out the man of the Hair Kingdom.
For I have prepared a special battle field.
So you're the present emperor? I see you've been prepared.
Meanwhile, back with Bo-bobo and friends...
Hajike
You chickens think ya can take on the Hajike Gang?
Hettoko Gang
The Hajike Gang is nothin'!
Twirly Head Faction
The Twirly-Heads are the future!
Hatenko had blended in perfectly with the group perfectly.
What's with this super-tense atmosphere?
If we keep playing around, the next enemy will...
There's a whole lot of enemies!
That's perfect!
We just have to head in the direction they're coming from, and we'll reach their base!
Ready, guys? The battle's starting! Let's all do that!
What would "that" be?
Idiot!
It's our usual thing!
Down with the Hair Hunters!
No, this is the first time you've done this!
And there are two weird guys!
Boss!
Let's do our traditional battle cry, too!
Alright!
Hajike Hajike Hajike Hajike Hajike Hajike...
Let's Hajike it up!
This is a tradition?
Let's roll out!
You're literally rolling?
Naughty Attack!
Naughty
Not you, though.
Onward!
Hatenko!
Is this the way to the Former Hair Hunters base?
Yeah, we're going in the right direction.
Before we get there, let me make this clear.
The Hajike Gang is the strongest!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
LOCK!
What did he do? They stopped moving for some reason!
He's pretty strong!
Yeah. He's not that shabby.
Is that all you got? Then it's my turn to rock!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
ROCK Soul
This is my soul!
You rock!
You're so dreamy!
They've all turned into groupies!
Not bad.
Long live the Twirly Heads!
That's good! But the Hettoko Gang's still in the running!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Man Boomerang
Step on me.
There's too many of them!
Perfect! Let's break through them with the Hajike robots!
Good thinking, Boss!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
100 Combined Hajike Robots
100 Combined? That's way too many!
Hajike Combination!
Ka-chink
Ka-chink  Ka-chink  Ka-chink  Ka-chink  Ka-chink
Shut up already!
Click
Complete!
It's off-balance!
And there's two or three left over!
The whole thing was pointless!
Goal
Last
There it is! The goal's in sight!
He has to be the last one!
Crap!
What do you say whichever team beats him rules?
Fine! But the Twirly Head Faction is nothing to mess with!
Don't forget the Hettoko Gang!
I'm the leader!
No friggin' way...
I never thought they'd be this strong...
That's so close! Who was it?
I'd rather have no teams be on top...
From this day forth, you are the Dengaku Gang!
It's Dengaku!
He got back from the aquarium at some point!
Why do I feel like I've been here before...?
This is my...
Maerchentic Amusement Park
It's my second home, A-block Base!
Run-down
I'm glad you could make it, Bo-bobo.
Tsururiina IV!
I've prepared a special stage for your defeat today.
Stage? You mean this amusement park?
My A-block base!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
This is the battle stage worthy of your showdown with the Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago...
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX!
Broadcasting
Room
Keep Quiet in the
Broadcasting Room!
We will await you in the ninety-nine attractions of Hell!
Remnant of the Hair Kingdom!
Let us put an end to our hundred-year grudge!
Grudge? I don't care about that!
I'm just gonna crush the Hair Hunters!
Restaurant
Kitty Land
Ice Cream
Let's start off here!
There's the enemy!
Nice to meetcha, Bo-bobo, Remnant of the Hair Kingdom.
Former K-block Captain
Chisuisui
We're gonna do this by the Triple Hunter rules.
It'll be a three-on-three battle. Choose yer fighters.
Former P-block Captain
Star Saber
I ain't really gonna care who shows up.
Coz none o' ya are goin' home alive!
It's the Hajike Gang's turn to shine!
Don't mess with the Twirly Head Faction!
They ain't listenin'!
Just choose your members and fight!
Who are you supposed to be?
Then I'll go!
Go.
Yes, Boss!
This is for A-block Base!
Is this three-man team gonna be alright?
What happened to the Dengaku Gang, hey?
It's touch-and-go! Bang! Bang! Bang!
He's getting super annoying!
The battle stage is here!
Finally, the heated battle of fate a hundred years in the making is about to begin!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Right now, Bo-bobo
is fighting here, in the Rampaging Gadget area of Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX, nah-la!
The team of three led by the newly awakened
Former F-block Captain, Ujikin TOKIO.
How will Team Bo-bobo face them?
And I really don't know about their teamwork...
Ujikin TOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Let the battle begin, nah-na-la!
Onwards, Rampaging
Gadget!
Blast Aside Friends
and Foe
Alike
!!
Onwards, Rampaging
Gadget!
Blast Aside Friends
and Foe
Alike
This here's the terrifyin' Rampagin' Gadget Area.
Now let's begin our deadly battle.
Team Hajike!
Twirly-head!
Hettoko Gang!
They've already begun!
Twirly Head Faction!
Guys, stop this meaningless rivalry!
This is perfect for us.
Fist of Summer Secret Technique: Ice-Cold Ice
Alright, take this!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Snacktime!!!
Ka-chink!
Tennosuke!
Those who get hit by mah Ice-Cold Ice all freeze up!
No problem here!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Tokoroten Press
Tennosuke Returns
Come forth!
Gadget!
What was that thing?
He is the rampaging mech, known as Gadget.
Gadget
These plates here make up Gadget's tracks.
If you don't plan out your moves carefully, you'll be blasted away!
No way!
This is getting out of hand!
You can call me Chisuisui the Swift!
Fighting here is a cakewalk for us!
Calculate, calculate!
Barbecue Bomber!
Barbecue House
Beef Life
How dare ya do in Chisuisui!
We'll send you flying, too!
Ujikin Toe Kick!
That bastard!
How can a mere Ujikintoki like him use techniques like htat?
He's strong!
Don'cha mess wit' Ujikintoki!
Too late.
We'll have to stop that giant-faced mech first!
Okay!
Right! Let's go!
Stop
Stop!
Falalel, Palalel, Stop Time!
He's pretty much doing this alone!
Take this seriously!
But we were!
There's much more to this area than that.
By changing around the plates,
you can change Gadget's course!
Crap! It's coming back!
Then I'll just...
use this plate...
He's gonna change the course!
and make a house of cards!
What the hell?
What's the point of that?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Pleasant Collapsing Plates
Time to change the course!
This is bad!
We have to rearrange the plates somehow!
Leave this puzzle to me!
You done yet?
Just a second.
What the hell are you doing?
How's my photography?
Oh, you've got something here.
Die!
But I believe I can do better!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The Legendary Photo Op
That's the fishiest secret technique yet!
Dammit!
We got distracted by the photos and didn't realize that the path drops off!
Hell yeah! Now go!
Serves you right!
If we keep going forward...
Forward...
The field's gonna explode!
What's wrong with this field?
Guys!
Memo
What an ingenious rule!
He's become the Battle Nerd again!
Hey, watch the battle, okay?
The plates are rearranging themselves!
What an intense area!
Worthless fools!
Ya guys piss yer pants or somethin'?
Your teammates are shaving you, you know.
That bastard's getting ahead of himself!
He's pissing me off.
We have no choice. Let's team up.
Enough of this clique war.
Alright! We're playing as a team from now on!
One of you focus on operating Gadget!
The other two will take them down!
That's a good plan.
But who's gonna...
Leave it...
Number (Nu) One
to me!
He's wearing another weird Nu thing!
Now then, time to make a path for you two.
It's still weird even when you try to act cool!
Nu Simulation!!!
Tennosuke's Quick Facts
Tennosuke's Quick Facts!
When I wear a "nu" headband, I feel smarter
When I wear a "Nu" headband, I feel smarter!
Alright! I see it now!
Now! Go, you guys!
Yeah!
You asshole!
Secret Technique: Arrow of Atonement!!!
Ya sonuvagun! How dare ya take out Chisuisui!
Fist of Summer Secret Technique:
Midsummer Countryside!
The scenery changed!
Fist of Summer Secret Technique:
Midsummer Countryside
Man, it's hot...
It's so hot I feel heavy...
I don't feel like moving...
I sure wish I could eat something cold...
I have some Ujikintoki for you.
Go ahead and enjoy.
That looks tasty!
Idiot! Ya fell fer it!
I'm super-spicy!
Now, eat 'n' writhe in pain!
Oh whoops, I forgot the ketchup.
Ya eat it with ketchup?
Well, yer free to put whatcha want on me.
Hurry an' come back!
Hurry! Eat me!
Not the cat!
It's fine. Everythin's good.
I've been through worse.
What was I doing?
Come on! What's the matter?
He's strong!
He's pressuring him! He might just win!
Hatenko!
Boss!
You need to...
Pump up the Hajike!
Hajike
Shut up!
That idiot! He had a lead on him! What about Hatenko?
I understand, Boss!
He's gone crazy!
Chirp, steamed buns! Chirp, steamed buns!
And there he goes!
My name is Star Saber!
Megaton Punch
Guess I can't pull it off as well as the Boss.
No way! Was Hatenko trying to use that legendary technique?
That weird attack was legendary?
There ain't no sign of Bo-bobo.
I'm sure he's around here somewhere!
I'm gonna take 'im down fer sure!
No one screws with Ujikin TOKIO an' lives ta tell the tale!
Where've ya gone, Bo-bobo!?
I'm right here!
Playtime is over!
Now time to pass the judgment of hair upon you!
Don't get ahead o' yerself!
Ya haven't yet seen what we're really made of!
The battle is truly ebbing and flowing!
Upon which team will the goddess of victory smile upon?
Hold it...
How're we supposed ta fight here!?
He just snapped!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, live life on the edge and you'll seize your chance!
Your lucky food is barbecue at a family get-together!
If you tied, helping your friends will eventually mean helping yourself.
And if you lost, don't eat shaved ice in a hurry, or you'll get brain freeze!
The new trio has started a sci-fi battle!
Then it's time for Plan Z!
Let's go, Tennosuke!
Yeah!
Wait, am I just bait?
I'll take you on a world tour as a reward!
I'll do it! Hold it, am I going as a station wagon?
You seem to get stuck in those kinds of roles.
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Changing Clothes for a Sci-Fi Battle!
Behold the New Trio!!
Unpredictable World Tour!
Let's Take Off on the Love-Love Wagon!!
Changing Clothes for a Sci-Fi Battle! and Unpredictable World Tour! In two parts!
It's all I ever do.