Time to change costumes, sci-fi style!
Triple Hunt Secret Technique:
Sci-Fi Change!
Complete!
They're going sci-fi on us!
If they're gonna go sci-fi, we'll go sci-fi right back at them!
Sci-Fi Change!
Complete!
Huh? Where's everyone else?
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
I messed up my transformation...
I actually lied.
I transformed into the Invisible Man!
What about the others?
Got a problem?
Not at all.
Huh? You haven't changed at all.
Hey!
All you listeners out there! Thanks for tuning in!
That's FM!
Sci-Fi and FM don't have anything in common but the "F"...
And with that, let's start the show!
We'll start of with a fresh, upbeat song!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Former A-Block Captain
Fishcake
Former B-Block Captain
Lambada
Former C-Block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former D-Block Captain
Former E-Block Captain
Combat Blues
Former F-Block Captain
Ujikin TOKIO
Former G-Block Captain
Roselily Kikunojo
Tsuru Tsururiin
Former A-Block Ca
Fishcake
Former B-Block Ca
Lambada
Former C-Block Ca
Jeda the Wind
Former D-Block Ca
Former E-Block Ca
Combat Blues
Former F-Block Ca
Ujikin TOKIOll
Former G-Block Ca
Roselily Kikun
The battle between Tsuru Tsururiina III's generation of Hair Hunters
who have awakened from their 100-year slumber,
and Bo-bobo, remnant of the Hair Kingdom, has been taken to new heights!
The stage of the battle is...
Maerchentic Amusement Park
Wow! The memories! It's my old A-block Base!
I'm glad you could make it, Bo-bobo.
Tsururiina IV!
I've prepared a special stage for your defeat today.
Stage? You mean this amusement park?
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX!
N-No way...
This is the Rampaging Gadget area of Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX.
The rules are a three-on-three Triple Hunters death match.
From the former Hair Hunters
are Former F-block Captain Ujikin TOKIO,
Former K-block Captain Chisuisui,
and Former P-block Captain Star Saber.
Facing them are Bo-bobo, Hatenko, and Tokoro Tennosuke.
Ujikin TOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
This is for A-block Base!
Changing Clothes
for a
Sci-Fi Showdown!
Behold!
Our
New Trio!!
And so the battle raged on!
Megaton Punch! Megaton Punch! Punch!
It's the Gadget! The Gadget's coming this way!
Let's call a truce for now.
We've gotta change its course!
Guess we got no choice. Let's get this over with!
Oh, crap! Just noticed we're one plate short!
Placeholder!
This'll work like a charm!
Don't mind!
I can't tell if they're on good terms or bad terms...
It rode on a different plate than normal,
and that caused the entire field to explode!
What the hell was that for, you jacket freak!?
My bad.
You're wide open!
Die!
Vampiric Killing Arts:
Bloodsucking!!
Well?
Drink up, my boy.
You're sick!
Megaton Punch!!
Is that all you got? Then take this!
Dot-eyed Ponch!!
That makes no sense!
Are you alright?
Alright, let's all recover our energy!
Recover their energy?
Triple Hunt Secret Technique:
Speed-Eating Recovery!!
Well, what you think?
My head hurts...
Oh, my God!
What else did you expect?
It's on! Now it's our turn for a collaboration secret technique!
Listen up, Hatenko!
Tennosuke and I are about to make the ultimate key, so put it to good use!
You can count on me!
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique:
Key Change!!
Now, fill me up with power!
Air
He's gonna burst!
All that's left is to harden Tennosuke, and it'll be complete!
Here we go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Coating of Life!
Please let me have Tenko's hand in marriage!
Father
I won't let you have my daughter.
He hardened!
It's all ready! Use this, Hatenko!
Use it!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique...
I can't use this, dammit!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
I Can't Use This Dammit!
Hatenko and Tennosuke's Collaborative Secret Technique: I Can't Use This Dammit!
That was incredible!
You're the incredible one here, Hekkun...
I give you my blessing.
Cold and Delicious
Tokoroten
Thank you, Father!
Then allow me to power us up with my special ability!
Time to change costumes, sci-fi style!
Sci-Fi Style?
Triple Hunt Secret Technique:
Sci-Fi Change!
Complete!
The shaved ice became a fortress!?
How could this be?
We're all doomed.
And you guys are supporting characters!?
You fools! This form has tripled our power!
This can't be good.
We'll have to assemble our power, too!
Bo-bobo! Tokoroten!
Oh, are we filming now?
You bastards...
Sci-Fi Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Heavy Smoke!!
Don't try and pass that off as some weird technique!
It's smoky...
Hey, it's working.
Now! Megaton Punch!
Don't even bother trying.
What!?
I'll pay you back hundredfold!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
There's a fly on your head!
It's really nasty being bitten by a fly in winter.
It's real itchy...
Outta my way!
I'm so bored up here...
I shouldn'ta turned into a giant fortress...
Are you stupid or something!?
Ah, hell!
I'm supposed ta be a man-made fortress!
Fortresses ain't supposed ta think! I gotta stay in character!
But a fortress should be able to join the battle.
Like a fortress...
Y'all are my enemy, fortress! Prepare yerselves, fortress!
That's nothing like a fortress!
And that verbal tic really ticks me off!
Can y'all take a guess...
what kind o' beans my Ujikintoki is made of?
What?
That's an obvious one!
Well lemme tell ya.
They're coffee beans!
Fist of Summer Secret Technique:
Ingredient Machine Gun!!
They're supposed to be Adzuki beans!
If they're not, then you're not ujikintoki!
I didn't wanna hear the truth...
That's Captain Ujikin TOKIO for you!
Wait, so he's not an ujikintoki?
Now you know the power of ujikintoki!
He's really not an ujikintoki?
Now we'll have to resort to Plan Z.
Plan Z?
It's a difficult plan that requires dedicated teamwork.
Plan Z
The method is all written up in this book.
OK, I'll do it!
Plan Z
Step 1. Use Tennosuke as bait.
Step 2. Abandon him.
End.
This is bullshit!
You're no match for us in sci-fi form!
And how is that sci-fi?
I'll show you what real sci-fi looks like!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Boei Cinema
Bobobo Scope
Full Color
Bo-bobo Theater
Sai Fai
Directed by: Habatake Hiroki
Starring: Ken Bobobo
Patch Tsuruda
Tanago Tokoroten
Heppoko Saburo
Beauty Yoshie
Matsukata Hatenko
Noboru Softon
Dengaku Shoko
Cameo Appearance by Service Mifune
A man is at his finest when he Hajikes!
Sai Fai.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
How is any part of that costume sci-fi?
Turns out it is sci-fi!
Alright! Let's crush the Shaved Ice Team!
Enemy fortress in sight!
They're invadin' me!
Entrance
Captain! I found the entrance!
Since when did I have an entrance?
Alright, men! Let's take over from the inside!
They went inside!
We're being invaded! Prepare the counterattack!
Go for it, my insides!
That was a corny near miss!
There's the fuel storage!
Once we take the adzuki beans, the fortress will fall!
Ah, hell! They found it!
Coffee
The adzuki beans are mine!
Those aren't adzuki beans!
What?
What's going on in there?
Let's finish this off with our Collaboration Secret Technique!
Key Change!
Bo-bobo! Harden it for me!
Yo, Tennosuke!
I'm the super star that you're a huge fan of!
S-Super star!?
Super Three Fists Secret Technique:
Gelatin Hard Attack!!
Amazing! They're fighting back with some real power!
Their powers are finally as one!
I-Impossible! We're back to normal!
Your brutish teamwork is nothing to us!
After this break,
Is the super-fun!
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX.
A three-on-three Triple Hunters battle had begun in the Rampaging Gadget area.
Bo-bobo, Tennosuke, and Hatenko
faced off against Ujikin TOKIO, Chisuisui, and Star Saber.
Ujikin TOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Ujikin TOKIO's team attacked in sci-fi style,
but Bo-bobo and his friends fought back in sci-fi style in return.
That's as far from sci-fi as it gets!
In the end, Bo-bobo's team combined their power,
and crushed the enemy fortress!
It's all lies...
Unpredictable
World Tour!
Love ❤
Wagon!
Let's
on the
take off
Now to finish you off!
I ain't givin' up! I ain't gonna lose!
Is that so?
If I done lose to them...
I'll have ta go back ta those days!
Back when I wouldn't sell!
Hey, wait for me!
Come on, let's swim!
Watch Out for Wild Ujikintoki!!
Danger
Ujikintoki frequent this ocean
Hey, look at this!
Hey, honey! Wanna taste of me?
Oh no!
I couldn't sell today...
A brood of jellyfish!
I ain't goin' back to those hellish days!
Your past was nothing.
What?
Tennosuke. Tell him about your past.
King of Tragedy
Alright, let me tell you the tale of when I was on sale.
Three years ago, in a certain supermarket...
Buy me!
Somebody buy me!
Dammit!
That Tennosuke's coming out again!
Hey!
Shit! They saw me!
We told you to stay in there!
You should be grateful we're even giving you space!
Push!
How tragic...
That reminds me of another story.
Let's see...
I just need tokoroten.
Tokoroten... tokoroten...
What the blue hell are you doing!?
And that's not even half of it.
What an unthinkable past...
Hang in there, Captain Ujikin!
Well? How'd you like them apples?
Then I guess I'll just have ta take out yer friends first!
Eat this!
Shaved Ice of Hell Attack!!
And then I'll eat 'em!
Well?
Betcha didn't see that one comin'!
I ain't got no shaved ice to give ya!
You dirty bastard!
First you challenge me to a three-on-three battle, but then you attack my friends, and on top of that...
you eat your own attack yourself! How cowardly of you!
Fine, then! If you like being unpredictable so much...
I'll take you to an unpredictable world!
What the hell?
Fist of the Nose Hair
Ultimate Secret Technique:
Paranormal Phenomena 7 Traveler!!
W-What is this about?
They're showing scenes from different countries around the world!
You will now experience seven paranormal phenomena!
Your guides will be me and...
Hamchin!
Hamchin
Let's get moving.
What the hell is this!?
Love
Alright! Everyone in the love-love wagon!
Getting packed, getting packed...
You stay out of this!
Wait! Wait! But I'm the guide!
First destination is Australia!
We made it!
What the hell am I looking at!?
It's Australia!
Bank of Koala
The Koala Times
Koala Bus
Eucalyptus Station
EucalyDrink
Aussie Ice
This is just your mental image of Australia, ain't it?
Hey, you!
There are no paranormal phenomena around here, mate!
Yer existence itself is a pure paranormal phenomenon!
What're they pissed fer?
Paranormal Phenomenon 1:
The Rage of Australia!!
We're ever so sorry!
Moving on!
The next paranormal phenomenon is...
America 's
Smith 's Room!!
How is this even a paranormal phenomenon!
Look at that!
There's a smiling face appearing on the wall! I'm scared!
But that's just a stain!
Evil spirits, begone!
You talking about us!?
Get out, afro-man!
Smith, you bastard!
And all that's left...
is cleaning the wall!
What's goin' on!?
And the third paranormal phenomenon is...
The New Zealand
Cyclone!!
Finally a proper one!
Amazing! It's super amazing, Ma!
It really is impressive!
Then please, take a closer look!
That's cruel!
What immense wind pressure!
But looks like we done lucked out!
We git to experience a real cyclone!
You were makin' it?
This isn't the real thing!
Power Up!
What's going on?
Boss battle!
And the fourth...
is a paranormal phenomenon in Japan!
What's this? Nothin's comin' out!
Look over there!
How cute!
Cute!
Mass Outbreak of Schoolgirls!!
No!
Can I get your email address?
Hey! Where are y'all takin' us?
They're super cute!
Seriously!
You bunch of liars!
And the fifth is in India!
Whaddya know? It actually looks like India.
The fifth paranormal phenomenon is the Curry Robot!
Paranormal Phenomenon Curry Robot:
Super-Spicy Roux Beam!!
It burns! It burns on my skin!
Alright, maggots!
You've seen plenty of paranormal phenomena, but this one's the last one!
Let's go! Last one!
Morocco
The Mysterious Country, Morocco!
Is this Morocco?
This is just your imagination, isn't it?
Doesn't it look just like Morocco?
I'll beat you, you asshole!
Now let's go see Morocco's paranormal phenomenon!
Trolley of Morocco!!
That's just a play on words!
How dare you leave me behind!
Ah! It's Hamchin!
And the seventh is the...
Paranormal Phenomenon of Tennosuke!!
It's straight outta a horror movie!
Well? Feel like giving up yet?
Stop bullshitting us!
You have no more paranormal phenomena left!
We've experienced all seven of them!
We survived through 'em all!
Now we'll beat you down!
You fools!
This Secret Technique
has a hidden eighth paranormal phenomenon!
Take this! The extra-dimensional paranormal phenomenon I'm about to cause!
Bo-bobo Eruption!!!
They're back!
Rampaging Gadget Area
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Sabe
Bo-bobo
Tennosu
Hatenko
Star Saber, Chisuisui, and Ujikin TOKIO are defeated.
Yes!
We cleared this stage!
Now let's just keep at it and crush the former Hair Hunters!
Alright, guys! Let's move out!
Yeah!
The three-on-three Triple-Hunt battles with the Former Hair Hunters...
What kind of foe will stand before Bo-bobo next?
And who, who, and who will fight from Bo-bobo's team!?
I wanna know, I wanna know, I wanna know!
I wanna know... but how long's this Bo-bobo Eruption gonna last?
Oh, and...
I'll go with that girl.
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, go out with a costume change and you'll have megaton good luck!
Your lucky food is discount tokoroten from the supermarket!
If you tied, when you go by coffee beans, make sure you don't buy adzuki beans by mistake.
And if you lost, you won't be at your best if you get stiff with nervousness!
The next stage is a water slide?
Don Patch, I have something to confess.
I was the one who stole your slice of cake!
Oh, that was you, Bo-bobo? How mean!
But why now?
Well, since we're on a water slide, I thought I'd let it be water under the bridge.
Nice one!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Water Slide of Hell! and Charge, Love-love Miss Torpedo! In two parts!
The Water Slide of Hell!
The Enemy is a Hot Sunfish and Swimsuit Gals!?
Charge, Love-love Miss Torpedo! I will Not Allow Any Foolishness!!
It's just an ordinary pun!