Today's Doggies
Woof.
Crap!
This show is all about dogs!
W-Woof!
Today's Breakfast
Today's break...
Breakfast!?
That's it! This is perfect! I'm fine the way I am...
as tokoroten!
Thank you, everyone!
I've finally become breakfast!
Today's Breakfast
was going to be this tokoroten
but it was expired
so I didn't eat it.
Honestly, those guys!
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Tsururiina IV has prepared a battle stage:
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX!
Right! And here, in the Rampaging Gadget Area,
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Sabe
Bo-bobo
Tennosu
Hatenko
there was a very fearsome battle of sweat and blood!
Let's take another look at it, nah-na-la!
Can y'all take a guess... what kind o' beans my Ujikintoki is made of?
What?
They're coffee beans!
They're supposed to be Adzuki beans!
Then that means you're not ujikintoki!
I didn't wanna hear the truth...
Bo-bobo and his friends faced them...
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Paranormal Phenomena 7 Traveler!!
The Rage of Australia!!
Mass Outbreak of Schoolgirls!!
Cute!
No!
And finally...
This is a symbol of our friendship!
The Triangle Flash of Love, Justice, and Desire!
Well done, you warriors of the light...
And that's pretty much how they defeated them.
No, no, no! Don't be so ridiculous!
It was really more like this!
Bo-bobo Eruption!!!
Rampaging Gadget Area
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Sabe
Bo-bobo
Tennosu
Hatenko
But meanwhile...
A mysterious man was looking down on Bo-bobo!
I'll go with that girl.
The Water Slide of
Hell!
The Enemy
is a Hot
Sunfish
and Swimsuit Gals
!?
Alright, people! Now let's proceed to defeat our next enemy!
By "proceed" you mean "procession?"
Rampaging Gadget Area
We all made it!
Water Slide
Our next foe is right here!
At a giant water slide?
Has Mercy
So you've finally marched to my ocean of Hell, Bo-bobo?
Former E-block Captain Combat Blues
I've been waiting for you with two of the strongest captains!
But I don't see the enemy anywhere around!
Where could they be?
Welcome.
The enemy?
I've been waiting patiently for you.
It's you!? Say it ain't so!
Beach volleyball!
Pathetic fools. You should never let down your guard in enemy territory!
Just you wait!
Beach volleyball!
You yellow bastards!
And you call yourself soldiers, low-life cowards?
Time to begin Operation Water Slide of Hell!
Beauty!
Fist of Traps Secret Technique:
Hell Delivery!!
What do you think you're doing!?
I'll guide you all to the battlefield of Hell!
The water's flowing in reverse!
That means we're gonna be going up the slide!
I'm getting swept away!
I'm getting swept away by the changing times!
Shut your damn mouth!
Beauty!
Don Patch!
Let me handle the position of the heroine.
Now get lost!
What the hell are you doing!?
Help me, Bo-bobo!
Beauty!
You bastard... How dare you do that to Beauty!
The name of this battlefield is "Requiem of the Battlefield."
Requiem of the Battlefield
It is an arena of death where we ride the current upwards and fight our way to the top.
Now, we're going by the Triple-Hunter rule!
Triple Hunter
Triple-Hunters Rule.
It is the Hair Hunters' ultimate formation consisting of a three-man team.
I've picked two of your contestants for you.
Now pick the last one!
Alright! I'm going up!
Wait, Bo-bobo!
Don't stop me, Tennosuke!
I'm not...  I'm just melting over here... so can you save me first?
What a coward, to drag Beauty into the front lines...
Combat Blues... I will never forgive you!
So I guess it's our turn to go.
Say "Ahhhh!"
Do you even want to fight!?
Former J-block Captain Swimsuit Girl
Former W-block Captain Swimsuit Gal
Wait a minute, you're captains!?
We're going up!
You and me...
A midsummer love...
Wa-Wa-Wa-Water Slide!
A rock!?
Don Patch!
Beauty! Hey, Beauty!
You OK there?
Bo-bobo! You came for me!
Damn, this is hard!
What are you trying to do?
That's way too hard on the horse!
Horse!
You're wide open!
Take this!
Fist of Traps Secret Technique:
Hand Grenades of the Soul!
What!?
There was water below us?
Dammit...
Kaboom!
He's making the explosion noises!?
Returning fire!
B-B-B-Beam!
Ow! I'm hit!
What in the true insanity of hell is he doing!?
Captain Combat Blues!
I'll feel better if you pet me...
There, there...
Are you really called Combat Blues!? Please change your name!
That was a close call.
In some way, I guess.
Alright, now chew on this!
Fist of Traps Secret Technique: Piranha Hell!!
Piranha Hell!!
But those are sunfish.
Sunfish
Alright! We'll return fire with piranhas, too!
I said, those are sunfish.
Sunfish
Go!
They changed their course!
But where did they go?
Crab:
Let's Cut Japan
Amberjack:
I'll Do It
Shark:
I Am Japan
Salmon:
Power of the Ocean,
Power of the River
Starfish:
The Power of the Star
Pufferfish:
Expanding Dreams
Squid
Sea Bream:
High-Class Government
Vote for me!
I'm counting on all of your support
Voting
Box
They're at the voting booth!
Oh, right! I forgot that today was fish election day!
They can't be fighting on an important election!
Squid Elected!!
I will change Japan!
Congratulations!
That's just stupid!
Captain Combat!
Come back to us!
I'll let you sleep with your head in my lap!
He's sprinting back up! What's his problem?
In that case...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Magical Girl Denbo-chan
Photobook
Denbo-chan Photobook!
Magical Girl Denbo-chan!
Don't forget to buy her CD, too!
Captain Combat!
I'm sorry.
Fight!
Engage!!
He's speaking in military terms?
You're putting up a good fight.
He's pretty tough...
Now it's my turn!
Fist of Traps Secret Technique: Killer Dam!
Fall!
Killer Dam
What just happened?
This is dangerous! We're gonna fall if we stay on! What do we do?
Alright, Beauty!
Special Seat
Get on my head!
In there!?
Let's fly!
With fans? That's impossible!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Frantic Wind Manipulation!!
Huh?
And land!
We made it! Good job, Bo-bobo!
You're late.
I've cut you off now.
What!?
What kind of helicopter is that!?
I'll have you begone!
I'll use the super-water pressure for...
Fist of Traps
Secret Technique:
High-Speed Water Clones!!
How's this!?
He multiplied himself!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Carp Climbing the Waterfall!!
This guy's powerful...
The power gap should be obvious by now.
Blues Helicopter!
Toss me my weapons box!
Has Mercy
Here you are!
Weapon
Plop
Annoying.
It's all over!
Within this box is none other than the greatest weapon in the world!
With this weapon, I'll have powered-up dramatically!
This is bad. Beauty's still by my side!
Can I protect her as I fight?
What could the greatest weapon in the world be?
Come out, my weapon!
Torpedo-colored
Life
Softon
Love, love, Softon... Softon, love...
Love, love, lovely, lovely-ly...
Softon lovely!
Imbecile!
Captain Combat!
Miss Torpedo!
I will not permit the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because I'm a torpedo!
It truly is a battlefield!
Amidst this cruel fight, the greatest weapon in the world turned out to be Torpedo Girl!
How will this battle unfold?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
In the battlefield of Hell,
a giant water slide,
Requiem of the Battlefield
XXXXXX
Combat
Blues
Swimsuit Gal
Swimsuit Girl
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Beauty
Bo-bobo and friends were fighting Combat Blues and the Swimsuit Gals!
Help me!
Let's go!
Combat Blues... I will never forgive you!
Take this!
What kind of helicopter is that!?
They were just about even, nah-na-la!
But I'm stronger...
No, I am!
Yeah, yeah...
There, there...
Just then, their powerful ally appeared!
I will not permit the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because I'm a torpedo!
Charge
Love-love TeacherTorpedo!
I will Not Allow
Any Foolishness!!
Captain Combat!
Captain Combat, hold it together!
Miss Torpedo!
We missed you!
This is the first time in my twenty-five years of combat, that I was punched back by a weapon!
It's unique, right?
I don't like this!
Huh? She went back in!
Dammit, of course!
She must've been dissatisfied with her entrance!
Flowers!
Let's lay down some flowers and call her again!
Miss Torpedo!
You can come on out!
There she is.
It's time for the long-awaited start the Torpedo Grand Prix!
On your marks...
I'm gonna win this!
Torpedo!
Three...
Torpedo?
Two...
One...
Torpedo?
Go!
Torpedo!
This torpedo's... too damn strong...
I've brought in one hell of a weapon...
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
You guys are being too foolish!
I will not allow any foolishness!
No, you've got it all wrong, Miss Torpedo!
That Combat guy forced us to be foolish!
He blamed it on someone else again!
No! I mean... That's not true!
Bo-bobo started being foolish first!
I'll be killed... If I don't deny it, I'll be killed!
It's the truth!
Cheeky brat!
Your teacher hates cheeky brats!
Miss Torpedo! That's not the full story!
That Combat is a bad guy who makes weapons...
Sale
and sells them to foreign nations!
Torpedo!
Down with Weapons!
Abolish Weapons!!
Abolish
Weapons!!
She's condemning herself!
Fine by me.
I'll take down this Combat myself!
Here I go!
Right! Torpedoes excel at underwater combat!
Help! I'm drowning! Somebody get me a life ring!
Some torpedo you turned out to be...
So you can't swim, Miss Torpedo?
Of course I can't swim! Look at me, I'm made of iron!
I'm made of iron, so I'll sink!
A wiretap!
I heard everything!
But what's the point of the wiretap?
If you can't swim, that means I can drown you all!
Fist of Traps Secret Technique:
Whirlpool Hell !!
The smell of Darjeeling tea...
This really speaks to me.
I-I'm not a life ring, dammit! Look at me!
Don Patch!
Well?
Painful, isn't-
He's drowning!
I'm going to die like this, aren't I?
My life is flashing before my eyes...
Team Torpedo!
What kind of past is this!?
Now to finish you off!
Fist of Traps
Secret Technique:
Underwater Rockets!!
Shit! Here it comes!
This calls for
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
I'll be the one to protect my students!
That was a close call.
Now I can die in peace...
The most dangerous one is dead!
You loser!
You don't know how great Miss Torpedo can truly be!
Now behold!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Love Road!!
Once she sees this face, she can't stop herself!
Softon!
Um... well... um...
I love you, torpedo!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Love Attack
Love Attack!!
It's back to a regular slide!
You're not getting away with this, you damn torpedo!
Huh? The torpedo's gone!
I've hidden Miss Torpedo!
You did what!?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Quiz
Which One's the Torpedo?
Torpedo Quiz!
Now, care to guess which one's the real torpedo?
That's obvious!
Which one? Which one is it?
You'll never guess!
I got it! It's this one!
I'm getting kinda pissed...
You're right!
He got it right!
And now, a kiss as your reward!
Oh, please!
I'm so embarrassed, torpedo!
Combat Blues.
You were nothing.
That torpedo is too strong!
I have to tame it somehow...
Should I use some kind of bait?
But what would a torpedo want, anyway?
I don't know. I don't know at all!
Think! Think! Think!
I've figured it out!
Excuse me, Torpedo!
Look! A putty eraser!
I'll hand it over to you if you come here!
It's a rare item!
And why the hell would I want that!?
Hey, Torpedo!
It's a brand-name purse!
The new Spring line!
I should've gone with a brand-name purse!
Answer Sheet
You truly are a rotten bastard, trying to win me over with things!
You listen! I'm going to give you the re-education of your lifetime!
Fist of the Bloody Murder Secret Technique
The Torpedo's Loving Education!!
There, there, there, there...
Quiet, now...
Okay, go to sleep now, torpedo.
Once upon a time...
Well done!
The Torpedo's Loving Education!!
What kind of secret technique is this!?
It's pretty amazing if you think about it!
The Torpedo's Loving Education!!
And so, the child grew up quickly...
Who are ya? Get lost.
That's no good!
This is not how I raised you!
Now you've done it!
Look up here!
Up?
Wait for it, wait for it...
An alligator!?
What the hell is that boy doing!?
Are you alright, Swimsuit Gal?
No more being naughty now, you two.
OK!
Hey! What's with the different treatment? That's sexism!
Dammit! Only a little more until the top!
I'll have to climb to the top...
We've been waiting for you.
Don Patch, good work bringing him here.
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Cross Goddess!!
They did it!
Requiem of the Battlefield
XXXXXX
Combat
Blues
Swimsuit Gal
Swimsuit Girl
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Beauty
Combat Blues has sunk!
Hold it... Somebody please save me!
Corn on the Cob
Goldfish Catching
Chocolate Bananas
Meanwhile, back at Dengakuman...
Too bad for you.
I almost had it, dammit!
I won't stop until I have that Hamchin doll!
He's alone.
This is a chance to test my transformation ability.
I'll start by tricking this brat.
I'm bound to get it eventually!
Beauty?
Yo!
Who are you!?
After a long, hard battle, Bo-bobo and his friends defeated Combat Blues.
But just then, a mysterious man had transformed into Beauty! What's he after?
And...
Where is the next battle going to take place?
And what's gonna happen to me?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, greet people with a smile and happy things will come your way!
Your lucky item is a photobook of a pop star!
If you tied, you'd better start getting in shape now if you want to stand out in the pool this summer!
And if you lost, setting up traps as a joke will put cracks in your friendship!
Alright, what's the next stage?
It's a robot battle in the skating rink!
Sweet! I'll show them the splendid technique of Joe of the Rink!
That's figure skating!
It seems we have to fight while riding weird mechs.
Can you control it?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Machine Battle on Ice! and The Penalty is Being Frozen!
Machine Battle on Ice!
Fierce Battle With No Rules!
The Penalty is Being Frozen!
That's So Cold, Baby!!
In two parts! You lose if you fall!