Kaboom!
Heartwarming
Nose Hair
Masterpiece Theater
Heartwarming Nose Hair Masterpiece Theater:
The Kasa Jizo in the Snow
Charge!
Well that doesn't sound good.
You're getting all wet.
Here, take my hat.
How's that?
Has Mercy
And they all lived happily ever after.
What's going on!?
This story's gotten real cold!
Now let's head over to the next stage.
Yes, let's.
A limousine!? Who do you think you are?
Beauty.
Want a ride?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
At the giant water slide in Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX,
called Requiem of the Battlefield, Bo-bobo and his friends faced
the former E-block captain from a hundred years ago, Combat Blues!
Requiem of the Battlefield
XXXXXX
Combat
Blues
Swimsuit Gal
Swimsuit Girl
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Beauty
A harsh battle with the Triple-Hunters rule ensued between Team Combat and Team Bo-bobo.
Fist of Traps Secret Technique:
Hand Grenades of the Soul!
Dammit...
Kaboom!
B-B-B-Beam!
Ow! I'm hit!
He sure is hopeless...
Fist of Traps
Secret Technique:
High-Speed Water Clones!!
How's this!?
Carp Climbing the Waterfall!!
And then...
Weapon
Come out, my weapon!
Love, love, Softon... Softon, love...
Love, love, lovely, lovely-ly...
Softon lovely!
However...
Imbecile!
Miss Torpedo!
I will not permit the slightest act of foolishness.
And that is because I'm a torpedo!
No! I mean... That's not true!
Bo-bobo started being foolish first!
Cheeky brat!
Your teacher hates cheeky brats!
We've been waiting for you.
And finally, Team Bo-bobo...
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Cross Goddess!!
Requiem of the Battlefield
XXXXXX
Combat
Blues
Swimsuit Gal
Swimsuit Girl
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Beauty
defeated Combat Blues!
But meanwhile, an enemy assassin...
was sneaking up on Dengakuman!
Who are you!?
Machine Battle
on
Ice!
Great
Battle
with No Rules!
Alright, gang!
The next stage...
is gonna be the ice skating rink!
What are you guys up to!?
No good.
I'm getting nothing but sweeties.
Same here.
Seriously!?
That's pretty rare! You should keep them!
And I managed to get some tokoroten!
Welcome to the Ice Mecha Ring, Bo-bobo.
The enemy's here already! Stop slacking off and listen to them!
What a treat.
I'm impressed you made it this far, despite being the scum you all are.
Detergent
The suds we are!?
On this stage, anyone not riding a machine is trash!
You'll have to play by our rules.
The shrub we are!?
So we've prepared machines for you to fight in.
The scream we are!?
We get the joke already!
I guess we're supposed to fight on one of those things!
Why's that?
Don't ask me!
You have your four machines to choose from, all of which have different specs.
I suggest you pick wisely.
We'll do just that!
You're picking by rolling a pencil!?
I'll be choosing this machine.
Insecticide
Summer
Ultra-Strength
What the hell kind of robot is that!? That wasn't one of the options!
Then I'll work my inspiration a bit...
and decide based on the machine's inner strength!
Bo-bobo's picking carefully for once!
I'll do it
This one!
Again, what the hell is that robot!? Does that even qualify as a robot!?
Then I'll go with this one!
Mandarins
I mean, not that I mind, but...
That's just a cardboard box!
Alright, that forms a team of three!
The two of us should be able to handle you on our own.
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
OK, listen up! I'll explain the rules!
This battle is called the Ice Machine Crash.
It's an all-out machine battle with no holds barred!
Whoever falls off of their machine...
will be removed from the arena by the Penalty of Death!
You're not familiar with this kind of fighting, so you can't make the first move!
Let's go! Start the battle!
He's already charging at us!
How dare you kill Don Patch!
The other guys are coming!
Fools! You're easy prey!
Feel the wrath of the Neo Machine Gun Beam!
Neo Machine Gun Beam
I counter with Ping-pong Barrier!
Ping-pong Barrier
Say what!?
In that case, let's aim for him!
Bring it on, guys!
I'll show you my machine's special move!
Radio
This thing only has radio!
Right-hand Radio!
And here's today's traffic report.
Traffic's moving smoothly on the Joban Expressway...
Left-hand Radio!
And now it's time for our music hour! Here's our first request:
"Break My..."
You idiot! Now fall to the ground!
I'm gonna fall!
Tennosuke!
I'm coming to save you!
You're the guy I expect the least from!
Quit being so annoying!
You're open!
Frog Tongue!
Now you can't move!
Fine by me!
Robot Discharge Attack!
Where's that finger going, robot?
What the hell!?
What's the big idea, robot!?
Oh shit, I'm out of energy!
I better go back and refuel...
The only refill spot is right here in the center!
I calculate your machines should be just about out of energy.
So what's your plan?
Refilling energy.
Okay, those clearly aren't robots, you bastards!
Alright, I'll show you my machine's true form!
Machine Change!
Super Eagle!
Transformation complete!
You know that's an elephant, right? Not an eagle?
Take this!
Eagle Claw!
Dammit! I'll fall if this keeps up!
Please, Bug-spray Robot! Lend me your strength!
Flyswatter Sword
And here's today's traffic report.
Traffic's moving smoothly...
Another radio!?
I can transform, too, losers!
Here he comes again!
Don Patch Robot Transformation...
Lightweight Mode!
x1.2 boost to speed!
What?
You say you can transform, too?
Alright, show me!
Bug-spray Robot Change!
Kagami Rice Cake.
Why cake!?
I'm coming for you, New Year's.
Where the hell are you going!?
This is hardly a challenge!
We've got this in the bag!
Not yet!
Now it's time for me to show you my ultimate transformation!
Let's go!
Nose Hair Change!
School!
That's the most intellectual transformation I've ever seen!
Crap, that's the bell!
Class is about to start
We got a math test in first period! We gotta move!
Oh, crap!
I forgot my protractor!
Talk about stupid!
Dumbass!
We were so drawn into the school atmosphere that we almost got off our robots!
Talk about a close call!
I was so close...
How dare you try and trick us, you son of a bitch!
They're finally on the offensive.
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Mecha Nose Hair Lock On!
The robot has nose hairs!?
That's mechanically impossible!
I have no time to deal with you scum.
Why don't you take a step forward and face me?
How sad...
You think you can take me on with such meager power?
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Bo-bobo has overpowered Lapalapa and Hagaioh.
But does he have a chance
against the creepy Jeda the Wind God?
That reminds me, we left Softon and the others behind... Are they alright?
At that moment, Softon...
I got a flower in both hands, torpedo!
Let go, you bitch!
I'll kill you for this, you fuckin' torpedo!
had been kidnapped by the torpedo.
Come on! Come to me! I'm your friend!
He's completely fooled.
He's a true blue moron.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
The third stage of the Triple-Hunters battles between Bo-bobo and the Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
was a machine showdown on the Ice Mecha Ring!
The former N-block captain Lapalapa,
and the former Q-block captain Hagaioh were the first to strike,
but Bo-bobo and his friends overwhelmed them with their... unique machines.
Quit being so annoying!
Fine by me!
Robot Discharge Attack!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Mecha Nose Hair Lock On!
I have no time to deal with you scum.
Why don't you take a step forward and face me?
And finally, he is about to come to blows with the leader of the Triple Hunters formation,
Former C-block Captain Jeda the Wind God!
He looks like he's gonna be powerful, Bo-bobo!
Hekkun, were you here all along?
The Penalty is Being Frozen! That's So Cold, Baby!!
The Penalty
is
Being Frozen!
That's So
Cold,
Baby!!
Captain Jeda's finally going on the offensive!
Go get him, Captain Jeda!
How sad.
To think that is all you have to offer.
I'm sad, too.
To see my friends in such a state, that is.
Insect located.
Idiot! Stop hitting me!
How do I look like an insect!?
Insect located.
Ultra-Strength
Exterminating insect.
Are your circuits fried, you crappy robot!?
Man
By the way, I'm sad, too.
I sent out fifty New Year's Cards last year but didn't get any replies!
Yeah, that's pretty sad.
Allow me to show you the gap between our powers.
Fist of the Wind Scythe Secret Technique:
Scythe of the Insurgent!
Here I come.
It's time for your milk!
I accept your challenge!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Best Of Luck, Don Patch!
You motherfucker! I swear I'm gonna fuckin' kill you!
You've angered your own ally.
How do you expect fight like that?
You think I care?
And now...
My hand slipped!
My turn now.
Fist of the Wind Scythe Secret Technique:
Fifty Unparalleled Scythes!
If you're gonna be using scythes, then so will I!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Start Out Warm Then Turn It Up to Hot!
That's a kettle, not a scythe!
That's nothing!
Silence, insect.
Damn you, robot!
Here, allow me to build on my technique.
Fist of the Wind Scythe
Evolved Secret Technique:
From Hell Typhoon!
These gusts are so strong!
I can't dodge them all!
In that case...
I'll just borrow two of Don Patch's spikes...
My charm points!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo Pinball!
Here they come!
You're going for the high score, aren't you?
They're coming this way!
Here, you can have them back.
My beautiful spikes!
On second thought, they don't look half bad.
Persistent, aren't you?
Then I'll take you out one at a time.
Starting with...
Dear God, please let it not be me,
please let it not be me...
Square guy! You're up first!
No way!
Now face me.
Damn you!
Desperate times call for desperate measures!
I'll just kill you before you kill me!
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Rolling Smack-Smack!!
That sure is desperate!
Fist of the Wind Scythe Secret Technique:
The Wind God's Gallows!
That's nothing!
Five Nu Handkerchief Guards!!
Cut him to pieces!
I'm just fine!
Penalty activated.
Dammit!
I got off my machine! What's happening to me?
In this stage, if your feet touch the ground,
you'll be pulled into the ice and made into an ice sculpture!
He's done for now.
Tennosuke!
He may have been stupid, but he was still our friend!
Let's go help him!
Got it!
Transform!
CANDY BALL!
Bo-bobo Fusion!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
They're turning into Bobopatch!
I have no idea what you're trying to pull...
Giant Divine Scythe
but it won't mean a thing before the Giant Divine Scythe.
Meanwhile, inside Bo-bobo...
Don Patch has entered successfully!
Starting up Bobopatch systems!
Roger, OK!
Perfect, I've hijacked the control room!
It's not every day that I get the chance to infiltrate Bo-bobo's body!
Better get back at him for everything while I still can!
Stupid
Time to cover Bo-bobo's body with graffiti!
Bwaaaah
Hooray!
Oh, wait...
Don Patch
Was Here!!
Revenge, revenge, revenge!
Natto
Tulip
Revenge, revenge, revenge!
Weird
Afro
Punk
Revenge, revenge, revenge!
What's this all about?
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
How come my name's below his?
This is total bullshit!
I'm way stronger than he is!
I'm supposed to be on top!
Take this and this and this and this and this!
Don Patch
Bo-bobo
That oughta do it.
Patchbobo Activated
Now, this is your last farewell!
How sad for you!
That's not Bobopatch!
Who is that?
More to the point...
Did he just stop it with that block of fish paste?
Nothing can slice through my shoulder armor!
He's wearing fish paste on his shoulder...?
I don't have much time. I'll finish this quickly.
What?
Konjac and Lotus Root!
No way! It's really strong!
Who... the hell...
Patchbobo.
Patchbobo
Bo-bobo and Don Patch
have fused in the reverse order of Bobopatch to make a new hero,
and his name is Patchbobo!
Has there ever been such a cool, yet strong hero?
What kind of fight will we see from Patchbobo against Jeda next time?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll be lucky when you act on your inspiration!
If you ever need a change of pace, try ping-pong!
If you tied, when you're low on energy, always try eating fresh fruit.
And if you lost, make sure you listen to the traffic report on the radio before you go out!
Don Patch and Bo-bobo have fused to make Patchbobo?
We'll show you our collaborative techniques!
Hell yeah!
What kind of moves are they gonna use?
But first, I gotta go to the bathroom.
Oh no! It's time for Yakkun's milk!
Before that, I think they need to work on their teamwork!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Hajike Combination Patchbobo! and Melee! Love Triangle!
Hajike Combination Patchbobo!
Showdown with No Fooling Around!?
Melee! Love Triangle!
Merry Battle on the Merry-Go-Round!?
In two parts!
Is this really gonna be alright?