Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
♥
Tortortor-tor    Tor-tortor
Torpedo
Girl
Softon
Miss Torpedo!
Softon!
Catch me if you can, torpedo!
Are you sure?
Once I catch you, I won't stop!
Venus!
Oh, Softon!
Hold it right there!
You can't have that woman!
Very well.
Stop it, you two!
Please don't fight over me!
Oh, beauty is such a curse!
Hey, wait!
What kind of story are you thinking up, bitch?
Torpedo?
I'm such a sinful woman, torpedo!
Miss Torpedo's running wild!
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt
Land MAX
Ice Mecha Ring
Okay! Time for a recap of the last episode, nah-na-la!
Bo-bobo and friends are fighting in the Ice Mecha Ring right now, nah-la!
Welcome to the Ice Mecha Ring.
Bo-bobo and friends faced off against Former C-block Captain, Jeda the Wind God's Triple Hunters formation.
The curtain has risen!
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Start the battle!
So they're fighting on ice this time?
It's the Ice Machine Crush!
A machine battle with no holds barred!
I should've guessed you would know about it, Hekkun...
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Best Of Luck, Don Patch!
It's incredibly dangerous!
If the pilot falls off his robot, he'll be dragged under the ice!
Fifty Unparalleled Scythes!
Fist of the Wind Scythe
Evolved Secret Technique:
Fist of the Wobble-Wobble Secret Technique:
Rolling Smack-Smack!!
Fist of the Wind Scythe Secret Technique:
The Wind God's Gallows!
That's nothing!
Five Nu Handkerchief Guards!!
Cut him to pieces!
Penalty activated.
Bo-bobo Fusion!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
They're turning into Bobopatch!
Meanwhile, inside Bo-bobo...
Stupid
Time to cover Bo-bobo's body with graffiti!
Bwaaaah
Hooray!
Oh, wait...
Don Patch
Was Here!!
What's this all about?
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
How come my name's below his?
This is total bullshit!
I'm way stronger than he is!
I'm supposed to be on top!
Take this and this and this and this and this!
How sad for you!
Don Patch
Bo-bobo
Patchbobo Activated
What!? You're not Bobopatch! Who are you supposed to be, nah-na-la!?
Who... the hell...
Patchbobo.
Who's this!?
The super-strong-looking warrior Patchbobo has been born out of pure coincidence!
Has such a warrior ever stood in such a low-level arena before?
No, I guess that's how this always goes.
Anyway, time to hajike it up, our hero Patchbobo!
Hajike
Combination
Patchbobo!
Showdown with
No
Fo
ol
ing
Around!?
I can only remain in this form for one minute.
That's more than enough time to finish you off.
Noodles and Garlic!
Noodles
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Death Lightning Yoyo
What!?
Captain Jeda!
W-What's going on? They're tightening me!
Explode!
Garlic Bomber!
Garlic Bomber
You bastard!
How dare you harm Captain Jeda!
No mercy!
Let's go!
The Legendary Don Patch Sword!
The Legendary
Don Patch Sword
The Evil
Radish Blade
The Evil Radish Blade!
He did it!
You're kidding!? A green onion...
and a radish!?
I guess your weapons are no match for my wind scythe!
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Sword of Good's Rule over Evil:
Sword of Good's Rule over  Evil:
Sugarcane Saber
Sword of Good's Rule over Evil:
Sugarcane Saber!
You still don't get it, do you?
How sad!
Lethal...
O
ki
na
wa
Infinite Slash!!!!
Impossible... My wind scythe can't be...
Amazing! He's in another class from his enemy!
He's overwhelmingly strong!
Is this really Patchbobo?
Son of a bitch...
He can fuse two objects together and make a weapon!
Just like a scientist of some kind!
That's a bit of a stretch.
Oh, right!
What about Tennosuke?
Tennosuke, I'm going to save you now.
Look at him!
He's sinking in the ice!
And so are we.
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Ice and Tennosuke!
Nothing's happening.
What's going on!?
What a nice rest that was.
Wait, what!?
I think I had a growth spurt in my sleep!
Look closer! It's cause you're fused with the entire field!
Damn you...
Captain Jeda!
You goddamn moron!
Let's go, Tennosuke!
And who are you?
Ice Cannon!!!
Tennosuke!
Beauty, what's for dinner tonight?
Don't look this way!
Thank goodness!
I'm back to my original size!
That was a close call.
Now we won't be pulled under the ice.
Ain't that right.
That's my lunch!
Give it back!
That's my special lunch I woke up super early to make!
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Lunch and Propeller!
Don't do it!
Attack!! Picnic Fighters!!
My lunch is on an air raid!
Attack!
What are you trying to do!?
Tennosuke!
God damn it!
This can't be happening to me!
My precious lunch...
I will not be defeated by the likes of you!
What!?
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Y-You're not serious...
Hagaioh and Jeda the Wind God!
Hagaijeda!
What did you do to me?
Impossible! How could this happen!?
I guess that settles this fight.
I can still make wind scythes in this form!
Wait, what!? What's with this weird wind scythe?
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit! What the hell is going on?
Now that he's like that, he's nothing to be afraid of!
They're all shaggy!
This is really uncomfortable!
Who do you take me for?
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Apple and Toilet Paper!
Mega Spark Handgun
Ow, ow, ow...
Come on! Really, who is this random hero?
That's Bo-bobo and Don Patch fused together.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
Now that I know, I'll gladly lend you a hand!
Now let us defeat them together!
Yeah.
That's the plan.
Why are you swinging the hammer near me?
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Tennosuke and Iron Hammer!
What is this? This isn't even close to a hammer!
Huh?
Victory Flying Crash
I can only remain in this form for five more seconds.
Talk about a long minute.
My next attack will settle this!
Hajike Matter Fusion!
Can't let you do that!
Nose Hair and Nose Hair!
Fist of Hajike
Secret Technique:
Summon "Double King Nose Hair"!!
I haven't had much screen-time!
Come over to Bo-bobo World!
He did it!
They're back to normal!
The Triple-Hunters formation
led by Former C-block Captain Jeda the Wind God, has been defeated.
Thank goodness, you two!
Your teamwork saved the day!
How dare you draw graffiti in my insides, you son of a bitch!
What exactly happened!?
Thanks to their impeccable teamwork, Bo-bobo's team successfully defeated Jeda the Wind God's team.
This fight is heating up more and more!
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Remember, kids, always brush your teeth before bed!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Don Patch and Bo-bobo fused to make Patchbobo,
who, after a hard battle with Former C-block Captain Jeda the Wind God...
Is that supposed to be Patchbobo!? That's not what he looked like!
won with a super fight!
That's not how he really beat him!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Ice Mecha Ring
Meanwhile, back with Torpedo Girl and company...
They're here at the Merry-Go-Round Stage, nah-la!
Here you go, Softon!
Say "ahhh"!
You goddamn torpedo!
Get off me! I swear you won't get away with this!
How about you shut up?
Here. This is for you.
Don't you fuck with me, torpedo!
Torpedo!
Melee!
Love Triangle!
Merry-Go-Round!?
Merry
Battle on the
Damn that torpedo...
Do you know Miss Torpedo well?
We're on-and-off.
Five years ago, at Hair Hunters J-block Base...
Hair Hunters J-block Base
You dare betray us...
So there aren't any remnants of the Hair Kingdom here, either.
I could really go for a game of poker...
What?
Found you, Hatenko!
I never thought I'd see you here!
This must be destiny!
You again, Torpedo?
This time, I'll have you...
accept my love!
Allow me to explain.
This mark is called the Murder Seal.
It is a cursed mark that sucks out all the life force from its target.
I got his OK!
What have you done to me, bitch!?
Don't be so forward!
That whore...
Softon!
She's back!
How handsome you are today, Softon!
Whenever I see you like this...
I-I...
What in the flying fuck are you doing!?
I must win tomorrow's race no matter what!
Food
I won't lose to those thoroughbreds!
How do you expect me to win?
Nothing's happening here...
Are there no enemies in this stage?
By enemies, you mean us?
Former X-block Captain
Model
Former V-block Captain
Yagyu
Former O-block Captain
Three-Thousand Years
Former X-block Captain
Model
Former V-block Captain
Yagyu
Former O-block Captain
Three-Thousand Years
The Authentic Brothers are on the scene!
That's an amazing trio!
That's how it is.
I seriously wanna kill him!
This is the stage of Hell, Mega-Satan-Go-Round.
We'll take your lives, authentically!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
We're on a date here! You can't just interrupt it!
You'll have to cancel it!
Th-Th-Th-
That's bullshit, you damn topknot!
My topknot!
New Spring
Give it back, you broad!
It's hard to write with.
What do you think you're doing!?
Dammit...
Mega-Satan-Go-Round, High-speed Rotation!
We can't keep our balance!
What?
What are they gonna start?
20XX
Fashion Show
Fashion
Show
My fashion show!
Really!?
I'm shaking!
Fool!
You've let your guard down!
Dammit! That show was a diversion!
Now! Go, Bakuten!
Huh? Why's it not moving!?
I guess they're all idiots.
Just watching them is pissing me off!
Wait! It's too dangerous to get close carelessly!
I don't take orders from you!
He's coming!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
Well then, take my three-thousand-year secret art:
Authentic "Ramen Wheel"!!
LOCK!
Too bad.
My power is just as authentic as my ramen.
Sounds great.
Who the hell are you showing off for, bastard!?
You dare to ignore Softon's warnings...
Who do you think you are?
No.
Thanks to him, we found out which enemy is worth our attention. That's commendable enough.
You did well, Hatenko.
Nice guts!
You sure are desperate...
Now what will you do about my iron guard?
He's eating my ramen!
By the way, where did Model go?
Fashion
Show
Part 2
And here's our new winter lineup!
Are you still doing that!?
Too foolish!
Torpedo Fashion Show
Torpedo!
The torpedo hijacked it...
My fashion show...
I hate to admit anything about Hatenko...
but these three have power off the charts!
These captains are no match for them!
What's wrong? Why won't you attack?
Seconds.
There's no need for that.
You have already begun
to walk the holy path of Babylon.
What?
Seconds.
By the Babylon-Go-Round.
What the hell is this!?
What the hell are you doing, you goddamn twirly-head!?
This'll make the children cry!
Babylon-Go-Round
Waiting Time
3 Hours
It's really popular! Do they actually want to ride this?
Now receive your judgment,
as your hollow myths collapse around you.
Judgment of Babylon!!
He's far too strong!
One of the horses turned into a toilet!
Softon, you're so dreamy!
And the torpedo came out of the toilet!
You're not bad. But I'm gonna handle the coup de grace.
You?
Miss Torpedo!
Show some respect to Softon.
You still don't know your place, do you?
She's coming!
Ramen Wheel!!
Dammit, Torpedo!
I'll kill you for this later!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Super-Low Altitude Lock On!!!
Collaborative
Secret Technique:
They did it!
Former O-block Captain Three-Thousand Years' Triple-Hunters formation...
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Three-
Thousand
Years
Three-xxx
Thousandx
Yearsxxxx
Yagyu
Yagyuxx
Model
Modelxxx
Torpedo
Girl
Torpedox
Girlxxxxx
Softon
Softonx
Hatenko
Hatenkoux
has been defeated!
What the...?
Over weight!
Softon!
These two are amazing...
but they may never team up again.
Meanwhile...
back with Bo-bobo...
I hope everyone's safe...
We've been to all the fun-looking stages...
Do you think there are any good ones left?
Good point...
If only there were a stage that would give our hearts a jolt...
Fish Feeding Corner
Found it!
No way!
Let's Feed the Carp!
Is this really fun?
Wait up, you two!
It's fun!
You wanted to be fed!?
How's that supposed to be fun?
Yeah. It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun!
That's Dengakuman!
Oh, you're awake!
What's wrong! Who did this to you?
A weird Beauty...
Me!?
Are you really that obsessed with being the heroine!?
Hey! Stop it! Stop doing that!
You're a demon! A demon!
A demon!
Quit being so annoying!
Former
B-block Captain
Lambada
Indeed, the power and cruelty of the Third's Generation are not to be underestimated!
Can Bo-bobo and his friends win all the battle stages?
Former
A-block
Captain
Fishcake
You guys...
We may be in trouble this time.
I'm one of the more powerful members of this team...
and yet they did a number on me.
But...
I don't plan on letting it end like this!
It's time for this battle to get real!
Better check it out next time!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll be happy when you pack a lunch and go on a picnic!
Your lucky lunchbox item is a tasty fried egg!
If you tied, hold on tight to the horse when you're on the merry-go-round.
And if you lost, make sure there's toilet paper left before you go to the toilet!
It's money! Money, money, money!
There's so much money to take!
Hey, I think that's the next stage!
What? Are you trying to hog it all for yourself?
No! You should focus on your opponent!
That's right. We called for backup. Let's beat our enemies and get rich!
I told you, those are coins for a game!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Three Choices of Fate! and Rice, Young Noble of Rice, Arrives!
Three Choices of Fate! Good Real World, Bad Heaven, and Regular Hell!?
Rice, Young Noble of Rice, Arrives! Allies and Enemies in a Free-For-All!!
In two parts!
So are those three choices rock, paper, and scissors?