Heaven
Real World
Hell
Heaven, Hell, and Real World...
Kinda hard to pick out of the three...
There's nothing to think over here!
This one!
Heaven-ho!
J-Just a second!
What is it, Beauty?
Doesn't this "Heaven" sound a little tad suspicious?
Really? Are you insinuating that it could be a trap?
Isn't it normal to suspect things like that?
So you'd think everyone you see is a robber?
You're a real selfish lady, aren't you?
Right?
I never said anyone was a robber...
Don't you worry, Beauty.
Even if it's a trap, we...
still have to go!
Heaven-ho!
Welcome!
W-What is this place!?
One Heaven.
Same here!
And make sure I get a fresh one!
Right!
Order up!
Thanks for the food!
Th-Those are calculators! You can't eat those!
Calculators?
How are these calculators?
But they're obviously calculators!
You're wrong, Beauty.
This is an indispensable item that will guide us to Heaven.
Look.
A remote control!?
And without further ado, it's time to start, nah-la!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
At Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX,
the newly-revived Tsuru Tsururiina III's generation of Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago
Tsuru Tsururiina III
Tsuru Tsururiin
Former A-Block Captain
Fishcake
Former B-Block Captain
Lambada
Former C-Block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former D-Block Captain
Former E-Block Captain
Combat Blues
Former F-Block Captain
Ujikin TOKIO
Former G-Block Captain
Roselily Kikunojo
Former A-Block Ca
Fishcake
Former B-Block Ca
Lambada
Former C-Block Ca
Jeda the Wind
Former D-Block Ca
Former E-Block Ca
Combat Blues
Former F-Block Ca
Ujikin TOKIOll
Former G-Block Ca
Roselily Kikun
fought with the remnant of the Hair Kingdom, Bo-bobo, and his friends,
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Three-
Thousand
Years
Three-xxx
Thousandx
Yearsxxxx
Yagyu
Yagyuxx
Model
Modelxxx
Torpedo
Girl
Torpedox
Girlxxxxx
Softon
Softonx
Hatenko
Hatenkoux
in three-on-three Triple Hunters matches.
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
At the Merry-Go-Round Stage...
She's coming!
Ramen Wheel!!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Super-Low Altitude Lock On!!!
Collaborative
Secret Technique:
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Three-
Thousand
Years
Three-xxx
Thousandx
Yearsxxxx
Yagyu
Yagyuxx
Model
Modelxxx
Torpedo
Girl
Torpedox
Girlxxxxx
Softon
Softonx
Hatenko
Hatenkoux
Team Torpedo was victorious!
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Meanwhile, at the Ice Skating Rink...
Bo-bobo Fusion!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Bo-bobo and Don Patch became Patchbobo through a new fusion...
Now, this is your last farewell!
How sad for you!
Fist of Hajike
Secret Technique:
Summon "Double King Nose Hair"!!
He did it!
and they defeated Team Jeda the Wind God!
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Three Choices of Fate!
Good Real World
Bad Heaven
Regular Hell!?
Alright, guys! Let's gear up and move onto the next stage!
Bo-bobo!
Let's roll!
I'm going on ahead!
Ouch.
My Patch Magnum car!
A Dengaku Hole-in-One!
And so, ten minutes later...
We've made it.
What the hell is this thing, even!?
Look! There are a bunch of huge coins inside!
That size... They must be 100 million yen coins!
Hunt
Yeah!
No.
Welcome, folks...
to the Medal Game Stage:
Triple Life-and-Death.
Who's there?
The name's Elbbub.
Former Z-block Captain
Elbbub of the Bubbles
Once you come in here, you won't be coming out alive.
It's a pleasure.
So you've shown yourself, Hair Hunter!
We'll beat the crap outta ya!
You should probably focus more on the enemy...
I'll say this in advance.
This stage will be fought with the Double Triple-Hunters rule: A six-on-six multi-stage battle.
Double Triple-Hunters
He's already got a rich man's face!
Now, let's begin!
We're being sucked in!
This is bad! If we go inside, we'll be right where he wants us!
We have to hold out here...
Only one thing to do...
What?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Tokoro Balloon of Friendship!
We stopped.
We overfilled him!
What are these holes?
That's the Yama Disc.
Yama Disc
Heaven
Area
Real
World
Area
It's an instrument of terror that will randomly send you to Heaven, the Real World, and Hell.
I fell already!
This is bad! We're going to get separated!
Dammit!
In that case...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Peep-Peep Squad, Roll Out!!
What is this secret technique even supposed to do!?
Calms us down.
Please, take this seriously!
Beauty!
Heroine
Now's my chance to take the role of the heroine!
Now, fall! Come on, fall! Fall!
How about you fall instead!?
Are you alright?
Yeah...
So you came to the Real World Area?
I welcome you here.
Get them!
Fist of Soap Secret Technique:
Capture Bubbles!
What?
Let's fight bubbles with bubbles!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The Angels' Bathroom!
Cancelled out!
And now...
Landing!
Bo-bobo!
Beauty's been captured!
What!?
She's going through the wall, soap bubble and all!
It's no use...
Beauty...
I've sent that girl off to Heaven Area.
And there's a different fighter in each area.
It's curtains for that girl!
I will save Beauty!
I'm afraid you can't.
Because she is in the Heaven Area.
She!?
Fist of Soap Secret Technique:
Bubble Kid Creation!
Get them!
Fighting Dengakuman!
Fighting Dengakuman
I've got this one!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Are you calling me? Are you calling me? I come from...
56km southwest!
The blazing-hot fighter!
The burning... The burning...
Fighting...
Dengakuman!
Those bubble kids are strong...
So that's one down.
Dengakuman!
What've you done with Dengakuman?
Beneath this stage,
there are some giant fans.
Whoever falls into them...
gets chopped to bits.
What!?
And they'll come out of the machine in pieces.
No way...
You mean Dengakuman's been...
No!
I have to put him together again!
What's with this creepy stage?
And we don't even know everything about it!
It won't be easy to save Beauty on my own!
In this case, I'll have to contact Softon and the others!
I love you I love you I love you I love you
You're wasting your time.
No electromagnetic waves can go in or out of this stage.
Dammit!
Then I'll send up a man-made satellite to transmit the waves outside!
Me!?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Stupid Satellite, Fire!
I'm not a satellite, you know!
Don Patch Satellite
Don Patch Satellite P506 makes its space debut!
Now I can call my friends!
I didn't see that coming...
If we're going to survive this A-class difficulty stage...
we'll need those two to help us!
Who exactly are "those two?"
Receiving...
Sending...
Los Angeles
Two million dollars, cash.
Is this enough for you?
I refuse.
I don't do service for money.
Mr. Serviceman...
Please understand that our country needs your service.
We'll give you three... No, four million dollars!
That's how...
Requesting Service
Bo-bobo
That's just how valuable your service is to us!
Some urgent business just came up. Excuse me.
Mr. Serviceman, where are you going?
To a comrade in arms.
So who's the other one?
Let me back!
Oh!
That sounds like Beauty in Heaven Area!
Let's change the screen!
Let me back!
If I'm not there, no one can stop Bo-bobo from going wild!
Who's there?
Napping
There's something really weird in here!
That's Beauty's voice!
Are you safe?
The Double Triple-Hunters Battle has begun.
Fist of Soap Secret Technique:
Poison Bubbles!
Touch these and you're dead!
Well then...
What?
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Spiked Sandbag!
There's no end to these bubbles! In that case...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Domino World Record Attempt!
Followed by a painful mistake!
All our hard work just went up in smoke,
like bubbles in water!
What!?
They took out my poison bubbles!
But...
What the hell!? Those huge coins are raining down!
Piggy Bank
Gotta save up!
Come raining down!
Come raining down more and more!
Rice
What? Rice?
But this stage isn't supposed to have rice...
That can't be right...
Give me back my
money, you jerk!
Bo-bobo
So the Young Noble of Rice finally decided to show up!
It's a harvest!
And what have you called me for?
It turns out that Bo-bobo's other backup...
is the former King of Hajikelists, Rice!
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Ellbub of
the Bubbles
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beautyl
Ellbub ofxx
the Bubbles
Life-and-Death Triple
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Ellbub of
the Bubbles
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beautyl
Ellbub ofxx
the Bubbles
Rice
Ricellll
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
The battle with the Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago continues.
In the Medal Game Stage,
Life-and-Death Triple
Ellbub of
the Bubbles
Ellbub ofxxl
Bo-bobo
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, Tokoro Tennosuke, and Beauty
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, Tokoro Tennosuke, and Beauty
Beauty
Beautyl
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, Tokoro Tennosuke, and Beauty
are fighting Elbbub the Bubble in a six-on-six Double Triple-Hunters battle.
But Beauty was sent to the Heaven Area,
and Bo-bobo used a satellite to call for help.
Don Patch Satellite
And who should answer his call but Rice, the former King of Hajikelists!
Life-and-Death Triple
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Ellbub of
the Bubbles
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beautyl
Ellbub ofxx
the Bubbles
Rice
Ricellll
Huh?
But where did Tennosuke end up?
Real World Area
Heaven Area
He's not in the Real World or Heaven Area...
I seem to remember someone mentioning a Hell Area...
Hell Area
Where am I?
It's scary! Feels like there'll be ghosts!
Where are you guys?
I know!
Nu Picture Book
This calls for my Nu Picture Book!
If I'm focused on my book, I can distract myself from the fear!
Once upon a time, there was a Nu old man...
There's one!
Please help me, Bo-bobo!
Rice, Young Noble of Rice,
Rice, Young Noble of Rice, Arrives! Allies and Enemies in a Free-For-All!!
Arrives!
Enemies
and Allies
in a Free-For-All!!
I have to save Beauty!
And that's why you've called me here?
I didn't think you'd be any help, but I just called you for the hell of it...
That makes five of us!
How about your side?
Where are the five others?
There's one of us each in the Real World, Heaven, and Hell.
Fast asleep...
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
So in other words...
It's five on five, right?
I'm in the process of assembling the others.
I can summon super-warriors who thirst for blood...
By sending these Blood Call Bubbles.
Blood Call Bubbles
Hopes
Dreams
So can you send off our hopes and dreams with them?
Hopes
Dreams
Ours, too!
I can't send those off!
Hopes
Dreams
They're flying on their own!
Oh, how nice!
Oh, how rice!
I'm home, Pa.
Roller Car
How dare you... How dare you... waste precious rice!
I did?
Now, let's get this party started!
What the hell!?
This stage is a Coin Drop Game.
The lower level is a danger zone.
When the upper level pushes on it...
You'll fall down, coins and all.
No wonder property was so cheap on the lower level!
Butcher's Shop
I've already opened up a butcher's shop!
You won't sell anything there!
Who was that voice?
I'll crush you!
Fist of Soap Secret Technique:
Bubble Change!
Here he comes!
Now it's my time to shine!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique:
Mega Ricesplosion!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Mega Ricesplosion
And now...
Wrap it in seaweed...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Going on a Field Trip!
I can't see it, but I can just tell that's not a technique!
I can't go on! I'm dying of starvation!
I'm gonna eat it now!
Wait! We're not at the summit yet!
Don't give me that crap! I'll eat it now!
Doppa!
Didn't you hear what I said?
Sorry.
I just got ahead of myself.
That's taking it too far, guys!
In more ways than one!
Just fight seriously!
She makes precise comebacks from the other side of the wall...
That girl's amazing!
I'm suffocating here!
Don't get ahead of yourselves, bastards!
Anything could be happening in the Heaven and Hell Areas while we're fighting here.
I'm not falling for such a cheap provocation!
That sounded like Tennosuke!
What is this?
The minced meat...
Jumping... Flying...
B-B-Bermuda Triangle!
Something really is happening!
It sure looks fun in there!
I got it...
Former B-block Captain
Lambada
Your Blood Call Bubble.
I'll join in.
Captain Lambada!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Lambada
Great going, Blood Call Bubble!
You've brought a big shot back!
Now join us, powerful warriors!
But first, let's see what you're made of.
More
Less
They're coming! They're coming faster!
Offering
What a gracious offering!
What the hell are you doing!?
There's so many coins!
I can't use my Secret Techniques!
Then how about I use up all these coins in that there vending machine?
Crab
They wouldn't fit.
I wouldn't think so.
The tables have turned!
Poison Bubbles!
Pop
French Bread!
Bread-bre-bread-bread-Eat your bread!
Now that it's come to this...
Give all your Hajike power to me!
What are you gonna do?
I'll direct the Hajike power of us three right at him!
Die!
Hajikelist Collaborative Secret Technique:
Hajike Cannon!
Nose Hair
Alright! We kicked his ass!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Memorized!
Soon...
The other warriors will come...
Hey! I don't hear Beauty anymore!
What!?
What now?
That's Tennosuke's voice!
Someone's coming out!
Tennosuke!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Tennosuke has fallen.
What could've happened in the Hell Area?
But more importantly...
Beauty! Are you safe?
They've defeated Elbbub of the Bubbles, but there are still many foes left!
And that's not all...
Not yet...
It ain't over yet...
New warriors are on their way!
Say something, Beauty!
Can Bo-bobo and his friends save Beauty and win this battle!?
Narita Airport
Meanwhile, that person is...
I'm back.
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, take a long bath to feel refreshed!
Your lucky item is flower-scented bath salts!
If you tied, you're going to have a week that alternatively feels like Heaven and Hell.
And if you lost, be sure you don't make any mistakes that'll make all your work go up in smoke!
Sorry to be so abrupt, but it's time for a quiz!
Who is the final backup I called?
That's a tricky one...
Come on... Come on... Service! Service!
It's a service question!
I-It's not Serviceman, is it?
Correct! As your prize, here's Serviceman's service!
A year's supply!
I'm so jealous!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Ultra Service Full-Throttle!! and Mythical Beasts vs Don Patch!!
Ultra Service Full-Throttle!!
Behold ❤ this Excessively Beautiful Body!?
Mythical Beasts vs Don Patch!!
Stay Firm Even With No Data, Goemon!!
In two parts!
I don't wanna see that!