Nu
Beauty Parlor
Good afternoon!
Welcome, Beauty!
So what'll it be today?
Let's see...
This summer
Afros will be in!
This summer, afros will be in!
That's going too far...
show your bad
side sometimes?
Why not
Why not show your bad side sometimes?
That's just not me...
Three hours of
styling every morning
Three hours of styling every morning.
That's a pass.
The Dengakuman Cut
It's finally here
Dengakuman Cut, nah-na-la!
It's cute, but a little childish for me...
What have you done!?
This summer, "nu" will be in!
But this is a "ne"!
I mixed up "ne" and "nu" again!
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Life-and-Death Triple
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Bo-bobo and his friends have arrived to the Medal Game stage
of Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX, Life or Death Triple.
There, the former captain of Z-block,
Elbbub of the Bubbles, threw him into the stage.
What!?
I've sent that girl off to Heaven Area.
Let me back!
Who's there?
Napping
There's something really weird in here!
And the stage held an even more fearsome trap.
Beneath this stage,
there are some giant fans. Whoever falls into them...
gets chopped to bits.
No!
I have to put him together again!
Amidst that fearsome battle, both sides called for powerful allies.
I'll join in.
Captain Lambada!
And what have you called me for?
Fist of Soap Secret Technique:
Bubble Change!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique:
Mega Ricesplosion!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Mega Ricesplosion
And now...
Wrap it in seaweed...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Going on a Field Trip!
Elementary School Field Day
In & Out Elementary School
Go Red Team!
That's not a field trip, that's a field day!
Die!
Hajikelist Collaborative Secret Technique:
Hajike Cannon!
Nose Hair
However, at that exact moment...
Tennosuke!
Can Bo-bobo save his friends who have been separated?
Mr. Serviceman, where are you going?
To a comrade in arms.
Ultra Service
Full-Throttle!!
Behold ❤
this Exccssively
Beautiful
Body!?
The six-on-six battle
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
by the Double Triple Hunters rule continues on.
Real World Area
We don't have any way of telling what's happening in the other areas!
Heaven Area
Napping
Who could be in there...?
Bo-bobo...
Hell Area
This is tricky...
I'll just have to use this to break down the walls!
Dengakuman Spoon!
Can you guys keep it down? You'll wake the enemy up!
That's enough! Just be quiet already!
What's all that racket...?
You guys made so much damn noise that I'm wide awake now!
Former D-block Captain Rem
What's the deal, eh?
But you're asleep! And you're drooling!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Rem
But she could wake up any second now...
And I can't fight back... What do I do?
Leave the fighting to me.
You're the final ally Bo-bobo called! Who are you?
This is a nightmare!
True To His Word
There are weird words coming up!
What's this all about?
Service!
Action Before Word
I came to find the truth.
It's not here. Go home.
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
God, I beg of you...
Please... please don't let him land in Heaven Area...
Your prayers are answered.
Oh, my God!
Shut the hell up...
Thanks to you bastards, I can't...
get a wink of sleep!
ZZZZZZZZZZ
Fist of the Fast Asleep
Secret Technique:
Snoring
What power! Is this even snoring?
Let the battle begin.
ZZZZZZZZZZ
That's amazing! He's dodging them all!
What lightweight movements!
It's excessively beautiful!
And he flew too far away!
Now it's my turn to attack.
Ser...
Vice! Vice! Vice! Vice! Vice!
That's pointless!
No! He blew her up with the air pressure! Phenomenal!
Now time to finish you off!
Ser...
Vice!
A flawless execution.
She's asleep!
In these conditions!?
How regretful...
Bo-bobo!
Get over here, for more reasons than one!
That was Beauty's voice!
We have to save her!
But how can we get into Heaven Area?
We'll destroy this wall!
Forceful as ever, huh? I do like that.
Don Patch!
Now to finish you off!
Help me...
Who's there?
The strongest man in the universe, you dumbass!
Bo-bobo!
Guess that's not gonna happen anytime soon.
That was just your imagination? Stop confusing us!
Heaven Area
The wall's too tough to break through.
There must be some way to travel between areas.
We have to get out of here and save Beauty, at any cost!
Don't even bother!
He's one of them!
He's come inside!
Damn, why now? We'll have to crush him!
Patch Slot Robot
Patch Slot
Weird Beauty
Goes to Paris
What the hell!?
Take this!
I finally found y'all!
Bo-bobo! Time ta settle the score once 'n fer all!
Former F-block Captain
Ujikin
TOKIO
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Lambada
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Ujikin TOKIO
What kinda stage is this? Is this here the entrance?
Sure is hard ta get in...
He's come out like the Sapporo winter festival!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Ujikin TOKIO has fallen.
You three are now my prey.
And I won't let a single one of you get away!
Rice, he's all yours.
That's a tall order.
Don Patch, we're going to find a way out of here!
Bold, aren't you? But I like that about you.
Let's start with the top!
That didn't work...
Don Patch!
You won't get away!
Not until you get past me!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique: Ricesplosion!
Alright!
Now we'll try from below!
Yes, sir!
Heaven
Real World
Fly!!
Operation Human Bird!!
OK, let's give this a try!
N-N-N-N-No, that's definitely not gonna work!
Now go!
Oh, hell yeah, I'm flying!
Bo-bobo, you dumbass! I'll go on ahead to Heaven without you!
Wait, this is Hell...
Now that I've sent the idiot to Hell, time to come up with a real plan.
How pitiful.
Another lost lamb for the slaughter.
Former R-block Captain
Roman Kikou
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Roman Kikou
Wait, he's actually a lamb!?
Rice Crackers
Why should I care, idiot?
Boil me, bake me, do what you like.
Think...
Think of a way to get out of here and into the Heaven Area...
That's...
It looks like I can get out through that coin slot!
You're not getting away!
I'll give you a lift, Bo-bobo!
Fist of Rice Secret Technique:
Gusto Burst
Perfect!
Nice, Rice!
Bagworm, bagworm...
How ironic.
You made an escape route by dropping all the coins into this area.
I won't let you off lightly.
I'll humiliate you, then kill you!
Bagworm, bagworm...
At that time, Bo-bobo was...
Hell
Real World
Coin Bank
Heaven
Bagworm, bagworm...
Yay! Now I can go to the Heaven Area!
Damn...
I'm running low on sandpaper...
What?
Beauty! I've come to save you!
Bo-bobo!
What's going on!?
Shut the hell up! Now I'm wide awake thanks to you!
Beauty! Relax and step back!
Bo-bobo!
Finally, Bo-bobo has made it to Beauty!
But how will he defeat this fighter with her mysterious techniques?
Vice.
After this break,
is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
In the Medal Game Stage, Bo-bobo and his friends have been separated.
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Hell Area
The Hell Area.
Heaven Area
The Heaven Area.
Real World Area
The Real World Area.
Each of these areas is seeing extreme battles.
Meanwhile, outside the battle stage,
the plastic model master Tennosuke had just finished Dengakuman,
but wasn't quite satisfied with the finished product.
This isn't how I imagined it.
No one cares!
Mythical Beasts
VS
Don Patch!!
Stay Firm
Even With No Data,
Goemon!!
Now that you have come here, I will bury you!
Prepare yourself!
Ow.
How dare you mock me! Then have at you!
Fist of Mythical Beasts
Secret Technique
Double Rasho Gate
One
Two
These are gates that will call mythical beasts from another dimension!
All manner of mythical beasts will come to devour you!
Fishing
Then I'll call some beasts of my own.
How? By fishing?
Hey, can you move a bit?
I can't see!
Oh, this is the real deal!
This is amazing!
See, I'm a bit of a perfectionist.
I-I accept nothing but perfection.
Got it.
That's a mythical beast!?
Fool!
I have already defeated that tokoroten!
Once someone has fallen from this area,
they are disqualified from this Double Triple-Hunters battle!
Look closer!
What?
He's...
A different guy!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Mask
the Tenzaburo
No, he's clearly the same guy!
Yeah, I'm the same guy.
He even admits to it!
The mythical beasts are coming!
It's all over for you!
There aren't any decent ones!
They're coming from the second gate!
I have my hopes for this one!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
They're all jelly-like!
I can't use them!
And they're all attacking me!
Fools! The enemy is right over there!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it right now!
I'm sorry...
I'll give you your money...
I'll give you your money, okay?
Wow, they're looking at me with super cold eyes!
Come on, cheer up, Goemon.
Who're you calling Goemon!?
Don't get the wrong idea, now.
These mythical beasts are all fierce and atrocious.
Even I have trouble taming them!
Okay, let's play with origami now!
Yay!
And he's taming them like it's nothing!
It can't be... How could that spiked brat...
tame these ferocious mythical beasts?
Yay! Look what I got from him!
He bribed them with stuff?
What could it be?
Amberjack Physiology
Episode
Set
Volume 1
Volume 2
Volume 3
Volume 4
Volume 5
This is perfect for a naturalist like me!
Amberjack
Physiology
Episode
Set
Retail Price
200,000 Yen
What the hell is this!? He bribed them with this!?
Then, I, too...
Come over here, mythical beasts! I'll give you candy!
I don't want it, you stupid Goemon!
You called me Goemon, too!?
Lame.
Damn you...
Who the hell is this spiked brat, anyway?
Could he be a kind of mythical beast himself?
I'll expose his true form with the
Fist of Mythical Beasts Secret Technique: Data Scope!
Expose his true form!
Scope on!
Mezzotopia
Patch
A relaxing home with a thirty-seven square meter bedroom.
The best living room for sitting together as a family.
You can see your children's smiles from the kitchen.
Mezzotopia
Patch
45 Million Yen
What the hell!? Is he some kind of showroom?
Prime Shinjuku Real Estate
Construction Begins This Spring
Located on prime Shinjuku real estate. Construction begins this Spring.
I'm not living there!
We have no true forms!
What!?
We are always...
just as we are!
Tokoroten
Jelly
Hey!
You've got some jelly in you!
Really!?
How could this be? I can't get any data on them!
Go!
What the hell are you doing!?
Idiot! Stop that! That gate is very delicate!
Dammit, it's gonna blow!
See? There are some weird things coming out!
7emon
6emon
4emon
3emon
What's with them... On closer look...
2emon
1emon
4emon
6emon
There's no Goemon!
Now let's all have fun with equations!
You dumbass!
That equation is far too risky!
There's no five here...
How could this be? Where the hell is Goemon?
I'll go, Brother!
No, you can't! You're one too many!
Dammit... Not now...
Control yourself, 6emon!
I can't just stand here!
I'm the answer!
So you're Goemon?
What!?
This hurts!
You moron!
So you finally show your true colors, Goemon!
Dammit, it was a trap all along!
I'd guessed you were Goemon from the beginning!
Come on!
Dammit, what's with this guy?
He tamed those mythical beasts and he exposed my identity...
What's with this brat!?
Former R-block Captain
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
_
TL Note: Ishikawa Goemon is a popular historical figure who, like Robin Hood, stole from the rich and gave them to the poor.
He actually was Goemon!
I've received the Blood Call Bubble and have answered its call!
Former Y-block Captain
Kanpyo
I will now begin my mission!
Target sighted!
Energy charging!
I must tame the next Mythical Beast to come out!
Alright, let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Don Patch's
Hundred Mythical Beast Night Train!!
Damn you! You won't get away with this, Goe!
This isn't over in the slightest, Goe!
The Fist of Rice is invincible!
You sucker.
I'll show you a Fist one rank above yours!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Aura of Polygons
What was that?
The scenery has turned into polygons!
Even me!
I can turn anything my aura touches into polygons.
There's no defense against this.
I can't move!
Now I'll take... your greatest expression!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Texture Hand!
What kind of attack...?
Now begone!
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Mask
the Tenzaburo
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
I will destroy all those who disturb my slumber.
Let's go!
Bring it.
Service!
What are you even doing!?
And she's sleeping again!
What's with this space!?
Rem sleeps soundly through the ruckus.
Does Bo-bobo even stand a chance?
And can they defeat the powerful Lambada?
Tune in next time, nah-la!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, get lots of sleep and you'll have a clear head!
Your lucky food is a Kanpyo sushi roll with lots of seaweed!
If you tied, next time you make a plastic model, put lots of sheets down so you don't stain the floor.
And if you lost, don't fall asleep in front of people, or they'll make fun of your snoring and drooling!
Heaven Area has become a dream world!
My butt!
Don't you dare fall asleep!
If you fall asleep in this world you...
How could you fall asleep at a time...
Never mind that! My butt!
Shut up!
We're trying to sleep here!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
This is the Country of Death,
the Country of Dreams!
Sleep, Sleep, Rem Rem
Showdown! Rem Sleep World!!
All Of You Take a Nap!!
In two parts!
Don't go to sleep!