Ramen
Cake Ramen
Ice Cream Ramen
Pudding Ramen
Chicken Ramen
Pork Ramen
Beef Ramen
Tickets, please.
Cake Ramen
Ice Cream Ramen
Pudding Ramen
Chicken Ramen
Pork Ramen
Beef Ramen
Tanmen, is it?
Alright.
What's going on? Is the cabbage a ticket?
Cake Ramen
Ice Cream Ramen
Pudding Ramen
Chicken Ramen
Pork Ramen
Beef Ramen
Ramen, is it?
Alright.
Cake Ramen
Ice Cream Ramen
Pudding Ramen
Chicken Ramen
Pork Ramen
Beef Ramen
Fried vegetable set?
With dumplings.
Mixed fried rice?
Arrest
You're under arrest!
Ramen
He went that way!
Why is this turning into a police chase?
Ramen
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Bo-bobo and company are on the ropes in the Medal Game Stage, Life-and-Death Triple.
Hell Area
Real World Area
Heaven Area
Hell Area
In the Hell Area, Don Patch fought against Roman Kiko.
What the hell!? Is he some kind of showroom?
Now let's all have fun with equations!
You dumbass!
That equation is far too risky!
How could this be? Where the hell is Goemon?
I'm the answer!
You moron!
So you finally show your true colors, Goemon!
Dammit, it was a trap all along!
Roman Kiko was confirmed to be Former R-block Captain Ishikawa Goemon.
Real World Area
In the Real World Area, Rice fought against Lambada.
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Texture Hand!
What kind of attack...?
Now begone!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Mask
the Tenzaburo
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Rice was defeated.
Heaven Area
And in the Heaven Area,
Bo-bobo and Serviceman began their battle against Rem.
Service!
What are you even doing!?
And she's sleeping again!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Mask
the Tenzaburo
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Can Bo-bobo and his friends defeat the mighty Rem and Lambada,
and be victorious in this stage?
This is the
Land of Death,
The Land of Dreams!
Sleep, Sleep,
Rem, Rem ♪
Service!
This isn't working...
My butt!
Butt, butt, butt, butt...
Tennosuke!?
My butt!
Where's the butt?
Calm your butt down!
What's gotten into you?
My butt! My butt! My butt hurts!
My butt hurts!
Your butt, you say?
There's something weird poking it!
This was stuck in it.
Was he the reason my butt hurts?
How dare you, you son of a bitch!
H-He's dead?
Kanpyo expends all his power in a single poke.
Thus,
Once he completes his once-in-a-lifetime poke, his life is over.
Oh, farewell, Kanpyo, you revolutionary of butts.
You may be an enemy, but I still admire you!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
You guys...
Stop being so damn noisy! I can't sleep a wink!
How about I send you to the world of sleep, so that you never make noise again?
What!?
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Sleeping Scales!
What's going on? I'm suddenly feeling sleepy...
Is it because of this powder?
In that case...
I'll just blow all this powder away!
Service Secret Technique:
Gentle Floral Breeze!
Just bear it... I just gotta bear it...
This is a proper secret technique!
It wasn't worth it!
Glance
This guy's really pissing me off!
Can't resist... I have to go to bed and sleep...
I can't tell if he's joking or serious...
We're in trouble!
We're right where the enemy... where Rem wants...
And she's asleep!
I can't take it... Must sleep...
Wakey wakey!
Where are we now?
What is this place?
Is this one of her techniques?
This is the world of dreams.
This is the Fist of Fast Asleep Ultimate Secret Technique:
Fist of the Fast Asleep Ultimate Secret Technique
Rem Sleep World!
As soon as you fell asleep in the real world, I pulled you into my world.
And if you fall asleep in this world, you become a Sleep Dweller,
and you will never wake up in the real world again!
What!?
Have a taste of the terror of sleeping!
Something's coming this way!
Put them to sleep!
Devil Sheep!
One sheep!
Two sheep!
Three sheep!
That's not gonna make them sleep!
Four sheep...
Five sheep...
He's getting sleepy, even in these circumstances!
Don't you fall asleep on me, Tennosuke!
Here.
Fire!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Scream of Fire!!
Stop disturbing us!
Service!
Service Dojo
Why are you teaching the sheep to Service!?
Service!
You're all... expelled!
Just fall asleep already!
Dammit! It's that powder again!
The same thing won't work on me twice!
I'll focus on my game and stay awake!
Bo-bobo!
Sleeping
Quest
That'll just make you sleepier!
Sleeping
Quest
What is this game? What's going on?
This world is real dangerous!
If this keeps up, she'll make us all fall asleep...
Now sleep...
Go to sleep...
She fell asleep first!
It's on, Rem!
I'll wake you up,
and get back to the real world!
Hell Area
Real World Area
Heaven Area
Meanwhile, in the Hell Area...
What is this brat about?
What kind of life-form is he?
I'm gonna examine you once more, Goe!
Fist of Mythical Beasts Secret Technique:
Data Scope!!
Don Patch Castle
Huh!?
Now he's changed into a castle!
Don Patch Castle
Don Patch Castle...
85 meters tall     Total floor area 169m²     Azuchi-Momoyama style     Two-stage Moat
A rather famous sword.
A dangerous trap!
Stay calm...
Stay calm and survey the situation!
Money Box
I found the money box!
Goemon, moving out!
There is nothing that Goemon cannot steal!
Defense!
Huh? That's weird.
I can't break in...
Defense!
It's got a strong guard...
Gotcha!
It was a trap!
You dumbass! You fell for it again!
You're one half-assed Goemon, aren't you?
I never thought he'd disguise himself as a castle...
You bastard!
Now I'll just locate your heart with this scope of mine,
and strike it with a blow-dart!
Oh, crap!
Patch, Patch, Patch...
Found it!
That's where your heart...
For Santa
is...
What the hell is that!?
Dammit...
I'll have to use my Goemon Calculations to derive his identity!
5 Goe
7 Goe
7 Goe x 8 Goe x (10 Mon + 5 Goe)
GoeX + √Goe ÷ Mon
(Goe/Mon + 2 Goe) ÷ Goe
Goemon
3 Goe ÷ 4 Mon²
6 Goe x 5 Goe/3 Mon
It's no use!
I can't even multiply by six!
I'm making no progress!
I'll have to observe and analyze his behavior...
and collate it with other mythical beasts' data to find out his identity!
Alright, boys!
If you want me,
then swim to me!
What the hell is he doing!?
I don't get it at all!
I'm...
Free as a bird!
I don't understand.
What is with him?
I am a master of mythical beasts...
but this is the first time I've encountered a life-form like him!
He's staring back at me!
Snap, snap! Snap, snap!
He's taking pictures!
Why... You... Cut it out!
Snap, snap! Snap, snap!
He threw it on the ground!
Alright! I've given you enough hints!
Now do you know what I am?
Of course I don't!
Now, go ahead and guess!
Go ahead and guess!
I'm giving you a hint...
A... cat?
Of course not!
To think that I would encounter such an inexplicable life-form...
This is why I can't quit being Goemon...
I've... lost...
Money Box
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Ishikawa Goemon has fallen.
Small-fry.
If you try and treat me like a mythical beast...
You'll never figure me out!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Hell Area
Real World Area
Heaven Area
In the Heaven Area of the Medal Game Stage,
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Sleeping Scales!
Bo-bobo and Serviceman challenged Rem.
Gentle Floral Breeze!
And then,
they were drawn into the world of dreams, Rem Sleep World, by Rem's ultimate secret technique...
Fist of the Fast Asleep Ultimate Secret Technique
Rem Sleep World!
Meanwhile, in the Hell Area, Don Patch defeated Goemon...
You can't fall asleep here!
We've got to get the recap done...
Showdown!
Rem Sleep World!!
All of you
Take a Nap!!
Real World
Dream World
Rem Sleep World
Rem!
I will defeat this ultimate secret technique of yours!
How long will it take before you fall asleep?
Let me take a peek at your Sleep Meters.
Sleep Meters?
There's a meter in the sky!
A nu-shaped meter?
My meter's still got lots of room on it.
Forget the room, your meter's scary!
Sleep Meters
Once these meters hit maximum,
you will fall into your eternal sleep.
Right... I'll take you on personally from now on!
Prepare yourselves!
Rem Berserker Version
In this world, I'm super vicious!
My power here increases twenty-fold!
I'll make sure you never wake up again!
No way...
As if we weren't sleepy enough as it was...
She's powered up twenty-fold on top of that...? It's hopeless!
In this world, we, too...
have our power increased twenty-fold!
You what!?
This is the Bo-bobo Bakaser Version!
That's counterproductive, you idiot!
See, I told you so!
Serviceman!
Real World
No Service
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Serviceman has fallen.
That's one of you who's fallen in the world of sleep!
Grieve him!
That's nothing!
We've inherited Serviceman's will!
Fist of Rice!
That's someone else's move!
My Fist...
consists entirely of moves designed to induce sleepiness!
Take this!
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Sleep Strike!!
Sleep
Bo-bobo's meter is rising!
I can't move my left arm!
The Sleep Strike sends the parts I strike into an eternal sleep.
Your left shoulder is fast asleep!
You're right!
What kind of left shoulder is that!?
I can't beat the pro basketball team...
And he's awake!
Damn you!
Then I'll put your arms and legs to sleep!
Sleep Strike!!
Sleep
In that case...
t
Deposit Pillows!!
Yay!
Pillow fight!
I'm back!
Is this guy even human?
And now for
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Great Class Trip!!
It's Kyoto!
Who're you calling Kyoto!?
Great Class Trip!!
Kyoto Map
Golden Pavilion... Golden Pavilion, let's see...
Is it here?
Why you...
Sleep
Sleep Strike!!
Now I'll put you to sleep with this!
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Evil Song Mattresses!!
We'd be dead by now if we didn't have these rug beaters.
But those are rice scoops!
It's not working!
It's all over!
Those mattresses will sing the lullaby of death!
Go to sleep, little one...
Now, go to sleep!
Bo-bobo!
Little one...
Sleep without a sound...
You were singing it, Bo-bobo?
That's strange... The boy's not sleeping!
Perhaps I got the wrong song...
Alright, this time...
I'll sing a heavy metal song!
One, two, three, four!
I'd prefer Beethoven's Second.
Just go to sleep already!
This is dangerous...
We'd have had the advantage in battle...
But all because of the enemy's techniques and the sleeping scales, the Sleep Meters keep rising!
Now you're finished for good!
Fist of the Fast Asleep Super Secret Technique:
Instasleep Murder Clock!!
This secret technique
can drastically speed up the time inside Rem Sleep World!
How long can you stay awake for now?
T-This Secret Technique is lethal!
Stop that!
If you speed up time...
Tokoroten Gift Set
Ten Inc.
Tokoroten
He got shipped off!
Me too!
He's devolving!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Monkey's Year-end Gift Attack!!
Damn you...
Secret Technique:
Death Dark Field!!
This pitch-black darkness will amplify your sleepiness!
In that case...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Light of Hope!
Firefly light? That's pathetic!
But he's really into his studies!
Bo-bobo...
Beauty!
That girl looks like she's had it!
But what's the deal with this smoke? It's all over the place...
Is something happening in the real world?
Reality Monitor On!
Reality Monitor
I hope these pikes fry soon...
What's that idiot doing!?
They're pikes! Pikes!
Wait, why is he grilling sneakers?
That idiot!
We're killing him once we get back!
Alright!
Now's our chance, Tennosuke! You take care of Beauty!
I'll defeat Rem on my own!
Okay!
Rise and shine, Beauty!
Tokoroten with no Honor or Humanity
It's time to start the picture story!
Leave me alone...
Trying to help her, eh?
Alright, then! Gather, Sleeping Scales!
Put him to sleep!
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Dragon Sleep!!
You morons!
How dare you surrender to tofu!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Wild Lasso Johnny!
So he sent me out anyway!
What's happening...?
He's matching my Fist of the Fast Asleep move for move!
This isn't possible!
What kind of guy is this? How do I make him sleep?
When you're a cowboy...
there ain't nothing like a glass of hot milk before bed!
He put himself to sleep!
He's finally asleep!
See? There was no way he could have been safe after taking the Fist of the Fast Asleep!
Just look at his Sleep Meter!
Sleep
It's maxed out!
Rage
Rage!?
Thanks to your attacks,
my rage has been filled to the brim!
I don't believe it...
So your sleep meter was...
I never had such a thing in the first place!
I have never fallen asleep once in my life!
Now...
I'm gonna destroy this world!
That's not possible!
That's just not possible!
There's no way my attacks wouldn't put you to sleep!
Sleep
Sleep!
Dammit, why won't you just go to sleep!?
Hey.
Don't forget about me.
It's because of that thing!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Golden Alarm!!
We're back to the real world!
You're right!
Dammit...
Rem!
Your greatest secret technique has been defeated.
Now it's my turn to attack.
But before I do that...
These are sneakers!
What the hell's wrong with you!?
But the pike!
Bo-bobo has defeated Rem's greatest secret technique.
His counterattack of rage is about to begin!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, sleep on a mattress dried on a clear day, and you'll have good dreams!
Your lucky drink is hot milk before bed!
If you tied, see how many sheep you can count before you fall asleep.
And if you lost, put your alarm clock somewhere where you have to get out of bed to turn it off!
Rem! My counterattack of love...
And romance...
And kind of weird...
My passion space will bring you to tears!
From your eyes, your nose, and your mouth!
Tears only come from your eyes!
And then we'll go on to crush Lambada!
Softon will!
They're leaving it to someone else!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Now, Rem's Past Will Be Revealed! and The Mighty Lambada vs the Power of the Black Sun!
Now, Rem's Past Will Be Revealed! A Touching Story of Tears (^^;)
The Mighty Lambada vs the Power of the Black Sun! We'll Get You Back For that Fourfold (^0^)
In two parts!
The Black Sun hurts real bad!