Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who is the heroine of this anime?
It's Beauty!
Say that again and you'll pay the price!
I'll ask you one more time!
Who is the heroine of this anime?
Where's the princess? Where is she?
Grandmother!
My, what big nose hairs you have!
All the better to kick your ass with!
You can't take away the role of heroine from me!
The wolf is scary! The wolf is super scary!
I wanna marry the princess!
This fairy tale will make girls cry...
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Dare no sei de sonna
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Dengakuman here, nah-na-la!
Right now, Bo-bobo and friends are in the medal game stage, Life-and-Death Triple, nah-la.
Real World Area
Heaven Area
This stage is split into three areas: Heaven, Real World, and Hell.
Hell Area
Incidentally, the losers get sent over here.
Losers
Hell Area
And yes, I'm there, too...
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Kanpyo
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro Tennosuke
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
In Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX,
in the Life-and-Death Triple battle by the Double Triple-Hunters rule,
Bo-bobo's fight with the former D-block captain,
Rem, raged on.
Gentle Floral Breeze!
This is the world of dreams.
This is the Fist of Fast Asleep Ultimate Secret Technique:
Fist of the Fast Asleep Ultimate Secret Technique
Rem Sleep World!
And if you fall asleep in this world, you become a Sleep Dweller,
and you will never wake up in the real world again!
What!?
Put him to sleep!
Fist of the Fast Asleep Secret Technique:
Dragon Sleep!!
Wild Lasso Johnny!
So he sent me out anyway!
He's asleep!
Sleep
Rage
Rage!?
Thanks to your attacks,
my rage has been filled to the brim!
That's not possible!
There's no way my attacks wouldn't put you to sleep!
Sleep
Sleep!
Dammit, why won't you just go to sleep!?
Hey.
Don't forget about me.
It's because of that thing!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Golden Alarm!!
We're back to the real world!
Dammit...
Now it's my turn.
After a harsh battle, Bo-bobo had defeated Rem's greatest secret technique.
And now, his counterattack of rage is about to begin!
Now,
Rem's Past
Will Be Revealed!
A Touching
Story of Tears
(^^;)
Huh?
Come to think of it, wasn't Don Patch trapped in the Hell Area?
I came in through here!
Rem! I will defeat you!
Now it's my turn to guide you through my world of dreams!
Let's go!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Bo-bobo World Nightmare!
W-Where are we? What are you trying to pull?
Bo-bobo World Nightmare
is a super-dimensional emotional space of love and romance!
A world where your evil, impure heart will be...
cleansed!
Since when did you guys have evil hearts!?
Prepare yourself!
Right now, the super-emotional story we're about to tell you
with our souls released...
Will cleanse the evil from your heart!
An emotional story?
Spare me the crap!
That's just plain ridiculous!
Dump Site
Then we'll just have to invoke feelings in that dishonest little princess...
We will give you all our love!
How about a drive?
Eat it.
I don't have anything.
That's not gonna move her!
Yes, it did!
The hell...? Did I just feel for that?
That's not possible!
My heart is hot...
New life is born!
Again!
Why?
I'm having feelings against my will!
Is this what he meant by cleansing my heart?
The passion will continue on!
For your hardened heart...
We'll give you a bunch of portraits of us!
What!?
I'm moved!
Stay back! Don't come near me!
That must've been harsh.
Bet you're tired from all the running.
You wanna go...
for tea?
Dammit! How could I feel for that!?
Chop!
And major leaguer!
Dammit...
I'll destroy this bullshit technique!
Next up we have...
Tom!
Nancy!
Jessica!
Downtown Runaway Young Love Confessions!
I can't stop this feeling!
Jessica's gone wild!
You son of a...
Amazing!
It's a combo of Hajike passion!
Alright!
Now it's time to bring you to tears!
Let's go, Parisienne!
What are you doing, Monsieur?
Into the Seine you go!
Je t'aime!
My litmus papers!
I've been collecting these litmus papers all my life!
They're all getting wet!
My litmus papers!
Oh, my poor litmus papers!
This won't work! Surely litmus papers won't invoke any emotion!
The Parisienne's litmus papers...
It actually did!
Alright, good work!
Arms Dealer
Damn you, damn you...
Right then, Rem!
Take a good look into the sky!
Now what!?
Can't you see it?
The blue bird of happiness!
I'm falling over here, dumbass!
I feel it!
N-N-N-N-No! I'm falling!
Idiot, just keep focusing downward!
You'll be fine! Just keep your focus downward!
Up!?
Now I'm safe!
In this world,
you can invoke emotions any time you want.
Even when you're in a UFO.
by Bo-bobo.
What!?
Heartfelt first contact with extraterrestrial life.
What an emotional first contact!
How the hell is this emotional!?
I almost bit the big one!
Now it's time for my emotional story!
Let's go!
Ne  Ne
Would you like your portrait done?
Ne
Portrait?
Would you do one for me?
Nu
Mr. Nu...
That's not emotional!
They didn't forget me after all!
My appearance should bring about the greatest passion of all!
I'm so emotional I feel like something's gonna happen to me!
I'd better hide from those weirdos for now...
What the...?
What's up with this gloomy atmosphere?
Where am I?
Good day everyone, and welcome...
People Who Dropped
10 Yen Anonymous
to People who Dropped 10 Yen Anonymous.
What!?
Listen to my story, and cheer up.
Today, I dropped 1000 yen!
Stop all this now!
I feel hot...
Dammit, I must put them to sleep...
I must put them to sleep!
I must put everyone in the world to sleep!
I... I was...
Father
Mother
I was born to two mattresses...
A legitimate child of mattresses!
Hey!
I heard you failed to put anyone to sleep again!
That's so lame for a mattress!
Some mattress you are!
That's why I swore...
That I would become...
The world's greatest mattress, who would put people into a deeper sleep than any mattress!
I will... become the world's greatest mattress...
and put people into a deep sleep!
I will...
Rem!
What is... this?
Bo-bobo!
So you've shown yourself, Rem's evil soul!
No! It's scary!
Something weird's coming out of her!
Something's coming out of you guys, too!
Now finally for the number one climax scene!
Passion!
Now, it's purifying time!
Fist of the Nose Hair Emotional Secret Technique
Romance Feeling Movement !!
I will not let a fragment of your evil soul remain!
Annihilate!
We're back to the real world!
Rem.
I think there's enough room in the world...
for one mattress that can't put people to sleep.
Even if it means you're useless.
You're the one who's useless here!
Thank you...
How emotional...
That was really different from the normal Bo-bobo World.
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
Former D-block Captain Rem
forfeits due to loss of will to fight.
This guy was real weak.
Rice got done in!
No sooner had Rem been reformed,
than their next enemy, Lambada, arrived!
How will Bo-bobo stand up against a foe
that not even Rice was a match for?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
In the Double Triple-Hunters battle in Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX's medal game stage, Life-and-Death Triple,
Bo-bobo released Rem from her evil soul
with Bo-bobo World Nightmare.
Romance Feeling Movement!!!
Thank you...
However...
Before they could even rejoice in their victory...
The Former B-block Captain Lambada stood before them!
This guy was real weak.
Lambada is holding Rice's face turned into a polygon, nah-na-la!
Scary!
Are you saying you defeated Rice, you bastard?
He was so weak.
I don't believe it!
Rice was one of the top three Prima Donnas in the world...
He didn't stand a chance!
Be careful!
Lambada...
is one of the three most powerful men of Margarita, after Tsuru Tsururiina III and Fishcake!
Not even all the captains of C-block and under could match him, even all together!
I'll crush you!
I'll finish you all off!
The Mighty
Lambada
VS
the Power of the Black Sun!
We'll Get You
Back For that
Fourfold
(^0^)
Alright! He's the only one left!
Go, Tennosuke!
No! I really don't wanna!
Then allow me to assist!
Softon!
Mr. Pink Twirly-head!
I will diffuse the reign of time!
Presence!
Succession
Succession!
Presence
Release
Yield
Release! Yield!
I shall become one with space-time...
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Solar Calendar of Ethiopia
Very nice!
The more, the merrier!
Oh, no!
That's the Aura of Polygons!
Anyone who touches that aura turns into polygons!
Get away!
I'll take it head-on!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hey Hey Aura
You guys!
I'm turning into polygons!
I turned into polygons!
Is that what happens? I don't see any difference!
Me, too...
You've got such a low polygon count! Who are you even supposed to be?
So what about Bo-bobo?
Poly!
Giant Monster
Polygon
Poly!
What's with that monster?
I don't think you know what a polygon is, Bo-bobo!
Looks like there's a stubborn one left.
Aura Expansion!
You've got nowhere to run!
In that case...
We'll just have to go forward! Let's go, Softon!
Yeah!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Polygon Crusher
Evasive maneuvers!
That's...
two down...
I'm escaping by the ground!
That's why I've always wanted that form!
I struck oil!
Hooray! We're rich!
Silence!
Time to finish you off!
Are you alright?
We'll protect you!
With this ultimate sword and shield!
But that's us! That's us!
Et tu, Pink Twirly-head!
We'll curse you...
Our sword and shield!
He's really strong...
But... I can beat him as I am now!
Now that I have gained the power of the Black Sun!
What? The Black Sun?
You don't mean...
The Secret Technique of the man from Cyber City
That's right!
The guy that did those weird taglines!
I believe his name was Despair Guy
Close!
Close, but not quite him!
It was... um...
J!
Black Sun Babylon
What am I looking at?
What's going on?
This is the new Fist of Babylon!
The Door of Destiny Has Now Opened
Just like J!
O sorrowful one,
I have come to give you the Black Sun.
What?
You are the only man in this world
who can master the Black Sun.
I was unable to draw out the monumental potential of the Black Sun.
My friend...
I entrust you with the great will of the Black Sun!
These black flames I have inherited...
is the light that shines upon the land of Babylon that wavers between illusion and eternity!
Advent of the Black Flame God of Babylon!!
Amazing!
He came down!
True Judgment of Babylon
Dammit...
You piece of trash!
Aura of Polygons!
What!?
It is useless...
before we, who have the divine protection of the Black Flame God of Babylon.
They all turned J-like!
Let's go!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Melody of J: Great Thanksgiving!!
J!
Shut up!
WITH REGRET
IN MY HEART
I SHALL FALL
LIKE A FLOWER
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Meteor Polygons
Meteor Polygons! Skewer them!
That's nothing!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Grandpa and Grandma's Spinning Table
Make him think we're a grandpa and grandma to drop his guard...
then strike!
This'll work!
It's not gonna work!
True Judgment of Babylon
Softon...
This is bad...
I can't keep the God of Babylon in the real world for much longer...
Softon!
Use the God of Babylon to judge us three one last time!
What're you talking about, Bo-bobo?
Don't drag us in there! We'll get done in, too!
I'll judge you!
You pink twirly-head bastard!
True Judgment of Babylon
This is good.
What's this?
Have you gone crazy now that you know you can't win?
This one's for Rice! Have a taste of our iron fist of rage!
What!?
The Judgment of Babylon who is judging Don Patch
who is judging Tennosuke who is judging me!!!!
Quadrupled!
No, that doesn't quadruple it!
The God of Babylon disappeared!
Well?
How was my judgment with the power of the Black Flame God of Babylon behind it?
Looks like...
We made ourselves useful...
No.
I didn't really need you.
You bastard!
I'll defeat you in the most humiliating way possible!
Just you try.
Bo-bobo...
Lambada received a quadrupled judgment that wasn't quadrupled at all!
As his rage reaches its climax,
What kind of hell lies in wait for Bo-bobo and his friends?
This week's damage
Damage
Special Bonus
Time Bonus
Wow! Amazing!
We got a high score!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you will encounter an emotional story of love and romance!
Your lucky item is a King Nose Hair sax!
If you tied, look up why litmus papers change color.
And if you lost, you'll lose your money if there's a hole in your pants pocket!
We've dealt out so much to him, but he's still not going down!
We'll have to seal his Fist of Polygons.
But how do we do that?
With charms, written oracles, and amulets! I'm going to buy some!
Later!
You're asking the gods!?
What about Don Patch?
I am currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Get It On with Polygons!! and Retro Game Counterattack (^0^)v
Get It On with Polygons!! Dancing and Beauty in High Spirits!?
Retro Game Counterattack (^0^)v Playing and Watching are Totally Different!?
In two parts!
Think seriously!