I will defeat you in the most humiliating way possible!
I'll turn your whole bodies into polygons!
Bo-bobo...
So...
What's a polygon, anyway?
It's this, right?
I'm trash!
Nope, that's a polyethylene bag!
But do you mean to say you've been fighting him without even knowing what a polygon is?
We're ever so sorry, Miss!
Then allow your teacher to give you an explanation.
A polygon is...
Love!
Miss Torpedo!
It seems you understand now.
That's all wrong!
A polygon is a figure with three or more sides, and they're used in computer games
to portray characters in 3-D.
Oh, what realistic tofu!
Not tofu. That's tokoroten.
It's very angular because there aren't many polygons,
so you have to increase the polygon count to draw something more complex.
I get what you mean!
You guys can't do it!
Give us a chance!
We're all done, Miss Torpedo!
That's too handsome!
Very Well Done
Excellent application of knowledge here.
What's this?
Very Well Done
You just pasted a picture on the monitor!
Now that you've learned about polygons,
It's time to start the show!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
At the Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX,
the battle between Tsuru Tsururiina III's generation, who have awoken from their hundred-year slumber,
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
and the remnant of the Hair Kingdom Bo-bobo and his friends,
raged on in a six-on-six Double Triple-Hunters battle.
The only surviving enemy was Lambada.
Just then, Softon rushed to their aid...
True Judgment of Babylon!
This one's for Rice! Have a taste of our iron fist of rage!
The Judgment of Babylon who is judging Don Patch
who is judging Tennosuke who is judging me!!!!
Quadrupled!
Bo-bobo and his friends have begun the final battle!
Get It On with
Dancing
and Beauty
in High Spirits!?
I will defeat you in the most humiliating way possible!
I'll turn your whole bodies into polygons!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Aura of Polygons!
I'll reflect it!
Bring it on!
There it is!
The Holy Mirror Barrier!
It didn't work!
My head's turning into polygons!
This calls for...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Dicso Ball of Desperation!
Disco Ball of Desperation
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fever Until Morning!
Wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble!
Ew, gross!
He's been staring at us all night! Is he trying to pick us up?
How annoying!
We just came here to enjoy the dance!
So fat chance, boy!
Oh, but can I have a drink ticket?
I'll keep you company if you buy me a drink...
Night Fever!
Patchmi!
Excuse me, sir! This club has a strict "No Fighting" policy!
Damn you!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Wine Red Juice!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique: Wine Red Juice
It's burning hot! What is this?
That liquid will turn you into polygons once it touches you!
Oh, I can't believe it!
Look at how smooth my skin's become!
That's cause you've turned into polygons!
These mellow ingredients will bring back the shine to your skin.
Eternal beauty is yours.
Why won't you realize that that's not a beauty product!?
Super-Moist Skin Elbow!
You shitheads!
There's more of them!
Okay, boys! It's time to drink your milk!
That's horselicious!
That's just dumb!
Let's make you a pig!
Now suffer the humiliation of your lifetime!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Texture Face!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique: Texture Face
What's happening to my face?
I've changed your face into an ugly pig!
No...
Bo-bobo!
What the hell!?
This isn't right...
I thought I made him an ugly pig!
But what's with... that face?
Now I believe it's my turn next.
He's drinking coffee!
Fly like a butterfly...
Sting like a bee!
Those moves are too elegant for a pig!
My techniques are supposed to be perfect!
I'll make pigs of you all!
Texture Face!
What in the flying...!?
Now!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Dance of Darkness: First Dance!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Dance of Darkness: First Dance
That's a questionable secret technique!
We're back to normal!
Small-fry!
Get on your knees and beg for mercy!
I'll show you!
Fist of Polygons Ultimate Secret Technique:
Polygonic Lucifer!
Polygonic Lucifer
Fist of Polygons Ultimate Secret Technique:
Snacks
We're so sorry.
I never thought I'd have to use this secret technique on the likes of you.
The aura of the Dark Lord Lucifer is pure evil,
and whatever it touches turns into a single polygon.
Now become a flimsy plate!
Here he comes!
Please, Angel!
You guys!
That was close.
It sure was a close shave.
Out!
You're the only one left!
Bo-bobo!
Just the face again!?
Softon! Now's the time to use that secret technique!
Alright!
Beauty, you too!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Super-Dreadnought Face Battledore!
That does it!
Look out!
Hey, man, this is real dangerous!
We'd better get on the enemy's side, while we have the chance!
Mr. Lambada!
Little Gift
Special delivery for you!
Oh, and by the way...
Here's a flat-screen TV...
And a heated table!
It didn't work!
Alright, screw that!
Bo-bobo!
Traitors!
Now die!
That's it!
Now that we've all become plates, if we join together...
We could make a weapon that will match it!
A weapon you can make from three plates...
We'll have to bet on that!
Combine!
Complete!
Three Plates
Mechanized Destruction Mech
Three Plates!
We had just enough!
That's not possible!
That's going far beyond three plates!
For the sake of the Earth...
You maggot!
Saber Buster Cannon!
Saber Buster Cannon
Awesome! They did it!
What the hell...?
My ultimate secret technique was defeated!
We're back to normal!
Hey, hey, little shrimp!
Now to finish you off!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique: Polygon Change!
What!?
I can transform into a replica of anyone I've seen once!
So long as you don't know which one's the real one, you can't attack!
What did you say!?
Die, Don Patch!
It didn't work!?
Did he figure me out?
Then I'll try him!
Bo-bobo! I'm the real one!
But how?
My transformations are supposed to be perfect!
How can he see through it?
Actually, he didn't see through it.
Lambada has been cornered by Bo-bobo's hot attacks of friendship.
Finally, finally,
will this long battle see its end?
Piece of shit!
Let's end this!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
The six-on-six Double Triple-Hunters battle is down to just Lambada.
Fist of Polygons Ultimate Secret Technique:
Polygonic Lucifer
Having defeated Lambada's ultimate secret technique, Polygonic Lucifer...
What the hell...?
My ultimate secret technique was defeated!
Bo-bobo and his friends are in the lead!
Can they claim victory at the rate they're going?
Retro Game
Counterattack
Playing and
Watching are
Totally Different
!?
I've seen through your techniques!
They won't work anymore!
I'll be the judge of that!
I can still turn anything into polygons!
He's been beaten so bad, yet still...
This guy is formidable!!
Well of course.
Among the Third's Generation of Hair Hunters,
he's one of the top three, along with Tsururiina III and Fishcake!
You'd have to be crazy to expect to win!
Bo-bobo!
Don't worry, Beauty.
I have a plan up my sleeve.
A plan? What kind of plan?
Why don't you show me this plan of yours?
Take this!
I'll turn you all into polygons!
Bo-bobo!
What!?
What is that texture?
Those aren't polygons!
I've turned unnatural, too!
What in the...?
What's going on?
What is this?
This?
This is the
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Retro Game Playing!
Retro game...
That means an old game, right?
So this is his anti-polygon plan?
But how?
In retro games...
Polygons don't exist!
Got it!
Today's latest games...
look like this...
But games back in the day...
looked more like this!
The art was all made of pixels.
In other words, everything was pixelated!
Are you for real?! I can't use the Fist of Polygons!
They've sealed his polygons!
Amazing!
Is this TV made of... cardboard?
You will now...
experience the good-old
retro games!
I've super shrunk!
First up is action games!
Afro Fight
Let's start!
What's up with these
pathetic graphics?
Take this! And this!
You loser! That kind of
attack doesn't hurt a bit!
Actual Damage
Hey, wait! Stop!
A 1-up Tennosuke!
Don't need it.
Finish!
Actual Damage
Stage cleared!
Now do you understand the severity of action games?
Damn you all...
And now for a shooting game!
I'm the pilot!?
Reality
Boss appears.
Really!?
Die already!
Giant Octopus Uppercut!
What just happened?
Absurd attacks are the
essence of shooting games!
Alright!
Now have a taste of our ultimate puzzle game!
Can you match our brain power?
Stupid Puzzle
Two Seconds Later...
He beat us at our own game!
I don't get it!
Our heads weren't made the same.
Softon! Help us out here!
I'm on it!
Babylon.
That's amazing!
And now for a racing game!
Go!
Nose Hair
Racers
Obstacles!
Seriously!?
Reality
You dumbasses...
Don't mess with me!
They came out!
Are they children!?
How was that?
It totally is made of cardboard!
You bastards!
Fist of Polygons!
Give it up.
Your polygons really did a number on us.
Now it's your turn to endure the humiliation!
Let's go!
The next retro game is a role playing game!
BOINAL
BONTASY
A Princess Appears!
What's with this
ridiculous outfit!?
How could I, Lambada,
be humiliated like this?
A Princess Appears!
Hero Bo-bobo
Appears!
Princess!
Hero Bo-bobo
Appears!
Gunman Tennosuke
Princess!
Appears!
Mage Don Patch
Princess!
Your kingdom is ours!
Princess is assessing
the situation
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Don Patch
Bo-bobo attacks!
Tennosuke uses
Psycho Gun!
Don Patch attacks!
Critical hit!
Princess was defeated!
Hero Bo-bobo's
Level Goes Up!
Gunman Tennosuke's
Mage Don Patch's
Level Goes Up!
This RPG doesn't even go easy on the princess!
Next up is a farming simulator!
Oinkton
What's going on!?
Training
Oinkton
The Oink-Oink Tournament is only a week away!
Go!
Now you've done it!
How dare you humiliate me!
Nu
The real humiliation is only beginning!
Nu Offering Game
© Project Tennosuke
Start Game
Nu
Options
Collection
Back
Bring it to me.
What's this game all about!?
Nu Offering Game
Instruction Manual
Catch the "Nu" falling from the sky.
Climb the pyramid and present them to Lord Tennosuke.
That sounds boring...
Enough bullshit!
Let's keep going!
Next up...
is a historical dating simulation game!
Heart-throbbing
Ambition
Continue
New Game
Horse = 60
Gun = 80
Infantry = 130
Summer
July
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
This is all jumbled up!
I suppose it's time for the confession.
You play this game?
But before that...
Military
Domestic
Diplomacy
File
Military
Domestic
Diplomacy
File
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
File
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Domestic
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Domestic
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Military
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Military
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Water siege.
What kind of game is this!?
I, Lambada, could never be defeated by such a ridiculous attack!
If only I had my polygons...
If only I could use the Fist of Polygons...
Time to finish you off, Lambada!
Last up,
I'll finish with the super-latest game!
That settles it!
I can use polygons in the latest games!
Now, bring it on!
The last game...
is this!
Super-Latest Game
Wait, "Super-Latest Game" is the game's title!?
W-W-W-What is this!?
Bo-bobo Fusion!!
I'll settle this
in one minute!!
Tanaka Sword!!
Tanaka
Tanaka Slash!!
Fist of the
Eyebrow Hair
Forever!!!
Gwaaaaah!!!
Actual Damage
Fist of the Eyebrow Hair Forever!!!
Lambada
Completely Defeated
No way!
They defeated Lambada, one of the top three!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
We finally did it!
Now the Double Triple-Hunters battle goes to Team Bo-bobo!
What about Rice and Serviceman?
N&Ns...
Thank goodness everyone's safe!
Huh? But I can't help but feel we're forgetting someone...
Let's see...
I'm the MVP of this fight!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, an old friend will save you from danger!
Your lucky item is a shiny hand mirror!
If you tied, make sure you can tell between what's real and what's fake.
And if you lost, if you give in to the devil's whispering, you'll live to regret it!
What's with that huge face?
That's the former A-block Captain, Fishcake!
I'll just eat that fishcake!
Hold it right there!
I'll join in this fight!
Just let it go, Tennosuke!
What did you say?
I'll show you that tokoroten is tastier than fishcake!
No one cares!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Fierce Oden Death Match! and Shock! The Power of the Fishcake Strike!!
Fierce Oden Death Match!
Bo-bobo vs Fishcake!!
Shock! The Power of the Fishcake Strike!!
The Dawn of the Fishcake is Near?!
In two parts!
Tokoroten is number one!