Our story begins long, long ago...
in the beautiful city of Edo.
By the decree of the third shogun Iemitsu,
Dengaku Prohibition
a dengaku prohibition order had been passed.
Tokoroten!
Get your tokoroten here!
Aren't you...?
W-Where am I?
Hey. Finally awake, I see?
Are you the one who saved me?
Surely you must know what I am...
Course I do.
You're dengaku, aren't you?
T-Then why?
You always gotta help people when they're in need!
Alright!
Once we get past that checkpoint, you'll be free!
Don't worry and put your trust in me.
Tokoroten!
Get your tokoroten here!
Please don't find out...
Tokoroten!
Hold it right there!
He found out!
You sure look suspicious!
Oh, perish the thought!
I'm just a humble tokoroten salesman, Mr. Guard.
Indeed, you do look like an ordinary tokoroten salesman.
For now, we'll give you this tokoroten DNA test.
Yes, Boss!
DNA Test
DNA test!?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Bo-bobo and his friends
were locked in a fierce battle with Lambada,
one of the top three of Tsuru Tsururiina III's generation.
I will defeat you in the most humiliating way possible!
I'll turn your whole bodies into polygons!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Aura of Polygons!
My head's turning into polygons!
Disco Ball of Desperation!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Disco Ball of Desperation
Damn you!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique:
Wine Red Juice!
Fist of Polygons Secret Technique: Wine Red Juice
It's hot!
That liquid will turn you into polygons once it touches you!
Now!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Dance of Darkness: First Dance!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Dance of Darkness: First Dance
We're back to normal!
Small-fry!
Get on your knees and beg for mercy!
Fist of Polygons Ultimate Secret Technique:
Polygonic Lucifer!
Polygonic Lucifer
Fist of Polygons Ultimate Secret Technique:
Snacks
We're so sorry.
And so, Lambada was victorious,
and the world was ruled by polygons, nah-la!
No, that never happened!
Bo-bobo and his friends attacked Lambada with games one after another, to counter his polygons.
Afro Fight
Actual Damage
Heart-throbbing
Ambition
Horse = 60
Gun = 80
Infantry = 130
Summer
July
What will you do
about your date today,
Sir Lambada?
I suppose it's time for the confession.
Military
Present
Love Letter
Water Siege
Special
Water siege.
Super-Latest Game
Eventually,
Team Bo-bobo's ultimate fusion, Bobopatchnosuke, took the stage.
Bo-bobo Fusion!!
I'll settle this
in one minute!!
Fist of the Eyebrow Hair Forever!!!
Life-and-Death Triple
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
We finally did it!
Now the Double Triple-Hunters battle goes to Team Bo-bobo!
However,
Bo-bobo still did not know that the next foe lay in wait for them...
Former A-block Captain
Fishcake
I absolutely must capture the remnant of the Hair Kingdom before the Third awakens.
Fierce
Oden
Death Match!
Bo-bobo
VS
Fishcake!!
Life-and-Death Triple
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Requiem of
the Battlefield
Rampaging Gadget Area
Ice Mecha Ring
Having defeated Lambada,
Bo-bobo and company headed for the next stage.
This is Eagle Star.
No sign of the enemy on my radar. Over.
Roger.
Remain on the lookout.
Enemy tank at 12:00!
Battle positions, everyone!
Roger!
Lock on!
Come on, take this seriously!
By the way, where's Hekkun and the others?
Those guys...
are taking remedial lessons.
Lessons!
What's going on?
You damn torpedo!
Is she going on a rampage again?
He exploded!
Just from the rubber bands?
Miss Torpedo's remedial lessons have a zero percent chance of survival!
We'll just have to...
defeat Fishcake and Tsururiina III on our own!
What's that sound?
Something gigantic is heading our way!
It's huge!
How dare you defeat my henchmen!?
You goddamn fishcakes!
He's so overpowering!
But...
Bo-bobo wouldn't give in to him!
He's way too strong...
Huh!?
We can't beat him!
Hey wait, you haven't even fought him yet!
Don't you get it?
It's just not possible! I just can't do it!
Stop throwing tantrums! What are you, a child?
Come forth...
Fishcake Castle!
Something's popped out!
And that's not even a castle!
I hereby issue you...
a challenge to a Triple-Hunters Oden Death Match.
Let's hear your answer.
My answer...
is this!
Very well!
That Triple-Hunters Oden Death Match or whatever...
is just what I wanted and not what I wanted!
So which is it!?
Oden Death Match
Allow me to explain one more time.
Fishcake
The Triple-Hunters is the Hair Hunters' ultimate formation,
Bo-bobo
where a team of three fights as one.
Fools.
It's raining fishcakes!
Whether or not you accept...
is up to me!
We've been forced!
We fishcakes are absolute!
That is the law of nature!
Those who are not fishcakes are not fishcakes! They must be wiped from this world!
Only fishcakes, who stand at the top of the food cycles,
are fishcakes,
and are everything!
I'm drowning!
Someone help me!
I'm melting over here!
Dammit!
He's too good!
Fishcake is too good!
We can't win! It's the law of nature, anyway!
Bo-bobo! Don't let him confuse you!
Can't win...
Now then...
Let the Triple Hunters battle begin!
Former I-block Captain
GUY Bo
Send forth your greatest warriors!
Former H-block Captain
Fishstick
Oden Death Match
Fishcake
Bo-bobo
Fishstick
GUY Bo
There's a fishstick in the group!
This is real bad!
Softon's used up all his strength in his battle with Lambada...
And these guys...
I'm melting!
So who should I pick?
Miss Torpedo! Hatenko!
Miss Torpedo! Where are you going?
To continue my lessons.
My other student is waiting patiently for me.
What kind of lessons are these?
And that idiot's dropped out!
That damn torpedo...
I'm gonna kill you!
Hatenko!
Lessons, lessons, lessons!
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
What was that explosion?
Has the enemy started their attack?
I sneezed...
His sneeze is that powerful?
Direct Hit
Go ahead and wreak some havoc, Fishstick.
Yes, Master Fishcake!
Here he comes!
That was...
nothing!
Let go, you bastard!
Well then...
Take this!
Fish Stick Killing Arts!
What!?
Fish Stick Killing Arts : Fish Stick Crush
How'd you like my constrictor move?
Tennosuke!
Dosukoi!
Rikishinosuke!
If you will not select your three, I will eliminate your friends one by one instead.
Fine then!
Then it'll be me, Hatenko, and Don Patch!
Oden Death Match
Fishcake
Fishstick
GUY Bo
Bo-bobo
Hatenko
Don Patch
Alright!
I get to fight alongside my Boss!
Boss!
Where are you hiding?
There he is!
Boss!
Buddha CRY Strike
I, GUY Bo, will defeat you.
The Oden Death Match has begun!
Dengaku in Oden? Will that work?
This Oden Death Match...
must have a trick to it!
It's a seaweed demon!
Come and face me, you low-life of the Hair Kingdom.
Fishcake!
If you take so much pride in being a fishcake...
Then I'll attack you with my fish feet!
Why!?
Don't you mean flat feet?
You're fishcake years too early!
Bo-bobo!
Fishcake is king of the foods!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair
Secret Technique
Eat Egg!!
Just eat it! Eat my soul!
Soul
He's not bad...
Dammit...
New and Former
A-block Captain
Food Battle
Let me in on this fight...
This was meant to be!
Oden and dengaku...
I'll call it...
Odengaku!
It'll be a big hit!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Shock!
The Power of the Fishcake
Strike!!
The Dawn
of
the Fishcake is Near!?
What the hell!?
Why didn't he pick me for this battle?
Isn't this a food battle?
How should I know?
Come on, eat it!
Eat my soul!
Dammit...
They left me, the former captain of A-block, out of this...
I will be a part of this food battle, no matter what!
Fishcake!
I will not tolerate absolute evil like you!
Eat my soul!
This soul...
He ate it all!
Faith!
Hope!
Dreams!
Wrath!
The Fishcake devours all!
Then one more on the house, please!
He did it again!
I'm true to my word...
Tickle, tickle, tickle...
Damn you...
How'd you like my soul?
This is looking bad!
I know!
It's time to use the Oden field to my advantage!
Let's go!
Secret
Technique
Cheer of the Oden Ingredients
Secret
Technique
Cheer of the Oden Ingredients
Fishcake!
Shut up! I demand silence from you all!
He snapped at them...
He snapped at us...
Boss! What are you doing over there?
I am not your boss.
I am Meatball Jiro.
Meatball Jiro!?
Some boss you have there.
You dumbass!
My Boss is the strongest!
Right, Boss?
Huh!?
Secret Technique:
Go For the Javelin World Record!
Secret Technique: Go For the Javelin World Record!
B-B-B-Boss!
Master Fishcake!
Leave this one to us!
Fire!! Homing Meatball Bombs
What!?
Two meters, ten centimeters! A new world record!
Such impudence!
My anger... calls for your death!
You've got to be kidding me!
He blew the oden broth upwards just by that shockwave?
That's correct!
He's riding on a cabbage roll!
I'm drowning!
Odengaku!
What about Bo-bobo?
Flooding!
The river's flooding!
Come on! Put it on!
What are you doing!?
And now...
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Collaborative Secret Technique
Keep the Rivers Clean
Why, you...
You got it?
You processed food?
You're tearing me apart!
Time is money!
Time moves on.
Fish~!!
Fish!!
We're back.
May 5th is Children's Day!
They made a weird carp banner!
I'll change that May 5th...
into Fishcake Day!
That's just crazy!
What a powerful aura!
Ouch!
I'll have to use the Idiot Guard!
I'm melting...
Oh shit!
I gotta find me a replacement!
And I found it!
Intelligence
Speed
Physique
Technique
Power
Power Source:
RZ Konjac Engine
0 Cylinder 0.001
Horsepower
CPU:
Autonomous Thought
System
Konjac E3C
Capacity 2-bit
Hyper Face Remodeled:
Beauty 0.0025
Body Hardness: 0.003
Crashworthiness:
(Only Against Konjac
Jelly) 0.4
Air Bags: None
This is my new
Secret Technique: Konjac Guard!
Good eye.
He picked the wrongest one!
Hey, hey, hey!
Fish!
Cake!
Strike!
Oh, dammit!
No!
Bo-bobo!
That was a close one.
I'd be dead by now if it weren't for the konjac.
But it pierced right through you!
Allow me to fill you in on one thing.
I use no Fist techniques.
I got to where I am with my fists alone!
Bo-bobo!
He's strong!
Go! Go! Fishcake!
Shut up and watch, idiots! You're distracting me!
He snapped at them again!
Alright!
Hajike Soul
Let's take vengeance for Bo-bobo, Hatenko!
Yes, Boss!
Hatenko!?
Let's go!
You're under arrest!
Damn that fishcake! He sent the broth flying again!
Those bells...
You're open!
Surprise attack!
LOCK!
My hand!
Stand back, small-fry!
I never let my guard down!
Pretty please, switch out with me!
Let me help you fight!
Let me fight in this battle!
Let me go, dammit!
Yahoo!
I'm begging you!
Let me fight!
I'll kill you! Let me go!
Found myself a surfboard!
Boss!
And now to beat up that Fishcake!
Fish!
Cake!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Landsurfer Blues
Strike!
And now the broth goes back down.
In this Oden Death Match,
I, the Fishcake, am the mightiest!
The dawn of the fishcake is nearly upon us!
We'll see about that.
W-When did he...?
I'll pay you back...
for everything you've done!
W-Wait!
You're not trying to eat me?
What? What are you doing to me?
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique:
Fishcake Flip
He got him!
Allow me to tell you one thing.
I got to where I was with these chopsticks alone!
Curses!
Flipping a fishcake is the greatest humiliation to a fishcake!
You'll pay for this! You will pay for this!
Is that so?
Next up is Fishcake's fearsome revenge!
Can Bo-bobo and his friends defeat Fishcake?
Dammit!
Let me in the food battle already!
Odengaku, odengaku!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, happy news will come from somewhere far away!
Your lucky item is a notepad that fits in your pocket!
If you tied, your plain, ordinary days will continue, but don't get irritated.
And if you lost, things that you meant as jokes will get you into trouble!
Okay, guys! Dinner's ready!
Hooray!
Here! It's a tokoroten and seaweed sugar sauté! Dig in!
What's with that bizarre combination?
It sounds nasty!
Then please try my cooking!
Former A-block Captain Fishcake! Eat up!
That's not cooking! That's a Hair Hunter!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Side Dish is Perfect (^0^) and My Name is Tenbobo!
Side Dish is Perfect (^0^)
Lightweight Lunchbox Coming Right Up!
My Name is Tenbobo!
I Hate Fighting (^o^)
In two parts!
And don't leave any leftovers!