It's time for another Bo-bobo Theater!
Bo-bobo Theater
The Old-Fashioned Writer
It's been a really long time!
Yoko and Toshio...
and Toshio
That's not right!
Now...
Yoko and Toshio...
and Toshio
Oh, my, my, my!
Whoa, there!
Bo-bobo Theater
The Modern Writer
Yoko and Toshio...
Yoko and Toshio
That's not right!
Oh, my!
Ambulance! I gotta call an ambulance, nah-la!
Gimme one ambulance!
Why did they shoot a missile?
Yoko and Toshio...
Yoko and Toshio
I can't get it right!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
In each of the battle stages of Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX,
Rampaging Gadget Area
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Saber
Bo-bobo
Tennosuke
Hatenko
Ujikinllll
lllllTOKIO
Chisuisui
Star Sabel
Bo-bobo
Tennosu
Hatenko
Bo-bobo and his friends
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
fought the Tsuru Tsururiina III's generation of Hair Hunters from a hundred years ago
Requiem of the Battlefield
XXXXXX
Combat
Blues
Swimsuit Gal
Swimsuit Girl
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Beauty
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
in one Triple-Hunters battle after another,
Ice Machine Crash
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind God
Former N-block Captain
Lapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
Hagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tokoro
Tennosuke
Former C-block Captain
Jeda the Wind G
Former N-block Captain
lllLapalapa
Former Q-block Captain
lllllHagaioh
Bo-bobo
Don Patc
Tokoro
Tennosuke
and narrowly won each one.
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Three-
Thousand
Years
Three-xxx
Thousandx
Yearsxxxx
Yagyu
Yagyuxx
Model
Modelxxx
Torpedo
Girl
Torpedox
Girlxxxxx
Softon
Softonx
Hatenko
Hatenkoux
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
Elbbub of
the Bubbles
Elbbub ofxx
Rem
Ishikawa Goemon
Roman Kikou
Lambada
Ujikin TOKIO
Bo-bobo
Don Patch
Tennosuke
Tennosukell
Beauty
Rice
Serviceman
Kanpyo
Kanpyo-kun
But before them,
stood Fishcake, one of the top three warriors of the Former Margarita Empire.
Fishcake created a giant oden battlefield,
and forced them into a fight.
Now then...
Let the Triple Hunters battle begin!
Former I-block Captain
GUY Bo
Send forth your greatest warriors!
Former H-block Captain
Fishstick
Oden Death Match
Fishcake
Fishstick
GUY Bo
Bo-bobo
Hatenko
Don Patch
Buddha CRY Strike
Having been chosen for the Oden Death Match,
Bo-bobo, Don Patch, and Hatenko
engaged in battle against Fishcake and his men, Fishstick and GUY Bo.
Dammit...
Dengaku in Oden? Will that work?
Fishcake!
Shut up! I demand silence from you all!
He snapped at us...
Boss! What are you doing over there?
I am not your boss.
I am Meatball Jiro.
Meatball Jiro!?
Secret Technique:
Go For the Javelin World Record!
Boss!
Fish!
Cake!
Strike!
Oh, dammit!
No!
Bo-bobo!
The dawn of the fishcake is nearly upon us!
The battle between Bo-bobo and Fishcake rages on.
Upon whom will the goddess of victory smile?
Fist of the Nose Hair
Super Secret Technique:
Fishcake Flip
Oden and dengaku...
I'll call it...
Odengaku!
It'll be a big hit!
Side Dish
is Perfect
Light
weight
Lunch
box
Coming
Right Up ♪
Time to put the fear of me into you!
Plop
Let's go, Fishstick!
Yes, Master!
Behold! This is the symbol of the conqueror:
The Fish Stick Armor!
You're on!
I can't move!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Drowned Body Kick!
Of course that was going to happen!
Such a fool!
Such an attack... won't work on me!
Grandpa! You'll never believe this!
There was a giant fish stick floating down the river!
Great! Let's eat it!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
New Folk Tale:
Fishcake Taro!
This folk tale is gonna make children cry!
That's hot!
Fishcake Taro is born!
That won't work...
What is this? A new kind of splatter film?
Next I'll put you on rice...
Gimme one Fishcake Lunchbox!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Station Lunch Sales!
That's a real weird secret technique!
Order up!
Come on! Give it here already!
Yes, yes, coming right up!
No! It's not gonna fit in the window!
Damn...
I couldn't sell any today...
What were you trying to do, exactly!?
Fish!
Cake!
Strike!
That was too weak.
Bo-bobo!
It's on now!
Time for us to use that move, Hatenko!
Alright!
Hajike Secret Technique: LOCK Surfing!
Smash him from behind!
That won't work!
Huh!?
Boss!
I'm gonna murder you, Fishcake!
Back to my point, let me in the food battle!
I'm begging you!
I'm gonna kill you, too!
Now for the Super Oden Cannon!
Sorry, what?
And fire!
He shot a seaweed roll from his mouth!
Alright! We found your time to shine, Tennosuke!
Fight that seaweed all you want!
Good for you, man.
Go!
Collaborative Secret Technique: Tokoro Cannon!
Tokoroten Represent
Time for a real food battle!
Tokoroten and Seaweed Sugar-dressed Western-style Sautee
Dinner's ready.
Tokoroten and Seaweed Sugar-dressed
Western-style Sautee.
Tokoroten and Seaweed Sugar-dressed Western-style Sautee
And they made some unusual dinner!
Come on, eat it!
Eat the Tennosuke cuisine!
It's actually working...
That's as far as you'll go!
I'll drag you both down!
Excellent work, GUY Bo!
Within this broth is the depths of oden.
I'll drown you all!
But I don't see them anywhere...
Where could they be?
Dragon Palace
What the hell!?
Welcome!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Banquet of the Nymphs!
This is nothing!
Is there no way to hurt him?
Now we'll use this to lure him in!
Fishcake
Secret Technique:
My Lovely Home!
That's not gonna work!
It actually worked!?
There was a squatter!
He's hard...
Don Patch!
Hopeless fools.
I am inedible to all.
On closer look, there are scars on his face!
To this day, many brave souls
have attempted to eat my face.
But none have been able to this day!
These scars are the proof of my might!
Those scars are nothing!
Scar
That's huge! You never had that scar before!
And you literally wrote the word "scar" on it!
You're telling me.
Nu
How in the world could you get that scar? Tell me!
I have a face of steel!
It can withstand any attack!
Circle... circle... vertical, horizontal...
Is that true?
It's the truth.
B-B-B-Beam!
Master Fishcake!
He's reeling!
I'll have you answer to that!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
400-Character Manuscript Paper Festival!
What's going on?
This is nothing!
I'll fill them all up!
Scratch Scratch Scratch
Sir, your deadline is approaching.
It's the birth of a new novelist!
Let's make this a bestseller!
Curse you!
You've entertained me long enough...
Man of the Hair!
But now it all will end!
Eliminate them!
Double Fishcake Strike!
That's an amazing shockwave!
There's no way to block this!
Don't give up! There's still a way!
Super Collaborative Secret Technique:
Twinkling Star Strike
How could it break through my Fishcake Strike!?
Master Fishcake!
The fishcake's face is gone!
Where's his face gone?
It's become...
It's become a star in the night sky!
How pretty...
I was careless...
These guys are strong!
Now become a shooting star and come back down!
It's time to settle this!
It's odengaku. Don't you think it'll work?
So how will Bo-bobo face
a star-shaped Master Fishcake!?
This is getting funner by the minute!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone! Get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX
Rampaging Gadget Area
Requiem of the Battlefield
Ice Mecha Ring
Merry-Go-Round Stage
Life-and-Death Triple
Oden Death Match Field
Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX.
The Triple-Hunters Oden Death Match raged on.
Well? Isn't odengaku great?
My Name is
Ten
bobo!
I Hate
Fighting
My Name is
Ten
bobo!
I Hate
Fighting
Come on down, Fishcake! Let's settle this!
Master Fishcake!
Get off me!
Come back, Master Fishcake!
Cut it out!
The sun's setting...
Let me fight!
As amusing as it would be to keep on shining in the sky...
Very well!
I'm coming, man of the Hair Kingdom!
A shooting star!
I gotta make a wish!
But that's Fishcake!
I want to be with Boss forever!
Boss!
I want to be a man that fits into a bicycle basket...
A fashion model...
There are no decent wishes here!
All rejected!
I don't see my body to return to...
Right here!
Now, come back!
My star tattoo!
It actually came...
Comfortable.
You moron!
Now!
New Secret Technique:
Insect Extermination Combo!!
It was a trap!
Go cling to that rock!
You're treating him like a starfish!?
Master!
Here's your body to return to!
My perfect body!
Now, fly back here!
Alright!
Hold it real tight!
I'm on upside-down!
This is truly a tragedy!
It's my allergies again...
Let's go!
Yeah!
They're coming!
Fishcake's Perspective
Fishcake's perspective, nah-na-la!
It's a new battle sensation, nah-na-la!
Secret Technique:
The Mysterious Chiropractor Dr. Bo's Drastic Treatment!
Master Fishcake!
We'll save you!
I can't let you do that!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
Key Guillotine!
What's up with these keys? I can't move!
Alright! Time to use that move!
Gotcha!
English Mustard
Hajike Secret Technique: Harassment Boys!
C'mon, laugh! Laugh!
Way to waste your key move!
Say...
haven't you fought enough for today?
How about you switch out with me!?
Let me in the food battle!
What are you playing at? You're getting real creepy!
Pretty please, mister!
Dammit,
why do you have to keep pestering me?
It's because you're not a type of food!
What are you, stupid?
It's not just me!
I'm saying, I'm not the only one who's not food!
I'll fuckin' slaughter you!
Unparalleled Fishcake Strike!
Behold!
This is the impregnable Fishcake Formation!
Fishcake Formation
Your counterattack ends now!
There's no way to attack him!
What a pain...
I'll draw his attention.
Get him once he drops his guard down.
Boss!
You're so cool!
He's way more serious than ever...
What's he planning to do?
Now, you guys!
His guard's down! Get him!
How!?
Alright, got it!
Secret Technique: Weapon Frenzy!!
Boss!
I'll at least finish him off with the Fist of the Key...
What the hell did you throw away my keys for!? You dumbass!
Hatenko!
Use this key, then!
Tights
Key!
That's nowhere near a key!
Super Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
Great Spinning LOCK!
Dammit! That's not a real secret technique!
And to finish you off...
Dengaku Shot! Eat up!
H-He's strong...
If I lose now... will I be eaten?
Food products are at the bottom of every food chain.
They can only wait to be eaten.
No! I refuse to be eaten by the likes of you!
Cheese
Cheese In Fishcake!
I will never be eaten!
Thus I declare!
He's got cheese in him!
That's clearly some kind of power-up!
Really?
You don't want to be eaten?
Are you serious about that?
What's with you?
There are foods in this world
Trash
who want to be eaten, but can't!
Tokoroten Fair
What strong persuasiveness!
If you want to give your opinion, then back it up with power!
Food Products Represent
Ten-chan
It seems we are destined to fight.
What's with the shameless sash!?
Food Products Represent
Ten-chan
Nu
I'll give it my all!
Nu-merangs
It's a new Nu item!
Double Nu-merang!
Fishcake Strike!
Food Battle Summit
Food Battle Summit!
1 Second Later
That was quick!
Tennosuke!
I have long thrown away my food pride!
Bo-bobo, we have to help Tennosuke!
Okay!
A diving suit!
Go!
Damn it all...
I was defeated in a food battle...
Tennosuke...
Bo-bobo...
I've come to save you, Tennosuke...
Bo-bobo!
The food battle isn't over yet.
Bo-bobo...
I'll fight alongside you.
OK!
Now... It's fusion time!
Caring for others will cost you your life!
Die in the sea of Oden!
Bo-bobo!
Let's stop... this meaningless battle.
Who's that?
Who is he?
I...
Phone Book
don't want to fight!
Let's solve this through discussion!
Sure. I'll hear you...
God Slasher!
Wait, what about the discussion?
What's with him?
What is up with him?
My name is Tenbobo.
Tenbobo
And I hate fighting.
And yet he's strong!
He's far too strong!
Does Tenbobo, a fusion of Bo-bobo and Tennosuke,
really hate fighting or not?
You have the duty...
Nay, the right to find out!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your hard work will be appreciated by those around you!
Your lucky food is ramen with pork soup!
If you tied, next time you fall to flattery, a little wobble will save your footing.
And if you lost, even if you run ahead of everyone, no one will follow you!
Is Tenbobo really a hero?
He has a peace-loving heart, a gentle face, and graceful moves.
No matter how you look at him, he's a super hero!
Okay, time's up! The hero stops here!
No!
One minute is too short! Let me stay as Tenbobo for longer!
Shh! You'll wake up Tsururiina III!
But he's already awake!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Extraordinarily Strong! and The Devil's Door Opens!
Extraordinarily Strong!
The Heartless, Ruthless Hero Is Here!!
The Devil's Door Opens...!
The Emperor of Darkness Finally Moves!!
In two parts!
It's not my fault!