I think we're lost...
Don't panic.
We've been dropping these Tennosuke crumbs as we walk.
Drop bread crumbs next time, you brat!
Rolling, rolling, Tennie's rolling, rolling...
Rolling...
Rolling, rolling, Tennie's...
Don't throw away your food, damn bird!
Eat Tokoroten!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo...
Did you drop a gold Bo-bobo...
a silver Bo-bobo...
or a normal Bo-bobo?
A normal Bo-bobo.
What honesty!
As a sign of my commendation,
I shall grant you a gold Bo-bobo!
But we don't want this!
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The food battle known as the Oden Death Match has finally begun!
Oden Death Match
Fishcake
Fishstick
GUY Bo
Bo-bobo
Hatenko
Don Patch
Explain why I'm not one of the members!
Hajike Secret Technique: LOCK Surfing!
Smash him from behind!
That won't work!
Huh!?
Boss!
Alright! We found your time to shine, Tennosuke!
Go!
Collaborative Secret Technique: Tokoro Cannon!
Time for a real food battle!
And they made some unusual dinner!
Tokoroten and Seaweed Sugar-dressed Western-style Sautee
Super Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
Great Spinning LOCK!
With his collaborative attacks of friendship,
Bo-bobo seemed about ready to defeat Fishcake!
However...
Cheese In Fishcake!
I will never be eaten!
Thus I declare!
You don't want to be eaten?
Are you serious about that?
There are foods in this world
Trash
who want to be eaten, but can't!
Tokoroten Fair
It's the cry of his soul!
That's incredibly persuasive!
The food battle isn't over yet.
Bo-bobo...
I'll fight alongside you.
OK!
Now... It's fusion time!
Let's stop...
Who's that?
My name is Tenbobo.
Tenbobo
And I hate fighting.
The beautiful pacifist warrior Tenbobo is born!
Can his heart of love bring an end to this battle
with Fishcake, who reigns at the top of the food chain?
Extra
ordinarily
Strong!
Ruthless
The
Heartless,
Hero
Is Here !!
I really...
Phone Book
don't want to fight!
Let's solve this through discussion!
Sure. I'll hear you...
God Slasher!!
Crime and Punishment!!
M-My ears... My precious ears...
My lovely ears...
So that's where your ears were?
I beg of you.
I really do hate fighting.
That's why...
Let's solve this through...
discussion!
He has no intention of discussing anything!
So he's a pacifist...
Where did you get that idea?
Very well then!
Then let us solve this through discussion, as you suggested.
You...
Obstinate fool!
Why!?
He actually understood you!
I...
I could never bear to harm anyone...
He's bringing a world of pain...
But he's overwhelmingly strong!
T-This can't be happening...
What is this unbelievable power?
H-He's too strong!!
I don't like him.
Boss!
I want to spend this short minute I have here...
as a time without fighting.
That's not gonna happen! And it's all your fault!
Master Fishcake!
Please tell me.
Why must you hurt people meaninglessly...
and fight without meaning?
Do you need to ask?
To display my power...
To make the weak know of my strength!
T-That kind of... thinking...
I can never understand it!
Fishstick!!
I've become bite-sized!
Fishstick!
Your mistaken way of thinking has hurt him.
No, you were the one who cut him!
I had no choice.
That question was part of my secret technique: Seven Pacts of the Wish for Peace.
This Secret Technique is my way of bringing peace!
I will now ask you six questions pertaining to peace!
If your responses lead to peace,
I will give you this peace badge.
What is that!?
But if your answers go against peace...
I must eliminate you... from this world.
Eliminate them!?
Now, I'll get right to it!
Question of Peace #1
"What do you think we must do now
to rid our world of war!?"
Question of Peace #1!
"What do you think we must do now to rid our world of war!?"
How foolish! Let war happen as much as it likes!
I'm disappointed in your answer.
I only want...
to save you all!
He has absolutely no intention of saving them!
What terrible ways of thinking you all have.
I said I don't want to hurt anyone!
You're the most frightening guy here...
Now then,
Question of Peace #2!
He's way too strong...
I'll have to get by with an answer he'll like...
Question of Peace #2
"What is the one thing we need most
to bring about peace in our world?"
"What is the one thing we need most to bring about peace in our world?"
That would be... love.
Exactly!
But...
That alone...
won't solve a thing!
He went from Heaven to Hell!
That's not fair! I just gave the perfect answer!
So what is the correct answer to that question?
It's money.
That's so pragmatic!
Next up is Question of Peace #3!
Question of Peace #3
"How do you avoid
an inevitable fight?"
Think of a way to avoid an inevitable fight!
I'm in trouble... If I don't get it right, he'll attack me!
Come on, think of something... Think... Think...
Think...
Incorrect!
He didn't let us answer!
I'm definitely going to kill him!
Next up is Question of Peace #4!
Make sure you listen very carefully.
Question of Peace #4
You expect me to hear that!?
Now you have three seconds to answer!
Three...
Two...
One...
Florida?
Give me a serious answer!
That's too much!
Question of Peace #5
"What is the significance
of protecting others...?"
Question of Peace #5!
"What is the significance of protecting others...?"
Love, love, love!
Pure love, passionate love, benevolence!
Any kind of love!
He's not even listening!
It means something different to everyone!
I agree!
It's finally time for the last question.
Why... Why do your eyes show such sadness?
Thud!
Very well.
I'll tell you why.
I was a fishcake...
that should have been eaten long ago.
Chow time!
My fishcake fell!
But fate...
somehow kept me alive!
And when I awoke...
I was in a dog-eat-dog world...
where only the strong survive!
And five years later...
I reigned at the top of the food chain!
As a fishcake!
But...
The truth is...
I may just have wanted to be eaten!
Who would want to eat you!?
Talk about harsh!
I can only remain in this form for five more seconds!
As my final act, I shall give you peace!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Stay back! You're scaring us!
Peaceful Legend
A World Without War
He really is the strongest!
And they're back to normal!
That was a good fight, Fishcake.
I don't believe it...
King of Foods
I won!
Former A-block Captain
Former A-block Captain Fishcake defeated!
Fishcake, is defeated!
Good work!
Okay, okay.
Good job out there, and all that crap.
Boss...
He's sulking because he hardly did anything...
Cheap, nah-la!
Tasty!
Odengaku
It's cheap, nah-la!
Oden
O
It's the cheap, delicious, and popular Odengaku!
They've opened up a weird store!
And Softon's got a weird part-time job!
Finally, the one who took pride in his absolute might...
The second of the three great powers of the Margarita Empire,
Fishcake, has been defeated by Bo-bobo!
But the final one...
The strongest of them all, is about to awaken!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the NU!
The Story
So Far
The story so far.
Fishcake Strike!
The raging Fishcake...
was touched by Tenbobo's kindness...
It's alright now.
and they put an end to their battle.
No, no, no! He really beat the snot out of him!
Well, we'll go with that for this week.
Either way works for me.
You guys again!?
I will not allow...
Any foolishness!
She's coming at top speed!
Torpedo Strike!
Torpedo Strike!?
Oh, no! We have to calm Teacher's wrath!
Take this!
Softon
Love Power!
Torpedo!
Shachihoko!
Shachihoko.
I don't get this!
Do something quickly!
Oh, right, of course.
He did this move...
and that move...
and Bo-bobo and his friends defeated Fishcake, the second of the Margarita Empire's top three.
Period. That's all. We'll leave it at that.
Who really cares, anyway?
Boss!
They're all doing a rush job!
The Devil's Door
Opens...!
The Emperor of Darkness
Finally
Moves!!
Ferris Wheel
Hekkun, were you alright being alone with Miss Torpedo?
I was fine.
And that is because...
I'm a torpedo!
Tor-tor-tor Torpedo
He's definitely not alright!
Wake up!
Huh? Beauty!
Hekkun!
Softon...
This is my gift to you...
That's the last of the captains!
I could never repay you, Miss Torpedo.
Oh my... He could never repay me...
Even despite our relationship...
She's blushing.
Assault!
Why me!?
Alright!
Now before the final battle...
Our whole team...
is assembled!
That pose makes it look like we're not all here!
The Third is finally awakening...
It's the end of the world...
If he hasn't woken up yet, that's to our advantage!
We'll crush him before he wakes up!
Alright, let's end this!
Keep it steady!
It's heavy!
They dropped her!
That's too foolish!
I didn't do it! I didn't! I didn't!
Totter, totter, totter... Hula dance...
He's in there!
We made it!
Look! Tsururiina III must be in there!
It's opening!
W-What intense pressure he's giving off!
No way...
Is this Tsururiina III's aura?
It's far too big...
Okay, pose!
The Devil's Door...
now opens.
Rejected !!!
He closed it!
Forget that ever happened!
It never happened!
Alright! We made it before he woke up!
They're trying to take him out before he wakes up!
He's yours now, Don Patch! Get him!
Crush him!
Alright, step on him real hard!
You guys handle the rest!
Fist of the Key Secret Technique:
Fist of Babylon Secret Technique:
Elimination!
Alright! Okay, Third!
Have a taste of my attack!
It's time for a walk! What lovely weather we're having!
What are you trying to do!?
Give him to me!
She's worshiping it! What's that torpedo doing!?
Let my feelings...
reach him!
Tsururiina III!
We'll end your life before you even enter!
This is the first time in anime history that anyone has tried this!
And it's all over!
What!?
What the hell!?
I'm sure the Third was in there!
He's gone!
Look up!
There's a weird box in the sky!
What? When did that get there!?
There's no mistake! That's the same guy that was in the casket a moment ago!
Is that Tsururiina III?
But how did he escape the casket?
A magic trick?
Hey, bastard! We can do you one better in magic tricks!
Surprising
Magic
Show!
You don't have to compete with him!
It's been a hundred years since I've seen this sight.
Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III
Is that Tsururiina III?
He's levitating!
Bring it on, punk!
I'm going up there!
That's not gonna take you there!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Card Audience
What is this? An attack?
No!
He's not even looking at us!
So he doesn't even think anything of us! How dare he!
Now, my loyal servants!
I am at last revived!
Give me a grand cheer!
A toast to the new world...
He's going to do something!
Cheers!
The Ace of Hearts and Ace of Spades are having a toast!
What... What did he just do?
It can't be!
The whole town just vanished!
Are you serious?
Is this the power of Tsururiina III?
He's far too dangerous!
I smell humans...
I smell humans, whom I hate the most!
Cool Evening!!!
I came to bring you some summer.
What's gonna happen... in this battle?
I've won.
Full house!
T-Three-of-a-kind...
What's gonna happen in this battle?
Too foolish!
Until next week...
Keep on flying, Don Patch!
That's all the time we have for today!
Tune in next time, nah-la!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, put all your plans into motion and you'll be lucky!
Your lucky item is a marine blue accessory case!
If you tied, someone younger than you will help you when you're in need!
And if you lost, think before you speak, or you'll regret it, nah-la...
We're finally confronting the Third. What's gonna happen?
I'll beat the shit out of the Third!
...Said Don Patch!
I never ever said that!
Miss Torpedo, please defeat the Third for us!
I beg you!
Miss Torpedo changed back to OVER!
That just can't be!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Popularity Rankings Announced!! and OVER vs Third vs Bo-bobo!
Popularity Rankings Announced!!
Who's first? Me?
OVER vs Third vs Bo-bobo! Three-way Battle
of the Deadliest Secret Techniques!!
In two parts!
I-I think a storm's brewing...