Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Indian Elephant Magic!
Indian Elephant Magic
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Leave Dumbo here to me!
Transform!
Acrobatic Ball!
I'll draw his attention!
So make sure you guys go and...
You know you're fighting an Indian elephant, right?
Not a seal?
You gotta fight magic with magic!
Three, two, one!
Robber!
Pirate!
Matador!
Now, bring it on!
Olé!
What were you trying to do!?
I have no option left but to call him!
Red Dengakuman!
Come on out!
Leave it to me, nah-la!
Can't use him!
I'll make pickles out of you, nah-la!
Yeah, yeah.
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Third is finally awakening...
Having cleared all the Triple-Hunters battles,
Bo-bobo and his friends head to the final battle.
And there...
It's been a hundred years since I've seen this sight.
Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III
Before them,
Tsuru Tsururiina III awoke from his long slumber,
and finally revealed himself!
What... What did he just do?
It can't be!
The whole town just vanished!
Are you serious?
Is this the power of Tsururiina III?
He's far too dangerous!
Popularity Rankings
Announced!!
Who's
First?
Me?
What business does a mere human scum have with me?
I came to bring you some summer.
I never imagined there would be humans so close by.
You were so small I didn't notice you!
Really?
Bo-bobo!
Human scum like you are eyesores!
Begone!
We copied him!
Begone, you abominable humans!
Doves?
Run away, guys!
Seriously, who does doves anymore?
That's no surprise.
Make someone disappear or something.
They're judging him!
Popcorn
Gather around, doves! Here's some food!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Dove Magic!
My popcorn's a smash hit!
They shall rain down upon you for all eternity.
T-This is the Fist of the Nose Hair!
But that's not possible!
Is he a remnant...
a remnant of the Hair Kingdom?
It's a pride of lions!
No... On closer inspection...
It's actually Bo-bobo and friends!
Hey! Stop pretending to be me while you do your commentary!
Did you see that?
This is the
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fist of the Beast King!
Jaw chop!
There it is! It's the Law of the Jungle Jaw Chop!
Just pick one.
Realistic or cheap. One or the other.
I've found you, Remnant of the Hair Kingdom!
But first I'll get rid of all the other humans!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Darts Magic!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Darts Magic
What?
A number's stuck onto me!
What are these numbers?
Could these numbers be...?
Correct.
These are the results...
Bo-bobo Popularity Poll
...from last week's popularity poll!
All lies! We didn't run this last week!
The Bo-bobo Character Popularity Poll...
In ninth place...
Softon
Softon!
In eighth place...
Torpedo Girl
Torpedo Girl!
Why, torpedo!?
In seventh place...
Hatenko
Hatenko!
In sixth place...
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo!
I'm sixth place? I'm only sixth place?
But why?
In fifth place...
Beauty
Beauty!
In fourth place...
Dengakuman
Dengakuman!
How unlucky!
In third place...
Tokoro Tennosuke
Tokoro Tennosuke!
Not bad at all...
In second place...
Heppokomaru
Heppokomaru!
And finally, in first place...
Don Patch
Don Patch!
Piece of cake.
So what's gonna happen now?
A party to celebrate me getting first place.
Those numbers are the order...
in which I will eliminate you!
No way!
Uh... how can I say...
Sorry...
There's no need for you to apologize, Softon!
Let's start from one.
Here they come!
I'm sorry I'm in first place!
I'm so sorry I'm in first place by a mile!
I'm coming in to save you, Don Patch!
Bo-bobo!
Except not really.
How the hell did you get first place!?
It's the revenge of sixth place!
Two!
You bastard...
Fist of the Fart!
I've come to help you!
You're in my way!
Or so he thinks.
But I guess he's second place, so he's fine on his own.
He's definitely sore about it!
Three!
Dammit... I can't protect them as sixth place...
Next
He died of his own will!
And five gets a bonus.
Dammit!
Why did it have to be Beauty!?
I'm not gonna make it!
No... I must at least protect Beauty!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Afterburners!
That's lame!
Beauty!
Bo-bobo... Beauty...
But what about Bo-bobo?
B-Bo-bobo...
You OK there, Beauty?
Bo-bobo... You're hurt real bad...
Ace Pilot
Gyro K. Schubert
Don't worry about a thing.
All we wanted...
was to protect the lone flower that bloomed on the battlefield.
Ejecting!
How dare you harm my friends...
I'm taking you down, no matter what!
I will eliminate all humans.
Good job
Pick it up!
Pick up that Dorayaki!
Dammit! He's gonna do something!
Hatenko!
Boss! Look out!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Cloth Magic!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Cloth Magic
That's two vanished.
No way... No way...
Don Patch... Hatenko...
Where did they go?
Relax. I'll find the trick behind his secret technique.
Bo-bobo!
I'm removing my limiter!
No, you pervert...
What was that about?
Tsuru Tsururiina III's Fist of Red Magic is fearsome!
Where have Don Patch and Hatenko disappeared to?
Does Bo-bobo have the slightest chance of victory?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Third
Bo-bobo!
Deadliest
Secret
Techniques!!
Three
Way
Battle
of the
I have gotten rid of the trash.
Now, man of the hair...
It's time to take your Hair Ball!
Hair Ball?
The Hair Ball...
is the source of the Hair Power that exists in all men of hair.
Hair Ball
Do I really have one of those!?
The Hair Ball...
Has that bastard really made Hatenko and Don Patch disappear?
I wonder.
Wonder.
There must be a trick behind it.
It's physically impossible for anyone to just disappear.
Bo-bobo...
Now let's go, Tsururiina III!
Artist's Representative
Dammit!
I have to draw Bo-bobo back in, and quick...
Make sure you draw me super cool...
I'm pretty sure he looked somewhat like this...
Exquisite.
That's totally off base!
Your Hair Ball is mine!
Why now!?
Sleight of Hand!
Sleight of Hand
His hand's inside me!
Hair Ball
At last, it's mine!
Centaur's arrow!
Impudence!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Box Magic!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Box Magic
Now suffer!
Bo-bobo!
Keep the Cleaning Equipment Tidy
I couldn't do the cleaning...
What's going on here!?
Secret Technique:
Cleaning Duty of Sorrow
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
String Magic!
What's going on? I can't move a muscle!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
String Magic
Now hand over your Hair Ball!
I can't move!
I can't let you do that!
Tennosuke!
Huh?
Not again!
Oh, right. I'm made of Tokoroten, so that was pointless.
It's mine!
Hair Ball
Finally!
Finally the Hair Ball is mine!
Hair Ball
Oh, crap!
Transform!
Blast off!
It flew away!
Hair Ball
I'm home!
Welcome back.
How dare you human scum jest at me!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Knife Magic!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Knife Magic
That's nothing!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Tight Buttocks Defense!
Wow! Those are some really tight buttocks!
I won't... allow...
She's acting different this time.
any foolishness!
Miss Torpedo's switching it up a bit...
Miss Torpedo! We've been waiting for you!
Now that you're here, we've got nothing to fear!
She turned back to OVER!
Announcer
Commentator
Oh, wow!
What could this mean, Commentator Beauty?
Don't you remember the fight back in OVER's Castle?
Only two more times!
If you piss me off two more times...
I'll have gathered enough infuriating power...
to revert to my true form!
What!?
My present form is nothing compared to my true form.
You will all be left as corpses in an instant.
That's a strong gust of wind!
It's full! Now it's GAME OVER!
Now I can revert to my true form!
Oh, crap! He's reverting to his true form!
What's gonna happen?
Torpedo Girl
Announcer
Commentator
I didn't even realize that!
You were there for it, Hekkun. You were even doing this announcer schtick.
Yo.
It's been a while, shitheads.
She's become the evil OVER!
What's gonna happen personality-wise?
I've been waiting so long to kill you all!
There's 0% Torpedo in him!
But OVER, now's not the time to be killing us!
That guy's really dangerous!
Please... Please lend us your strength!
A new variety of human trash...
Sure. I'll help you guys out.
Thank God!
I'm so glad he's not our enemy this time!
Go, go, OVER!
Do it, do it, OVER!
Take down the Third!
Of course.
Fist of the Bloody Murder Secret Technique:
Avocado!
Fist of Bloody Murder Secret Technique
Avocado
Bo-bobo!
That bastard! He betrayed us!
You dumbasses!
I had no intention of teaming up with you losers all along!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Explosives Magic!
You're in my way, trash.
Stand aside!
Oh no...
Now that Miss Torpedo's become our enemy, things couldn't get any worse!
Don't worry! I'll draw OVER to our side!
But you tried that already, and it didn't work!
It'll be different this time!
Secret Plan    Cardboard Box
I have a secret plan!
Secret Plan?
Halekulani.
Halekulani
Battleship
Battleship.
Purr-poo!
Purr-poo
Four Lords of Margarita
You look nothing like them!
Now, fight alongside us, OVER!
Fucking idiots.
You're an eyesore.
I'll take out all the trash here.
Don't group me with those shitheads, fucker.
I'll slice and dice up every goddamn one of you here!
You forgot to return the videos you rented, dumbass!
Wait, did you think you could just sneak that nonsense into this scene?
Begone!
Fist of Red Magic Super Secret Technique:
Sword Magic!
Fist of Red Magic Super Secret Technique
Sword Magic
Slice them up!
Fist of Bloody Murder Super Secret Technique:
Death Scythe Cutter!
Fist of Bloody Murder Super Secret Technique
Death Scythe Cutter
Get them!
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique:
Hair Planting!
This one's way more pathetic than the rest!
How's this three-way battle going to turn out?
Bo-bobo, don't you dare lose!
Secret Technique!
Secret Technique...?
S-Secret Technique...?
Get him!
He attacked with someone else's scissors!
You little...
Gimme back my scissors!
With these scissors of friendship
that I have borrowed from OVER...
Third! I will defeat you!
Now, finally Bo-bobo's counterattack begins!
The Tsuru Tsururiina III arc is reaching the climax!
You can't miss the next episode!
You didn't borrow them, did you?
They were just in your hands before you knew it.
Is this really gonna turn out okay?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, speak with more humor and you'll be popular!
Your lucky item is a T-shirt with a cute ornament!
If you tied, you will find warmth with a stuffed animal wrapped in a cloth.
And if you lost, don't doze off while eating ice cream, or your hand will get sticky!
Tsuru Tsururiina III! It's time to settle this!
Wait! You can't drop your guard around him!
That's right! He'll make you disappear with his cape!
You're one to talk!
Whoops, I've been eaten!
I've been eaten up!
No way...
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Menace! Fists of Red and Blue!! and Eat Bo-bobo and Transform!
Menace! Fists of Red and Blue!!
Versus the Afro El Dorado!!
Eat Bo-bobo and Transform!
He Looks Pathetic But He's Super Strong!!
In two parts!
That'll give him an upset stomach...