This is a scary story that actually happened...
The other day, I went to an interview for my child's entrance exam...
In & Out Elementary School
Examination Interview
Of course.
My child is very well-behaved at home, as well...
Scary...
My turn, nah-na-la.
This is a scary story that actually happened...
The other day, I was eating ramen...
Time to eat, nah-na-la!
It was all connected, nah-la!
Scary...
This is a scary story that actually happened...
The other day, in the grocery store below the department store...
Gulp...
Tokoroten
Festival
There was a Tokoroten festival!
Scary...
And of course, this guy will tell the last one.
This is a scary story that actually happened...
This room is actually...
Hundred Tales of the Stairs
End
That's how it ends!?
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III
has awakened from his hundred-year slumber.
T-This is the Fist of the Nose Hair!
But that's not possible!
Is he a remnant...
a remnant of the Hair Kingdom?
But the Emperor was as strong as you might expect.
How dare you harm my friends...
I'm taking you down, no matter what!
I will eliminate all humans.
And in the end...
Boss! Look out!
by the power of Tsuru Tsururiina III's magic,
Don Patch and Hatenko vanished without a trace!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique
Cloth Magic
Now, man of the hair...
It's time to take your Hair Ball!
The Hair Ball that Tsuru Tsururiina III is after...
Hair
Ball
is the source of the power of hair
that exists within men of the hair, nah-na-la!
Then, their savior appeared...
Miss Torpedo!
We've been waiting for you!
Now that you're here, we've got nothing to fear!
She turned back to OVER!
And so, the three-way-battle began
between the toad, the snake, and the slug, nah-la.
You got it all wrong!
Get him!
You little...
With these scissors of friendship
that I have borrowed from OVER...
Third! I will defeat you!
Menace!
Fists
of
Red and Blue!!
Versus
the Afro El Dorado!!
Good!
I've taken you down, Third!
You bastard...
How dare you steal my scissors!?
Bo-bobo... Please handle them carefully...
These are way too heavy!
Mere human scum...
Begone!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Cloth Magic
That's the move that he used to disappear Don Patch!
Get out of there!
No matter! I'll just use this cloth...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Teru Teru Bo-bobo
I just told you, that cloth's dangerous!
Let it shine!
But it's really powerful!
Good!
Now, I'd better put up an umbrella.
I'll taint you all in blue!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Great Cloth Magic
It's huge!
Where are we now?
Did we just get transported?
This is my second Fist:
Fist of Blue Magic Secret Technique
Blue Spirit World of Illusions
He can use two Fists!?
That's a special deal!
Two-for-one? Did he get it two-for-one?
The Red destroys the body...
while the Blue destroys the mind!
Fist of Blue Magic Secret Technique:
Silk Hat Parasites!!
Look out!
Hekkun!
Those bugs will devour all your human reasoning!
Destroy all humans!
Destruction is super awesome!
There goes his reasoning!
No way...
What about everyone else?
On Reason
Ergo, concordently...
He somehow gotten smarter!
Gotta hang up the hangers...
And what are you doing!?
Bo-bobo's Reasoning
Remaining
Thanks for everything.
Reasoning, come back!
Before the Blue, you human trash are all powerless!
Hekkun's...
got it the worst!
Now, give me your Hair Ball!
Hanger!
Hanger?
Fist of Blue Magic Secret Technique:
Box of Submmission
Now there is no escape!
Wriggle!
Wriggle Beam!
Wriggle Beam
I'm Wrig!
And I'm Gle!
Just give it to me already!
Bo-bobo!
Please don't lose!
What!?
When did he switch places with OVER!?
This is the Great Nose Hair Magic...
Hanger ESCAPE
Trick Re-enactment Start
Let's start the Trick Re-enactment!
Hanger!!
Dash dash dash
Fwip
He just shouted the word "Hanger"!
You can still protect your Hair Ball...
It would appear you still have some reasoning left in you.
The legendary skateboard warrior!
Again!
Now I shall suck out all your reasoning!
Fist of Blue Magic Secret Technique:
Crusher Hand!
Bo-bobo!
Bo-bobo's Reasoning
Remaining
Liftoff!
Fried batter...
He's had it all sucked out of him!
It's all over.
I have completely destroyed the Man of the Hair's mind.
Bo-bobo! Please, snap out of it!
Bo-bobo!
What foolish trash!
This is reality!
You have utterly lost!
No...
What are these?
What are... these?
What the hell are these?
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique
Afro El Dorado!!
You made a huge mistake, Third!
Because you stole my reasoning...
I activated this Ultimate Secret Technique!
Each and every one of us is an afro...
and is Bo-bobo!
That's way too amazing, Bo-bobo!
To think you had this secret technique...
Very true.
Now it's time to pay you back one hundredfold!
Red
If you're red and blue...
Blue
Yellow Afro
Then that makes me yellow!!
Let's go, Third!
That's how they're moving!?
What!? Is this happening!?
They're merging with my hair!?
Get out of my...
Bo-bobo Tufts!!
That's one mega afro!
My head's about to split...
The Third's afro split open...
Fried
Beans
Fried beans for lunch!
A weird Bo-bobo popped out!
Fried
Beans
Healthy
Good for you
Delicious fried beans!
God punch!
Actually I like green
soybeans better
God punch!
Tsururiina III!
I'll make you pay for taking my reasoning!
What!?
I'll fuckin' kill you!
For I am the Emperor of Hair!
Slash
Double Golden Strike!!
Human scum...
Bo-bobo's not half bad.
Oh! Hatenko, how long have you been here?
I thought he made me vanish with that cloth, but I ended up in this world.
I'm glad you're safe!
So where's Don Patch?
Check it out, check it out!
Yo!
There he is...
Yo, check it out, check it out!
Yo!
Yo, Asa!
Sha Sha Sha Sha Sha
Damn it all, I must have this power of hair...
No matter what it takes!
At last, Tsuru Tsururiina III has snapped!
The showdown of Hell... right after this!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the NU!
Time to recap the last half...
Here we go!
A cloth sent us flying to this blue world!
The Third had really bad magic... Magic Yakisoba sauce, yeah!
But our hero Bo-bobo didn't lose!
He unleashed his Super Secret Technique!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique
Afro El Dorado!!
Yeah! And that's when I came back in action!
I think from now on I'm gonna play a part...
I'm gonna play a part, I'm gonna play a part...
Shut up!
Begone...
He disappeared again!
Bo-bobo
Eat
and Transform!
He Looks Pathetic
But He's Super Strong!!
The blue world is disappearing...
We're back!
Look at this scenery! It really is the real world!
You're right, you're right!
Was this scenery there before?
It's all destroyed!
The power of the Afro El Dorado...
ended up dealing damage to the real world.
What are these statues!?
Who really cares?
Bo-bobo!
I'll take your Hair Ball...
and you along with it!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Tongue Magic!!
My statues!
Bo-bobo!
Companions on a journey, as compassion in life!
What!?
Hold on a second!
Patchmi
I haven't gotten packed yet!
You can buy whatever you need once we get inside the Third's stomach!
And what if they don't sell it there?
My pajamas!
I'll lend you my pajamas!
That won't do!
I have to have silk ones!
Oh, and my toothbrush!
But you can get toothbrushes anywhere!
Memories!
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
I finally have the Power of Hair!
Now I can finally be free from this abominable human form!
I can revert!
I can finally revert to my true form!
I shall release the seal of hair!
Now I will become...
The king of the world!
What!? What am I?
What kind of ridiculous form is this!?
Is it because I took in those two impurities along with the Hair Ball?
Oh well. At least I have the Hair Ball.
We're doomed...
Bo-bobo got eaten...
Hang in there!
Look at that! Is he like, the Fighting Self-Supporting Student or something?
Perfect!
Now Bo-bobo is dead at last!
Dammit... How could it come to this?
Bo-bobo can't have been...
No.
Those two can't be dead!
Those two are indeed alive.
I believe that, too.
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
New Main Character
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Tetete-te
Te-tetennosuke
New Program
Liar! You definitely believe he's dead!
Pathetic...
That Third looks so pathetic every time I look at him!
I should be able to defeat him as he is now!
Alright, OVER.
Make sure you get my exploits on film.
Who the fuck do you think you're ordering around!?
I'm talking to you, supporting character.
Alright!
Time to cook you up, Third!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Non-Trick Super Magic
He's ridiculously strong!
All of you are fools.
I may look like this, but I still have the power of hair within me!
Along with their deaths.
Oh, no...
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
Please answer me!
Your cries are in vain.
For they are dead.
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
Answer me!
Crap!
There they are!
And they're waving at me!
Oh well, she saw us...
Impossible!
They're still alive inside me!?
Amazing!
So they were alive after all!
I told you, didn't I?
Yeah, and? How are you thick-headed idiots gonna get out now?
What're you gonna do?
So I guess we'll just live in here.
Dinner already?
What!?
Here's your dinner.
Papa
Interest rates are up again...
Honey! Dinner!
Come on...
Put that newspaper down and eat up.
Okay, okay.
What's for dinner tonight, Darling?
Today, I cooked...
Bottle rockets on rice!
My favorite food!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Dinner that Shines in the Night Sky!!
Tsururiina III!
I will defeat you from your insides!
Transform!
Giant Table!!
Spin me, Bo-bobo!
Hell yeah!
Let's go!
Super Collaborative Secret Technique:
Giant Spiky Wheel!!
A whirlwind!
Alright! Now's our chance!
A chance to kill him!
Complete!!
Super Bloody Murder Hajike Secret Technique:
Super Bloody Murdder Hajike Secret Technique
Dazzling Rondo of Youth
They're just having fun!
Ready, Don Patch?
Let's ride this whirlwind out of here!
Okay!
I'll leave some graffiti on my way out.
And done!
Stupid
There's the exit!
Third!
I'm about to show you my Superior Secret Technique!
Take this!
Fist of the Nose Hair Super-Super-Super Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Super-Super-Super Secret Technique
Double Dentists!!
Upper-right, C-2.
C-3 for B.
Pathetic!
They did it!
They're back!
Double!?
What's with their tenacity!?
So you're back to your old self, Tsururiina III.
The Power of Hair is too much for you!
Bo-bobo!
Damn you...
Bo-bobo and his friends have the upper hand for now.
However...
The Emperor who has slumbered for a hundred years has only begun to show his power!
What will happen to Bo-bobo and his friends, now that they've truly angered Tsuru Tsururiina III?
The future?
Who knows?
Why don't you ask the wind?
Stay tuned next time, nah-na-la!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, sing and dance as hard as you can and you'll feel refreshed!
Your lucky song is Don Patch's rap!
If you tied, don't believe stories that are too good to be true, nah-la!
And if you lost, don't slurp your curry noodles, or your clothes will get stained.
It's finally the final showdown with the Third!
We'll show him how great humans are!
Come to think of it, you're not even close to humans. Go home.
That's mean! Come to think of it, you must not be human, because you can extend your nose hairs!
Who cares whether or not I'm human!?
You just contradicted yourself!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Finally Settled!! and The Curtain Rises! The New Emperor Play-offs!!
Finally Settled!!
Tsuru Tsururiina III Defeated!!
The Curtain Rises! The New Emperor Play-offs!!
Bo-bobo's Team Invades!!
In two parts!
And another new battle begins!