They're doing a shoot-out, nah-na-la!
One...
Two...
Three...
Their guns turned into cannons, nah-la!
And they're pointing them at me!
Yahoo!
Hi-yoo!
Why is this happening, nah-la!?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
String Magic!
Now hand over your Hair Ball!
I can't move!
I can't let you do that!
Tennosuke!
Huh?
The battle between Bo-bobo,
and Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III,
Hair Ball
who was after Bo-bobo's Hair Ball, continued.
OVER joined the fray,
turning it into a three-way battle.
Fist of Red Magic Super Secret Technique
Sword Magic
Fist of Bloody Murder Super Secret Technique
Death Scythe Cutter
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique:
Hair Planting!
It turned out that Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III could use two Fists.
The Red destroys the body...
while the Blue destroys the mind!
Fist of Blue Magic Secret Technique:
Silk Hat Parasites!!
Fried batter...
However, our hero Bo-bobo...
What are these?
What the hell are these?
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique
Afro El Dorado!!
Bo-bobo Tufts!!
Double Golden Strike!!
Slash
...rescued the vanished Hatenko and Don Patch.
But...
Bo-bobo!
I'll take your Hair Ball...
and you along with it!
Fist of Red Magic Secret Technique:
Tongue Magic!!
Memories!
I shall release the seal of hair!
Now I will become...
The king of the world!
What!? What am I?
What kind of ridiculous form is this!?
The reason is that he took in two impurities along with the Hair Ball,
in other words, Bo-bobo and Don Patch.
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
Answer me!
Bo-bobo and Don Patch were living peacefully
within Tsuru Tsururiina III's stomach.
Okay, okay.
What's for dinner tonight, Darling?
Today, I cooked...
Bottle rockets on rice!
My favorite food!
Dinner that Shines in the Night Sky!!
The Power of Hair is too much for you!
But they escaped from his insides...
and now, the battle has entered its climax!
Finally
Settled!!
Tsuru Tsururiina
III
Defeated!!
Human trash...
But I'm a dog! A dog!
No one cares!
I am the Emperor!
I'm on a different level, a different value, a different dimension from you trash!
All trash must bow before me!
I will crush all those who defy me!
Third...
You are below trash.
Indeed.
I'll smack that mistaken thinking out of your head!
Watch the greatness of humans as you die!
Fist of the Nose Hair Superior Secret Technique:
Nose Hair Human Express!
You're about to get a glimpse into human life!
Let's start with the birth of a baby!
Into the hospital! Go!
Dental Clinic
That's the dentist!
Now, today we'll pull the tooth on your right.
Yes, Doctor!
Now, please open wide...
Birth
Birth.
That's not possible!
What kind of dentist is this!?
When he pulled my tooth...
Now, today we'll pull the tooth on your right.
Yes, Doctor!
Now, please open wide...
That tooth became a baby!
That alone makes him not human!
And then...
The first thing babies do after they're born...
is receive a name!
Naming
Sanae.
Sanae
Kazuya.
Takako.
What kind of ritual is this!?
I've never seen anyone do this!
In addition,
Those who receive a top acrobatic score...
are unconditionally given a militant name.
Name:
Shogoson!
That completely unnecessary!
Naming Combo!
That's one strong baby!
Cease this nonsensical technique!
Life's only just begun!
Next up is the Elementary School Entrance Ceremony!
First Day of School
First day of school.
In space!?
Study!
Tennosuke!
Graduation
Graduation.
Thank you for everything, Teacher.
As of today,
we are ready to strike out on our own!
That's heavy! You can't spread your wings like that!
But this is amazing!
This Secret Technique may portray a messed-up life...
but it's attacking the Third!
Victory
And so...
we moved on to middle school.
That looks normal!
And right now, we...
are in the middle of Entrance Exam Hell.
Entrance Exam Hell
I don't get it!
What's going on here!?
You just gotta fish to survive!
Enough nonsense!
This technique is nothing!
We're getting to the climax of life!
Bo
The rebellious phase, dammit!
Rebellious Phase
But those are seals!
The seals are actually working!
Hey, bitch, I'm goin' to buy a new seal, so gimme some cash!
Mama
How could you talk to your own mother that way! Honey, say something!
Grow out of it!
Now that we've straightened out, we have to get a job...
Interview
So it's time for a job interview!
Job Interview
Sorry we're late!
You'll be rejected for that!
Did we get the job?
He's shameless...
Pass
You pass!
I like your spirit!
Seriously!?
Two days later
Bankruptcy
Tennosuke Corporation
My company...
Figures.
Having failed at our first job,
we take a new step forward.
Re-Employment
Re-employment.
Now we're sushi chefs!
Eat it! Eat it! Eat it!
Who eats sushi mid-battle!?
Seriously...
It's only common sense!
Human trash! Stop this technique!
You can't stop life once it's started.
Eventually, people fall in love...
He's totally my type!
and separate.
Heave-ho...
He's gone!
Where did he go? Where did that handsome hunk go?
Heartbreak Vacation
Heartbreak Vacation.
Make me whole!
What kind of farce is this!?
Transform!
Heartbreak Robot!
Everyone...
needs to feel my pain!
That's the worst robot ever!
What do you think, Third?
Have you had a taste of the greatness of human life?
Is this the power of mankind...?
That's right.
This is what the human life creates...
the infinite energy!
And...
No one lives this kind of life!
You're totally right!
So you're saying that this secret technique couldn't show the greatness of humans right from the get-go!
He withstood it!
I am Emperor Tsuru Tsururiina III!
You human trash and your techniques are nothing to me! I have endured it all!
Don't get the wrong idea, Third.
From here on out, I'll settle this fight with my own life.
Time to Settle This
W-What!?
The more we meet other humans in our life, the stronger we humans become!
You're about to find that out!
Stay back, trash!
Humans are Wonderful!!
Is anyone behind you even human!?
Humans exhibit their true power through the path they've travelled.
You, who have never took notice of the power of humans, have lost!
Perfect Victory
Perfect Victory.
Tsuru Tsururiina III is defeated!
Tsuru Tsururiina III Defeated
They saved the day!
They finally defeated Tsururiina III!
Your powers were with me, too.
Bo-bobo...
What's the deal?
We fought with you, too!
Meanwhile,
in the Blue World
Meanwhile, in the Blue World...
Boss!
Where are you!?
This is such a fascinating world...
We did it! We did it!
I've taken more damage than I anticipated...
I'd like to kill them here and now...
but I'd better retreat for now.
Running away?
I'm asking if you're running away!
You goddamn coward!
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to, Tennosuke?
Who do you think, blockhead!?
Don't get so full of yourself when you're half-dead!
Right, Bo-bobo?
Cardboard
It's a cardboard cutout!
Just kidding! I didn't mean a word of that!
Fist of the Bloody Murder Secret Technique:
Kabosu!!!
I got in over my head again!
Let's go have dinner!
Good idea! What should we have?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
After a long, hard, battle...
Cats all the way!!
Stay back, trash!
Humans are Wonderful, Meow!
Humans are wonderful, meow!
Bo-bobo defeated Tsuru Tsururiina III!
How deep...
So it was you after all.
The Curtain Rises!
The New Emperor Playoffs!!
Bo-bobo's Team
And so...
after that, Bo-bobo and his friends... recuperated from their fight...
After that, Bo-bobo and his friends... recuperated from their fight...
Take a right here.
OK!
in the sky!
Why?
Look here...
You'll never get your license if you keep this up.
Please, no, Instructor!
What's going on? What are you doing?
Well, we've defeated the Third...
I guess it doesn't hurt to take a break.
Temporary License
Olé!
Passion!
Advance with passion!
Hometown, alright!
Olé!
Driving School
Now my temporary license practice is finally over!
Carmen
Go back to your hometown
This isn't the temporary car license practice...
It's the Carmen license practice! How'd I mix them up?
Now for your final test.
All those with temporary car licenses, follow me.
What about those with Carmen licenses!?
Go home.
So cruel...
But I will get my license!
Watch me, Mama!
Carmen-ish Advance
Raging Flames
Natural U-turn!
Passionate Parking!
Olé!
Spanish Hill Driving!
Private service...
Don Patch!
Roger
Roger that!
That's for not taking driving seriously!
Something's coming!
Found you at last, Bo-bobo!
Mysterious Assassin
Skynyan
How cruel...
Who the hell is he?
A Hair Hunter?
Driving School on a Plane
Doubt it.
He's probably just a civilian here to get his license.
Welcome!
I don't think so!
Over here, too!
Go Patch Team
That's totally wrong! Close, but wrong!
I mean, how does that even work?
I'll kill you!
He's an enemy!
I'll send him packing!
I'll defeat you, and earn my right to enter!
Fist of the Parachute Secret Technique:
Ruthless Body Parachute!
What!?
Why do I get three!?
We're being blown away!
Bo-bobo!
I'm going super-fast!
This calls for a Super S-turn!
Parallel Park!
Now's not the time for games!
Bo-bobo!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Guts Cycling!
They're coming back with amazing guts!
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
I can't do three!
Here in the sky, my parachutes are unbeatable!
You can't even stand up straight!
Yeah, that's so true...
There.
I'm tired.
They're standing!
This makes no sense! Why?
Gum!?
This is my
Secret Technique: Gum Stick!
That's a Secret Technique?
And it's gonna take more parachutes than that to blow me away...
Wait...
I've got more parachutes!
So you're a Hair Hunter, aren't you?
And what if I am?
I'll demolish you!
All I want is the right to enter the tournament!
Fist of the Parachute Secret Technique:
Strong Wind Blowing!
Dammit! I can't hold on!
Bo-bobo!
Hurry! Eat more gum! Come on, eat all the...!
Calm down!
Well then...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Welcome
Bobobo Business District
Kite-Flying Contest in Strong Winds!
I'm tearing apart!
Hang on, young'un!
The dignity of our business district hangs on this!
Who are they?
Now!
October!
Secret Technique: Para-Guard!
Good boy. Good boy.
Why!?
Dammit...
Zero-Warning Dengaku Shot!
Now to finish you off!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
What are you doing!?
Stop it!
Here comes the groom!
What is this about!?
What are you trying to do!?
We can't be in midair without a skydiving wedding!
Have a happy life.
I know I may be inexperienced...
Here, take this parting gift from me.
Now!! Go forth on your new journey in life!!!
Skynan Defeated
Skynyan
is defeated!
I forgot their parachutes!
Is it just me, or did that Hair Hunter say something curious?
Something about the right to enter a tournament...
Yeah. I felt that he had some other objective
besides just defeating us.
So you've noticed.
Right, allow me to explain.
Who said that?
Mole
A mole!?
Wait, are you even a mole!?
Bo-bobo.
Your head is a ticket to entering the competition, mole.
What!?
What kind of competition?
It's...
The Margarita Empire's New Emperor Playoffs, idiot!
He snapped!
Just what I've been waiting for...
Five Ultimate Assassins
The Poet
Giga
Three Murder Brothers
Despair Guy
Katsu
Purr-poo
Halekulani
Ujikin TOKIO
Rem
Lambada
Kanpyo
It will be beginning shortly.
Now, finally...
This boring age will change.
I...
will become Tsuru Tsururiina V!
Is that true?
It's all true.
Softon!
Hatenko!
Every fifty years, the Margarita Empire
holds a summit battle to decide the new emperor.
Even among Hair Hunters, only captain-class or above can enter, mole!
He sure is well-versed in this stuff...
Those who don't have the qualifications...
must prove their strength by defeating Bo-bobo and his team!
Fifth
Bo-bobo!
Let me have your life!
Thank you for everything.
Z-block Captain
This guy's qualified!
Let's go, Bo-bobo.
Where to!?
If all the Hair Hunters are in one place, all the better for us.
We'll raid that tournament!
Yeah!
I'll crush them all...
The Margarita Empire New Emperor Playoffs
held only once every fifty years...
What kind of battle will it be?
And what will become of Bo-bobo!?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll be lucky if you email someone who helped you long ago!
Your lucky item is a photo album filled with memories!
If you tied, eat some healthy tokoroten once a meal for your tired body.
And if you lost, you'll have an urgent errand to run anytime you want to eat noodles!
Alright! Let's beat up all the Hair Hunters!
Let's go!
Wait! We've all been split up!
So it's just you and me now...
Today, the role of the heroine is mine!
Now's not the time for that!
There are enemies here!
I don't care!
Whatever!
I'll fight alone!
Are you trying to hog the spotlight!?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Beauty in Danger!! and Delicious ❤ Means You Lose!
Beauty in Danger!!
I'll Fight On My Own!!
Delicious ❤ Means You Lose!
Go For the World's Greatest Ramen!!
In two parts!
I'm the heroine here!