Alrighty, guys!
Today I'm doing rock, paper, scissors with you guys!
Do we have to?
It's a pain in the ass...
Let's go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
I did it!
I won in rock, paper, scissors...
so I'll take charge of today's opening!
So that was your big idea all along!
Right then, let's get right to it!
Today, we'll be doing a musical!
So that was your master plan?
Always!
Places, everyone!
Express your theme and motivation in a song!
I am Bo-bobo, the noble man of hair!
And I am the heroine!
I'm wobbling young and lively!
I love bittersweet Dengaku, nah-na-la!
Um...
I...
I'm...
I'm a battle nerd!
Battle nerd!
What kind of lame song is that?
Is that what you think of musicals?
You have no taste!
He's no good, nah-na-la...
But this isn't a musical anime in the first place...
I feel for you...
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
At long last..
Bo-bobo has defeated Tsuru Tsururiina III, the strongest man in the Empire's history.
Perfect Victory
Tsuru Tsururiina III Defeated
But meanwhile...
Giga
a semicentennial summit battle had begun
Halekulani
Five Ultimate Assassins
The Poet
with the Emperor's throne at stake!
Three Murder Brothers
I'll crush them all...
Beauty
in Danger!!
I'll
Fight
On My Own!!
Come on then! Tell us where it's at!
Occupied
Come on, spit it out!
Cockpit
Occupied
Having learned of the Margarita Empire's New Emperor Playoffs,
Bo-bobo and company set off to destroy that competition...
and made their way to Egypt.
Fifth Margarita
New Emperor Playoffs
You can become the Emperor!
Entrance
Alright, everyone listen up!
This is the only route that leads to the New Margarita Emperor Playoffs stadium!
All the champions of the Hair Hunters will be there!
Brace yourselves!
So we go in through this hole?
It looks like there was a big battle here, already...
Perfect! Let's get going!
We'll destroy all the Hair Hunters!
Yeah!
Fifth
Let's do this!
New Emperor
Let's become the new Emperor!
It's hot! They seem far more motivated than normal for some reason!
Now...
Let us make for the battlefield!
What's with this wall?
There are frog sculptures on it!
It's just for decoration!
Ribbit.
They stuck out their tongues!
Beauty!
Help me!
Hey!
I'm still here!
What's gonna happen to me!?
That's harsh.
But this sure brings me back.
Ow...
Where's everyone else?
Screw Panda Drop!
Don Patch!
You okay there?
What's going on? The place is filling up with water!
Allow me to explain.
This is Course #26,
The Devil's Undersea Tunnel.
This is real bad...
I'm alone with Don Patch...
Can we get out of this?
Hip Hop Patchmi!
We're finally alone.
Today, the role of the heroine is mine!
Hold it!
Now's not the time for this!
That doesn't matter!
Prepare yourself!
That doesn't matter...
What's with his tenacity?
What're y'all doin' here?
Who's there?
C'mon! This way!
You're Former F-block Captain Ujikin TOKIO!
Hurry, y'all! Gimme a hand!
You want our help?
You're still alive!?
Now!
Come here!
Fist of Summer Secret Technique:
Fist of Summer Secret Technique
Ice-Cold Ice!!!
Amazing!
He made a wall of ice!
But...
That didn't actually help.
Now we can rest easy.
I'll kill you!
Hey! Hey, you!
But why did you save us, when you're our enemy?
Hey!
Even though you didn't actually save us...
Go For the Fifth Emperor
I wanna go down this here road to become the next Emperor,
but there's a course guardian up ahead.
Guardian?
Fer now, we're better off stickin' together.
This must be fate.
Let's team up.
The ice on his head...
The ice on his head's gonna...
Alright!
You got it!
Let's join up!
He's not exactly the most reliable...
But in these circumstances, he might turn out to be a reassuring ally.
Now that I'm here with ya,
we're as strong as a hundred men!
It seems we have uninvited guests...
The guardian!?
You two!
We can't. We can't do it.
I'll give you my cherry if you'll let us pass.
Really, you guys!?
I am the guardian of this course, Higusari Seijuro.
Higusari Seijuro
And I won't let you pass.
I'll have you all drown!
No way...
Do we have to fight this guardian on our own?
Oh! Look at that! I see a shark!
There's a sunfish here, too!
Pay attention for once!
Galaxy Chain
Take this!
Galaxy Chain!
Sunuvagun...
Bring it on!
I'll show ya my power!
Eat this!
Midsummer Sun!!!
Fist of Summer Secret Technique:
I melted...
He's an idiot!
Hey, girl.
I see you're the only one left.
Huh? What about Don Patch?
What the hell are you doing!?
He ran away!
By the way...
The longer you stay here, the more water will pour in.
Now, what will you do?
H-Hey, are you alright?
Girl, I have an oxygen mask here.
If you hand over your friends,
I'll be willing to spare your life.
What the hell, man!?
Ya should be savin' me!
I can't accept this! Don't you sell me out, Beauty!
Here. What will you do?
Hey, what the hell?
Save me!
Me!
Hey, don't you dare sell me out, Beauty!
Hey, don't sell me out!
Don't sell me out!
Save me instead!
You've got to be kidding me!
I could never betray my friends!
I'll fight on my own if I have to!!
Hey... What was with that line?
It was pretty heroine-like...
It's almost like that girl's actually the heroine of this anime!
And am I just an orange fish?
This is stupid!
This is bad...
I can't let this continue on!
Foolish woman.
I'll have you die here!
Take this!
Planetic Chain
Hold it right there!
I'm the heroine here!
Let me go!
Hey!
You got the wrong heroine, dammit!
I'm the real heroine!
No you're not...
I'm the heroine!
I'm saved...
Is Bo-bobo... safe as well?
Ramen Land
Golden Ramen
Pork Soup
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo...
Thick Pork Soup
Delicious Soy Ramen
Ramen House
was in Course #33,
The Ramen Street of Death, eating ramen.
Ramen
Onion
Bo-bobo...
We'd better get a move on.
Is Beauty safe!?
Bo-bobo...
I'm sure she's safe!
Whenever I think about how she's with that idiot Don Patch...
I can't help but worry!
Beauty!
Is Beauty safe!?
He must be really worried...
Who's there!?
It seems another visitor...
has been drawn in by the smell of ramen.
Look!
That's J!
Meanwhile, in the undersea tunnel...
This is bad! The tunnel's still filling up with water!
The hell? The wall I made just done broke!
That ain't possible!
That had a hardness o' 100!
Oh, no!
What's this!?
The strongest man of the Four Lords of Margarita, Halekulani, has arrived!
What's going to happen to Beauty now!?
Never mind who's the heroine! It's money!
Money!
Dammit! They saw me!
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Delicious
❤
Means
You Lose!
Go For
World's Greatest
Ramen!!
Money, money, money...
That's the way...
This man's...
This man's sure ta be the Fifth Emperor!
I see the star of the Emperor o'er this here man!
He's completely corrupt!
So this is Halekulani...
What intense pressure!
So you're the guardian?
Fist of Gorgeous Secret Technique
Death Million Dollar Wing!!!
What beautiful techniques he uses!
He's gonna turn us into coins, too...
Money, money, money...
Hey, girl.
Since you're here, I presume the nose hair man is here, too?
Tell him that I'll be paying him back very soon.
A little more...
Just a little more...
What's your problem?
I'm your lunch dessert.
Really!?
H-Hold it right there!
Are you leaving me for him!?
So was I just a game to you? Answer me!
There was nothing between us.
Isn't that right?
How cold!
You're cold as ice! As ice!
Is this really alright?
We're saved, but...
Sin
Meanwhile,
Bo-bobo was on the Ramen Road...
How could this be!?
How could a man as strong as you have lost?
Are you alright, K?
He's J, Bo-bobo.
Hang in there, K!
That's J!
K!
He's J!
K!!!
J...
Tragic in more
ways than one
Mr. Onion-head!
That man was seduced by my ramen.
A woman!
Bo-bobo...
Be careful with her.
She's powerful enough to defeat J.
That's just what happens to anyone who challenges me, Menma, this course's guardian.
Menma
Bring it on!
I'll defeat you and pass through here!
Then I'll end your lives, along with the customers preceding you!
Customers?
Abandoned Ninjas
Give us a
good home
Ninja...
Abandoned Ninjas
Give us a
good home
It's the Three Stupid Civilizations!
Wait... Abandoned Ninjas?
Mesopotamian Civilization
Yellow
River
Civilization
Indus
Mouth Kick !!!
Fist of the Eyebrow Hair Forever
Oh, were you all abandoned?
Ninja...
All three of them are crawling to him!
Oh dear, what a real shame...
What happened to you? Go ahead and tell me.
Ninja...
Quit your whining, scum!
Two and two is four... Two and three is five...
Just talk properly!
Long time no see, Bo-bobo.
Wanna fight?
And now they talk properly!
Ramen Road
That's enough of your pathetic reunion.
Now, you must fight in this course's specialty,
the Ramen Battle!
Ramen battle?
What is that, hachoo?
Why would we do such a battle, xie-xie!?
They're really getting into it...
The rules are simple.
You make ramen and feed it to your opponent, and if they say "Delicious," you win!
Now, time to face my ramen!
Bring it on!
Ramen
I'll use this to bring you down!
You can't do that with instant noodles!
I'll defeat you and Bo-bobo with this ramen!
That's Khamen!
I'm done!
That's doesn't even look edible...
Dining Table Roulette Start!
Allow me to explain the rules.
You must eat all the ramen that stops in front of you.
If you leave any leftovers, you are disqualified!
I can't wait to see whose will come to me...
Stop!
Huh!?
They're all in front of me!
Bring it on!
I'll eat 'em all!
Disgusting!
He's hardened!
Whoever eats my ramen...
become so overwhelmed by its deliciousness that they can no longer move.
I'm pretty sure he said "disgusting"!
This is the Fist of Ramen Secret Technique:
Fist of Ramen Secret Technique
Delicious Hardening Ramen
And...
The moment before they freeze up, they leave a message about what they thought of my ramen.
Was that...
Frankly, the Khamen
really got to me...
Frankly, the Khamen really got to me...
I knew it!
That would make sense!
Mesopotamia!
You people can't even make proper ramen...
How do you expect to make me say it's delicious?
What do we do?
Don't worry!
You're Master Ramen!
The two of us shall make the greatest ramen in the world!
Yes! Let's do it!
Cooperative Secret Technique out of necessity:
Challenge for the World's Greatest Ramen!
Alright. We now begin your training.
Ramen Way
Yes, Master!
Wrong.
You have no taste, do you?
On closer inspection, the Master's acting really cold!
Five months later
And five months later...
they finally made the world's greatest ramen!
Is this world's greatest ramen!?
Who are you two?
Cup
Ramen
Cup Ramen
Delicious
Wait, they sell this at stores!
I wanna kill them!
We still don't know if this ramen will work on that woman.
Have a taste and tell me what you think.
Very well.
This is...
This taste...
is average!
Then just say it normally.
So it was no use.
Now to finish you off!
Fist of Ramen Secret Technique:
Fist of Ramen Secret Technique
Ten Super-size Ramen Bowls
Ten of them!? We can't evade all that!
Well then...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Ramen Gum
Ramen gum!?
Gum's not gonna work!
Now...
You can no longer escape from my ramen!
There's still a way!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Master, give those ladies
a free meal on me!!
You betrayed us!
He made them eat the ramen before the table stopped spinning...
I never thought that was possible...
Victim number 1!
Number 2!
The Culprit
is Bo-bobo
The culprit is Bo-bobo!
You sure are feisty...
However...
You can't beat my if you stay on the defensive!
Then take a look at the table.
My cooking has made it your way.
What? When did you...?
Hey.
Now, eat it.
I can't guarantee the taste, but I have confidence.
Eat.
I ain't eating you!
Gyoza Shot!
I left leftovers...
I lost...
Bo-bobo has won the ramen battle against Menma!
We did it, guys!
We all did it!
Well, come on, say something!
All our powers have become as one!
You're the enemy! You can't say that!
Seriously...
I can't take my eye off you for a second, can I?
He's a demon...
I expect no less of our arch-enemy, Bo-bobo!
He's gotten a whole rank stronger!
_Exit_
Bo-bobo, look over here! The door's opened!
That must be because we defeated the guardian.
The New Emperor Playoffs stadium must be beyond there.
Alright, let's go!
Beauty might be there!
OK!
There's so many Hair Hunters!
Are these all the guys who passed through the other routes?
Bo-bobo!
What? Bo-bobo?
Let's kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Let's kill him!
The New Emperor Playoffs have begun!
All those who are here are super-warriors
who passed through the routes of death!
Who will stand at the top!?
So that's Bo-bobo?
It seems like Beauty's not here yet.
Let's just wait here.
Kill him! Kill him! Let's kill him!
This feels so uncomfortable...
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your greatest chance for love will come this year!
Your love-love item is your special joke material!
If you tied, you will find a tiny source of happiness in your neighborhood, nah-la!
And if you lost, try getting a makeover and maybe people will like you...
We're surrounded by so many Hair Hunters!
The New Emperor's throne is ours!
You guys perk up your ears and listen...
to my soulful song!
Fever! Fever!
Now's not the time to be singing!
Our next enemy is a powerful Gold Badge warrior!
Oh, I melted.
Oh, now we fused.
I can't tell who's who anymore!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Begin! Scramble for the Badges!! and Run! Bobobo TV Station!
Begin! Scramble for the Badges!!
The Gold Badge is a Symbol of the Strong!
Run! Bobobo TV Station!
They're Here ~ The Menace of the Ratings!!
In two parts!
Wait, who are you?