A Question for All New Emperor Candidates!
What If You Were the Next Emperor?
A question for all new Emperor candidates!
What if you were the next Emperor?
Ex A-block Captain
I would rebuild A-block Base
that was crushed by Neo Hair Hunt Land MAX!
Ex Z-block Captain
I'd make a lot of friends, nah-la!
I'll be in movies! And of course, I'll be the heroine!
Boss...
I'll be your director!
In the name of the God of Babylon...
Former Hair Hunter Guardian of the Jet-Black Room
I will give hope and dreams to all the sinners!
Not that it's ever gonna happen...
But the world would be better off if the Margarita Empire just disbanded, anyway...
Isn't that right, Bo-bobo?
Exactly!
I would bring back the peace and freedom of hair...
I Won't Let You Guys Have It!!
and make all humans equal!
Become the New Emperor!!
Conqueror of the Universe
He's really into it...
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
Fifth Margarita
New Emperor Playoffs
You can become the Emperor!
Having learned that the Margarita New Emperor Playoffs were about to begin,
Bo-bobo and his friends headed to the grounds.
Let us make for the battlefield!
In each of the routes, they faced a guardian...
Before Don Patch, Beauty,
and Ujikin TOKIO, who they just happened to run into,
Higusari Seijuro
stood Higusari Seijuro.
Galaxy Chain
I melted...
Don Patch and Beauty had a hard time against him...
but with the arrival of Halekulani...
Fist of Gorgeous Secret Technique
Death Million Dollar Wing!!!
Higusari Seijuro was defeated.
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo, Heppokomaru,
and the abandoned Three Stupid Civilizations,
Abandoned Ninjas
Give us a
good home
fought Menma in a ramen battle.
Fist of Ramen Secret Technique
Ten Super-size Ramen Bowls
Hey.
I ain't eating you!
Gyoza Shot!
He was victorious!
Coffee ramen...
It was a good concept, but you should've held the lemons.
What kind of ramen is that!? It looks nasty!
Now, after the ramen battle comes the handsome men battle!
That can't be right! Aren't we headed...
to the Margarita New Emperor Playoff grounds!?
Begin!
Scramble for the Badges!!
The Gold Badge
is
a Symbol of the
Strong
!
Kill him! Kill him! Let's kill him!
Bo-bobo...
Defeat Him!
Kill him!
They're talking about you!
Let's kill him!
It's Bo-bobo and Hekkun!
Beauty!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Money!
Who's your friend!?
Well, it's a long story...
Come on, we gotta go!
One yen!
Wait, is this Don Patch!?
Why's he's staring at me...?
In center field... Softon!
There's a bunch of them!
Softon, what happened in there?
It was a fearsome route.
What's that!?
We made it, Jelly Horse.
He's riding on something creepy!
That just leaves Hatenko!
You guys sure took your time.
Yo!
Who's that?
Congratulations on making your way through the routes of death!
Tsururiina IV!
We will now begin the Fifth Margarita Empire New Emperor Playoffs!
Now, just try and take the throne of the Emperor from me!
These two have completely blended in!
Let's take that throne of the Emperor, or whatever.
And this Tennosuke is annoying.
Now let me ask you... Who wants to be the new Emperor!?
Come on, get excited...
That's Bo-bobo!
Oh! He's looking our way!
What's he doing in this tournament?
Why, you ask?
I have something to tell all the Hair Hunters!
Here's your mike.
Um...
You see...
I've come here to crush you all!
Yay! I said it!
Why are you riling up the enemies!?
Leave it to me! I'll quiet them down with my song!
That's gonna have the opposite effect!
Think of the situation!
We who were born into this age...
Viva!
Viva!!
Viva!!!
Ow!
See, what'd I tell you?
Snacks...
The first preliminary will be a Scramble for the Badges Battle Royale.
Bring up the bulletin boards.
Right away.
Something weird showed up!
That board will display who receives what badge: gold, silver, or bronze.
What!?
Gold Lion Badge
Metro
Dark Yaksha
Astarov
Jet K
Silver Pig Badge
Wild Challenger
Louisiana
Rekkamaru
Shrike Guy
Silver Pig Badge
Wild Challenger
Louisiana
Rekkamaru
Shrike Guy
Bronze Natto Badge
Gorbalski
The Poet
McNick
There are a bunch of enemies we've fought before on this list...
Natto badge!
I so want that one!
That really doesn't matter.
I was in charge of the badge design this year.
Silver Pig Badge
Wild Challenger
Louisiana
Rekkamaru
Shrike Guy
Shell
Halekulani
Lambada
Silent Yamada
OVER!? Halekulani!?
Even those two super-strong guys are only silver!
No way! They were from the Four Lords!
Silver is a pig badge. Not interested.
You said it.
Alright! What about us?
I bet we got gold!
Iron Scum Badge
Tokoro Tennosuke
Dengakuman
What!?
Jelly horse!
Don't touch me, scum!
So what kinds of guys have gold badges?
Me, for one!
So you're gold!? Who are you?
Assassination Squad Commander-in-Chief
Nenchaku
I'm Nenchaku, commander-in-chief of the Assassination Squad.
I'm going to figure out just...
how strong you outsiders really are!
Perfect! Bring it on!
You've got weird back hair!
His back hair talked back!
Alright.
I'll stop all your moves!
No way!
That guy's trying to look cool with cellophane tape...
But it's pretty lame, don't you think?
That's cool!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Taping Stop!!
This guy's bad news!
Bo-bobo!
This can't be all you've got.
Of course not!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Birth of New Life!
They molted!
He's got the power!
Super Jacket!
Super Bo-bobo!
You've got it on backwards, Bo-bobo!
My, what a helpless child...
Your personal grooming reflects of your personality, you know!
Sorry.
You guys go home.
Nenchaku vs. Bo-bobo, is it?
What an amusing match-up.
Nenchaku takes no interest in anyone other than the prey he hand-picks.
How convenient.
Bo-bobo...
If, against the odds, you defeat Nenchaku...
I'll consider you qualified to enter this competition.
Begone!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Drafting Stop!!
That's nothing!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Wriggling Champloo!
They kicked up dust to nullify the attack!
What kind of ridiculous attack is this?
But it's futile!
This fabric tape can make its way through the breaks in your little dust storm!
For real?
They're buried in dust! There's no break at all!
You've guarded yourself in dust?
If the gold badge is the symbol of the strong, we'll just have to collect them all!
But we can't get out!
Let us out!
Idiots!
Our only choice is to become a sugar cube!
There's no choice left but to become a sugar cube!
That's not possible! You're dust!
Yeow!!
They're headed for the enemy!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
STOP Tape Knuckle!!
W-We're safe...
Since we're dust, let's retreat into the closet!
Welcome to the Secret Closet Base #8!
Now that such a great dust such as you has come,
this closet will be safe!
Oh, by the way...
Yes?
Aren't you a little smoky?
Sorry! I'm just a piece of dust!
Trash.
Whatever. All hands, fire the Dust Cannon!
Sir!
What a strict person...
Take this!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
The Proud Dust Cannon!!
It's shooting some weird things!
Now go and tear up his throat!
What a plain attack!
I'll cut you apart, dust and all!
You fool!
Thanks to you, we're free!
You're cut! You've been cut!
How fun...
I'll settle this with my next secret technique!
Come again!?
Spring Summer Fall Winter
The Azure Sky
In a Day
Attack Again with Redoubled Efforts
Fist of STOP Super Secret Technique:
Spring Summer Fall Winter
Very nice. Very good handwriting.
Now's not the time to joke around!
This one's not so good, though.
STOP Net Jungle Gym!!
When did this...?
Just now.
Hooray!
It's a jungle gym! Let's play on it!
It's dangerous!
Yay!
I can't move!
It's a trap!
We all saw that coming!
I'm the only one who can move freely in this tape net.
Now die!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Open Body Taping!!
I'm tearing apart!
This tape is infused with my will.
I'll tear you all apart!
Bo-bobo!
T-This calls for...
What?
Complete!
Escaping Collaborative Secret Technique:
Patch Jet!!
You're not getting away!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Homing STOP!!
Well then...
Turn right!
Now left! And right again!
Something serious happened to your eyes!
It's serious!
Huh? Really?
You're right!
No way... Bo-bobo's being pressured!
Is this the power of the Gold Badge?
I'm iron...
Now it's time for you all to eat up!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Never-Ending Death Dinner!!
The fight's over.
My tape is super-adhesive and sticky.
Once it gets inside you, you'll get all sticky and melt!
N-No...
No...
No, I thought it was somen...
It's summer and all...
Based on the circumstances, that's impossible!
No!
Before the Gold-Badge bearing Nenchaku,
Does Bo-bobo have a chance?
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the show!
Your fortune will be revealed at the end of the NU!
Charge!
Bobobo TV Station!
They're Here
The Menace of the
Ra
tin
gs
!!
So this is all the great Bo-bobo has to offer!
No way...
Bo-bobo... Don Patch... Tennosuke...
You can relax, Beauty!
We're still alive and kicking!
It's a weird creature!
Have they fused together!?
We have...
stuck together!
Really!?
Now it's my turn!
The Legendary Fist of the Chainsaw!!
Fist of the Chainsaw!?
Fist of the Chainsaw!!
On closer inspection, Don Patch is the chainsaw!
That's deep!
Enough bullshit!
We're split in three again!
All the better for us! Now we can return to our old forms!
They haven't returned!
Alright!
Now that we're back to our old selves,
let's use that secret technique, Bo-bobo!
Don't you dare mess up, Don Patch!
Same to you, Tennosuke!
I don't know who's who anymore...
Let's go!
Super Collaborative Secret Technique:
Triangle High Tension!!
They had an amazing attack!
Damn you shrimps!
Just what we've been waiting for!
What!?
The energy you're sending into us through this tape...
We'll absorb it all in exchange for turning sticky!
There's no way you can do that!
I'm full!
Now to pay you back hundredfold!
Super-Giant Three Idiot Bazooka!!
Amazing!
They even destroyed the Tape Jungle Gym!
You've done something you shouldn't have.
You're all going to be publicly executed!
Today is the last day of the Hair Hunters!
Rejoice!
Your name will be forever engraved in the history of its downfall!
What about mine?
And mine?
You guys haven't gone back to normal?
It's a bucket!
Let's go inside!
What are you, old-fashioned toys?
Die!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Taping STOP!!
It's wrapping around us!
At this rate...
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
Mummy A Appeared
Mummy B Appeared
Mummy C Appeared
They turned into monsters!
Mummy Attack:
Egyptstic
Power of the Nile!!
What kind of attack is that!?
Dammit... Then I'll double it!
I feel like I'm in the hospital!
There is nothing my tape can't stop!
We'll see about that!
Fist of the Nose Hair Ultimate Secret Technique:
Bobobo TV Station Hour!
What's going on?
Bobobo TV
runs programs non-stop, 24/7!
Try and stop us if you can!
Bobobo TV
Jungle Morning News
First up, at six in the morning,
it's the Jungle Morning News!
They're really hyped up so early in the morning!
Cheetahs
First, we bring you the national jungle forecast!
What the hell!?
Horoscopes
Aries
Taurus
Gemini
Cancer
Leo
Virgo
Libra
Scorpio
Sagittarius
Capricorn
Aquarius
Pisces
Jungle
Forest
Waterfall
Cliff
Jungle
Waterfall
Forest
Jungle
Waterfall
Aries
Taurus
Gemini
Cancer
Leo
Virgo
Libra
Scorpio
Sagittarius
Capricorn
Aquarius
Pisces
Jungle
Forest
Waterfall
Cliff
Jungle
Waterfall
Forest
Jungle
Waterfall
Next is the Jungle Horoscope!
Which one's supposed to be lucky!?
What we're trying to say is that your hairstyle is jungle-esque!
His Molars Grew Out
Can You Hairdo It?
Making Crafts with Paper
Carnage
And from nine o' clock,
is the educational program Can You Hairdo It?
Can You Hairdo It?
Okay, kids! It's time to come out now!
Come on, you bastard!
I can't see!
They aren't the least bit disciplined!
Today we'll be using this folding paper...
to make a space battleship!
That's not even possible!
We're done!
That's totally wrong. Do it over.
Wait, that's amazing enough!
Okay, let's go out and test it!
Yes!
Fire!
Amazing!
They look like nonsensical programs at first...
but they all give damage to the enemy!
Damn you all...
I'll use my tape to stop this...
How about you shut up and look at the TV!?
You Laugh? You Lose!
Show
Hairtime News or something?
Next up is the noontime attraction, The You Laugh, You Lose Show!
You Laugh? You Lose! Show
Host: Bo-bobo
Isn't this a noontime show? This is way too low-key!
And thus, therefore...
Goodbye
Dispirited Fist.
For Tennosuke.
Their attack is low-key, too!
Drama
Mrs. Tokorote
"The Affair"
And next up...
is the popular afternoon drama...
Mrs. Tokorote
Mrs. Tokorote!
What am I in now!?
Seriously, what is this?
It's not housewife-like to have an affair.
Just what I thought I'd hear from Mrs. Tokorote!
Those words went right to my heart!
Mrs. Tokorote!
You're banished from the housewives association!
I'm shocked like a housewife!
Fin
I don't get it!
And now...
We're running two shows at once!
Take this!
Cooking
Double Iron Man
Cooking!!
Introducing the Secret Ingredient
The 4:00 cooking show, Double Iron Man Cooking!
Cement
This is totally pointless!
Anime
Stick Man
"Farewell, My Friend!
Jody's Counterattack of Rage!!"
And the five o'clock popular anime, Stick Man!
A flip book? How is that popular!?
Combined!
Flip Book
"Stick Man"
Sampling time!
Come on, eat it!
How'd you like the taste of Stick Man!?
And they're forcing him to eat it!
Dammit...
And finally, it's Prime Time!
Crime Special
"Runaway Islands 24-Hour
Great Police Dragnet"
Seven o'clock!
Runaway Islands 24-Hour
Crime special!
Follow the Runaway Car!!!
Great Police Dragnet
Finally a normal program!
Where's the runaway car!?
We'll catch him!
You're the criminals!
Samurai News
Today's Report
And last up...
is the late-night Samurai News!
Samurai News
Commentator
Newscaster
Bobobo Bank
Bank Robbery
Bobobo Bank was robbed at early morning today.
The thieves stole five million yen in cash and fled the scene.
Samurailence...
Japan is...
Rotten!
There's a berserk samurai at large! Isn't that way more newsworthy?
We are experiencing technical
difficulties. Please stand by.
Hey, what do you think you're doing!?
It's the producer!
We're still on-air!
Idiot!
Just run anything! I don't care what!
Set up another VTR! Hook it up quickly!
We are experiencing technical
difficulties. Please stand by.
And so, we became bamboo shoots.
That makes no sense!
Bobobo TV
is done broadcasting for today!
So you ended it on your own.
Now that I've weathered through it, I won!
Don't get the wrong idea.
This Secret Technique's true essence is only just starting!
This Secret Technique
converts the ratings of these programs into power,
allowing me to power up!
So it had that effect!
This'll work!
Silence!
Operator
Bo-bobo!
The ratings are in!
No one was watching!
That makes sense.
Has he powered up?
Either way, he's damn strong!
Nenchaku Defeated!
I've got a gold badge!
Alright!
Now for our planning session.
That's enough of that.
I'm gonna destroy all the Hair Hunters here!
Is he a monster?
That's the power of the guy that defeated the Third!
We can't beat him...
We can't beat him even if we all teamed up...
Before Tsuru Tsururiina IV,
and all the candidates for the next Emperor,
Bo-bobo has declared that he would destroy the Hair Hunters!
There's no going back now! He has to do it!
Bo-bobo! The fate of the world is in your hands!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, you'll have an emotional meeting at an art exhibit!
Your lucky item is a postcard with a foreign artist's painting!
If you tied, make sure you check out the place you go on your first date beforehand.
And if you lost, don't go out in sneakers without socks, or your feet will smell bad!
Finally, the preliminaries have begun!
What's with this arena? It's made of plastic bottles!
Come on, come on! Anyone, bring it on!
It's a mountain witch!
A mountain witch is nothing!
And next is the Grim Reaper!
Time for an emergency escape!
He ran away!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Badge Scramble Battle Royale!! and Samba de Bo-bobo!!
Badge Scramble Battle Royale!!
Dream Matches of Familiar Characters!?
Samba de Bo-bobo!!
Yaksha to Mountain Witch to Sambaman!?
In two parts!
Next week's gonna be a big battle!