Bo-bobo in Okinawa!
This sure is nice...
Now that's what I call nice!
Alright...
Now a bit more like that... Like that...
Very nice! These'll be great!
Oh, nice! Nice! Very nice!
No one's here...
Did they leave me behind again?
I wanna go to Okinawa, too!
I wanna go!
Oh God, please take me to Okinawa!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, you guys!
We've had nothing but battles for a while, and haven't had any time to rest.
And we thought it would be nice to take a vacation, even if it was a fake one.
You asshole!
Thus, Bo-bobo's team's staycation ended prematurely.
Ironically...
Only Tennosuke actually made it to Okinawa.
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The legendary summit battle has begun!
Fist of STOP Secret Technique:
Never-Ending Death Dinner!!
No one was watching!
I've got a gold badge!
Bo-bobo has received his first badge.
However...
The next enemy was already lying in wait for Bo-bobo!
Badge Scramble
Battle Royale!!
Dream Matches
of Familiar
Characters!?
Very well.
I approve of Bo-bobo's entrance.
Now for the first preliminary.
Let the Badge Scramble Battle Royale begin!
The stage will be the collection of a hundred stages behind you,
Black Mountain
Black Mountain!
Only those who reach Margarita Castle at the summit
Margarita Castle
will have cleared the first preliminary.
Additionally, to enter Margarita Castle, each entrant must have at least ten badges.
Gold.
Silver.
Bronze.
Any of them.
Now fight! Claim your badges!
Badges?
Just ten's enough, you say?
That's the Admiral for you!
Those badges don't mean a thing here!
You mean to say that these medals that I earned for fighting in countless battles...
were all for naught!?
Damn it all!
Fire!
He's blasting the Hair Hunters away!
Hey. Long time no see, Bo-bobo.
Word
Fist of Gothic Secret Technique
Textualization
Tennosuke
Afro
Ball
Eye
Hand
Leg
Spike
Tennosuke
Halekulani
Lambada
Haoh
The Poet
Giga
Bo-bobo...
We know how much of a trouble you are.
We'll focus on crushing you first!
They're attacking en masse! This is real bad!
Don't panic!
In order for me to get ahead in this fight...
I have found people that will temporarily ally with me!
Squeaknosuke
Super Rabbit
The Teacup
Model
Despair Guy
My greatest allies!
Who's great here!?
Alright!
We'll show you our teamwork!
Let us go!
He's forcing them along!
You sure have the guts, huh?
No, no, no! We can't do it! We'll be slaughtered!
I said go! Or else...
Damn it all!
Despair Guy attacked! He's really in despair!
Alright!
Everyone, follow his lead!
We're desperate!
But he's already done for.
Let's go!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Collaborative Secret Technique
Sweetheart Stupid Dance '98
That secret technique just screams "small fry"!
Enough with these stupid games!
I agree!
Whoa, now's not the time for games.
I have to head for the summit!
Wait, Bo-bobo! Are you running away from us?
I have no interest in anyone but those with gold badges.
I ain't gonna hang around you silver badges, dammit!
Come again? Fight me, Bo-bobo!
We'll fight you in his place.
At Mahjong.
Thirteen Orphans.
Enough messing around!
Well, never mind.
We just have to defeat him sometime this tournament...
Entrance
Alright!
Let's head into the mountain!
That's...
Mole
Badge Holders
The Mole!?
Mole
Badge holders at a low price! 500 Moles each!
500 Moles?
Hand it over!
Equipped!
Wow, they have flower-patterned ones, too!
That's pretty!
We made it!
Wait, what kind of arena is this?
Plastic bottles?
Bottle Edge Arena
And the other Hair Hunters are already fighting on it!
That doesn't matter!
Whoever's got a Gold Badge, come on out!
He's super high-energy!
Youth is wasted on the wrong people.
I know.
They're already drinking it!
Saltwater
But this is saltwater!
Bo-bobo's too strong...
Stand back, small-fry.
You're...
We have a gold badge right here.
What an amazing aura! Who's there?
My name is Dark Yaksha.
Bo-bobo...
I don't know whether or not you came to this competition to become the next Emperor.
But you're a nuisance. I'll get rid of you here.
Margarita Empire's Highest Official
Dark Yaksha (Gold Badge)
Don't get the wrong idea, now.
I couldn't care less about being the Emperor.
I only have one goal...
To destroy the Margarita Empire!
And then we'll take the Emperor's throne once Bo-bobo's spurned it!
That's the plan!
They're making people do all the work for them!
It seems you're taking the Margarita Empire rather lightly.
Unpleasant, indeed.
I'll have your blood rust my Skull Sword!
Skull Sword
What is that sinister sword!?
Since you're a Gold Badge...
I'll just have to beat the crap outta you!
What? What are you...?
Bruise Sword
I'll have your blood rust my Bruise Sword!
Don Patch!
I'm gonna murder Bo-bobo in his sleep.
Let's go!
Huh?
Hey, look here! See these bruises?
You did all that to make them... And you're not even gonna use them?
Chew them up!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Bone Serpent Consumption!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique
Bone Serpent Consumption
Well then...
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Eat Meat, Greedy Boy!!!
Now, eat, eat!
He got so thin his bone structure changed!
What an amusing technique.
Now it's my turn to kick ass!
Let's go!
Collaborative Secret Technique:
Go for the Bruise Big League!!!
Collaborative Secret Technique
My bruises are flying off!
Worthless...
My bruises became skewered dumplings!
Enough of these pranks.
Begone!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique
Bone Eye
Silence...
Huh...? What...?
Nothing's happening!
What the hell are those!?
My Bone Eyes bring the Grim Reaper upon anyone I look upon.
This can't be good! He's way too strong!
Bring it on!
Then try and figure this Secret Technique out!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hair
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Hair Eye
A similar class of move to my Bone Eye.
If that's the case, he's summoned something.
Silence...
There's nothing there, idiot!
You fell for it!
They must be eliminated!
Let me take care of Tennosuke.
It must be humiliating to be defeated by your own ex-lieutenant.
Who's that guy again?
Who knows?
So there are some strong people here. Who would've guessed?
But that's all the more reason for the Dark Emperor to be pleased.
I have a message, Dark Emperor!
The Four Lords of the Reverse Margarita have infiltrated the competition!
Dark Emperor of the Reverse Margarita Empire
Hydrate
Now the Earth will be covered in darkness...
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Samba
DE
Bo-bobo!!
Yaksha
Mountain Witch
to
Sambaman!?
Bo-bobo was fighting the gold badge-class Dark Yaksha.
Meanwhile, Don Patch and Tennosuke were...
We're drowning!
Saltwater
This saltwater is hell!
They made themselves drown!
Nuzube!
Nuzube!?
Nuzube...
They're shrinking!
He lifted them up!
That does it!
We can get out of here!
Let's go, Dark Yaksha!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
And now he's gone into a Secret Technique!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Guts Bat
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique
Yaksha Transformation
It's a mountain witch!
That's no witch!
Run away, guys! That is a foe even beyond me, a giraffe!
Mountain witches are the kings of the jungle!
Seriously!?
Emergency escape!
Don't leave us behind, Mr. Cat!
Now that I have transformed, my power is twentyfold!
He's coming this way!
He's gonna eat us!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Skull Wave!
The summer of 2005 is full of skulls and salt!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique
Skull Wave
Dammit! We have to calm the mountain witch's rage!
Mountain Witch, how about taking a little time to rest in here?
Present
Worn-down...
But he's a Yaksha!
I'll put an end to your life!
H-H-H-Hold on, j-just l-look inside!
The inside of this hut...
is built Arabian-style!
Elegant night...
He's wasting his effort!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Skull Wave!
You can't stop Arabia!
Saltwater
Dammit, where did he vanish off to?
Bobobo
Kendo Dojo
What is this?
Now!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique
Dojo Challenger Repelling Boys
Damn you...
He's gonna eat us!
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique:
Fist of the Skull Secret Technique
Skull Crest Strike
What is this thing!?
It's already over.
The Skull Crest is impossible to defend against.
That skull will extract every bone out from your body!
What did you say!?
My bones!
He's spouting fish bones!
There's no sense of any danger!
Give me back my bones! Please give them back!
I have no bones. What's going to happen to me?
Everything
It's taking everything out of him!
Then what about Bo-bobo?
Bone
A robot came out!
What's with him!? That's not possible!
Go, my bones!
Buster Beam!
Bone
I'll drop him...
That's a Cobra Twist!
Alright! I'll finish him off!
You've got me to deal with, Captain Tennosuke!
Dammit! He was here, too!
Run for it, Tennosuke!
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique:
Super Tokoro Bullet!
Fist of the Wobble-wobble Secret Technique
Super Tokoro Bullet
One hit?
Who did you take me for, Katsu?
This is the difference between me as a captain...
and you as a lieutenant.
Tennosuke's... so cool...
We were wrong...
Now you're alone.
I had no use for that shrimp anyway.
I only need to drink this Skull Juice!
Oh, no! He's going to power up even more!
W-What are you...!?
Let me go!
"Let me go!" and "Leave me" are things you'd say to a geisha!
Kan'ichi...
Hey, I'm right here!
Kan'ichi!
Golden Yaksha
Now!
Dammit! They stole my Skull Juice!
Well done, stupid cat!
Now we, too, can become Yakshas!
Let's go! Yaksha Transformation!
We'll become Yakshas!
Transform!
Fruit of the Earth!
Grace of Nature!
Pizzeria!
With our powers combined, we are the Three Yakshas!
The Three Yakshas
You look nothing like Yakshas!
You're going to become one!?
Let's go, Dark Yaksha!
Have a taste of the power of Mother Nature!
Mother Nature!?
The Power of the Earth and Sun!
The Energy of Water and Plants!
200 Yen Off Drinks Coupon!
One of those doesn't belong!
O Heavens! Give us the power of Mother Nature!
Okay!
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique:
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique
Breath of the Raging Mother Nature
That Secret Technique doesn't have anything to do with Mother Nature!
I can't win...
I have no choice but to revert to my true form!
His true form!?
Is he gonna power up?
You're too late!
Transform!
Sambaman
Dance merrily to the rhythm of summer...
And he, he, he will awaken!
Samba, samba, Sambaman!
I'll defeat you with the glamor of the Samba,
Crush you utterly...
Now that I'm in this form...
The rhythm of my samba will make samba addicts of you!
Samba addicts?
Listen to me!
Sambaphones of Death!
Sambaphone
Samba, samba!
The volume's so low we can't hear it!
What intense volume!
It's working!
Now that you've heard the samba, your body will begin to do the samba against your will!
Saury!
Samba, samba!
Saury samba!
Saury for dinner, with the rhythm of the samba!
Come!
Saury
To the Saury Empire of Dreams!
Saury!
The Saury Empire has fallen!
He's strong!
Now to finish you off with the Samba Step!
Samba step
Shake, shake, shake...
He did himself in!
That bastard...
I ain't losing!
What an amazing battle!
He shouted!
It's really queer down here at the bottom.
Feels like something's gonna jump out at me.
It's a goblin!
That goblin's really staring at me...
Wha- Hey- What are you...
Goblin
I'm being faxed!
I'm being transmitted from a goblin machine!
We've got a fax from Bo-bobo! What do we do?
Let's put it in the washing machine for now.
Good plan.
What?
All the laundry...
has turned into Aloha shirts!
What could this mean?
I guess I leaked some Samba juice!
Samba juice!?
We'll have to wear Aloha shirts this winter!
That's two down!
You two!
Samba!
It seems your Samba blood is crying out.
Samba blood? What have you done to me?
Everyone has Samba blood flowing through them!
The answer is in ancient times... In the true evolution of man that was erased from history!
Which is this!
Such a liar!
In other words, your Samba
is causing my blood to react!?
Samba is unbeatable, Samba is the strongest!
Samba, samba, samba, Sambaman!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
This guy's scary...
Karaoke
Hey, Samba bastard!
Let's have a Raise the Roof Showdown in the karaoke club!
No way!
Just kidding!
Raising the roof is my specialty!
"They're spaced out..."
is what a normal person would say.
But I'm the party master, Sambaman!
Samba, samba, samba!
Limbo!
Shut the hell up!
I broke a bone! It's literally broken!
Now it's my turn!
It's impossible!
If I couldn't do it, you couldn't possibly...
A hunter?
He got them excited!
Now it's time to raise the roof with my song!
Let's go!
He's a true pro!
You've now been defeated!
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm the greatest official of the Margarita Empire!
If I fall, the Margarita Empire falls!
Don't you look down on the Margarita Empire!
One more time! Samba Festival!
Go back to the South!
Dark Yaksha = Sambaman
Defeated
Now we have two gold badges!
Only eight left!
I've lost...
Well, as I promised before our fight...
I'll join you guys!
When did you make that promise!?
So you remembered, Sambaman?
What!?
Let's get a move on!
And so, Sambaman... didn't join them.
Meanwhile...
He lost.
The Surface Margarita Empire sure is pathetic.
Is that all they have to offer?
An unknown enemy...
And this man, who once stole the show...
He smells like a strong foe...
...were waiting for them.
Bo-bobo and his friends head for the next battle, with their proud mission in mind.
Will they make it out alive?
What will become of this dangerous fight?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, your grades will go up if you study with your friends!
Your lucky item is an accessory with a jewel!
If you tied, you'll have an unexpected discovery in the planetarium of a high-rise building!
And if you lost, don't buy things on impulse or you'll regret it, nah-la...
Hekkun's grown huge!
What!?
Is he having another growth spurt?
No! It's the enemy's trap!
I get it! Then we'll crush him!
I'm sorry... I'm not strong enough...
Don Patch?
I can't forgive myself.
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
The Battle Stage is a Giant Hekkun! and Transform!
The Battle Stage is a Giant Hekkun! Baby Mode Activates!!
Transform!
The Raging DO-DO-DO-DO-DO-DON Patch!!
In two parts!
What's with this Don Patch? He's way too cool!