Wind Chime
Summer just says yukatas, doesn't it?
I know...
Second Stage
Now if only we had some fireworks to go with it...
What's going on?
The stage exploded!
What beautiful fireworks...
How pretty...
That's just an explosion!
We gone and destroyed the stage.
Did they do that?
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby!
Baby
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Whose fault is it,
Dare no sei de sonna
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Typesetting:
SystematicChaos
Kazuhiko1412
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby
Baby!
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Idiot Survivor!!
Baka Survivor
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Battle Stage is a
Gi
an
t
Hekkun!
Baby Mode
Activates!!
Summer
What the hell, man? Who the fuck are you?
You wanna fuckin' go?
Ahh! He's scary!
Hekkun!
I'll prepare a more sturdy stage.
He's huge!
It's the giant monster Heppokaurus!
Wow, he's humongous.
No way... Hekkun's grown huge!
Take him down!
And conversely, I've gotten smaller!
Well, good for you.
I got it!
He must have eaten a bunch of rice!
That's not it!
May Heppokomaru become a giant
If only I hadn't made that wish on Tanabata...
That has nothing to do with it!
I'm buried so deep I can't move!
What did you do to me, you bastard?
I've injected you with my dark power.
You'll become the new stage.
Don't mess with me!
How dare you do that to my precious friend!
I'll crush you!
Ow! H-Hey, quit playing with my face...
Do it, Slim.
Slim
Here he comes!
This is bad!
We can't afford to hurt Heppokomaru!
Retreat into his hair!
Bo-bobo... You guys...
You're all thinking of me...
Proceeding with the mission.
Bagworm, bagworm.
They're all hanging down!
Now let's raise some hell!
Okay!
They aren't thinking of me at all...
Dengaku Punch!
Son of a...
Alright, let's go!
They're turning my face into a battlefield!
Bo-bobo! Please think about Hekkun!
Beauty's as kind as ever to me...
Curry Bread!
His hand's huge!
Slim keeps a giant within his body.
And he can bring that giant out by saying the magic word.
He's coming back around!
Mustard
Well then...
Secret Technique:
Great Volcanic Eruption!!
It's spicy!
Crap, it didn't work! He's too powerful!
In that case...
Nu
I'll have to pray to the Mighty Lord Nu!
Hey, what do you think you're doing, putting a weird altar on my head without my permission!?
Give me the power...
Very well. I shall give you the power.
Really?
Nothing is impossible for Nu.
Alright! I'm eternally grateful!
Curry Bread!
Dammit! He took out Tennosuke!
Well then...
Fist of the Nose Hair Super Secret Technique:
Tickling Earthquake!!
S-Stop it! It hurts!
Beauty!
Updraft...
We can't do this secret technique. Never mind the enemy, it'll put our friends in danger!
Bo-bobo... What about me?
Taking pity on your friends?
You can relax, Heppokomaru.
We'll turn you back to normal soon.
Uh... That kinda hurts.
Stop it right now! Turn Hekkun back to normal!
We'll give you a gold badge or whatever you want!
Gold badge, you say?
I have plenty of those already.
What the hell!?
He's super strong!
Excellent strength!
That voice...
W-Who is it!?
I was drawn here by the scent of the strong.
So here they are...
The strong!
Fishcake came out of my nose!
Looks like I finally made it.
Since when were you in my nose?
So you're finally getting fishcake coming out of your nose.
You've really grown, Heppokomaru.
Nope, he just went in without asking.
I missed my timing to come out two or three times.
It was hard.
Why should I care?
Do it, Slim.
Curry Bread!
That won't work, young one.
Now it's my turn to show who's boss!
Fishcake Lightning Drop!!
Yes! Fishcake!
Fishcake!
Will you fight alongside us?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I only want to fight the strong.
I applaud you for landing a hit on Slim.
As a reward, I will tell you who I am.
I am a Dark Warrior ordered by the darkness to eliminate all humans...
One of the Four Lords of the Reverse Margarita Empire, Halon Oni!
Halon Oni
Whatever!
I'll have you return Heppokomaru to normal!
The blood of the strong is seething...
Fishcake's here!
Come to think of it, where's Don Patch?
Sale
Grand Opening
Souvenier Shop
Inside Heppokomaru's Mouth Branch
Come on down! Come on down!
Grand Opening
Today's our grand opening!
What!? They're selling souvenirs in my mouth!
One keyholder, please.
Here. Thank you.
And what the hell is he doing to my uvula!?
Relax, old man.
I'll promise to come back with that belt.
Great, now get out of there!
Go, Slim!
Curry Bread!
Here he comes!
Alright!
I'll...
No, I'll...
Me!
Alright, you take him instead!
Fishcake!
I am...
The fishcake of steel!
Indeed, this fishcake...
is strong!
Dark Fist of the Sword Secret Technique:
Napalm!!
What!?
Idiot Guard!!
As usual!
Fishcake Fall!!
I missed.
Were those swords yours?
How cruel of you!
I only made use of a useless fat-ass.
You inhuman!
Heppokomaru! I'll be borrowing your hair!
Fist of the Nose Hair Secret Technique:
Hair Manipulation Spell!!
Surf's up!
My hair!
Weirdo
Weirdo complete.
Quit playing with my face!
Go, Heppokomaru's hair!
I won't let you take him!
What!?
This one's mine!
Dammit!
He beat me to it!
You wait there!
Food Products Represent
I ain't letting some fishcake take the spotlight!
You're still doing the food battle!?
Tokoroten is the greatest!
Let me go!
Dark Fist of the Sword
It won't work!
It's cutting!
You can keep cutting me!
But I'm not losing to some fishcake!
He put himself back together with cellophane tape!
I'll hold him down, Mr. Enemy!
Now! Get him!
Dark Fist of the Sword Secret Technique:
Big Bang!!
Fishcake Fall!
Are you okay, Tennosuke?
Bo-bobo!
I'm gonna beat down this guy!
So stay out of my way, Fishcake!
This is my prey!
Don't interfere!
Wanna fight?
Fishcake! Behind you!
Begone!
Fishcake Jujitsu:
Fishcake Chop!!
That's a weird chop!
Me, too!
That was just a coincidence.
What are you guys doing!?
My hair's back in shape!
What's with them?
They dodged my Dark Fist!
Should I activate it now?
No, not yet!
Come on. It'll be okay.
Here, have some gum.
We have him now!
And now, to defeat you for good!
Hey Fishcake! What do you say the first one to beat him wins?
I couldn't ask for more!
Let's go!
Shuffling our feet!
Ow, ow, ow!
Just walk normally!
Victory goes to who makes the first move!
Have a taste of my Fishcake Jujitsu!
What kind of stance is that?
Some kind of shockwave?
Idiot! I can just guard my front!
Fishcake Fist Tap!!
Fist Tap!?
What!?
He attacked from above!?
Don't you dare fall just yet!
Don't take me lightly, trash!
Fist of the Nose Hair Top-Secret Technique:
Leg Flick!!
Leg flick!?
It's working!
These secret techniques from above and below
together make a full-point combination move!!
Full-point!?
Those two are rampaging...
just like a dragon and a tiger!
That's giving them way too much credit!
Did we get him?
No, not yet!
Now, finish him off!
W-What!?
Mastermind
Grin.
Hekkun's gone into Baby Mode!
It's Hell on Earth!
Fishcake! Let's call it a truce for now!
This guy's dangerous!
What's that?
What have you done?
Everything up to now was merely the intro.
Now, go, Heppokomaru! Defeat that bad boy!
Calm down, Heppokomaru!
Great Mama
Your mama's right here!
And Don Patch is the first victim to Hekkun's wrath!
Heppokomaru! Your friend's right here!
He's looking at me! This isn't funny!
I won't be caught!
I'll make a getaway on this Nu-cycle T3!
He fell!
I'm not a toy car!
Wasn't he their friend a second ago?
What the hell is going on!?
Alright, now!
Airdropping toys!
Nice!
They're trying to get on Hekkun's good side with toys!
I'm gonna kill you.
That's not gonna get them on his good side!
Is this for me?
Thank you.
I'm gonna kill you.
Bo-bobo!
Stay tuned for part two!
Transform!
The Raging
DO
DON Patch!!
How disappointing.
Fishcake!
Watch my fight very closely.
Whatever strong foe you face...
Start by intimidating them with your eyes!
What pure eyes he has...
They're indeed the innocent eyes of a babe who knows nothing of the world's evils!
Don't look at me!
Don't look at me with those eyes!
What is that processed food guy doing...?
I am a sinner...
who is tainted by sin!
Are you offering me forgiveness?
Even unto a sinner like me?
So this is warmth...
He threw him!
Dark Fist of the Sword Secret Technique:
Homing!
Hekkun!
Idiot! Your back's wide open!
I have no more need for you!
I'll destroy this useless stage!
Oh, shit!
Heppokomaru's buried in the ground and can't counterattack!
Alright!
Let's dig him up,
and let him move his legs!
Take this!
Hekkun!
Go, Heppokomaru!
You did it, Heppokomaru!
He's still way more than we can handle...
Damn you trash...
Dark Succession Rite...
Activate!
Release the Dark Fist of Swords!
Return to the darkness, my power!
And...
In return...
Darkness!
Become one with me!
Halon Oni 2
I never thought I'd have to take this form in this world...
He powered up!
One more!
And they're not even looking...
The enemy transformed over there!
Now's not the time for making totem poles! Pay attention!
He's different.
That's a weak reaction!
Air Slice Wave!
They're coming my way!
The chief's in danger!
Fishcake!
It cut him in a crab shape!
Why!?
Why did you save me!?
You love fishcakes better than all the foods in the world...
I noticed when I first set eyes on you...
As a fishcake, I couldn't watch you die...
Fishcake...
The other day...
Sukiyaki
Yay!
I like konjac noodles better than fishcake!
It's all my fault!
It's all my fault Fishcake became a crab!
And yet, I...
I chose konjac noodles over fishcakes!
I'm a wretch!
Apologize all you like in Hell!
Look out, Don Patch!
He's gone!
I can't...
Anger
forgive myself.
What the actual...!?
What happened to Don Patch!?
He's quick!
Hey, hey.
What's wrong with you?
Focus on the enemy before you.
Save the talk for later.
Where'd this serious Don Patch come from?
Who are you?
Anger
DON Patch
Seems like you can at least provide me some entertainment.
Yeah, I sure will.
Come on, what's your problem?
Why did you change color?
And what's with this cloth? I can't tell what it's for.
Don't try and act cool on us!
Bring it on anytime.
Don't ignore us!
Hekkun slammed them!
Are you guys alright!?
Calm down, Heppoko.
You'll be back to normal soon.
No way! It didn't even faze him!
That weird Don Patch is clearly different from normal!
I'm gonna kill you.
You're wide open!
Air Slice Wave!
That's not gonna work.
And you won't hurt my friends either.
Victory
Hey! You turned my hair into victory!
What do you mean "Victory"?
Are you trying to declare victory with my body?
If you have that much fight in you, it shouldn't be fatal.
That's a relief.
What's he talking about!?
Return to your senses, Don Patch!
Now he should be back to his old idiot self.
That's overdoing it!
Thanks, Bo-bobo.
You've given me your fighting spirit, and I accept.
Wake up!
Thank you.
Now that I have so much fighting spirit,
not even death will keep me from winning.
Leave him to me. I'm gonna win!
This isn't working...
I'm starting to think you're cool!
Me, too!
Very nice, Boss!
We came to watch your victory, Boss!
The Lil' Patches came even though we didn't call for them!
You guys came after all!!
Yes, Boss!!
They communicated!
That must be something in their language only they can understand!
Now, Halon Oni. Let's fight.
I'll take my revenge on Crabzaemon.
Crabzaemon? Does he mean me?
Bring it on. I'll kill you!
Now finally,
we'll see the power of DON Patch!
How much power does he have?
Here I go.
He's fast!
He's weak!
That weird Don Patch is really weak!
Anger... I don't have enough anger...
What a let-down.
Begone!
Come to think of it, the same thing happened three years ago...
Two burger combos! On the double!
Right now, for all children who order a combo,
it comes with an original figurine.
Figurine?
Burger Captain
Here you go.
It's handsome!
My eyes have been stolen by him!
What about that!?
What?
Anger
That's why I can dodge that.
DON Patch changed shape!
What does this mean!?
He's super cool!
Now that he's in DON Patch mode,
Boss powers up the more he gets angry at events in his past!
He can win! Boss's past is the source of his anger power!
Don Patch's past?
I really want to know!
Long ago, I had a friend who used to train with me!
Ten Years Ago
Looks like we've fought to a draw yet again.
Yeah.
In five years...
Let's come back here and settle the score!
I couldn't ask for more.
It's a promise!
Yeah!
And then...
Five long years passed.
Thanks for waiting.
You made it! Let's settle the score...
Beauty!
Yeah!
Hold up, that was me!?
No, no, no! That past is a lie!
Back then, I was secretly trembling. How shameful!
Hey, what are you powering up for!?
That stuff wasn't true!
Bamboo Shoot Sword!!
Impossible! He's strong!
Now to finish you off!
Not yet!
What!?
Listen to my anger-filled past!
I was taught Japanese by cats.
I'm so mad at myself for that!
Hey, you bastard!
What the hell are you doing to DON Patch!?
You got a death wish?
No, no, no!
I don't want Don Patch to steal the spotlight!
It's not possible... This is not possible!
How could you beat my dark self so easily?
Anger
This is the power of my anger.
And...
The power of my friends.
They're slightly different! Who are they!?
Seriously...
I'm so pissed at my bad memory!
Does that kind of anger work?
Alright!
Boss has sprouted the Wings of Rage!
It's our turn to shine!
The Wings of Rage...
absorb even the slightest amount of anger!
Let's form a line and insult Boss!
Yeah!
Complete! Lil' Patch Road!
Lil' Patch Road
What are they doing!?
Anger Meter
Insult
Direction
Lil' Patch Road
Enemy
The Lil' Patch Road is a finishing move exclusive to DON Patch.
The further he travels, the angrier DON Patch grows, and the stronger he becomes.
Now, Boss!
Hurry and run over us!
It's hard for us to insult you, even if we're only faking it...
You guys...
I owe you one!
Anger
Get lost, pig!
Stay back!
Boss Rush!!!
I've lost...
Well done... I have no regrets...
But God...
I have only one request.
This man who defeated me...
If I have another shot at life...
I want to follow him!
Boss!
He became a Lil' Patch!
Why?
That happens all the time!
No, it doesn't!
Looks like God listened to my wish!
You're one of the Hajike Gang from now on!
He's gone back to the normal Don Patch!
And so,
The fearsome Halon Oni of the Four Lords of Reverse Margarita
began his second life as a Lil' Patch.
But Bo-bobo and his friends had no idea...
that moment by moment, the hand of darkness was approaching...
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Time for the final battle!
Let's break into Margarita Castle!
Rem! And Lambada, too! What happened to them?
I don't know anything about this Reverse Margarita Empire...
but I won't forgive anyone who harms my friends!
Bo-bobo really is a super hero!
And I'm the super heroine!
Now, bring it on!
Wait, who are you trying to be?
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Rush Into the Final Battle! and The Raging Super Bo-bobo!
Rush Into the Final Battle!
Enter the Terrifying Clock Face of Sacrifices!!
The Raging Super Bo-bobo!
Inside the Giant Nose Hair, Bears Come Out!?
In two parts!
A rival appears!