Today's finally the day we settle our score.
One...
You're back's wide open!
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Fine, then...
Cow bash!
Damn you...
Beam!
Goddammit, Beam! Beam! Beam!
Stop it this instant!
Don't fight over me!
Don't be ridiculous!
We ain't fightin' over you!
You damn Tokoroten!
Get the hell out of here!
You're pretty good.
So are you.
Bo-bobo! Don Patch!
Come back!
Idiot Survivor!
Translation:
SystematicChaos
Baka Survivor
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Stay in the fight!
Kachinokore
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Kachinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Baby
Baby!
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Presented By:
Hokuto no Gun Hajike Fansubs
http://hokutonogun.com/
Raw Provider:
Bleeds_Tricolore
Dare no sei de sonna
Whose fault is it,
That you're being so pathetic?
Shobokure tonnen
That's why I keep telling you,
Dakara yuteru yaro itsumo
Timing:
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Hey, are you trying to put up with me or something?
Nanka gaman shitennon chauno?
Ain't that right?
Omae souchaun?
Come on, I know you've looked happier than this before,
Motto ureshisou na kao shiteru toki aruyan?
Fuku katta toki toka sa
Like that time you went to buy clothes.
Yeah, you know what I mean!
Sou sou
Hey, you see that old guy's face over there?
Hore mi ano ossan no kao!
That's gonna be you one day!
Omae mo annan natte mau yo!
So, let's go out there and survive!
Sa!
Ikinokotte ikoze
Karaoke: Kazuhiko1412,
SystematicChaos
Climb up to the top,
Yojinobotte
Do a little gloating,
Kachihokotte
Spend some money,
Kane tsukatte
Make some money,
Kane kaseide
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Typesetting:
Drax
Rise up in the world!
Nariagare
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Baby!
Baby
Quality Checking
SpiritofHokuto20XX
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!
Fly up to the sky!
Maiagare
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Just doing it my way
Oreizumu DE
Baka Survivor
Idiot Survivor!!
Translation Check:
SystematicChaos
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Encoding:
SweetDevilStitch
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
Stay alive!
Ikinokore
Idiot Survivor!
Baka Survivor
Baby!
Baby
This is a FREE fansub
Not For Sale, Rent, or Auction!
The Margarita New Emperor Playoffs continued.
Bo-bobo's fight on Heppokomaru
went far beyond extreme.
Great Volcanic Eruption!!
My boy's grown so big...
Tickling Earthquake!!
No, this growth isn't something to be impressed by!
I am a Dark Warrior ordered by the darkness to eliminate all humans...
One of the Four Lords of the Reverse Margarita Empire, Halon Oni!
Halon Oni
Reverse Margarita?
Sounds kinda scary, nah-na-la!
Now, finish him off!
I'm gonna kill you.
Is this for me?
Thank you.
I'm gonna kill you.
Bo-bobo!
DON Patch.
Anger
Don Patch transformed!
Complete! Lil' Patch Road!
Anger
Get lost, pig!
Stay back!
Boss Rush!!!
He's too strong, nah-la!
And so, Bo-bobo and his friends
took a new step forward to face this new unseen enemy.
We will protect the peace and freedom of hair!
Rush Into
the
Final Battle!
Enter the
Terrifying
Clock Face
of Sacrifices!!
The Margarita Empire's New Emperor Playoffs Final Grounds...
Margarita Castle
Margarita Castle.
Octopascal
Bad news!
It's octopusly bad news!
These men calling themselves the Reverse Margarita Empire have infiltrated this competition!
Reverse Margarita Empire?
Never heard of them.
Well, just let them be.
My cosmos energy is about to be filled.
Tsuru Tsururiina IV
Isn't that right, Mako?
Mako
For I am the King!
So he had this up his sleeve?
Mako wasn't a one-shot character after all!
Far below the surface...
is the pitch-black World of Darkness.
And there resides the Reverse Margarita Empire.
I don't see Halon Oni anywhere.
He's probably playing around.
For the moment, I've brought two people we could use as sacrifices.
One weird guy got caught in the mix, too.
Serviceman
Hey. How was the surface world?
Emperor Hydrate.
Quite frankly, they were at a low level,
but we found a few possible sacrifices.
Those are convenient eyes!
That one's handsome!
Very good, my subjects!
Keep gathering more energy of Fist users!
Reverse Margarita Empire Dark Emperor
Hyrdate
And release me...
from this world of darkness!
Sliding Service!
Four Lords of Reverse Margarita
Crimson
So I guess that means we'll have to play along in that boring competition again?
Service!
Four Lords of Reverse Margarita
Three Sacks
It sure is a pain being too powerful.
Service, service!
Four Lords of Reverse Margarita
I hope I find a handsome man...
Service!
Hydrate's Right Hand
Byakkyo
Whether or not we three can return to the surface...
is up to you.
Failure will not be accepted.
Hydrate's Left Hand
Be-bebe
Now!
The Reverse Margarita Empire shall be revived!
We shall kill those surface-dwellers...
and create a paradise of darkness!
What a ferocious aura...
It's far greater than the Third's!
Former Hair Hunter
Rem
If he's let out to the surface, the world will be destroyed!
Meanwhile, Bo-bobo and his friends
were headed to the final battleground, Margarita Castle.
We've got quite a few badges here!
It's too early to relax, Beauty!
This badge-collecting is just the start!
The true summit battle...
will be in Margarita Castle!
In this competition, I will finally put an end...
to my long battle of fate...
with Tsururiina IV!
Bo-bobo
That means I have to watch all the past episodes of Bo-bobo to refresh myself on the story!
Momotaro
The dog, monkey, and pheasant are cool!
That's a copy of Momotaro!
The sun's setting! We have to hurry!
No can do!
We can't go any faster than this!
Why not!?
Apologies!
I must have made this pass the weight limit!
Fishcake! Since when were you there!?
I am truly sorry!
In return, I shall become a power source!
Is it just me, or does this fishcake want to join us?
We don't need the power of a mere fishcake!
They've already formed the Idiot Quartet!
I can't keep up with that!
It's an Antarctic Exploration!
Ow, ow, ow...
We made it... So this is Margarita Castle?
We made it, Bo-bobo.
Butter
They turned into butter!
And the stick kind! I don't get it!
Stick butter, eh?
Now what to do with it?
What the hell are you doing!?
Gatekeeper Trooper
Tsuruta
So you made it, Bo-bobo.
But from this point on...
Only those with at least ten badges may pass!
We have a load of badges right here!
Crap, I didn't claim any badges on the way here!
Hey, wait up.
Show me your badges.
Do these fishcake badges count?
Of course they don't!
Go home!
He's looking at us...
Hey, it looks like Fishcake wants to go inside the castle. Why don't we give him some badges?
He did save Hekkun, and all.
Never!
Too bad for you, Fishcake.
Now let's go inside!
Let's see...
Tokoro Tennosuke and Dengakuman
may under no circumstances
set foot beyond this point.
Bo-bobo...
Before you made it here...
Fifteen warriors have already made it into the castle.
The time limit is today at sundown.
You're the last one! Go inside and have a taste of hell!
Bring it on!
I'll survive and be victorious in this fight!
Now, let's head into the castle!
Castle Educational Tour
Alright, everyone! Single file! One behind the other!
Yes!
That ruins the mood!
Let's head out!
I won't let you go!
You just won't give up...
Somebody help me...
You're...
The Former Hair Hunter, Rem!
What happened, Rem?
What happened to such a strong warrior as you?
Captain Fishcake...
The truth is...
That woman there is our sacrifice.
Hand her over.
Oh, what luck!
That afro guy is a sacrificial candidate.
Really, can't we do something about this warp system? My clothes get dirty every time...
Some people came out of the ground!
I get it!
They're friends of worms!
They can talk with the worms!
I'm so jealous of them!
Three Sacks, you handle this guy.
Capture that woman and that afro guy.
OK!
We're going on ahead.
W-Who are they?
They seem real dangerous...
Professor Worm
Hey, you guys!
Can you tell me the latest worm news?
What the hell are you doing, Don Patch!?
Do you want us to crush you underfoot?
You'll have bad luck if you step on a worm...
Did you bring your badges?
Oh, it's fine, I'm with them.
I'll give you their badges for their entry.
I acknowledge them.
Very well. You may pass.
Us worm lovers have to stick together!
Come on. Go, go!
Why are you giving them our badges!?
Worm!
Giant worm punishment!
They entered the castle!
Participants
List
Secret
Those guys...
aren't on the list of participants!
Maybe they're secret characters?
Maybe they're secret caramels?
Now let's get to work!
We have to get all twelve as soon as we can!
Twelve?
Come forth, Table of Sacrifices!
Table of Sacrifices
What is this thing!?
That guy there is Lambada!
Former Hair Hunter
Lambada
Lambada let himself be captured...
so that I could go free!
I beg of you!
Please save Lambada!
Damn you!
Is that any way to treat my precious henchmen?
I will never... Never...
Forgive...
He folded over at a critical moment!
He really is a fishcake!
Huh!?
When did Bo-bobo and the others become sacrifices!?
No!
Don't "hehe" us! Explain this!
This must be hard on you.
Are you alright, Rem?
Bo-bobo...
I know you were my enemy,
but I ask this of you anyway.
These Reverse Margarita guys
plan to rid the world of humans.
You have to stop them!
You're the only one who can!
Who? Me?
I can't do that!
What a foolish woman!
You can count on that afro all you like, but he's still no match for us!
It can't happen, can it?
Naturally, naturally.
But we won't know for sure until I try!
Papa Sack!
He's torn apart!
Bo-bobo...
Bo-bobo!
There's not much time left until sunset! The castle's gonna close!
Heppokomaru.
Go on ahead inside the castle.
I'll join you after I've taken care of them.
After this break,
Is the super-fun
Bo-boroscope!
Everyone, get ready for rock, paper, scissors!
Alright, here we go!
Rock,
paper,
scissors!
Remember whether you won or lost.
Your fortune will be revealed
at the end of the show!
Bo-bobo...
We have to enter the castle before sunset...
If we're tardy, it'll show up on our record!
Let me go!
Songstress
There are fans in that castle waiting for me to sing for them!
Shut up, you guys.
The Raging
Super Bo-bobo!
Inside
the Giant Nose Hair,
Bears
Come Out !?
Before I go inside the castle,
I'm gonna crush these sacks!
Shut up, idiot!
Papa Sack
We're in the middle of Papa Sack's funeral!
There's a bunch of bags there!
Supermarket
My condolences.
The funeral gifts are bar codes?
Come to think of it, I think that sack
said he was one of the Four Lords of Reverse Margarita...
So are they with that shorty, Halon Oni?
Probably.
Have you already met with Halon Oni?
Yeah.
And we just defeated him.
Not even Lambada and I together
could take on these dark guys...
But they defeated one?
Bo-bobo is truly amazing!
I was the one that beat him.
Don't get ahead of yourselves, small-fry!
Halon Oni was the gofer of the Reverse Four Lords!
We'll show you the Dark Fist that surpasses your True Fists!
Fun Sack
Dark Fist of Three Sacks Secret Technique
"Funbags!!"
What could be inside?
What is this!?
Fools!
We are fully grown adults!
We have no interest in whatever's in those sacks!
Infrared Rays
Try something else.
They're really interested to find out!
I can't take the temptation!
Cheater!
You opened it.
Too bad!
This sack was full of meteors!
They're destroying the Earth!
And it's your fault for opening it!
That bag's destroying the Earth!
Somebody close that bag!
Stop it, asshole!
Winner
Get One Free
Dark Fist of Three Sacks Secret Technique
"Winning Stick!!"
No! Hekkun!
Just one hit...
That sack is strong!
Hekkun...
No...
Beauty doesn't want this!
For Beauty's sake...
Don't you lose, Hekkun!
Boston Crab of Love
What are you doing!? You'll break something!
The Dark Fists are assassination fists that can only be learned in the Dark World.
Their power is triple that of True Fists!
We're on a whole other level!
Our only targets
are the Afro and that woman, who are our sacrifices!
Take this!
Dark Fist of Three Sacks Secret Technique
"Mr. Plunger!!"
Is this the power of the Dark Fist?
What amazing power!
That really knocked him away!
No, he clearly did that himself!
Even Bo-bobo was beaten...
We can't win...
Really!?
Now do you see the power gap, scum?
Now hand over the Afro man and the woman!
If you do, we will stop attacking the Earth!
If I go...
that'll calm things down.
I have to go!
I understand.
I just have to go, don't I?
Rem
As the sacrifice!
At this point, your plan's already failed!
Master Fishcake is protecting me...
Alright. That just leaves the afro guy.
Bring him out!
He got away with it!
Now, hurry! I have little patience!
If we don't stop him, he'll destroy the Earth!
Help me! Bo-bobo!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
He's back!
Bo-bobo!
I will not pardon anyone...
who threatens the peace of this world!
Giant Emperor Robot
Gozaioh
It's the hero of some different anime!
Is this even legal!?
On closer look, her lips are way too thick!
It's a fake!
Dammit! I put too much on!
And now he's been found out!
Damn you surface-dwellers...
You dare make a fool of me...
Unacceptable!
I'll kill everyone except the sacrifices!
Dark Fist of Three Sacks Secret Technique
"Anger Sack Deluxe!!"
Help me, Bo-bobo!
Cry! Cry! Cry in pain!
68...
68!
That's how many supermarkets you've destroyed!
Something's coming from the sky!
They're the souls of all the supermarkets in Japan!
Big Special Sale!!
Big Bargain Sale!!
Thank you very much.
We hope to see you again soon.
Supermarket
By calling on the infinite power...
of the 5634 supermarkets in Japan...
Supermarket
They crashed on the robot!
Super Bo-bobo is here!!
It's him! It's Super Bo-bobo!
It's his infamous victory pose!
Now that he's come out of the left arm, it's as good as won!
Why do you hold such hope, trash?
That small-fry Afro...
will soon become our sacrifice!
Hey!
Stupid sack!
It seems you want to make me a sacrifice.
But the likes of you could never do it!
You won't have Rem, either.
Who do you think you're talking to?
We'll kill you!
Only Bo-bobo could turn around this terrible situation!
The Super Bo-bobo that surpasses the imagination...
Fist of the Nose Hair!
It's huge! This has never happened before!
You fool! It means nothing if it doesn't hit us!
There were bears inside the nose hair!?
You've destroyed the Earth far too much!
Nose Hair Sword!
Slice
Glory to the darkness!
Cutesy sack!
He's strong, he's strong, he's strong!
Bo-bobo really is the strongest!
Very well!
I'll show you the true terror of the Dark Fist!
Dark Succession Rite, activated!
That's the same thing that Halon Oni did...
He's gonna power up, Bo-bobo!
Just go ahead.
No matter what you do, I'll still leave you in the ditch.
Meanwhile, in Margarita Castle...
Ruby
Ujikin TOKIO
Halekulani
Choco Chocotto
Purr-poo
Giga
Battleship
Suzu
Third's Generation Hair Hunter Troopers
Kanpyo
Haoh
Jeda the Wind God
Hatenko
So here we have some sacrifices.
Now, let's get started.
Octopus-mouth Sack has declared
that he will release his Dark Fist and power up!
Can our hero Super Bo-bobo still be victorious?
But man, that was a huge nose hair!
How could he even breathe with that up his nose?
That really doesn't matter, does it?
To be continued!
How long are you going to keep that up!?
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Alright then, everyone, bottoms up!
Hai hai hai minasan kanpai
Everyone raise your hands and shout "Hooray"!
Saa minna de te wo age banzai
All you who want to party like there's no rules
Muhou chitai tannou shitai yatsuwa
Keep on, keep on jamming?
Keep on Keep on jamming
As we get mad, cry, and laugh,
Okottari naitari warattari
Shiteru aida ni
We take the past along with us.
Sugi TAKE wa tsure TAKE
Yo! Are you gonna miss the bus and show up late!?
Yo! Nori okurechatte chikoku ka yo
My manual drive is raising the tension gage.
Tension gage ageru jiriki kadou
I say "I can do it!" and fill up with confidence.
Kanou desu to jishin arige ni mato
Ready, aim, fire! ...I don't know.
Nerai uchi I don't know
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Everyone who wants to shout come on over!!
Sakebitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jump!
Everyone who wants to make a riot come on over!!
Sawagitee yatsu wa atsumare
We'll all burst out laughing! Burst out running!
Minna de bakusho bakuso
everybody say HOhoooo!!
Hip Pop Step Jumping!
Here's the results for the Bo-boroscope, nah-na-la!
If you won, something you've been doing for a long time will finally bear fruit!
Your lucky item is your heart full of dreams!
If you tied, keep your Nu handkerchief ready so you don't show your tears when you say goodbye!
And if you lost, make sure you check the calendar to see when your favorite show's on!
Finally, Three Sacks has powered up!
Whoever I face,
I will crush anyone who threatens the peace of this world!
Bo-bobo, you're so cool!
Alright, now let's settle this with a Bo-bobo Fusion!
Okay! But Don Patch...
you're not allowed!
What... Why?
You have to record my heroism on video!
He's ordering him around!
Next time on Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo:
Enter Super Denbo!! and Finally the Final Battle!!
Enter Super Denbo!!
Countdown of Love and Peace?!
Finally the Final Battle!!
Fist of the Nose Hair FOREVER!!
In two parts!
Next time is the last episode of Bo-bobo!
Don't you dare miss it!