Sensei, are you listening?
Sorry. I was thinking about what
to make for dinner tonight.
Wait a sec.
I was telling you about this
because you told me to!
The discrimination against the
Cursed Children in the Tokyo Area...
And your concerns about how your lives are
going to be, now that Enju-chan's identity
has been revealed at her school...
Your problems are so normal,
they're rather boring.
So you were listening!
Why does humanity have to
exterminate Gastrea, anyway?
Because it's the enemy of humanity.
But there are religious sects that
believe Gastrea is a messenger of God
that has come to cleanse the world.
As they see it, humanity is responsible for using up
all the world's resources, and destroying it.
That's just an extreme point of view
regarding humanity as unnecessary.
Besides, if Gastrea is a messenger of God,
what does that make the Cursed Children?
Agents of God serving as messengers
between humanity and Gastrea.
Enju is a human!
She is a human being with
a personality and a will!
She is nothing more and nothing less!
Exactly. See? You do understand.
Listen, Rentaro-kun.
At least you know who you are
and where you came from.
Enju-chan doesn't even
know that about herself...
Most of the Cursed Children in the
outer district were abandoned children.
They never know their parents
or anything of the outside world,
and are only viewed with scorn by most.
So who's going support,
teach, and lead those girls?
Aren't you two family?
Thanks, Sensei.
Oh, yeah...
I've got a message from your patron.
He says to visit the student
council office once in a while.
Hello?
Is this Satomi-san?
Yes.
I'm Aihara-san's homeroom teacher. Um...
Aihara-san came to school this morning...
I'll be right there!
#03 The Children of Fate
Stop coming here!
You tricked us!
Don't come near me!
Go home!
You stupid Gastrea!
Thanks to you guys killing anyone
and everyone, my family was...
That wasn't me! I am human!
I am...
I am... human!
Rentaro...
Enju,
let's change schools.
I do not... want to... give in.
I made... so many friends...
They aren't your friends anymore.
Even so...
Even so, do we still have to fight?
Yes.
Satomi-kun! We've located the Gastrea
that was the source of infection.
We're going to get there first!
Did you really have to call Dr. Heli?
I used up next year's tuition,
so if anyone beats us to it,
I'll have to quit school!
What is that?
It's a Gastrea!
There are spiders that use webs
as parachutes and travel around.
It's sort of like that...
I see...
This is one of the original abilities
that Sensei was talking about?
Enju?
Enju, wait!
Decrease altitude!
Huh?
Hurry!
G-Got it.
Enju!
Rentaro... I defeated it.
I have defeated it.
Well?
I fought it, didn't I?
Yeah...
I protected... everyone in school...
Rentaro!
You have me.
It may be true that all we
can do right now is fight.
And I know how anxious you feel,
being unsure which way to go.
But, Enju, you have me!
I care about you more than anyone else does!
Even if the world doesn't accept you,
I'll always be right by your side!
Thank you, Rentaro.
All right. Let's get what we
came here for and go home.
Yeah.
I wonder what's in there.
The Inheritance of the Seven Stars, huh?
I've got a bad feeling...
Well done, Satomi-kun.
Rentaro!
Found you, Enju.
Tendo Martial Arts First Style, Number 8:
Homura Kasen!
I'll show you a move of my own.
Maximum Pain.
Oh? You're still alive?
Enju... Run!
No!
Rentaro!
Wait right there, Rentaro!
Papa! Enju ran away! I want to cut her!
No, daughter of mine.
If they join with other civil
officers, it'll be a nuisance.
Let us finish our job here.
You're so weak... You're so weak!
Any final words, my dying friend?
Go...
to hell...
Goodnight.
You are Satomi Rentaro-kun, yes?
Nice to meet you.
There's a choice I'd like you to make.
Oh, Kisara-san...
Welcome back, Satomi-kun.
How long have I been asleep?
One day and about three hours.
They said your heart
started beating toward the
very end of the surgery.
You didn't give up on living.
Well done.
The government has given us some information.
The case that Kagetane took contains
a catalyst capable of
summoning a Stage Five Gastrea.
Stage Five?!
You mean, of the eleven that
almost destroyed the world?
Starting from Stage One,
Gastrea grows to Stage Two and Three,
then completes itself at Stage Four.
The Stage Fives exist outside of that evolution.
They've existed since the
appearance of Gastrea ten years ago.
They're larger than other Gastrea,
and Varanium magnetic fields
have no effect on them.
Monoliths have been destroyed in various areas
by these Stage Fives.
And the hordes of Gastrea that
infiltrate afterwards bring about
extinction.
Hiruko Kagetane has escaped the Monolith
barrier into the Unexplored Territory,
and has begun preparations
for summoning the Stage Five.
The government is about to launch
an extensive pursuit operation.
And if that doesn't stop them,
the Tokyo Area will be...
You're planning to go? Can you win?
I have to win!
You're going to die.
I'm prepared for that.
You're supposed to be resting, you know.
Sorry, Kisara-san.
I...
There's someone else you should
be apologizing to before me.
Enju?
Shh!
When did she...
Ever since you were brought in here.
Rentaro... you imbecile...
Man... I really am useless.
I made you worry, Enju...
I'm sorry.
Yes.
For you.
It's Seitenshi-sama.
Satomi-san, we will be initiating an
operation to pursue Hiruko Kagetane.
I would like you to participate in this operation.
Why me?
You should know that better than anyone else,
Satomi-san.
Just remember that I'm not doing this for you guys.
I wish you luck, Satomi-san.
Sensei?
From your patron.
It's perfect.
Thank him with the reward.
This is a farewell gift from me.
AGV experimental drugs.
If you can avoid it, don't use them.
While I was unconscious, I had a dream
of when you operated on me ten years ago.
What I did to you can never be
forgiven, no matter what I say.
I've never once resented you since that day.
I order you as the President...
Crush the Kagetane and Kohina pair and
stop them from summoning the Stage Five.
Give me a hundred times more
effort than you have in the past,
and I'll give you a thousand times back.
I will stop them, no matter what.
For your sake, as well.
That was close...
Damn it! Some pair is using explosives.
Rentaro... What is that?
That's...
A Stage Four?!
Enju!
Enju?
Don't move.
You're...
Wait! Enju!
She's not an enemy.
Do you remember me?
Of course.
Just a moment!
I do not know this woman!
Explain what this is about!
She's the partner of a Promoter named
Ikuma Shogen. She's an Initiator.
I'm Senju Kayo.
Nice to meet you.
I will not accept such a woman.
For crying out loud...
I only asked her to keep watch outside.
Why did she get so moody?
I believe the reason is clear as day.
Am I strange to you?
Um, well...
I'm an Initiator with the model of a dolphin.
I just have a higher IQ and
better memory than most.
You're the smart one,
yet you're the rear guard
and Shogen is the vanguard?
That's a pretty unusual style.
Shogen-san is all muscle,
right down to his brain.
On top of that, he's just
too stingy to do backup.
Let me see your gun.
What if I refuse?
That's fine, if you feel
nothing about being saved.
I have learned one thing.
Once you expect something in
return, your good deed fails.
Why did you use explosives in the forest?
A trap...
We could see a pattern of
flashing lights deep in the forest.
We thought they were fellow
civil officers and went closer...
And it was a Gastrea.
Without thinking, I used a high-explosive shell.
And then we were attacked by
the Gastrea in the forest,
and I was separated from Shogen-san.
Did the Gastrea inject any fluid into you?
The fluid it injected was a very small amount,
so there is no increase in the corrosion rate.
There is no need to worry about
me turning into a Gastrea.
Listen. Make sure you get
checked out once we get back.
You are worried about me?
Something wrong with that?
I'm a little envious of Enju-san.
She has never killed anyone before, has she?
I can tell by looking at her eyes.
And you have?
Indeed. Even on our way here,
I killed another pair that we met.
Why would you do that?!
Because Shogen-san ordered me to.
He said he wouldn't let anyone have the reward
for killing the guy in the mask.
I was scared...
My hands shook, but that was all.
I believe I'll get used to it soon.
Don't give me that shit!
The scariest thing about killing
people is getting used to it!
When you kill someone and realize
you won't be punished...
That's when people forget
all about punishment!
Are you able to say that because
you've killed someone before?
You have very mysterious eyes, Satomi-san.
I'm sure you have a complicated past.
You're so kind, yet you
have such a scary face.
Why am I
trying to talk like I know everything?
Sorry about that...
Forget what I just said.
Why are you apologizing?
What you're saying is right.
You are right...
There's... something wrong with me now.
I can immediately come up with various
arguments to what you just said,
and yet I don't want to deny your words.
I've never... felt like this before.
You...
Hey! If you're alive, reply!
I'm glad you're safe, Shogen-san.
Kayo, I have great news!
I found the bastard in the mask!
So you're really going?
Despite how he is, he is my partner.
What about you, Satomi-san?
Other than you two, there are
ten pairs attacking, right?
I'll at least see how the fight ends.
Do you know what that is, Satomi-san?
The Stairway to Heaven?
It is an example of a mass murder weapon.
A symbol of the Stolen Generation's hatred...
The current generation...
Is what's going on right now really
a wholesome attempt at revival?
That's where Kagetane is...
#04 Black Bullet
Rentaro...
Rentaro's the only one
who can save the world.
No one else but Rentaro...