Enju?! Thank goodness...
Come back right now! We need to regroup!
Enju? What's wrong? At least answer me!
Hey, Enju!
Is it... Tina?
Enju
No... Enju...
#07 In the Still of the Moonlit Night, the Dawn Sky
Is Enju okay?
She'll probably be all right.
However...
I have her on a heavy dose of anesthesia.
She'll probably be asleep for at least two days.
Two days...
Satomi-kun...
Is everything over now?
There will be a third meeting held between
Seitenshi-sama and President Saitake.
When?
Tomorrow night, starting at 8 PM.
Tomorrow...
Satomi-kun,
you reek of male stink.
The victim was shot from four places at once.
Destroyed heavy machine guns were
found in three of those places.
Apparently, something odd
was attached to them.
We've asked Shiba Heavy
Weapons to inspect them.
She could've easily killed
Enju if she'd wanted to...
The police officer from last time, too...
Is Tina trying to avoid killing
people as much as possible?
Still, that doesn't change the
fact that Tina's ranked 98.
Kisara-san was almost killed, and I was hurt.
And... Enju is still asleep.
Honestly, she's not someone we can handle.
Maybe we should get off this job...
No... If we do that,
Seitenshi-sama will be...
Hey, Satomi Rentaro!
A third meeting has been arranged.
I know that.
We've also set up a new protection plan.
Though, sadly,
since you've lost your Initiator,
you won't have a part to play.
Create a fake protection plan right now.
You're still planning to remain her bodyguard?
I will be continuing this job.
I'll protect Seitenshi-sama!
Are you that desperate to stay
by Seitenshi-sama's side?!
Don't bring me to your level.
More importantly, listen.
Send out that false information.
I'll handle everything else myself.
That's the sound.
There's no doubt about it.
The thought-driven interface, Shenfield.
That bit is
an aerial scouting device controlled by
a neurochip planted into the brain.
It not only finds the the target's position,
but also transmits information such as
temperature, humidity, and wind speed.
Sensei, how many of these
bits can you control at once?
Three.
What are you thinking?
I'm going to defeat Tina.
Don't even try it.
The ones ranked 100
or higher are all monsters that
have sold their souls to the devil.
Still, I...
Rentaro-kun, do you know
why Varanium is black?
No.
Because my hatred materialized.
That's not very scientific.
You're as no-nonsense as I've come to expect.
When I realized that, I learned something...
That my soul is being saved by your growth.
That I'm still connected to this
world through your existence.
You're not fair, Sensei.
Then...
But still... No...
That's exactly why I have to go.
I want to prove that
this hand you gave me is for saving people.
I'll protect Seitenshi-sama, defeat Tina,
rise up in the ranks, and solve
the mystery of this world.
I can't run away!
You're an idiot.
I need a favor.
What is it, Satomi-chan?
You're kidding!
What is this? You're amazing, Satomi-chan!
A 2-1 style Varanium artificial eye.
Kisara!
That's what's hidden inside
Satomi-kun's left eye.
Because of the high fidelity computer
with a graphene transistor CPU in a
super Varanium alloy shell,
even his thoughts are overclocked,
so the world through Satomi-kun's
eyes moves very slowly.
A sniper?
My life is nothing but pain...
So, right now,
this feels like the most fun
I've had in a long time.
Satomi-chan, you're amazing!
Your power level is 2200%!
Take me, Satomi-chan!
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Oh, Kisara. You're still here?
Miori, what's Tina's estimated level?
Huh? Oh, well...
Since she beat Enju-chan, who's at 8600%,
it'd be safe to assume that she's
at least 1.5 times stronger.
So over 12900%...
Have you looked through the protection plan
for the third meeting?
Yes.
But doesn't it seem strange?
There's one spot within the route
that would be so perfect for a shot,
it almost seems intentional.
Tina Sprout,
I've been informed that the
police officer and Initiator that
I ordered you to kill are still alive.
I could have sworn I finished them...
Who is your master?
You are, Professor Rand.
Then I'm sure you understand,
but if you are to fail your
mission, kill yourself.
Understood, Master.
Please, don't come, Rentaro-san...
As I thought, this location was a bust.
However, I am aware of where
the meeting is being held.
It is possible to target
Seitenshi when she comes out.
I won't let you kill Seitenshi-sama...
That princess bears the future
of this nation on her shoulders.
If you're intent on killing her...
You're going to have to kill me first!
You cannot defeat me.
We won't know until I try!
Come on, let's end this, Tina!
Rokuro Kabuto!
At this distance, even if I react
as soon as I see the gun fire...
That's one...
Satomi-chan, you alive?
I've got the results of the analysis.
Analysis? For the heavy machine guns?
Yep! The things that were attached
to the heavy machine guns
were remote control modules.
I see...
I'm in trouble, Miori! They've found me!
Satomi-chan, dodge!
Satomi-chan, take a look at the
footage I just sent you.
I've confirmed it with satellite footage...
There are five anti-material
rifles surrounding you.
Tina's controlling those
herself by remote control?
Yep!
This is what got Enju...
The girl isn't in that building!
The heat sensors picked her up on the
top floor of the building next door.
Crap!
That's... three...
Tina!
Go!
She hid below...
What's up, Miori?
Be careful, Satomi-chan!
She's nearby!
She's somewhere on that floor!
Kohaku Tensei!
A fourth?
Why... Tina?
Why do you kill people?
There is no other way for me
to prove that I have a purpose in life.
That's sad, Tina...
That's so sad.
Prepare yourself!
It's no use...
She's too strong.
It misfired?
I guess my luck has abandoned me...
Rentaro!
What's wrong?
I see... the Owl's element...
Is this a miracle you created,
Enju?
I... can't lose yet.
I'm here because I've got
Enju, Kisara-san, Sensei,
Miori, and Seitenshi-sama
all placing their hopes in me...
Unebiko Rifu!
Joka Hanameishi
Burst!
Rentaro-san, please finish me.
My body... is a mass of technology.
I must not... be taken alive...
by another country...
Why...
You saved Enju.
I've wanted to say this to you...
Thank you, Tina.
Rentaro-san...
Don't worry.
I'll talk to them so your
sentence won't be so bad.
Fighting... was all I had.
Now that I've lost, I lost everything.
This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
I'll have you take responsibility for this.
Sure.
Tina! Hey, Tina!
You've given us enough trouble.
Why are you here?!
We have seen Seitenshi-sama
safely to her destination.
She should be in her meeting right now.
More importantly, I've taken
care of your garbage for you.
You should be thanking me!
I'll kill you!
Let go of me!
As I thought. Without Varanium
bullets, she won't die so easily.
All of you, how many lead bullets
do you think it'd take to kill her?
Stop! Yasuwaki, you bastard! I'll kill you!
Excellent! That's the face I
wanted to see, Satomi Rentaro.
Hey!
This is the finale.
Damn it!
That is enough!
Seitenshi-sama?! What are you doing here?
I heard that you were acting
of your own accord,
so I stepped out of the meeting early.
Inconceivable! All for the
sake of some civil officer?!
Satomi-san, please tell me.
Since you saved my life, please tell
me what it is you want from me.
I want power.
I want the power to protect
the ones I want to protect!
Very well.
As the Tokyo Area head of state,
I hereby raise Satomi Rentaro's rank to 300.
And your access key to top-secret
information is now level five...
Which makes you Second Lieutenant
Yasuwaki's superior.
Wh-Wha...
Get away from me!
My finger! My finger!
Get lost.
And don't ever come near Tina again!
If you disobey, I will shoot you for treason.
A week has passed since that incident.
Since Saitake was abandoned at the meeting,
he went back to Osaka all pissed off.
In the end, I couldn't find any
evidence to connect Saitake and Rand.
Tendo Civil Security Agency
Tina was placed in Seitenshi's custody,
and she's currently being
held in the Sacred Palace,
where they're continuing her interrogation.
If possible, I hope they show her
some mercy in her sentencing.
Oh, Satomi-kun. You're late.
Rentaro! I was getting tired of waiting!
What are you talking about?
I came here right after school got out.
So, what did you want to talk about?
Have some water, Rentaro-san.
Oh, thanks, Tina.
Tina?!
What are you doing here?!
I hired her!
Hired?!
Well, even if she were released,
she doesn't have a home to go back to.
That's just too sad.
I finally have a protégé!
Both of you were almost killed.
How are you smiling?
Rentaro-san.
I will be working at the Tendo Civil
Security Agency starting today.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
Whatever comes of this, I'm not responsible.
#08 The Monument on the Border
The Monolith's... been destroyed?
There are already as many as 2,000 Gastrea
gathering outside the Monoliths...
Hey, Satomi Rentaro the pervert!
Come on, let's dance, boy!