You can't beat me.
I still consider myself the Phantom Sixth Man!
Did you overwrite
me?
We still need your strength.
I'm counting on you to help Rakuzan win.
The ball disappeared...
Was that...
Misdirection Overflow?
No, it's a little different.
Mayuzumi-san's prone to
drawing attention right now.
Akashi-kun directed Kagami-kun's
attention to him.
I'm Desperate
Yeah!
Nebuya!
Stop me if you can, Kiyoshi!
Muscle Dribble!
From Akashi's pass he's
pushing inside in a one-on-one.
Rakuzan
Seirin
It's like he's showing off his strength.
Damn it.
The way Akashi's treating Mayuzumi is
heartless.
There's no other word for it.
His job is simply to stand in
Kagami's field of vision.
Being treated that way must
be supremely galling.
The only reason he's doing it is because
he's wearing their uniform on the court.
The remaining shreds of his
sense of duty are the
only thing forcing his body to move.
Yeah!
Rakuzan
Seirin
They're back up to 20 points behind.
But if they don't stop Rakuzan's attacks,
they won't close the gap.
Damn it...
What can we do?
Defense!
Defense! Defense! Defense!
Rakuzan is attacking with the
Uncrowned Kings' one-on-ones.
Defense! Defense! Defense!
To close the gap, the second-years
have to stop the Kings!
Please!
Tsuchida-senpai...
They're getting excited.
But...
It won't work.
I'm not feeling it, though.
Kagami's all right, but this guy...
Can I ask you something?
What do you think of Mayuzumi?
Nothing, really.
We use him effectively to win.
Is there something wrong with that?
I'm not complaining.
I just
don't want to lose.
Really?
Three's probably enough,
but that annoyed me enough to use more!
Four!
Hayama's Lightning Dribble!
I can't pass him with four?
Is it harder to use speed
to mess with him because he
sees my entire body's
movements with Eagle Eye?
Your mentality has a big effect
on your performance.
A man's attitude can
change him dramatically.
Somehow he's managed to
handle that monster.
A camel told me.
Compared to Akashi,
you're barely a hump in the road.
Yeah, nice.
He likes it?!
Sorry. Honestly, I underestimated you.
Okay.
Here comes five!
Such power...
Is this the true strength of the Kings?
But I've never felt anything like this.
I'm scaring myself.
I'm frighteningly calm,
despite the situation.
He's coming.
He passed him!
Eagle Spear!
But that's not fast enough to reach him.
What? He's already on his second bounce?
It's no use! He's too fast!
Izuki...
Sorry.
No worries. Let's get them back.
That's not what I meant.
Huh?
I'm just glad I could do my best
against that monster.
I'm excited.
Izuki...
Let me handle Hayama.
I promise I'll do something.
You caught Kagami's cooties.
I don't like the sound of that!
Akashi, keep giving me the ball!
That's the plan.
But don't make any stupid mistakes.
'Course! I'm gonna crush them!
He made another basket!
Hayama's unstoppable!
But he was watching.
Instead of going for the Eagle Spear,
he watched him after he passed.
Izuki-senpai...
Kuroko,
I'm okay.
Let me do it one more time.
Next time
I'll stop him.
Yeah, yeah.
You're determined to stop me.
But unfortunately, no matter what you do,
you can't!
This is...
This is it! I will stop him!
Kuroko!
There's something I've realized
after letting him pass me.
Hayama dribbles incredibly fast.
But it places a heavy burden
on his receiving hand.
When he crosses back over,
he stiffens for a moment.
I was expecting this.
He dodged him!
He knew what was coming!
What? An Eagle Spear now?
It's no use! I can't stop him!
That should've been a blind spot!
Hayama's instincts and reflexes
beat Izuki's far-reaching prediction!
Hayama wins!
Are you sure you want to go there?
The Thunder Beast doesn't belong in there.
Crap!
What?
Kagami blocked him!
They stopped Rakuzan's attack!
Kuroko!
Koga, pass! Behind on your left!
Don't tell him!
That was close!
Go!
It's Hayama!
An alley-oop!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Kagami's alley-oop!
That's one step forward!
That's it!
It's not just on defense. It's on offense, too.
He's using Eagle Eye to
understand the situation
and predict several moves into the future.
You've relaxed mentally,
but that doesn't make you any weaker.
You're way stronger than me.
But that doesn't affect
my ability to stop you.
I'm glad you're not smarter than me.
SNAP
What?
Kotaro, throw the ball in!
Five seconds!
Don't act so smug just
because you stopped me once!
Damn it!
Why are you passing to me, idiot?
Do you know who's on me?
Crap!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Yes!
Another basket!
Yeah!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Kuroko!
What are you—
Why is this happening?
I let him steal the ball
because I was angry.
I was angry because Izuki provoked me.
I let him provoke me
because I underestimated him.
Akashi.
Sorry. I'd better avoid
one-on-ones for a while.
I really want to get them back right away.
But Izuki's a first-rate player.
I can't charge in without thinking first.
Really? You seem to have calmed down.
That's good.
You're off the hook.
That was close.
If you'd hadn't calmed
down, there's no telling
what would've happened to you.
Kagami's super wide range defense!
Damn it.
Focus. Focus more.
I feel like I'm sinking through
water when I enter the Zone.
The deeper I sink,
the sharper my skills get.
The Zone is deeper still.
You idiot, Kagami.
It's still not enough.
Shit!
Weak.
You're so focused on the Zone,
you relaxed your guard against threes.
You must be unflinchingly prudent
if you want to stop me.
But it's only a matter of time.
Even if you enter the Zone,
you'll run out of strength eventually.
No worries, Kagami.
We'll get them back.
Yeah.
Go, Seirin! Go get 'em, Seirin!
Rakuzan
Seirin
We got them back, but...
We don't have any shooters.
Kagami, Koga, and I can shoot threes.
But we've got nowhere near Hyuga's accuracy.
Rakuzan has scarier shooters than Akashi.
If they start going for threes against us...
Mibuchi!
Unlike Kotaro, I don't get
more or less excited
depending on who I'm facing.
Why do you look so smug?
Why? Because our team's Izuki
is freaking amazing!
What?
Huh? Wait, wait?
We're pressuring you guys
right now, right?
So, you know, I'd better
do my best, too.
I don't know how to respond!
He changes at the drop of a hat!
Is it natural?
Either way, he's a bit like Kotaro.
Coach...
Honestly, in terms of strength,
this might be the biggest mismatch.
Koganei-kun started playing in high school.
But he's certifiably athletic
from his years on the tennis team.
It's the reason he's come this far
with no prior experience.
I don't have any experience
to predict what he'll do!
All I can do is focus on
my opponent's movements!
Is this...
Wild instincts?
But it's only...
...at about that level.
That's not much!
I could shoot a normal three.
But I can't underestimate the Seirin boys.
I'll go with Earth.
He took a step back?
Did he know I'd use Earth?
No, that's impossible!
But since he stepped back,
it's easier to shoot Heaven!
Damn! I held the ball too long!
Hey!
Damn it!
So he's more than just a house cat.
We can't underestimate any of Seirin's players.
I can't believe he reacted when
I switched from Earth to Heaven.
You can't keep making the same shots!
Senpai!
Nice!
Thanks, Kagami.
Sure thing.
This isn't good.
They're catching up to Kuroko-kun's passes.
Without a shooter,
we can't spread their defense.
Kiyoshi...
You're not even trying to engage me.
You've become pretty meek.
Kiyoshi!
You look terrifying.
Come on. Let's have some fun.
I don't mind you saying that,
but I feel like you're calming me down.
Now, now.
You look like you're having fun, Koga.
Huh? Well, I'm not slacking. I'm desperate.
But playing in a game is still fun.
It's incredible he even became decent
after starting in high school.
He's got good instincts.
He probably practiced hard, too.
I hate to be a downer, but the
question is how good he is now.
An average player is
powerless against the Kings.
Look. He's coming.
Mibuchi!
Isn't he a sub for Seirin?
That must've been luck.
He can't stop him.
They don't know anything.
Make them eat their words, Shinji.
This is...
Even if you know what
this is, you can't stop it.
A three without a fake?
No, this is...
Void!
What? You're joining the basketball team?
What about tennis?
I'm quitting.
It's not right for me.
You quit baseball, soccer, and swimming.
You've never stuck with anything.
I told you, they weren't right for me.
There certainly is such
a thing as "the right fit."
But no sport is all fun at first.
There are things you won't realize
until you stick with something.
Things you realize by
sticking with something...
I'm still not sure what it is,
but it's made me think...
That I've been enjoying basketball lately.
That a lot has happened,
so I...
I want to win, no matter what!
He jumped during Leo's Void?
He didn't reach it, but...
Fall!
Damn. I think I just
missed my only chance.
On the next Void...
He can't stop it? No way!
Why?
During that shot, Mibuchi saw two truths.
First, that Koganei-kun
somehow moved during Void.
Second,
that he still couldn't reach the ball.
Even if Koganei-kun predicts it,
he'll calmly take the shot.
When he surprised him earlier,
that was his first and last chance.
It won't be the last.
Thanks to Koga, I know how
to stop his three pointers.
And how to beat Void!
Preview
Hyuga, you're going to play?
I know the risks, but it's not reckless.
I've got nothing on you.
Let Me Warn You
Let's win, laugh, and keep playing ball!
Yeah!