I will demonstrate my
superiority to everyone here.
Wait, Akashi!
No way!
Stop him!
Your defeat is absolute.
Why Don't You Give Up
They're down 12 points.
Akashi's defending from even farther back.
Like Taiga, his defensive
range is probably enormous.
The other four are matching that and—
No.
After all the mistakes they've made,
Akachin expects nothing from the others.
What? You mean...
He's defending alone, too?
No way. We're already within
Akashi's defensive range?
A steal into a fast break!
Kagami!
Focus! He must be stopped!
Damn you!
The way you struggle is laughable.
Stay there on the ground.
He made it!
Akashi is dominating!
Sei-chan...
Watch for threes while we're on defense.
Even you can handle that.
What?
Akashi!
I expect nothing from you.
If you can't do it, then I will.
The greatest threat on offense
and defense is Emperor Eye.
What?
If Akashi has abandoned his teammates,
then it's like the time
we played against Seirin.
Single combat between
two players in the Zone.
That was an even contest, but Akashi
is completely overpowering him.
Reacting to your opponents movements
can never beat predictions.
Out of bounds, black ball!
It's no use.
I can't play any better in my current state!
I've entered the Zone and
reached the bottom, but...
I can't open the new door I see there.
I need to move the guy
standing in front of it.
It'll never open if I just wait!
What am I supposed to do?
Kagami-kun...
Kuroko.
Why don't you give up?
Why would you say that now, Kuroko?
I'm not telling you to give up on the game.
I mean give up on fighting alone.
I said I was counting on you, but it
could be too heavy a responsibility.
If that's the case, let me help you carry it.
I can handle it myself!
I'm almost...
No, you're wrong.
Crying that the door won't
open won't get us anywhere.
We've got to do whatever we
can with it still closed.
Fine. I accept your help.
Let's do this together.
We'll beat Akashi!
We're counting on you, Kuroko and Kagami.
With his Emperor Eye and the Zone,
Akashi's defensive area is
larger than Murasakibara's.
So...
They're passing the ball around,
outside his range!
Yes!
Go!
If he makes this, it's over!
Stop him!
Kuroko, Kagami!
Kagami's in front?
They're not double-teaming me?
Tetsuya can't keep up with me and Kagami.
Even if he has an unexpected
plan, I can see the future.
No one can beat my Emperor Eye!
The difference between you and
Akashi-kun is the Emperor Eye.
So I'll make up the difference
by becoming your "eye."
Right!
What? Impossible...
How did you get there before me?
How did he do it?
Kurochin wasn't looking at Akachin.
How, then?
Kuroko was looking only at Kagami.
He predicted Kagami's movements.
And he moved in the opposite direction.
It allowed him to catch up to Akashi,
who predicted Kagami's movements.
It's different from Emperor Eye.
The observation skills
he honed for Misdirection
and the time they've spent playing
together allowed him to pull it off.
He can't use it on opponents.
He can only use it on allies with whom
he's spent time developing a solid rapport.
That rapport allowed him to see farther
into the future than Akashi.
Predicting the future of his allies,
Kuroko's very own Emperor Eye!
Yes!
All right!
Counterattack!
You're kidding, right?
Stop them, Kotaro!
He passed him!
Go!
A turnover?
And I...
I let it happen?
He's fast!
He caught up in the second
Taiga's roll slowed him down!
Akashi!
I can stop him with Emperor Eye!
What?
Tetsuya?
An alley-oop?
Don't be absurd. I am absolute!
I must not lose!
Make the shot, Kagami!
Leave it to me. I'll make it!
I'm carrying the team's
hopes on my shoulders!
I will make this shot!
He made it!
No way.
Sei-chan...
Rakuzan
Seirin
He finally did it by supporting
Kagami with his pseudo Emperor Eye.
Yes.
Kuroko's actions are surprising.
And Kagami is moving without
thinking about Kuroko.
Entrusting yourself completely
to someone and playing all-out
is impossible without a deep level of trust.
They beat Emperor Eye precisely
because of who they are.
Is this the first time he's been beaten
this badly since starting high school?
No.
The last time was probably when
we played in middle school.
Akashi           Murasakibara
And ultimately, Akachin won that battle.
I haven't heard of him losing before then.
Akashi                       Murasakibara
But Akachin tried to score and failed,
and he tried to stop them but couldn't.
So it's probably the first
time, not just in high school,
but in his life that Akachin's
experiencing defeat.
Rebound!
Akashi missed?
Is the previous play still bothering him?
I've never seen Akashi like this.
He's less composed than he's ever been.
He's unsettled, which means he's distracted.
He's leaving the Zone.
He made it!
We're down ten points!
Rakuzan
Seirin
We can do it! We can win!
You're at your limit.
Don't be absurd! I can't lose!
Give up. You can't win anymore.
Shut up! I will win.
I have until now, and I always will!
Okay, defense! Stop this shot!
Yeah!
I had no idea Akashi was this fragile.
The defeat of his Emperor Eye
must've been a shock, but...
A pass?
Akashi stopped playing alone!
What an awful pass.
It's like receiving the ball from a stranger.
This is Heaven. But this shot...
Run!
Go!
What? You're slow getting back!
What's going on with you, Akashi?
Yeah!
Yes!
He made it!
We finally caught up to Rakuzan!
We're just one basket behind!
One basket behind!
Rakuzan
Seirin
This is ridiculous!
A kid could've caught that weak pass!
You think that'll work now?
I've had enough of your crap, Akashi!
White team timeout.
Kuroko?
I don't believe it.
Is Akashi this fragile a player?
The closing gap shouldn't
be enough to agitate him.
But he's shaken because they
defeated his trump card.
And that psychological damage
is creating discord on the team.
At this rate...
You're out, Aka—
Wait.
You're embarrassing yourself.
Did you think I'd console or encourage you?
I'd never do that.
After everything you said,
this is all you can do?
I don't think so.
You're nothing like the
man I met on the roof.
In fact, who are you?
Who am I?
I...
I am...
You are my weakness.
Born to a distinguished family,
always standing above others,
and obligated to win.
Even when you lost your mother, your only
repose, you weren't allowed to stop.
I was already beginning to tear apart then.
Basketball.
The anchor my mother left me.
As long as I kept winning,
my stern father allowed me to play.
The Teiko basketball team's practices
were hard, but not painful.
More than that,
I enjoyed the ability to play all I
liked and spend time with friends.
Then we won our second national championship.
It would've been impossible with anyone else.
It happened because I had them. But...
The team began emphasizing victory.
At the same time,
their talents began to blossom.
Their growth planted the fear
that I'd be unable to keep up.
Believing they would leave me
behind, fear turned to panic.
I, Akashi Seijuro, lost?
That's impossible. It cannot be.
What is gained through victory
is lost through defeat.
I had to be the strongest to
continue playing with them.
That's right. That's why...
Who are you?
I'm Akashi Seijuro, of course.
That's why I was born.
They followed me once again.
A third championship was easy enough.
It was a thorough victory.
I was absolute.
Things were the same once
they became opponents.
I will continue proving my strength.
So you don't need me?
That's right. You stay here forever.
I meant to.
But the scent of defeat is making you crack.
You know nothing!
You allowed yourself to be weak!
Yes. I didn't understand.
I was trying to save it by winning.
Something irreplaceable.
I didn't know what else to do.
That weakness gave birth to you.
Desiring only victory
and abandoning all else,
I lost sight of why I wanted to be stronger.
And now you're about to
make the same mistake.
Our guilt will stay with us forever.
I thought it couldn't hurt to lose.
But it seems I was wrong.
It's because we're playing Kuroko.
We can't suppress our impulse to win.
How dare you ask who I am?
You're...
I'm Akashi Seijuro, of course.
Preview
I can't back down now.
Are you back to normal?
Yes, my eyes are open.
I want you to lend me your
strength so we can beat Seirin.
It Was You
I don't want to lose, either.
I'll play as hard as I can.