I'll show you something special.
There's no way I'll let him—
I can't jump?
Why?
Four fingers...
I'll stop him this time!
A crossover!
Could it be?
What? An alley-oop?
What a jump!
The Weight of Resolve
The third quarter will now begin.
Let's go, Seirin!
Fight!
Yeah!
They're really hyped up.
They're behind, but they haven't given up.
Don't be so sure.
They're just desperately
trying to shake off
the dark despair that will
envelope them any moment now.
We're counting on you, Hyuga-kun and...
Kagami-kun.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
A screen!
Rakuzan
Seirin
He already made one!
Hyuga's threes!
Defense! Let's stop this shot!
I'm surprised.
Despite the desperate situation,
Seirin's spirit isn't broken.
There are no quick comebacks in basketball.
But
as long as they don't give up,
they have more than a 0% chance of winning.
Sorry,
but when I said they couldn't win,
I wasn't just considering the situation.
What do you mean Seirin has a less
than 1% chance of winning, Aomine?
Not yet, but soon.
Because Akashi's on the other team.
He crushes his opponents'
potential until it's all gone.
Could it be?
The outcome is 90% certain now.
But Seirin isn't completely dead yet.
Their shooter Hyuga and
ace Kagami still remain.
I'll take Kagami.
Leo, you'll take Hyuga.
Defense, black No. 4!
Hyuga!
Damn. That's his third.
It wasn't long, but I had fun, Junpei-chan.
He faked a Heaven shot into an Earth!
No, wait! I didn't hit him!
This can't be happening now!
Not when we're so desperate!
No. 4, raise your hands!
Seriously? I didn't hit him!
Hyuga-kun!
Raise your hands!
He lost his balance! I didn't do anything!
Hyuga!
Please, I...
Technical foul, black No. 4!
That's four. They'll have to sub him out.
Yikes.
We came because someone threw a tantrum
over watching the game, but...
It wasn't a tantrum.
You can't be doing that, Hyuga-san.
It was intolerably foolish.
But I still can't blame him.
That's how badly he wants to win.
What?
I never thought you'd say that.
What does that mean?!
Since they beat us to reach the
finals, I was rooting for our rivals.
But this is the end for them.
It's not over yet.
They still have one last hope.
But...
It's not over yet, Seirin.
I won't stop until you're completely dead.
The door to the Zone is heartless.
It never opens for those who ask for help.
Rakuzan
Seirin
Black, time out.
The finals aren't always dramatic.
Sometimes the favorite wins all too soon.
Their spirits are completely broken.
Their lights of hope have been extinguished.
Seirin can't recover anymore.
Do you have your answer?
Not yet, but I won't run anymore.
That much I've decided.
No.
I want to win.
Kuroko?
I want to win!
Even if it's impossible, I want
us to become the best in Japan!
Coach, please.
Rakuzan
Seirin
When you're this far behind,
no sport is more boring than basketball.
But that's only if
the game ends here!
Seirin's original trickster
is coming back out!
No. 11, Kuroko Tetsuya!
What?
What are they thinking?
Nothing's changed.
There's no point in exciting the fans.
The original trickster? That's funny.
He's an impostor whose
tricks have been revealed.
Surely you're not so optimistic
that you think you can still win.
It's not like that.
I fight because I want to win. That's all.
No matter how this ends,
I will not run!
I see.
Your conviction is meaningless.
He's been nothing but selfish.
Does he have any idea how
crazy it would be if we won?
But the second-years can't lose heart
while the first-years still have hope.
We can't give up yet.
We will win.
Fight with only winning on your mind!
You can do it, guys.
You can do it, Kuroko.
Oh, no!
Yeah!
His screens are good,
but that can't be all.
Kuroko versus Mayuzumi!
Don't act like you can stop me.
You can't possibly do that!
Mayuzumi-san, wait!
No, you don't!
Kagami!
Rakuzan
Seirin
They closed the gap a little.
Mayuzumi versus Kuroko again?
I won't fall for it again.
Kagami's on the other side.
I can handle anyone else who comes.
He passed him! Kiyoshi's going to...
He's not moving!
Could it be?
He's letting Mayuzumi shoot?
Yeah. Seirin can't stop all of Rakuzan's
attacks, and they're not trying to.
If they're going to shoot anyway,
they'll make their worst shooter shoot.
I see.
They put this worthless player
in so I would pass him and shoot.
They underestimate me.
I'll show them what I can do!
Rakuzan's No. 5 made another basket!
I'll say it again, old sixth man.
You can't beat me.
He's not missing any shots.
Did they make a mistake?
Seirin got them back!
This reminds of something Takao-kun told me.
I guess you could say I hate
you because you're like me.
What?
Sorry, but I still consider
myself the Phantom Sixth Man!
What?
Where did he come from?
I lost him... Impossible!
What did he do?
Run!
Has his lack of presence returned?
That's impossible!
But if it is, this situation...
Is it the Vanishing Drive?
Nice, Kagami and Kuroko!
We're just getting started, Rakuzan!
Has Kuroko's lack of presence returned?
No.
No! That's impossible!
There's nothing you can do
about your own presence!
Here he comes! It's Rakuzan's
No. 5, Mayuzumi!
It's a one-on-one!
Did you
overwrite
me?
Overwriting.
He made Mayuzumi stand out more than himself.
That's why he kept letting Mayuzumi pass him.
A dim light is overshadowed
when a brighter light appears.
Similar to the old one, but better.
That's how he dug the new model's grave.
Hey!
Low pass, but...
I'm too close!
Rakuzan's missing?
Kuroko's applying a lot
of pressure on defense.
Since he's vanished from the court,
there's no telling where
the steal will come from.
But that's not enough
for Kurochin to beat Akachin.
Kuroko, you're amazing.
If you hadn't stood back up,
I may have given up.
I won't let your ray of
hope go out this time!
Bring it on, Akashi!
He's entered the Zone again!
But he can't beat Sei-chan.
Did he forget the first half?
But you're the only one who can
keep Kuroko's momentum going!
Please!
Kagami!
He backed off?
Did he stop marking him? Why?
Ridiculous!
Just shoot the three, Akashi!
Impossible.
He can reach from there?
He's even deeper in the Zone.
Deeper?
He's like a wild beast.
How could Akashi not know what to do?
Mayuzumi's still functioning.
The effects of the overwriting
aren't complete yet.
Now that I know, I won't pass you.
Once I return to the shadows,
you can't overwrite me.
There's nowhere to pass!
He thinks I won't pass him.
There's no one behind him.
What an obnoxious kid.
But I won't fall for it.
Until I find my target...
What? Why did I pass...
Crap!
Kurochin created a huge opening
just before he started dribbling.
Yeah. It was a moment's
opening under great pressure.
Mayuzumi reflexively took it
even though he knew he shouldn't.
That's the extent of his abilities.
Returning to the shadows.
Easier said than done.
It takes an ironclad rationality
capable of suppressing instinct.
The new Phantom Sixth Man
may be more skilled,
but there's one way in which
he can't beat Kurokocchi.
His history as the sixth man and
his will to fight for the team.
In other words...
Damn it!
That strengthened his overwriting!
The weight of his resolve to be a shadow.
What?
A dunk!
When did Kiyoshi get the ball?
The pass went through before I knew it!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Yes!
Kagami's stopping Akashi on defense,
and they're scoring with
Kuroko's passes on offense.
They can't let their guard
down yet, but there's hope
with the power of the shadow and light.
White, time out.
What will Rakuzan do?
They'll sub out Mayuzumi.
Letting Kuroko overwrite
him was a serious mistake.
Damn it.
Someone brought Seirin back to life.
Falling into a trap you can see
is nothing short of stupid.
If the overwriting made him lose
his lack of presence, he's useless.
Sub him out.
They're friendly when they can use me.
When they can't, they're hostile.
I'm so glad they're so easy to understand.
But I can't argue with
them, nor do I want to.
I'm glad to be subbed out.
Akashi?
Get your energy back, guys.
Ice and massage them.
Yes, ma'am!
Sorry. When we were just
getting started, I...
You worry too much, idiot.
Hey, that's—
You stole my line against Kaijo.
That's payback.
I was disappointed when you got
your technical foul, though.
I feel bad enough already.
Don't rub Tabasco in the wound, Teppei-san.
But have faith in your friends.
Having four fouls just makes
the situation difficult.
It doesn't end the game.
We'll need your threes again.
We're counting on you, Captain.
Now let's have some fun!
What? Koga, you, too?
Saying it really cheers you up, doesn't it?
Seriously?
I thought they'd sub him out.
Can Mayuzumi use Misdirection Overflow
without his lack of presence, too?
Probably not.
Huh?
That technique involves drawing
attention to yourself.
But Mayuzumi's only trained to direct
attention away from himself.
Having Mayuzumi on the
court should hurt the team.
But they still put him in.
Did Akashi give Mayuzumi a chance
because he thinks he can still grow?
Akashi?
Like they said, you made a mistake.
Subbing you out would be the obvious choice.
But we still need your strength.
We won't sub you out yet.
I'm counting on you to help Rakuzan win.
The ball disappeared...
Rakuzan
Seirin
Was that...
Misdirection Overflow?
No, it's a little different.
Mayuzumi-san didn't do anything.
He's prone to drawing attention right now.
Akashi-kun directed Kagami-kun's
attention to him.
You think Akachin cares about
potential or motivation?
He doesn't expect anything from him anymore.
He's just using him
as a passing tool.
Preview
I'm really glad I joined the basketball team.
The practices are a killer, though.
But it's fun with all the guys.
We're Desperate
It'd be even more fun if we won!
We'll show you what Seirin can really do!