Did you sleep well last night?
Yeah.
I felt calm after listening
to Kuroko's story yesterday.
I fell asleep the second I got in bed.
Really?
When we scouted Rakuzan this morning,
I realized just how ridiculously
powerful they are.
But strangely, I didn't feel panicked.
It's done.
How's that, ma'am?
Perfect! Thanks.
You really are a barber's son.
Don't call me a barber!
Let's win.
Do your best, Captain.
What's wrong?
Listen, Riko...
If we win...
If we win today's game, uh...
Hyuga Barbershop
That's disgusting!
Oh, sorry.
Man, it's cold. My neck is freezing!
Well? Do you like it?
Yes. It's delicious.
Oh, my.
Would you like some tea?
Yes, please.
Why is Kiyoshi eating with us?
We're all going to see the game today.
Since it's the finals, I'll be putting
the final touches on my makeup.
Mom already made that joke.
So good.
Thanks for the food.
You sure you should be here?
Sorry. I'll leave.
That's not what I meant.
What about your grandparents?
I had breakfast with them.
They wished me luck.
Are they coming to the game?
Well, they might be too old for that.
But they're always really interested
when I tell them about our games.
I see...
So I'd better bring them some good news.
Yeah.
You can do it, Satoshi-kun.
I'll be rooting for you.
Thanks.
I'll probably be riding the bench, though...
I don't know much about sports.
But without the guys on the bench,
I think the rest of the team would be uneasy.
So,
even if you don't play, you're
still essential to the team.
You're right. Sorry.
I'll do my best.
That's amazing!
If you win today, you're the champions?
Yeah. Come watch the game
if you're free tonight.
You're going to play?
Who knows?
I'm not a starter, so I don't know...
You've changed.
What?
When you played tennis in middle school,
Mom and I went to watch,
but you were sulking because
you didn't get to play.
I forgot! Did that really happen?
Mom scolded you when we got home.
She said, "How dare you
not cheer for your teammates
just because you didn't play."
Everyone wants to play.
But now we'd just rather win together.
You can count on me!
I'll call all our relatives
to go cheer you on!
You don't have to go that far!
Tada!
We made it together.
We're going to the game today.
Do your best, Rin-nii.
Thanks for coming, Tatsuya.
I wanted to settle this before the finals.
I know.
I'm sorry about what happened in America.
But I still wish we could be like—
That's enough.
I should apologize to you.
I'm sorry for everything, Taiga.
Let's play again.
Actually, I hope we do.
Tatsuya...
As rivals and brothers.
I'm going to watch the game.
Do your best.
Let me see you become the number one player,
bro.
Number one?
'Course!
Alex-san is coming by later.
Be a good boy.
Excuse me.
I'm Kuroko.
I'm really glad
I kept playing basketball.
Tonight I'm letting out all those feelings,
Akashi-kun.
Final Tip-Off!!
It's so cold...
I can't believe we're watching
the finals together.
Is it going to snow later?
Shut up.
You weren't really studying
for exams, anyway.
Nonsense.
We're a hundred times smarter than you.
I can't believe you're
watching the finals with us.
Is it going to snow later?
Shut up already, butt chin.
That's a butt chin.
Sure is.
Are cleft chins that bad?!
Well, well.
Hello, Yosen.
Imayoshi...
Haven't seen you since summer.
It's been a while.
I guess we're both out, huh?
We certainly failed.
We just met at the opening ceremony,
but it seems like so long ago.
Yeah.
Isn't the guy with his
bangs in his eyes missing?
Muro-chin?
He said he'd be late.
Hey, Mine-chin.
What?
Who do you think will win?
You mean the third place match or finals?
Both.
Third place is already decided.
They can't manage without him.
I don't know about finals.
Isn't that why we're here?
Kaijo
Shutoku
There will be a ten minute
break before the second game.
Rakuzan and Seirin, please begin warming up.
Yeah!
Captain, is something wrong?
Look. This isn't good.
They're just passing into layups.
They follow precisely the
same rhythm and never miss.
The layup is the most accurate basic shot.
But no matter how good they are,
I've never seen anyone
make 100% of their shots.
They've more than got the basics down.
They've absorbed them on a frighteningly
deep level through repetition.
A layup's never sent chills
up my spine before...
That was too long!
Was that your longest one yet?!
Yeah. I filled my stomach to capacity today.
I'm facing Kiyoshi, right?
We go way back.
I can feel strength welling up inside me.
What about you, Leo?
Hyuga Junpei.
Country boys aren't my type.
But I'll take good care of him.
Anyway, I'm worried about you.
You're on Kagami, aren't you?
Yeah, he's tough.
But it'll work out.
Right, Mayuzumi-san?
You never take anything seriously.
Do you understand our situation?
Sure do.
We just have to crush Seirin, right?
Fine, then.
Akashi, you're starting today, right?
Of course.
They are strong.
We mustn't let our guard down.
But I am absolute.
And Rakuzan always wins.
Our basketball is absolute.
The day has finally come.
Honestly, I'm surprised.
I thought it unlikely that
you'd make it this far.
Do you have your answer now?
Yes.
Then show me your basketball.
No.
I won't be showing you my basketball.
It's our basketball.
I see.
I accept your challenge.
It's over!
Shutoku places third in the Winter Cup!
Kise...
We'll settle this later.
Next time we'll both play at full strength.
Midorimacchi...
Of course!
We would've won if I'd been playing!
Why, you...
I'll beat you again!
Well, it couldn't be helped.
I hate to say it, but we're
just the opening act today.
I'll let the stars stand in the spotlight.
They're coming out.
Seirin High and...
Rakuzan High.
Kuroko.
Could you use this during today's game?
What?
This is...
All our spirits are in there.
We may not get to play,
but we want to fight with you.
Thank you.
I'll wear both.
Ogiwara-kun's and Seirin's.
It's time. Let's go!
Let's win! Seirin, fight!
Yeah!
Before the game begins,
allow us to introduce the teams.
In the black uniforms, Seirin High.
Their faculty advisor is Takeda Kenji.
Their coach is Aida Riko.
Their coach is a high school girl? Amazing!
Is that for real?
Next is their starting lineup.
No. 11, Kuroko Tetsuya.
There he is! The Phantom Sixth Man!
He's starting again today!
Everyone's eyes are on him.
No. 10, Kagami Taiga.
All right.
Looks like I made it.
Muro-chin.
I panicked when I got a little lost.
You can do it, Taiga.
No. 7, Kiyoshi Teppei.
We're finally here.
Let's do this. No regrets.
You can do it, Kiyoshi!
No. 5, Izuki Shun.
It's him!
You can do it, Shun!
He's got an important job today.
The Generation of Miracles'
Akashi is his mark.
If he can't handle it himself,
his team is screwed.
No. 4, Captain Hyuga Junpei.
Yeah!
Once he starts making shots, he's a
formidable shooter, even for Rakuzan.
He's a critical part of his
team's offense and psyche.
In the white uniforms, Rakuzan High.
Their coach is Shirogane Eiji.
Next is their starting lineup.
No. 8, Nebuya Eikichi.
Yeah!
No. 7, Hayama Kotaro.
No. 6, Mibuchi Leo.
The Uncrowned Kings, huh?
So they're all as good
as Kiyoshi and Hanamiya?
I hope they still are.
Now that they're on Rakuzan, it wouldn't
surprise me if they're stronger.
No. 5, Mayuzumi Chihiro.
Their only third year...
He seemed pretty strong during warm ups.
But he's got a unique aura.
He reminds me of someone...
No. 4...
He's here.
That's...
Captain Akashi Seijuro.
The Winter Cup final between
Seirin High and Rakuzan High will now begin.
Bow!
Let's have a good game!
Senpai, could you let me get the jump ball?
What's gotten into you?
You certainly jump higher
than me, but your timing...
Please.
Fine. I'm counting on you.
Huh? Wasn't Kiyoshi supposed to jump
so Kuroko and Kagami could score?
I'll let them decide.
If Teppei switched, he probably
felt it was for the best.
I've seen Kagami like this before.
He's full of fight,
but he's calm.
He's in the best mental condition possible.
Then maybe it's possible.
Maybe.
If anyone can scare Akachin,
as unlikely as it is, it's probably him.
It's starting.
The final tip-off!
Ignite Pass Kai!
Kai? I can't catch that!
Kuroko's overexcited!
You would've made it if you hadn't fumbled.
Too bad.
The first basket is ours!
You again?
Nice, Kagami!
All right!
Here!
Last night,
after hearing Kuroko's
story, I did some thinking.
If I'd been in his shoes,
what would I have done?
I said it was his fault,
but that can't have been the only reason.
Hitting him may not have changed anything.
I couldn't find an answer.
I just wanted to clear my head!
So I'll jump!
Is he serious?
He's fast. Could this be...
Hey!
I want to win with Kuroko and the guys!
Meteor Jam?
Seriously?
He dunked right over Akashi's head!
Kagami...
I thought he could only do that when...
I taught him the trigger
to enter that domain.
But what kind of moron
would enter right away?
His trigger for entering is
the will to fight for his friends.
Interesting.
The Zone, huh?
Preview
Focus. Grab the ball.
Focus. The team will support you.
I just have to move forward.
Akashi, no matter what you do, we will win!
Isn't It the Best?