Our most powerful and final weapon...
The final battle will be at
the Flames of Revolution.
In order for you to have
the time to truly decide whether
this world is worth saving or not,
we need the world to keep existing.
This will mean the end of Satomi Rentaro.
#13 The Ones Who Aspired to Be Gods
The Gastrea are projected
to arrive in ten minutes.
Why haven't the batteries come yet?!
I don't see any Gastrea in my field of view.
What useful eyesight she has.
No fair, Owl!
But not all of the civil officers
have powers like that...
There's no contact from the JASDF, either.
If we haven't received them by now,
we should assume we
won't receive them at all.
The Gastrea army have
come through the forest.
They are heading straight here!
Satomi-kun, at this rate...
Either the enemy comes
at us and we perish...
...or we go after the enemy and perish.
They will arrive in about five minutes.
All units, advance!
Rentaro!
Look!
What... are those lights?
This is... the Genan Festival?
Satomi-san, it is I.
Seitenshi-sama...
I see... So you did this.
Satomi-san,
each one of these lights is filled
with the hopes of the
citizens of the Tokyo Area,
as well as their prayers,
and their will to live.
I am leaving the future of the
Tokyo Area in your hands.
Go...
With the courage to never give up,
no matter what the battle, and to win.
Don't worry.
Enju.
I believe people have two faces.
Light and dark...
And this is the light.
If you can see the prayers and hope
filling each one of these lights...
I can see them!
We have to save everyone.
The Gastrea are here!
And Aldebaran is at the rear!
We will now commence operation
"Rapier's Thrust!"
All right. We're moving on to stage two.
All units, advance!
Tina!
I will assist with the assault.
Let's go!
A giant Gastrea is heading
straight toward us!
Run, Satomi-kun!
Rentaro!
Damn it!
Tendo Style Martial Arts:
Homura Kasen!
This isn't good...
So this is death...
So this is war...
Marvelous!
Should you be wasting
time here, Leader Satomi?
Satomi,
go.
Aldebaran is now only 100 meters away!
I see it!
Let's go, Enju!
We will now eliminate the enemy.
This is the—
What?!
Rentaro!
The EP bomb has been set!
It'll go off in one minute!
All units, fall back as fast as you can!
Well done.
Five, four, three, two, one...
It can't be...
Miori... Did it fail to go off?
Ren...taro...
I'm sorry, Satomi-chan...
No...
There's still one way.
Enju...
This is goodbye.
Huh?
I always...
wanted to be a person worthy of you.
For the year since I met you, I was truly happy.
I'm truly thankful
that I met you.
Don't g—
If I can apply enough direct force,
the EP bomb should go off...
Satomi...
But only
at point blank range!
Ren...taro...
Varanium-corroding fluid!
N-No!
Damn it...
Just a little more... and Aldebaran will be...
No... Not here...
Satomi, looks like they got you good.
Shoma-nii...
Why?
I'm pretty sure I've figured
out what's going on...
I'll go.
We have to... send an shock
wave deep into its body...
My attack has the ability to destroy
opponents from the inside.
No, Shoma-nii.
No! You'll die!
My attack is considered heresy...
I have to seal this attack
deep within the earth.
Along with Aldebaran...
Satomi...
Live on for my sake, as well.
Shoma-nii!
No!
Enju...
What is this?
Shoma-nii... along with Aldebaran...
I know... Tina saw everything.
What about the remaining Gastrea?
After Aldebaran exploded,
their movements became strange
and they started to scatter,
so they were easy to defeat.
Most of them escaped outside
of the Monoliths, though.
Satomi-kun.
Onii-san.
Are you okay?
Is this... all that's left?
This is it?
With the destruction of the
Stage Four Gastrea, Aldebaran,
humanity won The Third Kanto Battle.
It has been two days since the
victory of the Kanto Battle,
and it appears that the construction
of the new Monolith 32
is progressing as planned.
The height has already surpassed 300 meters,
and it is presumed to be greatly
affecting Gastrea in the area.
We have arrived, Kazumitsu-sama.
Welcome, Kazumitsu-oniisama.
No...
Should I call you the Vice Minister
of Land, Infrastructure,
Transport, and Tourism?
Kisara...
And I see you have a child, Rentaro.
Do you have the promised item?
Damn it! I thought I got rid of all these...
I had always thought it was strange...
Why did Aldebaran stick itself to the Monolith?
The one who was placing orders for materials
for Monolith 32 towards the
end of the Gastrea War...
was you, wasn't it?
I don't think I can approve of you
mixing other ingredients with the Varanium
so the Monolith could be
made cheaply and you could
pocket the rest of the money.
Logically, that purity should have been fine!
But it didn't work on Aldebaran.
And with the money you appropriated,
you were able to achieve
your current status.
The one who pulled the trigger
on the Third Kanto Battle is you.
You're one of the pieces of
human trash that should have
died in the battle with the Gastrea!
A true villain doesn't perish!
I can throw money around,
and while "death" is picking that up, I can flee!
Both parties, bring forth a witness.
I, Shiina Kazumi,
am here to witness this duel.
I swear that, even if either
participant in this duel is killed,
I will not go to the police or any
other administration of the law.
Do you two really have to go
through with this duel?
Rentaro, I must forever silence this
wench's mouth right here and now.
Satomi-kun, I've been waiting ten years for this.
I've finally tracked down one
of the people responsible
for my mother and father's deaths.
My battle with him is my destiny.
Damn it...
Tendo Martial Arts Divine Spear
practitioner, Tendo Kazumitsu.
Tendo Martial Arts Sword Drawing
practitioner, Tendo Kisara.
What is that style?!
Tendo Martial Arts Sword Drawing,
Ryukosogeki stance.
It is the style that I created to
destroy every member of the Tendo family.
Enough nonsense!
Amako Genmeika!
Tendo Martial Arts Sword
Drawing Zero Style, Number 3:
Agiosotoken.
That is the name of the move
I used to strike you, Onii-sama.
Z-Zero Style?
It is one strike, yet two.
The second strike is faster
than the speed of sound.
You couldn't see the second strike
that severed your left leg, Onii-sama.
Now, Onii-sama, talk.
About the attack ten years ago
in which my parents were killed.
Do you think that stray Gastrea appearing
in the heart of the Tokyo Area is plausible?
I don't know!
Th-There were a total of five
who were involved in the plan.
Myself, three of my brothers,
and Tendo Kikunojo.
Why did you do such a thing?
Father was going to expose the
darkness of the Tendo clan.
Darkness?
Everything like what just happened!
For the Tendo clan to obtain its current status,
many similar incidents have happened over time.
But then, Father suddenly decided
he was going to go public with it...
So we planned to eliminate him,
along with the rest of you...
I see...
A-Are you going to spare me?
Satomi-kun, Enju-chan, Tina-chan, let's go.
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Satomi-kun, he's annoying,
so could you shut the door?
Right...
Kisara-san, is this really...
It is one strike, yet two.
Satomi-kun,
the second strike didn't just take his leg...
Huh?
Rentaro?
What was that?
Don't look!
Satomi-kun, I did it!
I finally killed one of the people
responsible for my parents' deaths!
Isn't that amazing?
Is something the matter?
Aren't you happy, Satomi-kun?
This is our revenge!
It was your execution!
Why did you kill Kazumitsu-niisan?
You knew before you did it, didn't you?
Where is there justice in that?!
Satomi-kun, I've realized something.
You weren't able to slay Tendo Kikunojo,
who was behind the Kagetane
incident, or Saitake Sogen,
who was behind the sniping incident.
But I was able to slay Tendo Kazumitsu.
Do you know why?
Because I am "evil."
Your fists of justice
can never touch evil.
It is not justice that can oppose evil.
It is an absolute evil that
overpowers evil itself.
I have that power... I just confirmed it!
Tina... Enju...
I might end up as Kisara-san's enemy...
Now that we have overcome
this national crisis,
we have been given another
chance at harmony.
I believe that establishing
the New Gastrea Law
will let many of the souls who
died in this battle finally rest.
Currently, we are having girls,
who are all very young,
bear too heavy a burden.
At this time, there may not
be any other choice...
However, in the future,
there may come a day when
their burden can be lifted.
No, it is us who will make that day a reality!
Ceremony of conferment of decoration?
Yeah. At the Sacred Palace
where Seitenshi-sama lives.
Apparently they're going to congratulate us.
Is this attire appropriate?
It's fine.
I see...
Oh, that's right!
Here. This is for you, Rentaro.
An oath?
"One: You will not face an enemy alone.
Two: We will do everything together.
Three: Don't knock me
unconscious without warning"...
Yes!
"Four"...
A fatal accident has occurred
at the Third District Station.
We request your patience.
Now we're going to be late...
I wonder if it hurt...
I wonder if it was painful...
Was there nothing that we could have done?
Hey, Rentaro?
What is the matter, Rentaro?
I'm afraid I'm becoming
unaffected by the deaths of others...
Enju... Please stay by my side, always...
Don't let me go.
It's all right, Rentaro.
You and I will always be
together, forever and ever.