Hey, do you want to go
anywhere on the way home?
Why are you calling me at this hour?
We've got a job, Satomi-kun.
Come to the Ministry of Defense.
Ministry of Defense?
#02 The Mask of Madness
Did they call us here because
of what happened yesterday?
They just told us to come.
This way, Tendo Civil Security Agency.
Kisara-san, this is...
It looks like most of the civil officers
in the Tokyo Area have been called...
Hey, now... Are little kids playing
civil officers these days, too?
If you've got something to say,
at least introduce yourself first.
Satomi-kun!
Hey, brat. If you're a Promoter,
where's your tool?
Tool?
Your Initiator.
You're calling Enju a tool?!
Stop it, Shogen!
Mikajima-san!
If you can't obey me, then leave here right now.
You got it.
That's Ikuma Shogen of the Mikajima Royal Guard.
His IP Ranking is 1,584.
He's in the thousands?
He's considered to be in the top
1% of the more than 700,000
civil officer pairs in the world.
By the way, you and Enju-chan
rank around 120,000.
And yet she's such a brilliant Initiator...
So the top class of
civil officer pairs from the
Tokyo Area are here right now...
That's Ikuma Shogen's...
"I'm... hungry..."
What the hell?
Oose Future Corporation
So, one absent...
I'd like for those who will decline
this job to immediately leave.
Once you've heard what the job is,
you will not be able to decline.
The explanation for this job will now begin.
Greetings, everyone.
Seitenshi...
The ruler of the Tokyo Area...
And her advisor,
Tendo Kikunojo...
My adoptive father who took
me in after my parents died.
And Kisara-san's grandfather...
We have two jobs.
One is the extermination of the
Gastrea that caused the infection
of an individual in the Tokyo Area yesterday.
The other is to bring back the case
within this Gastrea unharmed.
Reward
That is all.
May I ask what's inside the case?
And you are?
I'm Tendo Kisara of the Tendo Civil Security Agency.
I've heard about you, President Tendo.
However, that is private, so I cannot answer.
The source of infection was a Model Spider.
If that's all it is, our Promoter
could bring it down by himself.
So why are you asking all of these
top class civil officers to do it?
Perhaps there's something in
the case that's so dangerous,
it warrants such an extraordinary reward?
That is something you do not need to know.
Who is that?
It is I.
You're...
I am Hiruko. Hiruko Kagetane.
I believe this is the first time we've met,
my lady, the incompetent head of state.
Have you been well, Satomi-kun?
Where the hell did you come in from?!
I walked right in the front door.
Though, I had all the little flies
that tried to approach me killed.
Let me introduce you...
Kohina, come here.
Yes, Papa.
Upsy-daisy.
When did she appear behind me?
I'm Hiruko Kohina. I'm ten years old.
She is my Initiator, and my daughter.
Papa, that guy's pointing his gun this way.
May I cut him down?
Now, now, not just yet. Be patient.
Aww, but, Papa...
What do you want?
I wanted to announce that I'll
be entering this race, as well.
And that we'll be taking the
Inheritance of the Seven Stars.
The Inheritance of the Seven Stars?
Yes, that's what is inside the case
that you were supposed to find.
That's why he was in that room?
Why don't we go over the rules?
Let's see who can claim the
Inheritance of the Seven
Stars first: all of you, or me.
How about we wager
all of your lives?
Shut the hell up already!
He's fast!
I'll split you in two!
Wha...
Too bad...
Fall back, Shogen!
A barrier?
It's a repulsion field.
I call it "Imaginary Gimmick."
Are you... human?
Of course I am.
Though, to generate this,
I've replaced most of my internal
organs with Varanium instruments.
Let me introduce myself properly, Satomi-kun.
I am formerly from the Ground
Self-Defense Force's Eastern Force,
787th Mechanization Special Unit...
Mechanization?
Hiruko Kagetane of the
New Humanity Creation Plan.
787th... The Anti-Gastrea Special Unit?
There's no way that exists...
It's up to you whether you
choose to believe me or not.
Get down!
Satomi-kun.
Here's a present for you.
Let's go, Kohina.
Okay, Papa.
Despair, all of you. The day of extinction is nigh.
Satomi-kun, where did you meet him?
Well...
I-It's terrible! The President...
That's the secretary of the
President of Oose Corporation
who was absent...
Th-The President was killed in his home...
and the body's missing the head...
I'm adding another
requirement for completion.
Please recover the case before that man.
If its contents are misused,
it can destroy the Monolith barrier,
and bring a great extinction
upon the Tokyo Area...
The contents are meant to be sealed away.
Tenchu Girls
Seriously, what is this?
That is a Tenchu Girls Bracelet
that is quite popular among us.
If you deceive your friends or tell a lie,
it will crack and break apart.
So why do I have this on?
For the couple's look!
Now you will not be able to deceive me.
If you were to be enchanted by
Kisara's boobies, it would break.
I, Satomi Rentaro, am in love with Aihara Enju.
It's not breaking.
That's because it's the truth.
That's how you took it?
Damn...
It's like what happened yesterday was a lie...
Someone!
Grab her!
A Cursed Child from the Outer District...
You thief!
Let me go!
You're the trash of the Tokyo Area!
Hey, why are you after her?
She stole something and then
almost killed the security
guard we called in response!
Why you...
Let me go!
What are you guys doing?!
Please take care of this gir—
Come on! Hold still, you!
You don't even know what I did!
I know exactly what your kind is likely to do!
Hold still!
Come on, walk! Stop resisting!
Quit flailing!
Be quiet!
Don't ever leave the Outer District again!
Rentaro...
Why didn't you save her?
You idiot! What are you doing?!
If they found out who
you were, you'd also be...
But she was asking me for help!
Why...
Did you know her?
Long ago, when I was in District 39,
I had seen her before...
Though I had never spoken to her...
She remembered me, as well.
Rentaro, you're a champion of justice!
There's nothing that you can't do!
Enju...
Enju, you go on home.
Whoa!
Why'd they bring her here?
She's still alive.
Put us through all that damn effort...
Damn it... Why?!
The ones protecting this city...
protecting all of you...
are Cursed Children
just like her...
And yet,
why can't I...
She's alive!
She managed to survive somehow.
She's got quite the vitality.
Thank you.
I'll pay for it, so please treat her properly.
You will? You sure?
Who else is going to pay?
Living expenses are going to be tight...
You seem tired, Satomi-kun...
Would you mind putting your gun down?
I refuse!
Kohina, cut off his right arm.
Yes, Papa.
Don't move, or your head will come off.
I couldn't cut her...
I couldn't kick her...
Oh?
Hey, pipsqueak. Tell me your name.
You're small, too! How rude!
I am Aihara Enju, a Model Rabbit Initiator!
Enju... I'll remember it.
I am Model Mantis, Hiruko Kohina.
I am unrivaled in close range combat.
I'll leave just that rabbit's head.
Can I cut her down?
How many times must I tell
you, foolish daughter?
No.
I hate you, Papa.
Now, Satomi-kun, let me cut to the chase.
Why not join forces with me?
What?
I'm not entirely sure why,
but I've taken a liking to you.
Have you
never once thought that the way things are
in the Tokyo Area is wrong?
This is a mere token, from me to you.
I heard that you're making
Enju-chan act like a normal girl
and having her go to school.
Why would you do such a thing?
They are the next generation of humanity
that have surpassed homo sapiens.
Only ones with power like us will
survive the Great Extinction.
Side with me, Satomi Rentaro.
I should have killed you the first time we met.
No matter how hard you work for them,
they will just continue to betray you.
Let's call it a day, Satomi-kun.
Pay a visit to her school tomorrow,
and come face to face with reality.
Rentaro... his Initiator is strong.
Can you beat her?
I don't know.
I see...
What do you mean?!
A rumor that Aihara-san was one
of the Cursed Children suddenly
spread throughout the school...
And Enju didn't deny it?
Satomi-san, you kept the
fact that Aihara-san was a
Cursed Child a secret from us, didn't you?
If I had told you upfront,
wouldn't you have denied her
enrollment into the school?
Anyway, Aihara-san seemed
to take it as quite the shock,
so we sent her home early.
Enju!
Welcome home, Rentaro!
What do you say? Care to join me?
Enju...
Your home is here!
The New Gastrea Law is a law that will give
the Cursed Children the
rights that they deserve.
I am certain that this will
serve as a foundation to a new
age that will come after the war.
I believe it is my mission
since taking the position
of Seitenshi from my predecessor
to use the passing of this law
39th District Map
You are here
as an opportunity to eliminate all fighting,
and create a society where all
humans can live together in peace.
What?
I'm a civil officer.
I'm looking for this girl.
I don't know her.
I'd like to ask some other people, if possible.
Okay, there's an Elder down here,
so please come wait inside.
Elder!
Are you the Elder?
"Elder" is just a nickname.
My name is Matsuzaki.
I take care of these children.
In order for these girls to live
among normal people someday,
I want to at least teach them
how to control their emotions,
so their red eyes won't show.
The Stolen Generation is cruel to them.
If only everyone could think like you...
Did this girl come down here?
Sadly, I haven't seen her.
I see...
Where are you headed now?
I'm going to search all over the 39th District.
It's her hometown, so I'm going
to look around until I find her.
By the looks of it,
you're a Promoter whose partner ran out on you.
Perhaps you could find another?
What?
It's not uncommon that a civil
officer pair doesn't get along.
To many Promoters, Initiators are
mere tools used for fighting.
Tools?
You could just contact the IISO and
make a contract with a new Initiator.
You're a good man, and I'm grateful to you,
but...
My reasons for looking for Enju have nothing
to do with Initiators or Promoters!
The first time I met Enju was a year ago,
when we were introduced
to each other at the IISO.
Let's eat.
We spent a lot of time
becoming more human together.
For a year since then...
We were always together, no matter what.
You don't know anything about us...
Stop talking like you understand everything!
Sorry...
I didn't mean to yell.
I'll be leaving now.
See ya.
He's a nice young man.
Are you sure you wanted to just
let him go like that, little girl?
#03 The Children of Fate
And yet we still have to fight...
Why must humanity exterminate the Gastrea?
Do you have any final words, dying people?
If I don't stop them, the Tokyo Area will be...