Who the hell are you?
The one who got in my way...
Just who are you?
#06 Tragic Irony
Here, I bought this for you.
Thank you very much.
I don't mind that you called and asked
me to show you around this area,
but could you not ask to go
the same day you call me?
It's way too sudde—
Hey, what are you—
I don't handle waking up early too well.
Should I not have?
It's fine.
The sniper last night...
Traitor
I'll kill you
I did some research on people likely
to try to assassinate Seitenshi, but...
Death to the one
trying to give rights
to the Gastrea
They're not it... That enemy is...
a much more dangerous one.
Give me a hint...
Let me see it.
Rentaro-san, more, please.
There, all clean.
Thank you very much.
Today was a lot of fun.
It's fine.
I had a lot happen yesterday, myself,
so this was a nice change of pace.
I like you, Rentaro-san.
H-Huh?
This is the first time anyone's
been so nice to me... I think.
It hasn't been very fun
since my parents died.
My life is nothing but pain...
So, right now,
this feels like the most fun
I've had in a long time.
Say, Tina...
I have to go.
Can we meet again?
Yeah... Give me a call again sometime.
You're late.
I've obtained the plans for the next meeting.
Those civil officers...
I've found out who they are.
Tina Sprout, you have a new mission.
Kill the president of the
Tendo Civil Security Agency,
Tendo Kisara, immediately.
Yes, Master.
Student Council Office
That cake the other day...
Yeah, it was great!
Listen carefully, Satomi-kun.
After we toss in the tear-gas canister,
we're going to shoot Miori
when she comes strolling out.
Two in the chest, and one to the head.
We're going to make that woman history.
Sorry, but could you wait outside?
N-No! I can't leave you alone with Miori!
Hey, Satomi-kun!
Welcome, Satomi-chan.
Miori! Open this door at once!
Otherwise, I'm breaking it down!
I'll be sure to bill your office for the damages.
Well, then... Let's go next door.
The bullet the sniper used was
from a .50 caliber Browning
heavy machine gun.
The rifling was clean.
No record of it being used in previous crimes.
Considering the angle,
I'm almost certain it was
fired from this building, but...
To be honest,
it's pretty much impossible
to hit something with two
sniper bullets from this distance.
Who are they?
Satomi-chan, you should be careful!
It's clear the enemy is an
impossibly skilled sniper.
In comparison, Seitenshi's bodyguards
are from an infant organization
that was only founded in the last ten years.
With things as they are,
it wouldn't be surprising if Seitenshi-sama
were to die any day now.
Miori, would you do some
research on Saitake Sogen?
He's the one who hired the assassin.
Satomi-chan, you're such a kidder...
Can't I ask you to have my back?
But we're talking about the head
of state of the Osaka Area here...
All right.
But in return...
I want you to show me your true power.
That has nothing to do with you.
Besides, that's not something I show just anyone.
Do you prefer Kisara that much?
If you were able to forget about Kisara,
you can do whatever you want
to my body, Satomi-chan...
What are you two doing?!
It's not... Th-This isn't anything!
Don't get the wrong idea, Kisara.
All right, Satomi-chan,
I'll be going ahead with
what we talked about earlier.
What did we talk about earlier?!
Why, of course...
That you'd transfer to my company
if I offered myself up for you.
You're kidding...
Oh, Kisara. It's really nothing.
Well, I'll be leaving now.
Hey!
Kisara-san, that really wasn't
what it sounded like...
You idiot!
You seem happy, Sensei.
Of course.
A bug fanatic with a pity-me face
like yours is unworthy of
prime real estate like Kisara-kun.
It's hard to believe she
doesn't have a boyfriend yet.
You should be trying a bit harder.
Though you're rude,
you are quite the gentleman...
But you lack the nerve to
push through a woman's hesitation
and make her yours.
That's your downfall, Rentaro-kun.
Shut up.
What did you want to talk about
that you had to call Enju here for?
This is late, but congratulations.
I hear you've defeated Hiruko Kagetane,
and reached the rank of
1,000, making you one of
the higher ranking individuals.
And so... I thought I'd talk to you about
the three prodigies other than me.
The other three prodigies?
Rentaro-kun, who do you recognize me as?
The person who is the
former chief executive of
the New Humanity Creation Plan.
I can only give you partial
credit for that answer.
The New Humanity Creation Plan is the name
of a mechanized soldier
project plan that was
a joint effort between four
countries, including Japan.
From the Australian division, Arthur Zanuck.
From the American division, "Next," Ayn Rand.
From the Japanese division,
Muroto Sumire. That'd be me.
And the one who brought us all together,
Albrecht Grünewald from Germany.
These four were gathered to protect
the world from the Gastrea invasion.
However, the project quickly dissolved.
Because we realized how high the
fighting ability of the Cursed Children was.
It hasn't been addressed publicly,
but many of the mechanized
soldiers that were relieved
from duty became Promoters.
They make up most of the
higher ranking individuals.
If you've decided to pursue your origins,
you're going to run into them.
You should be prepared.
Rentaro...
However, it's nothing to
be pessimistic about.
You've already defeated a mechanized soldier
that was created by Grünewald,
one of the four prodigies.
Hiruko Kagetane!
Then that means Rentaro's a
super prodigy himself, right?
No, that was more a miracle than anything.
I bet.
You really are a jerk, Sensei.
Of course. You just realized that?
We're going home, Enju.
What? I came all this way and
we're already going home?
No, I'd like you to stay, Enju-chan.
I want to ask you some questions.
I'm done with you, though, Rentaro-kun.
You should hurry back and get
Kisara in a good mood again.
Tendo Kisara is the granddaughter
of Tendo Kikunojo.
She is a master of the Tendo Martial
Arts and an expert in iaido.
But she is no match for you.
Who was it that got in my way back there?
A pair from the Tendo Civil Security Agency.
The Initiator's name is Aihara Enju.
The Promoter's name is—
I'm sorry, Master. What did you just say?
What the heck?
I'll fire Satomi-kun myself!
Even if he comes back,
I'm never going to forgive him!
Damn it...
You are Tendo Kisara, correct?
Y-Yes... Who are you?
Prepare yourself.
Too slow.
Just who are you?
That does not matter to you,
since you're about to die.
You're... scared to kill someone, aren't you?
Help... me...
Help me... Satomi-kun...
"Satomi"...
Help me, Satomi-kun!
Inzen: Kokutenfu!
It can't be...
Tina...
Why?
Why, Rentaro-san?
I see... so you're...
Rentaro-san, I...
Rentaro-san...
Listen to me!
Kisara-san, cut the floor!
Unebiko Yusei:
Yukikage!
Rentaro-san...
Did we win?
We didn't win. She ran away.
You know her?
Yeah...
Satomi-kun...
Kisara-san?
Kisara-san?! Kisara-san!
I didn't want you to see
me like this, Rentaro-kun..
Like that matters right now.
You won't consider getting a kidney operation?
It's not that easy to find a donor.
Not to mention...
When my body ended up this way,
I decided I'd spend
my life trying to rid the world
of the Tendo name.
If I were to forget this pain, I would
probably forget to exact revenge.
More importantly,
I've learned something from watching Miori.
S-So, Satomi-kun, you can...
You can hold my hand.
Huh?
What? That's not enough for you?
Holding hands is pretty hard to do!
How?
Because... I-It's like we're a couple...
Hurry... I'm so embarrassed, I could die.
But you lack the nerve to
push through a woman's hesitation
and make her yours.
K-Kisara-san.
H-Hey, Satomi-kun...
Where are you touching?
I didn't intend to let you go that far...
The size, shape, elasticity...
I hate to admit it, but I'd
have to give them a triple A+.
Huh?
E-Enju-chan, what are you doing?!
That's what I'd like to ask you!
When I went to the office,
it was full of holes,
and when I got here,
you had your boobs out,
trying to seduce Rentaro...
I do not have them out,
nor am I trying to seduce anyone!
There's no doubt that the attack
on the office today and the assassination
attempt on Seitenshi-sama are linked.
We'll have to take responsibility
since we let the suspect get away.
If I had been there, I'd have gone
after them and apprehended them.
By the way, what did Sensei have to say?
I'm not quite sure.
Something about my speed,
and something about shocks...
What the heck?
Since that girl came to kill
me because I was in the way,
there's no doubt there'll be another attack.
The fate of the Tokyo Area is in your hands.
I order you as the president:
Eliminate the sniper who is
targeting Seitenshi-sama,
and see justice done.
Yeah, I'll stop her.
I'll be the one to stop her.
Rentaro, is this going to work?
I'm not sure.
Hopefully it'll be enough to disguise us, at least.
Saitake Sogen...
He has to be the one behind this.
Satomi-san, that is going too far.
He's the one who proposed that meeting,
and you were attacked
on the way back from it.
Is playing dumb in spite of that
your way of preserving the peace?
I cannot cancel this meeting
without any proof.
You're going to be killed!
The actions I take are so I do not put shame
upon my title as the head of state.
If I am fated to lose my life
because of those actions,
then I have no choice.
Stop messing around!
Rentaro!
I'm going to protect you.
I didn't agree to be your bodyguard
just to let you get killed!
Thank you, Satomi-san...
Come on, Princess, let's go.
I am not a princess—
What is the meaning of this?!
Why is Seitenshi-sama riding
in such a piece of junk?!
We switched cars.
I've determined that the
limo is too dangerous.
Why, you...
How dare you make that decision
without my permission?!
That sound...
Look out!
Rentaro!
It's an attack! Protect Seitenshi-sama!
Rentaro...
Enju... watch the back...
She should still be targeting us.
Right, Tina Sprout?
Tina Sprout...
There's a flash!
Go into that parking garage! Hurry!
Rentaro, I will go after that sniper.
Go after her? Can you get there in time?
If I go alone.
Be careful. Come back, no matter what.
Who do you think I am?
I will be back shortly!
Everything's fine... Calm down.
Since the enemy's a sniper,
Enju has a chance.
And in this darkness...
Why did you come out?!
Satomi-san, where is Enju-san?
She went after the sniper alone.
No...
Please call her back immediately!
I used my authority
to run an inquiry on the name
Tina Sprout in the IISO.
She is ranked 97,
an Owl Initiator, and one
of the mechanized soldiers!
If Enju-san is alone, she will be killed!
Enju...
Enju?! Thank goodness...
Come back right now! We need to regroup!
Enju? What's wrong? At least answer me!
Hey, Enju!
Is it... Tina?
Enju
No... Enju...
#07 In the Still of the Moonlit Night, the Dawn Sky
The ones ranked 100 or higher
are unbelievable monsters...
Please, don't come here, Rentaro-san...
Come on, let's end this, Tina!