Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
Got your meatball.
Damn it, Haizaki.
If you're hungry, ask for extra
or go get another helping.
Quit taking people's stuff.
I don't mind.
Who cares?
You eat people's stuff all the time.
I only do it when I'm hungry.
That's the same thing, Aomine.
Also, don't chew so noisily, Haizaki.
It's low class.
What?
And you should learn to hold your
chopsticks properly, Murasakibara.
What?
I'm getting caught in your
crossfire, Zaki-chin.
Your fried chicken looks good, too.
Got your...
Take a single pickle, and I'll crush you.
You're more fired up now than
you are during our games.
Man, shut up.
I'm always telling you it's
not because I'm hungry.
Food always looks so good when
someone else is eating it.
I can't help myself.
Come to think of it, a second year
is joining the first string today.
Apparently he just started
playing two weeks ago.
What's his name?
Kise Ryota.
He's the first rapid promotion since us.
I know that guy.
I've met him before.
Who cares?
Kise Ryota, huh?
How unusual for you to remember
a person's name, Haizaki.
Call it a hunch, but I
think he'll be pretty good.
I don't think we'll be friends, though.
Now then...
Try not to drag me down, idiots.
Yeah, we know.
He's got an attitude.
Isn't that their captain?
Yeah.
He's an exceptionally quick point guard.
He's good enough to be a national champion.
He's a serious and well-mannered player.
Is Haizaki so strong he has to use him?
Though the Teiko Middle School team
and "Generation of Miracles"
are now exalted for their overwhelming
strength, it wasn't always that way.
Their great strength bred
resentment and antipathy.
They were practically considered villains.
Though I've only heard rumors,
it's possible Haizaki's brutality
contributed to that reputation.
It's Mine
What was that for?
You're stiff.
I don't know what happened between you guys,
but you just have to play your own game.
Don't let him throw you off your game.
Yes, sir.
Today I'll become her hero.
I'm gonna do my best!
No one's gonna beat me to the rebounds!
Those guys are too comfortable
doing it their way.
Their defense isn't bad.
In that case...
What?
He's fast!
He's quicker than he was this summer!
Damn it!
All right!
Kaijo scores first!
Nice shot.
That's it, huh?
Give me the ball!
What?
You're not going anywhere!
H-He's fast! He's way faster than before!
This is ridiculous.
Get out of the way!
Seriously?
He pushed his teammate aside!
Huh?
All right!
You got in my way and slowed me down.
That guy's his senior!
Sorry.
Kirisaki Daiichi's Hanamiya is a shithead,
but he was the center of his team.
This guy doesn't have a shred of team spirit.
I hate guys like him more than anything.
Let me tell you something.
Huh?
You should respect your elders!
He just passed him, but he's already...
Don't lecture me, idiot.
Who's the idiot?
You've got something to tell me, huh?
Fukuda Sogo is counterattacking!
These guys are fast, too!
All right! Come on!
A scoop shot.
That's Seiho's Kasuga's specialty shot.
They made it this far.
Their other players are pretty good, too.
Yeah.
Both teams are going all out
from the start of the game.
But Kise's hardly touched the ball yet.
No. It's coming.
This is...
A scoop shot?
Seriously?
He picked up the move he just saw in a flash!
The Generation of Miracles is the real deal!
Try harder.
Or was what you said earlier all talk?
It really is impossible for us to get along.
Our styles are too similar.
That's it, Kise!
This is still within our expectations.
But why do I feel like something's wrong?
I'll stop you this time.
Is this right?
That's the move I just used!
It's like he's saying he can
do anything Kise can do.
Is he doing it out of spite? What an ass.
His engine's finally running.
I hate to admit it, but we
wouldn't stand a chance
against a team with one of the
Generation of Miracles without him.
Yeah. In for a penny, in for a pound.
He'll be tough to deal with if
we let him get carried away.
In that case...
We don't just score from the inside!
Nice pass.
All right!
Nice shot, Moriyama-san!
How does he make shots with that form?
The spin on it was terrible.
In fact, it's hardly spinning at all.
His form comes from prioritizing his
own ease of shooting during practice.
As a result, his shot's unique
timing is difficult to block.
It's his own personal weapon.
Huh. That's pretty nice.
Fast break!
Shit! It's a counter!
Run back!
Quit scampering around, pipsqueaks!
I told you to keep giving me the ball.
He stole his teammate's pass...
If he'd joined our team, I would
have taught him some manners...
Are you getting fired up
while watching a game?!
It's not too late to start now!
Both of them?!
Bring the ball back, Haizaki!
What? Don't be stupid.
That shot
is mine!
What?!
That's Moriyama-san's...
...abnormal shot!
Impossible!
You must be joking!
That's not possible. He copied my shot
after seeing it only once.
Do Haizaki and Kise have the same ability?
No.
They're slightly different.
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
Kasamatsu's drive...
...was beaten!
Damn it!
This isn't good.
Have they been holding back until now?
They're far better than what we expected
from the videos and Kise's stories.
Our team's acting strange, too.
There's something wrong with them.
What's going on?
You're kidding, right?
I can't believe Kaijo's on the back foot.
What is Kise doing?
Their other players are lifeless, too.
Yeah. Something's wrong.
Huh?
Moriyama missed an easy shot.
First Kasamatsu,
now Moriyama. What's going on?
I'm not finished yet!
Nice rebound, Hayakawa!
The area under the hoop is my territory!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm just getting started!
I never have any idea what he's saying...
Hayakawa's rebounds are impressive.
He doesn't jump that high, though.
It's strange.
Well, there are two types of jumping power.
There's explosiveness and hang time.
Kagami, you possess the latter.
The secret behind Hayakawa's
rebounds is his explosive power.
Because he's initially very fast,
he reaches the apex of his jump
before other players,
even if he jumps after them.
Which means...
It allows him to jump from a
more advantageous position.
Huh. That's pretty nice.
Crap!
I released too late!
That's mine.
Hayakawa!
He lost the rebound!
I-I'm sorry!
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
This game isn't going well.
I need to do something.
Are you running again?
Not that I care.
Who said I was running?
That's...
That's the drive into a
rolling one-handed dunk
Kagami used in his first game against Kise!
That guy...
That's mine.
Sheesh. We really are similar.
Oh, right. You don't know.
You said we're similar,
but I'm not a copycat like you.
What did you say?
All right! This time...
Oh, no. It won't work, no matter
how many times you try it.
That doesn't belong to you anymore.
No way!
I can't believe he missed two in a row!
That's impossible.
Something's definitely up.
We can't use any of the moves Haizaki copied.
Kuroko, you said Kise and Haizaki's
abilities are slightly different, right?
Yes.
What does that mean?
Kise-kun replaced Haizaki-kun as a regular.
Haizaki-kun was lazy during practice
when he didn't skip it outright.
Since Kise-kun never saw him play in a
real game, it's possible he doesn't know.
Like Kise-kun, Haizaki-kun makes moves
his own after seeing them only once.
However, he uses his own rhythm and tempo.
When players see an opponent use
a move that appears identical but
has a slightly different rhythm,
they unconsciously disrupt their own rhythm
and become unable to use the ability.
Haizaki-kun doesn't copy moves.
He steals them.
This is mine.
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
The second quarter is now over!
We will now take a ten minute break!
Walk faster.
Kise, can you still play?
I can do it. Let me play.
I will defeat Shogo-kun.
Huh? What'd you say, Ryota?
I said I want to play for
the starting position.
You just joined the team. Don't be stupid.
Besides, you can't even beat me at practice.
What do you think you're doing?
I may not stand a chance
against the other four,
but I think I'm ready to take you.
You must not think much of me.
It's obvious I just don't
take practice seriously.
Fine. I'll give you a taste
of what I can really do.
Are you going to let them play, Akashi?
Uh-oh. Kise-chin's getting destroyed.
No. He's way too good for a beginner.
He's just strong.
He may be annoying, but that has
nothing to do with his skill.
More! I'm not done yet!
It'll end the same way every time.
You and I are cut from different cloth.
He wasn't ready for this yet, though.
I'm going to buy some snacks.
We're still in the middle of
practice, Murasakibara-kun.
Shut up. I'll crush you.
Kise has grown extraordinarily
quickly, though.
Shogo-kun, are you done with practice?
Yeah, sorry. I just finished.
You're drenched in sweat.
I'll take a quick shower.
Do you want to come with me?
Oh, come on.
That bastard...
Hey, isn't that...
That's Kise's new girlfriend.
Ryota-kun?
This guy just challenged me and lost.
Seriously? Talk about lame.
Anyway, that's that.
Later, Ryota-kun.
You won't let me have it
for free? Yeah, right.
The Generation of Miracles?
Don't make me laugh.
That's some big talk when
this is all you can do.
You're so insignificant, I can't
even call this killing time.
He beat Kise?
Damn it!
Is Kaijo going to lose?
Preview
Who said he was going to beat me, Ryota?
Not yet! It's not over yet!
No matter what play you
make, I'll just steal it!
Stay Out of My Way
I will win, Shogo-kun!