Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
He made the shot!
Kagami's crushing Kise in the ace battle!
I don't want to lose to him!
Player substitution, black!
Kise, you're out.
He made it!
Go!
What? A pass?
The second quarter is over!
Kaijo
Seirin
We're tied!
There's no good way for us to
handle all five Seirin players.
But we can still score.
Stick to them like your life depends on it!
Yeah!
A step back?
You're in plain sight.
He stopped it!
First it was Kise, now it's Kasamatsu!
We're not finished yet!
Don't underestimate Kaijo!
In Order to Win
We play Kaijo tomorrow.
We've beaten them before,
but don't let your guard down.
Hey, Coach.
This is our first time playing Kaijo.
What?
What are you talking about, Hyuga?
Did you forget?
You mean it's our first official game.
Yeah.
When we saw the Kaijo-Touou game
during the Inter-High
after our summer training camp,
I overheard someone talking.
Seirin? I know them.
They may have won a practice game,
but they're not in the Inter-High, right?
Kaijo must be stronger.
We're not playing for praise.
But I knew they were right.
We played and won a practice game.
Practice is preparation for the real game.
You can win a hundred practice games,
but it's meaningless if you
can't win the real game.
Crap!
He's got a keen eye for missed shots!
His reaction to offensive
rebounds is especially quick!
And No. 9 is putting all his effort
into screening out Kagami
to keep him from jumping.
Their teamwork is incredible.
Hayakawa!
Defense, pushing!
White No. 7!
Kaijo
Seirin
Basket counts!
One free throw!
Yeah!
Nice work, Kobori!
Crap.
Damn it.
Kiyoshi Teppei...
You're much better than me.
But I won't lose.
Because we want to win more than you.
We're more determined.
This is our chance for revenge.
Since you beat us once,
you're on the receiving end.
And you weren't in the last game.
I won't lose to a guy who just wants to win.
Say something, you moron!
Ow!
Don't just listen to him speak his mind!
It seemed reasonable, so I couldn't help it.
What?
It explains why they're strong.
Have you already forgotten last night?
You couldn't help it?!
Don't accept his logic, Iron Heart!
Sorry.
So don't call me that.
You've hardly done anything until now!
We're counting on you, Uncrowned King!
Don't call me that, either.
Where's the spirit you had when you
faced Murasakibara, Iron Heart?
I really don't like it.
Pull yourself together, Iron Heart!
Stop that.
Iron Heart, Iron Heart, Iron Heart...
Iron Heart...
I told you to stop!
We may be friends, but you
don't get a free pass!
Don't call me Iron Heart!
Don't you know it takes one to know one?!
What are you talking about?
That doesn't make any sense, idiot!
Well, you've let tons of threes through!
Shut up! I'm just getting started!
Shouldn't we stop them?
Leave them.
They'll stop eventually.
I'd rather die than make
lamer jokes than Izuki!
Kaijo
Seirin
Come on!
Let's get them back!
Are they going to be okay?
They'll be fine.
Focus on your own play.
It happens all the time.
What?
They've grown up since
you first-years joined.
But when they played together last year,
they were like that all the time.
Isn't that really bad?
They say the closer you
are, the more you fight.
They're the pillars that carried
the brand new Seirin team
to the championship league.
You can count on them.
I haven't forgotten.
This is our only chance.
This is our only chance to
play with these members.
No you don't!
I know, Hyuga.
This is our first battle against Kaijo.
We're not on the receiving end of anything!
Yes!
They pushed it through!
We've played before, but they're
not here for revenge against us.
If anything, it's the other way around.
We failed to keep our promise last summer.
He's starting to match my timing!
We're here to try again!
To beat Kaijo!
He stopped it!
He stopped Moriyama's irregular shot!
Nice, Hyuga!
It's time to strike back!
A screen to the outside and back in?
He made it!
Nice pass.
Nice screen.
See?
They're on the same page...
They're strong.
Kaijo's intensity is monstrous.
But Seirin's is just as strong.
Coach, put me in!
Go, Kagami!
Yes!
The Seirin-Kaijo game's already
entering its fourth quarter.
Our after-game meeting was long.
We couldn't help it.
We had a lot to reflect on.
Who's going to win?
I'd be excited to play either one!
How's the game going?
Since the start of the third quarter,
Seirin's held a lead and
maintained control of the game.
H-Hey, isn't that...
They look so strong.
The first finalists,
and strongest school, Rakuzan High!
And their first-year captain,
Akashi Seijuro of the Generation of Miracles!
Kaijo
Seirin
Yeah!
We're ten points ahead!
We're in control of the fourth quarter, too.
That's impressive.
He broke through that double-team.
Then he passed to finish the play.
It's simple but beautiful.
I can tell from that one play!
Seirin's amazing!
Akashi, what do you think?
Well, I can see how they
made it to the semi-finals.
They play well.
They don't look like a
team in its second year.
Kaijo's a good team, but they
can't handle them without Ryota.
According to our scouts,
Ryota was subbed out for an injury.
Until then, he used his new
ability for about three minutes.
Considering their abilities as well as the fact
that Ryota has only two more
minutes to use his ability...
If we can pull 15 points ahead, we'll win.
Naturally, it's not guaranteed.
But with 15 points, even with
his unstoppable Perfect Copy,
they can't make a comeback in two minutes.
Kaijo
Seirin
It will dramatically improve
our chances of winning.
With five more points, it's checkmate.
Coach.
Rebound!
He pushed it in!
Kaijo's not giving up!
We won't lose!
Don't let them pull any farther ahead!
We'll win!
Do everything it takes to pull ahead!
Be patient.
Be patient!
Please!
Do your best!
Do your best, guys!
Hayakawa-senpai...
Moriyama-senpai...
Kobori-senpai...
Nakamura-senpai...
Kasamatsu-senpai!
What?
The Inter-High game against Touou...
It's my fault we lost.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about, idiot?
You're our ace.
Have they ever said anything like that?
Leading his team to victory is the ace's job.
But you're not responsible for losses.
That's my job.
An ace just needs to face forward.
I...
An alley-oop!
They're 15 points ahead!
Kaijo is screwed!
Kise, wait! It's too soon!
I don't care. I'm going in.
We still have four minutes.
If you push yourself for over
two minutes on that leg,
you could suffer long-term effects.
Coach,
the ace's job is to lead his team to victory.
If I don't play now, I'm not the ace!
If I don't go, I'll regret it.
After all...
I love this team.
Fine.
But if I think you're in
danger, I'm subbing you out.
Roger that.
I'm subbing in.
Coach.
Isn't it too soon to sub Kuroko in?
He still can't use his Phantom Shot.
His Misdirection is pretty
weak against Kaijo right now.
I thought so, too.
We have a 15 point lead.
We can wait and see.
That's why I have to play.
To beat Kise-kun.
Nothing's scarier than when he's cornered.
Kuroko knows the terror of the
Generation of Miracles better than any of us.
So we're counting on you, Kuroko-kun.
I've steeled my resolve.
See this through.
You're Kaijo's ace, Kise.
The final four minutes.
Go get 'em!
Ow! Don't push me, Satsuki!
Hurry up! We're going to miss the game!
You said we didn't have to come.
I changed my mind.
I need to see with my own
eyes how this game ends.
Ouch...
You got lucky, Satsuki.
Huh?
Looks like all the players are here.
It's the climax.
Kaijo was barely hanging on.
If they'd waited any longer, it
may have broken their spirits.
For that reason alone, subbing
in Ryota was the right choice.
But there are four minutes
left in the game to his
two minutes of Perfect Copy.
Even if he makes no mistakes...
We're so far ahead.
They can't catch up.
We definitely have Kaijo on the ropes.
But...
Why do I feel so uneasy?
Hey.
You're finally here.
I've been waiting for...
Kagami-kun.
Yeah.
We can't let out guard down.
Yes.
I agree.
Until we hear the end of game buzzer,
there's no telling what will happen.
Don't relax until it's over!
Hands up!
Let me hear you!
Yeah!
Hey!
He's here!
Kaijo's ace, Kise!
That's right. I'm the ace.
The ace leads his team to victory.
I don't want to lose again.
I won't let them lose again.
I will lead Kaijo to victory.
Could it be?
We'll beat
Seirin!
He crossed over from Akashi's
Emperor Eye into Aomine's drive!
This is
Perfect Copy!
Yes!
But...
He's unbelievable.
But,
I had a feeling you'd do this!
That's why
this isn't enough to make me back down!
Kagami-kun!
Counterattack!
What?
And...
It's a layup!
Aomine's agility plus Murasakibara's blocks!
I can't believe he stopped Kuroko
and Kagami's counterattack!
This isn't good! Head back!
Wha—
You're kidding!
He copied Tetsu-kun's pass!
Kaijo
Seirin
Nice shot, Kobori-san!
Yeah!
We'll win!
I'll put everything I have on the line!
The final spurt of a cornered member
of the Generation of Miracles...
The pressure is incredible!
I can't believe he copied Kuroko's pass.
How much can this monster evolve?
But he's already using it
with four minutes left.
Is he using up everything now?
No.
There's another possibility.
What?
He'll make it last until the end.
Using Perfect Copy consumes a
tremendous amount of stamina.
But for some reason it's burning
less now than in the first half.
At this rate, it may last.
It puts a comeback well within their reach.
We were naive to think we could stay ahead.
We can't win
without stopping his Perfect Copy.
Preview
Damn it!
His Perfect Copy put them
in control of the game!
They're all cheering for Kaijo.
The fans are against us, too.
Focus!
We can't afford any mistakes!
This Time
Yeah.
We will win!