Sorry... I'm sure you're tired.
It's all right.
I've been thinking that I
should see Dr. Muroto soon.
I heard that despite being a genius,
she is extremely strange.
That's putting it lightly...
Huh?
Sensei!
Hey, Sensei!
Where'd she go...
No!
You really saved me, Rentaro-kun.
#09 The Protectors of the Barrier
My food supply had run out
and I was about to die...
But the sticky sweet fruit of dried
persimmons keeps stimulating
my empty stomach and it's rather unpleasant.
Rentaro-kun...
This means you're gonna be
locked up for a long time.
I didn't kidnap her.
Onii-san wouldn't do something like that.
Well, well...
He's felt the butts of a
hundred young girls in passing,
and invaded elementary schools to
steal stool samples a thousand times.
He is the grand master of all perverts.
I didn't know you were a
person of such stature.
I've been terribly rude to you...
Don't believe her!
By the way, just the day before yesterday,
Shoma-kun was looking for you.
Shoma-nii was?
I said you weren't here at the moment,
then he left without telling me anything.
He doesn't change, does he?
Who's that?
Nagisawa Shoma.
He's a senior practitioner of
mine in the Tendo Martial Arts.
He was so strong that I stood
no chance against him...
But one day, he suddenly left the dojo.
You respected him?
Yeah...
I was really sad when he left.
I didn't get why he left without saying anything.
Doctor, I'd like to discuss something with you.
I will soon have people pursuing me.
You mean Ayn?
When that happens, I will be
an inconvenience to everyone.
Wouldn't it be better if I left
the Tendo Civil Security Agency?
You idiot!
How foolish.
Huh?
Kisara-san, Enju and I aren't
so weak that you need to worry about us.
Tina-chan,
if I were to give a liberal translation
of what Rentaro-kun is trying to say...
It'd be: "You're a vital part of
my little girl harem plan,
so there's no way I'm letting you get away."
Or something like that...
She obviously made that up!
Say, Tina.
You don't dislike us, right?
Then there's no problem.
Don't worry. I'll become even stronger.
Thank you...
She's a good kid.
So how do you actually feel
about Enju-chan and Tina-chan?
Well, I think they're cute...
The things they do without thinking
make my heart skip sometimes.
Being so honest is a good thing. However...
Don't get too attached.
The Cursed Children are bound
by their body corrosion rate,
a shackle they cannot escape.
They are different from us.
Enju is human just like you and me!
But people who believe that are the minority.
If you want to change our world,
you should have become a politician.
There's more than one way
to change the world.
The freedom to see a bigger world
where we don't have to be
frightened by the Gastrea...
I'd like to give that to Enju and Tina.
And for that, I'll defeat all of the Gastrea!
I see. So that's your answer.
You truly are different from me.
Do you know what the most beautiful
thing in this universe is?
In Buddhism, apparently it's the
lotus flower... in other words,
you, since your name comes from that word.
You have a beautiful soul.
Seeing the way you are now,
I believe it'd be all right
to show you that thing.
This is the data I was able to get from
the Level Five access key you brought me.
This is...
Kanto Battle
The Gastrea and JASDF...
A time line going back twenty
years from the present 2031.
"Heaven's Ladder" Project
Secretly plotted by the government
"New Humanity Creation Plan"
Take a look right here.
Gastrea War Outbreak
2021/xx/xx: Nanahoshi Village destroyed
Kanto Battle
The Gastrea and JASDF clash
Something's not right.
All records from the beginning
to the end of the Gastrea War
should have been destroyed.
That's what the textbooks say, right?
However...
Gastrea War Outbreak
Your access key level is insufficient.
That's right. Someone is
concealing this information.
Nanahoshi Village destroyed
Nanahoshi...
Inheritance of "Nanahoshi," the Seven Stars...
Hello, Kisara-san?
Satomi-kun. Are you watching the news?
The whitening of the Monolith
has been discovered.
Look at this! It's unbelievable!
The official announcement hasn't been made,
Monolith 32 is turning white
and beginning to collapse!
but it looks like they couldn't hide it any longer.
It's begun, Satomi-kun.
Yeah...
Today, the day after the whitening
of Monolith 32 was reported,
an official press conference
is being held by Seitenshi-sama.
Including today, Monolith 32
will most likely be destroyed in four days.
What can you tell us about a
new Monolith being constructed?
Does this mean that you had prior
knowledge of this, Seitenshi-sama?
Seitenshi-sama Emergency Press Conference
She's having to bear the full
brunt of it all... Poor thing.
They say there are arguments
for and against using a lottery
to screen candidates
for the underground shelter.
Can't we have the other citizens
evacuate to other areas?
I heard the rich men have
already spent a lot
of money buying up all the airline tickets.
I'm sure it's only a matter of time
before everyone else starts rioting.
Rentaro, it's finished!
Is this really a tent?
It's just rags!
It can't be helped.
If we're not officially
registered as an adjuvant,
they won't give us a JASDF tent.
Just one more pair!
We're going to find them
today, no matter what!
There's no way I can sleep in such
a cramped space with this pervert.
I'm sorry... If only I could join you...
Don't worry about it.
Your rank's currently revoked.
Don't worry, Tina!
I shall capture the most
amazing comrades for us!
It's not as fun as you're making it sound...
Then I shall make it fun!
Rentaro! Hurry! Hurry!
There are so many people...
It's almost like a festival.
A festival? Really?
Oh! Rentaro, how about them?
No, let's skip them.
Take a look.
He's armored from head to toe.
People do that when they don't want to die,
but that'd be fatal in a battle against Gastrea.
Rather than increasing your defense,
it's better to make yourself
lighter to increase your speed.
I see...
So it's better to pick people with light gear.
Let's see...
I found them!
I shall scout them!
Whoa, hey, wait a minute!
They're harder to find than I expected.
Well, most of them are already
in other adjuvants...
Let's head back for today.
Indeed...
Don't look, Enju!
Apparently a civil officer did it.
What a fool.
He had no idea they were
on a totally different level.
Rentaro!
That's an impressive cut...
Who could have...
It's a fight!
What the hell?
Let's go!
Let's go, Rentaro.
It may be the one who killed them.
Right.
That's...
Shoma-nii!
Don't you know who I am?
The death row fugitive
wanted for robbery and murder,
Brick Nigel!
I never said you were weak.
Then why won't you drink my alcohol?
I'm not obligated to have you buy me a drink.
What?!
Why hasn't anyone realized it?
This match... They are clearly
on completely different levels.
You really shouldn't.
A battle without honor or dignity
is rather boring, whether you win or lose.
Shut up!
Amazing! That was amazing, Rentaro!
Rentaro?
That move... was Sandatama Kirin, right?
Your skills haven't waned a bit, Shoma-nii.
It's been a while, Satomi.
I've been hearing about
your recent accomplishments.
Do you know him, Rentaro?
Let me introduce you, Enju.
Rank eight in the Tendo Style
Martial Arts, Nagisawa Shoma.
He's my senior practitioner in the Tendo Style.
Ever since I heard that
you defeated a Scorpion,
I've been thinking about fighting alongside you.
Though I am unworthy,
allow me to join you in
your scheme with my power
as a rank eight in the
Tendo Style Martial Arts.
That would be reassuring.
But why are you a civil officer, Shoma-nii?
Why did you up and leave the dojo so suddenly?
I wasn't cut out for it.
That's all.
Hey... can I ask you one other thing?
The pair that was killed on the train tracks...
Did you guys do that?
What are you talking about?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Hey!
We brought it!
We're back!
Nagisawa Shoma. Pleasure to work with you.
I'm F-Fuse...
Fuse Midori.
I'm a Model Cat Initiator.
M-My specialty is smell fortune-telling.
Can you use magic?
M-Magic?
Well, you're wearing a witch's hat.
Midori,
you don't have to hide
anything among friends.
Is this even possible, Rentaro?
Yeah. I've heard of cases
where the animal factors
in the Gastrea virus strongly
affect the body of the host.
All right! Now we've got six!
That means our adjuvant is complete.
Wait.
Satomi, do you really
want to go with just six?
Well... I'd like to have five pairs,
so ten of us, if possible.
Do we really need that many?
I think the maximum number
of people I can direct,
as well as the number we'd
need to cover our blind spots,
is right around that number.
Huh... So two other pairs...
Just one more.
Kisara-san?
Tendo Style swordsman
and Promoter, Tendo Kisara.
Mechanized soldier of the
"Next" program and Initiator,
Tina Sprout.
The two of us
have arrived unannounced to
join Satomi Rentaro's adjuvant.
Hold on a second!
Tina's rank is currently revoked.
I personally had Seitenshi-sama withdraw that.
We're at a critical point where
the Tokyo Area being destroyed.
Then...
I just finished registering us.
Our rank starts at 9,200.
Though I'm sure our actual ability
is a little higher than that.
I'd say it's a bit more than "a little higher."
It's been a while, Kisara.
What?! You're kidding! Shoma-kun?!
Was I rude to address a senior
practitioner by her first name?
I don't mind.
We've known each other forever.
More importantly, where have
you been all this time?
More importantly, come here a sec!
Wait, Satomi-kun!
She's a goddess...
I have a goddess...
Bro, are you all right in the head?
Think about your health for a minute!
I already went for my dialysis today.
You will allow me to join your adjuvant!
That is your president's order!
Like I could listen to that ord—
Onii-san...
Do you not want me to be on your team?
Oh, damn it!
Pardon.
Commander Gado has ordered
all civil officers to gather
in front of headquarters at 1930 hours.
Thank you all for coming.
I am your commander, Gado Nagamasa.
You have all been chosen
to save the Tokyo Area.
I am proud to be able to
fight alongside you all.
That's...
Rank 275, Gado Nagamasa.
The Tokyo Area is currently in terrible danger.
The Gastrea are a fearsome enemy,
but if anyone is able to defeat them, it is us!
Kill them!
It is your duty to kill as many as possible
of the loathsome Gastrea
that killed our families and those we loved!
It is the victors who have created
our history up until now.
We will win and be the writers of history!
We shall kill them all!
Yeah!
That's a pretty effective speech for a
bunch of hot-blooded civil officers.
Indeed. He's just as I heard.
Currently, the Gastrea army and the JASDF
are glaring at each other from
either side of Monolith 32.
As soon as the battle begins,
we shall send in support squads
according to the request of the JASDF.
So we don't get any action
until they actually call on us.
Are there any questions?
Huh? Wait, Satomi-kun...
You're rather young. Who might you be?
Rank 300, Satomi Rentaro.
Ah, so you're...
Considering we're here as
the JASDF's rear guard,
the civil officer forces are
pretty distant from the JASDF.
Why is that?
We have only been
ordered to create our
encampment and be on standby.
Then why don't we move
our encampment closer?
There's a place near the
Flames of Revolution monument
where we could effectively hide
ourselves for guerrilla warfare.
Then we won't be able to
immediately respond to
the JASDF's call for aid.
Do you honestly think that call will come?
A one and a two...
No!
Wh-What are you doing?!
We wanted to see if you had a tail, as well.
I do not!
That really scared me.
Thankfully, the meeting ended before
anything drastic happened, but...
Do you just feel the need to
go after anyone in power?
I just wanted our doubts addressed.
More importantly, are you really
planning on fighting with us?
Jeez... Are you still going on about that?
Kisara-san...
If something were to happen to you, I...
Why can't you realize I feel the same?
I don't want to just sit there and pray
while you're putting yourself
in danger, Satomi-kun!
Please, Satomi-kun.
If I end up getting in the way,
you're welcome to leave me behind.
I won't let that happen.
I'll protect you, Kisara-san.
So don't worry.
Jeez... You idiot...
K-Kisara-san, I...
Huh?
I...
Ahem.
Whoa!
You bastard!
What are you doing to my goddess?!
Wha?
Kisara, you seduced Rentaro
by letting him grope
your huge boobs again, didn't you?
I-I didn't let anyone grope anything!
That's disgusting.
That didn't happen!
Uh, it might be a little weird
to reintroduce ourselves, but...
I'm Satomi Rentaro.
Aihara Enju!
Tendo Kisara!
Tina Sprout.
Katagiri Tamaki.
Katagiri Yuzuki!
Nagisawa Shoma.
I'm F-Fuse Midori.
Thank you all for helping me out.
For these three days between the destruction
and reconstruction of the Monolith,
let's see this fight through together!
Jeez, you're so dramatic.
My life is yours, Onii-san.
Rentaro,
you better not squander the
power I'm lending you!
Rentaro, since our team is together,
we need to have a cheer.
What the hell?
The Tenchu Girls always do a cheer!
We're all with you!
Of course we're going to win!
Yeah...
All right, let's do this!
One more time!
#10 Tokyo Area Defensive Battle
I realized that this happiness will end one day...
Let go of me!
Just who are we protecting?
Who are we supposed to fight for?!
For what?!