Rentaro...
We're going, too.
I will stay behind.
If someone doesn't hold them back here,
win or lose, we'll all die.
Don't worry. If I'm at a disadvantage, I will run.
Please take care of Shogen-san.
All right. Let's go, Enju.
Yeah.
#04 Black Bullet
It's so quiet...
Yeah.
What is this?
Sword...
My sword...
Ikuma Shogen?
Have you... seen my sword?
As long as... I have that...
I can... still... fight...
Papa, I'm surprised!
He really is still alive.
The end is near.
Let us finish this, Satomi-kun.
With the civil officers we have
in the vicinity, it'd take even
the closest pair at least an hour.
Kisara.
I called for her.
President Tendo, what would you say is the
success rate for the Satomi pair?
If I may voice my own expectation,
they will win.
No matter what.
What? They're up against the survivor
of the New Humanity Creation Plan!
They don't stand a...
Ten years ago,
Gastrea came into my house
and devoured my parents.
Because of the stress I endured at the time,
my kidneys are barely functioning.
At that time, Satomi Rentaro protected me,
and the Gastrea took his right hand,
right leg, and left eye.
On the verge of death,
he was taken to Section 22.
The performing surgeon was Dr. Muroto Sumire.
Muroto Sumire?
I-It can't be!
You will not retrieve the case.
Because...
We stand in your way!
A second defeat,
the annihilation of my comrades...
Sure! I couldn't have asked for
a better situation, damn it!
I will eliminate you!
Tendo Martial Arts First Style, Number 3:
Rokuro Kabuto!
He broke through Maximum Pain?
Artificial limbs made from Varanium?
Could it be that you're also...
I'll introduce myself, as well, Kagetane.
I am formerly from the Ground
Self-Defense Force's Eastern Force,
787th Mechanization Special Unit,
of the New Humanity Creation Plan...
Satomi Rentaro!
There was another one?
Another of the human weapons
born of the Gastrea War?
I am in pain...
I am alive.
What a magnificent life!
Hallelujah!
Don't be mean to Papa!
Cry, Sodomy.
Sing, Gospel.
We were created to kill.
If the Gastrea War were to recommence,
the significance of our lives will be proven.
Are you trying to tell me...
that's the reason you're...
What did the people around you think
when they found out your Initiator
was one of the Cursed Children?
Did they offer their blessings?
Were you touched by endless cheers of joy?
The world that we wish for
is different from theirs.
We have been chosen.
Now, Satomi Rentaro.
Come with me!
You've got to be kidding me, you bastard.
There's no way in hell
I can accept the future you're talking about!
Enju!
If you cannot abide...
Then die!
You have lost.
Am I... going to die?
Enju...
Rentaro! Please do not leave me alone!
The AGV experimental drug was
created from the Gastrea virus.
It gives humans the regenerative
abilities of the Gastrea,
but there is a 20% chance that they
will turn into Gastrea themselves.
If you can avoid it, don't use them.
R-Rentaro...
I won... that gamble.
Satomi-kun, you're...
Tendo Martial Arts Suiten Ippeki Stance:
Unebiko Ryu!
Inzen Kokutei!
Am I... going to...
lose to you?
Papa... Papa...
Hiruko Kagetane's signal has disappeared!
Rentaro!
It's all right now.
Papa!
No... No, Papa!
Papa...
She's no longer an enemy.
I won like I promised, Kisara-san.
Yeah, I saw.
But, Satomi-kun...
I've got some bad news I have to tell you.
A Stage Five Gastrea
has shown itself.
Is everything over?
We won't let it end!
Seitenshi-sama has given her consent to my plan.
The answer is to the southeast of your position.
Heaven's Ladder?
You're going to do it, Satomi-kun.
The Linear Electromagnetic Projectile Device.
Also known as Heaven's Ladder.
A railgun module that fires metallic projectiles
with a diameter less than
800 millimeters at near light speed.
If we shoot Varanium rounds at a speed
that would make regeneration impossible,
we'd be able to exterminate
even a Stage Five Gastrea.
Commencing operation of the
Linear Electromagnetic Projectile Device.
Power supply, nominal.
Dewar vessels for liquid
helium storage, also nominal.
Thank you, Satomi-kun.
We'll take care of the launch sequence here
as soon as everything is operational.
So all we have to do now is watch?
We couldn't do anything,
even if they told us to.
That's a Stage Five?
Yeah. The Zodiac Gastrea: Scorpion.
It's the Gastrea that almost
destroyed the world.
We've got trouble, Satomi-kun.
It's displaying a message saying
there's a problem in the chamber.
What does that mean?!
It's possible the Varanium
rounds haven't been loaded.
What?!
Damn it! There aren't any rounds!
Electrical power preservation system
coolant leak confirmed.
Please halt the experiment at once.
What do we do, Rentaro?
Because of the magnetic field...
Satomi-kun, it's not responding
to remote commands.
Satomi-kun...
Rentaro, you aren't going to...
I'm going to use my right arm as a shell.
There shouldn't be an issue
if it's super Varanium.
Varanium charge detected.
We can't regain control
of the launch sequence!
Without doing it manually on-site,
launch is impossible.
Satomi-kun, did you hear that?
We can't fire the railgun from here.
Please! You have to do it!
Hey, you've got to be kidding!
There's no way I can do it!
Kisara-san!
Satomi-kun, the world— Please—
Kisara-san! Kisara-san!
Energy levels at 100%.
Initiating manual trigger system.
Rentaro...
So I have to manually hit a
target 50 kilometers away?
Satomi-kun...
Satomi-san...
I can't. I can't do it...
I...
Rentaro, I am here.
If we miss, we're finished.
Of course we'll hit it.
The shell could veer toward the Tokyo Area
and cause an unprecedented disaster!
But if it's you, Rentaro,
it'll hit the target.
Enju...
You're the only one who can save the world.
No one else but you, Rentaro...
Enju...
I don't want to lose you, no matter what...
May I interpret that as a proposal?
You idiot.
Take it as me saying you're family!
A ten-year-old shouldn't be talking about love!
You're not scared anymore, right?
Yeah... Let's finish this!
Enju...
Yeah.
Go!
Why didn't you run?
So you've... found me.
You said you'd run if you
were at a disadvantage.
Satomi-san, how's Shogen-san?
He's safe.
Satomi-san... I...
Yeah... There's no doubt.
The corrosion rate in your body is over 50%.
Please let me die as a human...
As the one who acknowledged my existence,
I didn't want to let you die.
So I tried hard...
It was hard, but...
I'm glad I lived.
Right now, my heart
is filled with gratitude...
Thank you.
Hey, Satomi-san, you don't have
very many friends, do you?
I'll be your friend.
Yeah...
Thanks.
You are my irreplaceable friend.
Satomi-san, from here on out...
If you get lost in the darkness,
follow the compass within your heart
and go towards the light...
Please save
this world...
About the information leaked to Kagetane...
They're saying it was caused by Defense
Minister Kutsuoda's party going on a rampage.
Kutsuoda just hanged himself in
his detainment cell and died.
He worked for you, didn't he?!
The New Gastrea Law.
A law that will raise the social
status of the Cursed Children...
But you're all for discrimination.
You made it known that his daughter,
Kohina, was involved in this act of terrorism,
and encouraged animosity
toward the Cursed Children.
You even tried to summon a Stage Five Gastrea
that would destroy the Tokyo Area,
in order to stop the New Gastrea Law.
How could you forget?
Ten years ago, those bugs killed
my wife and many others.
They also took your arm and leg,
and you want me to grant the children
who carry their blood human rights?
They are the demons who will
bring destruction to this world.
Those girls are human...
I, Satomi Rentaro,
believe in Aihara Enju.
You fool...
You saved my life...
If you do not want to die,
survive, Rentaro.
When I was in the pit of despair,
I would remember those
words and pull through.
I have never forgotten what
happened that day ten years ago.
Seitenshi-sama...
I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
I saw what was inside the case.
A broken-down tricycle.
How the hell is that a catalyst
to summon a Scorpion?
What are Gastrea, anyway?
Please tell me, Seitenshi-sama!
I cannot tell you that.
Rentaro!
Oh, is your arm all better?
For the most part.
Did Sumire tell you the results
of my corrosion exam?
Yeah. 24.9%.
Oh, so it's barely changed at all.
Satomi-san...
If the hierarchy were to improve,
civil officer pairs would
be given special rights:
A quasi-class elevation,
and the access key to top secret information.
Satomi-san, rise through the ranks with Enju-san.
Then you will know
the reason you were born
and who you truly are...
Corrosion Rate
42.1%
Aihara Enju
((Medical Chart))
Percentage Until Bodily Breakdown
7.2% Remaining
#05 The Crimson Black Assassin
We've got a job.
It's a bodyguard request.
Rentaro, I have a bad feeling about this.
Who are you?
What is your mission?
The assassination of the Tokyo
Area representative, Seitenshi.