Teiko Middle School
Dai-chan, have you decided
which club you're joining?
Huh?
Don't ask the obvious.
I'm joining the basketball team.
This school's supposed to be pretty strong.
I'm excited to play.
Really?
Maybe I'll be the manager, then.
Want me to pack lunches for you?
No way.
I wouldn't be able to play if you did.
What does that mean?
Sorry.
My bad.
Wait, what?
What's wrong?
I just...
Never mind.
Hey, do you like books?
Why not join the literary club?
Actually, this is a phone book.
Phone books are books, too.
Why are you walking around with a phone book?
It's Oha-Asa's lucky item.
Say, you're huge!
Amazing!
You should join the volleyball team!
I don't know...
Sounds like a pain in the butt.
Isn't that guy really hot?
He's so cool!
Please join our club!
Actually, I...
Are you sure here is fine?
Yes.
You don't need to drive me to
and from school anymore, either.
I'll let your father know.
It's not my father's business.
Besides, they'll mock me if I
show up like this every morning.
At least let me do as I please at school.
Did you already join a club?
I'm on the basketball team, of course!
Let's work hard to get into games
so we can play against each other!
I'm joining the basketball club, too.
Blue Sky
First we'll test you to
divide you into classes.
Only the first string will play
in official games as regulars.
I heard no one is placed into the
first string out of this test.
Seriously?
So we'll be second string at best?
I guess we'll aim for second string, then.
Good luck.
They're excited about something.
What club are they?
What should I do?
There's probably nothing I can't do.
I will now announce the results!
We'll start with the third string.
If your name is called, go stand
in front of the third string coach.
No. 2, Saito Nobuo.
Yes, sir!
No. 4, Nakazawa Katsuhito.
No. 10, Fujita Hiromichi.
No. 12, Takagiku Yuji.
...Shimida Shunsuke.
No. 30, Tanaka Jun.
No. 31, Kuroko Tetsuya.
That's all.
Next I'll announce the second string.
Yes!
I'm in the second string!
All right!
No. 14, Kuroki Dai.
No. 35, Yagi Masao.
Next I'll announce the first string.
Did he just say first string?
You're kidding, right?
No. 8, Aomine Daiki.
No. 11, Midorima Shintaro.
No. 23, Murasakibara Atsushi.
No. 29, Akashi Seijuro.
That's all.
Those of you who didn't make
the second string, work harder.
Yes, sir!
The other day I got my uniform!
I'm still riding the bench during games,
but I'll work harder so I can become a starter!
How are you doing?
Teiko's really strong,
but as long as you work hard,
I know you can succeed.
Faculty Office 2
Stay late to practice?
Sure you can, but make
sure you leave on time.
Okay.
Yeah, I guess...
You're so lucky to be
Aomine-kun's childhood friend!
Does he have a girlfriend?
What?
He carried the last game.
He's so cool!
Oh!
Be careful.
Thanks for everything.
I appreciate your daily support.
Let's go, Midorima.
Akashi-sama's cool, too.
"Sama"?
He's only a first year,
but he's already the vice captain!
I see...
You've been thinking a lot lately, Akashi.
Yes, I suppose.
Are you thinking about nationals?
We won, but it was close.
Looking ahead to the next two years,
our victory isn't guaranteed.
Is it not enough for us to get stronger?
We're already strong enough.
But our methods are too orthodox.
We need variety.
A sixth man who can change
the flow of the game.
That kind of player.
Have mercy, have mercy, have mercy...
Who are you?
Huh?
Aomine-kun?
I heard rumors about a ghost in the gym.
I thought you were him.
I'm just staying late to practice.
That's amazing.
Most of the first string
guys don't even do that.
Okay, I know.
We'll practice together here every day.
We'll stand on the court together someday.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Only good guys like basketball.
Let me be clear.
You're not good enough for our team.
What?
I know you've practiced hard.
But your rank has fallen.
I won't make you quit.
It's your decision.
How...
What? Why?
I like basketball.
But I can't help the team.
There's no such thing as
a player we don't need.
You may not play in games,
but I can't believe someone who stays so
late to practice is completely useless.
I can't guarantee you'll make
it if you don't give up.
But once you give up, you'll have nothing.
Aomine.
Akashi...
I haven't seen you around lately.
This is where you've been?
Yeah.
The other gym gets crowded.
We always practice here together.
Together?
Who's this guy?
I'm interested in him.
Sorry, but could you come with me?
I've never met someone
so devoted to basketball
who failed to produce results.
Sorry, but I'm not in any
place to hear those words.
Sorry. That's not what I meant.
I'm impressed.
You're not unathletic.
Based on your history and practice,
you're an experienced player.
But I feel nothing when I look at you.
This is truly exceptional.
Normally, you can sense an
experienced sports player.
They can't help it.
But you're hardly even there.
However, that isn't your
weakness, it's your strength.
If you can use that,
you will become a powerful
weapon for the team.
Use my lack of presence?
Is that possible?
Sorry, but that's all I can say.
Find me when you have your answer.
Is he the sixth man you mentioned?
Were you listening?
You really think he'll change?
Who knows?
I sensed potential in
him, but he's a stranger.
We're not friends.
I'm not obligated to help him.
I simply dangled a thread in front of him.
Whether or not he'll climb it
is up to him.
What can you do for the team?
That's what you discussed with Akashi?
Yes.
I'm not a good shooter.
All I can do is pass or assist other players.
Well, Akashi can't do everything.
There must be something only you can do.
Like what?
Like a pass that curves like crazy.
Like, "swoosh"!
Swoosh!
That's enough.
I'm staying here.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Misdirection
Techniques
Hey, Akashi!
You have a guest.
Haven't seen you in three months, Kuroko-kun.
Did you find your answer?
Yes.
Then let's test you immediately.
Um...
If possible, could I show you in a game?
Nijimura-san.
That's him.
Oh, right. He's the one you mentioned.
Shoot!
When did he get there?
Where'd he come from?
What is this?
His passes are surprising,
but how can people lose
sight of him during a game?
Misdirection.
What?
It's a technique used in magic tricks
for directing a person's focus.
Magic?
For example, before he intercepts a pass,
he uses his gaze and movements
to direct his mark's attention
to the ball or another player.
Combined with his natural lack of
presence, he seems to disappear.
Second String
Third String
Did you know this would happen?
No. He exceeded my expectations.
Starting today, you're on the first string.
You got your chance.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Is there a Kuroko-kun here?
That's me.
He's invisible...
He's barely there...
I brought Kuroko Tetsuya-kun.
Thanks.
You're here, Tetsu.
Hey. I've been waiting for you.
Welcome to the first string of the
Teiko Middle School basketball team.
100 Battles 100 Victories
Remember this.
From this moment, you have only one purpose.
Winning.
It's Haizaki.
What? Give me that!
Haizaki, where are you?
Sorry, but I've got a cold.
Haizaki's out with a cold.
Kuroko.
You'll start instead.
Let's have a good game!
Tetsu, relax.
You're hopeless.
You're like a newborn fawn.
Calm down, Kuroko-kun.
We'll start slow.
Sorry. I tripped on my own feet.
I'm okay.
You're not okay at all.
I don't believe this.
Tetsu...
He was subbed out after only a second.
I wasn't expecting this.
We have no choice.
Nijimura.
Yes, sir.
Teiko, player substitution!
It's Teiko's captain Nijimura Shuzo.
He's the strongest middle
school power forward.
I'll lecture you later.
First, let's win.
Yes!
Fool!
We're playing to see how the
first-years work together.
You have to hold back.
Has your nose stopped bleeding?
Yes.
Okay. You'll switch with Nijimura.
Out of bounds!
Black ball!
What was that?
Are you messing around?
No, I'm not.
I'll crush you.
Please don't do that.
I see.
I understand his style.
It's interesting, but...
He makes too many mistakes.
Is it nerves?
Is his style not his own yet?
Or is it both?
Minamihara
Teiko
Good Luck
Minechin, what's that?
Satsuki made me lunch.
Want some?
No, it looks gross.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Huh?
Isn't this Minechin's wallet?
Where did he go?
The convenience store.
I'll take it to him.
Don't just throw things at me.
Huh? You're just slow.
You're demoting Tetsu?
We still have a game this afternoon.
Can't he play one more game?
No. He's not worth observing anymore.
I'm demoting him.
If he fails again, you can demote me, too!
Put him in one more time!
I know he'll save us someday.
I'm not sure why, but I know he will!
Say hi.
Hey...
Haizaki's face looks awful...
A second string guy found him in an arcade.
He seemed pretty healthy,
so I brought him here.
But he seems nearly dead...
Our starting lineup this
afternoon is Akashi, Midorima,
Murasakibara, Aomine, and Haizaki.
Kuroko, you'll play in the second half.
Got it?
Haranishi
Teiko
You need to fix the speed of your passes.
First string members are quick.
You need to pass sooner than you would
for second or third string players.
You have a timing issue.
Also, your Misdirection is most powerful
when you control your lack of presence.
Don't wear your emotions on your sleeve.
You must have the will to fight.
But keep it hidden.
I understand.
The ball...
Curved?
Passes keep coming from Akachin
with impossible timing.
This is super easy.
Does it make this much of
a difference when it works?
Kuroko Tetsuya, this year you'll
officially join the bench.
You're No. 15.
I expect great things from our new sixth man.
From: Ogiwara Shigehiro
Congratulations!
I knew you could do it.
See you at this summer's nationals!
It's a promise!
Preview
Kuroko's a regular, huh?
I guess you weren't wrong.
It's the product of his hard work.
But you're the one leading the team.
Nijimura-san...
...Sorry
I expect great things from you, Akashi.