Aomine-kun's not with you?
No. We're rarely together anymore.
I see.
I only talk to the others when
I have news about the team.
They're getting stronger and haven't lost,
but it's kind of sad.
Yes.
Hey, Tetsu-kun.
Do you remember what I asked you?
Momoi-san?
You'll
always be together, right?
You'll be friends forever, right?
Sorry, I don't remember.
What did you say?
What?
Uh, never mind.
It's no big deal.
Anyway, I'm going the other way.
Right.
See you later, then.
What is Victory?
Teiko
Dojimasaki
The team has become stronger.
But no one smiles anymore.
They fulfill their obligation
to win without emotion.
I haven't seen him smile in so long.
Games are kind of boring, aren't they?
Our opponents have been too weak to offer
real competition for a long time.
What do they call those five decent guys?
You mean the Uncrowned Somethings?
Yeah, them.
They were tough, but they're
all gone this year, right?
It's so easy, I don't
have any desire to play.
Mine.
That was my basket!
Your fault for missing.
Either way, you're dead last.
I'll catch up!
Damn it!
They're competing to see who
can score the most points!
Why did you do that during today's game?
What are you talking about, Kurokocchi?
We're just playing around.
I think it's rude
to the other team.
You're the one who said
we shouldn't slack off.
We're playing a game to
motivate us against weaklings.
Right, Midorima?
Don't be absurd.
I want no part in your game.
There're tons of people.
We're playing here today?
Tokyo Middle School
Basketball Tournament
Looks like they're playing
the middle school qualifiers.
Teiko
What?
Teiko Middle School...
They're more imposing than we are!
Aren't they middle school students?
Let's go.
What's wrong, Tetsu-kun?
The game already started?
I'll have a staff member give it to them.
Tetsu-kun?
Go!
They're a good team.
Yes.
They probably love the game
and give everything they have.
It's Teiko!
They're as imposing as professionals...
They don't seem like middle school students.
Teiko's amazing.
They sure are.
I'm going to go say hi to my friend.
Hey!
Hey, Kuro—
If you're not saying
anything, let's go, Shige.
We've got a game.
Meiko
Kyoizumi
Get it!
Get the ball!
Defense!
Meiko
Kyoizumi
Yeah!
We're in the finals!
We did it, Kuroko.
The time has come to fulfill our promise.
We're playing Meiko in the finals.
It's the same no matter who we play.
Coach.
What is it?
Could I be a starter in the next game?
You're raring to go.
What's gotten into you, Kuroko?
Do you have some reason for this?
Yes.
They made it!
What was that pass?
Teiko's so strong!
Seriously?
Amazing...
Kuroko, you've become incredible.
But why?
Why aren't you smiling?
Infirmary
Is Kuroko-kun here?
Yes, but he hasn't woken up yet.
Really?
Who are you?
What do you want with Tetsuya?
I'm Ogiwara Shigehiro of Meiko Middle School.
I came to see Kuroko.
Our opponent in the finals.
Unfortunately, Tetsuya won't
be playing in the next game.
Though it won't change anything...
Good luck.
Hey, wait.
Do you enjoy playing basketball?
Tetsu-kun!
How do you feel?
Akashi-kun, Momoi-san.
How'd the game go?
We won, of course.
The finals start in five minutes.
I'm playing.
Tetsu-kun!
No. The doctor told you to rest.
You'll stay here.
But...
I know. It's Ogiwara-kun, isn't it?
I saw him in the hallway.
He said, "We'll play again sometime."
I see.
Akashi-kun, please take the finals seriously.
Please.
You don't mind if we crush them?
It'd be worse if you held back.
I'm sure that's what he'd say.
Fine.
Akashicchi! How's Kurokocchi?
He'll be fine, though he can't play.
I see.
Let's win and tell him
about it after the game.
Yeah.
What were you talking about earlier?
We're tired of competing for points.
But that's a pain in the ass.
That's what makes it fun.
It's stupid. Do as you please.
Tell me more.
How did the game go?
The fourth quarter just started.
We have a huge lead.
I'm going to check it out.
You can't, Tetsu-kun.
I want to see for myself how it ends.
That should be enough of a lead.
Three-time champions, here we—
No.
What?
Something's wrong with this game.
Teiko
Meiko
We still have time! Don't give up!
What are you talking about?
The game's already...
I know.
But we can't just give up.
Shige...
If we have to lose,
let's at least make one shot
and lose with dignity!
Could it be?
Tetsu-kun!
I let you pass me so you'd make that shot.
Hey, Murasakibara!
I got it.
Did they do that on purpose?
Why would they do that?
We were trying to let
you have your moment.
But look, they're matching.
We did it.
Matching?
They did it so
the score would be all ones?
Ogiwara-kun!
Kuroko...
Akashi-kun...
Why?
They trampled on my promise to my friend.
I can't hear anything they're saying.
We won, but my chest hurts.
I can't breathe.
Can you really call this victory?
I don't understand anymore.
What
is victory?
Why did you do that?
We simply controlled the game.
Our players were far more focused
than if we were just trying to score.
That's not what I meant! I told you—
Why didn't you ask us to
take every game seriously?
Do you ignore it when you have
no personal stake in the game
and ask for special treatment
against your friend?
What? Your friend was on that team?
You should've told us.
Yeah, right. We would've
been bored just scoring.
Right, Midochin?
It doesn't matter how you play.
I simply do everything humanly possible.
It's not that we don't play seriously.
We can't since they're so weak.
With that much of a gap between our abilities,
how could we have played a game
that would satisfy both sides?
I don't know.
But that day's victory pained
me more than any failure.
Even if there was no other way,
I don't want to feel that way again.
So
I'm quitting
basketball.
Meiko Middle School
Kuroko-kun?
The finals really stung.
Talking to you still hurts.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I...
Shige, right?
He transferred.
He said he was quitting basketball, too.
Why?
That game obliterated our spirits.
Shige loved the game more than any of us.
I think it was hardest on him.
Sorry, that was harsh.
But...
I wish you wouldn't quit.
What? Why?
You have the same eyes we have.
Before the game, I met Teiko's captain.
His eyes were horrifyingly cold.
The other four had the same eyes.
But Kuroko was different.
I was too shocked to say anything,
but there was still warmth
left in Kuroko's eyes.
I was powerless against those icy eyes.
But Kuroko can face them
again and melt them someday.
Shige left this in his locker.
Graduation
Teiko Middle School
From now on, we're rivals.
We'll meet again at the national
high school tournament.
Yeah, but you don't have to be so cold.
We just happened to pick different schools.
Happened to? I think not.
There are only a handful of strong schools.
But none of us thought
to attend the same one.
None of us like being lumped together
as the Generation of Miracles.
If we compete, someone must come out ahead,
and no one is greater than ourselves.
To prove that,
we're driven to eliminate all others.
Not by reason, but by instinct.
I guess so.
Yeah.
I won't deny it.
I doubt Kurochin understands.
No.
Though he wants something different,
Tetsuya will join our contest.
He doesn't have all the answers yet.
But he's made up his mind.
He won't change the way he plays.
So you're the bad guy.
I shouldn't have worried.
The only surprise was
Akashi's dual personality.
If you thought he was wrong,
you should've hit him.
Act first and worry about logic later.
But you sat there and waffled.
You're right.
I couldn't do anything.
It's my fault Ogiwara-kun quit basketball.
I told you to stop waffling!
Ow!
He even gave you that
wristband as a keepsake.
He's not dead.
But I shouldn't have accepted it.
There's no way Shige thinks that.
You're just determined to
reject his forgiveness.
Anyway, what are you going to do?
"This is who I am,
but please accept me anyway?"
If that's what you're asking for,
I'll beat the crap out of you.
We're already friends.
Isn't that what you thought?
You're right. Well said, Kagami.
But...
You're dominating the conversation!
We've got lots to say, too!
Why?!
Kuroko, come here!
You need to be toughened up, too!
What?
Let's go, guys.
Thanks for the food, Kagami.
It's no big deal.
No big deal...
That was one big meal.
You know, like food.
You're still not funny!
Kagami-kun, there's something
I still haven't told you.
What? There's more?
The day I graduated...
Do you have your answer?
Not yet,
but I won't run anymore.
That much I've decided.
Why didn't you tell everyone?
I forgot to,
but it doesn't matter now.
I have my answer.
I just have to show them our basketball now.
Let's show them our style.
And
let's win the tournament!
Preview
We finally made it this far.
The finals, huh?
Yeah. Let's tear them to pieces!
To pieces...
This is no time for peace!
You're right.
Pieces, peace...
Final Tip-Off!!
What? Hey!