This is the enemy's base.
Isn't Pleiades that thing there?
Yeah,
it looks like it is.
With its limbs having degenerated
to such a short length,
it wouldn't be able to get any food,
let alone move on its own.
Well, then...
If you're going to strike,
you should do it now.
I was going to blow it up
with plastic explosives,
but my backpack went down the river.
Then there's only one way...
I've always wanted to fight one of those.
I shall take care of it.
Your strength alone won't be enough!
Then, shall we?
Yeah.
#12 Crisis Point
Rokuro Kabuto!
Endless...
...Scream!
Burst!
Papa, hurry!
Damn it! The wound...
Why are you...
Aldebaran...
We're saved...
Looks like Aldebaran and the
others have started to move.
Move?
Enju...
Yes?
Seitenshi-sama, listen!
I defeated Pleiades!
Now you can use missiles and fighter jets!
Understood. We will commence fire support.
Good... Now if they'll just
continue to disperse...
That's Aldebaran?
Yes!
Aldebaran is immortal.
That's... impossible...
Rentaro!
Enju...
Why did you leave without saying anything?
I was worried about you!
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
You fool!
Stop! I'm injured there!
Satomi-kun.
You took too long.
Thank goodness, you're all safe...
Satomi-kun... no, Leader Satomi.
Commander Gado
has died in battle.
In accordance with article 40
of the civil officer manual,
the officer with the next
highest rank assumes command.
Satomi-kun, please...
Lead us.
I didn't hate you, Gado.
Why, there you are, my comrade.
Rentaro, what's the meaning of this?
He saved me.
Saved you?
I saw him kill one of our
comrades in the tent village!
They decided to pick a fight,
so I merely gave them the fight they sought.
I missed you, Enju!
Let's cut each other, Enju!
Hold it!
You guys are the enemy of all
of us civil officers, aren't you?
Papa, can I cut them?
You may kill half of them.
Wait! This isn't the time to argue!
Our common enemy is the Gastrea!
If you have time to fight with each other,
think of a way to defeat as
many Gastrea as possible!
I'll be keeping close observation of
your capability as a commander.
Are you all right, Satomi?
Yeah...
Shoma-nii, where's Midori?
Midori was trying to save an
Initiator she didn't know....
And then the Gastrea...
A neurotoxin stole her ability to move,
and the Gastrea virus
was injected into her continually
until I managed to save her...
According to Sumire-sensei's examination,
her corrosion rate is already...
Satomi-kun, kill that girl.
You once fought me for the sake
of maintaining order in the world.
You won that battle.
This is the world that you wished for.
You must make amends with it.
Leader...
I have a request...
Please grasp a finger of your choice.
Are you touching my thumb?
Yep.
You didn't cheat, did you?
No!
Because of my ears,
I was never needed by anyone.
Not even my mother...
But then Shoma-san needed me...
And so did you.
The thing that'll make Shoma-nii and me happy
is you getting better as soon as possible...
I smell confusion from you, Leader.
Confusion has a smell?
It's sort of intuitive.
Also, concerning Tendo-san...
Kisara-san?
I detect a very strong smell
of destruction from her.
She is most likely very easily
influenced by the darkness.
But...
If you're the commander, Leader Satomi,
I think she'll do okay.
Midori...
I'm relieved...
H-Hey...
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
You don't intend to follow me, do you?
Of course not!
Leader...
I might... take a little while in the bathroom.
Right...
Where are you?
Midori!
Midori-chan!
Hey!
Midori!
Shoma-nii!
Midori
didn't want to burden
everyone in the adjuvant...
Satomi, let's just say that Midori ran away.
This will just upset everyone...
Midori and I were a lot alike.
We were both empty,
and our contract was pretty much
to remedy each other's loneliness.
Satomi, I didn't quit the Tendo Style.
I was excommunicated.
You saw it, too, didn't you?
That was a technique that I modified.
But destroying the enemy from the inside
isn't a part of the Tendo Style.
Our master didn't allow it.
That's also why I became a civil officer...
I should have been there to finish her...
I was her partner...
I'm sorry, Shoma-nii...
The ones who killed Midori are the Gastrea!
If you want to mourn her death,
swear to me that you'll defeat Aldebaran.
Stand, Rentaro.
If you don't do it,
even more brutal deaths await.
We have to stop the Tokyo Area from
drowning in a sea of blood!
Satomi Rentaro!
You have to do it.
Hey, look!
That's Commander Gado's...
I'm Satomi Rentaro, and I will
be taking over as commander.
Hey! The Tokyo Area's done for!
Let's all run for it!
Huh?
What? You wanna fight?!
Anyone else have any questions?
Chikaze, kill him!
If you move even a little,
your head's gonna fall off.
What brought this on?
This is not the ending I wanted, that's all.
Listen up! Anyone who tries to run,
or threatens the peace of the
group will be eliminated!
I'm not as kind as Gado was!
You're going too far, Satomi-kun!
That's how it should be.
You saw it, too, didn't you?
Everyone was trembling in fear of the Gastrea.
At this rate, they won't be able to fight.
That's why, from now on,
I'll be the one they fear
instead of the Gastrea.
But... then they'll curse you, and hate you...
Then no one will be on your side, Satomi-kun!
And I don't need anyone... At least for now.
You idiot!
Even if the whole world turns against you,
I'll always be by your side!
I'm sorry...
Those are the actions of a dictator.
You are not meant to be a commander.
Nagamasa-sama would have been more—
Gado is gone.
Not to mention,
didn't we lose twice because
his methods were wrong?
You dare ridicule Nagamasa-sama?! You lout!
A fiery little one, aren't you?
Did Commander Gado being ridiculed make
the blood rise to your head?
Who are you? State your name!
Nagisawa Shoma.
I've actually just lost my partner, as well...
How about it?
Want to pair up with me?
I will not serve two masters.
Don't you think we could fight Gastrea
more efficiently if we paired up,
even if only temporarily?
You're suggesting we pair up
until Aldebaran is defeated?
Then I shall lend you my strength
for a short amount of time.
Do with it as you please.
Hey, Satomi-kun, what is the meaning of this?
I hired her as a tactician.
We need a weapons specialist if
we want to defeat Aldebaran.
But did it have to be Miori
and Shiba Heavy Weapons?
Kisara.
Maybe you aren't aware,
but the Tokyo Area's in
real bad shape right now.
No one else has the resources to back you up.
Aldebaran's forces have started to move.
When are they expected to arrive?
11 PM.
So a little more than half a day...
So, Miori...
Is there a way to defeat Aldebaran?
Who do you think I am?
This is a special bomb created
by our engineering division,
the Ekpyrotic bomb.
EP bomb for short.
It has 20 times more power
than the 500 pound bomb
that the JASDF dropped on Aldebaran.
Using this, you can completely
annihilate Aldebaran.
The only thing, Satomi-chan...
You can't just hit Aldebaran with this bomb.
According to our engineers' analysis,
it has to detonate within Aldebaran's body.
It can only destroy it using the increase
in power from being in a sealed state.
So you're saying that we're
going to have to blast a hole in
Aldebaran's ridiculously hard shell,
throw the EP bomb into the
wound before it regenerates,
and activate the bomb
after the wound has healed?
Bingo!
How the hell are we supposed
to blast a hole in its shell?
We don't have a weapon with
that kind of piercing power...
We do.
Just one thing
that has more power and reliability
than a tank cannon...
Our most powerful and final weapon...
Where?!
Me?!
Yep!
This plan will now be known as "Rapier's Last!"
We'll abandon this post,
set up a camp in the rear,
and face Aldebaran from there.
The rear?
There isn't a place to set up an encampment...
The final battle will be at
the Flames of Revolution.
You're going to find Aldebaran
with those lights?
Yep. This plan hinges on
how fast we can find the enemy.
We're just waiting for the batteries.
Right. We've asked the JASDF for help,
and they're transporting
them by land as we speak.
I see...
They're taking too long...
We're getting into our positions!
Right!
What's wrong, Enju? It's time.
Rentaro, do you remember the last time
we came here?
I wasn't thinking... This place is...
Rentaro, I don't understand...
Why does the Stolen Generation
do such terrible things to the Cursed Children?
We just want a place in this world...
Everyone says that
the civil officer system is just a
good way for the Gastrea and
us to kill each other...
A good way to get rid of the trash...
Enju,
is that what you think, too?
I believe that working for a
civil security agency is a job where I can risk
my life for others.
Which do you want to believe?
Rentaro...
Rentaro! Rentaro!
Rentaro!
Enju, you don't have to decide right now.
But... in order for you to have
the time to truly decide whether
this world is worth saving or not,
we need the world to keep existing.
Right...
I'm all right now!
Enju...
Commander,
everyone's in position.
All right!
It appears that you finally have all the cards,
King.
Yeah...
Queen,
jack,
ace,
and joker.
The adjuvant of five pairs
that I originally had in mind
has finally coalesced in the eleventh hour.
All the preparations have
been made, Aldebaran!
These are all of the batteries.
This will mean the end of Satomi Rentaro.
#13 The Ones Who Aspired to Be Gods
We will now eliminate the enemy!
Yes... This is war.
Target confirmed.
Satomi-kun, at this rate...
Rentaro!
Enju... This is goodbye.