Rakuzan
Seirin
We got them back, but...
We don't have any shooters.
Kagami, Koga and I can shoot threes.
But we've got nowhere near Hyuga's accuracy.
Rakuzan has scarier shooters than Akashi.
Mibuchi!
Is this...
Wild instincts?
A three without a fake?
No, this is...
Void!
He jumped during Leo's Void?
The rebound's mine!
Damn.
Thanks to Koga, I know how
to stop his three pointers.
And how to beat Void!
Let Me Warn You
Hyuga, you're coming in?
Yeah. I know the risks.
But this time I'll beat Mibuchi.
Sorry, Hyuga. I wasn't strong enough.
What are you talking about?
You're the reason I can fight.
I'll crush him for you, too.
Yeah. I'm counting on you, Hyuga.
We have ten more minutes.
There's no need to rush.
But don't try to maintain the point gap.
Keep attacking until the
end and crush Seirin!
Yeah!
Leo,
they're putting Hyuga back in.
He may have four fouls,
but don't let down your guard.
I know.
Eikichi, there's still
life in Kiyoshi's eyes.
Pull yourself together.
Yeah.
Kotaro, how long are you going
to stay out of the fight?
You need to score again.
Of course.
And I'm supposed to keep playing like this.
How economical of you to use
me until I've got nothing left.
But...
I'm not sure what it is.
But something seems off about Akashi.
The break is now over.
Let's go!
Teppei?
What's up, Riko?
Nothing. Never mind.
Kiyoshi!
Yeah.
Let's win!
Seirin, fight!
Yeah!
It's finally the fourth quarter.
This will determine the
Winter Cup championship.
Can Seirin make up a 20 point difference?
Who knows?
But they haven't given up.
When it comes to killing giants,
attitude matters more than strategy.
A three already?
He's already on him!
Coach, will you do me a favor?
What?
Can you stop my hands from shaking?
Wait, what?
But you sounded so in control.
That's irrelevant.
I've got four fouls.
The pressure's killing me.
Sheesh. Turn around!
Okay!
WHACK
Ow!
He's fast.
Yeah!
Nice, Captain!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Yes! Let's go, Rakuzan!
With four fouls, I thought
he'd barely be able to play.
But this is the best he's played all game.
Let's stop their attack!
Yeah!
Defense! Defense!
Their defense is good.
Hyuga really pulls his team together.
But how can he fight when he
can't afford a single foul?
You can do it, Junpei.
That's Heaven!
But Hyuga knows it's coming!
A fake? Then he's going for...
Earth! Hyuga-san's fifth foul!
Captain!
He's not jumping.
Did he predict this, too?
Mibuchi, your form is practically
identical before you
jump for each of your shots.
But your center of gravity
is slightly different.
Heaven, Earth, Void.
Your center of gravity shifts towards
the direction you're jumping.
As long as I know which way...
Go, Hyuga!
Hyuga!
This is the strongest he's been all game!
Teppei, are you...
That idiot!
I can't make the right call about
my future or injury anymore.
All that matters is this moment.
It's no use. He still can't get in position.
I thought that might be it.
No matter what we say,
you're always reckless.
Even if we subbed you out,
you'd force your way back on the court.
I won't stop you anymore.
Kiyoshi, how long have you been a center?
Don't let that musclebound moron beat you!
He's fast.
Go!
Kagami!
Yeah!
Now you've done it, Junpei-chan.
I'll crush you.
Right back at you.
And stop calling me that!
He's mad, but he hasn't lost his cool.
I don't need to worry about Leo.
But...
Damn it!
Calm down, Ei-chan.
What are you doing, Kotaro?
You've got a short fuse like me. Be careful.
Kiyoshi's strong.
If not for his injury,
he would've been as strong as us.
Don't underestimate him.
Shut up. I know.
Another shooting guard showdown!
Hyuga Junpei...
He's dangerous.
He can distinguish between my
three shots and react accordingly.
Then I'll use Void,
unstoppable even if you see it coming.
But maybe he's figured
something out about Void.
Should I avoid threes or pass the ball?
No, that's why I must fight!
A Rakuzan player can't back down.
I'll risk all my pride and shoot Void!
That's it!
I know why the defender can't
jump when he takes that shot.
It's because of how deep he
crouches before he jumps.
When Mibuchi shoots Void,
he crouches lower than normal.
And when he jumps,
he stops moving just as the defender's
knees are fully extended.
The defender expends all the power of
his crouch, leaving him unable to jump.
But Mibuchi still has strength
from crouching so low.
He uses the remaining power to shoot.
That's the secret behind Void.
My back hurts...
Has Riko always been that strong?
No, of course not.
She just hit me extra hard.
With not just her own,
but the entire team's hopes.
I don't care if you're an
Uncrowned King or Rakuzan!
No matter how strong you
are, I'll stop this shot!
Yes!
Hyuga!
They broke Rakuzan's defense!
With the return of their shooter,
their defense spread out,
making it easier to create
space on the inside.
No you don't!
How did he reach that?
But he's too late. Kiyoshi's in control.
A three?
It's a good shot.
There's no spin or shift.
Three shots in a row!
But Akashi isn't saying anything.
What is he thinking?
It's strange that he's emphasizing
one-on-ones with those three.
Why doesn't he attack himself?
Could it be?
Is he preventing even Akashi from attacking?
What's going on?
Kagami's becoming even more impressive.
Today's Seirin-Touou game was
interesting.
Honestly, that hadn't occurred to me.
I have experience with the Zone.
But what's truly surprising is how
Daiki deliberately entered it.
It's possible
with sufficient focus to push open the door
and awareness of your own
trigger to unlock it.
Sei-chan, there you are.
Yeah.
What is it?
We've got a game tomorrow.
We wanted to get a light workout.
It sucks that we haven't played since
the first day since we're the top seed.
I'm glad you're here. I need an opponent.
Sure. What do you want, a one-on-one?
No. Three-on-one.
Huh? Hey, Akashi.
I'm pretty sure you can't beat us.
Don't complain about the results.
Good. This should work in an actual game.
Seriously?
Akashi's a monster.
But we should consider this my trump card.
Using this would mean Rakuzan
is in a dangerous situation.
And one more thing.
Let me warn you.
My trigger for entering this condition is...
They're using a stealth
full-court man-to-man defense.
This can't be good.
Considering the range of
Kagami's defense in the Zone,
there's hardly any passes Kuroko can't steal.
Leo!
Crap!
Kuroko!
He stopped.
Even at full power,
Kiyoshi-san can't beat Nebuya-san.
He doesn't have to win.
He just needs enough to
compete to stay in the game.
He put pressure on his leg to spin again!
We're ten points behind!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Damn.
Mibuchi, the four of you will
go during our next attack.
What? Sei-chan, what do you—
Run.
They broke through in a second.
Crap! Go back!
He's not moving?
Think later! Focus on defense!
He has the same eyes...
Let me warn you.
My trigger for entering this condition
is the intent to achieve victory
not by using others,
but by taking it for myself.
In other words,
when I fight with my strength alone.
When I lose hope in and abandon you.
Are they going to score again?
I'll make the shot.
He can't stop my Meteor Jam
like he did in the first half.
Take this, Akashi!
Akashi-kun?
I will demonstrate my superiority
to everyone here.
Akashi's Zone.
Wait, Akashi!
No way!
Stop him!
He changes speed so quickly!
He's too fast!
You have defied me.
It's not enough for you to sit.
Kneel.
Damn! A fake!
Witness my sublime form and realize
your defeat is absolute.
He made it!
He took the ball from hoop to hoop!
Even without us...
No, he's stronger without us.
Such a monster shakes our very existence.
Does he really not need us?
They called for a time out.
But is there anything
they can do to stop him?
I'll do it.
Kagami! You mean you'll do it by yourself?
We're counting on you, then.
What? Don't you think you
agreed too quickly, Captain?
It's a valid verdict. Yeah, nice.
You, too, Izuki-senpai?
You heard them, Kiyoshi.
Okay.
Why is everyone agreeing?
Why are you objecting?
What?
It's how we've always played.
Against the Generation of Miracles,
we always face this situation.
Eventually we have to rely on our ace.
If we didn't have one, we'd be screwed.
But we have Kagami.
That's good enough.
Kagami-kun.
You know what this means, Kagami-kun.
This fight will determine
who wins and who loses.
Win, Kagami!
Yeah!
Aomine, I've been wondering.
What?
Earlier you said something.
He's even deeper in the Zone.
What did you mean?
It's a metaphor.
When you enter the Zone,
you open a massive door.
Inside it is water.
The more you focus, the deeper you sink.
If you sink far enough, you reach the bottom.
That's when you're fully
immersed in the Zone.
You can perform at your true best.
But there's an even bigger door.
A faceless figure stands
before it like a gatekeeper.
What if you open that door?
Who knows?
I've never opened it.
But I'm certain.
Beyond that door lies a
Zone greater than the Zone.
If Kagami has any chance of winning,
it's by opening the second door.
Preview
You've entrusted your ace
with the game, Seirin?
Then I must simply shatter your hope.
I can't lose.
The weak must kneel before the strong.
Why Don't You Give Up
I am absolute.