G-Gastrea!
What is this?!
The garrison... Why?
Tokyo Area 39th District
3rd Provisional Elementary School
So...
As of today, I will be your teacher.
#08 The Monument on the Border
My name is Satomi Rentaro.
My hobbies include observing
bugs, collecting plants...
I also like microbes.
And uh, I can do martial arts.
Any questions?
Me! Me! Me!
Give it your best, Satomi-sensei.
What are you freaking out about?
You're the one who agreed to
be their teacher, Satomi-kun.
I know that.
Yes, you right there.
Sensei! Is it true that you're
living with Enju-chan
with plans to get married?
It is.
Of course it's not!
You're just a freeloader!
All right, I'm handing things
over to your other teacher.
I'm T-Tendo Kisara.
Um, uh...
Sensei!
I heard this from Enju-chan,
but is it true that your boobs
are so big that you can't see your feet?
What?!
Are you and Rentaro-sensei dating?
Are you going to get married?
We aren't dating! Nor are we getting married!
Yes!
New
Gastrea
Law
And so...
The ruler of the Tokyo Area is...
Seitenshi-sama!
Correct.
I've never seen Seitenshi-sama.
Seitenshi-sama looks just like that.
New
Gastrea
Law
Seitenshi
Seitenshi-sama!
Good day, everyone.
Are you having fun studying?
The Monolith's... been destroyed?
The Gastrea found clinging to Monolith 32
last night was a Stage Four,
known as Aldebaran.
Because of the Varanium-corroding
fluid it injected,
in six days, Monolith 32 will lose
its magnetic field and be destroyed.
We've begun building another Monolith,
but it'll take nine days to complete.
According to our analysis,
with the amount of Gastrea that
will flood in during the three
days after its destruction,
all the citizens of the Tokyo Area will die,
or be turned into Gastrea.
To avoid panic, we're controlling
what information goes out.
But in a few days,
the Monolith will begin to whiten.
It's not something we'll
be able to keep hiding.
There are around 2,000 Gastrea
gathering outside of the Monolith.
Two thousand?!
Aldebaran is commanding them?
Wait a sec.
How did a Stage Four Aldebaran
attach itself to a Monolith?
I thought all Gastrea other than
Stage Fives were affected by the
Monolith's magnetic field.
We're not sure just yet.
And it looks like a Model Ant
has charged in to buy some time for Aldebaran.
It willingly sacrificed itself...
So, what is it you want me to do?
I'd like you to form an adjuvant.
Adju...
Adjuvant.
A squad system wherein a team of civil officers
works with the JASDF.
You're telling me to put
together a team and fight?!
Precisely.
Satomi-san, I'd like you to
be the team leader of
the civil officers and join in the battle.
Battle...
It'll take three days for the
new Monolith to be completed
after the original is destroyed.
We will intercept every last
one of the Gastrea that invade.
This will be a battle to decide
the fate of the Tokyo Area.
I can't drink anymore...
You drank too much.
In six days, the Tokyo Area will be...
It's hard to believe.
Huh?
Divine punishment on your heart!
Let me go! All the time...
That's right.
Tina's spending the night today.
How was that?
Made you feel dizzy, didn't it?
Well, Rentaro?
Go on, Rentaro-san.
Please try it.
It's delicious!
You're right, it is.
Really?
Then, next, I will make anchovy pizza.
What about other dishes?
Other? Then I can make carbonara
pizza or marinara pizza—
Those are all pizzas.
Pizza is all I can make.
Seriously?
Are you awake, Rentaro-san?
You can't sleep?
So you knew what Tenchu Girls was, too?
Enju-san showed me the whole first season.
I saw the soul of japanimation.
You'd take it that far?
I'm grateful to you, Rentaro-san.
This life is like a dream that I'd never
be able to experience if I were
still with Professor Rand.
Tina...
I always wanted an older
brother like you, Rentaro-san.
May I call you "Onii-san"?
S-Sure...
Tina!
No headstarts!
Onii-san, don't you have something
you want to talk about?
Yeah...
The Monolith is being destroyed?
You're not surprised?
I am surprised.
But that doesn't change what we must do.
Yeah... I'm going to tell Enju, as well,
but knowing her, she'll say
she wants to fight, too.
You're okay with that?
The Tina Sprout that was rank 98
has already died once, in that
battle with you, Onii-san.
The life I have now is a new one.
Do with it whatever you wish.
I thought we'd finally
see some peaceful days...
A year ago, Kisara-san and I set up the
Tendo Civil Security Agency for revenge.
At the time, I had nothing but
my hatred toward the Gastrea.
When I first met Enju,
she had been betrayed by
humans so many times
that her eyes were even colder
and more vacant than ours.
And yet, only a year later...
First, Enju and I changed,
and that spread to Kisara-san.
President Tendo seems nice to begin with.
Well, yeah...
Anyway, you should go to bed.
Then let me use your arm
as a pillow, Onii-san.
Wha?
Good morning, Satomi-kun! I'm coming in.
Good morning, Kisara.
Good morning...
Except, can't you say you're
coming in before you come in?
Shut up. I've come to take Tina-chan back.
Huh? Where's Tina-chan?
Um...
Good morning.
Wasn't last night fun, Onii-san?
It was a little scary at times,
but I was happy that you
taught me new things.
Tina...
I'm calling the police...
Hold on a second!
I was just talking to the
night version of Tina.
What do you mean,
"night version," you pervert?!
Tina beat me to it!
What's wrong?
The Tokyo Area leader of the movement
to expel the Cursed Children
was attacked and killed late last night.
According to eyewitnesses, the suspect
was a child from the outer district...
This is bound to have an adverse affect on
the public opinion of the Cursed Children.
There is surely no chance of the
New Gastrea Law passing now.
Onii-san, were you on the
phone with Matsuzaki-san?
Well, it's been pretty dangerous
since that incident.
I'm fine.
You're not tired today?
I've been gradually shifting
to a more diurnal lifestyle.
Where are we headed?
To recruit people.
This time, it won't be just a pair,
but we'll be fighting the
army of Gastrea as a team.
If I don't gather people for the team,
we won't even be able to
participate in the battle.
But why did you bring me with you?
I don't really have any other
opportunities to show you
around the Tokyo Area.
Where do you want to go?
A date with Onii-san...
What's wrong?
Onii-san!
Sorry...
That's about all I can get you.
No...
This is fine.
I will treasure it for the rest of my life.
I hear a song.
Y-You...
I am a
Cursed Child
from the
Outer District
What happened to your eyes?
I thought Cursed Children
were immune to diseases...
I poured lead into them.
My mother, who abandoned me,
hated my red eyes.
Are you a Cursed Child, too?
How did you know?
You're so pretty...
I have to rely on others to survive,
so I don't know how to
do anything but smile.
Thank you...
Man, you're terrible.
I'm not. You are.
You shouldn't come around here for a while.
But I have a little sister...
All this? But why?
Don't worry about it! Just promise me!
Okay...
Don't forgive the Gastrea!
Throw out the Cursed Children!
Don't let the Gastrea factor live!!
Don't forgive the Gastrea!
Throw out the Cursed Children!
New Gastrea Law Rejected
Katagiri Civil Security Agency
Broken
Is this really the place?
Hey, anyone home?
Hey! It's the pervert, Satomi Rentaro!
It's Katagiri's little sister.
It's Yuzuki! You damn fucking pervert!
It's been a while.
I haven't seen you since the Kagetane fiasco,
so about three months?
I hear you've made it big.
What do you want? Did you come to brag?
I wanted to talk to your brother about a job!
We don't want any jobs from a pervert!
Looks like business is good,
older brother Katagiri.
No need for sarcasm, boy.
What do you want?
Well...
Want me to guess?
That damn fucking scenario with the Monolith
getting destroyed is hanging over you,
so you have to go around trying
to recruit people for an adjuvant,
but you've been turned down
everywhere else, so you came here.
How's that?
Right on the money.
Well, a young upstart like yourself is hated
by all the civil officers in the Area.
Shut up.
So... when's it going to be destroyed,
and how many enemies are there?
It hasn't been on the news yet,
but it'll be destroyed four days from now.
The enemy numbers 2,000.
Four days from now?
Two thousand?!
The exit's back there.
Yuzuki, our guests are leaving now.
If we don't do anything,
the Tokyo Area is finished!
You'll both die, as well!
Aldebaran is a terrible monster.
The story about that thing turning three cities
into wastelands is famous, you know.
So what's the government going to give me
in return for facing that thing?
A promotion in rank, and
somewhat of a reward, probably.
That's damn fucking bullshit!
You want us to risk our lives for that?
You can probably negotiate
a little on the reward...
You don't get it, boy. It's not about money.
Then how about fighting for me?
F-For you?
The pervert... The pervert asks us to fight for him?
Onii-san, they're...
That's great!
Huh?
Huh...
You've changed in the short time
since I've seen you.
I forgot to mention one thing.
I won't work for anyone weaker than me.
Yeah, I know.
Rank 1,850, Model Spider, Katagiri Yuzuki!
Also rank 1,850, Katagiri Tamaki.
Sorry to drag you into this, Tina.
Onii-san, if we're going
to do this, let's win.
Formation Delta.
What are those weird things
floating around you?
I am a Model Owl, Tina Sprout.
My rank is currently being revoked,
so I don't have one.
Rank 300, Satomi Rentaro!
What do you mean, "300"?
You're just a pervert!
Come on, let's dance, boy!
Homura
Kasen!
A Varanium chainsaw?
You realized that too late, boy.
A spider's thread?
I see... His sunglasses allow him to see that...
You can't run!
Die, you bastard!
Inzen: Shoka Hanameishi!
You bastard!
If that had been anyone
but me, they'd be dead!
You're still alive?
You got a problem with that?!
Looks like the girls are almost
done with their fight, too.
Looks like the winner's been decided...
Take a look at this.
Just give up!
You have no chance of winning!
Don't blame me if you get hurt!
What the hell?
Looks like the winner's been decided...
Please stand, Yuzuki-san.
You're strong.
I'd just be in your way if I were
part of the adjuvant, wouldn't I?
That's not true.
I think you can be proud that you were able
to give me that much trouble
when I formerly ranked at 98.
N-Ninety-eight?!
Seriously?
Katagiri Yuzuki-san,
please join Onii-san's adjuvant.
I love you, Tina-yan!
You're so strong and cool!
Marry me!
Did we pass?
Do you really have to ask?
#09 The Protectors of the Barrier
The freedom to see a bigger world
where we don't have to be
frightened by the Gastrea...
It's begun, Satomi-kun.
A battle without glory or enjoyment
is rather boring, whether you win or lose.