Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin
High's shadow and light.
I sensed it the first time we met.
After playing against him,
that feeling crystallized.
Now it is total certainty.
He is like us, the Generation of Miracles.
He's a member of the Generation of
Miracles that followed a different path.
That's why I feel it so strongly.
It's instinct.
I don't want to lose to him!
Change gears.
We're on offense.
Let's get them back.
I know.
That's right. We'll get them back.
We won't lose!
Don't Underestimate Me!!
What?
Nice, Kagami!
Fast break!
Wasn't Kise-chin's jump
way lower than normal?
Damn it.
He made the shot!
Kagami's crushing Kise in the ace battle!
It's not over yet. I can still fight!
Failing now would be too lame!
I don't want to lose to him!
Player substitution, black!
Kise, you're out.
What? Why me?
If you sub me out now—
Kise.
Listen to the coach.
A sub?
Could it be?
Kise-kun...
Kise...
I knew it.
It's your leg, isn't it?
It's been bothering you since then.
You knew?
You have to let me play, though!
I can play through the pain!
I don't want to lose like—
Considering where we are,
you've already lost.
What?
I know you overworked yourself
because you were desperate to win.
It was wrong of Haizaki to
stomp on your injured foot.
But that's not an excuse.
It's all part of the game.
The game doesn't care.
Damn it.
You shut him down hard again.
Not really.
If he were so badly injured
he couldn't go on again,
the coach never would've put him in.
He'll be back.
But we can't roll over
just because he's gone.
Show them what you're made of.
Yeah!
This is our chance.
Yeah.
We'll focus our attacks around Kagami.
Okay.
Kagami-kun...
I know.
I feel bad for him.
That's why I'll play as hard as I can.
Okay.
They're double-teaming him!
You're not going anywhere.
He's Nakamura, a top eight
player in middle school!
He's famous for his defense!
Kagami, pass!
Okay.
All right! Go!
This is the Phantom Shot!
Damn it! It's no use!
How does this shot even work?
He made it!
That's two baskets in a row!
Damn it!
Sorry! If I'd been guarding
him more closely...
You should be double-teaming Kagami!
What are you, stupid?
Besides, if you stick closer to him,
you'll only be more susceptible
to his mis-whatever...
I figured out why that shot disappears.
Really, Kasamatsu?
Yeah, but I don't have time to explain.
Keep our current formation.
They'll have to bench Kuroko,
but I won't let them do it for free.
I'll crush one of their weapons.
Rebound!
Yeah!
Crap.
Nice rebound!
He's good.
Kobori, outside!
His form is still terrible!
He made it!
Kaijo's keeping up even without Kise!
Yes!
Coach, isn't it time?
You're right.
To sub out Kuroko?
Yes.
But Kaijo's not handling Kuroko very well.
Couldn't he stay in?
Kuroko-kun's just doing
a good job avoiding them.
What?
His Misdirection isn't effective
for as long against Kaijo
since we've played them before.
Once that runs out,
he'll only have his Overflow left.
I see.
So we'll sub him out the
next time the ball's dead.
Mitobe-kun, get ready.
He's keeping his distance.
Even if he's afraid of letting me
through, he's still faster than me.
What's going on?
Izuki's outside shooting
percentage isn't very good.
Is he making him take the shot on purpose?
Then I won't shoot.
With two guys on Kagami,
there's a more certain route we can take.
Go, Kuroko!
Kasamatsu?
Is this why he kept his distance from Izuki?
A step back?
That's it.
I thought the ball's trajectory was
high, but it's just the opposite.
The unique low form of the shot is the
secret behind his disappearing shot.
In the case of a normal shot,
the defender looks upwards.
But because he thrusts the ball out from
his chest, the ball's position is low.
The defender looks down.
The rapidly rising ball
quickly flies out of sight.
At the same time, he misdirects the
defender's attention towards Kagami,
making him lose sight of the
ball as though it disappeared.
But stepping back instead of jumping
broadens your field of view.
If you have the speed to block it...
You're in plain sight.
He stopped it!
First it was Kise, now it's Kasamatsu!
Kasamatsu!
Senpai...
You're kidding, right?
That shot beat Murasakibara...
And unlike Kise, he knows how it works.
They've completely overcome the Phantom Shot.
Player substitution, white!
Kuroko.
Kuroko...
We were late subbing him out.
Now they'll think we subbed out
Kuroko-kun because they beat him.
It could affect our morale.
I'm sorry.
My shot was blocked just
before I was subbed out.
I'm sorry I made us lose control of the game.
Huh?
His reaction is surprisingly normal.
You're not shocked?
Of course I am.
But it's okay.
Seirin hasn't lost the game yet.
Besides...
Kuroko.
Leave it to me.
We have an ace we can count on.
What?
The double-team was trying to stop his
drive, but he broke right through them?
K-Kagami?
Keep giving me the ball.
What?
I feel like I can't lose right now.
He made it!
Amazing! He tore right
through the double-team!
Damn it.
He's extraordinary.
If we're not careful, he could
inflict even more damage than Kise.
Crap!
It's a three! Take the shot!
What?
That's way too high!
Go!
What? A pass?
The second quarter is over!
Kaijo
Seirin
We're tied!
We're back to square one!
How did you manage that pass then?
Why?!
We're on break. Let's head back.
Seirin High
Locker Room
Guys, listen up. Let's talk
about the second half.
I have nothing to say!
What?
Nothing!
But, Coach, you told us to listen.
It means things are going well.
We'll keep playing like this.
Kise-kun's foot is injured,
but he'll definitely come back
before the end of the game.
We'll establish as much of a
lead as we can before then.
Keep attacking!
Yeah!
Kagami-kun...
Hey.
Aomine's shoes are surprisingly comfortable.
Let's go all-out in the second half.
Okay.
Anyway, are you okay?
They stopped your Phantom Shot.
Do you have a plan?
I don't know.
Hey! Don't you think you say that too much?
But I don't have time to mope.
I have to do something.
Kaijo High
Locker Room
Please, Coach!
Put me in!
I'm the only one who can stop Kagami!
Am I wrong?
No. The last two minutes.
Until then, I can't put you in.
But at this rate...
Kise!
Moriyama-senpai, say something!
Get...
"Get on the court."
I wish I could say it.
We're that powerless to
stop Kagami right now.
Kise...
Senpai...
I understand your point.
Kaijo
Seirin
The third quarter will now begin!
I knew it.
I understand your point.
But you still can't play.
What? Why can't I—
Shut up!
That's an order, moron!
Don't talk back to me, first-year!
He's really spirited.
Come to think of it, he was
like this when I joined Kaijo.
I'm Nagaoka Shohei.
I'm from Iwai Middle School.
I'd like to play the shooting guard position.
Okay, next.
Me? Since I'm last, I'd better make it good.
I'm first-year Kise Ryota.
I play basketball for fun,
and I'm great at karaoke.
Wait, I mean the other way around.
I'm from Teiko, and I'll play any position.
I'll have to miss a lot
of practice since I model,
but I look forward to being on the team.
Isn't he one of the Generation of Miracles?
He's a superficial idiot...
Shut up.
I asked for your name, school, and position.
Just give me the answers I
asked for, you flashy moron!
Ow!
This is no way to treat the
promising rookie you scouted!
I don't care!
First-years shouldn't talk
back to their seniors!
I don't like that kind of rigid thinking.
You think being a few years older
makes you more important than me?
Besides, I'm probably better at basketball.
I am more important.
What?
Regardless of your skill, this is
the Kaijo High basketball team.
It's not because I'm older.
The second- and third-years have all worked
hard for this team for longer than you.
I'm telling you to respect that.
I don't care if you're one of
the Generation of Miracles.
Now you're Kise Ryota, Kaijo first-year.
And I'm the captain, Kasamatsu Yukio.
You got a problem with that?
I knew it wasn't swagger,
but I still didn't like it.
But I liked being "Kise of Kaijo."
Kaijo
Seirin
Yes!
Kaijo
Seirin
We just keep scoring!
Damn it!
Please! Hang in there
until I can get back in!
Calm down, Kise.
You need to recover before
the last two minutes.
I still don't know when to block his shot!
Kaijo's hanging on, but Seirin's
unstoppable right now.
Let's get them back!
Hyuga! A three?
No, you don't!
Nice shot, Mitobe!
Nice teamwork!
Even without Taiga, there isn't a single
player on Seirin they can leave unguarded.
What will Kaijo do?
Let's keep going.
Kasamatsu?
But what about Kagami?
I hate to admit it, but not
even double-teaming him works.
We expected this the moment
we learned about Kise's foot.
But we weren't expecting
him to grow so quickly.
There's no good way for us to
handle all five Seirin players.
But we can still score.
Kaijo
Seirin
We'll do everything we can,
but we can't help it if they score.
But we will get them back!
Stick to them like your life depends on it!
Yeah!
I sound pathetic. I hate it.
We're desperately hanging on,
and Kise's our last hope.
But I'll happily do it if it means we'll win!
He's fast!
That's his full-speed drive!
It's not over yet! Go!
Eagle Spear!
He did it!
Senpai!
Kasamatsu!
What?
Rebound!
He made it!
He forced the ball in!
Kaijo's incredibly determined!
Guys...
We're not finished yet!
Don't underestimate Kaijo!
Preview
Kise, you should rest.
I know.
I know, but I...
You idiot, I already know
what you want to say.
Save your strength so we can win.
In Order to Win
Senpai...
I will!