Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
You're going to move for me.
Shintaro, you are strong.
But you will lose.
Not even you can stand against me.
I never allow those who oppose me
to look down at me.
I Will Give Them to You
They haven't given up?
No. He's trying to do something.
If they're trying to close the gap
now, they'll need Midorima's threes.
But as long as Akashi's
on him, it's impossible.
They only have ten seconds before
they receive a violation.
Do they not know how to attack?
I'm sure that's partly true,
but what they're about to attempt
is probably pretty risky.
What do you mean?
Shutoku
Rakuzan
Considering the remaining time and point
gap, a single mistake could be fatal.
Hesitation and uncertainty lead to mistakes.
In other words, they'll make
their move when they're ready.
Hey, Midorima Shintaro-kun.
Hey. I'm Takao Kazunari.
You're joining the basketball team, right?
Me, too. Nice to meet you.
How do you know my name?
Everyone who plays basketball
knows your name.
Huh? What's that?
Oha Asa fortune's lucky item for the day.
It's tape.
Are you serious?
What's so funny?
You don't think it's hilarious
that their lucky item is tape?
And I forgot to say something,
but what's with the way you talk?
It's freaking hilarious!
He seems frivolous.
My first impression of Takao wasn't good.
Okay, next! Shuttle run!
Yes, sir!
Run, run, run!
You're falling behind!
Touch the floor!
Shutoku's practices were as grueling
as Teiko's, if not more so.
Club Resignation Form
Boys who were successful in middle school
quit every day, one after another.
Among the first years, not a single
student stayed late to practice.
What's so funny?
It never ceases to amaze me.
Seriously, your shots are way too high.
Shut up. Don't get in my way.
Sorry, sorry.
I don't mean to put you down.
Anyway, what do you think you're doing?
Huh?
Recently you've always been
around when I stay late.
You seem to compete with
me during practice, too.
Do you bear some kind
of animosity against me?
Sort of.
I guess you don't remember me.
I played against you once
in middle school and lost.
I kept practicing after I
quit out of frustration.
When I finally got into high school,
the guy I swore to defeat became my teammate.
It's laughable.
But there's no point in being hostile now.
If anything, I just wanted
you to acknowledge me.
Maybe that's why it seemed
like I was competing with you.
Why didn't you say anything?
What?
Why are you laughing?
Are you serious? You want me to tell you?
"After you destroyed me, I worked
really hard! Please acknowledge me!"
Talk about lame!
I'm sure I don't have to tell you not
to, but don't acknowledge me yet.
I'll practice harder than you.
I'm just doing what I decided to do.
Eventually I'll send you a pass
that will impress even you!
Don't you forget, Shin-chan!
Don't call me that.
It's too familiar, Takao.
This is a gamble.
I must trust my teammates
more than I trust myself.
It's not enough for me to do
everything I possibly can.
But I am certain.
There isn't a man on this team who hasn't
done everything humanly possible!
He's entering his shooting motion.
Without the ball?
These guys...
What is he doing?
Could it be?
He caught the ball mid-air
and shot a three-pointer?
Is that even possible?
Yeah!
From that height, even if
Akashi could see the future,
he couldn't intercept the shot.
But that was more than just difficult.
Midorima's amazing for making
the shot, but that's not all.
Passing the ball right into Midorima's
hands takes unbelievable accuracy.
I can't imagine the old Midorimacchi
doing anything like this.
What?
Midorimacchi only takes shots
he's absolutely confident in.
But no matter how accurate the pass was,
what he just did was less
accurate than a standard shot.
He may be trying to beat Akashi,
but he'd never take a shot that might
miss unless he really trusted his teammates.
Rebound!
This old dude's still going for rebounds!
He's got a lot of stamina!
Fast break!
He made it!
That's three in a row!
Shutoku
Rakuzan
Shutoku's closing the gap!
Their style is different,
but they're like you.
They're like the light and shadow of Shutoku.
You're right.
But catching a pass mid-air
and making a three...
That's an incredible move.
But why are they holding back?
I think everything may be going
according to Midorima-kun's plan.
On Teiko, the Generation of Miracles
were forbidden from exercising
their full strength.
It was because their bodies hadn't caught
up to the magnitude of their strength.
Though they all knew what
they were capable of,
no one has ever fought at full strength.
In other words, this is Midorima's
first time experiencing the Emperor Eye.
He knew he couldn't win without gambling.
Yes. Though the move is powerful
and effective against Akashi-kun,
it's likely very risky, as well.
But the risk was worth it.
Look. Akashi's unconcerned
expression has changed.
Shutoku's not dead yet.
The game is just getting started.
This is more than I expected, Shintaro.
I couldn't ask for more.
This is pointless.
Move!
My orders are absolute.
Midorima!
More!
Don't give up!
There is no shame in falling!
The only shame is in not getting up!
Akashi!
Impossible! How did he get
there from the ground?
He changed plans in a second!
His judgment is terrifyingly fast!
What?
Otsubo!
Otsubo-san, you're the best!
You're not going anywhere!
You're kidding, right?
He could've shot a normal three just now.
He's so confident.
Go!
Four in a row!
Shutoku
Rakuzan
They're catching up to Rakuzan!
More!
Keep going!
They're making their move!
They're going for a full-court press!
And Midorima and Takao are
double-teaming Akashi.
This pressure...
What are you doing?
That's your own basket.
Wh-What did he...
An own goal?
He was aiming for that.
What is he thinking?
Akashicchi...
Akashi...
When did I say you could let your guard down?
The game isn't over yet.
Did you relax after we
established a large lead?
I can tell because you were reeling after
they scored just a few baskets in a row.
If the game were closer, you wouldn't
have disgraced yourselves in this way.
In that case, we should lose the gap.
Cool your heads.
But if we lose, you can
blame me all you want.
We will have lost because
of that shot I took.
I will accept full responsibility
and quit the team.
To pay for my crime,
I will gouge out my
eyes and give them to you.
I will gouge out my eyes
and give them to you.
What are you talking about, Akashi?
You don't need to do that!
It's only if we lose.
If we win, there's no problem.
I'm not worried because I am certain.
We cannot lose with you on the team.
Hey, this is just a high school team!
There's no way he'd really
gouge his eyes out!
But why did the other guys react like that?
It's hard to believe,
but Akashi might really do it.
He's dangerous enough.
Either way, it was an effective
way to inspire his team.
The expressions of the
Rakuzan players changed.
Shutoku
Rakuzan
Yeah!
Damn it!
Even though the gap has closed,
they're strong enough to hold them back.
Rakuzan's attacks are relentless.
Akashi's speech got them back on their feet.
But Shutoku still has a chance.
He may be able to predict the future,
but he still can't stop Midorima's shots.
Unfortunately,
this game is already over.
I have something to tell you.
You will not even be able
to touch the ball again.
What?
That's impossible, Akashi.
Not even your Emperor Eye can stop our shots.
Height is certainly an important
factor in basketball.
At first glance, it seems
as though I can't stop you.
But let me tell you something.
I am absolute.
I see everything that will happen.
Changing it is easy.
It's quiet.
Shutoku's more cautious
than they've ever been.
Of course they are.
They can't afford to make mistakes now.
Akashi just stopped the momentum they
gained from their consecutive threes.
If they fail, they won't
have time to make up for it.
This moment will decide Shutoku's fate.
It's coming.
They're double-teaming Takao this time!
What?
Takao!
Such incredible pressure!
It's impossible for him to pass
accurately into Midorima's hands now!
We knew you'd do this.
You think I'd be Shin-chan's partner
if I lost my cool over this?
Don't underestimate me!
He got past them!
And Midorimacchi's entering the motions!
He started moving just before Takao did.
He believed Takao would make it past them!
Go!
I told you.
I am absolute.
Your shot has a weakness.
Because you're left-handed,
he has to pass from your left side.
And your shooting motion
is the same every time.
In other words, I can easily predict
the timing and path of the pass
even without my Emperor Eye.
I used my eyes for only a moment
so I could get a head start on
him at the moment of no return.
I intentionally let him slip past
the double-team on this side, too,
to close the distance between us.
But I used my Hawk Eye to
confirm Akashi's position.
He shouldn't have been able to
reach it even if he got a head start.
Could it be?
Did he intentionally slow himself
down during the first half?
Just barely enough so
Shin-chan wouldn't notice?
I hadn't realized you already
made your opening move.
You exceeded my expectations,
but not how I had imagined.
Shogi and basketball are the same.
Didn't I always tell you?
An opening move only works
when you plan ahead without
your opponent's knowledge.
He doesn't just rely on his
physical or mental capabilities.
He also has frighteningly
well-design strategies.
This is the captain of the Generation
or Miracles, Akashi Seijuro!
Damn! Damn!
Does this mean Akashi was in control
of everything that happened?
Don't give up!
You can still do it!
Defense! Defense!
Sorry, but I don't like loud noises.
Could you be quiet?
Not yet! It's not over yet!
You're not taking that shot!
Wait, Takao!
A fake!
He made a three while drawing a foul...
Could it be?
You're kidding, right?
I'm actually greedier than I look.
A three-pointer and the basket counts.
Seriously? That's a four point play.
All right!
Huh?
No way. Yours always hurt.
You should've started with that, Leo-nee.
I told you, I can't do it anytime.
Shutoku
Rakuzan
It's over, Shintaro.
Akashi!
I must express my respect for all
of you, Shintaro and Shutoku High.
Not a single one of you lost the
will to fight until the end.
But you fell short.
Sleep now, veteran kings.
Kaijo
Seirin
Preview
This is Rakuzan's true strength...
Hey, can I leave now?
But they haven't played the finals yet.
Can I leave once they do?
There's still another semifinal game.
I Can't Help But Laugh
Atsushi?!