The final tip-off!
I want to win with Kuroko and the guys!
Interesting.
The Zone, huh?
Isn't It the Best?
What? Again?
Kagami-kun...
Amazing.
His offensive power is incredible
when he's in the Zone,
but...
Isn't this bad?
The Zone consumes a lot of stamina, right?
Will he last until the end of the game?
Of course not.
Suppose you fill a bathtub with hot water.
What? A tub?
Entering the Zone is like pulling the plug.
The water disappears before your eyes.
Simple enough, but does he think I'm stupid?
No, maybe he likes you.
If they don't do something,
he'll be running on empty before halftime.
We can't even touch him on defense!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Amazing.
He's keeping Rakuzan at zero points.
No one even comes close to Kagami.
Mitobe-kun, get ready to sub in.
Coach?
I'd rather keep going than try to stop him.
But Kagami-kun needs to focus on offense
so he doesn't run out of stamina.
Kuroko-kun, you're out.
What?
You're subbing Kuroko for Mitobe?
I see.
Overall, Mitobe's stronger
on defense than Kuroko.
I was ready to give everything I had...
Don't let it get you down.
They're subbing him out already?
I wanted to see him play more!
The fans want to see you, too.
You'll be out there in no time.
Yeah.
Kagami, focus on offense.
We'll handle things back
here while you charge ahead!
Got it!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Coach, shouldn't we call a time out?
There's no need.
Damn. Is Kagami stronger than
Midorima when he's in the Zone?
We can't touch him.
We'll keep offense as is.
On defense, Kotaro, we'll switch marks.
Akashi...
You're getting carried away,
Kagami Taiga.
I knew it.
Kagami-kun...
It's a clash of the aces.
The results will affect the flow of the game.
What should we do?
Do we stick with Kagami
or attack with just us?
The latter option is lower risk, but...
Give me the ball!
If I can crush Akashi
now, we'll take control!
Kagami...
It still sends shivers down my spine.
But it's now or never.
The Zone versus Emperor Eye!
Kagami's speed beat Emperor Eye?!
Kagami!
I can do it!
I'll finish this now!
Go, Meteor Jam!
Beat Emperor Eye?
Don't underestimate me.
I let you pass me.
Unbelievable.
Kagami-kun took a larger step
forward to avoid Akashi-kun.
His drive went wide, taking him
slightly farther from the hoop.
And he can't use his Meteor Jam
when the defense is too close.
No. 5 and No. 8 were slow to help.
It was the perfect chance.
But even that was a trap.
I thought they'd use a flashy
trick to stop Kagami's Zone.
But stopping him with their
first move was superhuman.
It just goes to show...
Akashi isn't unbeatable
because he has Emperor Eye.
He's unbeatable because of how he uses it.
Let's stop their shot!
That was my mistake!
I know I had other options!
Idiot. He's losing focus.
Crap, a screen!
Switch!
Aka-chin's rushing to end a game for once.
If they lose this, he'll leave the Zone.
But I hope that's all.
If full power doesn't work against him,
it could throw him off completely.
But Kagami-kun beat Kise-kun's
Emperor Eye once before.
Now that he's in the Zone, maybe...
Don't make me so angry.
How dare you compare a fake to the original.
Your head is too high.
Akashi's inside!
Eagle Spear!
Not even this timing worked!
Crap!
No, you don't!
If they don't stop him now, they're screwed.
The points they'll lose
from the momentum lost
in the ace showdown are bad enough.
It wasn't Kagami's mistake alone.
It will be engraved into all their heads.
"No matter what we do,
Akashi is unbeatable."
Damn!
What?
Mitobe!
Nice, Mitobe!
Yeah, Rin-nii!
He got me!
No worries, Leo!
I was naive.
It wasn't as though no one was on him.
But more importantly...
Mitobe-kun's fired up, too!
Everyone on our team is today!
Let's go! Counterattack!
We need to go hard on offense...
But how?
Can I beat Akashi?
Mitobe-senpai...
He says, "Don't worry about it!"
Even I understood that!
Yeah!
Is he out of the Zone?
Yeah, he's back to normal.
He still has some strength.
It was probably the best
possible way to leave the Zone.
You've got some good teammates, Taiga...
Offense! Let's get them back!
Yeah!
We haven't lost momentum completely.
Even without Kagami-kun's Zone,
we stand a fighting chance.
So...
There he is!
Seirin's super sixth man!
Go!
Whoops.
Why are you doing that now?
Sorry.
It's okay.
Huh?
He avoided Kuroko?
Go, No. 11!
The fans see him, too...
That can't be right.
Normally nobody notices him.
Great. Akashi got you,
but you haven't given up.
What? Of course not!
What are you talking about?
I mean, come on...
It's no fun playing guys who
have lost their will to fight.
You passed us twice.
I'll pass you five times.
Five? Wouldn't people normally double it?
How did he get that number?
Well, whatever.
I'll pass you so many times,
you can't keep up!
Kagami!
There are others who feel
"wild" like Taiga!
This guy...
There it is! No. 11's miracle pass!
You touched the ball?
Yeah.
But that's not the problem, Junpei-chan.
Junpei-chan?
No, you don't!
Here we go!
Four!
It looks like it disappeared!
He made the shot! Hayama's Lightning Dribble!
Let's go, Kuroko! Get on offense!
We'll need to work together
to score against Rakuzan!
Pass the ball around!
Something's not right.
Kuroko hasn't been able
to shake the defenders.
Is Kuroko's lack of presence weakening?
Coach, um...
The ball's free! Get it!
They intercepted Tetsu-kun's pass?
No...
So this is why I felt uneasy
about teaching Tetsu to shoot.
Damn it. How did you...
I didn't do anything.
I just blocked what I saw.
What he saw?
So when he caught up to my three...
Could it be?
I can't bear to watch this folly.
How could you abandon your greatest strength?
Once you reached your current
style in middle school,
I helped you work on pass variations,
but wouldn't let you shoot or dribble.
Do you know why?
Because I knew it would make
you lose your lack of presence.
The Vanishing Drive, the Phantom Shot.
How could a player who uses such
flashy moves not stand out?
The last nail in the coffin was your
buzzer beater in the semifinals.
When you learned to shine dimly,
you ceased being a shadow.
No longer the Phantom Sixth Man,
you're worth less than the average player.
And you didn't notice until now.
You disappoint me, Tetsuya.
Damn it.
They're hardly better than normal feints.
Izuki!
I was too gentle.
Kuroko-kun.
They have to sub him out.
There's no point in keeping
a useless trump card around.
He might not come back.
Kuroko-kun!
Not over there. Come here.
Don't give up.
You'll be back out there soon.
What?
What? They're sending him out again?
Sorry, Kuroko-kun,
for sending you back like this.
No, I'm sorry.
Here I go.
What are they thinking?
Just over three minutes
left in the first quarter.
We'll give you everything we can.
So go out there and let them destroy you.
Fight once more
so we can win.
The Vanishing Drive!
He passed him?!
No!
He sees him!
Kuroko can't come back if we
just take him off the court.
We need him to keep playing
so we can find a way to revive him together.
Kuroko...
They can see that, too!
No, you don't!
Rakuzan
Seirin
Rakuzan made a comeback!
I don't know what you're thinking.
But it's naive to think
you can beat us with him.
Rebound!
Damn!
Yeah!
Yeah! Vice Claw!
Kiyoshi!
What you just said...
We're not naive. You're underestimating us.
Rakuzan
Seirin
Good job tying them after the first quarter.
But you're out again, Kuroko-kun.
We couldn't come up with a
solution in three minutes,
but we got some information.
You're out during the second quarter
so we can come up with a plan.
Okay.
Cheer up, Kuroko.
We'll need your passes again to win.
We can't go down without a fight.
Kagami-kun...
We scraped through the first quarter
even while you were useless.
Don't worry about us.
I know, but couldn't you
sugarcoat it instead?
You're right, though.
I'll return to the court.
To win.
Yeah!
We're counting on you, Kuroko!
We stand a chance in the second quarter.
They may be Rakuzan,
but they're not all monsters.
Especially No. 5...
Even Mitobe can handle Mayuzumi easily.
We know Seirin's strength.
We'll stick to the plan
in the second quarter.
Got it, Akashi?
Yes, sir.
All that's left is to destroy them.
Kotaro, Eikichi, Leo.
You'll score.
I'll pass you the ball.
We couldn't use it against
Shutoku's Hawk Eye user.
But there's something we can
use against the limited range
of the Eagle Eye.
Satsuki, what's Rakuzan's No. 5 like?
Huh? Give me a second.
Let's see...
Mayuzumi Chihiro. Third-year. Power Forward.
Technique
Power
Speed
Mayuzumi Chihiro
Third-Year DF Height 182 cm Weight 69 kg
Mental Strength                          Offense                                Defense
Stamina
Flexibility
His speed, power, and
technique are all rank C.
He has no particular strengths or weaknesses.
He became a regular in his third year,
shortly after Akashi joined the team.
Before then, he wasn't
even on the first string.
Seriously? Sounds just like someone I know.
What?
Akashi failed his pass?
I got it!
What?!
Was that...
Misdirection?!
You're joking...
Is he just like Kuroko?
He's a little different.
He is like Tetsuya, but his
fundamentals are all stronger.
Tetsuya is the old model.
Mayuzumi Chihiro is the
new Phantom Sixth Man.
Preview
It's finally your time
to shine, Mayuzumi-san!
He was playing the whole time.
Just keep the good passes headed my way.
Ei-chan, no fair!
I'll make a ton of shots, too!
Miracles Don't Happen
Shut up, boys!