Was that...
Misdirection?!
He is like Tetsuya, but his
fundamentals are all stronger.
Tetsuya is the old model.
Mayuzumi Chihiro is the new
Phantom Sixth Man.
Miracles Don't Happen
Rakuzan
High School
You're Mayuzumi-san, right?
Hello.
You're acting awfully familiar.
Don't you mean "nice to meet you"?
We were teammates until just the other day.
How unusual.
Most people have a hard time remembering me.
That's probably because I
know someone just like you.
By the way, what are you reading?
A light novel.
A light novel?
Yeah. You don't know what they are?
Are they interesting?
They're easier to read compared to normal novels.
Some people don't like them,
but if you do, they're interesting.
You think it's stupid
because of its cover, don't you?
No. I just thought you're very much like
the Phantom Sixth Man.
Teiko's...
So it's not just a rumor?
No. That's what I wanted to discuss.
Mayuzumi Chihiro.
I want
you to become the new Phantom Sixth Man.
No.
I love myself.
Specializing in passing sounds boring.
I'm not that desperate to play.
There's no point in playing
if I don't feel good about it.
Who is this guy?
He suddenly changed.
Interesting. I like you even more now.
You could become a greater
phantom player than Tetsuya.
Yeah!
He made it!
Rakuzan's on a roll!
I wasn't expecting a player like him.
The new Phantom Sixth Man, huh?
Nice pass!
I'm not doing it for you.
I feel good when my passes succeed.
So long as you're open,
I'll send the ball your way.
One basket! Let's get them back!
Yeah!
But what about Mayuzumi?
We have to do something about him!
I know! Why not put Kuroko on him?
He's familiar with Misdirection,
so he won't lose track of him!
No, that's impossible because...
Mitobe-senpai!
He predicted its trajectory
based on its target and path!
Then I won't pass.
I'll shoot instead.
He can shoot, too?
Kuroko-kun may be able
to prevent his Misdirection.
But in a one-on-one,
he doesn't stand a chance.
See that? That's my style.
I'm nothing like you.
He's looking at me...
No, he's observing me!
Rakuzan
Seirin
A seven point difference...
We need to do something.
Okay.
Black team player substitution.
A sub?
But who?
What?
Aomine-san, what are they...
It doesn't mean shit.
He's like a chihuahua standing before a lion.
What are they thinking?!
B-Bring it on!
Come on.
He's so weak, he doesn't know what to do.
Sei-chan, throw in!
Okay.
He's so scared, he can't even look at us.
We wouldn't blame you for
sending someone better instead.
You're so kind.
Are you stupid?!
But it's okay.
We're totally serious.
You can do it!
Furi!
I don't know what you're thinking,
but there's nothing you can do!
He passed him!
Of course he did.
This is what they wanted!
They're quick to help!
Oh, right.
Akachin might not be able to use
his ankle break from there.
That's it.
They were quick on me, too.
They assumed he would pass him.
No, they let him pass on purpose!
I get it.
They want to get Akashi on the inside.
You can't ankle break someone
without crossing over to
throw them off balance.
In other words, it requires
a certain amount of space.
Once he enters the crowded key,
there's no room to do that.
First they cut off Mayuzumi.
Then they send Kagami
against Akashi in a place
where he can't use his ankle break.
That's Seirin's plan.
Akashi!
He can still step back and pass him!
It's not over yet!
Rebound!
Close!
Damn it!
That worked out surprisingly well.
But that means the first-year
was just bait, right?
Yeah. She may be trying to win,
but it's still a terrible thing to do!
As far as I saw in the Kaijo game,
all he can do is support his teammates.
I don't need to guard him closely.
Mayuzumi!
Crap!
I... I made it!
He made it!
That's it! Get them!
Yeah!
Nice shot, Akashi!
No matter how hard he tries,
he's still a chihuahua.
He can't beat a lion.
But...
White team, time out.
Perhaps we didn't need
to call one when we had a lead.
It was unnecessary.
No. We're switching between
defense and offense more quickly.
It's getting harder to issue detailed instructions.
That was well timed.
They've given up on trying to stop Akashi.
It doesn't affect us much,
but we should narrow
down our choices, as well.
We'll focus our attacks.
First around you.
Furi?
Huh?
Are you hurt?
No, but...
Huh?
You're kidding.
You're out, Furihata-kun.
What?
I'm okay! I can still play!
You can't.
You've got no strength left.
What? You mean he's just exhausted?
I don't believe it.
Furi may have been playing hard,
but he's not that weak.
Is that just how brutally hard it is
to face Akashi Seijuro?
What are we going to do, Coach?
Let me play!
Fukuda...
I just need to stay on Akashi like Furi, right?
Kawahara and I can do that!
Fukuda-kun...
We're counting on you!
Captain...
Hyuga-kun!
The time out is now over.
Oh, come on!
We're counting on you, Fukuda-kun.
Same thing on defense.
Okay.
One more thing!
Close the gap on offense!
Yeah! Let's go!
Yeah!
Um, what did she mean by close the gap?
Didn't you hear Hyuga?
We'll score three points.
Kuroko, I couldn't do anything...
It's frustrating.
I want to become stronger
so I can fight alongside the guys.
Yeah. Me, too.
They're pumped up.
Hyuga-san should start making
threes once they're on offense.
Rakuzan's going for threes, too.
Which means both teams' attacks
will be focused around the same position.
It's a shooting guard showdown!
The end of the first quarter pissed me off.
I'll crush you this time.
He's a complicated character.
You shouldn't do that.
A fadeaway three?
Damn!
His form is incredibly efficient.
I'm falling in love again.
In middle school, I thought Mibuchi's form
was the best of our generation.
So smooth and sharp. It's seriously cool.
Wait! I shouldn't be thinking
about that right now!
Izuki!
He's not my role model anymore.
He's the enemy I must defeat!
He's faster!
Barrier Jumper!
Yes! Nice shot, Captain!
Nice!
Yeah, of course!
His form looks like yours.
You think so, too?
But they just look similar.
He's made it his own.
It's different.
Not bad.
They're answering threes with threes!
See?
Crap!
No you don't!
I've changed my mind about you.
You're a far better shooter than I thought.
So to thank you, I'll show you
something special.
He's seriously going for it?
Mibuchi has two common shots.
Evading his opponent while
making the shot, or "Heaven."
Then there's making the shot
while striking his opponent, or "Earth."
But there's actually one more.
It's an ordinary shot?
There's no way I'll let him—
I can't jump?
Why?
A shot his opponents can't respond to.
"Void."
Hyuga stopped moving?!
Mibuchi "The Demon" Leo
has three kinds of shots.
How can he stop someone from moving?
It's not just that. I was captivated.
No, what am I thinking?
I should be thinking about
what we should do to win!
Can we win?
It's no use!
He's completely adjusted to
the Barrier Jumper's timing!
Oh my.
Kiyoshi!
Nice!
Nice, Hyuga!
You were right to pass the ball in!
He was faster than I thought.
Sei-chan, I'm good for just one more.
Yes, it looks that way.
I'm finished measuring him.
I won this battle.
He went right into the
shot without faking!
It's Void!
Fake?
This is...
Earth! Damn it!
Defense, black No. 4!
Basket counts, one free throw!
He made the shot and drew a foul!
And it was a three!
That's a four point play!
Hyuga messed up. He backed off.
It wasn't wrong, though.
He passed, and they scored.
For the team, it was the right choice.
But it's now clear
Mibuchi is the better shooter.
No worries, Hyuga!
We'll get them back!
I know!
Izuki, pass me the ball.
Kiyoshi...
I'm in an attacking mood, too.
What's wrong? You suddenly
feel like playing?
Let's go, Nebuya!
He's so heavy!
He won't budge!
My muscles have finally warmed up!
Time for me to get my revenge!
Out of bounds!
He's so strong!
Kiyoshi...
The way you reacted...
Don't tell me you've
forgotten our battle!
I remember playing you.
It's what you said after!
Don't mess with me.
At the end of my first year of middle
school, I was matched up against you
and experienced my first loss.
It was frustrating.
After the game, you told me...
Basketball isn't just about power.
You'll get stronger if you
hone your skills, too.
I had a thought then.
I'll just pack on more muscle!
That's his answer?
With enough muscle, I can do anything!
Nebuya "Herculean Strength" Eikichi!
Sorry, I forgot about that.
But I'm still ready to throw down.
I don't mind contests of strength.
Kiyoshi "Iron Heart" Teppei!
Muscle Screen Out!
What's up with centers?
Do they all have to be loud?
What?!
There's still the aerial battle!
Vice Claw!
Muscle Rebound!
He's as heavy as a boulder!
Could you stop saying "Muscle
Whatever" every time?
Yeah, it's annoying.
Muscle Dunk!
Izuki! The ball!
You won't beat me!
He's going for it!
It's a power contest!
Hey! You're using your Right
of Postponement now?!
Nice, Kiyoshi!
No, that was bad.
Passing and being forced to pass
mean different things.
That was definitely the latter.
But wasn't that...
Yes, you're not wrong.
But the gap will slowly widen.
In other words, this is the
difference in their strength.
Four fingers...
I'll stop him this time!
A crossover!
He evaded Kagami and made the shot!
The Roaring Drive!
Hayama "Thunder Beast" Kotaro!
Wait, is that all?
What?
I thought I'd have more
impact like you guys!
I feel like some rare beast
that's been spotted!
Damn!
While I was distracted,
he got into my blind spot!
Yeah!
Disappearing is my job.
But don't forget I exist.
I won't let you shoot.
Damn!
Come on! What's wrong?
Kagami and Kuroko are strong rookies.
But they're not the only
reason they made it this far.
It's because they had the second-years.
Hyuga and Kiyoshi in particular are
the pillars of their outside and inside.
Breaking them is like
breaking the team's legs.
I can't pass him!
There's nothing I can do.
Is this how much better they are?
Fukuda!
Out of bounds!
White ball!
It's just like Furihata.
Fukuda's exhausted.
Black team player substitution.
Another first-year?
Do they have a plan?
They just switched him out
since he was exhausted.
They're prolonging their strategy.
What? Why isn't Seirin doing anything?
They should be doing something!
Don't yell at me.
It's not that they're not.
They can't.
Coach...
I'm so powerless!
Make it!
He made the Middle Jumper!
Well, it's bound to happen.
Even against Rakuzan, they're
sure to score some points.
But that's all.
The weaklings can make a last-ditch effort.
But ultimately they'll be pushed
out by a stronger power.
It's over.
Crap!
That's unusual.
Is he excited?
No, he's showing off.
What?
What? An alley-oop?
What a jump! He can reach the hoop?
Did you think it was exclusively
a larger player's skill?
I can do this anytime I feel like it.
It's too late.
Kurochin can't recover from
the loss of his lack of presence.
Even if he does, they're too far behind.
Both in points and strength.
Miracles don't happen.
They can't even win with one.
Preview
You're out of resources, huh?
We may be for now.
There's nothing you can do.
Why not give up, old model?
The Weight of Resolve
Even so, I can't let it end here!