They're synchronizing their movements
with a second of eye contact.
Super high-speed teamwork
matching Kagami's Zone speed.
The Direct Drive Zone!
If we can stop them,
victory will be in reach!
Dig deep! Give every last drop!
I will win.
You're far too inexperienced to beat Rakuzan.
Again and Again
This is terrible.
Just when they started riding the momentum
from being only three points behind...
Akashi's shot made the gap even wider.
They're down seven points.
Forty more seconds.
Rakuzan
Seirin
Hurry, Seirin. There's no time.
Defense! Focus up, everyone!
Once we stop them, it's over!
Yeah!
So much pressure.
We need to score as quickly
as possible, but...
They're double-teaming him!
This is bad.
At this rate, he'll instantly consume
the little strength he has left.
Izuki!
He's barely pushing!
That's not strong enough to go
for a shot under the basket!
Kiyoshi!
Damn!
We're keeping a close eye on you!
There's less than 30 seconds!
Please!
Captain!
That's a sideways long pass!
Don't let up on your mark,
Hayama and Mayuzumi!
What's the time?
Twenty-seven seconds left.
Defense!
Give them everything!
Yeah!
Defense! Defense!
Their defense couldn't be better.
But Rakuzan is unbelievable.
They're unshaken.
There's no way they can steal the ball.
What's he doing?
The rest of his team is fired
up, but he's staying cool.
Calm down. Don't get too excited.
You need to be clever.
I may not be able to catch
Akashi off guard, but it's
possible against the other four.
I need to stay calm to win.
A point guard with inferior skills
has to use his head to win.
It's no use.
Rakuzan
Seirin
Rakuzan won't rush their attack.
They'll use up the remaining 24
seconds without forcing a shot.
They won't show any weakness.
No.
They will shoot.
Their pride will force them to shoot.
But Rakuzan knows Kiyoshi is
at his limit, too!
What?
Huh?
Run!
Let's go!
Kagami!
Damn it!
Izuki!
This pass...
A coincidence?
But it was equal to Akashi's passes.
They'll make it.
For sure.
There's a way.
Not just to retaliate, but to win.
I haven't practiced it.
But I've seen more than enough examples.
As long as I have an idea of
what I'm doing, it could work!
Could it be?
Basket counts, one free throw!
Rakuzan
Seirin
He made the three!
And he gets one free throw.
It's a miraculous four point play!
Yeah!
You did it, Captain!
Junpei!
What?
They were four points behind.
We could've won if I'd let
him shoot a normal three,
but...
Sorry, guys.
Don't apologize.
Now isn't the time to blame yourself.
The next rebound will be the moment of truth.
Leave it to me. I'll get the ball.
I'll jump for it, too.
Don't do anything crazy.
It's too late for that.
Getting rebounds is my job.
So
don't accidentally make the shot, Hyuga.
You're one to talk.
Let's have some fun.
This is the final play.
One free throw!
Huh? Crap.
I'm about to cry.
Damn it.
It's his fault for saying it's the last play.
This is
the end.
That's not what I meant.
But it can also mean that.
This is the last play we'll make together.
But I don't regret anything.
All that's left is to give everything I have.
Rebound!
My entire being rides on this play!
He did it!
Stop them! Don't let them shoot!
Who? Who will it be?
Will he take it himself?
Or will he pass?
Piece of crap! I knew.
I was keeping an eye on him!
But the moment I thought someone
might shoot, I forgot about him!
Did he avoid shooting until now
to prepare for this moment?
Go!
Akashi!
It's over, Kuroko!
No, not yet.
I am a shadow.
Time's up!
Seirin High
wins the Winter Cup!
I lost.
So this is defeat.
This is awful.
It's hard to describe this pain in my chest.
I don't think I can stay
composed until we line up.
But
that's why...
I'm glad I played basketball.
And I'm glad I met you.
You...
No, your team won.
Congratulations.
And prepare yourselves.
Next time, we'll win.
Yes.
Let's play again.
And again and again and again.
Yes.
Again and again.
This isn't the end of everything.
In fact, this is just the beginning.
We will fight by playing
the game we love again
and again.
Hey.
Huh? Where are the upperclassmen?
What are you talking about, you idiot?
They're seeing Kiyoshi-senpai off.
We just had a going away party for him.
Oh, shit. That was today?
You're so forgetful.
He said we didn't need to, but...
I told them they didn't have to come,
but I can't believe they really didn't.
You wanted them to come?
They're just doing what you wanted.
They're probably sad, too.
Take care.
Yeah.
After surgery, depending on how rehab
goes, he could recover quickly.
You'll see the guys who couldn't
come today soon enough.
We'll be waiting.
Yeah.
That was an amazing game.
I had goosebumps.
Monthly Basketball had a
huge article on Seirin, too.
Kuroko, I've decided.
Next year, I'll play you guys.
We'll duke it out. I promise.
Okay. I look forward to it.
Tetsu-kun!
Were you waiting long?
No, it's okay.
Here's the thing you asked for.
Thank you.
Wha—
What's wrong with you, Kasamatsu?
Kasamatsu and I have the
same first choice school.
That college is full of cute girls.
Can't you take your exams more seriously?
You think you'll pass
with that kind of motive?
What? But...
Evaluation Exam
That's a bit...
Yeah.
Kobori, you're applying there, too, right?
It's my backup.
Cheer up, Kasamatsu!
I know. Let's go check out the gym!
You'll feel better once
you knock Kise around!
That's an awful thing to say!
Look around you, Kise!
That won't work against Seirin!
Yeah, I know!
You understand him now?
No, just by feel.
By feel. By feel, huh?
Once again!
Yeah!
Oh, well. Time to study.
Isn't this pretty bad?
What's bad?
Otsubo-san, Miyaji-san, Kimura-san.
They're all third-years.
You and I will be the only ones left.
Everyone else is keeping at least
three of their core players.
Won't we be pretty far behind?
You don't think much of me, do you?
Miyaji-san.
I fell one step short of my brother,
but this year I'll surpass him.
Miyaji Yuya 2nd Year SF
(Miyaji Kiyoshi's Younger Brother)
As your captain, I'll prove
it to you with results.
I'm not as gentle as Otsubo-senpai.
Prepare yourselves.
And next year, Kimura-senpai's
brother is joining, too.
Seriously?
We still have first- and
second-years with potential,
and the new first-years are promising, too.
It's not as simple as who
has how many guys left.
You're right. Sorry.
Come to think of it,
Otsubo-senpai has a younger sibling
who wants to play basketball, too.
What? Just how many brothers
do we have on the team?
I've got a picture.
Otsubo Tae-chan.
A girl? She looks nothing like him!
How did the practice exam go?
All right, I guess.
By the way, I met Seiho's Kasuga.
He's pretty smart.
You can't be serious.
What do you mean, Atsushi?
It snows too much in Akita.
Yeah, I agree.
I thought it was a natural
disaster at first, too.
I'd understand if this
were dried wheat cakes...
Sorry, but I don't get you.
Also, I've been wondering...
But why are you here?
Of course we're here!
We haven't graduated yet!
Did you think school ended
when the season ended?
We will be missing a few days starting
next week for entrance exams.
Our first choice schools are in Tokyo.
I thought you couldn't get
into college without studying.
That's why we're studying!
Quit messing with me!
Huh?
You can have this, then.
What?
Maiu
Katsu Curry
Flavor
Study hard.
Yeah.
They're just snacks.
Practice, practice.
You've been smiling more since
Aomine-san started attending practice.
You think so?
Aomine's late? That brat!
Captain...
Hey, Momoi.
Could you do that again?
If you don't come,
I'm burning this.
Give me back my Mai-chan!
You're here.
That's one underhanded way to...
You just have to show up.
You don't have to play. Just watch.
What?
But don't blame me if you run out of
steam before Kagami at the end of a game.
It'll just end like it did last time.
Hey, you! I told you to get closer!
Just watching is boring.
What?
I'm saying I'll play.
I'm hungry.
Are you sure we don't need
to practice since we lost?
What are you talking about? Today is special.
The third-years retired from the team.
They're leaving, huh?
I wonder if that was all right, though.
He never showed up.
Mayuzumi-san.
It's you, Akashi.
And honorifics? I thought we were equals.
Only when I'm your captain during practice.
Now we're just a first-year and a third-year.
Thanks for your hard work.
Sure.
Are you sure you didn't want to
attend the retirement ceremony?
Yeah. That's not really my thing,
and I'm not that attached to the team.
It's not like I've got great
memories from being on it.
The last year wasn't bad, though.
Thanks to you.
Yes.
Anyway, just leave me be until graduation.
It'd be lame if we kept talking after today.
What are we going to do about practice?
Huh? You haven't heard from anyone?
Do we have the day off?
Of course not, idiots.
Captain, hey!
What about seeing him off?
I'm here because I already did.
These days you can e-mail
guys in foreign countries,
and it's not that hard to get there.
It's not the last time we'll see
each other, so I made it quick.
You seemed more hurt and quiet
than anyone else, though.
Shut up, Izuki!
More importantly, I can't
ignore what you just said.
You think we don't have practice?
The Kanto Inter-High qualifiers start
right after the newbie matches end.
When did you get too good to
care, huh, you little brats?
At this rate, you're not getting
out of a buck-naked confession.
What? But we already did that.
And now it's reset.
When the new semester starts and new
players join the team, we'll do it again.
And we'll aim higher this time.
Doesn't that mean another championship?
Of course.
Everyone else is practicing
with their new lineups
and reaching out to players
to strengthen their teams.
If we just sit around, we'll fall behind.
Come on. Let's start practice.
But Kuroko's still not here.
He was just in the club room.
He should be here soon.
Sheesh...
Kagami, go check on him.
Who, me?
Hey, Kuroko.
What's taking so long?
Hurry...
Huh? Where'd he go?
Did you call?
You... I told you!
Sorry. I was getting a photo from Momoi-san.
Oh, of that thing you planned
for your birthday...
No, wait!
Practice! Let's go!
Okay.
You're late, Kuroko!
Now let's start practice!
Seirin, fight!
Yeah!