Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
This is mine.
That shot is mine!
Like Kise-kun, Haizaki-kun makes moves
his own after seeing them only once.
That's mine.
However, he uses his own rhythm and tempo.
What?
Haizaki-kun doesn't copy moves.
He steals them.
The Generation of Miracles?
Don't make me laugh.
That's some big talk when
this is all you can do.
Stay Out of My Way
That's pretty nice.
Hey, toss us the ball!
Who is he?
He looks like a middle schooler.
Isn't that Teiko's uniform?
That place with the unusually
strong basketball team?
Really?
Hey, shithead. Come here.
We'll play with you.
Damn it!
Who is this guy?
I thought your moves were pretty nice,
but they weren't worth stealing.
You guys are nothing.
You should be grateful I was
willing to play with you.
A-Are you
one of the Generation of Miracles?
The Generation of Miracles again?
Since I quit, every time someone mentions
Teiko, everyone always brings them up.
That's fine, I guess.
I'll just steal it if I want it.
Bring me a drink!
Make it snappy, idiots!
Since Haizaki joined, the team has changed.
But he's still strong.
Strong enough to crush Kise Ryota
of the Generation of Miracles
and corner the mighty Kaijo.
Physically he's Kise's equal, and he
can steal his opponents' techniques...
He's more of a problem than we expected.
Kasamatsu's moving the ball around,
and Kise's doing his best,
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
but as the game drags on, we lose
more abilities and offensive strength!
What should we do?
At this rate, we'll be in serious trouble!
Another one-handed dunk.
But that rhythm...
He's way worse than usual!
I just took that during the second quarter.
It's not yours anymore.
It's mine.
Captain!
Give it to me!
Damn it!
I'll show you how to do it.
You do it like this!
Fukuda Sogo's in complete
control of the game.
I had no idea Haizaki was so strong.
Impossible!
He's copying him perfectly.
Something's wrong with Kise's movements.
He's not his usual self.
You're right.
Though his moves have been stolen,
I can't imagine Kise-kun falling this hard.
This isn't good.
What?
Kise learns moves after seeing them once.
He should have a pretty significant
number of moves stored up.
But not many of them will
work against Haizaki.
On top of that, they'll be stolen as soon
as he uses them, making them useless.
He's been carefully choosing
from a limited set of choices,
but he's starting to run out of options.
But...
And that's not the only problem,
is it, Kise?
Kise!
You're going too hard! Save your strength!
It's not enough.
What?
I can't get there like this...
He's overworked?
Probably.
I can't imagine Aomine-kun was the only one
who injured himself during the
Inter-High's Kaijo-Touou game.
Kise-kun has probably been practicing
hard without recovering completely.
But...
Don't lose in the preliminaries!
Of course.
But there's no way he'd
lose to that shithead.
He promised to win so we could
play in the semifinals.
He won't lose!
He made another shot!
He's amazing! He's shutting out Kise!
Is he as good as the Generation of Miracles?
Impossible...
Kise doesn't stand a chance.
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
I'm starting to run out of moves.
Damn it. And my foot...
Come to think of it, you used to grovel on
your knees in middle school, too, Ryota.
Oh, right.
And I stole your girlfriend, didn't I?
That was pathetic.
I dumped her as soon as I
was done with her, though.
That bastard's head is big enough!
It's unspeakable.
Hey, you!
You've crossed the line!
That's enough!
Yeah, yeah. I'll be careful.
Kise...
Ki-chan...
Are you
going to take this lying down?
Kuroko?
I believe in you, Kise-kun!
Kurokocchi...
Shogo-kun, you know...
Before I beat you,
you should know you have
the wrong idea about her.
What?
The way she followed me around and called
herself my girlfriend was annoying.
She was totally arrogant and always
bragged about herself.
She just wanted people to
know she was dating a model.
All you did was take one of the stupid women
who flocked to me because of my appearance.
Don't let it get to your head.
What?
Kise!
Go back!
You have nothing left!
You're just dregs now, Ryota!
Who?
Doesn't that mean we can be friends now?
Our styles are completely different!
What...
What?
Is that...
...the Generation of Miracle's Midorima
Shintaro's high trajectory three-pointer?
I thought he couldn't copy the other
members of the Generation of Miracles!
He overcame that,
but using their abilities
takes a major toll on his body.
At most he can do it for five
minutes. But right now, Kise can
use all the abilities
of the Generation of Miracles.
It is a flawless imitation.
A Perfect Copy!
If it's women or titles you
want, you can have them all.
I have a more important promise to keep.
I will make it there.
Stay out of my way!
Piece of shit!
It's no use!
Not even I
can steal their abilities!
Kise's amazing! He's unbelievable!
Kaijo's catching up!
All right!
We're seven points down!
Let's close that gap!
Don't be ridiculous, shitheads...
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
A scoop shot!
Haizaki, what was that?
The idiot is shaken.
Why are you stealing your
teammates' abilities?
His reactions and intensity rival Atsushi's!
Even his blocks...
He can even copy Murasakibara?
In his game against Touou, Kise-kun
recreated the rapid speed change
of Aomine-kun's changeover
by dropping his minimum speed.
He also achieved the range
of Midorima-kun's shot
by holding the shot with his dominant hand,
and he's reproducing Murasakibara's defense
with his jumping ability and predictions.
But the abilities of the Generation of
Miracles aren't reproduced that easily.
Kise Ryota's basketball sense is bottomless.
Bastard...
Shogo-kun, you said you'd steal the title
of the Generation of Miracles, right?
How do you feel now?
It's a comeback!
Kaijo's making a comeback!
What? Akashi, what did you just say?
Quit the basketball team. That's an order.
What?
I'm actually being considerate of you.
100 Battles 100 Victories
Teiko Middle School Basketball Team
Though your behavior is hardly praiseworthy,
you have contributed to
Teiko's victories until now.
However, you cannot beat Kise.
In the near future, he will
replace you as a starter.
You are too proud to stick around.
He'll replace me?
It'll happen sooner or later.
But either way, the result will be the same.
You bastard...
Was Akashi right?
I have to admit, though...
Ryota, you're strong.
I don't care what happens now.
I'll destroy you!
Did you think I didn't notice
your foot was injured?
His foot...
It happened so quickly,
the referee didn't notice!
This is the end!
I thought I told you
to stay out of my way!
You won't win!
I will!
Kise!
Go, Kise!
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
The game's over!
Yes!
Kise!
We did it!
Ow!
You're killing my brain cells!
Our next opponent...
...is Kaijo.
You guys were a terrifying team that
didn't give up until the very end.
Win for us, too.
You were strong.
You go on ahead, Satsuki.
Huh?
Hey, Dai-chan!
Kaijo's not coming out yet.
If you're thinking about getting
revenge on Kise, don't bother.
Daiki.
If you'll go home quietly, I'll let this go.
Whatever, idiot.
I'll do what I want.
If you're going to play ball,
I don't care what you do.
But don't mess with them by
doing stupid shit off the court.
That's odd.
Have you always been such a good little boy?
You lost to Kise, Haizaki.
You have no idea how much
he and Tetsu have trained.
Don't do anything else stupid.
I see.
Now I really have to destroy them.
I told you, I don't care.
Unfortunately, unlike you guys,
I don't give a shit about basketball.
If you want me to stop,
make me!
Then I will.
What should I do now?
I'm sure it'll work out.
You don't care as long
as it's basketball, huh?
Haizaki-kun!
Huh?
Tetsuya.
Is it true you're quitting
the basketball team?
Yeah. So what?
But you have such amazing talent. Why?
Why did you even come here? Are you stupid?
It's not like we're friends.
That's not the issue.
Shut up.
I'm tired of basketball.
That's all, idiot.
It's tiring and makes me stink.
I have way more fun hanging out with girls.
Is that how you really feel, Haizaki-kun?
You really are an idiot.
Do you think deep down I'm actually serious?
Some guys really are bad to
the bone, or even terrifying.
Later.
You'd better not pity me or anything.
There's no guarantee the rest of you who
stay on the team won't be worse off.
That's right.
It's worse for the guys who stayed.
What's wrong, Kuroko?
Nothing.
And so, the curtains closed on
the fifth day of the Winter Cup.
Seirin
Shutoku
Kaijo
Rakuzan
Only...
...the four semifinalists remained.
Preview
Satsuki!
You can't just show up at someone's house
and start digging through their stuff!
Dai-chan, you have the same shoes as
Kagamin but in a different color, right?
What? Kagamin? Shoes?
I'll Take It
Here they are!
Hey, don't take those out!
Hey, Satsuki!