Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
Who's gone soft?
No you don't!
And that's Aomine's change of pace!
He can even copy Akashi's Emperor Eye?
The Vanishing Drive!
Not even Murasakibara could
stop that invincible shot,
and he blocked it?
The True Light
Kise's not stopping!
Since the game started, no one's
been able to touch him!
They're already 13 points ahead!
Kaijo
Seirin
It's like fighting the whole
Generation of Miracles at once.
Shit. He's out of control.
And it's only been three minutes?
His Perfect Copy will last
another two minutes, too.
Man, this is rough.
I'm taking a break.
What?
Copying them is really tiring.
I can't be falling over
at the start of the game.
The game's just getting started.
I need to save some fun for later.
But I got what I wanted.
We're in control of the game.
This is terrible.
Uh-oh. They're losing already.
But...
Kise-chin's Perfect Copy
is certainly impressive.
But he only has two more minutes
to use at the end of the game.
It'll happen sooner or later.
No. It's not that simple.
Huh?
Every game has its own flow.
Their surprise attack succeeded.
It'll keep affecting the game.
That was probably Kaijo's true aim.
Damn it!
We need to be closing the
gap as quickly as possible!
Don't worry about it, Hyuga!
Yeah!
Kagami!
A fadeaway out of a full drive.
Another old move.
But...
What?
They failed another attack.
So this is what you meant.
Yeah. They're completely off balance.
Seirin initially planned to
establish a lead and hold it.
But after that unexpected surprise
attack, they've fallen far behind.
They want to close the gap.
But their impatience dulls their
attacks, leading to mistakes.
At this rate, their attacks
will keep failing.
Member change.
Furihata-kun.
You're in.
What?
Izuki-kun!
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
You've been wanting this for a long time.
You guys always get to play,
but sometimes we want to play, too.
That day has finally come.
I'm okay.
Calm down...
It feels totally different
once I'm on the court!
Kuroko and the upperclassmen
have been playing like this?
We're counting on you.
Your mark is No. 4.
Huh? What?
Is he a secret weapon they've
been hiding until now?
I guess not.
I don't know what the coach is
thinking, but do your best, Furi.
Do your best?
Is that English? Can I eat it?
Let's do our best, Furihata-kun.
Huh?
He doesn't even see Kuroko...
Is he going to be okay?
What? They sent a petrified first year?
I can't do this!
It's too scary!
They subbed in a first year point guard.
What kind of plays will he make?
Let's go!
Calm down!
Keep it together, Furi!
Thanks, I guess!
What?
Shit. This invisible kid...
Sorry. Give us a minute.
He's still nervous.
What?
That's not my problem!
Furihata-kun!
It's okay.
In my first game, I tripped
and got a bloody nose.
Kuroko...
Seriously?
Seriously.
Coach, are you sure about this?
He's the biggest wuss around.
That's why you subbed him in, right?
His cowardice isn't a weakness.
There are some things only a coward can do.
That's right. Just watch.
He's still stiff as a board.
Even if he weren't nervous,
I doubt he'd work against us.
Hey!
It's Kagami!
It's a one-on-one!
I'm not missing the next one!
Let's go, Kise!
Bring it on!
Kagami, stop!
C-Calm... Calm down!
Huh? What?
You're the one who needs to calm down!
You're not coming?
Shut up.
We have to get this back under control.
This is...
Seirin feels different.
They're passing the ball around
and attacking carefully.
I see.
Their goal was to slow the pace down.
But they're not just taking it easy.
Kobori and Hayakawa were quick to respond
when they thought Kagami was coming.
Even if he made it past Kise,
they would've caught him immediately.
This guy...
Coach, is this...
Yes.
Cowardly is just another way to say careful.
In other words, cowards
never attack recklessly.
He's the perfect player when you
want to change the pace of the game.
Uh, what should I do on the court?
Nothing special.
Do what you always do.
Take your time and play at
your pace like you always do.
But you can't just be careful.
It may seem obvious, but you have
to take it to the finish line.
Yeah, but what should I do?
Don't be stupid. What are you talking about?
You have teammates.
Rely on them as much as you need to.
Kaijo
Seirin
All right!
Nice pass, Furi!
Looks like you're starting to loosen up.
We did it.
I messed up!
He stopped me before I could get anywhere!
Captain!
No. 12 doesn't stand out
much, but he moves well.
By supporting his teammates well,
he allows them to move around freely.
I sensed it during their last attack,
but that first year point guard...
He compensates for mistakes and
avoids dangerous situations.
He's good at assisting his allies.
This is rough!
I'm going to die!
Where are the upperclassmen?
They're staying late to practice.
Are they really human?
Hey.
Huh?
I'm thinking of quitting the team.
What?
Where did that come from?
If you work hard, I'm sure...
I like basketball, but...
Kagami, Kuroko,
and all the upperclassmen are amazing.
I can barely keep up with
them during practice.
No matter how hard I try,
I don't think I can play in a game.
Kawahara...
I've actually
thought the same thing.
Everyone thinks the same
thing when they see Kagami.
That he's cut from a different cloth.
But watching Kuroko, I think something else.
He's still amazing,
but maybe there's something I can do, too.
Even if I ride the bench until the end,
I still want to play
basketball with the guys.
I'd probably regret quitting.
They're fast!
We can intercept the pass!
It's ours!
What?
Kuroko...
Go!
Nice shot, Furi!
I wasn't expecting this ambush.
But they'll sub him out soon, right?
Yes.
And even if they do,
it won't change their weakness.
It's Seirin's greatest weakness.
We'll focus our attacks
around Kasamatsu even more
during the second quarter.
Yes, sir.
I'm counting on you.
You don't have to tell me!
Ow...
Furihata-kun, you're out.
Good job!
Okay!
Izuki-kun, you're up next.
I'm okay to go-kay.
Nice one.
Now that we're back on our feet...
No response?
We'll go with the plan we
established before the game.
We've got something this
time to double our strength.
We'll focus our attacks around Teppei.
Leave it to me.
I knew this was coming.
Come on!
Again!
He's passing from under the net!
Damn it!
Don't worry, Kobori!
Offense!
A center showdown...
It's Seirin's greatest chance of winning.
They're going for the mismatch.
It looks that way.
But isn't this more obvious?
Isolation, huh?
They created space for Kasamatsu
to penetrate the key.
In other words, they want a one-on-one.
That first-year did his best,
but he's still only a first year.
After that underwhelming performance,
I'm not holding back.
Look closely.
He's way faster than you.
Predict his movements.
Left...
No, right!
What?
My prediction was right! So how...
You're kidding, right?
He still can't keep up?
That's as far as you go!
Go, go, Kasamatsu!
I'm not finished yet.
He's fast.
Aside from the Generation of Miracles,
he's the fastest opponent we've faced.
Izuki!
They'll probably keep attacking like this.
They're assuming they'll pass you.
In other words, they think
you're our weakest player.
Yeah, I know.
Captain, isn't that a little harsh?
What? Don't be so easy on him, moron!
Izuki started playing his
second year of grade school.
He's been playing longer than any of us.
Don't worry.
This isn't enough to get him down.
No one's put more into basketball than him.
Encouraging him is senseless.
Shit!
Go back!
Sorry, but you can't stop me.
One more time! One more time, please!
You want to keep going, Izuki?
I'm nearly there.
I nearly have the technique
Kagetora-san taught me.
Since I'm so clumsy,
it takes me far more practice
to learn a single ability.
I just have to keep practicing
until I can do it.
Izuki!
This is it.
Eagle Spear!
What?
He waited until my defenses
were lowest, just after my drive...
And used his Eagle Eye to tip
the ball behind his back?
Not changing the direction he's facing
dramatically increases his speed.
But is that even possible?
All right!
Mad men make mad interceptions!
Shut up, Izuki!
I apologize.
Honestly, I underestimated you, Izuki Shun.
Well, I'm more than just a pun master.
What? Puns?
When did you make any?
You didn't notice?
The pressure is incredible.
He's not backing down,
even though he knows he'll pass him.
Don't falter!
Pass him, Kasamatsu!
If I pour all my nerves into it,
I should be able
to go fast enough to outrun his tip.
But...
Kasamatsu's strengths are his
outside attacks and quick drives.
If his opponent approaches him
to prevent a shot, he drives.
If they back away to prevent
a drive, he shoots.
It's one of the most orthodox
and powerful styles.
Right now a drive would be effective.
But he can't go.
If he dives in carelessly, it's likely
he'll be caught by No. 11's steal.
If I pour my senses into a drive,
I won't be able to avoid the invisible kid...
Damn him!
He has multiple threats.
His talons are the real deal!
Senpai!
He's coming.
I don't want to back down now, but...
It's all you, ace!
This guy...
Looks like you're finally warmed up.
In fact...
Now that I'm facing you, I can tell
you're a totally different person now.
Interesting...
I'll stop you!
Kagami!
Go!
He stopped the shot!
Neither ace is giving any ground!
Senpai...
Give me the ball again, please.
Leave him to me.
He's finally warmed up.
Okay.
Sheesh. I can't refuse my
ace when he looks like this.
Fine.
I'll break through this time.
I'll stop him again.
The tension is incredible.
They're like master swordsmen facing off.
Hey, Satsuki.
Do you believe in destiny?
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't have a fever!
I know it's out of character.
But lately I've been thinking.
Was it really a coincidence that
the Generation of Miracles and Tetsu
came together at the same time?
I don't know if it means anything.
It's just something I sense.
We were on the same team.
Then we became enemies.
Recently we all made it to this tournament.
If destiny does exist, then his
appearance must have been fate, too.
One like the Generation of Miracles
that couldn't become one of us.
The last awakened one with as much
talent as the Generation of Miracles.
The Miracle that never was.
The...
...true light destined to meet his shadow.
I win!
Damn you...
Preview
I won't be beat!
I'll do my best to get
rebounds and everything else!
Calm down!
I have no idea what you're saying!
No matter what happens,
I believe in Kaijo's ace, Kise!
Don't Underestimate Me!!
You're right.
Let's support him with everything we've got!
Yes, sir!