Tendo Martial Arts Sword Drawing
First Style, Number 1:
Tekisui Seihyo!
She's unbelievably fast
with a sword, as always...
Not to mention that's Yukikage,
a sword meant to kill.
Rentaro! How long are you
going to keep me waiting?
Listen.
Just because they're rubber bullets,
it doesn't mean they won't hurt.
I'm aware of that!
How was my fighting?
Try not to high kick while wearing a skirt.
You know you liked it.
#05 The Crimson Black Assassin
You still haven't found a
new school for Enju-chan?
Nope...
Why not have her go to a
school in the Outer District?
You mean that open-air classroom
surrounded by abandoned buildings?
What's important is finding a place where
Enju-chan feels comfortable, isn't it?
Well, I'll consider it...
Regardless, you'll need money, right?
We've got a job. It's a bodyguard request.
Bodyguard? For who?
Believe it or not, you've been
hand-picked by Seitenshi-sama herself,
Satomi-kun.
Good day, Satomi-san.
The day after tomorrow,
President Saitake,
who represents the Osaka Area,
will be visiting the Tokyo
Area for an informal meeting.
Saitake Sogen? For what?
I do not know.
But I believe his biggest reason
for choosing this moment
was Kikunojo-san's absence.
That's right, the geezer's in China
or Russia or something now, isn't he?
I would like for you to be next
to me when we are traveling,
and behind me when I am
in meetings, and guard me.
You already have bodyguards, don't you?
Indeed. Let me introduce them to you.
I am the head of the bodyguards,
Second Lieutenant Yasuwaki Takuto.
We'll be counting on you if
anything should happen,
Satomi-kun.
I only came here today to get an explanation.
I haven't agreed to take the job yet.
I will look forward to a positive response.
Don't expect too much.
I'm lost.
Damn it. This place is too big.
What are you playing at?
Satomi Rentaro, refuse this job.
What?
Lord Tendo left Seitenshi-sama
in my hands before he left.
The spot next to Seitenshi-sama
belongs to me.
I'm not taking orders from you.
Shatter the bones in his arms and legs.
Bastard...
What's that noise?!
It came from over there!
Let's go.
I'm going to kill you...
I'm going to kill you, Satomi Rentaro!
What happened here?
I thought I heard gun shots.
Please tell Seitenshi
that I'll be taking the job.
That hurt, damn it!
You run over someone's foot with
a bike and have nothing to say?
Man, it's totally broken.
You're gonna have to pay the bill for that.
Yeah!
You're not worth talking to.
Go call your parents.
Who the hell are you?
Hey, let's go.
R-Right...
I've never seen a superhero before...
Um... Where am I?
There. All clean.
Thank you very... mu...
Hey.
Caffeine?
I'm nocturnal, so this is the only way
I can stay awake during the day.
What's your name?
Where'd you come from?
Where's your guardian?
And what are you doing out
here in pajamas and slippers?
I'm not sure.
You're not sure? Then what about your name?
It's...
Tina.
Tina Sprout.
I'm Satomi Rentaro.
All right, Tina, I'm asking you again.
Where's your guardian?
I don't have one.
Then where'd you come from?
I believe, today, I woke up in my apartment,
brushed my teeth, took a shower,
changed my clothes, and then quickly...
Don't lie! You haven't changed,
and you haven't taken a shower.
It's obvious you just woke up.
Wow... You know me better
than I know myself.
Forget it. Just go to a police box.
I can't really do that...
I've realized that you're
more than I can handle.
You can call me if something happens,
but just go to the police box. Please.
Why are you calling me right now?
You might have given me a fake
phone number, Rentaro-san.
Hello?
I failed to mention this,
but I know where my apartment is.
What?
Today was a very fun day.
I hope we'll see each other again.
Well then, goodbye, Rentaro-san.
What the hell was up with her?
I have successfully
infiltrated the Tokyo Area.
On my way to retrieve the item.
Tina Sprout, let me confirm.
Tell me, what is your mission?
The assassination of the
Tokyo Area representative,
Seitenshi, Master.
Rental Box
Little girl, where'd you come from?
You shouldn't be out here this late.
Where's your house?
Master, this is an unforeseen incident.
A police officer is talking to me.
Kill him.
Hm?
This is pretty bad...
Did the Cursed Children go on a rampage again?
The police officer who was attacked
is apparently unconscious
and in critical condition.
Why can't everyone just get along?
I don't know.
All right. Let's go home.
Okay, it should be ready now.
Let's ea—
Who the hell is it at this hour?
Satomi-chan!
M-Miori?! What are you doing here?
Take care of me...
Rentaro, who is this woman?
This is Shiba Miori.
She's the student council
president at Magata High School
and daughter of the president of the large-scale
weapons company, Shiba Heavy Weapons.
S-Satomi-kun...
Kisara-san?!
M-Make sukiyaki with this...
I'm... hungry...
Please, Enju...
Dispose of one of them.
What are you talking about?
These two hate each other so much,
putting them together causes
some horrific chemical reaction.
I thought you had a cold.
Actually,
it seems the cold medicine and
energy drink worked wonders.
And then I got hungry suddenly.
Sorry to have you feed me.
Indeed, you should be.
I'd prefer it if a snake like you,
who didn't bring any ingredients
and got to eat for free,
would leave immediately.
Oh, you're here, Kisara?
Your boobs are so big,
I couldn't see your face.
By the way, Satomi-kun,
I sent off the paperwork.
Got it. Thanks.
They want you to start tomorrow,
so the rest is on you.
We have work, Rentaro?
Yeah. Bodyguard duty this time.
I'm counting on you.
All right!
So you must be Enju-chan.
How do you like the feel of those shoes?
Huh?
Those are shoes my company
designed for fighting.
I see!
Also, the Varanium bullets that
Satomi-chan fires off everywhere
are provided by my company, too.
But Rentaro can't afford to pay for all that.
It's free.
It's free?!
When we civil officers use a weapon,
we're promoting the company that made it.
The moment I laid eyes on
Satomi-chan, it struck me.
I knew he would make it big someday.
So we gave him the okay,
with some conditions.
What do you mean by conditions?
There are a few.
One of them was that he would study
at Magata High School with me.
Satomi-chan belongs to only me.
H-Hey, get off of me.
Say, Satomi-chan, why don't
you quit Kisara's company
and come work for our civil security unit?
Say, Satomi-kun,
this is delicious and all,
but don't you think something's missing?
Huh?
It's...
Miori's blood.
You're not going to back down, are you?
There we go.
I'll send you to hell.
I'll make you grovel before my Shiba Style!
So much for getting my
security deposit back...
Rentaro, do your best at work!
Satomi-san, you've met President
Saitake previously, right?
When I was taken in at the Tendo mansion,
the geezer dragged me around everywhere,
including to all kinds of parties.
How would you describe President Saitake?
A dictator.
Surely you jest...
I'm serious. Sapporo, Sendai, Hakata...
All the Area heads are the same.
They all restored their
Areas within a generation
from the age of devastation
after the Gastrea War.
They're all extremely efficient,
yet dangerous guys.
And among them all,
Saitake is the most dangerous.
Be careful.
I thank you for the warning.
Satomi-san, please do not leave my side.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Seitenshi-sama.
Is this boy next to you
the brat Tendo adopted?
You're still alive, huh?
Watch your mouth. You're only a civil officer.
Please take a seat, Seitenshi-sama.
Rentaro, I heard that you
destroyed the rail gun module.
What if I did?
That weapon was to be
transferred to the moon's surface,
and eventually used to target
and destroy the Gastrea on Earth.
And yet you...
You weren't just going to
target Gastrea, were you?
You intend to threaten other
countries with violence?
Seitenshi-sama, you lack vision.
We have to consider what will happen
after we exterminate the Gastrea.
The country that recovers from
that unprecedented disaster first
will become the leader of the new world.
That is what I'm after.
All those who get in my way will be eliminated.
Stop fooling around.
I am not fooling around.
I will have anyone with
power take part in my plan.
My will is the will of Japan.
The will of Japan, in other words, is my will.
Don't be so depressed.
Even Kikunojo had problems handling Saitake.
You did well just by not
agreeing to everything he said.
And you didn't yield to him, either.
There's no one around me who says
what's on their mind like you do,
so it was refreshing.
So that's why you chose me?
It is said that President Saitake
is getting money
and weapons from other countries.
What's in it for them?
Varanium.
As an archipelago of volcanic islands,
Japan produces Varanium in abundance.
I'm assuming that, in exchange for Varanium,
he is getting aid from other countries
to help him take over all
five Areas of Japan.
Satomi-san, countries from
all over the world will be
contacting the various Areas
of Japan in the future.
There will be powerful,
high-ranking civil officers
sent in for assassinations and sabotage.
What are you trying to say?
The Tokyo Area does not currently have
the leeway to let efficient
people just fool around.
I will have you working for me continuously.
That's rather selfish.
I am aware that it is selfish.
I intend to reclaim this
land from the Gastrea,
and connect all of the Areas of Japan.
And that is when the
citizens will remember...
that once, we were all brethren,
gazing up at the same sky.
Even if I'm threatened with
assassination or murder attempts,
I will not yield.
I must embody peace,
not with words, but with actions.
You're the type of idealist that dies young.
I don't want to be a person who
can't even speak her ideals.
Then conduct yourself better.
You're an idiot...
though I don't dislike you.
Thank you very much.
It's no use with Rentaro.
I'm sorry?
Rentaro has a thing for big boobs,
so if your boobs are smaller than Kisara's,
he won't acknowledge you as a woman.
That's disgusting...
Seriously, what are you saying
right after you wake up?
Rentaro.
What?
I have a bad feeling...
Get up! Hurry!
Crap!
Seitenshi-sama! Are you all right?!
Get her to the cover of the buildings!
Rentaro, we must hide quickly!
No, it's fine.
The enemy's already gone.
Who the hell are you?
I'm sorry, Master.
I have failed.
There was someone rather
skilled among her bodyguards.
I shall retrieve the Shenfield and retreat.
Did you see any civil officers?
Yes. However, he was too far away,
so I couldn't make out his face.
I see...
The one who got in my way...
Just who are you?
#06 Tragic Irony
This is the first time anyone's
been so nice to me...
I will get that sniper!
I didn't agree to be your bodyguard
just to let you get killed!