Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
I'm going to win, Akashi.
That's impossible, Shintaro.
Because I always win, I am always right.
He's fast!
Nice pass!
You're not going anywhere.
Three should do it.
How is he dribbling like this?
My eyes can't keep up!
It disappeared?
I Don't Know
What is this?
I'm going to kill them all.
First-years! You did a crap job mopping!
Don't slack off!
Yes, sir!
Miyaji-san's angry again today.
So scary.
You, too!
Quit dragging your feet!
Yes, sir!
Today was rough, too.
He was super pissed.
Miyaji-san's definitely the
scariest upperclassman.
What's up, Shin-chan?
What are you doing?
Go home already.
Otsubo-san, I thought we weren't
supposed to stay late to practice
during testing periods.
Oh, you mean Miyaji?
Don't worry about him.
The coach gave him permission.
His grades are good.
I only ever thought of him as scary.
Seeing that side of him was surprising.
Right. You guys don't know.
I'm used to seeing it, though.
Does Miyaji scare you?
He's super scary.
He's made Shin-chan wet
himself a bunch of times.
I haven't wet myself!
He's a strict guy.
On others and himself.
He practiced more than
anyone else and finally
became a regular the summer
of his second year.
He didn't become a starter
until his third year.
It's not that he doesn't have talent.
But he made it this far through
backbreakingly hard work.
Kimura's the same.
That's why they feel the greatest pride
and responsibility of all the regulars
and why everyone trusts them.
He may be a little too strict on
you underclassmen, though.
Besides, there are some good things about...
Oh, right.
Midorima, this is from Miyaji.
You were looking for this, right?
It's Oha Asa's lucky item for tomorrow.
An idol fan.
What? Oha Asa?
An idol fan?
Does this belong to Miyaji-san?
Yeah, he's a fan of Miyu Miyu.
A fan?
Thank you.
Also, I'm a Mamiring fan.
You know, in eighth.
Seriously? You, too, Otsubo-san?
Do you guys do that crap together?
Yeah.
He passed him!
Such amazing dribbling!
Damn it!
A double clutch!
He's so agile!
He made the shot!
He's so good!
He passed two of Shutoku's defenders!
His dribbling is so loud.
They say it's better to dribble harder,
but I've never seen anyone dribble that hard.
And why does his dribbling seem so strange?
Don't worry about it.
Let's switch gears.
Yeah.
Three should do it.
I barely saw it, but is that even possible?
Hayama only touched the ball
with three of his fingers.
"Three" meant the number of fingers
he was using to convey his entire
body's strength to the ball.
Does that mean there are two
higher levels of that dribbling?
Seriously?
Shutoku
Rakuzan
The gap's getting wider.
Nice pass!
That hurt, you muscle-bound gorilla!
Thanks!
That's not a compliment!
Damn it!
We're managing to score with Shin-chan,
but the difference is too great.
Miyaji-san's not the only one.
They're completely overpowering
Otsubo-san, too.
They're leaving Kimura-san open
by double-teaming Shin-chan,
but he's struggling, too.
Akashi hasn't done anything yet.
He's just passing effectively.
But we can barely keep up.
Sorry, but the rest of your
team is just holding you back.
What did you say?
We're barely keeping you under
control by double-teaming you,
but the other four are average at best.
Especially him...
How long do you think
he'll last against Kotaro?
Crap!
You're not going anywhere!
Weak!
Damn, damn, damn!
When did he...
He's so fast getting back!
Nice!
Holding me back?
What are you talking about?
A screen!
You're not taking this shot!
I don't know of anyone who holds me back
on this team.
He dunked it!
Shutoku's keeping up!
Nice pass.
Midochin...
There it is!
The high trajectory three!
Yeah!
Shutoku
Rakuzan
Midorima Shintaro's not easy to handle.
What should we do? Should
we put another man on him?
No, that's not necessary.
Putting more men on him
would be counterproductive.
You may be Uncrowned Kings, but it will
be difficult for you to stop Shintaro now.
We'll put one man on him in the second half.
What?
I will take on Shintaro.
They're here.
The second game's teams are
warming up during the break.
You're not interested.
You seem to be doing all right.
I'm not so sure.
Akashi hasn't used his eyes yet.
If he does use them, it will
be during the second half.
Then the true battle will begin.
Hey. I haven't seen you since
the opening ceremony, Tetsuya.
Yes, Akashi-kun.
This is Rakuzan and Akashi Seijuro...
They seem different from everyone else.
Hey. You haven't forgotten me, have you?
You pulled some dangerous crap on me then.
I'll beat Kise, and I'll beat you.
Of course I remember you, Kagami Taiga.
I should warn you.
Only those who serve me are
allowed to look me in the eye
when they speak to me.
I never allow those who oppose
me to look down at me.
Lower your head.
What?
That wasn't strength!
What did he just do?
Kagami!
Kagami-kun!
Tetsuya.
If you intend to fight me,
you must prepare yourself.
I'm the one who discovered your power.
You will come to realize what that means.
He discovered Kuroko-kun's power?
Yeah.
So his eyes allow him to
discover hidden powers in people?
No.
Akachin's good at that, too,
but it's different on the court.
He makes everything powerless,
both offense and defense.
That's how his power works.
You'll see soon enough.
Shutoku
Rakuzan
The second half is starting!
I knew you would do this.
Come, Shintaro.
This is what Shin-chan predicted during
the break, but are they serious?
Midorima versus Akashi!
They're challenging each other already.
It's a one-on-one with both teams' aces.
Whichever team wins this is sure
to take control of the game.
What?
He's going for a three without a fake?
Impossible!
I can't believe he intercepted
the ball before he jumped!
His reactions are too fast!
He's not fast.
He just sees it.
What?
Akachin's eyes make both
offense and defense powerless.
You're not passing me!
Pass you? I don't need to.
You're going to move for me.
He did a crossover during
the second I was reacting!
Crap!
I never allow those who oppose
me to look down at me.
Lower your head.
He can predict every movement
with his eyes.
All abilities are rendered useless.
People can't even remain standing.
Akashi Seijuro can predict the
future movements of his opponents.
Shutoku
Rakuzan
Shutoku is fourteen points behind?
They were tied at halftime.
What? He dodged it?
He was in his blind spot!
Do his eyes give him the same
field of vision as the Hawk Eye's?
It's no use. I can't get
into a shooting stance.
He intercepts the ball the second
he starts to shoot or dribble.
Shin-chan can't move a single step!
Hey!
He even saw through that pass fake?
The triple threat.
The most basic form in basketball.
The stance sets up shooting,
passing, and dribbling.
No matter how quick someone
is, just before he moves,
he always enters the corresponding form.
Akashicchi's future-predicting
eyes never miss that moment.
No one can even move in
the face of his defense.
Not even fakes work against him.
You're not going anywhere!
Why don't you get out of my way?
You can't seriously think we'll do that!
Don't get ahead of yourself, first-year!
No. My orders are absolute.
What's going on? Damn it!
We can't even stay on our feet!
What was that?
An ankle break.
Skilled high-speed dribblers
use that technique
to throw their opponents off
balance and make them fall.
The technique can only be performed when
your opponent's center of gravity is
on his pivot leg while he's turning.
For Akashicchi and his
future-predicting eyes, it's easy.
Is he passing behind his back?
He passed to the other side with his elbow?
Nice pass!
Yeah!
Emperor Eye.
As long as he has those eyes,
I can't imagine Akachin losing.
He's crushing Shutoku like they're children.
This is Akashi Seijuro.
Damn it.
I'll just have to...
Hey, don't forget about us!
Akashi!
Shintaro, you are strong.
But you will lose.
Who do you think commanded
the Generation of Miracles?
Not even you can stand against me.
Shutoku
Rakuzan
A 20 point difference...
This is the true strength
of Rakuzan and Akashi.
Come on, Shin-chan.
How long are you going to keep sitting there?
I'll break your glasses!
Hey!
Can't you see those characters?
Pull yourself together!
Indomitable
Make the shot, Midorima!
Go get them, Miyaji!
Go, Takao!
Midorima, Takao. We still have time.
Don't give up before the game's over.
Let's get a basket.
Let's go win.
Hey, Shin-chan.
Miyaji-san was really scary
during practice, wasn't he?
Yes.
Otsubo-san was serious and strict, too.
Practice was hard enough already,
but they never let anyone relax.
I thought I would die
during our training camp.
I puked a bunch of times.
But the watermelon Kimura-san
brought us was really good.
Yes.
The more I think about it,
the more I wish
we could keep playing basketball with them.
Yes.
The game isn't over yet.
Because Midorima-kun and
his team haven't given up.
Let's go, Takao.
Sure thing.
Let's show them
what we have up our sleeves!
Preview
Rakuzan is strong.
No one can deny it.
But the game's just getting started.
Of course. Are you ready, Takao?
I Will Give Them to You
Yeah.
I'll make sure you can make
your shots, Shin-chan!