Here's the uniform you ordered.
Thank you.
I have a message for you, too.
Starting tomorrow, someone's
joining the first string.
I heard about that this afternoon.
That'll make this quick, then.
Apparently it's been only two
weeks since he joined the team.
Yeah!
They want you to mentor him.
His name is Kise Ryota.
It's Nijimura.
I've given it a lot of thought,
and I think it's for the best.
For the team and for me.
Please make Akashi Seijuro
the captain.
...Sorry
I don't get it.
Last year you asked me to make
first-year Akashi the vice captain.
The coach and I both
sensed Akashi's potential and
made an exception for him.
But why are you in such a
hurry to have him take over?
My father's been in the
hospital since last spring.
He's stable now, but they're not
sure how he'll be by nationals.
If something happened to him,
I'd abandon the game to go see him.
If I heard his condition worsened,
I wouldn't be able to play.
I love basketball, and I was afraid
to accept my father's condition.
That's why I haven't said anything until now.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
I'll tell the coach.
Hey, Akashi.
Hello.
You were listening, weren't you?
Just the last part.
That's the worst part.
Anyway...
It's a little early, but you're
the captain now, Akashi.
It hasn't been decided yet.
It's as good as decided.
After hearing what I said,
you still want me to be the captain?
Are you uncertain?
No. I'm just worried about you.
I'm sure you are.
But I'm not worried.
I'm counting on you, Captain Akashi.
Yes, sir.
Kuroko and Kise accompanying
the second string
turned out exactly as we expected.
Yes.
I'm surprised you accepted Kise so quickly.
What?
Midorima, you still don't
recognize Kuroko's talent?
No, we do.
Both Murasakibara and I.
And the upperclassmen.
Then there's no problem.
Kise just got there quicker than usual.
He and Kise fill the same position.
You mean Haizaki?
Come to think of it, he...
Yes. The idiot skipped again.
But unfortunately, he's good.
He'll be our starter,
and Kise will be his sub.
No, I don't think so.
Haizaki is no match for Kise's
potential and rate of growth.
Additionally, Nijimura-san
will become the sub.
Haizaki's terrible behavior is intolerable.
Keeping him would only hurt the team.
We no longer need him.
I'll ask him to quit the team.
Normally Akashi is calm and mild-mannered.
He's talented and popular.
But sometimes he becomes
a different, cold person.
At the very least, he seems
like a different person to me.
But if that's the case, which
one is the true Akashi?
I see.
Haizaki quit the team, huh?
Can't be helped, I guess.
Aren't you being a little cold?
You tried and failed to stop him, right?
There's nothing we can do now.
Haizaki is a proud man.
If one of us or the upperclassmen had gone,
it would've been counterproductive.
But...
Quit being so soft.
You're teammates and rivals.
Since when have you become strong
enough to worry about others?
If you've got time for that, run!
Gather 'round!
We have less than two months
until national qualifiers.
The coach is taking over command now.
What?
Seriously?
What's he like?
Oh, right. It's your first time.
That's right.
I'd better introduce myself, then.
I'm Shirogane Kozo, the coach.
Nice to meet you, Kuroko-kun.
How do you know my name?
Why shouldn't I?
I know all my players' names.
Yes, sir!
You don't need to be so stiff.
He came to practice all the time.
Really?
He likes to see his players
in their natural state,
so he often watches from the second
floor without saying anything.
He seems nicer than I expected.
You're wrong.
Huh?
Practice has been fairly easy until now.
Your real practice starts now.
It will be much harder, but don't worry.
You're young enough that it won't kill you.
He's just a total hard-ass.
I have an announcement to make.
Akashi...
Yes, sir.
Starting today, Akashi Seijuro will
replace Nijimura as the captain.
Seriously?
The third-years may not like it,
but it's so the team can win.
You must accept it.
Nijimura, you've done a great job until now.
Thank you.
That was a surprise.
I knew he was amazing, but I can't
believe he's the captain already.
But he's still only a second-year...
Can he handle it?
There's nothing to worry about.
Akashi comes from a prominent family.
Seriously?
His family has him take
advanced education courses
so he can succeed them one day.
He will pull the team together
even better than Captain Nijimura did.
Really?
Midorimacchi, you seem
pretty well-bred yourself.
Not like Akashi.
Anyway, Murasakibara,
stop eating while you walk.
No way.
Hey!
Hey...
Do they not get along?
It's not that bad.
Midorima is pretty uptight,
and Murasakibara's relaxed.
They've never really liked each other,
but it's been especially bad lately.
Is that why, then?
They've been playing really well lately.
Why are you standing there?
If you had screened him,
I would've been wide open!
What?
I wouldn't need to do that if
you'd just pass me the ball!
I should decide!
Stop fighting!
What are they doing?
I told you...
Don't slur your words!
What are you going to do, Captain Akashi?
Let's observe a little longer.
I've had enough.
I don't like this, either!
Stop fighting!
Even I could beat you right now.
Play me after practice,
and I'll prove it to you.
The team that scores ten points first, wins.
Akashi
Murasakibara
Midorima
I see...
We just have to beat them
with our teamwork, right?
Kuroko
Aomine
Yes.
Akachin, are you holding back?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm playing how I always do.
Sheesh...
What?
Ow...
What are you doing, Kise?
Tetsu was passing to me!
What? That was obviously a pass to me!
What? That was mine!
No, mine!
What?
Why are you fighting now?
This is stupid.
I see how unbecoming it is now, Kuroko.
You're puking?!
Problem solved.
Huh?
Oh, good...
That's Aomine's 50th point!
He's unstoppable!
Excuse me.
Good work yesterday.
Huh?
Where are Aomine-kun and Kise-kun?
And Midorima-kun...
You were puking a lot. Are you okay?
They're accompanying the
second string to their game.
Don't do that.
They should be playing right now.
Teiko
Harada
Aomine-kun?
Aomine-kun...
Aomine-kun!
Why do you look so out of it?
It's nothing.
You've been on a roll lately.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, listen...
Never mind.
You sure?
Since you adopted your new style,
you've been staring at people a lot.
Yes. I'm observing them.
Tetsu-kun!
What?
It's for my Misdirection—
You've been all over Tetsu lately.
I can't help it.
Let me go, please.
You interrupted our conversation.
Huh? What?
Oh, right.
What were you talking about?
Hey, Momoi-san...
When people look at you,
you tend to look back.
What?
Say what?
Everyone has their own habits and reactions.
I observe and analyze them.
It's a necessary part of
directing someone's attention.
Do you know what my habits are, too?
You always avert your eyes when you lie.
You got me.
But I won't make you tell me.
Tell me when you feel like it.
Got it.
There you are!
You guys want to get ice
cream on the way home?
Yeah, good idea.
What about you, Momocchi?
I need to take this game data to Akashi-kun.
Akachin's been asking you to
collect a lot of data lately.
Good work.
Apparently I'm pretty good at it.
Another time, then.
Yeah. Later, guys.
Ow!
The third- and second-years have
reached a level of potential
far beyond typical middle school students.
They're almost certainly
the strongest players ever.
Reached their potential, huh?
Actually, I'd say the opposite about them.
National Middle School Basketball Tournament
Regional Qualifiers
They're still developing.
They haven't reached their maximum potential.
They're terrifying children.
Someone called them the "Generation
of Miracles." I couldn't agree more.
There's no way they won't win.
That's not resolve talking.
It's certainty.
Congratulations on making
it through the first round!
Uh huh.
Yes.
Yeah.
You don't seem very excited!
Actually, why are you so excited?
We always win.
Kurokocchi's been really
happy since yesterday.
It was Tetsu's first time
in an official game.
Winning is good.
We'll keep doing what we're doing.
That's what I'd like to say,
but I do have one suggestion.
This team is strong.
Once our victory is certain,
we become unmotivated.
So I'm assigning a quota.
Each man must score 20 points per game.
Why not? Sounds fun.
Right, Aominecchi?
Sounds like a pain in the ass.
Huh? You're not into the idea?
Normally you're all over this kind of stuff.
Who cares, as long as we win?
I don't like having to do this, either.
But frankly, you seem especially unmotivated.
When scorers don't care about earning
points, it affects team morale.
Fine.
You want me to score, right?
Your ace is skipping practice, huh?
You're like Aomine-kun, so I
thought you might understand.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not sure, but he seems
different from Haizaki.
He still likes basketball, right?
Yes.
Maybe he stopped practicing
because he loves it so much.
All I can say is he's helped
you countless times before.
It's your turn to help him.
That's what friends do.
Yes.
If we win two more games,
we're going to nationals.
You'd better not lose until
we fulfill our promise.
Of course.
Later.
Thank you.
Ogiwara Shigehiro
Call Ended
Wow!
How did he make that?
The harder I try, the more
boring basketball becomes.
Basketball's just a game, anyway.
We can throw the rest of the games...
No, we can't.
What?!
Ice cream?
I can barely keep up with
the rest of the team.
Honestly, I don't understand how you feel.
But no matter how much stronger you are,
if I were your opponent, I would
never want you to hold back.
Besides, you'll find someone
better than you soon enough.
You're right.
The National Middle School Basketball
Tournament will now begin!
I'm hungry.
I want my snack now.
The opening ceremony just ended.
Can we get an interview?
How will your team finish this year?
Think you can win again?
Us, too?
Akashi's amazing.
He's used to giving model answers.
Aomine!
Hey, it's been a while.
Who's that?
How have you been?
That's Inoue-san from Kamizaki Middle School.
He's a power forward like Aomine-kun.
When they played last
year, it was a great game.
I'll beat you this year.
You can't beat me.
Kuroko!
Long time, no see!
Ogiwara-kun!
It's been two years.
You've changed.
So have you.
Um...
You've got rice on your face.
Huh?
You haven't changed.
Yeah, well...
Now that we're here,
I don't know what to say.
Yeah.
But I've really been looking forward to this.
We'll definitely win.
So will we.
Let's do our best.
Yeah.
The Teiko versus Kamizaki
game will now begin!
Bow!
Let's have a good game!
What is this?
Kamizaki
Teiko
Have you given up already?
Why? I was looking forward to this.
I thought I'd at least have
a good game against you.
You don't get it.
You're a monster.
No one can compete with you.
Is that sarcasm?
Tetsu, it's no use.
The only one who can beat me
is me.
Aomine-kun!
Shut up. Leave me alone.
I had a bad feeling,
but I wasn't expecting this.
Sorry, Kuroko. We lost.
What?
We were so close, but...
It's no use!
I'm so frustrated, I can't talk.
You guys won, right?
Yes.
I see.
Congratulations.
I'd like to cheer you
on, but I have to leave.
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize so much.
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry.
Preview
You've been on fire lately, Murasakibaracchi.
I just feel so powerful.
Yeah, but you're still eating too much!
I can't play if I don't eat.
We Are No Longer
I feel kind of irritated...