Huh.
All right, time's up.
Please pass your answer sheets forward.
How was it?
I couldn't do it.
It was hard!
Now pass these around.
My Dream
for the Future
"My dream for the future"?
When we're doing this,
it feels like the fact that the
Monolith will be destroyed
#10 Tokyo Area Defensive Battle
in three days is a lie.
I see you're hard at work.
Matsuzaki-san.
Thank you both for conducting
class during such a busy time.
It's fine.
Doing this takes our minds off of things, too.
That goes for the children, as well.
That's why I'm very grateful to the two of you.
I'm done, Rentaro!
Let's see...
My future dream is to marry Rentaro
and kiss him as much as I'd like every day!
I'm done.
Uh, right...
My future dream is to marry Onii-san
and kiss him as much as I'd like every day.
You guys...
All right, time's up.
Pass your print-outs forward.
Wha—
Hold it, Rentaro!
What about your answer to my proposal?
Proposal?
That's enough. Go back to your seats.
That ends the class for to—
Kisara-sensei, how much do
you have in your wallet?
Huh?
Uh...
All right, we're gonna go on a field trip.
Wow! That's amazing!
These are called The Flames of Revolution.
Flames of Revolution?
In the past, there have been two big battles
in the Tokyo Area, against the Gastrea.
The latter of those battles, the
"Second Kanto Battle," happened here.
The Flames of Revolution were
built to commemorate our victory,
and as a memorial for all of
the people who lost their lives
in the Gastrea War.
So it's the same as the Genan Festival?
Oh, you've heard of that, huh?
I know it, too.
It's that thing where there are pretty
shiny things in the sky, right?
We all let balloons fly, right?
That's a festival to honor all of the people
who lost their lives in the Gastrea War.
Speaking of, this year's Genan
Festival should be soon...
Rentaro-sensei, are we going to die?
Will we get to see the Genan Festival this year?
Don't be silly.
Don't you understand why I brought you all here?
The Flames of Revolution are proof that
the humans won against the Gastrea.
Even if the Monolith is destroyed,
the JASDF will protect us, so don't worry.
But...
Don't worry.
Kisara-sensei and I
will both be fighting on the front
lines as civil officers, too.
You two are going to fight, too?
Yeah.
Well, now that I've ended up as your teacher,
I'll definitely protect you.
Everyone come here!
We all agree!
Sensei, you pass.
That means we like you, Sensei.
There are five of us who want to
court you with the intent to marry.
I'm one of them.
Me, too.
Same here.
Wh-What?
But...
H-Hey...
Wai—
The JASDF will protect us,
so everything will be fine, huh...
But if they underestimated
Aldebaran's power even a little...
Satomi-kun, are you awake?
Kisara-san?
Would you like to take a walk with me?
Try touching it, too, Satomi-kun.
Varanium-corroding fluid is terrible, isn't it?
The Monoliths are made of blocks.
They transport them all at once by air,
and build them up on-site.
The target height is 100 meters.
As long as we can build the
blocks up to that height,
the normal Gastrea will
no longer be able to enter.
Wait a minute.
So even if we work desperately
to build this Monolith,
wouldn't everything be over
if Aldebaran injected the
Varanium-corroding fluid again?
No, wait. More importantly...
Why isn't Aldebaran going
after any other Monolith?
I wonder if Aldebaran used up all
its strength attacking the Monolith.
So much so that it had to rest...
I guess that might be possible,
but I think the problem lies with Monolith 32.
That can't be...
Actually, you're right.
I never thought of that.
All right. I'll look into Monolith 32 myself.
Thanks.
Kisara-san, what are you—
Satomi-kun, why don't you sit next to me?
It's... pretty amazing.
Yeah... It's beautiful.
Satomi-kun.
It might be inconsiderate to say this, but...
I'm happy right now.
At the agency, we have Enju-chan,
Tina-chan, and you, Satomi-kun.
It's like a family.
Just that makes me really happy.
Kisara-san?
But when I realized that this
happiness could end someday...
I got really scared.
I'm going to protect you, Kisara-san.
Enju, Tina, and I aren't going away.
Right... That's right.
Thank you, Satomi-kun.
The day's almost over.
Eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one...
Only two more days until
the Monolith is destroyed.
The underground shelter disclosed by
the government was opened today,
Disappear, Cursed Children    Go Away
and the 30% of the Tokyo Area
population selected by the lottery
have begun taking shelter.
However, citizens have voiced their
doubts about this evacuation plan.
Don't Forgive the Tyrannical Government!!
The government had already decided
who would go into the shelters!!
The plan...
She's still smiling.
What a creepy little brat!
What the hell are you doing?!
That voice... I'm sorry!
I promised you...
But I had no choice...
Move! If we don't take care of them,
they'll attack the human race again!
I'm a civil officer.
If you come any closer to her,
it won't be a warning. I will shoot.
So in the end, civil officers are
on the side of the monsters.
Can you stand?
Yes...
You seem to be okay.
H-Hey.
I'm sorry.
I made your face turn sad, Mr. Civil Officer.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you very much.
I now know your voice and face.
You're very much my type.
You dummy.
Hurry and go home.
Don't come here again.
Rentaro, I have returned!
We're back.
Hey. How was school?
It was fun again today.
I see.
Sorry to leave it all to you today, Kisara-san.
What's wrong?
When it was announced that you weren't coming
and it'd just be President Tendo teaching us today,
she was booed quite a bit.
No one likes Kisara-sensei anyway...
Er... I like you, Kisara-sensei.
Stop trying to cheer me up.
Oh, Ane-san!
Some weird guy dropped this off
for you while you were out.
Wow, that was fast.
They already finished investigating, I see. Thanks.
What is that?
You know, what I said
yesterday about Monolith 32.
I had it investigated immediat—
Kisara-san?
What does it say?
Huh? Hey...
It appears that Monolith 32 is a rather new Monolith built at the end of the Gastrea War.
The person who ordered it to be built was the current Vice Minister of Land, Infrastructure,
Transport, and Tourism, Tendo Kazumitsu. In regards to the production of the Monolith,
there was a special government order that it not be a general public works project or have a
competitive bidding system.
"Tendo Kazumitsu"...
Kazumitsu-niisan?
Kisara-san...
Hurry and get ready, Rentaro.
We will be late.
I know.
You actually had a whole day off today,
so why are you going to the school now?
You're just going to get more attached.
That may be...
But I have to at least go say hi to them.
Try not to make it too gloomy, Sensei.
I'll get ready quickly...
It's fine.
You were up late last night waiting
for Kisara-san, weren't you?
You can come with her once she wakes up.
'Kay...
All right. Let's go.
Yes!
What do you have there?
It's the Tenchu Girls DVD that you got for me.
Everyone's going to love it.
Then we're all going to play Tenchu Girls.
Rentaro...
Do you not enjoy being a teacher after all?
Nah, I enjoy it.
Rentaro, there are adults...
What is the matter, Rentaro?
Hey!
A b-bomb...
There's no doubt about it.
They're all my students.
Mirei...
Hm?
Her name.
This is Mirei.
Next to her is Ruka.
And next to her is...
Their names don't matter.
The victims are children with no family registry.
If you can identify them,
that's more than enough.
Unhand me!
Hey!
Stop struggling!
I told you to unhand me!
Rentaro!
Why did you come here?
I told you to go home.
But... what about school?
You don't have to go anymore.
Then... Then if I can't go today,
can I go tomorrow morning for just a bit?
Enju...
No! I want to see Micchan!
I want to see Sasana-chan!
I promised them that I would
show them Tenchu Girls!
See? I brought it like I promised!
So, please, Rentaro....
Please get her out of here.
Come on. Let's go.
No! Rentaro! Rentaro!
Stop struggling!
Unhand me!
Um... I wanna be a teacher!
I want a candy store!
I want to own a candy store!
I want to be a bride.
I want to be a florist.
My dream is to be a bride. Of course, I want to be Rentaro-san's bride...
...So when I become a beautiful woman, please marry me...
Satomi-kun, can you talk right now?
How's Tina?
She's finally starting to calm down.
We're doing okay.
I see...
Satomi-kun...
Apparently there were Varanium fragments
in the bomb to maximize casualties.
The guys who have a grudge against
the Cursed Children did this.
Kisara-san...
Who are we protecting?
Who are Enju and I
supposed to fight for?!
And for what?!
We're civil officers.
See justice done, Rentaro-kun.
Justice?
Exactly where is there any justice
in this cesspool of a world?
Tell me!
Listen.
If we're able to save the Tokyo Area,
there's a chance that some
people might throw away
a little of their hatred and
change how they think.
We're fighting for that small change,
not for rage or hatred.
What a shitty job being a civil officer is.
But that's exactly why it's worth doing!
Thanks, Kisara-san.
I'm going now. I have to go back to Enju.
Right. I understand.
Kisara-san? What's wro—
Why... There should still be one more day...
I see. The wind...
It's pretty much impossible to
predict air currents accurately.
We had totally miscalculated
the wind's movement!
Satomi-kun...
I know.
Enju.
Rentaro...
Monolith 32 has collapsed. Let's go.
#11 The Heart of Taurus, The Spear of Light
At this rate, we'll all die.
There is no way to defeat Aldebaran.
Let's go.
They are immortal!
Well, fancy meeting you here.