Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
It's all over now!
In the quarterfinals of the Winter Cup,
we beat Murasakibara Atsushi
of the Generation of Miracles
and his team, Yosen High.
I'll be waiting for you in the semifinals.
Of course.
I'm Just Playing As Hard As I Can
An interview?
Yeah, for Monthly Basketball.
It means we're in the spotlight, too.
What do you think they'll ask us?
Your thoughts on the games,
your hopes for the future.
That kind of thing.
Seriously? I'm super nervous.
We're not very good at that kind of thing.
Don't be so weird about it.
Just act natural.
That's right. Be natural.
You're right.
Okay, guys! Let's relax!
They completely failed to relax.
Good work, everyone.
Th-Thank you!
It's an honor to be interviewed
by Monthly Basketball!
The intensity of the Yosen
game still has us reeling.
Anyway, it's incredible that you made it to
the Winter Cup only two years
after your team formed.
On top of that, you've made it this far.
Th-Thank you.
Which game made the greatest
impression on you?
Well, it's hard...
...to choose just one.
Of course.
If I had to choose,
it'd probably be the Shutoku game.
That was the finals of the
Winter Cup preliminaries.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We can't lose!
That's our line!
Rebound!
Though it ended in a tie, I believe
both teams played the game their way.
I'd like to play Shutoku again.
Yeah.
It sounds like they're talking about us.
They're probably saying they'd
like to play us again.
I completely agree.
The tie was a little unsatisfying.
The game was simply too short.
That's what I'm saying.
Eventually we will win.
Of course.
Though we've got a huge
mountain to climb first.
Our opponents leave nothing to be desired.
The Eagle Eye is an incredible ability.
Yes. Apparently a lot of
Uruguayans possess this ability.
Eagle Eye, Uruguay. Eagle Eye,
Uruguay. Eagle Eye, Uruguay.
That's it.
Just ignore him.
If that's what Izuki says,
then maybe we should just assume a
lot of Uruguayans have the Eagle Eye.
We can't do that.
What about you, Kagami-kun?
Um, I'm just playing as hard as I can.
What do you think, Coach?
Kagami-kun leveled up during the Touou game.
I believed in the team, but honestly,
they achieved more than I expected.
What do you think about Aomine?
Next time I'll definitely win.
Didn't you win this time?
He won, but he said he'll win next time.
Kagami-kun is pretty modest.
That's not modesty. It's stupidity.
What about you, Dai-chan?
I lost. Next time I'll win.
That's all.
You're saying the exact same thing.
How do you feel about
advancing to the semifinals?
He says he's very proud.
I-I see...
Your next opponent,
Kaijo High, is very strong.
He says the last time we played
against them was in a practice game.
This will be our first real game
against them, so he's very nervous.
R-Right...
Thank you. We should get going now.
What about Kuroko-kun?
What?
We have to interview him.
Oh, right.
I forgot.
All of your games were amazing.
Thank you.
You supported your team against Shutoku...
The Vanishing Drive!
You won't get past me!
...and Kirisaki Daiichi...
...and Touou...
Kagami-kun!
...and against Yosen just now.
Well, personally speaking, um...
I'm just playing as hard as I can.
I didn't get to make a pun about Yosen.
That's my only regret.
Don't give up.
You'll have an opportunity
to make one eventually.
Idiots! Let's go.
Kagami-kun, do you have a minute?
What?
I'm really mad right now.
Why?!
We won the game!
The problem is what happened after that.
Are you happy
with what happened with Himuro-san?
You think you can stop me?
Interesting!
He jumped on the first release?!
Impossible...
He's like a bird!
I lost, Taiga.
As per our promise, I won't call
myself your brother anymore.
Yeah, I know.
I can't help that.
Win or lose, we're not brothers anymore.
That's the promise we made.
What are you two, idiots?
What?!
I told you to throw that out!
I couldn't throw it away.
If anything, it sounded to me
like you were asking me not to.
I won't deny how you felt then.
But is it really so difficult to
continue being brothers and rivals?
Himuro-san may have a lot on his mind, too.
But deep in his heart,
he should understand.
I just saw him walking outside.
Go make up with him.
Close game, Tatsuya.
Yes.
But I feel refreshed now.
Sorry, Alex.
I was...
Don't worry about it.
Athletes get worked up
before games all the time.
Anyway, it was a good game.
It was worth the trip.
Alex...
Hey, she's cute.
Are you foreign? Half?
Can you speak Japanese?
Who are you?
So you can talk.
Give me your number.
Let's go somewhere together sometime.
Come on.
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't casually touch me!
What?
Stop.
I'll hear what you have to say.
Huh? Were you in the game they just played?
You really do look like
a loser up close.
Did you say something just now?
He dunked it!
That's Kise Ryota of the
Generation of Miracles!
The game hasn't started,
and Kise's already on fire.
If we win this game, we'll play Seirin next.
I'm sure that's part of it, but I
don't think that's the only reason.
What?
Yesterday, while we were watching
videos of today's opponent...
That's impossible...
That guy...
What was that about?
Nothing...
I just saw someone I knew.
He really tried to hit me.
Isn't he an athlete?
What is he thinking?
What's this?
You're a better fighter than you look.
I hate guys like you.
Tatsuya!
Tatsuya...
I joined the Teiko basketball team as a
starter at the beginning of my second year.
In other words, before then,
someone else was the fifth man.
The most dangerous man on the team...
What are you doing?!
Who the hell are you?!
What?
What?!
Haizaki's going to be in the next game?
Yeah.
I thought he quit.
He's a major player on
Shizuoka's Fukuda Sogo.
Just remembering him is pissing me off.
That annoying guy is back.
He's not here.
Not that I expected him to actually warm up.
Kasamatsu-senpai, can I stop warming up?
What?
We just started...
Fine. Don't let your body get cold.
Okay.
Let go!
You just beat Atsushi.
I was watching.
You're not bad.
He knows Murasakibara? Who is this guy?
Let go of me, you brat!
Whoops...
How scary!
That's not how a woman kicks.
Alex! You bastard!
Stop!
Tatsuya!
Stay out of this.
You're not the only one who will
suffer if we get into a fight here.
What happened?
He suddenly tried to pick a fight with me.
He was hitting on Alex. When I
tried to stop him, this happened.
He did what?
A basketball player shouldn't
punch people on a whim!
Anyway, shut the hell up!
He doesn't care about basketball at all!
Hey, come on.
You've got some guts to
throw a basketball at me,
Ryota.
Kise?!
Hello.
You know this guy?
Well, yes.
His name is Haizaki Shogo.
He was a starter for Teiko
until I joined the team.
And
Akashicchi forced him to quit the team.
He was good, but as you
can see, he's violent.
He disappeared when I joined the team.
At least, he should have.
How did this come about?
No reason. I'm not doing this for revenge.
If I had to give a reason,
I'd say I'm just killing time.
I don't care about basketball,
but people starting calling you the
Generation of Miracles after I quit.
I thought I'd steal the title
from one of you five again.
I used to be a starter.
No one would have a problem if I beat you.
Besides, since you're my next opponent,
I have all the more reason to do it, Ryota.
After all, you became the fifth man
without beating me once.
He beat Kise?
Kagamicchi.
I need to ask you something.
Who's that beautiful blonde?
This isn't the time for that!
She's Tatsuya's and my master!
What? Seriously?
Yes, seriously!
I'm really sorry,
but could we end this here?
I more or less understand the situation,
but I need to fight him in the next game.
I'll beat him.
I don't care about being one of
the Generation of Miracles.
I told Kagamicchi that once.
But it's not so worthless I can just
let you have it for free, Shogo-kun.
I'm not trying to buy it
off you. I told you, Ryota.
I'm just telling you to hand it over if
you don't want it anymore, you idiot.
Why did you come here, Taiga?
Oh, right.
Sorry. I'll tell you another time.
I promise.
Kise!
You'd better not lose!
Of course I won't!
Hey, Kagami! Over here!
Welcome back. How did it go?
Kuroko,
do you know a guy named Haizaki?
Why do you know that name?
I just met him.
Where have you been, Kise?
You're just barely on time!
Sorry!
Everyone's ready!
Now we just have to win!
Let's go!
Yeah!
What?
He's on their team?
Kuroko, what do you think?
He was selfish and out of control.
But it's true he was a starter.
He's definitely strong.
Kaijo
Fukuda Sogo
The fourth Winter Cup quarterfinal game
between Kaijo High and
Fukuda Sogo will now begin!
Bow!
Good game!
Preview
Haizaki Shogo. He's insane...
But it's true he was strong enough
to be a starter for Teiko.
Kise will be okay, right?
Yes. Kise-kun will settle this on the court.
It's Mine