The playoff game between Teiko
and Kamata West will now begin.
Bow!
Let's have a good game!
This is the last game.
If we win, we're champions
for the second year in a row.
Do you have anything to say?
I'll make as many threes as I can.
That's all.
Nothing, really.
Let's finish this quickly
so I can have more snacks.
You guys are all over the place!
It doesn't matter.
Our team brings those scattered
personalities together.
We only need one thing in common.
Let's win!
Yeah!
Don't do anything for Aomine.
Huh?
Keep doing what you're doing.
Encouragement and consolation
would be counterproductive.
If he needs it, I'll do it.
We Are No Longer
Teiko
Kamata West
Aomine.
Hang back a bit.
I need to apologize to you.
I realized immediately you
possessed incredible talent.
That you loved basketball
more than your peers, too.
I knew this would happen
if your talents blossomed.
I knew, but I said nothing.
I couldn't say anything.
My desire to see your
talents blossom was greater than
my consideration for your feelings.
I'm sorry, but please.
Don't waste that talent.
What?
Your problem can't be resolved immediately.
But it may be eventually.
Don't give up.
I can't guarantee anything, but you'll
have nothing left if you give up.
Hey, that's...
Yes, I stole it.
You were listening?
I get it.
There's no turning back now, but...
I still want to win.
Teiko
Kamata West
We did it!
Now I can eat, right?
Want some?
Yes, please.
What? Seriously?
Why are you just standing there?
You can celebrate more.
Go.
You can at least be honest
about your feelings now.
That's that, I guess.
Yes.
The third-years quit,
but there's nothing to worry about.
We still have the Generation of Miracles.
I wouldn't be so sure.
What?
I'm actually worried.
They're too strong.
We'll have to help them
keep the team together.
They'll be fine.
As long as you're around, I'm sure—
He'll live.
But unfortunately, he can't coach anymore.
So as of today, I am your head coach.
We'll practice as normal starting tomorrow.
Got it?
You made the shot,
but there were two guys on you.
You should have passed the ball to me.
Really?
Who cares? I made the shot.
Mukkun's becoming stronger, like Aomine-kun.
But that's why I fear his sudden growth.
Murasakibaracchi, that was an amazing shot!
Really? But...
I just feel so powerful.
If I actually tried, I could
probably crush my teammates.
If I can make it from here...
You must play the five students known as
the Generation of Miracles in
every game, no matter what.
Chairman's Office
What? But—
Those heroes will do much
to publicize our school.
I heard they haven't lost
since they joined the team.
But they're still children!
We shouldn't give them special treatment!
I'm telling you to give
them special treatment.
Murasakibara-kun was amazing today.
Yeah, he was.
But I'm afraid of his growth, too.
It reminds me of how Aomine-kun changed.
Have you talked to him recently?
Not since nationals.
I want to do something,
but I don't know what.
Momoi-san?
You'll
always be together, right?
You'll be friends forever, right?
Yes. We'll always be
together.
Seijuro,
I heard you won the national tournament.
Yes.
What about school?
It's going smoothly.
Fine, then.
Keep doing what you're doing.
A member of the Akashi family
must excel in all domains.
Yes, Father.
Don't be ridiculous!
Quit letting me past you!
Even if you can't stop me, if you do
nothing, you're not helping at all!
I'm trying.
You're just too good.
None of us can stop you...
Damn it!
I don't have time for this!
Aomine-kun!
Wait, Aomine!
Aomine...
Head Coach...
As his coach, I can't overlook what he did.
But if forcing him to practice
will make him quit the team...
If you don't want to,
you don't have to come to practice anymore.
But you must come to games.
If you play and win, we won't have a problem.
Aomine-kun,
let's go back to practice.
Why?
Why practice?
Even though I'm guaranteed
to win any game I play?
Do I need to crush my disheartened
opponents even harder?
I understand how you feel, but...
You understand?
What is it you understand? Tell me.
What could someone so powerless understand?
Even I'm
jealous of you and the others sometimes.
But crying about it won't do any good!
That's why I do my best to pass—
Who do you pass to?
Even without your passes,
I could beat anyone myself.
The only one who can beat me
is me.
You haven't passed to me once since then.
It happened so recently,
but it seems so long ago.
I don't
even know how to receive your passes anymore.
I'm not sure Aominecchi
should be playing games whether
he comes to practice or not.
I don't know what the coach is
thinking, but I'm hesitant to agree.
About that...
If we don't have to practice
as long as we win,
I don't want to practice anymore.
Don't be stupid.
He'll never allow it.
But I can't lose.
Besides, I've only been listening to you
because I thought I couldn't beat you.
But lately, I think that might
not be the case anymore.
I don't want to listen to
someone weaker than me.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
You're joking, right?
Move.
If I have to do it by force, I will.
Don't flatter yourself.
One-on-one.
First to five.
What have I done?
Why couldn't I have trusted Aomine?
Why?
What?
No way...
Akashi               Murasakibara
I didn't think it'd be this one-sided...
Honestly, I'm pretty disappointed.
I can't listen to you anymore.
Whatever.
Once I make this, I'm doing what I want.
I, Akashi Seijuro, lost?
That's impossible.
It cannot be.
I must win, no matter my opponent.
No matter what.
Winning is everything.
Winners are validated and losers are denied.
Because I always win, I am always right.
What just happened?
I don't know.
Something's different.
Akashi-kun's not his normal self.
You're pushing your luck, Atsushi.
Don't make me so angry.
I never forgive those who defy me.
Not even my parents.
Akashi                          Murasakibara
5                             4
Well, I'm out.
Good work, guys.
Wait, Mukkun!
I just have to come to
practice tomorrow, right?
No, that's fine.
You can do as you please as long as we win.
What?
What are you saying, Akashi?
That's not what—
The same goes for you two, as well.
As long as we win,
I don't care what you do.
At our level, forcing everyone
to cooperate is pointless.
It's more effective if we don't.
But...
It sounds like you're telling
us not to use teamwork.
That's exactly right.
Teamwork will only get in the way
of the Generation of Miracles.
That's what I said.
You're late.
Looks like you failed.
Yes.
Then it can't be helped.
Give up on Aomine.
Once a plate cracks, it
will never be whole again.
But as long as it's still useful,
things are fine as they are.
Akashi-kun?
What was up with Akashicchi?
He was like a different person.
A different person...
He's exactly right.
That demeanor, which I've seen
many times before, is him.
What are you talking about?
No,
who are you?
I'm Akashi Seijuro, of course.
Tetsuya.
There's another, different Akashi inside him.
I can hardly believe it myself.
But...
I heard you told the others they
don't have to come to practice.
Teiko's doctrine is victory.
You made the right decision.
Prioritizing victory and
abandoning teamwork...
It is truly strong.
But can you really call this a team?
Murasakibara isn't coming today?
Neither is Aomine-san.
Things have changed.
What has?
It seems so inhuman now.
We've lost our sense of companionship.
It's been like this since the coach
and Akashicchi changed their policy.
You seem irritated, too.
I will follow the team's policy,
no matter what it is.
I just don't like how Aomine
and Murasakibara are acting.
Whatever the reason,
I can't understand why someone
wouldn't come to practice.
I can't be friends with someone who
doesn't do everything humanly possible.
You don't usually practice shooting.
Akashi-kun...
You don't need to do that anymore.
You're right.
Do you like basketball?
I don't understand your question.
Do I need to like it to win?
I'm not sure anymore.
The team has clearly changed
ever since you changed.
This again?
I haven't changed.
I always had two personalities.
The other simply took over.
I'm not hiding anything.
Whether or not you believe me is up to you.
But if you call that change,
then I say it was necessary.
The team didn't change because I changed.
I changed because the team changed.
Now that our talents are awakening,
we have no rivals outside anymore.
If there are any, they're within the team.
Forcing us to work together
could make the team implode.
We shouldn't work together anymore.
What are you...
That's why you and Daiki had a falling out.
The light became too bright for his shadow.
If you were comparing two
lights, it would be obvious.
Isn't anything more important than winning?
No.
Vague ideals are powerless.
You might
be right.
People change as they grow.
Maybe I was just desperate
for things to be like
they were before nationals.
If you want to quit, I won't stop you.
But if you're staying, you must accept it
if you want to keep being Teiko's sixth man.
Preview
Hello, Kuroko?
It's been a while, Ogiwara-kun.
Did something happen?
No, I'm fine.
That's fine, then.
If you ever want to talk, call me.
What is Victory?
Okay.