Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
It's finally time.
The Winter Cup semifinals.
Our rematch against Kaijo. Against Kise.
Let's do this.
Alex, what—
Why are you sleeping in my bed?!
It's super cold.
Don't take all the covers.
Then put some clothes on!
How dare you throw clothes at your
master using a move I taught you?!
Sheesh...
Alex, were you okay last night?
Yeah, of course.
What about Tatsuya?
It was just a scratch.
He went back to his hotel
immediately afterwards.
I see.
I can imagine why you showed up then.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Tatsuya felt the same way.
Yeah.
Anyway, are you ready?
Yeah, of course.
Huh?
I'll Take It
Your shoes fell apart?!
You idiot! Why do you only have one pair?!
What's wrong with you guys?
You don't have to be in sync like this, too.
You guys?
Hello.
Why are your shoes falling apart?
I could ask you the same thing.
We can't find my size anywhere.
Kagami-kun, your feet are pointlessly large.
What do you mean, pointlessly?
Hey, there's a place here.
I'm going to go ask.
Move, move!
Oh, sorry! I'm in a hurry...
Oh, crap!
I'm really sorry!
That jacket...
Did they have your size?
No.
Very well.
Huh?
I'll ask. She usually comes
through in times like these.
Their basketball shoes fell apart?
Both of them at the same
time? Are you serious?
Will they make it in time?
They'll probably be okay on time.
Our match is in the evening.
Whoops.
Sorry...
Oh, are you okay?
You should be careful.
Th-Thanks...
Coach!
Hey, you've got to protect your girl.
That guy...
Let's see.
Tape, cold spray, and...
Is that everything?
We need powdered drink mix, too.
What is it?
Give me more.
Y-Yes, sir.
What's with that guy?
He's eating more than Kagami.
And he's ripped. Is he a pro wrestler?
Tetsu-kun!
Sorry for calling so suddenly.
It's totally fine.
In fact, I'm so happy.
I appreciate you helping us look for shoes,
but what are you doing here?!
I could ask you the same thing.
Dai-chan has lots of basketball shoes,
and he said you could have some.
What? I didn't say that!
Don't be ridiculous, Satsuki!
You guys wear the same size, right?
29.5 centimeters.
How do you know that?!
Here.
Hey! You can't just take my shoes!
These are the same ones I wear...
He happened to have a pair.
They're a different color.
But you've always worn the same
type of shoes, right, Kagamin?
Her information network must be insane!
And did she say Kagamin?!
But...
This isn't a bad color.
Fine. If you can beat me
one-on-one, you can have them.
Why do I have to do that?!
I have a game after this!
We'll play a best of three.
It'll be quick.
I told you...
Just do it.
While we're at it, I'll give you a lecture.
Aomine-kun punched Haizaki-kun?
But you could say he had
to do it to help Ki-chan...
Wouldn't it be bad if someone found out?
Yeah.
But I don't think Shogo-kun
will do anything else.
I'm not sure how to put it,
but I think he's kind of
relieved Dai-chan stopped him.
He's twisted, but they both wore
Teiko uniforms at one point.
Satsuki,
I'm finished. Let's go.
Isn't it a little soon?
I said it wouldn't take long.
How did it go?
I crushed him.
Hey, wait!
One more! One more time!
I want the shoes, but more than
anything I hate ending on a loss!
Let's go one more time!
Don't you have a game?
What are you talking about?
Here.
They're yours.
What's going on?
Either way, I don't need them anymore.
I... I can't take these when I lost!
Take them back!
Just wear them, you idiot!
You're good the way you are.
And you're playing Kise, right?
If you play like trash because you're
wearing uncomfortable shoes, I'll kill you.
We'll postpone our match.
Thanks, then. I'll take them.
We're just postponing our game!
Just go!
Seirin High
Locker Room
Sorry I'm late.
You're late.
Did you get shoes?
Yeah.
Yes.
The Rakuzan-Shutoku game is starting soon.
Um, just how strong is Rakuzan?
They're a super strong school
that's been participating
in the Winter Cup since its inception.
They've won more tournaments
than any other school.
For the past five years they've
won all three major titles.
In a word, they're the
strongest high school team.
And their lineup this year is
the strongest it's ever been.
Akashi Seijuro of the Generation of Miracles.
Yeah, but he's not the only one.
Do you remember the Uncrowned Kings?
Five prodigies overshadowed
by the Generation of Miracles.
There's Kiyoshi and Hanamiya.
And the remaining three
players are all on Rakuzan.
I am unfamiliar with loss.
What?
Is that a snide remark?
No, I'm sorry.
It was just a thought.
It's not something I desire.
I'm simply interested in
it because it's unfamiliar.
I meant nothing more than that.
That's what you call a snide remark.
If that's the case, I will
introduce you to it eventually.
You're right.
If we ever face each other, I don't
think I'll be able to hold back.
Though I have no intention of losing.
By the way, Shintaro...
Shut up. I concede.
Midorima, what is that?
My lucky item.
Today's is nice and small.
What's your rank today?
Second.
What? You should at least take first.
I'll bury you.
But it's my fortune.
It's time! Let's go!
Yeah!
They're out!
The veterans of 11 consecutive appearances!
The veteran kings, Shutoku High!
They're here!
The strongest high school team!
The emperors since the beginning
of time, Rakuzan High!
I ate too much.
That's gross.
Why would you eat so much before a game?
I'm stronger when I eat meat.
Anyway, look! Look at them!
They're bad news!
Shut up.
They look seriously strong, dude. Crap!
Right, Akashi?
Yes, they are strong.
What? Sei-chan, you're starting today?
The coach already approved.
Really? That's good.
No one we've played against
so far stood a chance.
Maybe I should've eaten more.
I put the towels over there.
Okay.
Let's go.
Since they're so strong,
I thought they'd be more uptight.
They're pretty normal, though.
What are you talking about?
You're going to get burned.
There's nothing normal about them.
No. 4 is their captain, Akashi.
No matter how amazing a first year
is, that almost never happens.
What's even more incredible is
not a single player on the bench
or the rest of the team seems
to have a problem with it.
Neither do the Uncrowned Kings.
They all have their quirks
and a lot of pride.
All of them accept him as their captain.
As someone who knows them,
something seems really out of place.
At the very least,
you can't call someone who
leads so naturally "normal."
What a pain in the ass.
If you want to watch the game,
watch it yourself, Murochin.
Don't be that way, Atsushi.
Can I leave?
I have seaweed and salt chips.
I'll have some.
It's starting.
Who do you think will win?
Who knows?
When it comes to shogi,
Akachin's never lost a game.
Shogi?
They played a lot during breaks.
I can't imagine Akachin losing.
I'm going to win, Akashi.
That's impossible, Shintaro.
Have you ever forced me to concede?
Shogi and basketball are different.
They are the same.
I have never been wrong.
Because I always win, I am always right.
The first semifinal game of the Winter Cup
between Rakuzan High and
Shutoku High will now begin!
Bow!
Let's have a good game!
Yeah!
Just kidding.
Crap! Already?
You're always right?
Don't make me laugh, Akashi.
Don't talk like you know everything
when you've only ever won!
Come, Akashi.
As promised, I will teach you
about loss.
Really?
It didn't even touch the hoop!
He's like a high-precision machine!
He's got an aura around him.
Sheesh. Is he really a first year?
Takao, you're on Akashi. Got it?
Sure thing. Can I say something, though?
Sorry if I can't handle it.
No, do your best!
Are you even trying?
I'll do my best!
But even Midorima's scared of him!
I'm not scared!
Don't turn on us!
Focus.
Focus, focus, focus.
He's fast! But...
Nice pass!
Rakuzan
Shutoku
The first quarter's over!
Neither the kings nor emperors
are giving any ground!
Atsushi, was he really
the captain of your team?
Yeah.
What's going on?
He's definitely good.
He's got the skills, and he
has a broad field of vision.
He's as good as you'd expect
a point guard to be.
But he's not so good that I can't keep up.
Is this really the captain of the
Generation of Miracles, Akashi Seijuro?
The game's going well.
No changes to our game plan.
I'll leave the detailed
game-making to you guys.
If you need to fix anything,
listen to Akashi.
Yes, sir!
Akashi's definitely not holding back.
The course of this game
closely resembles shogi.
Right now we're still feeling each other out.
They'll probably start making their move...
...soon.
Anyway, we should try to make the first move.
The break is over!
The second quarter will now begin!
Don't underestimate me, Akashi.
It was rather leisurely of you to so obviously
watch and wait during the first quarter.
Surely you don't think you can
win without using your "eye."
I don't underestimate you, Shintaro.
If anything, I couldn't
be playing more carefully.
One must be careful how
they play their trump card.
However,
at this rate the game may
end before I even play it.
What did you say?
They're
double teaming Midorima!
And Shin-chan doesn't know what to do?
We expected this from Rakuzan!
Their defense is strong!
But we knew it would be!
All right, a one-on-one! Come on!
What are you getting so excited about, huh?
I'll run you over with Kimura's truck!
Huh? He's good at dribbling!
Yeah!
Hey! How could you just let them pass you?
Sorry.
You're not asleep, are you?
Keep it together.
Sorry, sorry.
Kotaro.
I'll get them back!
Don't be mad, Akashi!
That's fine, but if you don't
want to play, I'll sub you out.
I'm fine!
No one's better at dribbling than me!
Hayama!
Will he get his revenge already?
What? You're not going anywhere.
No, I'm going to do it.
Three should do it.
Three?
The harder you dribble,
the faster the ball travels and the
more difficult it is to control.
But that...
If you had trouble understanding
me earlier, allow me to rephrase.
How is he dribbling like that?
My eyes can't keep up!
It disappeared?
I don't need to do anything myself.
That's all.
Preview
Shintaro, you are strong.
However, I know how this will end.
Don't underestimate Shutoku, Akashi.
I know you better than anyone else.
I will defeat you.
I Don't Know
You are determined.
Let's see how long that spirit lasts.