Teiko Middle School
The Teiko Middle School basketball club.
Even amidst their brilliant record,
there was a generation of five prodigies
known as the "Generation of Miracles."
Kise Ryota.
Midorima Shintaro.
Aomine Daiki.
Murasakibara Atsushi.
Akashi Seijuro.
They are threatened by Seirin High's
shadow and light.
Rebound!
He pushed it in!
We won't lose!
Don't let them pull any farther ahead!
We'll win!
Do everything it takes to pull ahead!
An alley-oop!
They're 15 points ahead!
Kaijo is screwed!
The ace's job is to lead his team to victory.
If I don't play now, I'm not the ace!
We'll beat
Seirin!
This is Perfect Copy!
We were naive to think we could stay ahead.
We can't win without
stopping his Perfect Copy.
We'll win!
I'll put everything I have on the line!
This Time
Kaijo
Seirin
Kise's extending the limit
of his Perfect Copy?
It's likely.
That would mean our lead isn't safe anymore.
If we don't do something, we're screwed.
Um...
There may be a way
to stop Kise-kun.
I can't talk to him.
He's really focused.
He's never seemed more
dependable than he does today.
We can do it.
A comeback is well within our reach.
Good. We're in control.
The team is quiet, but morale is high.
This is when miracles happen.
I see.
It'll be hard, but with the right timing...
We may be able to stop Kise.
Okay!
We can't afford any mistakes.
Focus, guys.
Even if our plan succeeds,
Kaijo's team isn't just Kise.
Don't stop until the final buzzer sounds.
Be even more careful with
passes and teamwork.
Don't miss any easy shots.
Do everything you can to keep our lead!
Let's go, Seirin!
Fight!
Yeah!
Shit! He can use
Akashi's Emperor Eye on defense, too?
All right!
Okay!
Crap!
Don't worry, Hyuga.
Change gears.
Yeah.
Offensive mistakes are bad,
but this is the bigger problem.
I'm counting on you.
Stop Kise's Perfect Copy!
What?
Kuroko's on Kise?
Kurokocchi, what do you think you're doing?
It's obvious.
Kagamicchi's waiting behind you.
You're trying to do what you did before.
Let me pass you and steal the
ball when Kagami stops me.
But I've beaten it once already.
Surely...
You're not trying to use the same move!
No, it's different this time.
Eagle Spear!
Got it!
This is...
Taiga, Kuroko, and Izuki's triple-team!
The left side is open.
But Tetsu let him pass on the right,
leaving Kise's center
of gravity on the right.
It's too late to cross over now.
The timing's perfect!
There's nowhere to run!
Impossible...
Did he just use Kuroko's passing skills?
He used the centrifugal force of the spin
to pass the ball from a standstill.
Crap! He's too fast!
So high!
He made the alley-oop!
Kise's unstoppable!
Yes!
Kagami-kun!
It doesn't matter what you do.
No one can stop me now.
He's strong.
Wow! That didn't stop him, either.
If only that were their only problem.
What?
Seirin is falling into a pattern of failure.
At this rate, Kaijo will swallow them whole.
Looking good, Kaijo!
They're catching up!
They've got this!
Go, Kaijo!
Counterattack!
This isn't like Izuki.
He's practically begging
for the ball to be stolen.
I'll stop him this time!
What?
Could it be?
A Phantom Shot?
No way!
I understand the passes...
But Phantom Shots can't be
made without Misdirection.
No, he's not using it!
By recreating the irregular form
and shooting a high trajectory
shot like Midorima,
Kise's quick shot flew out
of his field of vision!
Kaijo's closing the gap!
Kaijo
Seirin
They might make a comeback!
Oh, man!
Go, Kaijo!
Kaijo! Kaijo! Kaijo!
Nice! Keep up the pressure!
Ow!
We can do it!
Kobori-senpai, you, too?
I'm doing great, too.
Pass me the ball anytime.
Got it.
Let's go! I'm ready to jump!
Kaijo! Kaijo! Kaijo!
What is this?
Most of the fans are cheering for Kaijo.
It's like we're the bad guys.
The fans are on Kaijo's side.
They subbed out their ace
but desperately hung on.
Their ace returned in their time of need,
and now they're catching up.
Anyone would want to root for Kaijo.
Seirin will suffer for it.
The fans go wild each time the gap closes.
They're delighted when they fail.
No one cheers when they score.
The pressure is rising, and they're
out of their comfort zone.
It's incredibly difficult to play
normally under these circumstances.
Over here!
Hyuga shot an air ball?
Nice, Kuroko!
That was close!
Too bad!
It's not Kaijo's ball!
Damn, this is hard!
Time out.
Coach?
We just took one.
Hyuga-kun's words during the last time out...
We can't afford any mistakes.
Focus, guys.
I should've noticed then.
"No mistakes, no failures."
That kind of thinking tenses you
up, leading to more mistakes.
Make one mistake, and it's a vicious cycle.
Thinking about it leads to more mistakes,
dragging down the quality of your play.
Crap!
Kiyoshi fumbled the ball?
Crap! Run back!
Too slow!
You barely caught up,
but your stance is a mess!
You're wide open.
Kagami!
Go!
Kaijo! Kaijo! Kaijo!
Pushing, white No. 10!
Two free throws!
Of course!
That was way too strong!
Did he do it on purpose?
Sorry...
What is Kagami doing?
They'll hate us even more.
No, it wasn't on purpose.
He's just desperate.
I don't give a shit if we're villains.
Villains only exist and lose
in the world of fiction.
This is our story!
We decide how it goes!
Villains only lose in the world of fiction.
This is our story!
We decide how it goes!
Kagami...
That was lame.
I'm amazed you came up with such a lame line.
How could you even say that?
Well, you said, "I'm your shadow!"
It's our story! Our story!
Stop saying that!
Kagami, you're a script writer?
Wow...
Please shut up...
It's just, you know...
Don't worry about the fans!
We'll definitely win!
We know. You don't have to tell us.
Now I'm relaxed.
Let's enjoy the last two minutes.
Hyuga, that's my line.
But the situation hasn't changed.
We need to do something.
Excuse me.
Kagami-kun's lame line made
me think of something.
Haven't you said enough?
What is it, Kuroko?
This time I know how we
can stop his Perfect Copy.
Kaijo
Seirin
Seirin, time out!
You can do that?
I'm not sure.
But it's possible.
Perfect Copy allows him
to recreate the abilities of all the
members of the Generation of Miracles.
He can combine and use them
in response to the situation.
Since he's recreating them,
they're the same as the
ones we've faced before.
And we have a player who's faced
them as more than an equal.
Predict who he's going to copy?
Perhaps "induce" would be
more correct than "predict."
It's the only way Seirin can stop Ryota.
Misdirection requires
more than just technique.
You must also interpret the actions
and habits of your opponent.
Since Tetsuya observes people
on a daily basis, it's possible.
He can use the trends and habits of
Kise's play to restrict his next play.
But depending on the situation,
he has countless options.
It will be incredibly difficult for even
Tetsuya to manage that in two minutes.
If you need to observe him,
why don't you come out?
No. I want to watch Kise-kun from up close.
I won't be any help for a while,
but will you let me stay on the court?
Fine.
Unfortunately, Kise-kun doesn't
seem to be running out of steam.
Either way, we can't win
without stopping Kise.
We'll have to let Kuroko handle it.
Let's go! We haven't lost yet!
Don't give up before it's over!
Seirin, fight!
Yeah!
They're really hyped up.
Be careful.
Seirin's just getting started.
Two free throws!
He made both!
It's totally within reach!
We're counting on you, Kagami.
Letting Kuroko observe Kise means
sending the ball his way
on offense and defense.
But one mistake could cost us the game.
We need to hang on and draw
out all the plays we can.
Got it.
This expression...
He's planning something.
Little tricks won't work
against his Emperor Eye.
Full speed drive!
He's fast!
Yes!
It's no use! He can't pass him!
He stopped at that speed?
His legs are amazing!
Go back!
Will it be Aomine's drive,
Akashi's Emperor Eye, or some combination?
Damn it! There's no point in thinking!
Just focus!
Why isn't he trying to pass him?
Could it be?
Midorima?
Crap!
If he shoots a high trajectory three now,
we'll lose time while it's in the air!
Kuroko will have way less to observe!
He faked Midorima-kun's three?
They have a lead, but since
Seirin needs time to stop Kise,
that's the worst move he could use.
That's why his fakes are working.
All his choices give Kaijo
the strategic advantage.
A one-man alley-oop!
Change gears!
Let's get them back!
He's already here?
Crap! It's going out of bounds!
Don't give up!
We have to win!
Hyuga!
Hyuga-kun?
I'm okay.
Sorry, Fukuda.
Uh, it's okay...
Captain! You're bleeding...
Huh?
I cut my lip a little.
Don't worry.
Anyway, you do what you have to do.
I believe in you.
Yes, sir!
Seirin's desperate...
Amazing...
Don't be beat, Seirin! Keep trying!
Seirin! Seirin!
Kaijo! Kaijo!
Kaijo
Seirin
He made it!
Kaijo made a comeback!
Yes!
All right!
Nice!
The next attack is Seirin's last
chance to see Ryota's play.
Whether they succeed or fail,
only Kaijo's attack will be left.
If Tetsuya doesn't have an
answer now, Seirin will lose.
Preview
You haven't given up yet, have you?
No. We won't lose.
I am the ace.
No matter what Seirin does,
I'll lead Kaijo to victory.
You are my greatest rival.
The Greatest Player
I'll keep fighting until the end.