We continue to offer funeral songs to the ones selected out.
Hence, the Undertakers.
We will resist GHQ,
who rules this country as though they own it.
We will fight
against everyone and everything that attempts to select us out.
Self-Posession
Now, I think you all know this,
but GHQ has declared a Level 2 state of emergency
in connection with yesterday's incident in Roppongi.
If any of you have info on these terrorists who call themselves the Undertakers,
you're supposed to report it to the authorities immediately.
Okay, one last thing.
Our class has a new transfer student.
Come on in!
A girl!
Hey, she's cute!
This is Yuzuriha Inori.
This... is a joke, right?
What's up with you?
Wait, I've seen her from somewhere before...
Inori?!
For real?!
From Egoist?! There's no way!
It's the real thing.
Awesome!
So, everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
I'm yours
Say, there's lots of happiness in this world, isn't there?
Someday, if we're together
Even if someone calls you a liar
and tries to hurt you with cruel words,
even if the world does not try to believe you
and places a crown of thorns upon your head,
I can take your side, and yours alone
I know your pain and loneliness
So everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
My name's Kusama Kanon. I'm the class rep.
Ask me if you have any questions, okay?
I said I wouldn't join the Undertakers,
Do you have all your books and things already?
If you're missing any, I'll go borrow them from the teachers.
so why did she come to my school?
We have P.E. today, so—
I-Inori!
Um... So, what do you think about the Undertakers?
Why would you randomly ask something like that, Souta?!
Well, Egoist's songs seem kind of Undertaker-ish, you know?
So I thought maybe she liked them...
Yeah, right!
Oh, so, what are the other Egoist members like?
Hey, can I have your autograph?
Me too, me too!
Cut it out, guys.
You're putting Yuzuriha on the spot.
Sorry. This guy's name is Tamadate Souta, and he's a huge fan of yours.
So forgive him for being rude, okay?
Oh, and I'm Samukawa Yahiro, by the way.
Me, Yahiro and Shu over there
formed this club called the Contemporary Visual Culture Club,
and I was wondering... um...
I'm telling you, man, chill out.
You guys, too.
We're going to be in the same class for the rest of the year.
So let's just take it slow, okay?
Sorry, Inori.
Sorry, my bad.
But I just know that her coming here
must have something to do with me...
One, two, three, four.
Man, when you see Inori in person, she's kinda like a doll, huh?
Hmm? Yeah, I guess so.
Like, she looks more like CG in real life, or something...
How could you say that, Shu?!
Inori is not CG! Open your eyes, moron!
Don't you ever say that to her face, got it?
Inori's sensitive and easily hurt, you know!
He called me a moron...
Why doesn't anybody think about how my feelings can get hurt?
There I go being selfish again, huh...
Anyway, I'll just try not to get involved with her anymore!
I-Inori?!
Why?
What are all these boxes?
W-Wait!
Inori!
What the heck was that for?!
Hey! Wait!
Why are you at my apartment?! And why can you open the door?!
Funell did it for me.
Uh...
Excuse me, Inori?
Don't be polite.
Uh, I really can't be rude right off the bat...
Hey, Shu.
Wh-What?
I'm starving.
Ow.
So... what do you want to eat?
Rice balls.
Well, Keido, how will you take responsibility for what happened in Roppongi?
Rest easy, Sir.
I will be putting Major Segai in charge
of all Undertaker-related matters from now on.
Segai?!
Who is he?
Are you familiar with the Norma Gene?
It's a genetic drug that's been in vogue lately.
Am I right, Dr. Ouma?
Yes, sir. It was an incidental discovery
during the development of the Apocalypse Virus vaccine.
When I assigned him to figure out its distribution channels,
he gave me a whole picture of the industry within a week.
Then he's sharp?
Almost too sharp.
If we give him worthy prey, he'll hunt it with all his energy...
and hang it up to dry.
My apologies, that was a work e-mail.
Now, where were we?
Ah, yes. "To talk, or not to talk, that is the question," I believe?
Let's roll him.
Man, this is a problem...
How do I explain it to Mom when she gets home?
Ouma Haruka. Senior Researcher at Sephirah Genomics.
Only comes home about once a week.
Unlikely to be back here for several days.
So you've done a whole background check.
A burden?
Ouma Shu, am I a burden to you?
Um... you're not a burden, but...
I just don't know why you're here...
To protect you.
C-Coming!
Yo, sorry to come so late.
What's up?
I just remembered something.
This is that movie we were talking about. Wanna watch it?
Um, thanks... You came all the way here for that?
You were acting weird today. I thought so, anyway.
Did something happen yesterday?
Good question... I'm not really sure.
I see.
Huh?
Why are you...
A message came. Come with me, Shu.
Err, there's a really good explanation for this!
What would that be?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, see you tomorrow!
Tell me if anything happens, all right?
Thanks, I will!
Is Samukawa Yahiro your friend?
Probably, I guess.
He's a great person.
He really looks after the people around him, and he can be sympathetic...
Totally different from me.
Don't you have any friends, Inori?
Does a person have to have friends?
Yeah, I just finished. The OAU is very interested.
They gave me a condition, though. I'll report in more detail later.
Thanks for coming.
Eh...
That's some outfit.
You don't look like a wanted criminal at all.
You can't change the world just by running around with guns.
Tsugumi, anyone tailing them?
All clear!
More importantly, what are you planning by sending Inori to my school and apartment?
We have a problem.
Someone witnessed us during the battle yesterday.
If this person were from the fort, I could have taken care of it,
but it seems it's an outsider.
A student from your school.
From my school? Why would...
The Norma Gene. Have you heard of it?
Yeah, I think it's some drug that's really popular these days...
That guy was there to buy it?
During the deal, this person was called "Sugar".
Though that's probably an alias, of course.
There's a good chance you and Inori were seen.
Find this person.
Are you kidding? How many students do you think go to my school?!
There's no way to find one person!
Actually, there is.
Draw out the Void.
I get it, you can see them.
You can tell what people's Voids are, can't you, Gai?
Oh.
I mean, you couldn't have made that plan in Roppongi if you hadn't known.
It's convenient how quickly you figure things out.
It's true. I can see Voids.
And in that battle, I sensed the presence of the witness,
and that witness's Void.
Under the Temporary Disaster Law currently in effect,
terrorists have no human rights.
If the witness identifies you, you won't escape harm.
I trust you understand?
I've informed Inori of the Void's shape.
If you value your peaceful everyday life, protect it for yourself.
Shu?
It's okay. I can do it.
Have you memorized the Void rules?
First, Voids can only be drawn from people seventeen years old or younger.
The reason is unclear. Or else it's a secret from me.
Second, when you withdraw a Void from someone,
that person loses their memories of the time surrounding the event.
That's from the shock of the intron memory field being released, I think?
But that works in my favor.
Anyway, right now I need to experiment.
Hare will forgive me even if I screw up...
I think.
Now!
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
Wow.
He's got guts!
Why, Shu? If you'd just said something, I would have...
Shu.
Hold it right there, Ouma Shu!
Scum!!!!
It's over.
He needs to get that sex drive under control.
What a total creep.
And I was on track to get through three years of school without standing out!
Maybe everyone could do me a favor, and just forget about this?
Or die?
How did I screw it up?
Her eyes, maybe.
Eyes?
You weren't looking at them.
But that's necessary when you're drawing out a Void.
That's another rule?
But I can't do that!
I get nervous when I make eye contact with people,
and I lose my grip on the conversation...
Shu.
Yes?
Do you think I'm looking into your eyes?
I'm looking in between your eyebrows.
Gai told me the important thing is for them to think you made eye contact.
I'm gonna bring someone down this time!
Souta!
What's wrong, Shu?!
Forget everything!
Is this it?
No.
Yeah, I kinda figured it wasn't...
But I've got the hang of it now!
Just you watch. Now, this starts for real.
Here I go!
Pardon me!
No.
Sorry, pardon me!
Seriously, I'm sor...
Huh?
What is this?!
Okay, so what Void am I supposed to be looking for?
Shears.
Really?
Uh-huh. You'll understand when you see them.
What are Voids? Why do they come in so many forms?
A Void's form and function
reflect things like the person's fears or complexes.
You could say it's the shape of their heart.
Voids are... the shape of their hearts?
Huh?
Then... why is yours...
a sword?
There you are!
Ouma Shu!
Crap!
Shu!
This way!
Hold it right there!
This is rough! I've done nothing but run around since yesterday.
Yeah, but if you'd joined the Undertakers, they'd have put you through worse.
True.
The class rep will probably cool down after a while,
so let's apologize to her then.
Yeah... but will she actually forgive me?
She might just cut me into pieces with a pair of shears.
What, are you talking about that movie from last night?
I've been thinking. Your tastes are kind of unusual, you know?
Where did that come from?
I'm not saying that's a bad thing.
I'm just trying to say appearances can be deceiving sometimes...
Sugar.
So I was seen.
And now you're judging me?
No... I mean, knowing you, you must have had your reasons, right?
Some kind of reason...
Shut up!
You're gonna keep pretending to be friends?!
It was all over from the moment you called me "Sugar"!
So don't pretend that everything's okay!
It's because guys like you just assume I'm harmless
that I have to keep acting that way!
I have to keep pretending to be someone I'm not!
It's all your fault!
Yahiro!
This is Yahiro's...
That's that, then.
No!
You can't do that.
Why not?
Gai said he succumbed to temptation,
and he'll be a threat to us if we don't eliminate him now.
What do you guys know?!
Shu...
Maybe it's weird,
but I don't want to forget the persona Yahiro worked so hard to build!
I don't want to just assume it was all a lie!
So put that down, Inori!
If you say so, Shu.
Thank you.
After that, when Yahiro woke up, we made a promise to each other.
We promised he wouldn't tell anyone about the Undertakers,
and I wouldn't tell anyone about the Norma Gene.
I felt like it was the first time Yahiro and I really met.
Report from Inori! "Witness problem solved. Steer clear from now on."
Oh.
Is that okay?
I'll let them do what they want.
Shu... can I stay with you forever?
I want to know you. And the others. So...
I-I think you can do what you want.
What's this?
Hey, who are they?
GHQ?!
Sorry.
What?
What gives, Yahiro?
What gives?!
Ouma Shu.
You...
are under arrest.
These days you love me no more
nor am I still treasured by you
Now I am all alone
What did you tell me when we parted?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender