The reality of the destruction around us fills our mind
The raging rain sounds like a storm of tears
Notice
that your eyes were given to you to acknowledge others,
that your voice was given to you to tell others how you feel
and that your hands were given you to hold those dear to you
All living things
bear witness to my song
Your heart contains all its truth
Even when all you see in your path are storms
remember that your strength is no coincidence
and on it,
rely
Mana will be reborn by consuming Inori.
Our lost Eve...
You're too late,
Shu.
That can't be!
What's going on?
What's this light?!
Something's starting to happen!
There's no doubt about it.
Okay. We'll hold them off here.
You go up as quickly as possible.
Ayase! Cover them!
Roger! But...
You really got me last time.
But this time will be different!
Now, I have the Gespenst!
Tsugumi, you still can't take back control?
The defenses suddenly got stronger!
I keep trying to erase it, but it keeps coming back like a zombie!
Someone on par with Tsugumi...
Kenji...
Is that you?
Good morning, Triton.
I see you're awake, Mana.
Shu!
I'm so happy!
You came for me!
It was terrible!
There was this annoying woman who kept getting in my way!
But it's all right now.
I crushed her and took this body for my own!
What was she thinking?!
That manmade monster.
Stop!
Shu!
Inori's no monster!
She cried for me!
You look and sound the same, but she's not like you!
She's human!
You're mean, Shu.
Your big sister loves you so much.
I loved you even when my body was blown to shreds.
And yet,
you reject me again, Shu!
Stop right there.
Gai?
Leave the rest to me.
You hurt me, Shu.
If you hurt someone, you must be prepared to receive the same amount in return.
I won't forgive you
even if you apologize.
This is...!
It's started, Gai.
What's going on?!
There's genomic resonance values higher than Lost Christmas coming from Tokyo!
It's even affecting the Endlave remote control system!
This is...
The Fourth Apocalypse has started.
The evolution and selection of life on this planet.
Yahiro!
Discard our weak bodies and achieve an eternal consciousness within the crystals.
That's the next stage.
The Voids were just a sign of a new world,
where hearts are material!
It's because you're using normal weaponry!
We'll crush you!
We won't let you!
Don't underestimate us, you son of a bitch!
Ayase! Connect with a cable!
Tsugumi! An evasion program!
Tsugumi?!
You bitch!
Damn!
What?!
Lieutenant Daryl!
The Void Genome Emulator is still being tested!
Don't overuse it!
What are you talking about?
I won't stop until I've butchered them all!
Souta!
Gai!
Back in Roppongi, you said you'd save Mana!
You told me to stab you to save her!
How did it come to this?!
You can't understand, Shu.
You were chosen, yet you chose to let go!
You could never understand!
How is it, Kurosu?
The girl you tried to save is ending the world.
I win.
You did this to the world...
To Shu... just for that?
I will not deny it.
Are you going to shoot me,
Haruka?
I can't let them through.
I will hold them off.
For him...
How persistent!
Damn, I can't keep up!
Tsugumi.
Hold out until my signal.
Can you do that?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Back then, I would've let you
have Mana and the place of Adam.
But now, you're unworthy.
Die, Shu.
My body's numb.
Am I going to die here?
With everyone's Void's in me?
Don't give up, Shu.
You can still move.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Please, everyone...
use me!
What?
What's going on?
Kenji,
it's checkmate.
There are people
who trusted me with their lives.
I can't die here.
I will get Inori back for sure.
Now!
Ayase, sorry for the wait!
Let's go!
Leave remote control to me!
Gai...
Don't get in my way.
I'll defeat you with all I have!
That voice...
I knew it. You're there, aren't you?!
Tsugumi!
Aye!
What?!
If I take you out, I can be myself!
I can be Daryl the butcher!
Shut up! We'll fry you first!
Inori?
No!
We did it?
Brother!
In the end, the winner was neither Kurosu nor I.
Go, Haruka.
Gai!
It's okay, Shu.
Just stay yourself.
Where am I?
The place where selection converges.
The world beyond the Apocalypse.
Gai...
This is
the utopia of the Da'at.
This whole planet will turn into
memories inside the crystals.
I have been celebrated as a king,
but in the end...
I have always been afraid of being selected out.
That's the reason why
I wanted Eve...
Mana.
Back there,
when you stabbed us in Roppongi,
I believed that Mana would be freed that way.
But Da'at,
the will of the natural selection
will not allow Mana to die.
Even if she died, she'd just be reanimated again.
There is just one way to save her.
That is to let her finish her role.
That's why I risked it.
I would become the devil myself and bring about the Apocalypse.
Then you would come to stop us.
My role ends here.
Gai!
Now go
and save Inori.
Shu...
Don't blame yourself...
I...
got a lot of feelings from you.
It's all
thanks to you.
Hey, Shu...
Where are you?
Shu?
Shu...
Please stay with me.
I'm on your side.
Okay?
Inori...
Let's go together.
This feeling!
I felt it too!
It's Ouma!
Shu! Are you going to become the new Savior!?
The entire framework is in havoc because of the Genome Crystal!
The whole building will collapse soon!
Guys...
Dr. Ouma! Are you unhurt?
You?
If you get another chance,
be more kind to people!
Deep down, you were a nice guy, Daryl!
I can feel the hearts of everyone flowing towards me.
Their memories...
Even the people who hated me were born
and loved by someone.
Inori...
Take it.
Inori!
Wait! Shu's still in there!
I know!
But, I can't let you die here either!
Shu!
Hey, Yahiro!
You're early.
You're busy with work?
Kinda.
But I left early today.
Can I sit here?
Sure.
Ayase, you're okay with an Earl Gray?
These days you love me no more
That's so nice of you, Tsugumi.
Just for today.
Teacher exams are coming up, so I'll turn into a demon again at home.
nor am I still treasured by you
He's not here yet?
He'll be here.
Now I am all alone
He was looking forward to it.
Ah, there he is!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
What did you tell me when we parted?
Sorry for the wait.
The words hung in midair and never reached me
Then, to this year!
Cheers!
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender
Thank you
very much
for watching
until now!
Production I.G., Team 6