Medic!
Serious damage to Unit 322! Emergency bailout!
Second Lieutenant Saen was injured in the backlash!
What the hell... just happened?
How dare you do that to Saen!
Stay away!
So, everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
I'm yours
Say, there's lots of happiness in this world, isn't there?
Someday, if we're together
Even if someone calls you a liar
and tries to hurt you with cruel words,
even if the world does not try to believe you
and places a crown of thorns upon your head,
I can take your side, and yours alone
I know your pain and loneliness
So everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
So that's the power of a Void?
Now, Ogumo.
Yes, Commander.
Inori...
Wake up!
Inori!
What was that?
Ouma Shu.
I'll give you fifteen seconds.
Recover Inori and get out of there.
H-Huh?!
Tsugumi! Where's my next target?
Direction: ten o'clock. Distance: 400!
That's too far away! Don't you have a closer one?
You can withdraw if you don't like it! You're working too hard anyway, Aya!
Your poor craft's had about all it can take!
But I want to do all I can...
Hey, there's a stocky one. Glad I rushed over here!
He's fast!
Bailout!
Huh? Where's the screaming?
That's it?
That's just no fun.
What? You're telling me a foot soldier did this?!
The battle footage is too distorted to say for sure, but I believe so, sir...
A personal anti-Endlave weapon?!
How can I report that to the higher-ups?!
Second Lieuteneant Daryl Yan entering.
My goodness, Lieutenant Yan! Welcome!
To think the Major General's own son would honor our mobile cockpit with a visit!
You certainly live up to your reputation for bravery and hard work.
Are you here on your father's orders?
No, I came on my own initiative.
I was bringing a new-model Endlave to the operations center,
and I heard the report that a battle started, so I thought,
"sounds like fun!"
I see. Well, then, we'll be glad to have your help, Lieutenant.
Cut the jokes.
You expect me to touch that fatty flesh?!
I'll do as I please, got it?
And if you get in my way...
I'll tell Daddy on you.
That little shit!
Expand the search area! Capture and interrogate everyone,
women and children included!
Um...
I'm sorry, Gai.
Ah, Ayase. Report your status.
I lost my craft.
I apologize. It's my responsibility.
I see.
Yes, that is a shame.
I gave you the cruel order to hold your position for eighteen minutes
in that old-model Endlave, and you rose to that task.
And yet you claim responsibility...
I suppose that means I'm not a fit commander?
N-No! It happened because of my failure! I...
I'm kidding.
I'm glad you're all right, Ayase.
And Aya's heartbeat soars to the top of the chart!
Shut up, Tsugumi!
Um, so...
Are you awake now?
Inori.
Gai... did I get the job done?
No. I'm disappointed in you, Inori.
Hey!
Aren't you being a little mean?
I don't mean to barge in, but...
she worked really hard! And she even got badly hurt...
I know.
But results are everything. She failed us greatly in the final moment.
Failed you? How?
She let you use the Void Genome.
That cylinder?
That was supposed to be for my use.
The cylinder she gave you was one of only three enhanced genomes
that Sephirah Genomics had successfully cultivated.
The power it bestows on its user is the King's Power.
The King's Power?
It can analyze intron sequences in the human genome,
and draw out the power hidden within them by converting them into Voids.
What's a Void?
An idea which has acquired form. The sword you used was one of them.
That was Inori's Void.
Different Voids can be extracted from different people.
Void technology trespasses into the realm of the gods,
and what you obtained today is its crowning achievement.
You are no longer allowed to powerlessly stand by
and turn a blind eye to others' lives like before.
You'll fight with us.
But, I can't just—
Remember this, Ouma Shu.
There are only two paths you can choose.
You can sit quietly and be selected out of this world, or you can adapt and change!
What is it?
Things have gone sour, Gai.
The damn whitecoats have stormed the undergroud parking lot in Area 14.
The underground parking lot?
Yeah. Somebody said it was safe,
and about 100 people taking shelter there got caught all at once.
On top of that, the new-model unit that took down Ayase
belonged to Kill-'em-All Daryl.
That makes things a little tricky.
Daryl... ah, the Kaleidoscope, huh?
Gai, this is an unexpected predicament.
Given the current difference between our power and theirs,
a rescue mission isn't worth the risk.
I recommend we pull out.
No, we can't pass this up.
This isn't an unexpected predicament. This is divine intervention.
Attention all members:
We are about to exterminate the Anti Bodies and rescue the residents of the fort!
Furthermore, this operation won't be a covert one like the ones so far.
As of this moment,
we, Undertaker, are making our existence known to the world!
So work with all you've got!
Aye-aye!
All right!
Only you. All right, I'll knock out a script.
But are you sure this isn't a bit too soon?
What's your answer?
It's pointless to resist!
Spill it. Who's your leader?!
Tell me!
The Special Virus Disaster Response Bureau, commonly known as the "Anti Bodies."
They can unilaterally designate people as symptomatic,
and have been granted the authority to dispose of them based on their judgment.
Please, don't!
What do you think my husband's done?!
Mommy, potty!
Wait just a second, Ryo.
He isn't sick!
Mama!
Please!
What a heartrending sight... my heart quivers.
Officer!
I'm begging you, please spare him!
What do you think you're doing, you filthy hag?!
You'll infect me!
That's fucking disgusting! How dare you?!
The cornerstone of GHQ's public security operations—
their cruelest, sharpest fang.
That's the enemy we're fighting right now.
No matter. Just do it.
Kill them!
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
Ugh, this "mommy" crap...
No need to be so annoying just because you gave birth to him.
This can't be real.
Alpha Team, are you in position?
Not yet.
Hurry up!
I know!
Gai!
Begin the operation!
Missiles incoming!
Intercept them!
Undertaker, eh?
Don't you dare let them go!
They're here!
It's started...
Listen up, Shu.
After Alpha Team's long-range attack,
we'll draw the Endlaves as far away from the enemy camp as possible.
And once we've drawn them the preset distance,
Charlie Team will make its move.
Points Red, Blue, and Yellow are now under our control.
Distance to planned point: seven.
Now take good care of my babies, Aya!
Leave them to me.
Look out, I'm gonna step on you!
Target has reached D-line!
Game... over!
Now!
Abort! Abort your attack!
What?!
We have multiple missiles locked on!
How are there too many for us to intercept?!
A word of advice to Major Guin,
commander of GHQ's Anti Bodies Squadron Three.
He's on an open channel!
We are Undertaker.
Release your hostages and surrender.
If you agree, we will spare your lives.
What now, Major?
We're the ones holding the trump card.
Listen up, terrorists! We will never bow to terrorism.
If you continue to resist, we'll set off the gas we've planted underground.
If you don't want that, show yourselves!
So, you call yourselves "Undertaker?"
I assume you must have a leader, correct?
I'm the leader.
"Undertaker" is quite the sinister name, isn't it?
The world always forces a choice on its inhabitants.
Survival of the fittest...
that is the law this world operates by.
We continue to offer songs of mourning to the ones selected out.
Hence "Undertaker."
The name signifies that we are always on the singing side—
that we are the survivors.
You clearly don't understand your position here.
Which one of us is about to be selected out?
Where's the genetic weapon your people stole?
Confess!
Well, that's the first I've heard about that.
I'll give you a count of ten to tell us.
Then we'll shoot you full of holes.
Right on schedule.
Wow... it's all going right according to his plan.
And if I mess up here, everyone will...
Believe.
You can do it. For sure.
Because I... belong to you now.
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
Go, Kaleidoscope!
One!
Time's up!
What?!
Blooming wildflower
I beg you, please tell me
Why do people fight and hurt each other?
Good work.
You overcame one of your own limits today.
That's something you can be proud of.
Come with us, Shu.
I know there's something you can do.
I wonder...
What would have happened if I'd taken his hand that day?
But I made the right choice.
That had to have been a once-in-a-lifetime adventure.
Today, my everyday life begins once more.
Okay, one last thing.
Our class has a new transfer student.
Come on in!
A girl!
Hey, she's cute!
This is Yuzuriha Inori.
This is... a joke, right?
It's the real thing.
These days you love me no more
nor am I still treasured by you
Now I am all alone
What did you tell me when we parted?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender