The reality of the destruction around us fills our mind
The raging rain sounds like a storm of tears
Notice
that your eyes were given to you to acknowledge others,
that your voice was given to you to tell others how you feel
and that your hands were given you to hold those dear to you
All living things
bear witness to my song
Your heart contains all its truth
Even when all you see in your path are storms
remember that your strength is no coincidence
and on it,
rely
Hey, it even swallowed up the Diet Building!
It's practically right in our faces now!
What should we do? In another week, this place will be...
What are you doing?
Mr. President!
What happens if the enemy takes us by surprise
because you took your minds off observation duties?
Would you take responsibility for the casualties?
What's his problem?
Secret Service, take them to the disciplinary cells.
Yes, Sir.
Seriously?!
Screw you! Where do you get off—
I can do whatever I want with this, you know!
If you don't like the sound of that, then obey me!
You're not sleeping yet?
I can't sleep at a time like this. There's only one week left until the Exodus.
And...
Gai wouldn't be idling before an operation.
The leader of the Undertakers?
Did he threaten his members into doing what he wanted?
What's this about?
There's resentment building amongst the students.
You're going too far, Shu.
So what if they resent us? They all want to be safe as soon as possible, right?
When Hare...
That happened to her because there was no discipline.
I know it was probably the people who resent us that attacked Arisa,
but there's no going back now.
You said it yourself, Yahiro.
Of course, we still need ways to ensure that they don't feel oppressed.
S-Someone help!
Inori?
What's wrong?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Someone help me...
Hello?
Yes.
The student body is on the verge of collapse.
Yes, Ouma's keeping them in check with his power for now...
Criticizing President Ouma isn't allowed, even for a Rank S like you.
Who were you talking to?
If you don't want to tell me, that's fine.
I can easily find out just by looking at your call history.
All right.
Will you draw it out, then?
My...
Void...
You sure about this, Nanba?
Yeah.
I already received an advance payment, after all.
Well, I guess this means it's about time.
Here goes.
Hey, what's this about?!
"Ouma Shu's hiding it,
but if your Void breaks...
...you'll die with it"?!
What the hell? He's hidden that from us to use our Voids?!
This is unforgivable... He's going to pay for this!
Drop dead, Shu!
Go to hell!
A total of ninety-eight cover-ups and fabrications have been unearthed
in the reports from the Japanese government.
I knew it was a mistake to entrust this to Keido.
We've been reaching out to them for almost a decade now...
Don't you think we've done enough?
You want to abandon them?
The U.N. would exchange the defunct Japanese yen at a fixed rate.
In that case...
Now that your representatives have reached an accord,
let's hear the details of your plan.
It's not very nice to spread idle rumors.
"Rumors"?
The rumor that if your Void breaks, you die.
Are you sure that's not the truth, rather than a just a rumor?
It's a rumor. If it wasn't, our whole establishment would break down.
So you've come to silence me this time?
"This time"?
Anyone who defies your establishment is punished.
Isn't that what you've come to say?
We would never order something like that.
I see. Let me tell you who did it, then.
I... wonder if I'll pay the penalty someday.
Penalty?
For the sin of trampling all over people's hearts...
Then I would pay for it, too.
Why would you say that?
I'm probably the one who hurt Kuhouin.
What are you talking about?
I thought she was about to cause trouble for you, Shu.
It made me shudder inside...
and I probably...
I'm afraid of myself.
Because I'm a monster...
It's okay.
Don't worry.
In this school, I'm the king.
I'll never let anyone hurt you.
Shu.
I found out who attacked Kuhouin Arisa.
Who was it?
Yuzuriha Inori. I have testimony from an eyewitness.
I see. So?
You're too hung up on Yuzuriha, Shu.
If we allow special treatment, we'll lose control of the students.
If an enforcer of the rules breaks them—
Shut up!
Weren't you the one who kept the details of Void death from me?!
You've kept just as many secrets as she has!
Stop it, Shu!
Don't you get it? It was to keep everyone alive!
Liar!
Don't try to brush this off.
You think I'm an idiot, so you're just trying to use me!
That's not it! I figured something out after what happened to Jun.
People make a lot of mistakes. Correcting those mistakes requires power.
That made me think that I needed to work with you!
You expect me to believe that?
I know you're planning to sell me out eventually,
Sugar!
Yes, I'm sure I sound like I'm lying.
I suppose these are the consequences of my actions...
Get out of here, Yahiro.
You never thought of us as friends in the first place.
Isn't that right?
Yes, that's right.
Samukawa was sent to the Rank F tents.
Like they say, you reap what you sow.
Also, have this.
It's what you asked for.
The date and time of the Exodus, and information on the students' Voids, too.
What do you intend to use it for?
A coup d'état.
I'm going to force the emperor and his new clothes out of power.
Move out, starting with the groups who are ready.
Our destination, Tokyo Tower, is about four kilometers away.
We'll take a break after each kilometer and do a roll call.
Regarding the details, follow your squad leader's orders.
There's something wrong with the mood today.
Kuhouin will give the signal.
We know.
Has Team B received the news?
Don't get the timing wrong.
Are we sure the Secret Service is with us on this?
Kanon?
Nanba.
Yes?
What does everyone think of me?
They're grateful to you, the leader who will free them all.
I see.
The students are on the move.
Just as the leaked plans said they would.
Are they headed for Tokyo Tower?
Yes, Sir.
Unless something changes, we'll make contact with them on Sakurada Street.
I see.
So, we're about to witness the advent of the true king.
I've measured the maximum value of the genomic resonance in Tennozu.
The index variation is 281.
Honestly... you've done well, collecting them...
I'll go over the plan one more time.
The machine controlling the Ghost Unit is here in Tokyo Tower.
I'll use Voids to send a high-voltage current through its struts.
If I short the machine that way,
I should be able to render the Ghosts powerless.
You will create a path to get me there.
Go to your designated posts and hold back the enemy's defense Insects.
If we succeed, we'll be able to get outside the wall.
Let's give it our all.
They're here!
Don't be afraid! We have Voids on our side!
Let us move forward, Ouma.
Not for anyone else, but for our own futures!
Begin the operation!
There are twenty Auto-Insects, just like we expected.
Damn it!
Mr. President, the path is open.
Did I just use them as glorified decoys?
Shu...
Inori...
It's okay. Don't worry.
This isn't the time for soul-searching.
Kazumi!
Sir, where are you going?
Let's go!
I'll do this. I'm doing this!
I don't...
...want to lose anyone else!
Come, everyone.
Let's cross the red line while we can.
Quickly!
It's over, Inori.
Come on, let's follow them.
What's with you three?
What do you think you're doing?!
Shu!
Stay back, Inori!
You can't go out there, Ayase!
Tsugumi?
Great work, Mr. President.
Your work is done now.
We'll go on alone from here.
There you have it.
Arisa! Did you do this?!
Do I really need to answer that?
I'm not doing anything wrong...
I'm not...
Souta?
How dare you use us as tools!
Who said you could peek inside my heart?!
Coward!
Parasite!
Drop dead! We're sick of you!
Shu!
Hey!
Inori!
Gai?!
You came for us.
Long time no see, Shu.
Shu...
My arm!
My king's power...!
We'll now take a vote on United Nations Resolution 17,
the project to terminate Japan.
Approved by majority vote.
We'll now proceed to drop the RM warheads.
"King"?
Have you forgotten? You were just a usurper.
The king has always been me.
Now that I am all alone in this world,
what should I feel and think?
After we spend countless days together
and shared our feelings,
we will never be truly apart
I took you for granted, and now you are gone
That's the pain I've come to bear
Even if I had held onto your hand when you left me,
and not let you go,
I would have done it purely out of self-interest
I'm such a horrible liar
When I whispered that I was doing it all for you
you had already stopped believing it
Now I run to you to make up for it,
no matter how often I may fall or get lost
Wait for me, I'm coming to meet you,
no matter what hardships may await me