Jun!
Are you all right?
Hmm? What is it?
Thank you very much.
There's no need to blame yourself. You're only human, aren't you?
What a shame.
We let them escape, eh?
It seems as though we have a bingo.
So, everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
I'm yours
Say, there's lots of happiness in this world, isn't there?
Someday, if we're together
Even if someone calls you a liar
and tries to hurt you with cruel words,
even if the world does not try to believe you
and places a crown of thorns upon your head,
I can take your side, and yours alone
I know your pain and loneliness
So everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
Okay, I'm gonna start filming!
Scene where the heroine finds out about her lover's death, take five!
One week?
Isn't it bad for the leader to be gone that long?
Some matters can't be settled unless I go in person.
Behave yourself and enjoy school for a while.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be a good boy.
It's not true. I can't believe it.
Cut, cut!
Shu's just different lately, somehow. Bolder, or something...
He's like a different person.
Maybe something happened in Oshima.
Huh?
A vacation on a southern island! A summer love affair!
And so the young man climbs the stairway to adulthood!
Stop it!
Seriously, though,
Life really doesn't go the way we want it to, does it?
Are you talking about Yahiro?
I even went to the orphanage, but they say he hasn't visited.
We used to play there together all the time as kids, too...
What I'm looking for is at the aquarium?
I'm not looking for a fish, you know...
What about you?
Um, "Your lucky item of love is a tiger-striped tea kettle."
Huh?! Where are you supposed to find that?
It's a...
tiger-striped tea kettle.
Yeah...
Pardon me!
Shu!
Huh, so you two haven't gone home yet?
Is this yours, Ouma?
Souta's using it for the film. It's the lover's... memento, I guess?
Anyway, he says he's gonna have Inori hold it.
I forgot something in the club room!
I'll go deliver this for you, so you go shopping with Hare for me, okay?
Um, sure?
Wai— Kanon!
It's your lucky chance!
Go for it.
Go for it! Lucky chance!
What does she mean, "lucky chance"?
I... have no idea.
I'm told there's a ghost about.
Someone entered the Oshima lab with Dr. Ouma Kurosu's ID.
Dr. Keido Shuichiro, you were once close colleagues.
Can you offer any explanation?
No, Sir, I can't.
Hey.
Where are we getting off? For your shopping.
Will you have lots of bags?
Oh! Yeah, I will.
I wonder if we'll be able to carry them all...
Um!
Hare... are you okay?
Shu, I...
To me, you're...
Dammit.
Yahiro.
Shu.
Oho, having a little fun?
No, Yahiro, this is just—
Yahiro. Is that all you have to say to me?
What do you want me to say? You want to air everything out right here?
Hare, I need you to go shopping by yourself, please.
Huh? But...
There's something I want to talk with Yahiro about.
Ouma Shu. Keeping an eye on you...
...was clearly the right call.
They told me they were going to put Jun down.
So we took advantage of the confusion and ran away.
I figured I couldn't let him stay there any longer.
Go ahead and laugh.
I sold you out to get us into that place,
and in the end I ran away from it.
Jun!
Did you fall again? Do you hurt anywhere?
It's okay, Jun.
This is my...
friend.
We've acquired the fugitive Cancerous.
Hell yeah! Nice guts!
Do you really need my Endlave for a simple little Cancerous hunt?
No, no, boy!
You know what they say, a dragon goes full force even against a slime!
Like a dragon would seriously eat a slime...
Got that, Scarface?
Okay, Dan! Leave the rest to me!
We'll clear this mission with guts!
It's called "knowing how to get ahead."
Could you lend me some money?
We need money to run and eat.
Is that why you went out of your way to show Jun to me?
Please, Shu. I'm the only one left who can protect him.
Please.
Shu?
Where's Gai?
He left already, why?
I have someone I want you to harbor.
He's an Apocalypse patient. The Carcinogenesis has started already.
Hold on a second!
You need to talk to Shibungi, and then we'll give you the ord—
We're heading to Point Yellow-One now.  Pick us up there in an hour.
Shu, you...
This doesn't mean I've forgiven you for what you did.
But...
Jun hasn't done anything wrong.
Look it over. We'll have to use this very soon.
Wrong.
This song is wrong now.
Sorry, Jun. Bear with it for just a little while, okay?
So they've finally come out.
Are you ready for gene capture?
The system check is done. But why use something like this?
Is it wrong to want to get to know the person you're in love with?
Do it, please.
Anti Bodies?! How have they found us already?!
Calm down!
We saw this coming. For now, just move!
A terrorist attack?!
D'ya think the Undertakers are back or something?
We're in trouble!
Let's use that!
No!
This has to be a trap.
Opening up an escape route and luring in the enemy is a basic tactic.
If you keep thinking like an amateur, you're going to die.
What did you just try to do?!
I have a Void on my side.
I have the power to draw poeple's hearts out as weapon.
I can even take down an Endlave.
You're telling me to believe that?
You sure you're not the one who called in those guys?
Hypocrite.
Shut up, you traitor!
Shu.
I don't betray people like you do.
I don't abandon them!
And I'll make sure Jun escapes, just like I promised.
All you have to do is shut up and let me use you!
Jun!
You don't need to worry. Your big brother's safe.
N-Not that!
Not that? What do you mean?
You again, eh?
You faceless bastard!
Jun, I'll be right back!
Run, run!
But today, I've got something special!
This thing will follow that light.
Not bad. How about some continuous fire, then?
Jun!
Hey, Segai! What's going on here?!
This is unexpected, but I must say it's intriguing.
That object and the Apocalypse Cancer displayed the same reading...
What is this?!
It migrated?
What's happening?
What does this mean?
Jun!
Jun, are you okay?!
How can I ever explain this to Yahiro?!
Did the Apocalypse Virus cause genomic resonance in the machine?
Then, the one there is...
Reboot PINs! I'll input every last one!
Hey, what's wrong? What happened?
Bastard!
Major Segai, you're in danger! Please move away from the action!
We'll withdraw for now. Abort the operation.
Sir!
What are you...
Please, stop!
This is... Roppongi?
From before Lost Christmas?
That's right.
Are you... Jun?
We finally get to talk.
Wow, thanks!
This is a one-time deal, got it? Just for your birthday.
This is December 24th, 2029.
It was the happiest time of my life.
Lost Christmas is about to happen.
I want to be on my way now, and just take this one happy memory with me.
Shu... please use that Void to cut off my life.
My brother's Void is the Void that severs life.
It's the Void to lay my body to rest with.
That's... crazy...
The crystals that stole my freedom
gave me the ability to see Voids in return.
And I saw there was another big brother besides the one he showed me.
Let's eat pizza today!
Really?!
I'll order you the tomato one you like, okay?
You're in the way. You're in my way.
I've seen unkind sides to kind people over and over.
Friends, ladies in our family, people from the health center...
And you're probably the same, Shu.
If I live any longer, this sadness will hit me again and again.
I'll end up hating my brother.
I want to go out as the me who loves my wonderful big brother.
Come on, hurry.
Lost Christmas!
I'm scared! I'm scared!
It's okay; your big brother is here for you.
Yeah.
Forever. I'll be here for you forever!
Please! At this rate, I'll end up killing my brother!
Brother... was it a nuisance having me around?
Did I wreck your life?
Did you hate me?!
Well, here's how I feel about you!
Thank you.
I love you, big brother.
Life doesn't go the way we want it to, does it?
Where are we?
That's right— Jun!
Where's Jun?
He's dead.
What did you just say?
He died.
Shu!
I'm the one who killed him.
Shu...
These days you love me no more
nor am I still treasured by you
Now I am all alone
What did you tell me when we parted?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender