Blooming wildflower
I beg you, please tell me
Why do people fight and hurt each other
Valiantly blooming flower
What can you see from your field?
Why can't people forgive each other
Have you secured the key?
Yeah.
Good work. I'll guide you out.
We'll meet up in thirty seconds.
The rain passed, and summer took on blue hues
All alone now
You trembled before me
Without saying a word
When your friends wilt around you
What do you think?
With your leaves unable to speak.
Please, Funell. Get this to Gai.
How do you convey love?
Summer's sun clouded over, the wind streamed by
I'll cover you
The two overlapped
Now get that to Gai, quick!
Funell...
I shall sing the proof that you lived
Oh, crap!
For the sake of those who have no names
Morning, Shu!
What's the huge yawn for?
Well...
Were you surfing the net or something?
Or playing a game?
Reading?
Something like that, I guess...
Huh. Fine, then.
Danger
Lots of them out today, huh?
Didn't you see the news?
Apparently there was some terrorist attack or something yesterday.
In Odaiba... no, I guess it's called "Ward 24" now.
Hey, Shu!
Oh, sorry, I'm not done with that video for the competition yet.
I didn't come to harp on you about it...
What did you want, then?
I'll get it done by the deadline, don't worry.
Now look, Shu, I—
Let it go, Souta.
He says he can do it, after all.
Okay, we're counting on you!
I feel bad for Souta.
Why? I think I'm trying hard to be socially perceptive here.
You're not succeeding.
Oh...
You're way too dense.
Rise!
I'm dense?
Maybe it's true that my mind works out of step with everyone else's.
It's just that I don't know what to say to other people.
So I hide my nervousness and go along with what they say.
that's how I've made the quasi-friendships in my life.
Right now, Japan operates as a "quasi-independent" nation.
That's what my mom says.
Was a biological Weapon Used!?
Ten years ago, the Apocalypse Virus pandemic wreaked havoc on this country,
Anarchy Reigns
and we relied on an unbelievable amount of help from many other countries.
And we're still dependent on them even now.
Japan's foundations are just barely holding together.
We hear it every day...
"We can't leave this to you."
"You don't have the power to protect the people who are important to you."
But... should we really just accept that?
Isn't there something more that I can do?
Blockade
Zone
Blooming wildflower...
I beg you, please tell me,
Why do people fight and hurt each other?
Valiantly blooming flower...
Wha—
Um, you've got the wrong idea!
I totally didn't want to—
Hey, are you—
It... it's not done yet!
It's a view of my hometown, and—
It's pretty.
Huh?
Um, would you like a rice ball?
London Bridge is falling down, falling down, falling down.
London Bridge is falling down, my fair lady.
Um, you're Inori, aren't you?
The Egoist singer?
London Bridge is falling down, falling down, falling down.
So, what are you doing here?
No, more importantly, why are you so hurt?
We have to get this to Gai.
Take this.
Take this, um...
Shu! Ouma Shu!
You might be able to do it if you try.
But you'll never be able to if you don't.
Ouma Shu... are you a coward?
Huh?
What was that?
Funell.
Inori!
Woah there.
You a student?
Y-Yes, Sir!
Um, that girl is hurt. Please don't treat her—
This woman is a criminal.
If you defend her, we'll purge you too, as her accomplice.
What does the data check show?
She's definitely a member of the Funeral Parlor in Rappongi.
Little terrorist scum!
Bring her in.
Yes, Sir!
Should I really just accept this?
I felt... a little relieved, because I wasn't in danger anymore.
That's how pathetic I am.
When you get right down to it, she was way out of my league.
Take this.
I wanted to take it.
I wanted to get close to her, and touch her hand!
Forget about it, Shu. Rest a while, and you'll be fine.
After that, just go back to your normal self.
We have to get this to Gai.
Seriously? You're telling me to go there?
This might be my last chance to not hate myself.
It had to be here, of all places...
I'm told you've dispatched a squadron to Roppongi.
I believed it was necessary.
That'll provoke unnecessary hostility.
I can't allow it if it's not for an aid mission.
I understand that.
So, just how dangerous is this stolen Void Genome?
That's—
Level 3A classified information.
And so you can't even tell me, GHQ's Supreme Commander?
I'm afraid so, sir.
But please, don't worry.
My Anti Bodies have already apprehended the culprit,
and are searching for the stolen genome as we speak.
Still don't want to talk?
We've been granted the authority to dispose of the diseased without warning.
If you don't tell us where you hid it,
I'll just have to purge every single resident of this neighborhood.
You'll regret this later.
Attention all units.
All residents in our operating area are designated as Stage IV+ infected.
I hereby authorize infection control measures!
What shall we do with the girl?
After we commence hostilities, get rid of her outside.
Is this it?
Hey, you!
Y-Yes?
That thing cook?
Excuse me?
That thing cook rice?
Well, no, I don't think it does...
Leave it.
N-No, I can't do that!
You messin' with me? Just hand it over.
I'm very sorry, but it doesn't belong to me!
She worked so hard to protect this...
So... I'm sorry!
Greetings, my deceased fellows.
"Deceased"?!
Yes. The current situation doesn't allow for your survival.
Therefore, you are all dead.
Don't tell me he's...
...Gai!
You got some balls, kid.
Shit, who is this guy?!
Wait, what?
That's Funell, right? Give it back!
You're Ouma Shu?
What about the girl who was with that?
Well... I...
You just abandoned her?
Gai! The GHQ whitecoats are invading!
Damn those bastards! They're firing live rounds at anybody they see!
Tsugumi, what's the word on Ayase and the others?
They're...
Enemy incoming on our left!
Beat it, you're in my way!
Go, Shu!
Don't you dare let go of that thing! Protect it this time!
But... what can I do, exactly?
How many are we up against?
Not sure yet! More keep coming!
Keep it together!
What do you think you're doing?!
Inori!
Do something that's not like you for once, Shu!
What...
What is this?
Shu, please...
...use me.
Take it this time, Shu.
Who...
This is power.
The guilty crown given shape through the bond between hearts.
What... is this?
These days you love me no more
nor am I still treasured by you
Now I am all alone
What did you tell me when we parted?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender
I'm in charge of key animation for the
Guilty Crown: Lost Christmas PC game.
—Chuo Higashiguchi