Away on Business
I see you have obtained the
Hierophant Arcana and the
Justice Arcana. Congratulations.
-Margaret
Hide and seek it wants to play again
Like a detective, I won't let it get away
It's constantly costuming with loads of fake
I will strip search if I have to
Though I'm not afraid to know it, don't know how
I am so determined
To chase after what's hidden and seize this day, this moment
WANNA KNOW
Enter key to accelerate
WANNA GO
Ignition turned on
It's about that time to drive to truth
WANNA SEIZE
Stranger than in movies
Ignorance is not bliss
They say that truth will out
Can't keep on hiding
There's no turning back now
I'm gonna go on
I'm gonna go get what I want
As such, for the culture festival,
Study
Hall
||
Maze
Movie
Room
|||
Rest
Stop
||
Group
Date
Café
|||||
Movie
Room
|||
Rest
Stop
|||
Group
Date
Cafe
|||||
Maze
||
our class will run a group date café.
No, no, no! Stop right there!
What the heck is a group date café?
Whose bright idea was this?!
Well shit, that was supposed to be a joke.
It was you?!
I've never been on a group date before, so I was a little curious.
You voted for it?!
I only vaguely remember it,
but I think we enjoyed the King's Game.
Not you too, Narukami!
Actually, I was kinda curious myself.
I thought it'd be fun for some laughs.
I can't believe this class.
Well, I wish you and Amagi the best in your other event.
Huh? What event?
Miss Yasogami Pageant
Entry
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
I can't believe people actually entered the beauty pageant!
They must be pretty confident in themselves.
Why'd you sign us up without asking first?!
I mean, you guys know how popular Amagi is here.
On top of that, we now have an idol and the Detective Prince!
What's the point of having a beauty pageant if all these incredible heroines don't take part?
What does that have to do with me?!
Well, excuse me for not fitting in!
So, do you want us to enter?
You bet! Right, Yu?
Listen carefully now.
This beauty pageant...
Minutes Later
Q.E.D. You must enter the beauty pageant!
F-Fine! You've made your point.
What can we do? Can we could back out?
This is quite the predicament.
Wh-Why don't you guys just enter?
Well, I mean...
Just enter the damn thing!
It would clear away all of my doubts.
I'm beggin' you!
Make me a man!
What are you talking about?
I said enter the pageant, dammit!
Aren't you a detective?
How is that related?
It looks like we don't have much of a choice.
The guys seem to be enthusiastic about it.
I might as well put on a show for 'em.
Narukami and I are on the basketball team, remember?
With the festival coming up, there have been a bunch of no-shows.
Just deal with it.
But seriously, our class's event is so lame.
Why'd it have to be a play?
Don't whine, Hammy.
Hammy?
Narukami, shoot!
Where'd "Hammy" come from?!
Nurse's Office
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
It's no big deal.
You don't have to worry about me.
Ow, that hurt.
I'm sorry you had to carry this for me.
It's okay.
Are you going to practice now?
Yep! After all, the culture festival is just around the corner.
I see.
Um...
I thought I could hear you play since I'm already here.
Huh?! But I'm not very good.
I don't mind.
Uh, okay...
I wasn't really supposed to perform at our concert.
The symphonic band only has two trombone players.
One of the seniors normally performs since he's really good, but he got hurt.
Is that so?
I may not be talented,
but I still love music.
I keep at it because it's been my dream to make others feel good through my music.
That's a good dream.
I've got to practice!
Um, thank you very much.
My head feels all better now.
Something wrong?
I'll go once you can put on a good show.
That was kinda mean.
Yasogami High's "Miss" Yasogami Pageant
The fallen angels of the night flutter down to Yasogami High!!
Entry
Tatsumi Kanji
Hanamura Yosuke
Entry
Narukami Yu
Yikes! They're seriously cross-dressing?
That's so wrong!
Satonaka!
Yes?
"Yes?" my ass!
You entered us in the cross-dressing pageant, didn't you?!
Oh, that?
Rise said we should all have fun with this.
Don't give me that!
This is cross-dressing, dammit!
That's what you get for signing us up without asking first!
Don't worry.
We'll make you absolutely enchanting.
Enchanting, you say?
You sure?
Yeah, I guarantee it.
Wait! Why are you suddenly cool with this?
If we gotta do this, might as well go all the way with it!
There's nothing manly about being a woman!
Come on, man. Tell 'em!
I'll do my best.
You rock, Narukami!
You totally get it.
What kind of joke is this,
making us all enter?
Let's give it our all.
Leave everything to us!
We'll be your producers!
Please make me cute.
Isn't Risette entering this year's beauty pageant?
Entry
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Awesome, isn't it? This year rocks!
They went all-out with the posters.
Is it true Ms. Kashiwagi's entering?
They say everyone in Inaba's gonna show up.
I can see that happening!
This really stinks.
I'm not the idol Risette anymore.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go shopping.
Yeah...
Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
Group
Date
Café
Ch-Check out our group date café...
It's a group date café...
No one's coming, huh?
We won't be using those.
Okay then.
We gotta get the ball rolling.
Ball?
When people see how fun it is, they might join in on it.
What's with these hideous decorations?
Oh, perfect timing!
Now there's an even number of us.
And there goes the ball.
What? But there are four dudes and only two chicks!
Someone's gonna have to go on the girl side.
That was quick!
Hurry and take a seat.
And you're already in character.
We might as well enjoy the ride.
What ride?
What's going on?
W-Well, let's get started.
S-So, got any hobbies?
H-Hobbies? Um...
I love kung fu, but I mainly just watch it.
Geez, this is so embarrassing!
M-My hobby is, um... defeating Shadows?
Hey!
Shadows? What are those?
Hey, stupid! That's not a hobby!
O-Oh yeah, sorry.
Uh, Yuko, what's your hobby?
Changing and fusing Personas?
Those aren't hobbies either!
Okay, we'll ask the next question.
What type of girls do you like?
Oh, straight to the point!
Let's see. I like kind—
Kanji, you're up.
Lemme talk!
I, uh, like kinda mysterious girls
that look strong but are surprisingly...
I wonder who that is!
You're up, Nagase.
I hate girls.
What?!
Whatcha blushing for?!
I'm not!
Can I go now?
Wait! You can't leave!
I don't think I could survive this getting any more awkward!
It's your turn. Got any questions?
Nice going, Amagi!
Let's see.
Which one of us would you choose to be your boyfriend?
Wh-What made you bring that up?!
That's a little personal.
H-H-H-Hold it!
What's wrong, Hanamura?
I can't say,
but I felt like I was about to cross a line that must never be crossed!
My, you're so naïve.
Knock it off!
I need a drink! Something cool and refreshing!
I need something to cool my head!
What's gotten into you, Hanamura?
Sorry, but I forgot to bring drinks.
But it's a group date!
I ordered delivery, though.
Hello.
Thanks again.
Th-These aren't drinks.
I'll just help myself.
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Courage
Heroic
Diligence
Thorough
Understanding
Effeminate
Expression
Enthralling
Knowledge
Professor
Performing
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
To be Romeo or to be Juliet?
That is the question!
Hamlet, huh? He really is a ham.
The problem here is that I am Hamlet!
That he is.
Hey, have you heard about the band being totally screwed this year?
Yeah, you could even say they're trom-boned.
Music Room
I'm sorry I keep messing up.
I was afraid you wouldn't be up to it, Matsunaga.
Long time no see!
Iida!
Where's your cast?
I recovered just in time for our big culture festival concert.
Oh, about that...
Oh, I get it.
Let's have Iida play the trombone!
It would totally suck if she blew it during the concert.
Wouldn't you all agree?
I'll step down.
You can have the part.
Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah...
Could you let her play?
Uh, who are you?
Every day she's—
Are you really sure about this?
Yes. I'd hate to hold everyone back and ruin their concert if I messed up.
I see.
I feel like such an idiot.
I thought I was one step closer to realizing my dream.
I'm so frustrated!
Thank you. I'm happy you tried to defend me.
I'm frustrated, but I'm also happy.
After all that practice, it made me remember just how much I love music.
That's why I'm frustrated and happy.
You'll get another chance. I'm sure of it.
Yeah...
I know there's
no need to cry, but...
But the tears won't stop!
Then let's go.
Huh? Go where?
There's a culture festival today.
We should go enjoy it.
Stir-fry Noodles
Haunted House
That was scary!
Narukami!
Ebi?!
What, you on a date?
You're hot stuff!
Am not!
Is she your girlfriend?
How many girls are you two-timing on?
What?!
Keeping it a secret?
Then I know just where I'm taking you!
You're coming with me!
No!
W-W-Wait!
I'll see you later!
THE Long-Nosed
Fortune-Teller's Manor
I-Isn't this...
THE Long-Nosed
Fortune-Teller's Manor
Hey, I need you to read Narukami here.
I'm very particular about this sort of thing.
What an impertinent customer.
Too much curiosity killed the cat.
Ugh, you picking a fight?
I'll trash your stall if your reading's off!
Wait. I don't think that's a good idea...
Shuddup!
Now hurry up and tell me about his love life!
That theme puts me at an even greater advantage.
How so?
His love life is...
Don't go there!
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's time for the main event for day two of the culture festival!
It's the "Miss" Yasogami Pageant!
"MISS" PAGEANT
Well then, let's get this rolling with Entry No. 1!
The beautiful wilds of Inaba gave birth to this quick-tempered, explosively destructive babe!
From Class 1-3, it's Ms. Tatsumi Kanji!
Hiya!
Gross!
This is awful! It's just disgusting!
Entry No. 2!
This lively beauty is the heiress to Junes!
She's the prince of disappointment the moment she opens her mouth!
From Class 2-2, it's Ms. Hanamura Yosuke!
H-Hi!
And here I thought Hanamura could pull it off.
That's freakishly plausible!
Entry No. 3!
Carrying the bittersweet tang of the city, she's made more girls cry than there are stars in the sky!
It's the transfer student who waltzed into Class 2-2, Ms. Narukami Yu!
What a shock!
Why?!
Look at me.
Finally, we have a new heroine who signed up at the last minute!
Calling herself "King of the TV World,"
she's a cute, sexy little number!
Her name is Ms. Teddie!
Doodly-doo!
Gimme your hearts!
Is that really a boy?
What a cutie!
He's totally pulling it off!
Oh, boy. I see where this is going...
"Miss" Pageant
Calculating
Remaining
The results are in! The glorious winner is...
the last-minute entry, Teddie!
Yahoo! I'd like to thank Naoto for doing my makeup.
Team "Naoteddie" won!
As winner, Teddie will get to help judge the real pageant held later today.
Yahoo! Yay!
Oh, Teddie...
His happiness is rubbing off on me.
Teddie, how do you feel?
This is exactly what I wanted.
The girls will have to get judged
in swimsuits for their pageant later today!
Wh-What did he just say?
We should kill him.
I like where this is going!
That's weird.
I put up posters all across town,
but I only see our fellow classmates.
Did you want everyone to come?
I don't really care.
Seriously?!
Yep! Supposedly Kanamin's in the shopping district for a location shoot.
Awesome!
What are we doing here watching some beauty pageant?
Let's go check it out!
Kanami...
Risette's Shocking Retirement as an Idol
Rise Kujikawa Quits! The Lead Role Goes to Mashita Kanami
Now then, it's time for the main event!
Miss Yasogami Pageant
It's the real Miss Yasogami Pageant!
Entry No. 1!
From Class 2-2, it's Satonaka Chie!
Uh, my favorite food is pudding.
Liar! It's meat!
Next is Entry No. 2!
From Class 2-2, it's Amagi Yukiko!
I-I'm sorry...
Not at all.
It's a pleasure.
Entry No. 3!
From Class 1-2, it's Kujikawa Rise!
Yahoo! I'm Risette!
You can tell she's an idol.
Sorry I'm on hiatus right now!
Next up is Entry No. 4!
From Class 1-1, it's Shirogane Naoto!
Huh?
Shirogane Naoto?
I-I can't do it after all.
Shirogane?
I-I'm sorry, but I'm not feeling well.
Uh-oh, she's dropped out!
What a pity, huh, Kanji?
Yeah. It was a good shot, though.
Clean up your bloody nose.
Calculating
With Entry No. 5 and No. 6 on stage,
Announce the Results
I'm going to announce the winner.
Votes from the guys were everywhere,
but the girls all focused in on one contestant.
Thanks to that, the clear winner is...
Shirogane Naoto!
But Shirogane is currently away at the moment.
She won without competing?
That's hilarious!
I can't believe I lost in a beauty contest!
Ms. Kashiwagi, I'm so disappointed!
Same here, Ohtani!
Man, I lost.
But I can see why I wouldn't appeal to the girls.
Symphonic Band Concert
So this is where you went.
Yu...
Mashita Kanami Surrounded by Fans While Shooting in Inaba
The new Idol Mashita Kanami is on the rise.
I'm so confused.
She's filming in Inaba for her starring role in—
Losing the beauty pageant really isn't a big deal.
And whatever Kanami does is of no concern of mine...
or it shouldn't be.
So why am I so...
It's natural for you to be upset.
Risette is also a part of who you are.
Yeah, she is, isn't she?
I thought I came to terms with that on the other side, but...
It's hard to acknowledge who you really are...
I think...
Thanks,
even though you suck at trying to cheer someone up.
Back off!
I think I'm going to return to the entertainment industry this spring.
I'm going to accept that Risette is an important part of me and give it another shot.
Okay,
sounds good.
Would you like to be my manager?
No thanks.
You're so indifferent,
although that's what I like about you.
Well then, let's join up with the others.
Sure, why not?
Group Date Cafe
To Yu! From Rise!
I look at the rustic scenery
along the path to school
we walked together
Campus in spring,
the summer festival
These were the days we spent
shoulder-to-shoulder
laughing together
From past to present
I've always
looked back on these
carefree days
From today to tomorrow
We move forward while treasuring the bonds we've made
Let's go to the Amagi Inn!
I'll be the reporter.
The inn is haunted?
There's long hair in it!
Th-That's my line!
Is he a pervert?
Women sure are scary.