So this is Tsutsugami Gai’s…
You’ve belonged to this side since the beginning.
What made you think that you could cuddle up to some human?
You monster.
Something’s not quite right…
The reality of the destruction around us fills our mind
The raging rain sounds like a storm of tears
Notice
that your eyes were given to you to acknowledge others,
that your voice was given to you to tell others how you feel
and that your hands were given you to hold those dear to you
All living things
bear witness to my song
Your heart contains all its truth
Even when all you see in your path are storms
remember that your strength is no coincidence
and on it,
rely
I’m sorry, Mana.
What?! She should be here!
Mana’s not here.
She never has been.
You never change, Haruka.
You’re honest with yourself, and you’re an idealist who never gives up.
Just like him… like Ouma Kurosu.
You’re the one who killed him, weren’t you…
...Brother.
So you knew.
Why? You were best friends!
“Best friends”? Me and him?
Come on, hands in the air.
What is it? What do you think I’ve done?
Please don’t move.
You…
Is this revenge for betraying you?
I don’t care about what happens to me.
Tell me where Inori is, please.
Her?!
Attention all units.
Dr. Ouma Haruka has committed high treason and is now on the run.
Anyone who finds her is to arrest her on sight.
I repeat:
Dr. Ouma Haruka has committed high treason and is now on the run.
Anyone who finds her is to arrest her on sight.
That’s one of the cases Sephirah uses to transport top secret…
What’s so funny?
It’s all clear!
I’m afraid that it’s all clear to me now!
Mr. President, about Dr. Ouma…
I would love to be the one you send to track her.
Where are you going, Comrade Arisa?
I’m going after Dr. Ouma. I’ll tell Gai myself.
W-Wait! You didn’t say “Master”...!
Let me speak with Ouma Haruka once we find her.
Understood?
Is that your condition for telling me where Inori is?
I’m sure she knows what Gai’s plan is.
I want to know him.
His past, his desires, his weaknesses, his pains…
Everything.
The Kuhouins… I have nowhere else to go now.
Dr. Ouma Haruka, am I right?
It’s been a long time, Haruka.
Kurachi!?
When I heard you were on the run, I thought you might come here.
I have slight problem.
However… I’m afraid that this is no longer the Kuhouin mansion.
Then Mr. Kuhouin…?
It was a hero’s death.
I tried to kill Mana to prevent Daath from carrying out its plan.
But I failed.
Wait moment. I thought Mana was—
My daughter.
In other words, Shu’s older sister?
You know Shu?
I’m a member of the Undertakers.
I see. The Undertakers…
What was Shu like?
I’m his mother, but I neglected him…
No, that’s not it.
I’ve just been running away from him, haven’t I?
Haruka isn’t my real mother.
She got remarried to my father, but he died shortly after.
She raised me anyway, though.
It wasn’t out of a sense of duty or anything.
I really did care about Shu.
Shu lost a parent, and I lost him…
Still, the two of us were…
Yes, perhaps we were only licking each other’s wounds.
Then you can assure me that this building is a hideout of the Undertakers?
Y-Yes…
I can’t hear you!
I-I’m not lying! Please believe me!
I’m picking up a signal, Sir. It’s the real thing.
Magnificent. You’re an honest woman.
This is just a small token of my thanks.
Someone’s here.
Excuse me, we heard that there was vaccine here…
How much would you charge for some?
We heard that the government stockpiles are running out…
I have two young children at home! Please!
You want to keep it all to yourself, don’t you? Despicable!
Yeah, he’s right!
Come out and face us!
Open the door!
We said we’d pay you!
You’re mistaken. There’s no vaccine here.
Liar!
You can’t fool us.
Show us you really don’t have any!
All right. I’ll open the door, so come and see for yourselves.
See? It’s just an office.
There’s no vaccine anywhere.
Being a champion of justice just doesn't pay.
Ogumo!
Don’t worry about me! Just run!
You too.
You bastard!
Too bad.
We seem to be short two…
Shouldn’t we go back?
It’s dangerous for us to go.
Let’s try asking a different team.
What is this?
The last hope.
Don’t tell me it’s...!?
A Void Genome.
Our last and worst hope.
There’s no way we can take on Gai!
What, this doesn’t piss you off at all?
But even Ogumo got taken down…
We’ve only lost contact with him.
Argo’s out checking on him right now.
How is he?
Getting worse little by little.
Can’t we do anything about it?
I’m sorry. Our vaccine can't treat those that hit Stage III.
Argo’s back!
What about Ogumo?
He’s not with you?
Yes he is.
But…
He’s with me.
No way…
I’m sorry. He was protecting me.
No…
Ogumo…
How far you’ve fallen, Gai.
Five years ago…
In the hell of the African battlefront,
I saw a natural talent in the child soldier who tried to kill me.
I’ve worked to make you king ever since.
However… Is this what you wanted, Tsutsugami Gai?
To become the unsightly idol you are now?
I’ve only ever had one goal, then and now.
You people chose to build dreams on it
and then chose to be disappointed, that’s all.
All right, what were the Undertakers to you, then?
What did we fight for?
Do you want to know?
And yet, believe it or not, I thought of you as a friend.
A king has no friends.
He only has subordinates. Pawns.
Then as one of your pawns, I suppose I should express my gratitude.
Thanks to you, I have a new wish:
To kill you.
Here.
Thank you.
If I used that, would I be able to fight Gai?
At the very least, you'd gain the same power he has.
But...
It's also possible that every gene in your body could have an extreme rejection reaction.
I'm a horrible person.
I don't want to let Shu use it,
but I do want to have someone use it.
I can understand that a little.
Because I've seen Shu suffer because of his power, too.
It's not just that.
If he used it again, he'd probably die.
That's how dangerous it is.
Let's pull out all the stops.
Today is a party!
It looks like we're too late.
Hold it right there, Ouma Shu!
Haruka!
Leave me behind...
Just shut up.
I don't want to abandon anyone anymore.
Yahiro...
No need to hold back!
Make the bullets pour down like rain!
Lay waste to them like a storm!
It's no use—
I can't contact anyone.
We'll have to go back.
But if we go back, we'll be caught in a pincer attack.
Then what do you suggest?!
Sorry.
Dr. Ouma, please use the Void Genome on me.
Shu once gave me the courage and power to stand up and fight.
So this time, I want to stand up on my own.
Even if it means a confrontation with Gai!
Ayase, where's this coming from?!
It's okay. I've been thinking about this for a while.
Please!
I won’t let you!
Three ampules were produced.
I've been searching for the remaining one for quite some time.
I should’ve known that you had it, Dr. Ouma.
I'll be taking it now.
To do what?
I want to behold it, that mystical and sublime light.
I'm quite sure the truth lies beyond that light.
Yes, I dare say I would do anything to have it.
Talk until you’re blue in the face!
You little tomboy!
I won't let you have it!
Shu!
Give it back, Shu.
Do you understand what that is?!
Of course I do, Ayase.
Everything started with this.
I should be the one who bears the burden of this sin.
No! That's our sin!
There won't be a second time, Shu!
The Void power will kill you!
Thanks, Mom.
Even if we're not really mother and son,
I'm glad I got to be with you.
I really feel that way.
But you see...
This is the one thing I can do.
Shu!
Don't!
Yes, this is it! This, this!
No, Shu!
I should have known it would be you.
I've been running away all this time.
But right here, right now, I'm going to reveal myself!
His right hand!
Shu...
A royal gun salute to mark the king's birth!
I'm sorry, Ayase.
Shu...
No need to hold back! Fire every bullet you've got!
I know this is selfish and inconsiderate,
but would you let me rely on your powers one last time?
Shu, you...
Ouma Shu!
How about this?
Do you have it in you to kill me?
I've decided.
I'll get my hands as dirty as I have to, for their sake.
It's inside me...
Inside me…
Another person's heart...
...the light of the Void!
Shu!
Look!
Shu's body!
The cancer?
But it wasn't there a second ago!
It's mine.
That's my cancer.
Then Shu's Void is...?
His Void gathers everything and assumes its weight.
Strengths, weaknesses, light, darkness...
Everything.
Shu... Are you telling me that's your destiny?
Are you telling me that's your will too, Kurosu?
If the Apocalypse virus turns misery into bad will,
I'll assume that bad will, too.
The bad will can sink into my body.
I'm coming, Inori.
Now that I am all alone in this world,
what should I feel and think?
After we spend countless days together
and shared our feelings,
we will never be truly apart
I took you for granted, and now you are gone
That's the pain I've come to bear
Even if I had held onto your hand when you left me,
and not let you go,
I would have done it purely out of self-interest
I'm such a horrible liar
When I whispered that I was doing it all for you
you had already stopped believing it
Now I run to you to make up for it,
no matter how often I may fall or get lost
Wait for me, I'm coming to meet you,
no matter what hardships may await me