Keep life going.
For the sake of new lives to come,
It's been a while
don't forget to get vaccinated
since I took this monorail to school.
This is a government bulletin.
The time I spent with the Undertakers felt much longer than it really was...
And the truth is, going to school scares me.
Hey, look.
Isn't that the guy who got picked up by GHQ?
Oh, I know about him! Hiromi said she saw it all.
So he's a criminal?
Let's go.
Hey, he ran away.
Inori, watch out! That guy's a criminal, you know!
That's not something you say without evidence.
If you're a true Tennozu First High School student, you should be ashamed of yourself.
So, everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
I'm yours
Say, there's lots of happiness in this world, isn't there?
Someday, if we're together
Even if someone calls you a liar
and tries to hurt you with cruel words,
even if the world does not try to believe you
and places a crown of thorns upon your head,
I can take your side, and yours alone
I know your pain and loneliness
So everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
round dance
Shu!
Did the GHQ employees treat you well?
It must have been a nuisance to be interviewed,
but we have to cooperate with the government, don't we?
Y-Yes! Apparently a cell phone I found belonged to GHQ, so...
I see.
I'm sure plenty of people spread nasty rumors,
but if you ever need anything, I'll—
Shu!
Is it really Shu that I see afoot?!
How was GHQ?! You got interrogated, right?!
Did they feed you pork on rice?!
Wait, it's GHQ, so would they have hamburgers and stuff?
Er, no...
Ouma.
Can I ask something too?
Is the military really full of homos?
Huh?!
Were there any scary soliders?
Did you see any Endlaves?
You're climbing the stairway to adulthood, you jerk!
Ouma, I didn't know you knew President Kuhouin.
Miss President, please shake my hand!
Be quiet, everybody! Calm down!
It looks like I was worrying too much.
Yes, it does.
But...
Um... thank you. For looking out for me.
No thanks necessary.
I only did what any student council president would.
Kuhouin Arisa, student council president.
She's the heir to the Kuhouin Group,
an all-around hottie, a star student,
and she's got a sparkling personality. Amazing, huh?
Anyway, here's the World History homework,
and this folder has the Infection Control text.
It's kind of heavy stuff, but...
Thanks. You're a lifesaver, Hare.
Nah, it's nothing.
Huh... I forgot we had an Infection Control exam.
Hey, Shu.
Has something changed?
Hmm? What do you mean?
By the way...
What happened to Yahiro?
I heard he hadn't come to school since the day I got picked up...
Do you know anything, Inori?
You're worried? He betrayed you.
I don't really know.
Shu! Are you home?
Haruka!
Haruka?
You—hide!
I'm ho—
Oh, my!
Haruka! You're wearing that again?!
Shu, you're not happy to have your mother back home?
That's not it...
Okay, then.
Hello, there! I'm Ouma Haruka.
My name is Yuzuriha Inori. Shu's been kind enough to let me live here.
It's not what you think! Er, she has a violent older brother,
and he's really awful to her, so I'm hiding her here!
But, see, he acts like a saint in front of other people,
so nobody doubts him... plus he's really tough...
...and kind of cool...
What am I saying?
No, okay, the thing is—
Man, am I hungry!
Huh?
Inori, are you hungry?
What do you want, pepperoni pizza or cheese?
Hmm, I kind of think I want cake.
Shu, would you go pick some up?
What, now?
Yep. We'll have a tasty dinner while you tell me the whole story.
Gai, are you sure it was okay to let Shu go back to school?
He'll make a good decoy.
Well, Inori's with him, at least.
Gai, the last few fights have left us short on equipment.
We got some money out of the OAU, didn't we?
We may have funds, but we don't have a way of buying weapons,
or means of transporting them.
We need a partner.
Controls on the market are only getting tighter.
The Kuhouin Group's overall distribution control
is down 25 points from last year.
Article 301 of GHQ's special law taking effect last month is what—
I don't need excuses for your failure.
Bring me results next time.
Arisa. You're coming with me to the party tomorrow.
Yes, Grandfather.
I'll be leaving the backroom jobs in your hands too one day.
So plan accordingly.
I know, Sir.
I know.
Because I'm Kuhouin Arisa.
Inori's cute!
A little strange, but...
How to put it... she makes you feel protective, I guess?
I suppose...
She's a lot stronger than me, but...
she seems really weak sometimes, too.
Hey!
Cut it out, you drunk.
Can't a mother cuddle her son?
I... guess so...
There it is!
Thank goodness!
With this, I can manage to make an impression at tomorrow's party!
Gotta strike a good blow when you take a new post
or you don't make an impression, right?
As of today you guys are my subordinates,
so let's show some guts, okay?
I don't mean any offense, Colonel Eagleman, but—
Dan!
I told you, keep things friendly and call me "Dan"! Remember?
Mr. Dan... these Dragoons are surface-to-air missiles,
and therefore are not designed to fire on a ship at sea...
We can do it!
If they can fly up, they can fly sideways too!
And what ship might we be targeting?
Awesome question, Scarface!
I'm Segai.
A Jap who's hostile to GHQ is having a party at sea.
He must be planning to strike a deal outside of quarantined waters.
Where did you obtain that information, Sir?
An upstanding citizen reported it.
You see, most Japs understand
that this country can't live without us at GHQ!
It's been ten years now since GHQ took over administration of our country.
It seems that was rather too long for us to bide our time.
We, the Japanese people, must raise our heads and stand on our own two feet.
Are you nervous, Shu?
Of course I am! You just called me up out of the blue with a mission.
A little late for cold feet.
Yeah, maybe.
So, what's the mission, anyway?
There's someone I want to talk to.
But the guy's not the type to appear on the public stage very often.
So we're forcing ourselves on him at his party?
Precisely.
I didn't think you'd do me the honor of attending.
Did you tell Keido about today?
No.
And after all, I bear a part of the responsibility for this.
It was an accident.
A tragic accident.
Haruka?!
She was talking about this party?!
I'm sorry.
Ouma?! What are you doing here?
Crap!
Stop right there!
Gai! The rest is up to you!
Stop right there, Ouma Shu!
What exactly are you doing?
Please excuse me. You reminded me of an old acquaintance.
Acquaintance?
Yes. Her name was Catherine...
...and she was my pet armadillo when I was young.
She really was just like you,
the way she'd curl up into a tight, little ball to protect herself.
I feel bad, making you a GHQ errand boy like this.
Not at all, Sir. With the Leukocyte Plan impeded,
it's only natural that the Anti Bodies be dropped.
And Daryl and Rowan?
They didn't run away fast enough.
Right around now they're with the sportsman, throwing the first pitch.
We've finished preparations to fire the missiles sideways, Sir.
Nice! Way to show some guts!
See, I knew you could do it!
You have got to be kidding me.
Where's our target?
It's en route from Point L-11 to Point R-22, just like the report said.
I'm Ouma, with Sephirah Genomics. Pleased to meet you.
This might be the first time I've ever seen Haruka at work.
Shu, get a message to Gai! Dragoons are targeting that ship!
Dragoons?
They're tactical missiles. A commercial ship doesn't stand a chance!
Haruka!
Get off that thing now! There's a ferry, so take Gai and—
No!
If I run, what happens to the people on this ship?
We can't do anything about that!
What are you going to do, Shu?
Gai and I will manage something, just you watch.
I don't recall sending you an invitation...
Tsutsugami Gai of the Undertakers.
I imagine you'll grant me an invitation next time.
What's that?
Sir, I'd like you to purchase Japan's future.
Gai!
Excuse me.
Tsugumi says GHQ missiles are coming for this ship!
So they want to take us down, ship and all?
Give me your orders, Gai. What do we do to save this ship?
Wait on the quarterdeck. I'll be there in five minutes.
Got it.
Okay, let's give this a whirl! Target: R-14!
Dragoon... fire!
I'll save you for sure!
Miss Arisa, please give me the next waltz.
No, please dance it with me.
Here, give me your hand.
Hey! Who the hell are you?
Sorry, but we're doing a rock 'n roll number.
You've got less than a minute before impact!
Let go of me! I've never met such a rude man before in my life!
I'm honored to be your first.
Don't get smart with me! I—
Close your eyes.
I'm about to cast a spell on you.
A spell to let you become your true self.
My true...
Yes. Your true self.
After I count down from three, open your eyes.
Good. Don't move.
Three. Two. One.
Zero.
Ouma?!
Pardon me!
It's dead on target!
The Dragoon has... vanished...
What?!
Impossible! Are you sure your instruments haven't gone haywire?
We didn't have enough guts!
Huh?!
All right, then... Next time we'll fire all of them!
But Sir...
Okay, men, let's get serious now!
Fire!
They've launched more Dragoons!
One, two, three—that many?!
Shu!
On it!
The coward's shield that armors the weak self inside.
That's your Void, Kuhouin Arisa.
Hey!
Why aren't you shooting?!
Well... we're out of missiles, Sir.
I concede that your group has a means
of defending against a second-order Leukocyte.
A live demonstration makes for very convincing evidence.
You have a deal.
Thank you very much. I'll inform Gai.
I have good news.
The Kuhouin Group will be aiding us with our domestic routes.
Yay!
I can operate Steiner!
But I wonder how GHQ knew about the party at sea...
An upstanding citizen reported it.
Huh?
Someone who calls himself upstanding can't possibly be that.
Only you, Gai.
You suddenly fainted on deck. Don't you remember?
No.
But I must thank you for carrying me here.
You talked in your sleep, you know.
Eavesdropping? What a disgusting hobby!
You really suck at this.
At what?
I'm perfect in academics, sports, etiquette—everything!
You suck at letting people spoil you.
See you later!
Haruka, don't come outside in that!
Okay, okay.
For crying out loud...
It looks like fun, though.
You look like you're having fun.
Hey, Inori.
For the first time, I think maybe I'm glad I can use Voids.
I see.
Yeah, I know. We have to protect Shu's future.
These days you love me no more
nor am I still treasured by you
Now I am all alone
What did you tell me when we parted?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender