This is where we part.
Goodbye, Ouma Shu.
This is why I can't leave you... to your own devices...
Gai...
A Void? That entire town?
Yes. Roppongi Fort is a phantasm given form by a single girl's heart.
Ouma Mana, I assume?
Here's the Void information I promised you.
Take it.
I appreciate your cooperation.
But the fare you paid only gets you this far.
What a cold man.
Don't tell me you're...
So you finally remember? You're as dense as ever...
... Shu.
You're...
So, everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
I'm yours
Say, there's lots of happiness in this world, isn't there?
Someday, if we're together
Even if someone calls you a liar
and tries to hurt you with cruel words,
even if the world does not try to believe you
and places a crown of thorns upon your head,
I can take your side, and yours alone
I know your pain and loneliness
So everything that makes me whole
I'll give that to you now
So you finally show yourself... Daath grave keeper...
Grave keeper?
Shuichiro worked so hard that we decided to cooperate.
Follow him... Shu...
They plan to... sacrifice Inori... to awaken Mana!
Mana?
Where are you taking Inori?!
Shu!
What's going on?
Inori!
Ouma Shu, if you're that determined to come with us,
please do so after you've remembered everything.
All the memories of Mana that you yourself sealed away...
Shu. All set.
Open your eyes now, Shu.
This is amazing, Mana!
Isn't it? This is your big sister's secret place.
You're the only one I'll tell.
Huh? What's that?
Is he dead?
Everything's okay!
Can you hear me?
I'm Shu. Ouma Shu.
I'm Ouma Mana.
And you are?
Maybe he's not sure.
We're asking your name. Your name!
Well...
"Triton."
You came from the sea. So you're Triton.
Isn't that a great name?
That's right... My big sister Mana and I met a boy that day.
That boy Mana called "Triton"...
Gai.
And we spent a summer together.
The year of Lost Christmas...
The last summer we could all spend smiling.
Hey, are you serious about jumping?
It'll be fine! Believe in me!
You're next! Come on!
See? You did it.
Yeah.
And as we spent time together,
he became special to me enough to call him a best friend.
I had Mana, the gentle big sister I loved, and my best friend Gai...
That was the happiest, most fun summer of my life.
So why... why did I forget?
About Gai, and Mana too.
Awake now?
Where are we?
Inori!
What is this?! Please, give back Inori!
This girl has never been more than an "instance body" we created
to use as an interface for communication with Mana.
The words "give back" aren't really appropriate.
Created?
And as the first person who ever touched the rock that started it all,
Mana was the first one infected with the Apocalypse Virus. In other words, Eve.
Her soul which had lost its body is now being poured into a new body,
and thanks to our labors, she is about to set foot in this world again.
Her resurrection will mark the second coming of Lost Christmas.
The Apocalypse Virus shall run rampant over all the Earth.
I must bear witness to that event.
Daath seems to have some hopes for you,
but if you ask me, you're just a child.
So stand back...
...and watch quietly.
Inori!
You mustn't interfere.
He's about to propose to Mana through Inori.
Propose...?
You see, her chosen partner
will become the progenitor of the next generation, the new human race.
Even the selfish Eve can be controlled, if you use the stone.
I trust we can count on you to bless their future together?
This can't be...
Marry?
Yep. If I marry someone, will you be lonely, Shu?
Marry who?
Someone! Maybe Triton.
Triton?! You can't do that!
I'm joking, Shu.
I'd never marry that guy.
He looked at me with adult eyes, you know.
Leering eyes.
Think that's gross?
I don't know.
But you can look at me with adult eyes, Shu.
Sis?
I love you, Shu.
It's the virus, isn't it?
Those spots are from the virus in that rock.
Dad said it makes people go crazy.
What do you want to do with Shu, Mana?
I'm the one who brought you back from the dead.
That means you're mine.
I can do whatever I want with you.
Right?
M-Mana...
I am going to tie the knot with Shu.
And I won't let anyone get in my way. Got that?
Hey, Shu.
Promise me...
that you'll marry me.
O ye chosen fittest pair, perform the coming together of blood
that shall shape the new race.
Stop it!
Bad Shu.
You have no right to get angry.
You shunned me, didn't you?
I was right there back then, wasn't I? Shu.
What do you mean?
You don't remember anything? Did you forget?
I'll have to punish you, then.
Are you okay, Shu?!
Ayase!
This is why I can't leave you to your own devices!
Gai! What about your wounds?!
He didn't hit any vital organs. The cancer crystals saved me.
Tsutsugami Gai.
I've been waiting for this moment.
The moment I can confront you... and Mana!
My hidden camera footage was as staticky this time as when I shot the Void,
but I believe you can see it clearly.
It's Sephirah's prototype filter.
Why did you let us through?
I was booted out of the arena, you see.
This is my little way of picking on him.
You're too late, though.
Destiny can't be changed.
Shu! Run!
Shu!
Tsugumi! Emergency bailout!
Gai, I can still fight!
Spiral nuptial vows, here and now.
Remember, Shu.
Some part of you must remember what happened that day.
That day?
Lost Christmas.
December, 2029.
We were in Tokyo.
Your new mother, Ouma Haruka, had brought us here.
And on December 24th, I asked you to come to a church in Roppongi.
I wanted to talk to you about the Mana you didn't know.
But the one who came...
wasn't you.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Open it.
You're my knight, aren't you Triton?
So keep on protecting me.
Take a shot at that star.
Triton.
I loved you, you know.
Just kidding.
Triton?
Triton! What happened?
Triton?!
Take this, Shu.
Let's use our genes to make a new world.
It's okay. Don't be scared.
Let's do something fun together, Shu.
Stay away from me... you monster!
Sis?
No!
Sorry.
Sorry, Shu.
Don't be scared.
Your big sister's scared, too!
At this rate... I'll become someone who isn't me!
And so Mana ended up destroying herself with her own out-of-control power.
Yes... Mana looked to us for help that day...
And we couldn't give it to her.
So Gai, you said...
I'm going to get stronger.
Goodbye.
I'd forgotten.
I was protecting myself by forgetting!
Shu. You can tell right now, can't you?
We have something we need to do.
Get Mana's heart back.
That's right.
They awakened her against her will,
and we're going to put her to sleep again!
Use the Void's power to consign her bad will to oblivion!
Memory's shackles are undone, and you're in new king mode, eh, Ouma Shu?
Time is running out. Draw out my heart, Shu.
And then give me the Void!
The way you are right now, I know you can do it!
Draw it out without letting go of my hand.
This is... Gai's...
Run, Shu.
You're going to cover me while I head for Mana.
Got it.
Here we go.
Inori!
Who are you calling, Shu?
Gai!
A Void that forces other Voids to manifest?!
A gun that draws out people's hearts, then...
Gai, go!
Right!
Stop!
Stand down, Shuichiro.
You failed.
Gai!
Stab Mana right through me, Shu.
I'm a dead man either way. So...
But—
Shu, what do I look like to you right now?
As a child you were decisive, and brave, and... strong...
I wanted to become like you.
Gai! What are you...?!
You can become me whenever you want. Just like I became you.
Do the rest on your own.
Come on. Hurry up!
Gai!
Shu...
What did you tell me when we parted?
Tri... ton?
The words hung in midair and never reached me
Mana... I finally reached you.
I know my dreams and wishes are illusory
Gai! Gai!
and yet I cannot give up on them
You said, "Don't let go, hold onto my hand"
and, "We will always be together"
I'm sure Gai is satisfied.
I could hear him saying thank you.
Your hands as I held them were warm
and tender