Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next.
Hey, girls!
Let’s go swimming!
C’mon, hurry up!
I’ll come later.
It’s bad to swim so soon after eating.
I’ll be fine! I’m going in first!
Hey! Not so fast, it’s slippery!
Too late.
Spinning around…
Geez, what energy!
Can’t we tone it down or something?
I doubt it.
Hey! Looky there!
Ain’t those babes super hot?
Awesome!
The one on the right…
Half Caucasian? What a babe!
That tall one is a real looker, too!
The short one knows the ropes.
She’s probably got experience.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Nara!
Karasuma!
Harima!
Tenma Tsukamoto in a sudden downpour
Kenji Harima, all “turtles” on his report card
There, once around the world!
Are the others ready?
B-Boys are hitting on them!
Yay! I’ll join them!
But wait a minute! If I went
over now, would I be in the way?
A definite 5th wheel?
They’re 3 to 3.
Couples all over the place, too.
Careful,  it’s slippery.
And right now Karasuma-kun and I are on bad terms.
Agh! It’s frustrating!
Never mind! I get hit on, too!
I mean, I wanna get hit on!
Me?
Yes, I’m studying in Japan.
My mom is in Sweden running a company.
Never mind about me.
Huh? But that leaves me nowhere.
Come on, just talk to me.
So, what’s your capital per asset ratio like?
I went around twice, already.
They’re still at it!
I’ll have to go around again.
Fine! Now I’ll make it a test of speed!
Here we go!
Hey, are you okay?!
Huh?
Aren’t you Tsukamoto-san?
Oh, I thought I’d drowned
a girl in middle school.
Middle school?! I’ll have
you know I’m sixteen. Sixteen!
Whoever you are, since
you’re in middle school,
show more respect for your elders!
Are you kidding? I’m in your class.
I’m Nara. Kentaro Nara!
I know that.
What a grouch. You’re a
middle-schooler, after all.
So you want to be like your friends
and get asked out by boys?
Sure, I know I’m kind of childish compared to them, but I want to look like…
A woman…
once in a while, too.
But you’re like a buddy
who’s easy to talk to.
Kind of clueless, in a good way.
Cruel!
Not that I have trouble talking to boys,
but it never leads to anything romantic.
Oh, why, oh why, should that be?
If… If that’s the case…
Maybe I should ask you out.
I said maybe I should ask you out.
Yay!
Now I can brag about this to Yakumo!
Umm… uh… Well, how about karaoke after this?
Nara-kun’s so nice!
After all, Karasuma-kun
was never this sweet.
What’s wrong?
Thank you.
But I’m sorry. There’s this boy I like.
Don’t let go, now.
Don’t worry. You’re swimming fine.
Tsukamoto likes a guy? Who?
Hey, hey.
Maybe I should let go and practice.
Then I’ll get better.
Huh? You think so?
Tsukamoto-san!
That scared me.
But I swam 15 meters! A new record!
Thanks, Nara-kun!
Huh? What’s wrong?
Oh, uh… nothing.
You’re weird!
Tsukamoto feels… soft…
Huh. You came with your
friends from middle school?
Yeah. They’re all cool, good guys.
Then I can be their friend, too, can’t I?
Sure.
Oh, that’s them. Hey!
Yo, Nara. Where were you?
Huh? Tsukamoto, how
come you’re with Nara?
These are your friends?!
Yeah.
This girl is their friend, too?
That makes it easy. Let’s go out.
No, we can’t!
Let’s decide this with a contest.
Contest?
Sounds like fun.
Hey, Sawachika!
If we win, you buy us dinner
on the way home.
Oh, Akira, that’s mean.
We’d planned to go
to my favorite restaurant.
A high school student’s allowance
couldn’t even pay for the appetizer.
You’re gonna do it?!
Nice bluff, though. We actually
planned to eat at a noodle stand.
But, if these two are serious, we can win!
Okay, we’re in! What about you?
Let’s see, what contest should we have?
Swimming!
What’s going on? Swimming contest?
Hey, the girls are cute!
I’m rooting for the blond one.
Among the eight of us, the fastest swimmer will win for his team!
I can’t lose. If I end up dating anyone,
I’ll be betraying the guy I like.
I know I can’t win…
But…
With the four of us, we can’t lose!
On your marks.
Get set…
Go!
You should have told me you couldn’t swim!
We’re sorry.
We thought at least one of us could.
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
There should be a set schedule for rain!
Lucky. I’ll wait under here.
Yo. You came in from the rain, too?
Eh? Yeah…
What’ll I do?
I’ve been distant from Karasuma-kun ever since the curry incident.
I’ve got to make up with him.
This has got to be a chance from God.
I wonder if Karasuma-kun is mad at me.
Or disgusted with me.
I want to be friends again.
Um, Karasuma-kun—
A k-kappa costume…
Karasuma-kun had his rain gear all ready.
Karasuma-kun, I know it’s after the fact, but…
Don’t you have the wrong “kappa”?
No, don’t do it! If I correct him,
he’ll never make up with me!
I love Karasuma-kun.
That’s why I’ve got to be quiet.
No, I’ve got to tell him!
Karasuma-kun! Um…
I’ve been wanting to tell
you from the start.
That’s… that’s…
Here. You can borrow this.
I can’t leave you here all by yourself.
But this kappa set is only for one.
Weren’t you getting upset because you
didn’t want to stay here all by yourself?
You thought I was going to leave.
Huh? Or was I mistaken?
No. You weren’t mistaken at all.
Sis should be around here.
Yakumo!
Did you come to get me?
Sis?
Sis, what’s that?
Karasuma-kun lent this to me.
It’s a little big, though,
since it’s a boy’s size.
Karasuma-kun said he’ll be fine
with just the head piece!
Really? Isn’t that nice?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Look, there’s Harima.
Yeah, they say he’s back in school.
Rumor has it that he stayed away,
because he got involved in a fight.
No wonder he looks even scarier.
Like a wolf that crawled out
of a world closed to decent folk.
Too many things happened, so he couldn’t care less about the rumors.
Crime and Punishment
Dostoyevsky
About summer vacation…
I always wanted to go to the beach.
Actually, it’s not like I told her
how I felt and she rejected me.
I’ve still got a chance.
From now on, in school,
I’ll talk to Tenma-chan all I can!
And so, summer vacation starts tomorrow.
But now this happens!
Anyhow, we’ll hit the beach first!
We made a date with those boys, after all.
Still, I don’t know why we have to date
guys who seem like they’re all talk.
Mikoto is just too much of a prude.
Anyhow, you should get more experience.
Otherwise, you’ll screw up
when the real thing comes along.
I don’t know who she’s
interested in, though.
It’s just like Mikoto to save herself
for her true love. Beautiful.
You sure act weird these days.
It’s summer.
What’s that mean?!
I heard that.
Tenma-chan’s going to the beach
with those guys?
I’ll get them! No, I’m jealous!
I’ve got to hear more.
I’ll casually go closer…
Danger!
I gotta go to the toilet.
Men’s Bathroom
Crazy hag! She’s mad
at me for that incident!
You made a mistake!
I’d never say I liked you!
For crap’s sake!
Maybe I should grab that guy going to the
beach with Tenma-chan and beat ’im up!
Help…
But even if I did, I still wouldn’t
get to go to the beach with her!
So maybe I should just
ask Tenma-chan out!
Huh? Hey, that sounds like
a more constructive way.
Yeah, that’s it.
Right. I’ll do that.
Okay, here’re your report cards!
Harima!
Yes.
Oh, that reminds me, Harima…
About that letter you gave me, it was…
Shut up, or I’ll make you.
Try a little harder: modern language,
classical literature, math, science…
Crap. Nothin’ but turtles.
You’re just like me!
Ten—! I mean, Tsukamoto!
I got all turtles, too.
Th-Thank God I was born stupid!
Here goes!
Tsukamoto, I want to talk to you.
If you want…
How about going to a movie with me?!
And here’s where we’ll be going.
That’s a pretty nice place.
Is breakfast included?
Maybe that was kinda sneaky,
whisking Tsukamoto-san away like that.
But I like her, too.
I’m fine, but what about him?
Dad, where are you?! Dad?!
Are you okay with this, Harima?
Yeah.
Summer’s here, but I have
to take review courses.
Awful. At least, that’s what I thought.
But Akira-chan’s my tutor. Lucky!
Lucky!
That reminds me, Tsukamoto-san,
we’re sleeping overnight on our trip.
Are you packed?
Yes! All set!
I forgot! There was that beach-trip problem!
Interesting.
Crud! That guy going with her…
Naturally, he’s after Tenma-chan.
The Cutest!
She’s the cutest girl in the bunch.
Damn it!
Who’s going with her, anyway?
I’ll find him and I’ll pound him with my fist of justice, I mean, fist of love.
No, no, no!
I’m a changed man.
I’ll try a more positive approach.
Right!
What’s so funny, punk?!
Don’t I look good in my bikini shorts?!
Tennoji is the same animal as always.
I’m never gonna do those things anymore.
Right, guys?
What? All three of you can’t go?!
That’s right. We had a run-in
with a weird delinquent.
Rats. I can’t be the only guy there.
I guess I’ll have to
talk to Tsukamoto-san.
But this might be good!
It’ll be a way to get
closer to her naturally!
Okay! I’ll go to school tomorrow!
Tsukamoto-san is taking review lessons!
Let’s see, what guys
can I get as replacements?
Imadori-kun is popular with girls,
so he’s dangerous.
Hanai-kun is too bossy.
And Harima-kun seems to like
Tsukamoto-san, and he’s scary.
Anyhow, I’ve got to
hide it from those three.
Good mor—!
Oh, Nara-kun! What’s up?
Did you come about the trip?
I heard about it!
The trip’s called off?
But after all that planning,
it seems wasteful.
So here’s my idea. We can
just invite three other boys!
Oh no!
What? He’s Tenma-chan’s date for the beach?!
Bad Dude
But I’m a delinquent.
I can’t just go off on a trip with a bunch from school.
No, no, no!
I’m a changed man!
Fine. I’ll put on a smile and…
Mellow Dude
I wanna go to the beach!
That’s it! Here goes!
Mellow Dude
I wanna go to the…
I wanna go to the beach!
Beach, beach, beach…
Okay! Imadori’s in!
No need to be that sudden…
Forget the smile. That’s not the real me.
Aloof!
Want me to come with you?
That’s it!
Want me…
Want me to come with you?
Okay! Hanai’s in!
Now we need just one more!
What about inviting Yakumo?
That’s one extra girl,
but that can’t be helped.
Whaddya mean, “Can’t be helped”? Jerk!
Yakumo? I’m not sure she’d go.
She’s really bashful around people.
Ah, summer! Review lessons are over.
I sure wanna go swimming!
Harima-kun’s dying to go.
They used to call me, “Kappa Harima.”
Nope,
there’s nobody else you can invite from our class.
Everybody’s probably busy.
I’ve got so much spare time.
All right. I’ll ask Yakumo and see.
Please do.
Time to flirt, time to flirt.
Hey, hey, I’m being left behind? Dammit-t-t!
I missed my chance to go to
the beach with the girl I love!
Ten—, I mean, Tsukamoto…
I’m sorry. I came back for something.
And…
She knows how I feel.
Harima-kun! Come with us to the beach.
Don’t tell me… Could Tenma-chan…
You’re my goddess, after all!
I accept your love!
Harima-kun, good luck, okay?
What?
I’m rooting for you!
I don’t know what girl you like, though.
See you at the beach!
No way…
That’s a big mistake, Tenma-chan.
Wait a minute.
This might be my big chance.
In any case, I’m going to
the beach with Tenma-chan.
And… and…
Awwright!
Kenji Harima will make a
comeback at the beach!
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
A rugged spirit awakens my wild side.
Just wait, Tenma-chan,
it’ll happen at the beach!
Next on School Rumble:
Save me at the beach!
Save me naked!
Just save me! For real!
“Save me at the beach! Save me naked! Just save me! For real!”
Why do these things happen to me?!
Haruki Hanai, Homemade Box Lunches.
Kenji Harima, Fully Bared.
Kyousuke Imadori, Locked on Target!
Kentarou Nara, Arises.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!