Coming up next!
Coming up next…
CLOSE THE TAP TIGHTLY AFTER USE
CONSERVE WATER!
Thank you.
Hot, isn’t it?
Man, it’s summer.
Suou, is something wrong?
Mikoto isn’t that cute, is she?
N-No, there’s nothing, especially…
If something’s bothering you,
you shouldn’t hold it inside.
It’s not like you.
Yeah… He’s right.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Summer
Friendship
Fireworks
Women’s fight— 2-round match
Hanai, expert martial artist.
Harima, new hire at Dankousha.
I was wrong. I’m sorry, Harima-kun!
It doesn’t bother me.
Oh! You really changed your style.
Yes.
That’s great, Tazawa-kun. This is much better.
Wow, this is amazing.
Is that so? Uh, my name is Harima.
Your use of this spread is very good.
It’s not “Tazawa”…
You’ve got potential.
But in real life,
things between Tenma-chan
and me never turn out like that.
Oh, no! I can’t let Blondie see this.
If Tenma-chan should ever
find out what’s in here!
Harima-kun, you’re the worst of the worst!
That girl’s gonna tell her! I just know it!
Wait a minute!
Why is she chasing me?!
Can she be after this?!
Why are you running from me?!
I can’t let her see this!
Stop, I said!
Crud. Sawachika just won’t answer.
I don’t even know why
she came at me like that.
Well, Harima seems to
be involved in it somehow.
Move!
Harima?!
Hey! Over here!
Café El Cado
Sorry I dragged you in here like this.
Oh. No…
Can she be after my manuscript, too?
So the thing is… um…
I want to ask you about something.
Ask me something?!
So it’s about this, after all?
You see…
I see.
Before I knew it, everybody
found out about my comics.
You are cute, after all.
But why the panic?
I’m sorry. I see I’ve interrupted your date.
D-Date?!
Look, there’s an important reason for this…
Sorry! To tell the truth,
I’m drawing comics!
Harima! Take care of that!
Iced coffee
American coffee
What was that all about?
Stop!
But she wouldn’t, would she? Jerk!
Why should I run from her?!
She really is fast. But never
underestimate a martial artist!
Rats!
Idiot!
Wonder if she gave up?
Why’d she give up?
Yo, Hanai! I’m back.
Whoa, I really messed up today.
Hey! What happened?
I ripped my skirt, so I’m gonna
change to my sparring uniform.
What happened?!
I fell, that’s all.
Liar…
Hey!
Um, excuse me…
Please give Suou-san’s coat
and bag back to her.
What did you do to Suou?!
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
I don’t know what’s going on, but ain’t
you underestimating me a little?
I don’t know what’s going on, either.
If possible, I’d like a calm explanation.
However…
since you’re a delinquent
whose only answer is violence,
sometime I wish I could teach you a lesson.
Just try it.
Agh! My manuscript!
I’m not falling for that!
Take that!
Why didn’t he dodge it?
Arm lock?!
Y-You stopped, didn’t you, bastard?
I got no interest in you, and I didn’t
think it was worth it to give my all.
But I can’t stand being underestimated.
It’s for real now.
I won’t have to hold back, either.
I’ll beat you to a pulp, head on.
Yes?
Eri-chan? It’s me, it’s me.
Um, about tomorrow’s fireworks show…
We haven’t set the place or time, yet, right?
Right.
How about meeting at 5 o’clock
in front of the station?
We can walk around first.
I guess so.
Okay, 5, then. Don’t come late, now.
I won’t. I’m not you.
Don’t worry! I don’t come late.
Ah, it’s not 5 o’clock Tenma Time, right?
What’s Tenma Time?
30 minutes over the arranged time.
You’re mean! That’ll never, ever happen!
5 o’clock
Meet in front of the station
Okay, if I’m late, I’ll treat you to ice cream.
Let’s see, about 30 cups.
You’ll get fat, Eri-chan.
But I’ll probably help you eat it all.
Say, Tenma?
Thanks.
Okay. ’Night, then.
Actually, I’m sorry.
I don’t think I can go.
I wonder if Sawachika’s coming…
to the fireworks show tomorrow night?
Mail?! Sawachika!
Tomorrow?! It can’t be, right?
And of all times, why now?!
He’s coming back…
Starting today, I’ll be your home tutor.
I’m Masahiro Kouzu. How do you do?
Don’t be so formal.
We’ve met before, besides.
Yes. Shall we begin, then?
Since middle school days, Kouzu-senpai was known for his smarts,
and our parents were friends,
so he came to be my home tutor.
Oh… wrong.
That’s… wrong.
Uhh… wrong.
Excuse me! I know I’m stupid!
You're correcting me so much just because
you don't want to teach me for free, aren't you!
But…
I know!
Join our martial arts school!
Build that puny body up!
Then we’ll be even!
To my surprise, Kouzu-senpai really did join.
Kouzu
I thought that he was naturally smart.
But I was wrong.
He was a hard worker.
And, as I watched him…
amazingly, I wanted to study harder.
I found that studies were
more fun than I thought.
And…
High
School
Entrance
Exam
Hall
May you pass the exam
Yagami Shrine
High
School
Entrance
Exam
Hall
High
School
Entrance
Exam
Hall
High
School
Entrance
Exam
Hall
But once the entrance exam was over…
… we were no longer teacher and student.
Even if we happened to pass in the hallway,
we stopped saying “hi” to each other.
Oh, no!
I can’t be wasting time!
Subject: How are you?
---------------------------------
Hi! Kouzu-senpai is
coming home, so we
are having a drinking
party.
The date and time are:
This was so sudden…
He’s coming back.
He’s coming back!
But tomorrow’s the fireworks show!
What awful timing!
What? You can’t go?!
I’m really sorry! There’s just
something I can’t get out of.
What’ll I tell Eri-chan?
I’m really sorry! I’ll call Sawachika.
Okay. ’Night.
I wonder if she’ll answer the phone?
Yes?
Sawachika? It’s me.
What?
U-Um… I-It’s kind of hard to say this… I…
So you want to break our date,
no questions asked for now?
What’s going on?
I’m sorry!
Tell me honestly. Is the reason… a guy?
Yeah.
A-Actually, the boy I like is coming home.
I… Last year, I was too chicken
to tell him how I felt,
and I always regretted it!
It’s been six months, and he’s coming back!
That’s why I want to tell him this time!
I understand.
You’d choose a guy over your friends, huh?
You’re the lowest.
Come off it!
You’re the one who dissed me first!
Why should I apologize?!
I’m gonna settle this, here and now!
The number you have dialed is…
It’s hopeless!
Forget it! I’m going to bed!
I know I’m wrong.
But I have a right to love, too.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Yagami Ginza
Maybe I should have had my hair done.
No, it’s bad to seem overeager.
Netami Bar
Here it is.
And it’s a bar! I’m getting
even more nervous!
This is nothing. It’s just like sparring.
Calm down, calm down, you…
I’ll tell him… I’ll tell him everything.
Hey, Miko-chan! Over here!
Look at this guy!
He ain’t changed one bit!
Yo, great to see you, Mikoto-chan.
Hey, is it true?
Masahiro, you actually
tutored a cutie like her?
Shocker, ain’t it?
This clueless, timid guy, bringing home a girl?!
What?
Lie
This is a lie.
Please
Please.
Uh
Uh…
Lie
But
But.
Please
Could I have been…
Fool
… a fool?
How do you do? The name is Suou.
He has helped me a great deal!
Wow, look at you, Teacher! She’s so pretty!
You make a great couple!
I’m laughing.
I really am a fool.
I hate it. To end like this…
I hate it.
You’re asking me out?
I’m sorry. I can’t go out with you.
’Bye.
Sawachika-san was asked again?
Who can resist? She’s pretty
and gracious to everybody.
Hey, but don’t you think
she’s getting a little too confident?
Really. She so thinks she’s all that.
Oh, Sawachika-san?
What’re you doing in a place like this?
Uh… oh, I thought I’d take in
a movie by myself, for a change.
Yagami Cinema
Only horror films are playing here.
Really?
Oh, well. I guess I’ll go home.
If you’re free, come over to my house.
We’re having hot pot.
But you gotta carry the groceries.
Yagami Cinema
Hey, how about having a drink with me?
It’s Miko-chan’s friend.
Real pretty, ain’t she?
Forget it, Tetsu.
You’d never win, even if you were 20 years younger.
Whaddya mean? I still got what it takes.
Why not go out with me and see, girlie?
Um… I’m sorry!
You got shot down!
Oh, man!
Ah! Look at you, Sawachika-san!
Did you come to party?
You forced me to come here!
Oh, my… You can make a face like that, too?
You’re right. This is how I am.
Is it a problem?
Suddenly, this endless feeling
Not at all.
Even if people talk dirt about you,
I feel as if it’s part of me now.
there’s no need to humble yourself.
It’s tough to watch that.
She knows about those rumors, and yet…
Flowing deeply, loudly inside of me
What do you mean? Don’t talk
as if you know everything.
It’s none of…
At times I’ve wounded and hurt you.
None of my business. I know.
Sorry. That’s the way I am.
So let the seasons change, please stay
I see. The way you are?
Yup, the way I am.
I wake up from a dream but I haven’t forgotten you.
Never, will I sleep again, ever.
You’ve never seen Japanese fireworks?
So, please, just let time stand still…
Okay, let’s go to the next
fireworks show together.
We have a special place for ourselves.
Sweet dream forever
You know Yagami Shrine, right?
I love you so much, yet when I’m this close to you.
You go through the woods in back.
It’s a narrow and pretty rough road, though.
I want to be sure again, to meet you once again.
But then…
if you go to the end of the road…
Do you have a same feeling as me?
Sweet dream forever
Blindingly bright
Mikoto… you came.
Yeah.
Am I bothering you?
You see…
Never mind.
I’d better go… for now.
Pretty, aren’t they?
Yeah.
I got…
I got dumped.
The guy who dumped you is stupid.
Thanks.
Yeah, well, it was one-sided
on my part, though.
I was comforted by Sawachika!
How stupid, two women
watching fireworks alone.
Hello, Tenma?
It’s me. I’m with Mikoto.
You coming?
Eri-chan! Miko-chan!
I’ve brought the gang!
Wow! This place has a great view!
You’re late, Tenma!
Sorry, I got lost.
Now, now, Sawachika.
So pretty!
Hey! Be careful!
Watch out! You won’t be
able to climb back up!
Are you all right?
Why the heck were we fighting up here?
I don’t remember.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Our gang gets together
on an outing for the tea club.
But I see Harima talking to Yakumo.
After Eri-chan and Miko-chan,
Harima’s chasing Yakumo now?
Her big sister won’t allow it!
Next on School Rumble:
But it’s the Tea Club…
It’s the Tea Club, but…
It’s the Tea Club, so…
You’re a player, aren’t you, Harima?
Tea club function.
Camping, go!
Night activity. Scavenger hunt.
Purposely paired.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!