Coming up next!
Hatenkou Robo Dojibiron is coming up next!
When you watch TV,
keep the room lighted and don’t sit too close.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Karen’s Love, Not Yet…
Karen’s Love, Little by Little…
Karen’s Love, And Then…
Today on Day Duty, Imadori and Ichijou
DAY DUTY
Imadori
Ichijou
The date promised… Does he remember?
What? Beard?
Yes. What do you think about it?
Well, that depends on the person.
Some look good in it, but others don’t.
What about a stubbly beard?
Stubbly? What’s that?
Mangoku! Mangoku! He looks so cool!
Um… Tsukamoto-san?
Uh… Have you seen Imadori-kun?
We have Day Duty today.
Oh, I just saw him in the hallway.
He was talking with Mihara.
Really? Thank you.
Poor you. Day Duty with Imadori…
Oh, no. Not at all. ’Bye.
She’s a nice girl.
We haven’t spoken that much, though.
That’s why I’m worried about her.
Well, what about this Sunday, then?
Huh? But…
We can’t go swimming, anymore,
but the beach is nice.
There’s a deserted island, too.
Didn’t you go there with Suou-san and the others this summer?
Silly. You just don’t understand.
The last of the summer beach
has to be with you girls.
What’ll I do?
Should I call out to him?
But…
Hey, Imadori!
Yes, Miko-chin!
Oh, I know! You’re worried
because I’m talking to other girls!
Idiot.
You and Ichijou are on Day Duty, right?
Thank you, Suou-san.
Um, I’m sorry to interrupt your conversation…
The thing is you and I have Day Duty…
Here!
Take him.
Oh, thank you again, Suou-san.
Agh, what a pain, what a pain.
They should make somebody else do this.
But it’s our job.
Do you really need me?
Couldn’t you manage by yourself?
We have to tie up
this lumber and carry it.
What? Are you serious?
This is pretty heavy.
We’ll need help!
Yes?
Look, can’t you manage fine by yourself, Ichi-san?
What?! No, I can’t!
After all, aren’t you Ichi-san?
The girl with the power of ten million?
No! Please help me!
And please stop calling me “Ichi-san”!
Um, did you go to the beach?
Yeah, with Miko-chin and the gang.
What about you?
Me?
That’s so nice. I envy you.
I wonder if Imadori’s forgotten
he asked me out on a date.
If I let go, maybe she won’t know?
So what did you do this summer?
Yes! Push-ups, running,
and basic strengthening
of the abs and back muscles!
From morning till night…
Nothing exciting…
This is heavy!
I’m sorry!
But didn’t you go on a date at least once?
U-Um… I… I’m supposed to go…
on one… w-with you…
I’m hungry…
He did forget, after all.
1 plus 1 is 2.
2 plus 2 is 4.
Add one more and that’s…
I wanted to go on a date…
Then come with me!
Ha! Ha! Hatenkou Robo!
Déjà vu?! This seems so familiar. But why?
She’s no D-cup. I’d never ask her out.
Salary
Yay! Money, money! Date!
Right now, I can ask Ichijou
on a date with this.
I accept.
Umm… It’s my first date!
I look forward to getting to know you!
It totally slipped my mind!
I see. No wonder she’s been
talking about a date.
That’s probably why she got me
to help on Day Duty. That means…
I’m about to be eaten alive!
B-Bad… If we keep talking about dating,
this powerful alien monster girl will…
Okay. From here on in,
no more talk about dating!
I won’t let her bring up the subject!
Kyousuke, don’t fail!
Miko-chin! How about a date?
Forget it, idiot.
I don’t think she heard me!
Our date! When do you want to go?
He remembered!
Wow, you’re really into it,
aren’t you, Ichijou?
Yes, sir! I’ve got to
put in two days worth.
Tomorrow I’m…
So you know? Tomorrow,
you’ve got to take on a match!
Tomorrow?
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Wow! What beautiful scenery!
This was fun.
Oh! Photos from camp?!
Yeah.
Look at these pictures.
Wow! What a romantic shot!
You ladykiller, Hanai!
Woo, woo.
That’s not my hand.
Hey, hey, what was going on here?
What happened, anyway?
Oh, what happened was—
Don’t you dare!
Wow! This is a great shot!
Yakumo-chan looks so good!
Yeah!
Wow, maybe Yakumo-chan
is bigger than a C-cup?!
Imadori, why you…
I’m not telling you!
But Miko-chin is number one, after all!
She’s a D-cup!
Pervert!
I thought Miko-chan was bigger…
N-No, I’m not!
Good grief…
So that’s it.
It slipped right by me.
I’m still too green.
Imadori-kun, your obsession
with breasts is bad.
Now, now, you’ll get there soon,
so don’t worry.
I’ll bite you!
Harima…
Lately, Harima has been letting
his beard grow like crazy.
Oh, you think so, too?
That reminds me, where is Harima-kun?
On the roof, probably.
What’s up with that, though?
That beard.
Like Abe Lincoln, somehow…
I’m going to call him.
To show him the pictures.
Right!
I’m sorry!
Kare-rin! I’m sorry.
Oh, I wanted… um…
to see Imadori-kun… um…
Oh, please don’t call me “Kare-rin”…
Imadori-kun? He’s in there. Shall I get him?
Imado—
I’m sorry. Um… um… you see…
What?! It’s that way with you and Imado—
C-Can’t breathe!
Oh, I’m sorry.
B-But how nice, to have a date…
But… I just found out a practice match
was suddenly set for tomorrow,
so I can’t go.
No!
Think carefully, Kare-rin. This summer,
how many matches have you had?
Um… about 25.
I’m sure. How many dates?
How many dates?!
Uh… um… not a single one.
It’s decided! You can enter
all the matches you want, later.
You should go on that date!
Fine! Leave everything to me! Everything!
I’ll take care of everything!
You just go on and enjoy your date. Okay?
Thank you.
Imadori-kun is late.
What’ll I say when he gets here?
“Oh, I just got here, myself…”?
I’d better practice.
Hi, there. Wanna go for tea?
Who are you?! Beat it!
Oh! Too bad!
Hi, there. Go for tea?
What? Go away!
Oh! Too bad!
Oh! Meeting someone?
See him later. Wanna go
for tea with me first?
I-I just got there myself!
I-I’m sorry. I didn’t get
that joke you just made.
Don’t worry about it.
Shall we go?
That was close.
Meat
Doowah.
Go for it.
Rope! Rope!
Sis, this isn’t pro wrestling.
I-Imadori-kun, what kind
of sports are you good at?
Anything.
What about contact sports?
Hate it. I don’t do
stupid things like that.
Uh… um… uh…
Wh-What’ll I do?
There’s nothing to talk about.
Well, if she’s bored,
she’ll probably go home.
I know! Those things!
I’ll give him those things
I got from Tsukamoto-san!
ONE
You don’t know what to do on a date?
Leave it to me!
Here!
What’s this?
It holds the secrets of dating.
If you need help on a date, open that bag.
There are three bags.
Thank you, Tsukamoto-san!
The secrets in the bag
will surely help you.
I wonder what’s inside? A book
with lots of topics, maybe?
Wh-What should I do with this?
Tsukamoto-san, I don’t understand!
Gimme.
Look, look. Giant boobs.
Yay.
I don’t quite understand,
but Imadori is terribly happy.
Thank you, Tsukamoto-san!
I’m over it.
Wh-What’ll I do? I opened the
first bag less than five minutes ago.
I’ll open the second bag!
Movie tickets?! Special show?
For kids? I don’t think
Imadori will want to go.
Ichijou…
Oh, this isn’t really…
You did good.
Doowah! Hatenkou Robo, Dojibiron!
Impact Merge!
You mustn’t give up!
The one who cherishes you is always beside you!
Doctor!
Now we’ve got to go for it!
Right!
That’s it, that’s it. Go, go. Yay…
Go, go…
I’m glad. It’s dark, and it’s hard to see his face…
But I can still be so close to him.
So this is what a date is.
That was fun!
Dojibiron is the greatest.
It’s gotta be movies to make you feel good!
Didja see that Hatenkou Chop?!
You’ve got guts!
You’re so anxious to get beat up?
Q-Quit it! It’s your fault
for standing so close!
Imadori-kun!
I’ve got to save Imadori-kun! But…
I don’t want him to think I’m a violent girl.
Wh-What can I do?
I know! I still have one bag left!
Please, help me!
Wh-What’s this?!
H-Hold it!
Meat
R-Release that person!
What kind of stunt is this?!
You’re giving me an apple to go away?!
Don’t make fun of me!
I’m sorry.
You’re Dojibiron?
The one who cherishes you
is always beside you!
Farewell!
Imadori-kun! Thank goodness you’re safe.
When I went to get help,
Dojibiron came to save you.
No, it was you.
Rats!
I’m missing the bag
that I put your mask in.
I wanted to be a tag team with you!
Sis, there’s no tag team
in amateur wrestling.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Miko-chin!
Will you help me with this?
Here, here! I’m up next in ancient lit.
Why should I help you?
Honestly, you’re so hopeless.
I’ll help you, but quit calling me
“Miko-chin.” It’s embarrassing.
Huh?
“Huh,” nothing!
But you’re “Miko-chin” to me.
There’re other ways to address me!
Um… well, then… “Mikoto.”
Imadori-kun sure is pushy.
He doesn’t care who’s around.
Why does Mikoto put up with him?
But look, don’t the two of them
look strangely natural together?
Don’t you think?
I don’t know.
Shallow guy!
You’re calling him shallow?
I’m not really shallow.
I don’t ask guys out on dates.
You always say people should
fall in love lots of times.
No, that’s not it.
Imadori’s insincere, somehow.
Your pet opinion is that people are free to fall in love.
Everybody’s way is different right?
That’s true, but…
Is Mikoto so important to you?
What?!
Hey, look, look!
Don’t they look like a
husband-wife comedy routine?!
So this is it, Miko-chin?
Tsukamoto-san!
Yes?
Kare-rin!
How did the date go, Kare-rin?
Um, that name is a little
too good for me, after all.
Um… Thank you for your help.
Here’re the bags I borrowed
and some cookies to thank you.
Yay! Awesome! Thank you!
Oh, no. They were such a big help.
Oh, and I washed it for you.
The mask.
Oh! Here it is!
But how come?
So did everything work out?
Y-Yes. I think we might
be a little closer now.
Imadori-kun might not think so, though…
You did it!
Oh, I’d planned to make a rabbit,
and put some cuts in the apples,
but I didn’t finish.
Still, I knew you could make do with it.
Yes, that’s why it was so easy!
To crush in one hand…
I’m so glad, though, that it worked out!
I envy you!
Oh, not at all…
Now you and Imadori-kun will…
What’s wrong, Tsukamoto-san?
I… I forgot! Imadori-kun likes Miko-chan!
G-Good luck, okay?!
Yes! Thank you for everything,
Tsukamoto-san! ’Bye…
D-Don’t worry about it!
Wh-What’ll I do?!
Agh, how irresponsible!!
I was happily rooting for
Miko-chan and Imadori-kun just now!
Bad thumb!
Kare-rin likes Imadori-kun.
But Imadori-kun likes Miko-chan.
Nothing’s working out!!
I wonder how Imadori-kun feels…
You beautiful creature,
are you free after class?
You’ve been on my mind.
Please go out with me—
Doowah!
Wh-What’s the big idea?!
Silence!
Listen carefully!
The one who cherishes you
is always—
I’m sorry, Kare-rin.
The truth is…
The truth is Imadori-kun likes Miko-chan.
I know.
Kare-rin!
There were two Ichijous.
She’s a space alien, after all!
Doowah!
Hatenkou Robo, Dojibiron! The movie!
Dojibiron Red
Yui Akae
1 plus 1 is 2
Dojibiron Pink
Mamiko Momoto
2 plus 2 is 4
I’m off!
Dojibiron Yellow
Ami Kishimizu
Add one more and that’s…
There, there.
Dojibiron Green
Hitomi Midoritame
5! Go! Go! Go!
Dojibiron Blue
Kaori Aomizu
All their courage brought together
Impact! Merge!
Impact! Merge! Hatenkou! Hya!
Go, #1!
Fly, #2!
Race, #3!
Burrow, #4!
Sing, #5!
One in heart
Five at the switch
Come together for one goal, never, never quit
Ha! Ha! Ha! Hatenkou Robo
Dojibiron!
Hatenkou Chop!
Fire!
I am Ganji Nishimoto.
Itoko-sensei agrees to pose for paintings.
And the subject matter is “nudes.”
Next on School Rumble:
Dreams for Art!
Promises to God!
Wish on a Star!
“Dreams for Art” and two others.
Sara Adiemas, nun at a church
Hiroyoshi Asou,
supervisor where Sara works part-time
Kenji Harima, his beard is too long.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!