Coming up next!
School Rumble...
is coming up next.
If you can read this, please install VSFilter or switch to the second subtitle track.
in a bright room and from a distance!
Please watch TV
These feelings I want to tell you are so heavy
At this rate, I'll be flattened down
So many feelings I can't describe into words
It just won't reach, to that special person
This short yet very far distance
The sky is always blue,
But you just can't keep staring at it
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
You, who always pretend to be tottering
I just want to jump onto your chest
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
Rising softly into the air,
I am drifting above the clouds again today!
Sketch Me Tender!
Aim that Arrow Message!
Teach-Me Pajama Party!
Suou Mikoto, her family runs
a contracting firm.
Sawachika Eri, a princess.
Takano Akira, loves part time jobs.
Today's art assignment will be portrait sketching.
Portrait
Sketching
Please study your partner well, and sketch them with your best effort.
Geez... my partner, huh?
Yeah, sorry it's just us.
We're the leftovers, I guess.
At least we can do it without any pressure.
Really? I find it rather boring to draw another girl.
But... it's quite hard to draw this part here...
Which part of me are you drawing?!
Haha, I'm kidding.
It's finished.
Hey, who is this guy again?
I'm the one who should be asking!
Oh, no! I'm paired up with Karasuma-kun!
Nice to meet you. Good luck!
She said "Good luck," but it's quite difficult for Karasuma-kun to sketch her when she covers her face like that...
Oh, no!
If I keep looking into his eyes...
I'll...
Ah, she froze.
What's with her...
Well it's easier for him to draw her now.
Karasuma-kun is looking at me...
Karasuma-kun is looking at me!
Look at me! Look at me with your whole life's worth!
Ah, but I want him to look at my future self too, just like this... forever!
I woke up late this morning and didn't brush my hair properly...
Karasuma-kun... excuse me... eh... restroom...
Sure. Go ahead.
I knew it, it's all over the place!
Why did it have to be today?!
It's Yakumo's fault! She didn't wake me up on time!
I'm back. Sorry for making you wait.
It's okay.  It's bad for your body to hold it in, you know.
He's got it all wrong...
That's not it! Karasuma-kun, you moron!
You know, I did this for you! All for you!
Even when I say that,
this is just for myself, isn't it?
All I wanted was for you to see the beautiful me, even for a bit.
And so... oh, stop it... there's no use thinking about it.
I'll just draw normally. Right... normally.
What should I do? When I try to draw him, our eyes will naturally meet.
I can't! I'm too nervous to look at him.
That's it! In a time like this, If I just bend my focus a little bit and draw...
What... what is that face?
She has a weird look in her eyes.
She's obscuring her vision.
There! I did it!
It's no use.
In this situation, I won't be able to draw anything.
Tsukamoto-san.
Sasakura-sensei.
It's fine if you don't think you can draw well.
See with your heart and just draw with your feelings.
See with my heart...
With my feelings...
That's right. His image is already in my eyes...
Even with my eyes closed, I will never lose sight of him.
In the end she closed her eyes.
The eyes of the heart, eh?
Portrait
Sketching
Alright, everyone please submit their work.
Tenma! Were you able to draw him after all?
U-Um... yeah...
Let's see, let's see.
This is...
Nicely done.
Seems like... I can occasionally draw really well.
What are you talking about?
But why is he looking sideways?
Ah, crap!
Sawachika, going to the cafeteria today?
Karasuma-kun, how did you draw me?
Did he draw me to be cute? If so, maybe he thinks I'm cute!
No, that's just wishful thinking! But still...
I want to see it! I want to see it so badly!
Lemme see!
UKIYOE
Note: Ukiyoe, a style of painting using woodcut blocks. Originated in 17th century Japan.
What should I do?
A love letter to Karasuma-kun...
If I can at least give it to him in an impressive way...
Lack of sleep?
I'm worrying over something!
Can't you tell just by looking? Geez.
I'm sorry.
By the way, it's about to start now...
What? It's already time?
The SequeL
The Three Who are Slashed
Note: "Sanbiki ga Kirareru" (The Three Who are Slashed) is a parody of a famous samurai drama "Sanbiki ga Kiru" (The Three Slashers). Tenma and Harima are big fans of Mangoku.
Further yet, the cast names shown are also parodies of the real cast from the original drama.
Ue-sama played by Takahashi Hideki
Mangoku played by Yakushamaru Kouji
Ika played by Shuufuutei Koyoru
Who the hell are you?
There's no use...
... talking!
Hey, hey.
Yeah! Go get 'em! Mangoku! Go! Go!
Nee-san, I can't see!
An arrow message?
That's it!
Nee-san, what do you mean by "that's it"?
It's a secret.
I won't tell someone who doesn't even notice her own sister's worries.
Produced by TV Touto
The luckiest blood type for today is... A! Just the other time...
Nee-san, I still don't understand what you're trying to do, but...
Isn't that bow a little excessive?
A presence! I feel a presence!
Yakumo-dono, I shall go without breakfast.
What are you planning to do?
Just watch! You will be shocked, Yakumo!
Even more than this?
I'm off!
I'm so worried.
Yagami Station
Guess I'll get some coffee. For a man like me, it's gotta be a "Sasuke"!
Hey, you punks! Don't forget the meeting tonight!
Be...
Be on your toes...
Chief!
The only way to deliver this love letter of overflowing passion...
... is with an arrow message. This is it!
Thank you very much.
Mangoku is so cool!
A killing intent!
Who the fu--
What the hell was that?!
It's not over yet.
If this doesn't work, then from the top...
Horseback Archery!
I am not disheartened...
Ah! Karasuma-kun went into the bank!
The target has stopped! This is my chance!
Now, Karasuma-kun...
Prepare thyself!
Headline: Great achievement for high school girl! Nabbed robbers with model guns - Bravery with bow in hand.
Amazing!
No! That's not the point!
Astonished
Why is it so hard to confess?
What's up? You look spaced out.
I know! When you're in doubt, you can always count on your girlfriends!
What? A sleep-over?
Hey! I said stop it! That tickles!
Take this!
This is great, isn't it?
This is a terrific bubble bath, isn't it?
That was a good bath.
Yup. I haven't laughed like that for quite a while.
I'm kind of thirsty.
Tada! I've brought some barley tea.
Cheers!
Alright, I'm alive again!
This iced tea is good!
It's... barley tea.
Um, if you don't mind, please have these...
Wow, Yakumo! You're so thoughtful! My stomach is growling.
Thank you so much.
Oh, no, you've always looked after my sister.
Please excuse me. Have a good time.
She does this every time. She's really a good little sister.
Do we add soy sauce?
And look at the older one eat.
Wow! This is awesome!
It's really nice when we're together... just us girls.
Yeah. Every once in a while, it's great to get away from guys.
Once in a while?
And the food was great!
You mean she is always around guys?
Yeah! That... er... that...
A-Amazing really...
Deep-fried tofu?
Yeah... that!
Yeah, that! I should ask my chef to make it sometime.
Eh... er... yeah...
Let's see...
Chef?
She really is a princess.
And the pickles were good, too.
These people must be really loaded.
Hey, you're right!
Right now, do you have a person you lik--
And you know, the taste is rather subtle. My family runs a contracting firm, you see.
--ike-lik-
or so I say...
Haha...
That's why I feel like I'm eating food rations every day.
Aha!
Hmm...
Ahem...
Yakumo-chan's food sure has a certain something,
Oho...
Ahemhemhem...
that gives people an 'affectionate' feeling.
Um... ah... hmm...
You said it.
*cough*
B-By the way...
Um, Miko-chan! Say... do you have a person you like?
What... why are you talking about this all of a sudden?
And it's so pin-pointed...
Oh? But you're not denying it either. How very honest and typical of you, Mikoto.
Who are you talking about?
But isn't it strange?
Three people confessed to you this year, but you turned all of them down.
Really? Miko-chan, you're amazing!
How... how did you know about that!?
Well, it'll never match my five confessions, though.
Five times?!
You sure fooled everyone, eh?
8 times
About... about that... I wanted to ask...
H-How would you all confess?
Umm... you see my friend's friend was worried about trying to confess...
And erm... you see...
She was troubled and I wanted to seek your advice on it...
... what to do when in love, or something like that...
And yeah, it's really for my friend's friend, okay? Really...
It's a friend of my friend's friend...
Ah, she's blabbering...
So that's what it's all about.
I've never confessed, so I wouldn't know.
I've never done it either... or rather, I've never felt like doing it.
What? Uh...
I see...
W-What about you, Akira-chan? Do you have any good advice?
Well I can't say this would work, but...
I've heard of the "Suspension Bridge Effect".
"Suspension Bridge Effect"?
You know, the "Suspension Bridge Effect" really works! I tried it last time.
Yeah! I've heard about that!
That's the way to go about confessing, right?
"Suspension Bridge Effect'?
So, so, what kind of effect is it?
If I'm not wrong, it happens when a person crosses a suspension bridge and he sees someone of the opposite sex...
His fear of falling down causes his heart to pound.
He then mistakes that for the heart-pounding feeling felt when falling in love with the opposite sex.
In short, when the other party is in a state of fright and he sees me,
he will fall in love with me, right?
Well... simply put, that would be it, I suppose.
Karasuma-kun, I love you!
You're gonna fall.  You're gonna fall!
R-Really?
Psychologically, yes.
But in practice, I don't think it'd work.
It's simple to make someone fall in love with you.
What? How? Tell me!
You just have to be cute!
But that only works for someone like you, Eri-chan...
Don't be silly.  That's what clothes are for!
Dress yourself up.
Take a peacock for example! Even animals know how to do it.
Actually, it was meant to intimidate others...
And it's for males, too...
Yeah, like a peacock, you know?
Peacock?
A peacock, huh?
Karasuma-kun, I love you!
Really?
You're imagining something weird again, aren't you?
You don't know anything, Princess!
What do you mean, Mikoto?
Where people are involved, it's about the heart! It's the inside that counts!
Be confident and go at it with a "Bounce"!
Miko-chan!
You're absolutely right! Thank you so much!
I think my courage bounced up somehow!
BOUNCE?
Miko-chan, you cheater...
With breasts that big, you can bounce into anything you want!
What in the world are you talking about?!
Somehow I think I'm even more discouraged now.
I'm going to the toilet.
Oh, yeah. Before I forget those ideas, let me write them down.
If I combine everything those three said...
Confession of Love
Battle Plan No. 5
ME
peacock's feathers
dangerous place... rooftop
Strike with a BOUNCE
Karasuma
Somehow this doesn't seem right...
Ah, forget it!
How would anyone confess while dressed up like that?!
Who would ever do it? How silly!
He would
Boys are always... always...
... chasing after girls.
All day long, always thinking...
... about girls.
But even so, boys are still so silly.
See? They don't understand at all...
... how the girls feel.
Hey there, you silly, silly, guy.
Shall I reveal it to you, you silly guy?
That's right! The most important thing is this world,
the thing you absolutely cannot take for granted,
I think it's the timing after all, isn't it?
That's right! When you say "I love you,"
or when you're on a date, or no matter what you're doing.
Ooh, when you're kissing, too.
When you say goodbye too, no matter when it is.
That's right! The most important thing in this world is...
I think it's timing, isn't it?
Or is it so?
Yikes, I'm really late.
Yakumo is gonna get so mad at me.
Ah, a shortcut through the forest.
Should I use it to get home?
Which reminds me, Yakumo said...
Nee-san, don't take that shortcut, okay?
Why not?
I heard perverts lurk in there.
Oh, I thought you'd say there's a bear or something.
Nee-san! A pervert is much scarier than a bear you, know!
That's right. Yakumo, I will keep our promise!
Karasuma-kun!
Tsukamoto-san, I will protect you!
Karasuma-kun, you would for my sake?
This is it! Using this chance, we will fall in love...
Switch ON
I'll take the shortcut!
Tenma-chan.
I'm glad I followed you.
This is my chance!
If some pervert comes and harasses Tenma-chan, I'll save her!
And then, our love will grow!
In any case, I would probably be mistaken as the pervert instead.
And that's what you'd expect, right?
But...
You're too naive. This police uniform will work flawlessly!
There is something different about me today.
I'm lost!
Oh, no! I've lost sight of Karasuma-kun!
What if I get attacked by a pervert now?
Well if it isn't another stupid high school girl...
And no one's around, either.
What an easy target...
Hurricane Kick!
Molesting is a crime, sir.
Punishment
Are you okay?
Yes. You saved me...
This is perfect.
Now Tenma-chan has certainly fallen for me!
Thank you very much, Mr. Policeman!
Oh, shit!
I can't believe how thick-headed she is!
Sure, I look like a cop right now...
But if I take this hat off, she'll definitely recognize me.
But I think it's really wonderful for you to save someone you don't know like me.
It must be a very honorable job.
It's my duty...
I must be on my way.
Please be careful from here on, Tsukamoto-san.
I will. Thank you so much.
How did he know my name?
Oh, well.
A delinquent like me, going on a field trip? Just to create a chance for love?
But why the heck am I playing cards with him?
Next time on School Rumble!
Pigs go Boo Boo!
Cats go Meow~
Frogs and Kappa go GA GA GA!
Pigs go Boo Boo!
Cats go Meow~
Frogs and Kappa go GA GA GA!
Damn it! I can't read his expression.
Hanai Haruki, has a crush on Yakumo.
He wanted to see Yakumo in a hakama,
so he started the Aikidou club.
Look forward
to the next
episode!