Coming up next!
Love is a fight! Love is laughter!
School Rumble, coming up next!
The Three Slashed
If you can read this, please install VSFilter or switch to the second subtitle track.
Please watch TV from a distance and in a brightly lit room.
Alright! Go get 'em, Mangoku!
Note: Unlike the bad example you see here.
Go for it! Go for it!
These feelings I want to tell you are so heavy
At this rate, I'll be flattened down
So many feelings I can't describe into words
It just won't reach, to that special person
This short yet very far distance
The sky is always blue,
But you just can't keep staring at it
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
You, who always pretend to be tottering
I just want to jump onto your chest
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
Rising softly into the air,
I am drifting above the clouds again today!
Pigs go Boo Boo!
Cats go Nyaa~!
Frogs and Kappa go GAGAGA!
Yagami High School, on spring field trip.
Tsukamoto Tenma, snack allowance of 500 yen.
It's a great day for a field trip.
Field trip eh? Brings back memories of my elementary school days.
At our age, I wouldn't call it a field trip. It's more like "Recreation".
I don't see much of a difference.
So where are we going today?
Dunno!
It's Karasuma-kun!
He looks kinda special today!
Yeah, no kidding...
I wonder why snacks are so tasty on days like this? It feels different somehow!
Are you gonna change seats once the bus leaves?
There seems to be good ambience today.
Makes me wanna start conversations with boys I don't know.
I think I'll pass on that.
That's it! Alright, I'm definitely gonna sit next to Karasuma-kun!
Note: She is snacking on "Pocky", a very popular Japanese stick snack with chocolate topping. Yummy~
Tenma-chan, the way you eat snacks and stuff... is heavenly.
I must sit next to you today!
You eat like a squirrel...
I'm a bit nervous...
K-Karasuma-kun!
Alright! I will do my best!
Hey!! Why am I playing this card game with him?
Tenma-chan is sitting right there!
Note: This is a card game where you need to trick your opponent into getting the joker.
And this guy is damn good! I can't read his expression at all.
Darn...
I can't really see Karasuma-kun from here.
And to think I've gotten this close to him...
Harima-kun, please move...
Argh! Why do I face away from Tenma-chan like this?!
Ack! I got the Joker again!
Alright bathroom break. Please be back in 15 minutes.
Okay!
Freakin' hell!!
Goddammit! What have I done?!
Hmph, it's ok. There are still plenty of chances.
Just for today, I've prepared all kinds of things to talk about.
I read a bunch of magazines too. There will be no mistakes.
I will definitely sit next to you today, Tenma-chan!
The bus is departing.
Ah, gotta go.
Sign: "Sugaa mo Red Bread Elderly's Community",
or better translated as Peaceful Garden Graveyard Expedition.
Pun: Sugamo Jizo is a street where many OLD and ELDERLY ladies hang out.
This is the wrong bus...
Oh my, what a handsome young lad.
Kiddo, don't be concerned with Shiru-san. She's always like that.
I can't take this! And this old man is too damn good!
I shouldn't be doing this here!
Driver, please stop the bus!
What the... the match is not over yet!
Dear! You don't have to leave yet.
But I have to go!
Plea... Please let me go!
Tenma-chan!!!
What the hell is this!?
Wait a minute!
I want to get back on the school bus!
Stop!
There's no one, no one! No one at all! Which means...
Chance!
But, what should I talk about?
"I just want to have a chat with you, Karasuma-kun".
...but that's kinda obvious isn't it?
Yo! I'm having fun here!
Hmm, that's wrong too...
Gosh, Tenma's so vexing!
I know!
Okay!
I'll just have to do it!
K...Ka...Ka...Ka...
Hi, Karasuma-kun!
May I?
Sure.
Well then...
SO mean!
You shall feel my wrath of love!
I'll shake her chair...
This bus is shaking a lot...
Goddamit! I must be with Tenma-chan!
I must get back on the bus, no matter what!
Tenma-chaaa-
Tenma-chan, I'm coming back now!
Strange, I feel sick...
Sensei, can I sit up front?
What's wrong? Bus sick?
See ya later, Karasuma-kun.
Victory!
I did it! This moment has finally arrived!
Crap, I feel sick too...
Even more than Eri-chan.
This must be karma!
Sensei, can I sit up front too?
Tsukamoto, you too?
Are those two alright?
Who knows...
I will not give up yet!
I will sit next to her!
Tenma-chan, wait for me!!!
No one knows why.
All of a sudden, when she least expected it, she came to have this special power.
Good morning.
Ah, Good morning, Nee-san.  Breakfast is ready. Your bento is over there.
Translator's Note: "bento" or "obentou" is a Japanese lunch box with all kinds of delicious things inside.
I'll be leaving early today.
Hmm? How unusual.
Huh? There are 3 bentos...
One for Yakumo, one for me, and...
Could it be for someone she likes?
Hurray! Hurray! Fight Yakumo!
I'm off...
I see... Yakumo is finally in love...
I will lovingly watch you from afar.
But unlike me she's very naive.
What if she's being tricked by some bad guy.
I'm worried. I'll sneak up and at least find out who he is.
Oops, forgot to lock up.
Nee-san?
What? The bento was for a cat?
I really thought you were in love.
Carp? No its a cat.
Translator's Note: "Koi" means love in the conventional sense, but also means the fish species, carp. Same pronounciation but different kanji spelling.
N... nevermind.
What's this? A stray cat?
You've been taking care of it all this time?
Yeah, but...
Hmm, it's ignoring us.
He doesn't trust me yet...
A cat trying to act tough!
He's being cautious.
I'll leave the bentou here okay?
Eat it when you want to.
Jeez, Yakumo! Why do you bother with this?
There's something I want to find out.
Just forget about some cat and try to get a guy or something!
Ack we're late! Let's go Yakumo!
See you later, okay?
Hey check it out!
Isn't that Tsukamoto from 1st year?
She is so cute!
For real. She's got style too.
I heard she is the most popular girl of this year's freshies.
Yeah, for sure.
It's not just the looks, I tell you.
She's athletic as well.
Once, the track and field teacher wanted to recruit her.
And she's smart.
She ranked 8 on her midterm exam.
An ideal girl like that really exists huh.
She is definitely popular with guys eh?
However, she doesn't seem to get involved with guys at all.
Maybe she's really picky?
Nah. Apparently, she just doesn't know how popular she is.
Such a waste...
Tsukamoto Yakumo... you can say that's her only weakness.
Hi there!
Sara... Good morning.
You seem so out of it. What's up?
I think I just saw a cat.
Cat?
I see... so it's that black cat huh.
I'm not sure.
A cat came to return the favor... that sounds like a fairy tale!
I guess you're right.  It's not... possible.
Got it? This part will be on the test.
So please write it down in your notes.
That day, Yakumo was a bit different from usual, to say the least.
I'll pick it up.
Oh! First contact with Tsukamoto! Today is my lucky day!
In other words, she is able to hear the thoughts from guys who like or are interested in her.
T-Thank you.
YES! I gave her a good impression!
But it proved useless to Yakumo whose heart has never been moved.
Library
Tsukamoto-san right?
Yeah whatever, muahahaha. Time to move in! I'll make her an adult.
You look like a hard working and responsible person.
Won't you like to join the Student Council?
I am sure you will help out for the school's sake right?
After the sun sets, just the two of us in the classroom!
But I... have to go home early.
Just the two of us... Just the two of us.
Well how 'bout a quick look at the student council room?
Come on! Let's go! let's go!
Stop! You are scaring her.
My name is Hanai Haruki!
I am the head of the Aikidou club.
By the way, I am your sister Tsukamoto-kun's classmate.
Your sister's classmate.
I'll be straight to the point. Would you like to join the Aikidou club?
Do you want to do Aikidou?
I... want to see you wearing a hakama!
I want to see you in a hakama!
Admirably, here is a guy who thinks and speaks the same.
For Yakumo, this is the first guy to ever do so.
I... I... I'm not interested in martial arts.
SHOCK
But that doesn't make her like them either.
But self-defence martial arts is very useful against perverts and molesters!
For example, if I were to...
Grab her right arm.
I missed my aim?
Now I will grab her left arm.
Alright, this time for sure...
What the? I can't even lay a finger on you!
Of course if you can read his mind, you can also easily dodge him.
Argh! To think her sister is a complete klutz!
I-I'm sorry.
When someone speaks ill of her sister, Yakumo gets serious, quickly.
Yakumo! The stove!
I wonder if it's okay.
Yakumo! We should try something different today.
Eh? I was gonna make curry.
Well, let's try making a different kind of curry then!
I'm not sure what it is but cheer up Yakumo!
Nee-san...
It seems that Yakumo can hear Tenma's heart too.
What would you like it to be?
I'm gonna write down my favorite ingredients, and Yakumo, you get to choose!
Okay.
Okay, pick!
Left hand is ketchup. Right hand is banana daifuku.
Left.
Here.
Banana daifuku.
Yep, banana daifuku.
Translator's Note: "Banana Daifuku" is a kind of Japanese mochi cake. In anycase, putting cake into curry is just...
Nee-san... You got your hands wrong, didn't you? Mistaking right for left...
Never! Yay, yay! Banana daifuku curry!
But to Yakumo, her sister is someone she would never scold.
And it goes without saying, that Yakumo loves her sister the most.
Itadakimasu!
Yuck!
Really? I think it's pretty good!
I brought dinner.
You're not here?
Poor thing, you can't get down right? Come here.
That's it. Slowly. Just a bit more.
Ouch...
Are you ok?
Meow Meow Meow
I can hear it now.
Ever since I've been able to hear people's hearts,
I was always wondering what your thoughts would sound like.
But I guess, in the end, cats go "meow meow" in their hearts, huh.
What a shame...
Drats, I forgot my umbrella.
No big deal. Let's run for it.
It was sunny out earlier.
Did you bring an umbrella?
Nope.
Okay, we can share mine.
Thanks. What about you Akira?
I have one.
Um, is it okay not to wait for Tsukamoto? She said she had some plans, but...
I am definitely sure she didn't bring an umbrella. Positive.
Nope. I am sure Tenma has one.
So it's okay to go on ahead.
How do you know?
I have a feeling...
Anyways I'm so hungry!
Great! Everyone left!
Miko-chan, you're so naive!
It's true that I didnt bring an umbrella, but...
See?
Yakumo brought me one anyways!
This is pouring hard.
I'm sorry everyone. I don't really have plans.
But I can't give this up.
Because I...
I've always been waiting for this rainy day.
Today I shall not fail!
I will share an umbrella with Karasuma-kun!
Translator's Note: This theme of boy-girl sharing an umbrella is so big that in Japan, there's even a word for it: "Ai-ai-gasa"
Just you wait Karasuma-kun!
Oh no! If Karasuma-kun brought his own umbrella, it will be pointless!
How could I have overlooked such an essential thing...
How could I, how could I, how could I?!
That hurts.
Karasuma-kun! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's okay. I'm fine.
Umm, by the way, I wanted to ask you if...
...you have an umbrella?
Not really.
YES!
Umm, I have an umbrella!
If you don't mind, perhaps we can share it.
I have a raincoat.
Rain... !?
Rain... Raincoat!?
A high school student wearing a raincoat in this era!?
I knew it Karasuma-kun!
That you are different from the common boys in many senses.
That's why I like you so much.
But, what should I do?
I can't share an umbrella with him like this!
Who cares if you have an umbrella! Let's share one!
Why would you wanna do that? We'll get wet with only one umbrella!
So what! I've always wanted to try it! Come on, it'll be fun.
I guess...
I got it! There's also this way!
I can try to talk him into doing it!
Karasuma-kun! I have a favor to ask!
Will you share an umbrella with me? I would be really happy... I mean I'm sure it'll be fun!
Translator's Note: Karasuma said he had a "kappa". A "kappa" usually means a "raincoat" but can also be a legendary frog demon.
Kappa...
I love it!
Karasuma-kun, even if you're a Kappa I still...love you!
Boys are always, always...
...Chasing after girls.
All day long, always thinking...
...About girls.
But even so, boys are still so silly.
See? They don't understand at all...
...How the girls feel.
Hey there, you silly silly guy.
Shall I reveal it to you, you silly guy?
That's right! The most important thing is this world,
The thing you absolutely cannot take for granted,
I think it's the timing after all, isn't it?
That's right! When you say "I love you"
Or when you're on a date, or no matter what you're doing
Ooh, when you're kissing too
When you say goodbye too, no matter when it is.
That's right! The most important thing in this world is...
I think it's timing, isn't it?
Or is it so?
Eh!? Softball? I'm so not good at sports.
But Karasuma-kun is watching me! I must do my best!
Next Episode on School Rumble!
My Burning First Love!
Burning Tea Party!
Burning Softball Match!
My Burning First Love!
Burning Tea Party!
Burning Softball Match!
A blue bug flies and lands on blue honey?
Osakabe Itoko, Harima's roommate.
The sexy and cool physics teacher.
Look forward
to the next
episode!