Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next, next!
Second year, class C, Shigeo Umezu,
member of the track and field team, 17.
He has a girlfriend
he’s just begun seeing.
Madoka Kido, also on
the track and field team.
They began seeing each other in summer.
It was a favorable beginning.
However, he had a concern…
I can’t kiss her… Why is that?
Chance after chance…
I just cannot kiss her.
I am a coward!
But, today is the athletic meet.
I’ll show off how good I am and
when the excitement is at its highest…
Just wait and see, Madoka!
I will surely win this race. And I’ll…
… kiss—
It’s a pig! A pig’s running wild!
Shigeo’s been hit by a pig!
Are you alright, Shigeo?
Madoka…
Sorry.
It can’t be helped, it was the pig.
I can’t say it that I wanted to make
a good showing and then kiss her.
Don’t be so disappointed.
I’ll make up for it, I promise.
Girls are strong, you know?
You’ll be there, too.
So… I have a request of you.
If I come in first, as a reward,
will you kiss me?
Oh, no, are you alright?
I’ve been troubled by it
all this time, and she just…
Well, how about it?
But, you’re sure to come in first, right?
Then, it’s not a reward or anything.
What am I saying?!
After Madoka gave me this chance,
I’m giving it up!
Isn’t it supposed to be a reward?
Now, I’ll have to win.
Well, it’s my turn.
Y-Yeah…
What can I say… women are…
Women are…
Yahoo!
Napoleon?! What are you doing here?!
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Women’s Battle!
Men’s Battle!
After the Battle…
The championship will be determined
by the boys’ and girls’ relays!
The fourth runner, Eri Sawachika.
Kenji Harima, aren’t you going to run?!
Inﬁrmary
Thank you very much!
Be careful, okay?
I worked hard today.
I’ve seen all those who were
hurt in the cavalry battle…
I can finally take a break.
There’s still someone left.
Who can it be?
Did you get hurt during
the cavalry battle?
No…
Then what are you doing here?
Well, um… I did get hurt!
But it’s nothing!
So, I thought I’d just
come get a compress.
But just for that, I…
So, you hesitated
coming in just for that?
You don’t have to worry
about something like that!
Why don’t you just show me the wound?
You’ll be running in the
relay next, won’t you?
Yes…
Then, I should take care of it accordingly.
You’re different from
when we first met, aren’t you?
Have we met before?
She doesn’t remember… that? None of it?
She didn’t even see me?
Oh! That time!
When I pushed Hario down in here,
you happened to be present then?
Hario?
Something like that would make him
look like a pervert, wouldn’t it?
That was an accident, just an accident.
I hadn’t seen him for a
while and I got so excited!
Um… why Hario?
Oh, it was Harima.
I’m sorry, it’s an old habit.
Um, you and Harima-kun know each other?
I guess…
It’s hard to explain our relationship.
Well, I was the landlady and
he was the tenant, I guess.
Like I said… Don’t let it bother you.
What?
Am I mistaken?
I thought you might be jealous.
What are you saying? Jealous?
You must be joking!
I was just curious, that’s all!
If there’s something going on between the school’s infamous delinquent
and the new beautiful nurse, anyone would be interested.
Beautiful nurse?
That’s a good one.
It sounds indecent!
I’m going back. It’s almost time.
Oh? What about your injury?
I’ll take this compress.
Are you sure you’re alright?
You are truly kind, aren’t you?
But you needn’t worry.
Is that so?
Next is the relay race between classes,
Second year Girls’ Division!
Look at this close competition!
Class C: 220 points, Class D: 218 points.
On your mark!
The turning point of the battle
is the relay race.
It holds the key to the championship!
Set!
And they’re off!
Miko-chan! Do your best!
In the lead is Class C!
The gap grows wider!
Mihara!
The second runner is already on her way!
Class C’s Kozue Mihara is fast! Very fast!
At this rate, they can
shake free from Class D!
Why, Harima?!
I got hurt because that pig ran about during the 100-meter race and crashed into me!
Isn’t it only natural that you
take my place in the relay?!
Did it hurt, Napoleon? Were you hurt?
Are listening to me, Harima?
Please, you’ve got to do it!
Impossible. I won’t.
I said you have to run!
In the first place, why are you
keeping the pig at school?!
I’ll tell on you, you bastard!
Shut up!
Whether it’s a pig or a giraffe,
where I keep it is none of your business!
Just beat it!
Oh, there you are.
Class C’s Megumi Sagano is still on top!
The fourth runner is Eri Sawachika!
Class C is up there all alone!
I’m not going to let anyone
get the better of me!
Bring it on!
Runner Sawachika is fast!
Contrary to that beautiful figure!
No, perhaps the magnificent
running is because of the figure!
Sawachika-san is tremendous, isn’t she?
Strange…
Eri-chan is usually faster…
She hurt her leg?
That’s right.
Did Sawachika-san fall in an odd way during the cavalry battle?
Hario… Harima-kun, you were
on the same team, weren’t you?
Yeah…
She came to the infirmary earlier.
She said it wasn’t that bad,
but it’s been bothering me.
Could it be… when she…
Damn! It has nothing to do with me!
She went and shaved off my beard!
Serves her right!
Isn’t that so, Napoleon?
Where are you going?
I’m going to feed him.
Ah, it really hurts.
I can’t stand it!
Just a little bit more…
My legs are heavy…
I might not make it… but…
But I don’t want to lose!
The baton! Where’s the baton!
The baton…
There you go.
It’ll be okay, now.
Thank you very much.
Don’t mention it.
Eri-chan, I was so worried.
Are you alright?
Yeah…
Hey, let’s go watch the boys’ relay!
It’s going to start soon.
I don’t think so.
I’ll stay here for a little while longer.
I’ll be along soon.
Thanks, Tenma.
Okay…
See you later, then.
Rich Girl… I’ll win… for you.
We’re even after that! Okay?!
Yes…
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
At last, the final event of this meet!
The boys’ relay begins!
In the second year division,
Class D is on top!
And five points behind is Class C.
For us to win, we have
to take first place.
It will be okay, we’ll win!
How about a penalty game if we lose?
The heroic gladiators are
now entering the arena!
Imadori!
Oh! Miko-chin!
What’s the matter?
Make up for what you did
in the cavalry battle, now!
I know! I didn’t do it on purpose.
You’re going to keep
holding that over me?
But…
Thanks for protecting me
from Harry’s kick!
You’ll give me a kiss
if we win?! Miko-chin!
When did I say that?! You idiot!
Asou-senpai!
Senpai!
I’m rooting for you!
Please do your best, okay?!
Sara…
You bastard! That’s sneaky.
When did you become close, dammit!
It’s not like that!
How come all the girls only call to you?!
Yakumo-kun is watching.
Do your best, Harima-kun!
Go! Shadow Warrior!
Tenma-chan is watching.
Yakumo-kun is…
Tenma-chan is…
What’s going on?
Hey, look at the slack
faces on those two!
They don’t look ready for this!
Hey, are you guys okay?!
You have no sense of readiness!
Well, this is to be expected.
What’s going on with Class C?
For some reason the morale
of the troops is disturbed?!
How fragile they are.
Women are specters.
They are fools after all.
I had thought they were good competitors,
but it seems I overestimated them.
Remember! The relay is different
from individual short-distance races!
I’m giving you a plan for certain victory,
so listen carefully!
In a relay, the handing of
the baton decides everything!
The timing of the handoff
must be perfect.
That’s what I was just going to say!
You’re pretty knowledgeable
about it, aren’t you, Imadori.
I’m surprised.
The relay will redeem us from
the dishonor of the cavalry battle.
I was going to say that, too.
Well, I can be serious
about things sometimes, too.
If we win, we’ll be heroes.
Harima, we’re counting
on you to be the anchor.
Who do you think you’re talking to, dumb ass?
Easily… easily.
On your mark!
Ready!
They start all at once!
He’s fast! As you’d expect from Class D!
Even this unknown runner is a grade above!
Class D is on top!
Shit!
Next is… Class C has passed the baton!
He’s fast!
So fast! Runner Asou is running vehemently!
He overtook the top runner in seconds!
Imadori!
Leave it to me.
What’s this guy doing?
What?! Imadori is in a crouching start!
I was stupid to have believed in him.
Hey!
What “hey,” you idiot!
You!
Okay!
Oh! He suddenly began tumbling!
A grand tumbling display!
And now, he’s started to run!
Is this part of some plan?!
Did you see that? I started
with tumbling to build up speed!
It’s called special rolling.
He’s been overtaken!
A great miscalculation!
Huh?
How?!
With this lead, we win.
With me and Harry left…
It’s a shoo in.
Tougou, don’t underestimate us.
Us? You’re placing a lot of confidence in Harima.
Don’t make me wait.
I’m not so patient!
Imadori’s finally arrived!
I will exert myself as much as I can, Imadori!
Special rolling!
Don’t do it!
Runner Hanai’s yell is tremendous!
He’s taken on the look of a demon!
The wind god has swooped down upon us!
It can’t be! He’s…
Hanai’s closing the gap?!
He’s putting pressure… on me?!
No! My concentration!
It’s okay! We’re still leading!
I’m up next!
We can win!
Hurry up and go!
What?
Don’t you know?
A come-from-behind win is
the most impressive kind of win.
Come after me, Japanese Samurai!
This hairstyle is a defeated soldier.
Hair?
Oh, no! What if the cap
falls off while I’m running?!
Harima!
He’s getting closer!
Take it! Our manly spirit!
Four-Eyes, you really don’t think
of people’s feelings, do you…
Damn!
I have to do it!
Harima is…
Harima intends to win!
Harima!
Harima-kun’s fast!
I changed my mind about him!
What’s happening?
You really are doing your best.
That’s great, Harima-kun!
He’s getting applause
from the other classes!
Even a second faster!
I have to reach the goal
before the cap falls off!
The more I run, the more it slips back!
God, please… this is the
first time I’m praying…
Please give me… a miracle!
It can’t be!
Goal!
Kenji Harima is first!
Class C wins the championship!
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
After the battle, you are
a valuable school friend.
Why did I have to pair up with a guy?!
Is this the only duty of the committee chairman?!
I’m surprised at how delicate you are.
Really?
Hi.
Let’s see… where’s Karasuma-kun?
Karasuma-kun is in charge of the records.
They’re all acting like
they haven’t noticed.
Dancing the Oklahoma Mixer so enjoyably.
Oh, well…
Now, I won’t have to hide my head anymore.
And I’m back to being all alone again.
I guess, that matches me, the delinquent, best.
Let’s dance.
What are you talking about, Rich Girl?
With that leg of yours… and me, bald…
There’s nothing to be ashamed of.
You’re dancing with me,
so you should be proud.
Come on.
Hey, Rich Girl…
I’m okay… I’m fine…
Today is special…
It’s special, understand?
Hey, look, over there.
Sawachika-san!
Why?
You know, Beard…
Your dancing sucks.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Is a person’s fate governed
by money or chance?
That is the perpetual mystery
that surrounds the seas of the time.
The next School Rumble:
“Irritation, Indecision, Wandering”
Irritation
Indecision
Wandering
Stormy weather is coming.
Harima, still mistakenly thinking Tenma likes him.
Tenma Tsukamoto, the Queen of Thickheadedness.
Café El Cado, the manager’s preferences.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!