Coming up next!
The gurugu mawaru love comedy, School Rumble...
If you can read this, please install VSFilter or switch to the second subtitle track.
When watching TV,
watch in a bright room and from a distance!
So you came, Harima.
We'll definitely settle our score today.
Get him!
No matter how delinquent he is, a man in love should never chicken out.
Y-You bastard!
I won't lose to anyone who confronts me.
That's because right now, I'm in love.
Everything's for your sake, Tenma-chan.
Harima-kun's been coming to school every day lately.
Is he planning to take over the school?
Nee-san.
You forgot your lunch.
Ah! Thanks, Yakumo.
Nee-san...
Are you alright sitting here? Aren't you scared?
Why?
There's this weird aura...
Ah! Harima-kun!
That's not good, you shouldn't put the chair... on your bag.
I feel sorry for the bag.
Everything's for your sake, Tenma-chan.
School was once a place that I didn't care about.
You've changed it to an oasis that soothes my heart.
This is ridiculous. I'm even coming to school on time.
And attending classes, even up until cleaning duty time.
Sheesh, it makes me wanna laugh at myself.
He's laughing...
He's definitely plotting something sinister, I'm sure.
These feelings I want to tell you are so heavy
At this rate, I'll be flattened down
So many feelings I can't describe into words
It just won't reach, to that special person
This short yet very far distance
The sky is always blue,
But you just can't keep staring at it
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
You, who always pretend to be tottering
I just want to jump onto your chest
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
Rising softly into the air,
I am drifting above the clouds again today!
The Test That Can't Be Understood!
The Toilet I Can't Leave!
The Unbelievable Physical Examination!
A 30-minute School Anime,
and it's not about delinquents.
The female lead, Tsukamoto Tenma,
as seen by Harima.
For today's English lesson, we'll be having a simple test to determine everyone's level.
Ready... begin!
What the heck is this? Is this even Japanese?
I guess I have no choice. This is also something I must do to be with Tenma-chan.
If I think of it as protecting these blessed times...
Te-Tenma-chan! You forgot to write your name!
She hasn't realized it?
If I remember correctly, those who forget to write their names will get zero.
If it goes on like this...
If this carries on, Tenma-chan will...
We're still in the middle of the test.
I can't speak up to warn her.
What on earth should I do?
What should I do...
I know. I'll try to inform her by lip-sync.
Doesn't work, huh? It's kinda difficult to tell her like this.
In that case...
Dammit! I gotta think of a better way.
Flapping my mouth like that... It's not like I'm a goldfish!
Isn't there some other way?
Argh, I have no choice...
I'll use a clear and orthodox way.
That was close! I forgot to write my name.
Even if I seriously answered these questions, it would be pointless.
Be careful, Harima.
Tsk. That was so laughable.
Everything is for Tenma-chan's sake.
Wh-What!? Hey!
I was referring to you, don't you realize?
Don't you know the proverb,
"one man's fault is another man's lesson"?
But in anycase, she's so damn cute!
Oops!
Not you!
I'll let you know even if it's by willpower!
This is it! It's perfect!
Got the answer to last question!
What is this? Isn't this a bit too easy?
Let's go!
Did it work?
Why does it have to turn out this way?
It's no use. This girl is too thickheaded. It's impossible to make her realize it.
Dammit!
What should I do?
That Harima has been seriously worried for a while now.
Is Harima really a diligent student?
I know! How about if I write Tenma-chan's name on my answer sheet,
and I'll be her scapegoat, being the one who forgot to write his name?
And then...
Huh?
Sensei, this answer sheet has my name on it, but it's not mine.
Eh? That's strange...
Harima's the only one who didn't write his name.
Huh? Could it be that for my sake, Harima-kun...
What a kind person!
It was really Harima-kun, right?
I'm a man who won't ignore what he sees.
Harima-kun!
I love you!
Me too.
It will work.
Everything is for you Tenma-chan,
For the sake of our happiness!
I'm returning yesterday's test.
Tsukamoto, you got a zero!
Eh?
Sorry! I'm sorry, Tenma-chan!!
I was a huge dumbass!
How about it everybody? Shall we have tea at Mercado's today?
Yeah, why not?
Oh! There's a special sale time at the supermarket after evening hours. I have to go...
What should we have for dinner tonight?
Oh? Tenma, you make your own meals?
That's unexpected.
Huh? Erm, yeah something like that...
Yakumo's the one who makes them, right?
It's just as you said...
Just as I thought.
Tsukamoto sure seems pampered.
Eh? You think so?
It-It's Karasuma-kun!
Huh? Why am I hiding?
That's because... somehow, I don't want the person I like to see me come out of the toilet...
Oh no!
Since I came back inside, I can't go out again!
I'm such an idiot...
It's just a bathroom, but it is a bathroom!
What should I do...
Um, I can't get out.
He's still there.
Ooooh!
Karasuma-kun, you idiot, idiot, idiot!
What nerve you have to stand and chat right in front of the girls' bathroom?
But that's what I like about you.
Wait! No!
Now is not the time for that!
He's still there...
In that case, it's a contest of endurance!
That's right! I'll show you what a girl's willpower is.
Come to think of it, endurance is a requirement for love.
That's right! This is a trial!
Alright, I'll endure! I don't think he can stand there and chat for more than 10 minutes.
It should be okay now, right?
Ah! The sunlight sure is bright!
He's reading a book...
Moreover, it looks like a novel...
Plan two!
Sheesh, where did she go?
Tsukamoto, are you still in the bathroom?
In this situation, I can't choose any other way.
Huh? What are you doing?
As long as even I can't recognize myself, it's okay.
Oh! You came at the right time!
Guess who!
I'm leaving now, Tsukamoto...
Huh? How did you know?
Sigh, I can't be bothered with her.
Plan three!
I'll use this to divert Karasuma's attention, and use that chance to escape!
Ready! Set!
Fly!
You dare to hit me?!
You sure have some guts! Who the hell did it? Was it you?!
It's not me! It's not me!
Or was it you?!
It wasn't me, either!
I'm sorry, Harima-kun!
I'll apologize later...
There isn't much usable stuff left...
Ah! I'm stuck with no way out!
I'm completely unable to get out now...
Eh? I can't pull it off.
Why, you!
This is it!
Right side, okay!
Left side, ok!
Distance from ground, 30 meters. Gradual descent, begin!
I will not give up!
I will not... I must not... let Karasuma-kun see me come out of the bathroom.
This is a girl's determination!
I'm finally down.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Be careful, okay?
It's good that you aren't hurt.
Nee-san. I'm not angry that you didn't make it to the special sale...
No! No! That's not it!
U-Umm
It's been a while. Please be gentle...
Nee-san.
Who are you talking to?
Ah! No.. I err.. umm... with this!
This?
What's wrong with the scale?
Oh, yeah!
The physical examination is tomorrow.
What's with that calm reaction?
I'm jealous. Yakumo, you're so slim. Hmph.
Whatever, just get out!
Why you...
As if I'm gonna lose to a scale!
I don't really think the scale is at fault here...
Let's go! Tenma!
Please put me in your care.
This must be a dream... ah, I gotta wake up soon...
You'll catch a cold, Nee-san.
I skipped breakfast today.
I didn't eat anything for three days!
Thanks to that, I lost 700 grams!
You'll give in soon.
Once it's over, I'm gonna eat all I can.
Three days' worth of food for just 700 grams?
Oh, Tenma! Seems like you've gained it again.
Your weight.
Ah! Bull's eye.
Even if your weight has increased, it's probably the same as mine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Mikoto-chan!
Although the sizes of your breasts aren't same.
A... B...
Hmm, I think it's a B...
As for this one... it's an A, I suppose.
Imadori-kun, what are you doing?
Guessing blood types?
This, man! This!
Well, without taking measurements, I can still figure it out with just my eyes.
Those throbbing chests, those shy and cute postures.
Ahh! It's like a page from the sweet and sour lives of students.
Fuyuki-kun, what are you taking those pictures for?
Foolish question! I'm preserving these as pictures for graduation.
Isn't that risky today?
Fuyuki! I'm reserving a full set, okay?
Ehh?! You'll get into serious trouble!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing, Hanai?!
I, Hanai Haruki, will not allow such behavior on the school grounds!
The pickled seaweed we ate at the cafe the other day was delicious!
Yeah.
I preferred the cider flavored one.
Yeah, well...
Karasuma-kun is also taking the physical examination, isn't he?
I'm interested. His height is 171 cm.
No, 172 cm.
His weight... he seems light, since he's so flexible.
Hmm, but I do not know anything about boys' weights.
I want to know! I want to know Karasuma-kun's body information! Things that only I would know.
His height, his weight, breadth of his shoulders, his vision, his sitting height, his foot size and his chest measurement~!
His chest... may be even bigger than mine...
Hey, hey. Don't you think the guys are a little excited today?
They're probably fantasizing about today's physical examination.
I-I-I'm sorry!
What are you sorry about?
Tenma, you sure like to break the flow of our conversations.
It's not the first time she's done it.
But it's really disgusting. Guys who have only strong imaginations...
Note: "Kangofu" in Japanese refers specifically to "female nurses".
Geez. If they want to watch that badly, they should become doctors or nurses.
You sure are extreme.
And you should say "male nurses."
Note: "Kangoshi" is a gender-neutral nurse more appropriate for male nurses.
I'm saying IF they wanted to! IF!
I only made a little mistake.
Be a doctor or a nurse?
That's it! I'll become a nurse!
It seems like at that moment, she suddenly decided her career path.
Ah! I'm not gonna worry about it.
I hate it when she says it that seriously...
No, no. I'm not talking about my career path.
You're not?
I have something to do, so I'll be going now.
That's a relief.
Well, there's a subtle feeling of wrongness here...
Don't tell me she's...
Alright! A perfect disguise!
That idiot! Anybody can recognize that hairstyle!
That's not the point!
Seems like she has a motive. Oh well, I can guess what she's up to.
I haven't worn a name tag since elementary school.
She's happily writing her name on the name tag.
She's definitely gonna write "Tsukamoto" on it.
Hey, what should we do?
Leave her alone!
You're serious?!
Nah, actually I wanna see what happens.
I agree. It's better if we don't interfere.
Alright! With this...
Karasuma-kun's personal data...
... will be mine!
Sorry for the wait!
I'll be in your care, Doctor!
No, no. I was also late. Sorry.
Due to certain circumstances, I'm here as the replacement. My name's Harima.
Nice to meet you.
The physical examination that was due to be conducted today, has been cancelled.
I repeat.
Boys are always, always...
...Chasing after girls.
All day long, always thinking...
...About girls.
But even so, boys are still so silly.
See? They don't understand at all...
...How the girls feel.
Hey there, you silly silly guy.
Shall I reveal it to you, you silly guy?
That's right! The most important thing is this world,
The thing you absolutely cannot take for granted,
I think it's the timing after all, isn't it?
That's right! When you say "I love you"
Or when you're on a date, or no matter what you're doing
Ooh, when you're kissing too
When you say goodbye too, no matter when it is.
That's right! The most important thing in this world is...
I think it's timing, isn't it?
Or is it so?
Ahh! It's so hard to confess!
And it's so simple with spoons...
I know! I'll have everyone sleep over and ask about their experiences.
Next on School Rumble!
Sketch Me Tender!
Aim That Arrow Message!
Teach-me Pajama Party!
Sketch Me Tender!
Aim That Arrow Message!
Teach-me Pajama Party!
Miko-chan, your breasts are too large!
Tsukamoto Tenma,
likes historical dramas.
Mangoku's comrades,
Ue-sama and Ika.
Look forward
to the next
episode!