Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next.
Takano-senpai had her part-time job
and Hanai-senpai kept bothering Yakumo.
So that’s why you came
back early from camp?
What happened to the other kids?
They stopped to relax at a hot spring.
It’s no longer a tea club function, is it?
That’s right.
Oh, my…
But is it all right?
To have this in school?
Why not? It’s summer vacation.
In the first place, the one
who left him here is wrong.
He’s not yours?
I’d never keep something like this.
His owner’s away,
so I’m only looking after him.
I’ve never seen these people before.
Who can they be?
No. 6, it’s time.
She’s pretty, but she never
calls me by my name.
I’m Pyotr.
This is the name people gave me. I don’t know my true name.
I don’t even remember
where I came from anymore.
But it doesn’t bother me.
Eat.
I’m treated like a dumb animal…
… somehow.
Are there other animals with numbers?
Yes. I left the ones with relatively
normal sizes in the storehouse.
Teacher, I don’t think it’s working.
What a bother he is.
Mr. Giraffe…
Over here.
He ate it!
Oh… I can’t get back up.
His legs are pretty weak.
Lack of exercise, isn’t it?
Don’t you take him for walks?
Would you take him?
Would it be against the Road Traffic Act?
No, that’s not the problem.
But it’s sad to keep him
cooped up in a small space.
You’re right.
Keep coming, keep coming, keep coming…
Watch your head.
Stop.
At night, he’s kind of scary, isn’t he?
Is it safe? If people see him…
It’s only for a little while.
I’ve even brought a ball.
Do giraffes play with balls?
Want to play?
I don’t know why, but this girl is kind.
Wow! He likes you, Yakumo.
Thank you, Big Sister. I’m stupid,
but I’ll try my best to remember you.
Oh, I remember something…
That’s right. Until a short while ago,
I had a dear Master.
But he’s not here now. Why?
Maybe I was…
Mr. Giraffe!
… abandoned?!
I want to see my Master!
Stop, Mr. Giraffe!
Mr. Giraffe!
I’m sorry. I’m sorry, Big Sister!
I’ve got to find my Master!
Wasn’t camping fun?
Uh… yeah… It went so fast.
You don’t have to walk me any further.
Huh? I see.
Thanks for walking me home.
Hey, no problem.
Oh, I almost forgot!
Hey, by the way,
who’s the girl you like?
Come on, tell me!
It’ll be our secret!
About that, Tsukamoto…
I couldn’t decide whether to tell you or not.
But now I can! That’s what I feel.
I… um…
Actually, I… love… y—
I was looking for you, Master.
I’m home, Pyotr.
Awesome, awesome!
Did you see it, Yakumo?!
How come you’re here, Yakumo?
Why’d you run off, Mr. Giraffe?
Thank you, Big Sister.
Mr. Giraffe…
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
At the Height of Summer, a Giraffe’s Feelings!
At the End of Summer, Panic Party!
After Summer, Changing Now!
The start of the incident!
Mysterious animals at Yagami Shrine.
The reporter— her 3rd year on the job.
Well?
No, no signs of stopping.
How can we dry the laundry? I’ve got
to complain to the Thunder God.
What’s wrong, Yakumo?
I discovered the Thunder Kid.
A runaway?! And you
didn’t pack any clothes?!
And you don’t want to
give your name, right?
Even after we let you come in.
What’s the big idea?!
I’m appalled!
I didn’t ask to come in.
Man, how impertinent!
It’s raining hard.
I think you should spend the night here.
Look, Yakumo!
A strange kid like that is dangerous!
That boy is all right.
How do you know that?
I just do.
You’ve got to be more cautious, Yakumo!
He may be young, but he’s still a man!
You’re such a pushover!
Savor your food!
The boys in school weep because
they can’t taste Yakumo’s cooking!
Who cares about that?
But your big sister
sure is the better cook.
Yakumo is my younger sister!
What?! Pancake-Boobs here is older?!
What?! See? Kids have no sensitivity!
Sure, Yakumo is bigger than me,
but my friends are bigger than her!
They’d beat you up.
Uh… Sis…
Lecherous brat, you seem really
interested in Yakumo’s chest.
I shall punish you! With a game!
Bring it on!
Old Maid!
Shogi!
Check.
Othello!
I won every game.
What?! I’m not finished yet!
The ultimate secret weapon!
Teacher, if you please!
Igo.
I don’t know this game!
That’ll teach you!
What’s wrong?
You know, I didn’t really
run away from home.
Big Sister Yakumo
is really pretty
I didn’t know what to do
I only wanted to meet her
I want to look at her all the time and be with her
It’s all right.
’Night.
Don’t forget to thank us for feeding you
and letting you stay the night.
You didn’t do anything for me.
Smart-mouthing me again!
Um…
No, nothing!
Bye!
I can’t say I wanna come again.
Wait!
Come to visit anytime.
Right!
Well, he was a hateful kid, but it
was noisy and fun, wasn’t it, Yakumo?
Yes.
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
It went by so fast.
Summer vacation is over already.
Yes…
It’s like waking from a dream.
Strangely sad, isn’t it?
That’s right.
Senpai!
I’ve been waiting for you.
Teacher is inside with one more person.
What’ll I do?
The second term is starting.
Anyhow, we’ll move them to Yagami Shrine.
The shrine?!
We can’t leave them in the gym, can we?
But that place is…
Yes, it’s just a matter of time.
They’ll eventually be found.
Um… it might be better
to send them to the zoo.
No! How can I let strangers
look after these guys now?!
But that’s your ego talking, Harima.
What? Here?!
It’ll be okay. Nobody will come.
Really? But this lion
statue is kind of scary.
Don’t be silly. It’s just a figurine.
Look.
Reporting from the skies above
Yagami Shrine right now.
A couple has reported seeing a lion here.
Also reported were sightings
of a zebra, panther, panda, sheep,
ostrich, penguin, armadillo and others.
There are also witness reports
that beautiful young girls brought
a giraffe to the park late at night.
Fear is mounting among the local people.
Beautiful young girls?
The local hunters’ association is scheduled
to carry out a hunting expedition in the next few days.
It’s a big mess, isn’t it?
We’ve got to do something…
They… trusted me.
Big Sister Yakumo! I’ve come to visit!
Shuuji?
Younger Brother
What’re you doing here, Big Brother?
Older Brother
I wonder if there really
are animals in here?
3rd yr on job
1st yr on job
2nd yr on job
But a video of them will
make an incredible scoop.
I’m getting it!
What’s that?!
A giraffe?!
After it!
The scoop’s mine!
Who are you?!
Giraffe.
It’s a costume!
And who are you guys?!
We’re rehearsing for a play here.
I play the lead.
What’s the idea? My camera!
Don’t shoot our play without permission!
What’s the title of your play?!
Kitten Tales
Kitten Tales.
GORILLA
But you’re a gorilla!!
What a waste of time.
Who’d find any animals around here?
It worked, didn’t it?
Yeah…
Whaddya think of my idea?!
You’re a good kid who
thinks of his big brother!
I had to pay Big Sis Yakumo
back for putting me up that night.
I thought I had a terrific scoop…
Hey, you guys, cut it out alread—
Come on out, guys.
We’re moving you to a safe place now.
Hold it, you brats!
Oh, no, you don’t.
Pyotr!
You couldn’t hide?
I-I’m sorry…
I want a full explanation.
I called a hunter, too.
Wait a minute!
They didn’t do anything wrong!
We’re just gonna put them to sleep.
Big Sis Yakumo!
Out of the way, you kids!
Younger Sister! Stop!
It’s dangerous!
Gotcha!
Run, guys!
Run, quick! Go!
Get out of the way!
I’ll fire!
Let go!
Forget it!
Senpai!
Big Brother!
Everybody!
Look there!
Why are they doing
the Awa Odori Dance?
They understand how
you feel about them.
They don’t want to cause you any trouble…
So they’re letting people know
that they’re not harmful animals…
… by doing the Awa Odori Dance.
You can let go now, right?
Itoko…
I’ve already arranged it with the zoo.
You’re quitting? It’s a great shot.
Never mind.
Later, the animals were
taken by a zoo nearby.
Since they’re so friendly and can do tricks,
they’re greatly loved by the children.
After the incident, Harima-san has
been visiting the zoo often.
It’s one of the few customs observed by
Harima-san, who hates anything scheduled.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
It’s the second term!
The school uniforms are fresh!
The familiar school scene!
Yes! It’s the new school term!
Lazy
But somehow, I feel so mellow…
Isn’t your mind still in
“Summer Vacation” mode?
That’s not true!
You don’t understand!
Nobody says it out loud, but inside,
they’re flush with excitement.
When I see him again,
Karasuma-kun will sparkle!
Yo, Tsukamoto!
Oh, ’morning, Miko-chan!
Yo!
You cut your hair?!
It looks great!
It’s the new term, after all.
See, Yakumo? This is the
power of the new term!
Never underestimate it!
Those two are dating?!
When?!
That, my dear, is the power of summer.
One other person has changed.
Ichijou-san?!
She braided her hair. It’s so cute!
That’s not all.
A shorter, but ladylike, skirt.
A touch of eyeliner. Light pink lipstick.
I can relate! A midsummer night’s dream…
Another girl stricken with
the sickness called love.
You’re the sick one.
How nice. I guess we
have to have changes!
All I ever did was run into Karasuma-kun and
tag along with him to watch pro wrestling.
There’s no way to change.
I want to fall in love and change, too!
If love makes a person change,
then conversely if Karasuma has changed…
Would that mean that he was
dating someone during the summer?!
Something like that…
Shake
No, no! That would never happen!
Which is it?!
Please come already, Karasuma-kun!
’Morning.
Karasuma-kun!
What happened during summer, anyway?
I’m totally clueless!
But Karasuma is still Karasuma!
I’ve got to accept him as he is!
Beard is wonderful,
beard is wonderful,
beard wonderful, beard… beard…
Beard… wonderful…
“Beard”?! C-Could she mean me?!
Watch out.
Tenma-chan’s in a total
love mode toward me.
Beard
I guess it’s definitely mutual now.
Lemme get closer…
Oh… I forgot to take this off.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
She was abroad…
Your Manhattan, miss…
Leave it there.
Yes, mis—
That’s as far as you go!
Meddling witch!
Where’s the brat?!
Talk or die. You choose.
All right. I’ll tell you.
He killed Mama and Papa…
Damn Regino.
I, Giorno, will protect the Family!
But why did you save me, Akira?
Hold on tight!
The little game of tag is over, little one.
Regino… after Papa, I loved you most!
The Godfather must never trust anyone.
Huh? Your dress?
Giorno, you asked me why I saved you, right?
It’s because… You remind me of my love.
Get down!
Akira, stay in my country with me.
When you grow up, come to Japan.
I’ll make some good tea for you.
Senpai, how was your summer vacation?
Ordinary. I had a little trouble, though.
Trouble?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
I’m Karen Ichijou.
Imadori-kun remembered
that we had a date.
But I’ve never dated before.
What should I do?
In the next School Rumble:
The one who cherishes you
is always beside you!
Karen’s Love, Not Yet
Karen’s Love, Little by Little
Karen’s Love, And Then…
Karen Ichijou,
Heavyweight in the Amateur Wrestling Club
Kyousuke Imadori,
always the Shallow Lightweight.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!