Coming up next!
School Rumble will be coming up soon.
Question (#1): Which line is longer?
The answer is in the episode.
Mr. Super asks that when
you watch TV keep the room lighted and watch from a distance.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
The First Shopping Trip!
The First Box Lunch!
The First Heartbreak! Huh?
Eri Sawachika has never
gone grocery shopping alone
Tenma Tsukamoto has never
made lunch by herself
Hi, Sawachika-san.
I’m Sano from 2-A.
I’m sure you know me.
You’re not seeing anybody yet, are you?
So how’s about—
Hey, do you like meat-potato stew or curry?
Oh, meat-potato stew, I guess.
I thought so…
Were you thinking of cooking it for me?
No.
Never dream of it.
What did you want?
So I thought if you wanted, we could go out…
I’m sorry.
Shot down!
Doomed from the start!
You can’t hog her all to yourself!
Hey.
Don’t reject a guy so coldly.
Times like that,
he’s like a peacock,
ready to spread his wings
and jump off a roof.
I have someplace to go,
so I won’t be needing the car.
It’s not that I don’t like a boy’s honest confession
But then you know…
Huh? Curry or meat-potato stew?
Suddenly everyone is looking this way…
I hear guys prefer meat-potato stew.
Don’t feel bad, but then you know…
Potatoes?!
Do they? I wouldn’t really know…
What? “How do you make it?”
No matter how popular I am, I can’t decide
Well, first, you’ll need:
round onions, potatoes, carrots, beef and stock.
Onions.
Potato.
Carrots.
I don’t know what I should do
Beef!
Who’re you making this for?!
5 potatoes
1 carrot
1 onion,
sugar, soy sauce
stock or sake
beef round or
belly pork
Good luck!
But that’s okay, it’s better that way…
How about one for you, miss?
until I ﬁnd my true love
Do I eat it right here?
Feel my feeling, the one and only in this world
Strange… I don’t see any red price tags
Tenma said to look out for…
Be my being, with my very own color,
Tonight’s dinner is
Daddy’s favorite, isn’t it?
I’m sure he’ll love it!
Right!
Maybe my heart feels a bit lonely inside
She’s cooking her first meal?
Doesn’t Eri’s family have a cook?
I’m calling somebody
Why doesn’t the cook fix
the meat-potato stew?
Perhaps, it might be him
Look, that wouldn’t show how Eri feels.
What, Miko-chin?
How she feels about what?
Feel my feeling, I’m treasuring it
It looks like rain.
Ah! You’re right!
I’ve got to get home
and take in the laundry!
Be my being, with my very own color,
Hey, Tsukamoto! You’ll fall!
You’ll trip.
I’ll sing that truly wonderful Love Song
I’ll sing
F-Father!
The butler, Nakamura,
told me you were here.
You came to get me?
Tonight, for dinner, I’m—
About dinner…
I’ve got to leave Japan on business.
Sorry, I can’t have dinner with you.
Oh, don’t worry about it.
Actually, I made a date to have
dinner with my friends tonight.
Besides, I know how busy you are,
traveling all around the world and all…
I see.
What a shame. We haven’t spent
time with each other in a while.
I’ll come again soon.
Want a ride home?
Don’t worry about me.
Good luck with your work.
Right. ’Bye, now.
I see.
If it’s not far, I can walk you.
Only a short ways.
Which do you like?
Meat-potato stew or curry?
Curry.
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
So let’s do the second exercise together…
What’s wrong?
I love you
Yo, Sara-kun. ’Morning!
Have you seen Tsukamoto-kun around?
Yakumo said she was
stopping by the faculty office…
I see! Thanks! Excuse me!
He’s gone.
So then this guy goes…
Like that!
You’re kidding!
It’s true.
Is that well-known?
’Course!
Moderately.
I wonder where Karasuma-kun is going?
End of the month, no money… Itoko won’t
lend me any. Not even lunch money.
You skipped lunch, too?
All you can do is fill your
empty stomach with water.
This always happens
at the end of the month.
Okay! I like you. The next time
I get paid, I’ll treat you to lunch.
You listening to me?
By the way, what do you like,
curry or meat-potato stew?
Curry.
I knew it! I think we’re gonna get along!
Okay. Next time, I’ll treat you to curry!
Karasuma-kun…
I know. Box lunch!
I could get closer to him
if I made him a box lunch!
Why didn’t I think of it before?
All right! This is my time to shine!
I’m home!
Curry? For school lunch?
Right. Curry! In Tupperware
with rice and sauce. Two apiece.
Um… Me, too?
Mildly spiced, of course!
Karasuma-kun!
Uh… um…
I made too much lunch.
Won’t you help me eat it?
All right!
Guess I’ll drink some water…
Tenma sure seemed happy
when she went outside.
With a big box lunch.
She said it’s curry for two.
Who’d make curry for a box lunch?
That means…
What does it mean?
Yo, Harima. I’m gonna settle
the score once and for all today!
I’ll be waiting behind the gym after school!
Don’t forget!
My beloved Tenma-chan made
curry that I love, and for two?!
Could she have made it for me?!
I’m so glad!
Do you know what’s inside, Karasuma-kun?
I guess you don’t.
But it might be something you love.
Rice… both boxes!
A horrible mistake!
—
Salt
Rice ball.
Th-This is nice.
Two boxes of curry
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
You sure can’t stand Hanai-sempai, can you?
Your rejection instinct isn’t
that strong against other boys.
Uh… Um… It’s not that
I dislike him in particular.
I’m just not comfortable
around boys, so I…
So a really direct approach like
his scares you away even more?
I see.
But now you have to go to 2-C,
your sister and Hanai-sempai’s room.
Because of…
The two boxes of curry.
Don’t worry. I’ll go with you.
Thank you, Sara.
Now, let’s hope that Hanai-sempai isn’t here.
I love you
What’s wrong, Yakumo?
Hanai-sempai is in there.
How do you know?
All right! Off I go! To see Tsukamoto-kun!
I love you
What’s wrong, Yakumo?
Hey, Hanai! Got a minute?
What’s up?
I love you
And you get this…
I see.
Got it? I’m going now.
Hey, what’s your hurry, anyway?
I’m going to see Tsukamoto-kun now!
Biggest Fool Over Yakumo In This Era
Sounds great! That girl’s so cute!
Maybe I should come with you.
Me, too!
What?
I like her, too. Leave her for me!
Hold it, hold it, hold it, you guys!
I’ll just do it fast, and it’ll be fine.
It’ll be fine.
Yakumo!
Are you okay, Yakumo?
Sis, didn’t the box lunch
cause problems for you?
Huh? What problems?
Kenji-kun, time to leave for school.
Come on, don’t make me nag!
You gonna skip school again?
Well, I guess that’s
what delinquents do, but…
I’m coming in.
What about school?
Ain’t going.
How can a tough street fighter
like you be so weak inside?
I ain’t going.
I can’t trust guys or girls, so I ain’t going.
Mr. Super’s Super Fun Science!
How are you, kids?
On today’s Super Fun Science,
we’re going to study optical illusions!
Problem #1! Look carefully at this picture!
Which line is longer: line number 1, or number 2?
It’s gotta be 2.
The correct answer is,
they’re both the same length!
You’re kidding! You’re sure? Seems fishy.
Let’s measure it with this ruler.
Ain’t 2 just a little longer?
1 is this long. And 2 is… See? The same length!
This is called an optical illusion.
Amazing, isn’t it?
Illusion?
Illusion, huh?
The Three Slashed!
So… you’re going away? What a shame.
Mangoku-sama…
Take care.
Thank you very much.
Mangoku, don’t tell me you left
because you knew that the girl
was in love with you?
Nonsense. You got it all wrong.
That girl wasn’t interested in me.
Don’t put up a front like that!
You knew, didn’t you? Actually?!
Right on! Right on, Mangoku!
Only I know the pain you’re suffering now!
Calm down and listen to me.
You and I are actually siblings.
Then… Then you’re my… brother?
Brother and sister?
You’re my brother.
That’s why we felt so close to each other.
You misunderstood, didn’t you?
So that’s it!
Could it be?!
It was all an illusion and misunderstanding!
Tenma-chan and Karasuma are…
Isn’t it good, Big Brother?
It sure is, Little Sister.
They’re siblings!
Siblings
That’s why we’re so close to each other.
Is that so? So that’s it!
Idiot
To tell the truth,
I’ve always… loved you.
Crap!
I-I made a big mistake!
Kenji-kun, you’ve got company. What’ll I say?
Wh-Who is it?!
Well, it’s someone you know well.
It’s Ten—
It was a misunderstanding, after all!
Ten—
Tennoji…
That’s right. It was too good to be true.
Harima, you bastard.
You got your nerve,
skipping out on our fight!
I wanna see you for a minute.
Huh? What’s wrong with me?
Was I so bad… at fighting?
Sheesh...
You ain’t no fun today!
Come back if you wanna get even!
Sis, are rice balls enough
for lunch tomorrow?
They’re fine, fine!
Harima… Harima…
Kenji Harima, are your tomorrows all gone?
Is this the end of your love?
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Karasuma, you actually
prefer curry to rice balls?!
Why didn’t I notice that sooner?!
I’ll cook you some
delicious curry this time!
Next on School Rumble: “Manga Blues!
Big Sister Blues! Kappa Super-Bad Blues!”
Manga Blues!
Big Sister Blues!
Kappa Super-Bad Blues!
Oh, no! Iori!
Kenji Harima: Broken love, broken dreams.
Big Sister… Who is she?
Don’t miss
the next
episode!