Coming up next!
School Rumble is…
… coming up next.
When you watch TV,
keep the room lighted and don’t sit too close.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
But It’s the Tea Club…
It’s the Tea Club, But…
It’s the Tea Club, So…
Tea Club Camp.
By the way, it’s still summer vacation.
Tenma and Harima—
Master of misunderstanding, showdown for the title.
The mountain is silvery…
Is that a Japanese camping song?
Huh? Don’t you know it, Eri-chan?
Not true. Don’t be fooled, Sawachika.
Oh, you, Tenma!
Gotcha!
Here! Our camping ground!
Now we’re really in the mountains.
The air must be so fresh!
Yahoo!
I wish Sara could have seen this.
Let’s see…
Is that the cottage we’ll be staying in tonight?
It can’t be helped.
This trip was planned at the last minute.
But does a tea club ordinarily go camping?
Oh, that’s where we’ll cook!
It’s for training of the mind.
What will we cook?
Curry, of course!
But it’s not purely a tea club outing anymore.
Curry?
We came because you said there weren’t
enough people with only you and Yakumo.
Was Hanai-senpai unable to make it?
No, I gave him a fake date for the trip.
What?! Suou went camping with
Yakumo-kun and the others this morning?!
Damn you! You tricked me, Takano!
Nothing to do until our part-time job starts…
Ha-Harima! Let me use your bike!
Yo, four-eyes, that’s how
you ask for a favor?
I-It’s like this!
Omigosh!
This is my big chance to see if
what Tenma-chan said is true!
Get on!
Thanks…
Sure thing! Let’s go!
Hey! How can you leave me behind?!
Dammit! Stop!
Takano-senpai, what should I do?
Gather firewood.
Alright.
Yo, Yakumo-kun.
That idiot!
Miko-chin!
Oh no!
Therefore…
Leave all the cooking to us, and the
women are free to enjoy themselves!
Really?!
Imadori, get the dishes!
Harima, gather firewood!
Yeah.
Crap!
He was the one!
Wonder if he knows a lot about animals?
A delinquent gathering firewood…
Something’s wrong, here.
E-Excuse me…
I’ll help.
Ten— Tsukamoto-san’s younger sister!
Th-Thank you.
Not at all.
That’s Tenma-chan, for you!
She taught her sister well.
You’re the worst, Harima-kun!
Why did Tenma-chan say that?
Her younger sister might know.
Maybe he doesn’t remember me.
What’s that?
It’s my special secret curry spice!
You should just buy the roux at the
convenience store at the foot of the hill.
No! Yakumo-kun has to taste
the best curry in the world!
You take care of the curry, then.
Hey, know where Yakumo is?
Yeah. She went to help gather firewood.
What?!
Huh? What’re you doing?
Um…
Forgive me for asking, but…
Recently, was your older sister
angry about something?
For instance, did she say that somebody
was “the worst,” or something?
Well, she did say she talked
to Suou-san and Sawachika-san…
That’s it!
And what did she talk to them about?
I think it was about a man…
Wh-What sort of man?
Um…
With a beard… and sunglasses…
The resemblance is coincidental.
And what did she say about him?
Uh… um…
She wondered why he practiced
confessing his love.
She couldn’t understand
his feelings, she said sadly.
Wh-What?!
I-It can’t be…
No… but… That could lead
to only one conclusion!
Namely!
Tenma-chan realized that when I practiced
my confession of love on the trip…
it was actually what I felt for her?!
Th-Then…
You’re the worst, Harima-kun!
Then what she really said was…
I’m the worst, Harima-kun. Please forgive me.
Th-That’s what she meant to say!
H-How terrible.
It was all because I jumped to conclusions!
Of course. Tenma-chan would
never say I was the worst!
Um… it hurts.
S-Sorry!
I don’t know my own strength.
I can’t read his mind at all.
But I know he’s a good person.
Now, we’d better be heading back.
Don’t tell your sister
what we talked about.
He doesn’t remember, at all.
I wanted to talk about animals.
It’s kind of… a pity.
Oh, and by the way…
The rice balls were good.
Thanks.
What’s wrong? Let’s go back.
Yes.
I didn’t expect things to go this far.
He wasn’t satisfied with
just Eri-chan and Miko-chan.
He’s even trying to hit on Yakumo!
He’s lost all sense of decency!
You’re a player, Harima!
I’ve got to… I’ve got to protect Yakumo!
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
We’re back.
Late! You’re late, Harima!
Good work, Yakumo-kun.
Hey, Beardy…
Buy me some tea.
Um… I just came back from working hard.
Buy it!
Damn this spoiled blonde!
She’s still mad at me!
But I was to blame. If I’m not careful,
she’ll tell Tenma-chan!
Here.
I don’t like that kind.
Hey, cut it out!
I can only take so much!
Buy it.
Yes, ma’am.
Uh… Um…
Yakumo! Forget him! He’s an animal!
I saw him! I saw Harima-kun hitting on you!
He wasn’t…
No, I know it!
His eyes were dead serious!
But he was wearing sunglasses.
And he doesn’t seem like a bad person.
You don’t understand men, at all!
But how could you?
You’ve never dated, after all.
You haven’t either, Sis.
Just look!
Tenma-chan’s looking this way!
See that oily, disgusting face?!
He’s totally after you.
But I only wanted to talk to him—
You don’t know anything about men, yet!
Listen, Harima is a player, right now.
All men have those periods.
So stay away from him!
Is it such a bad thing?
When you get to talk to Karasuma-san,
you seem to be so happy.
Th-That’s because Karasuma-kun isn’t a player!
But you just said all men are the same.
No, no, no!
It’s hopeless! I can’t beat Yakumo
when it comes to logic…
No! I can’t give up now!
I’ve got to protect Yakumo.
After all, I’m her big sister!
She’s worried about me.
All right, I’ll do as you say.
Big Sister Power!
No arguing
Anyhow, just do as I say! Got that?!
I only wanted to talk to him about animals.
But it’s been a while since she’s
used “Big Sister Power.”
Harima!
Ten… Tsukamoto?
Got a minute?
I challenge you!
I challenge you to be my partner
in tonight’s scavenger hunt
and fight me, one-on-one!
Could this finally be Tenma-chan’s
confession of her love for me?
Agreed?!
Yeah…
I accept!
The mask hides his sappy-looking grin.
At last… At last it’s done!
Yakumo! I made my secret curry spices!
Oh, Hanai, you took too long,
so we started without you.
I’m surprised you managed to
bring frozen curry here, Takano.
This is the tea club, after all.
Here! After-dinner coffee.
Very thoughtful, Tsukamoto.
By the way, I ground the beans up.
Nobody asked you.
Fresh-perked.
This is the tea club, after all.
Here, Imadori-kun.
Thank you.
I get to drink Tenma-chan’s fresh coffee!
Lucky I came!
Here, Harima-kun!
She’s so into me.
These beans must be some sort of sign.
Love beans, perhaps?
We’re drawing straws to find our
partners for the scavenger hunt!
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
It’s time for the scavenger hunt!
Bring back a charm from a
small shrine along the forest path.
We’re really going
all out, aren’t we?
This is the tea club, after all.
First team up!
Aren’t you trembling, Senpai?
Not really…
Yakumo-kun!
Start!
Don’t get lost!
Next!
I got Miko-chin!
Hands off!
Try anything, and you’ll be sorry!
Start!
Wait up, Miko-chin!
Next!
I’ll catch up to you soon, Yakumo-kun!
Start!
Harima-kun, I’m sure you know
we’re paired up on purpose.
Yeah.
Are you prepared?
I won’t run or hide from it.
Excellent. Let’s settle this.
Go!
Tonight, I’ll finally settle
this with Tenma-chan.
That means… we’ll connect.
I didn’t expect this rain.
I wonder if everybody’s okay.
We’ve gotta find shelter!
I wanted to tell him to stay away
from Yakumo, too, but now…
Harima-kun! Look out!
Thanks, Tsukamoto!
You’re tall, after all!
Tsukamoto?!
S-Sorry! I was able to jump over this.
Th-That’s okay.
Hang on tight.
Right.
Harima-kun, we’ll have to
call a truce, for now.
I didn’t know there was
a deserted school here.
Fire. Warm yourself.
It’s turned into a big mess,
hasn’t it? I’m sorry.
It’s okay. Don’t worry about it.
Harima…
No, I mustn’t!
I couldn’t hope for a better scenario.
Harima-kun!
Listen, when a girl falls in love…
She can only see that person in her eyes.
I think you’re a truly sweet person.
I know you are!
But a girl wants her love
to be sweet to only her.
Please, Harima-kun!
So you just can’t date two girls at once.
Don’t be a player!
You didn’t have to tell me that, Tenma.
You’re the only one in my eyes.
Yeah, I understand.
Thanks for telling me.
Oh, I see. You understand?
I don’t know why, but this
is really getting good!
O-Oh, no!
Tenma-chan will catch cold like this!
She’s gotta take off those wet clothes!
B-But…
Mwahahahaha
If I suggest it, she’ll think I’m a pervert!
But this girl’s pretty dense, so she
won’t catch on to a casual hint.
How can I get her to strip
without appearing like a creep?
Th-That’s it!
You strip, too.
What do you mean?
Let me explain…
Um, you don’t think?
That’s right! He’s serious!
That’s how he is!
He even made a pass at me
and caused me a lot of trouble!
That’s awful! I’m stopping him!
Don’t be silly. Even Tenma has
enough sense to stop him.
She’ll just punch him one! That Beard!
All right, Harima-kun.
W-Why?!
You can turn around now.
Right.
How’s this? They’re pretty thick,
so ain’t they warm?
These school curtains…
You’re right.
It’s kind of embarrassing, but it’s better than catching cold, isn’t it?
Y-You still can’t trust him.
Is that so?
By the way, Harima…
Who’s the girl that you like?
Who? Why, it’s…
You really want to know?
Quit snickering!
Yes, yes, tell me, tell me!
Come on, I can’t understand you.
Speak clearly.
Are they little kids?!
Tsu… ka… mo… to Ten… ma.
What? What? I can’t hear you!
Geez! Okay, I’ll sit next to you.
So who is it?
S-She means…
Please understand.
It’s awfully embarrassing
for a girl to say, “I love you.”
So you say it first.
Passion Unleashed
OUT OF CONTROL
What’s wrong, Harima-kun?
Oh! You okay?
Running out of firewood?
Well, it’s gonna get a lot hotter
in here, so wait a minute, okay?
Let’s make it easy!
I’ll make firewood out of this wall!
Just the thing. A cloth to burn!
Here goes!
Pull!
What’s this? Something’s caught on it.
A mouse?
Crap. Big mouse?
But tonight, I am fearless and invincible.
What happened, Harima?
Oh, nothing. Maybe we should head back.
Looks like the rain’s stopped, too.
Right. Guess so.
Eavesdropping is wrong, after all.
Heaven punished you.
You were listening, too!
This is stupid! Let’s go back!
Oh, please wait!
We’re back!
What happened to Imadori-kun outside?
All kinds of things happened. All kinds.
He won’t get up for a while yet.
I’ll let him sleep some more.
Where’s Yakumo-kun?
Hasn’t Yakumo-kun come back yet?!
I’m worried!
Yakumo-kun!
Welcome back.
Um… we got wet in the rain… and um…
Got extra clothes?
Sure.
How come?
This is the tea club, after all.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Summer vacation’s ending!
I wanted to play some more.
Next on School Rumble:
“At the Height of Summer, a Giraffe’s Feelings!
At the End of Summer, Panic Party!
After Summer, Changing Now!”
At the Height of Summer, a Giraffe’s Feelings!
At the End of Summer, Panic Party!
After Summer, Changing Now!
About three parts.
Next episode, it’s giraffe anime.
The industry first. (Kidding)
Kenji Harima kept animals at school.
At summer’s end, a small battle begins.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!