Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next!
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Mission 1: Confession of Love!
Mission 2: Night Offense and Defense!
Mission 3: Tweet!
Beach Trip continues.
Tenma Tsukamoto joins in the mood.
Hanai and Mikoto, childhood friends.
Memory of summer days.
Traveling Dragon
Wow, it looks delicious!
Dig in!
Hey everybody, how far
were you able to swim today?
Two meters.
Zero meters.
What? Why?
You both didn’t improve at all!
I was able to swim 20 meters!
What about you, Miko-chan?
Five kilometers.
Why? How were you able
to swim so far, Miko-chan?!
Did you do some kind of
secret training with Imadori-kun?!
That’s wonderful! Maybe I
should learn from Imadori-kun, too.
Yeah, sure. Then, I guess
I’ll teach Tenma-chan next.
Oops.
Don’t get cocky, kid.
Clever.
Are you alright, Imadori-kun?
I’m fine. I’m fine.
I’ll wipe it for you.
Thank you, Tenma-chan.
You’re so kind.
Hot! I spilt soup on my leg!
Really, you are hopeless.
Stop it, you bastard!
You really did it, Mikoto.
Getting yourself all alone
with him until this late.
What did you do?
Tell us the story later, of course.
Keep at it!
Oh Miko-chan, you are so bashful!
Wait a minute!
Could it be that Harima-kun’s current bad mood is because…
… he’s jealous of Imadori-kun and Miko-chan?!
I see… the one that
Harima-kun likes is Miko-chan.
Harima-kun, Harima-kun…
I’d like to talk to you about something outside. Okay?
Yes!
Already… No… Finally, Tenma-chan must have noticed my charm.
Actually, I heard…
there is someone you like.
Yes!
Have you told her how you feel?
Ah… well… I did a number
of times, but she didn’t notice.
Yes, well, she’s kind of thickheaded.
No! It’s okay!
This is just the beginning!
H-Harima-kun. Okay, I understand.
You’re a good person, Harima-kun!
I’m with you! If that’s okay with you!
I’m moved!
Can I hug you, Tenma-chan?!
Practice with me! Your confession of love!
I…
lo…
I can’t say it!
Oh! That’s no good, Harima-kun!
That’s the 23rd time!
Come on, with your huge body!
He’s so happy,
it’s unbearable.
I’m sorry.
It can’t be helped.
I’ll show you how it’s done.
Ah! Hey!
Wait.
Be right with you.
She doesn’t remember my face.
Harima.
Nori
(seaweed)
Actually, I’ve… liked you
from a while back!
Minor Dyspnea
Ah! That’s terrible! How can you laugh!
Who do you think I’m doing this for?!
Really! How many times have I
gone through the motions with you?
You should realize it already.
That’s it!
Really?! Am I good?
Then, now it’s your turn!
I’ve seen that face before.
Where was it?
Come on, let’s continue!
I lo… lo… I can’t say it!
Okay then, I’ll do it for you again.
Really! I wish you’d hurry up
and figure it out.
You’re kind of thickheaded, you know?
That’s it exactly!
The words are different from before,
but it’s getting close to the core!
I feel like I had a bad experience…
It’s your imagination.
I’m on the verge of remembering…
Never mind that! Let’s continue!
Listen to me.
I… love…
Y…
Yo…
I can’t say it
What?! That was great just now!
It can’t be helped!
I’ll do it one more time.
No matter how you look at it,
I love you. Can’t you tell?!
Put yourself in my shoes!
Is she doing this on purpose? Damn…
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Tsukamoto’s over there.
I want to sleep beside her.
Kentarou Nara………… Retired
D-cup, D-cup…
A man determined to get to
the front, Kyousuke Imadori
He’s gone around five times already.
Maybe I should let him know I’m awake.
I’ll just attack from behind, already!
But he’s the man who can’t scream out.
Kyousuke Imadori… Retired
Just a little bit more and Tenma-chan…
Takes refuge in a safe zone from the beginning
Akira Takano
Caught you, Yakumo-kun.
You bastard! Why do you keep interfering!
Yakumo-kun…
On top of it all this guy’s strong!
They’ll break, they’ll break!
Let me go, dammit!
Yakumo-kun…
I love you.
You moron.
What is it?
His clothes came off
during the grappling.
Wait, wait a—
Kenji Harima … … Retired
What’s the matter everybody?
You all seem tired.
I couldn’t sleep.
I had the worst dream.
And what’s with all the injuries?
It’s nothing.
Akira-chan, show us the video later.
What should I do?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Stop.
Haru-bo, you did well!
Irresponsible of the old man to call in
opponents from a different school
for the karate match.
But Haru-bo is certainly
good enough to take over this dojo.
If he does, his brains would be wasted.
That’s true.
Yasaburo, give your son some praise!
It’s alright.
You did good against that
national level competitor, Suou.
No, it was hard work, hard work.
What’s the matter, what’s the matter?
You won, too, so look happy!
Chop, chop!
Oww! Stop that!
Suou’s birthday party…
They’ll ask me to perform something.
If I do something strange,
Suou will be mad at me again.
Damn! I can’t think of
anything everyone would enjoy!
However, the man, Haruki Hanai
cannot disappoint everyone!
A sleight of hand set or something…
anything… Isn’t there anything?!
Yes… that was the summer of our
second grade in elementary school.
You are really weak!
Uncool!
And you’re the son of that dojo?!
You’re weak and you’re
learning martial arts!
Acting like you’re good at it!
I knew that best myself.
I only did it because Dad
forced me to take it up.
Really, you should stick to studying!
I was a victim of bullying.
I’m finished!
Haruki! You must eat all your food.
If you don’t eat it all,
Miko-chan will leave you behind!
I’m the brainy type.
I don’t know why they always compare us.
Miko-chan is sunny and everybody’s hero.
But me…
Are you okay?
We’re having noodles with
everybody after practice, right?
We have to make ourselves extra hungry!
There was no way
I’d ever match Miko-chan.
Here, Hanai.
No, I’m…
Don’t hold back.
Here, here, eat some more!
I… I’ve had enough!
Oh, you’re spilling, look!
I’m sorry.
One a hero, one the object of harassment.
Suitable debt kept on building.
Fun With Music
At the next class, you will perform,
so form yourselves into pairs.
Violent like a dam breaking,
the strongest bullying,
“shunning by all” began.
As though I were just air,
a surprisingly strained sensation.
Before long, I stopped going to school.
I did nothing wrong.
I withdrew from that hated school myself.
Hanai!
Miko-chan!
The recorder presentation!
I’m the music monitor, so teacher
says you should pair up with me!
I’m not going! I’m not going!
I absolutely won’t go!
What?!
Come on out! I’ll blow
on this until you come out!
I should have given up,
but I became stubborn.
Even then, Miko-chan persisted.
On the hot summer days…
On windy days…
In violent rain…
Miko-chan is late today.
Mikoto!
I told you, you don’t have
to go to school today!
Hurry up, let’s go home.
Miko-chan’s Mom.
No! I’m staying here!
Stop this right now!
You have a cold, you know!
I’m the worst.
Oh! So you finally decided to come?
Teacher’s nagging me to perform.
Let’s go do our best, okay?!
Miko-chan never said anything.
Not about the cold, not about
her mother scolding her… And…
Suou! Aren’t you embarrassed
playing with a boy?!
You look good together.
When’s the wedding?!
Th-That’s none of your business! Go away!
Then why are you pairing with Hanai?!
In the first place, teacher told you
to pair with someone else!
Miko-chan didn’t pair with me
because teacher made her do it?
Pairing with Hanai is embarrassing!
Ow!
It’s not!
It’s not embarrassing at all!
Don’t ever come near us again!
Come on, hurry up,
let’s continue practicing.
Miko-chan must have been really, really embarrassed.
Why are you crying?!
And on top of that,
you’re playing it all wrong!
Snap to it, come on!
I’ve decided… I will be
a hero like Miko-chan.
Yo! Hanai, we’ve been waiting!
Give it your all, Hanai!
I want Yakumo especially to hear this.
I can’t read his mind today.
First! I, Haruki Hanai,
will play the recorder.
Get back! You’re rotten!
Mikoto had
forgotten
completely
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
It’s soooo hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Yakumo! Why is the air
conditioner not working?
Because you were playing samurai
and swinging the broom, chasing Iori.
Then you went and hit the air conditioner with all your might.
The electrician will
be here in the evening
I can’t wait. I can’t wait. I’ll melt.
Okay! Let’s do this!
Let’s play Rock-Paper-Scissors and the winner takes refuge!
She can go to play in a place
that has air conditioning!
The loser stays home
and watches the house, okay?!
There you go again,
deciding things arbitrarily—
Come on, first time is stone!
Rock, paper…
I don’t want to
watch the house.
I wanna go play.
I’m throwing scissors.
The sign
for victory!
Scissors!
Hurray!
You are really weak at this!
Actually there’s a trick to reading what
the other person will throw.
You do this and look through your fingers
Probably better
off not reading
her sister’s mind.
Sorry, Yakumo. I’ll be going!
Be careful.
Oh, the electrician.
You can’t come to repair today?
Yes…
What shall I do? I have to make it
cooler somehow, before Sis returns.
I know… there’s that…
Yes. If Sis will wear a yukata…
yukata = summer kimono
Yay! A yukata! A yukata!
She can forget the heat with that.
Oh, let's get some water.
Were you watching?
I’ll bathe you.
Iori!
You ran all the way here…
It’s really cool here.
Dumplings, dumplings…
Sis!
What is it, Yakumo?
What’s the matter, Yakumo?
Is there something you want?
What could it be?
Won’t you tell me?
Come on, leave it to me!
It’s okay. After all,
I’m your big sister!
Yes… that…
I’ll get that out.
I’m home! Yakumo, I brought ice cream!
A wind chime!
Ohh, that’s good!
Just looking at it makes me forget the heat!
You did it, Yakumo!
Yeah!
Ah, Tsukamoto-san.
Karasuma-kun, I didn’t think
I’d get to meet you here!
I’m on my way to watch pro-wrestling.
Do you want to go?
I do!
Have You Ever Seen One?
Not that cute, is she?
I Look Forward To Getting To Know You!
Next on School Rumble…
I have a pro-wrestling date with Karasuma-kun!
Yahoo!
Their respective adolescence.
Their respective summers.
Swaying emotions.
Broken friendships.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!