Coming up next!
New Year’s Greetings
Happy New Year!
School Rumble is coming up next!
When you watch TV,
keep the room lighted and don’t sit too close.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Have You Ever Seen One?
Not That Cute, Is She?
I Look Forward To Getting To Know You!
School Rumble is currently in Summer Vacation.
Harima, Hanai and Imadori
working at their part-time jobs.
Tenma and Karasuma on a pro-wrestling date.
Iori!
Don’t be mischievous.
Iori…
He’s been behaving badly lately.
It’s hot, hot hot!
Yakumo, isn’t the air
conditioner fixed yet?
The electrician said
he’d be here about noon.
What? Everyone’s coming over
to do homework today.
It can’t be helped.
But I’ll die in this heat!
There are people who are out
even in this heat, you know.
They go to work.
Play sports.
And lots of other things.
Yuki, you can’t today no matter what?
Not even for a little while?
Is that so… Okay, then, next time.
Damn… Let’s see, who’s next.
Kyoko-chan, are you free today?
Is that so? Okay, then another time.
What’s going on?
What’s happening today?!
Next is—
I’m sorry.
Huh? Imadori-san?!
Oh, is that you, Ichijou?
Yes.
Oww…
I’m really sorry!
It’s alright. What’s that?
Amateur wrestling?
Yes.
Amateur wrestling, huh?
It must be rough in this heat.
Let’s see, who haven’t I called yet…
We practice every day.
Every day? I can’t believe it.
Rather, for me, summer vacation
is time to have fun with girls.
Shouldn’t you be getting a boyfriend?
N-No, ah, things like that…
Is it really fun doing amateur wrestling?
Isn’t there anything you should be doing?
I’m not good at anything else,
and even in wrestling, I’m not so good.
But, I’m satisfied. So it’s fun right now.
Sports…
Is it something you can get so serious about?
Eri-chan, here’s some barley tea.
Thank you.
Miko-chan will be here soon,
but Akira-chan will be a little late.
Is that so? We won’t get
anywhere without Akira.
True. It’s hopeless with us,
a pair of dummies.
A pair?!
Wait a second. The only subject I’m poor at is Japanese.
It’s going too far ranking me
the same as you for that.
Say, Eri-chan, do you
understand this problem?
Listen when people are talking to you!
I see, you don’t understand it.
It can’t be helped.
I’ll have to do it myself.
Excuse me!
Oh, never mind.
Scratch
Say, Tenma.
What?
There’s something I want to ask you.
What is it? What is it?
Ask me! Ask me!
Have you ever seen a male body?
Ah, no, not that…
Ah, darn. If I’m quiet,
it just emerges into my mind.
That!
Because of it I end up
asking Tenma a stupid question.
All this because that super pervert
does something totally ridiculous.
But why ask Tenma, who is probably
the densest about such things?
I have.
I’ve seen male bodies.
W-Wait a minute. What?!
Isn’t that ordinary?
Something like that…
Th-That couldn’t mean…
Tenma has had an adult relationship?!
Even I haven’t had one yet!
D-Do you mean with Karasuma-kun?
Oh geez, how did you know?
Yes, that’s right!
Noooooo!
Shocked
Actually, just the other day…
Karasuma-kun and I…
Wh-What’s the matter, Eri-chan?!
C-Could it be you haven’t seen one?
And she seems the type
that likes martial arts.
I have.
Of course you have. It’s only natural.
I-I’m mortified. To lose to Tenma…
Of course! Even Tenma wouldn’t
do something like that,
Like having the mouth blocked?
That’s just the beginning!
And him seizing you from behind?!
That’s really a great move, isn’t it?!
I… I’ve lost.
But guys really like
that stuff, don’t they?
R-Really?!
Th-Then, if Akira hadn’t
come just then… he would have…
I don’t know what’s going on!
Umm, Eri-chan, actually, I wanted
to talk over something with you.
What?! There’s more?!
Just ask me anything!
Er… Um… I think Harima-kun…
… he likes Miko-chan.
I want things to go well between them.
But, I don’t know about these things,
so I’d like your help.
I think it would be
good for Miko-chan, too.
I was surprised that Harima-kun
liked her, but she is cute.
But Mikoto…
… isn’t that cute, is she?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Hello! We’re here to repair
your air conditioner!
Thank you very much.
Please show us the outside unit first.
Oh,
sexy
girl!
Summer’s
great.
Silence......
That guy is very quiet.
Oh, it’s this way.
Oh, is that it?
Okay, part-timer, the ladder.
Right.
Well, I’ll leave you to your work.
Iori! What are you doing here? Come.
You’ve hurt your leg.
Wait, lori!
What shall I do? He’s angry,
I’ve been scolding him a lot lately.
Look, look.
Look, a mouse. No?
Here, you like fish.
Come now, and you get a second one.
No good… all because
I scolded him too much.
Leave it to me.
Come here.
Let me see… Oh, it’s a thorn.
There’s a thorn behind its leg.
He’ll be alright now.
Thank you.
Ah… umm…
Do you like… animals?
Well… not especially, but…
One day, they suddenly
seemed to like me.
This house… I remember it somehow.
It… it’s really hot, isn’t it?
Shall I open the window a little more?
I guess.
But the air conditioner’s broken, so the
window’s as open as it will ever be.
This silence is no good.
I have to do something.
I know!
Say, Eri-chan, about this question…
Classics
Sorry, I don’t know.
That’s okay.
Classics
What about you, Miko-chan?
Oh, Classics?
Let’s see… It must mean this.
Oh, it does?! Thank you!
Not at all, that’s nothing.
Say, say, Miko-chan,
about this problem…
I don’t know that one!
Math? Let me see.
This is done like this.
I see! You’re good at this!
You gotta be able to do these
if you’re thinking about college.
What am I going to do?
There’s no air conditioner, but it’s cool here!
Study questions won’t work.
I have to think of a more fun subject!
Isn’t there… isn’t there anything?!
Sorry I’m late. The pictures
from our trip are developed!
Thank you! Akira-chan! Show us!
Let’s look at the pictures!
Let’s all look at the pictures!
See how much fun!
What’s this? Imadori
really likes you, Miko-chan!
Woo-woo!
I have nothing to do with him!
You couldn’t tell.
Aren’t you already dating that bearded delinquent in secret?
Look! If you have
something to say, say it!
Why have you been
acting sneaky anyway?!
Spreading malicious gossip
behind my back! You coward!
Aren’t you ashamed of yourself?!
Is that so?! Then hear me out!
Unlike you, I don’t
mess with just anybody!
You get all cozy with
your childhood friend.
We go to the beach, you get
picked up and disappear somewhere!
And, what about Harima-kun?
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Everything you’re saying is strange!
In the first place, I saw you and Harima
holding hands very friendly-like!
That? He suddenly appeared, grabbed
my hand and confessed his love!
I can’t stand this! I’m going home!
Eri-chan!
It’s alright. I’ll see you later, Tenma.
Miko-chan, is that true?!
Harima-kun confessed to Eri-chan?
It’s true. I thought it best to be quiet
about it and left the scene right away.
How can that be?
Harima-kun was practicing
confessing his love to Miko-chan.
He was working so hard at it.
To think he was after both of you…
You’re the worst, Harima-kun!
Hey part-timer, just tell me
why you’re crying. Come on.
N-No… It’s nothing.
I can see it’s not nothing.
No, I… I have no idea
what’s going on anymore.
Oh, it’s adolescence?
Is it the anguish of adolescence?
I’m alright. I will do my job precisely.
Refreshments.
Umm… I don’t know what’s going on,
but please do your best.
I’ll help myself!
Salty.
So it’s adolescence after all.
Salty!
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
I don’t mind referring you for
a part-time job, but why so sudden?
What happened to your last job?
I’m not fixing air conditioners anymore.
That’s what I’ve decided.
Whatever. If you insist,
I won’t hesitate to refer you.
Thank you.
Ginjiro Moving Center
Okay, you guys, let’s get to work!
Hitch up your britches!
Yes, sir!
Huh? Why is the beardy here?
Why are you here?
I want a lot of cash for dating.
You’re out of cash, but you want
to date? You are truly a fool.
Never mind that, start working!
I’ll work without you telling me!
Detachment! I’ll be detached
and work earnestly!
That’s all I can do, now! Go, Kenji!
Hey, newcomer! That’s the spirit!
Carrying that alone is a great feat!
I’m being acknowledged?!
Hanai’s working hard as usual, too!
Well, this is training for me!
You shouldn’t s… strain yourself!
Y… You, too.
You were having a lot of trouble going up those stairs just now!
I’m surprised!
I’m impressed. Very impressed.
Wh… What, this is nothing.
E… Easy…
You’re some workers!
Haven’t seen anyone carry something
like that alone since Ichi-san, I think?!
I-Ichi-san?
Isn’t that so, Ichi-san?
Huh?
E-Everybody?
U-Umm… I’m Ichijou!
We’re in the same class.
Er…
Hello. This is the first
time we’ve talked, isn’t it?
Yes…
It’s that amateur wrestling girl.
C-Come to think of it,
she was in our class.
I didn’t know she was
working in the same field.
What, you know each other?
Having these big brutes bow down
to you, you are something, Ichi!
No… umm…
Really, you are too good to be female!
Too good to be female?
But I am a girl.
Lifting heavy things is
just applying dynamics.
I get tired just like everyone else.
Out of my way!
I-Imadori-san?
You don’t have to strain yourself,
Ichijou. I’ll take care of this.
This isn’t a job for a girl. Rest a bit.
Ah… Thank you, Imadori-san!
Sure!
Heave-ho!
This is light.
Yes! I know what to do!
If I carry these slowly,
one at a time, I can goof off!
That girl might have carried
all the small boxes at once.
With this, I won’t have
to do any heavy work.
Salary
I did it!
Is it alright to receive
the same amount as that girl?
That was a good workout.
Money! Money! A date!
Isn’t it great?
Really. Right now, I can ask
Ichijou on a date with this.
Yay! Yay!
I accept.
What did I say?
Umm… It’s my first date!
I look forward to getting to know you!
Oh, noooo!
My usual bad habit got me
into this outrageous situation…
Yay! An air conditioner and shaved ice
hit the spot in summer, doesn’t it?
Staying indoors all day
is bad for your health.
I know, I know!
I have all kinds of plans to go out.
Like the fireworks display
with Miko-chan and the gang.
That’s right… Miko-chan and Eri-chan…
I wonder if we’ll be able to go
to the fireworks display.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
I’m Sara.
When I told Yakumo I’d never seen
a fireworks display in Japan,
she invited me to go with her.
On the next School Rumble:
Summer
Friendship
Fireworks
“Summer, Friendship, and Fireworks.”
I’m going to wear a yukata.
Harima, heartbroken again.
Currently submitting a manga.
Easily misunderstood Harima.
And easily misunderstanding Hanai.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!