Coming up next!
Don’t touch the channel!
School Rumble is starting soon!
Tenma’s request: When you watch TV,
keep the lights on in the room
and watch from a distance
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Survival After School!
Arrival When Confessing!
Hospital For Two!
Kenji Harima, confesses today.
Yellow roses mean
“Everything about you is lovely.”
It’s over. It’s over.
Let’s go have some cake on the way home.
Then, shall we stop by El Cado?
We have room cleaning duty from today.
Oh, that’s right.
Then we can’t go.
They sell out so fast.
They do.
Let’s see… I guess around here is okay.
Wait!
Hey, don’t run away!
I’m such a klutz.
Everybody gone?
Then, let’s lock up.
There’s somebody still in here!!
It won’t open!! Isn’t there anybody there?!
Silence
There’s nobody…
I know!
T-Too high…
No good. I can’t get down.
These things always happen to me.
Ah, well, shouldn’t be a problem.
When club activities start,
somebody will come…
Just stay calm.
It’s so tranquil.
So mellow.
It’s making me… sleepy.
What did you say?!!
What was that?!
E-Evening?!
All the clubs were off today!?
I’m going to miss the
“The Three Slashed” rerun
about the fake 10,000 bales of rice…
I wonder if Yakumo is taping it…
At this rate, I won’t be able
to do my homework either.
What will I say tomorrow?
“I was locked up, so I couldn’t do it…”?
I hope Yakumo doesn’t find the
pudding I hid in the refrigerator.
Stop it! Stop it!
I’ve got to think positively!
I should use this situation effectively.
Yes, let’s see…
How about imagining I’m marooned
on a deserted island?!
I’ll imagine I’m in an extreme situation…
Yes, I’m being tested.
It’ll be my chance to verify
my confidence!
Oh, looking at it that way,
this is becoming exciting!
Let’s see. Upon landing
on a deserted island,
what is the first thing I would do?
Build a raft? Build a fire?
No, no, it has to be food!
Okay! I’ll go look for
coconuts or something!
Explore, explore… Huh?
A pastry… Oh my, and I was only fooling.
But, why is there a pastry
in a place like this?
Expiry date is the day after tomorrow.
It’s still fresh.
Come to think of it, I’m hungry.
I wonder if it’s okay to eat this…
No, no! No matter how hungry,
someone threw this away.
This is dange…
I have no will power…
Spicy hot!
Spinning Extra Spicy Curry Pastry —
Spicy enough to make your eyes spin
E-Ekthtra thpithy curry pathtry?!
I hate thpithy food! Geeth!
Water! I want water!
But, what shall I do. There’s no
plumbing in here. This is true survival!
Water! God, grant me rain!!
A sprinkler?
Move, you…!
Huh? What makes this move?
There’s no switch…
My mouth’s still burning!
I’m getting irritated!
Come on!
I did it!!
Water, water, water!
Oh, it feels so good!
I know how castaways feel, yeah!
I have no change of clothes or towel.
Why didn’t I think of something so ordinary?
When I think… what if I won’t
be able to ever go home.
It’s a little enjoyable… but, it’s sad
after all. I wonder if Yakumo is worried.
And… I wonder what Karasuma is doing?
I’m having a hard time
sleeping… on this mat.
Ah! Were you sleeping?
I’m sorry for making such a commotion.
Karasuma-kun, did you come to save me?!
Soft
Soft?
Embarrassing!!!
Tsukamoto is amazing.
Actually, it was Karasuma’s pastry
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Cleaning duty… I forgot completely…
But, let’s go to El Cado for cake
on the way home after all.
Yeah.
So, the four of us… Huh?
Come to think of it…
Where’s Tsukamoto?
She cut out?!
No, Tsukamoto’s not the type
to cut out of something like this.
She probably just forgot and went home.
What?
Yeah. She wanted to watch that
rerun of “The Three Slashed.”
That sort of thing distracted her
and she just went on home.
Boy, that girl is really hopeless.
Crap. She went home? I was looking
forward to cleaning with Tenma-chan.
Huh?
How unusual. He’s actually cleaning…
Oh well, I would have been killing
time until evening anyway.
Dammit. He could have set an earlier time.
Calling me out again
with a letter of challenge.
You don’t give up, do you Tennoji?
Until I crush you to pieces,
I’ll keep on challenging you to fights.
Here I come!
With a battle cry?!
Your fighting is weak,
but your battle cry is good!
However!
As long as you’re in love with Tenma-chan,
I’m showing no mercy. See you.
Wait! Are you saying that you’re
in love with Tenma-chan, too?
You bastard… don’t go calling her “chan”!
You… you’re wasting your time.
What do you mean?
You’re down, aren’t you?!
Not the fighting.
Tenm… I mean Tsukamoto-san, said
she already has someone she likes.
What did you say?!
What was that?!
Don’t make up stories!
It’s not a story.
Thank you. But I’m in
love with someone else.
So?
That… That can’t be!
I… I’ve never heard about this before!
T-Tenma-chan has someone… she likes?
Yeah, and night fell, it was terrible!
So, you didn’t go home.
Damn… Tenma-chan likes someone?!
She’s never shown a shred of that!
Who is it? Who is the guy
that Tenma-chan likes?!
I’m going to find that out!
The next problem is a little difficult, but…
Hanai.
Yes, Ma’am!
The relation of energy,
area, and speed at the perihelion where r,
Who is it?!
The rate of variability is 0…
Who is the guy that Tenma-chan likes?
… so that is the result.
That is a very precise answer.
Just as I expected.
Hanai is amazing.
Yeah, he’s like seriousness clothed.
Could it be that Tenma-chan…
… likes that serious guy, Hanai?!
No, no, it can’t be. It’s just my hunch,
but those aren’t the eyes of love!
Then, who?
Him?! No, it can’t be!
Him?
No, it isn’t.
Crap. Who in the world is it?
I can’t keep up longer. This is bugging the hell out of me.
That’s Torimaru, was it?
Harima mistakes the name “Karasuma” for “Torimaru.”
The kanjis are very similar, but differ by one stroke.
He stares out the window
all day long. He’s strange.
Well, he’s totally out of the running.
That stupid and faintly dull boy
wouldn’t even have a one percent chance
of taking my Tenma-chan’s heart.
You’re a good guy… er… Torimaru!
Ahh, tell me, Tenma-chan—
Huh? She’s looking my way.
Those are the eyes of love?!
Could it be?!
Me?!
Is it me?!
It is me!
It’s me!
It must be! That burning look!
Actually, I kind of thought so, but…
Tenma-chan’s in love with me!
Flag: Congratulations Kenji Harima.
I am wonderful. November 2004, Lucky day
I have no choice but to confess now!
Sorry, Tenma-chan. I’ve never cursed
being so thickheaded as I have today!
There you are!
That delicate body burning
in love, waiting each day.
It must have been harsh.
It must have been difficult.
But that’s all over now!
Listen carefully, Tenma-chan.
You don’t have to say anything.
Right now, I will tell you!
Tenma-chan!
Harima-kun?!
Watch out!
I love you!
Yagami Hospital
It’ll take ten days for you to recover…
I feel like something really great happened today, but I can’t remember what it is.
However, someone with
as bad luck as you is rare.
My memory is spotty…
Well, I guess for an
accident as bad as that,
complete recovery in ten days
is actually pretty lucky.
Come in.
Harima-kun, I came to see how you were doing!
Oh! Why? Lucky!
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Harima-kun, I came to see how you were doing!
Oh! Why? Lucky!
Osakabe-sensei, hello.
Are you here to visit as well?
Well, something like that.
Are you all right, Harima-kun?
Ah… I-I’m fine!
I’m not fine! A white hospital room!
I’m in pajamas! Tenma-chan in
plain clothes carrying flowers!
What’s going on? My heart’s pounding!
He’s so easy to read.
Tsukamoto-kun…
I know you just came, but can
you arrange those flowers?
Oh, sure!
You can finally breathe, I guess.
I hate to say it myself, but I’m pitiful.
Well, now…
I’m in the way. I’m disappearing, Kenji-kun.
Wha… What?!
Stay, please stay, Itoko!
I’m hopeless alone, I can’t do it!
Stop it, you’re being cowardly!
Itoko!
And when you call someone, remember the “San”.
San… Itoko-san! Don’t abandon me!
Who said I was abandoning you?
Relax. I have this.
What’s this?
An intercom I made myself.
Intercom?!
Put this on.
I’ll give you conversational advice,
so you can just follow along.
It’s a good thing this hospital allows mobile phones.
You are lucky after all.
Why do I have to put on
something like that?
I’m not forcing you.
Let me have that!
Since you asked, I have to comply.
Put this on the collar of your
pajamas and this in your ear.
It’s just like a detective’s. Cool, huh?
Does she make these as a hobby?
Do your best. See you.
Is it really going to work?
Okay, Tsukamoto-kun’s coming back.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Come in.
C-Come in.
Hi.
H-Hi.
It was a terrible accident.
I was so worried.
But I’m glad you’re fine now.
Thank you.
Th-Thank you.
Actually, I brought some black tea. Can I brew some?
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
They’re only tea bags, but it tastes good.
It’s better if the water is freshly boiled.
I like black tea.
Is that so? That’s good.
You’re shaped for easy childbirth.
What?
Note: In Japan, women who have big bottoms are said to have
easier childbirth. It “is” a compliment, although very embarassing,
and so only old people use it.
What are you making me say!
Can you see it too?!
That’s the first time
anyone said that to me.
My heart’s pounding.
We’re alone! She came to see me!
Ah, Tenma-chan in plain clothes
looks three times cuter!
But, I’m glad.
Actually, you’re sort of a delinquent,
and I wasn’t sure if flowers were okay.
N-Not at all!
Flowers are important to a delinquent, too!
Eh? Ah… Is… Is that so?
If it’s a flower like you, that is.
Is what you really want to say?
Like I said, how come you know?!
I’m… No, rather, I can’t say
something that embarrassing.
What are you saying?
She came just to see you.
You have to say something sensitive.
But…
Relay your feelings frankly.
That’s a basic of successful love.
Uh… I… I see…
O-Okay, I’ll say it!
A flower like you, that is!
I said it!
Note: “Kimi mitai” means “like you” referring to the flowers beautiful like you. However, Tenma in all her intelligence interpreted “kimi” as “egg yolk”, the alternative meaning.
What’s like a yolk? Is it a story
about eggs? What happens next?
Ah… No, there used to
be ice cream like that.
The texture was just like
the yolk of a hard boiled egg!
How can she be so thickheaded!
It took everything I had to say it
and this is what I get!
Tenma Tsukamoto cannot
connect conversations
when there is more than
10 seconds in between.
But really, you actually
said something like that.
Huh? What?!
No, nothing.
Kenji can’t make those connections either.
Hey, what should I do?
Go carefully. Tsukamoto is frighteningly
slow when it comes to attention from men.
Even in class there should be
many boys interested in her.
Itoko! Tell me their names later.
I told you, don’t panic.
Everything will be fine.
Right now, you are one step ahead.
H-How do you know?
You are about the only one who is able to
say something so embarrassing yourself.
Yes, embarrassing. Very embarrassing.
Really embarrassing…
Itoko, there’s something
that’s bothering me.
You’re not really just having
fun at my expense, are you?
Oops, I’m suddenly getting interference!
I’m going to stop transmitting for a while!
Eh? Wha… What’s that?!
Farewell, Kenji-kun!
Itoko! Hey! Ito…
This is terrible!
I’ll have to do this on my own.
What? What happened?!
I’m sorry, the apple!
What, is that all?! It’s okay.
I got some from Itoko a little while ago.
That’s just enough for me.
What? You ate some earlier? Then…
It’s fine!
I was just hungry for half an apple!
Argh! I don’t know what
I’m saying myself! Damn!
She’s laughing at me! Oh, no,
did I do something wrong?!
I’m glad.
We sit right next to each other,
but we haven’t talked before, right?
It’s good we talked about
all kind of things today.
It makes me feel good.
Th-That’s so. Now that
you mention it, it’s true.
But I went out of my way
and depended on Itoko for help.
I just had to be myself.
No, it’s not too late!
I’ll be frank! Frank…
I’ll hug you!
I love you!
If you want Tsukamoto-kun, she left while you were thinking.
She said to take care.
Look, it’s Tsukamoto-kun.
The one you love so much.
Shut up!
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
The teacher told Yakumo to go and look.
Is our class so untrustworthy?
Next time on School Rumble, “Cleaning The Pool!
Running Around The Pool! War At The Pool!”
Cleaning The Pool!
Running Around The Pool!
War At The Pool!
See? We are properly…
… not cleaning the pool!
Hanai and Harima both hate to lose.
Hiroyoshi Aso, hidden big wheel of 2-C.
Our original goal was to clean the pool.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!