Coming up next!
Sch—
School Rumble is coming up next!
School Rumble
Request from Hario Harima:
When watching TV, keep the room
lighted and don’t sit too close to the set!
He’s here!
That bastard’s finally here!
Harima’s returned!
Get him!
Looks like you’ve been jilted…
What did you come here for?
You know there’s no place for you here!
Go to sleep!
What’s the matter, Harima?
Are you running away?
Have you turned into a coward?
Karasuma…
You were quick…
Did you want to eat a
home-made lunch that badly?
I came from the bottom of hell
just to defeat you!
A waste of time.
Tsukamoto-san’s heart is already mine.
T-Tenma-chan!
Too bad, Harima-kun.
Unforgivable…
I can never forgive those like you,
who use wicked techniques
to steal people’s hearts.
Too bad… Until a little while ago,
you ruled this campus…
After losing your dear Tsukamoto-san
and being tormented by me…
In the end you were driven to the ends
of the earth. That is just too miserable.
I pity you from the bottom of my heart.
Don’t be ridiculous!
The battle hasn’t ended yet!
I will take back Tenma-chan
and the peace of the campus!
You never give up, do you?
I challenge you, Karasuma!
Here I come!
Take this!
You can’t beat me.
I wonder about that.
How… did you become… so strong?
Grief… Grief changed me.
I have… lost.
Tenma-chan!
Harima-kun.
Tenma-chan, the villains are gone.
Everything will be alright.
That’s good…
I… actually… Actually, Harima-kun…
It’s alright. It’s alright.
That’s all over.
We can live for the future!
Harima-kun!
I love you.
I do too.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Manga Blues!
Big Sister Blues!
Kappa Super-Bad Blues!
Where is this?
Whose room is this?
Kenji Harima, brokenhearted.
What is he doing here?
Umm, Karasuma-kun, are the
rice balls a little too big?
That’s good…
Umm, Karasuma-kun,
does it taste good?
That’s good…
I’m enjoying this,
but is it boring for you?
That’s good…
This is quite a masterpiece…
It’s quite good for a first effort.
Thank you.
By the way, why did you
decide to write a manga?
Th-That’s…
No… no… It’s alright!
If you don’t want to say…
Well… Then, why did you bring it here?
Because I’m a big fan of Nijou-sensei, whose work are published in your magazine.
It’s true, there is an influence here.
The way you drew the eyes.
Isn’t there? I thought so, too.
Ah, if that’s the case,
there’s going to be a New Face Award
in the next Jo Nijou Awards.
Nijou-sensei will be a special judge.
Why don’t you submit this work?
I think you could at least
get an honorable mention.
Do you really think so?
Once you win the new faces award,
the next step is to aim
for a serialization.
You’re still young.
You needn’t be impatient.
Y-Yeah.
Nijou-sensei’s work certainly encouraged me!
That writer saved me. I aimed
for him when I wrote this!
I understand, I understand!
I got really excited by his
“Genroku Self-defense Force” myself!
Oh! It was the same for me! No wonder!
The one who produced that work
knows what it’s about!
They go into enemy territory only
to find it extremely peaceful…
There was no reason for them
to go there at all.
Yeah, yeah. Ah, that was really popular, wasn't it?
Look, Nijou-sensei just arrived!
Thanks for coming by, Nijou-sensei
Well, then… I’ll keep this…
This was a mistake.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Where are you going?! Hey!
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Café El Cado
It’s raining hard, isn’t it?
It’s just a shower, so it’ll end soon.
Tsukamoto-san’s face remains slack…
I wonder why?
Nothing special…
Don’t hide it. Don’t hide it.
We already know.
Recently you’ve been
conversing with Karasuma-kun
and it looks like you’re getting cozy.
How? Why? How come you know?!
Didn’t take much effort.
It’s obvious.
Figures…
Hey, you. What are you doing
out in the rain like this?
It was… a dream.
The last road left for me to take…
Writing a manga…
And becoming a little famous…
Somewhere, she… that girl I once loved…
She would by chance, pick up my book
in the corner of a book store…
“Strange,” she’d say, smiling a little…
Just that… would have made me happy.
Oh, my, looking closely,
you’re really young.
And on top of that, handsome.
You’ll catch a cold.
You have nowhere to go, do you?
Come to my place, ah, what’s your name?
My pen name is Hario Harima so that the
kids would think it funny and remember it.
You know, I wonder about
rice balls every single day.
Are rice balls Karasuma-kun’s favorite food?
Are you sure he’s not just enduring it?
You’re right, Karasuma-kun said he liked curry.
That’s it, Karasuma-kun felt sorry
for me because I was so down.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Why didn’t I notice all this time?!
I’m sorry! I was depending
on his kindness! I’m so awful!
Okay, tomorrow, I’ll go back to the
beginning and ask Yakumo to make curry!
Men like home cooking!
If you want to get to a man’s heart,
food is the best bet.
But I can’t cook…
Even if it’s bad, if you put
your love in it, that’s enough.
Love!
Y-You’re right. If it’s love,
no one can beat me!
Okay! I’ll try home-made curry!
To tell the truth, when I first
saw you, something went off.
You’re just the same as me.
I was also jilted a little while ago.
Men’s clothes.
Don’t be nervous.
Just think of it as your own home.
I’m out of beer, and I don’t
have much cash this month…
It can’t be helped. I’ll just have
to make do with low-malt beer.
Here.
No, I’m…
That’s right. You’re a minor.
That’s not what I mean. I need
stronger alcohol to get drunk.
… so in the end, I was just
wrestling with myself, you know.
A small but warm home with two children…
On her birthday, I’d secretly
get champagne and flowers ready…
But it was all a fleeting dream!
What are you going to do with this?
This thing This is piece of trash!
Wait…
Throw it away!
The manuscript was destroyed like my dream!
You can fall in love many times.
For example… Right now,
right in front of your eyes…
Right?
N… No… I’m…
Is that so? That was unreasonable,
wasn’t it? Don’t let it bother you.
Good night.
I’m sorry.
To Hario Harima-kun,
I read your manga.
It was very interesting.
I think you have talent.
You shouldn’t quit.
Buy yourself some food
with this 1000 yen.
I… I can’t take this money!
I’m already in her debt!
After she said she was
short on cash this month…
There’s more…
It’s not as good as Nijou-sensei’s
“Genroku Self-defense Force” though.
I’m a fan.
–
Nijou-sensei
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
The ingredients are all here!
Sis, are you sure you can do it yourself?
Shall I help?
I’m fine! I’m fine!
There’s no meaning
if I don’t do it myself.
You take it easy and
watch TV or something.
Uh… Okay…
Now, here goes!
Oww! I cut my finger!
Here are the bandages!
Let’s see… Next is…
No, no, put the meat in
before the vegetables.
Yakumo, the fire extinguisher,
the fire extinguisher!
Hey, Bro, see you here a lot recently.
Yeah, well… Umm…
I have nothing else to do.
Finished!
Curry made with love!
Well, then, let’s give it a taste.
Never tasted anything like it before.
I’m glad you’re here.
Iori, taste this.
What’s with this face?
Come on!
Iori!
What’s for dinner tonight?
What do you want to eat, Shin-chan?
Pancakes!
Okay, okay.
Today is the third day.
Hario, I left lunch money
on the table, okay?
Okay.
No matter what I said, in the end
I keep returning to that woman’s place.
What am I doing anyway?
Hey, where are you?
Where did you go?
Tenma-chan!
Of all places, we just had to run into each other here at the edge of the world.
She seems to be looking for something.
Could it be me?!
But, you won’t find me
the way I am now.
I’m not the Kenji Harima
you know anymore.
I’ve fallen as far as I can go
and my hair has fallen out on top.
I don’t want you to see me.
It’s better for both of us
if we just pass each other by.
Farewell, Tenma-chan.
What?!
Iori!
Iori,  Iori!
That’s Tenma-chan’s pet cat?
He’s being washed away!
I want to help!
But I mustn’t have anything more to do with you.
Someone! Someone! Please help me!
Please save him! Please save him!
Someone else will save him.
Iori!
Someone’s jumped in!
Iori…
Thank you very much.
Tenma-chan, look at how
I’ve changed and laugh at me!
Are you… Could you possibly be… Umm…
A kappa?
I’m Sanpei.
Thank you, Kappa-san.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something.
Tenma’s feeding him rice balls again.
She just doesn’t learn.
But she messed up the curry.
There’s only one thing to do.
What do you mean?
Next time on School Rumble:
Please, God!
Please! Real Animal Divination!
Please! Tenma!
I have a secret plan.
Wait, the signs don’t say that.
Yeah!
Mikoto wants to go on to university.
She’s in love.
Eri is worried about something.
She’s going to see a fortune-teller.
Akira likes to scheme.
“I have a secret plan.”
Don’t miss
the next
episode!