Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next!
It’s supposed to be around here…
What’s that?!
3,559.
Hey! You must transfer all the
water in the jug without spilling a drop!
What an intensive training.
But… something’s different.
It’s not the usual composed Hanai!
What could have happened?
Have you noticed?
Right now, he has the
power of a drawn sword.
Yes… He has lost the scabbard of reason.
A beast starving for blood.
In his heart, he is… battling evil itself.
Lose yourself and you
cannot conquer your path.
However, with love a man becomes strong.
It is a thing beyond our control.
Well, putting this matter off…
If you want to drop him,
now is the time.
No, I’m not here for that.
You are strong but unable to show
your feminine side, isn’t that so?
He is one that can understand that.
Suou? What are you doing here?
Well, you haven’t been
home for two days.
Two days… Has it only been that long?
I feel like I’ve been here half a year.
By the way, who was
that old man just now?
A stranger.
Grandpa!
You know you mustn’t go off by yourself!
Miss, now is the time for you, too, you know!
Geez! I am Akiko!
Akemi-san!
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Hanai Counterattacks!
Karen Sparkles!
Reunion with Big Sister
Mikoto Suou, worries about her childhood friend.
Struck while being told,
“Don’t make your parents worry!”
That Suou… Why did she hit me?
But… downtown hasn’t changed at all.
He’s so cool…
Definitely the best in our school!
Those sunglasses look so sinister, it’s great.
Students from my school.
Would a kiss be okay here?
Yes, I think so.
I wonder if he has a girlfriend?
I’d like to go out with him one day.
With Harima Kenji-san.
Girls!
Tell me all what you were talking about!
In… in the alley behind the coffee shop
we were picked on by some delinquents.
He helped us.
I think he’s still there.
Thank you!
So that’s it!
So that’s what it’s all about!
Yakumo-kun must have been
deceived in the same way.
And, I think… it was all an act!
I won’t permit it! Harima Kenji!
So this is the place!?
Th-This is…
Da… mn… Har… ri… ma… Ken… ji.
Wait! Harima Kenji!
The intonation is different…
What?
My name is Harry McKenzie.
Who?
Harry McKenzie… Didn’t you
call because you knew it?
However, young man, when asking
a person’s name, give yours first.
Isn’t that the manner of this country?
I’m Haruki Hanai.
I’d like to ask you something.
Did you do this?
I wanted to settle it peacefully,
but Japanese are belligerent.
I was in danger of serious injury.
It’s strange.
They all have joints dislocated and
there are some with back injuries.
Amateur fights wouldn’t end this way.
Then, are you saying this?
That I assaulted
all these men by myself?
No, I wouldn’t go that far, but…
Of course. That would be impossible!
I couldn’t have done that! Nice!
You have good reflexes.
Th-This guy…
Wait a minute! There’s a lady watching.
Hanai-senpai?
Y… Y… Y… Y… Yakumo-kun!
Ah, there’s a good reason for this…
But, what are you doing here?
Ah, um… actually, my part-time job…
Miss, it’s dangerous.
Please step back.
You bastard!
Alright! I’ll take you on,
you dishonorable man!
Just what I want.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Huh?
Harima… and Yakumo-kun on a date?!
No, that’s not it at all.
Then, what are you here for?!
In this deserted back alley!
Answer me!
Well, actually…
Oh, no! Wait, Kenji! At this rate the
fact that I’m drawing manga will leak!
On top of that, this is the last person
that needs to know!
To defeat you, of course!
That is a wonderful goal.
I’ll show you the result of my training!
Come now, you have nothing
to do with this. Step back!
Ah, the manuscript!
Stop there… Younger Sister.
You pick it up! Bastard!
That’s a nice punch.
But it’s nothing, if you can’t connect.
He…
Aren’t I your opponent?
Interesting.
I thought there were no samurai
in this country, but… there is.
So, you finally realized it?
What’s the matter? Why do you falter?
It’s too late for you to notice how terrible I am now.
This is a samurai?! So this is sakayaki?
Sakayaki: shaving the forehead, samurai-style
Your cap…
This baldy is the one who stole your heart?
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Hey, that girl’s here again.
Yeah, Gon-something-or-other from 2-D.
She’s huge.
It seems she came to study from Mexico.
Ichi-jou!
I’m eating lunch with you!
So that’s it, you practice
wrestling together!
You seem very strong, Lala-chan.
She challenged me to a match once,
thinking I was someone else.
Ichijou, that’s not a normal high school student conversation.
Oh? So your name is Lala-chan.
Ichijo, I’m taking this.
Ichi-jou!
Yes?
What is that boy?
He is Imadori-san.
Pleased to meet you.
Buzz off!
You don’t have to be so cruel.
Yeah, yeah…
Her size is definitely…
D!
You bastard!
Um… that’s dangerous,
swinging that around…
It doesn’t warrant something like that!
Hurry up and disappear!
Are you alright?
Not a problem. Not a problem.
One plus one is two.
I was saved by Ichijou, wasn’t I?
But…
I wish she stopped her sooner.
Imadori-san!
Miko-chin, she’s picking on me.
Is that so?
Not “is that so?”
I see…
Ichi-jou, you like that boy?
Is that true, Ichijou?
I’ve never… thought about it…
Someone as strong as you are,
what are you afraid of?
Take him by force! It’s irritating!
I’m not like that…
Ichijou, tell us the details later!
Hey! You with the big breasts!
This one’s way stronger than you!
Miko-chin, get her with your hyper-kick!
You can take that blockhead
with one blow!
What?
Watch your mouth! I have nothing
to do with this, you know!
There are those in every country.
Worthless men and thieving women!
Lala-san!?
Thieving women?!
My father was careless with women.
When I see trash, it irritates me!
You want a match?
No, thanks!
Wait a minute!
Something like that, even I can do!
I’m sorry!
Iron Claw!
What power!
Is he alright?
Leave it alone!
Leave it to me!
Doowah!
Do you remember?
Mask, mask!
Is it fun picking on the weak?
Want to fight?
Hey, hey, the two of you, cut…
Why don’t you cut it out?!
Harry McKenzie?
He’s in the same school?!
He not only took the words
out of my mouth, he has presence!
Oh? You’re…
You know him, Harry?
Well, something like that.
It seems there are pretexts involved.
This is interesting!
I, chairman of 2-D, Masakazu Tougou,
have a proposal!
Let us, 2-D and 2-C students, settle all
our disagreements at the athletic meet!
How about it?
He said it!
Just what I was going to propose!
We accept.
Why not?!
Rather, are you okay, Tenma?
Not fighting here, you are
an awful coward, Miko-chin!
You are a shrew,
just as the rumors say!
They aren’t so strong!
Even after this?
What?
These marks!
So that’s it… I’ll look forward
to that athletic meet, Miko-chin!
There’s more.
What?
Banana?!
It’s… it’s all over for me…
What size?
About the same as Miko-chin.
Well done, soldier.
A true man.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Hey, hey, you guys!
There’s a new nurse!
And I heard she’s really good looking.
We know.
Already? First thing in the morning?!
What’s with the get-up?
Anyone can see.
The place injured people
go to is the infirmary.
Don’t tell me… you hurt
yourselves for that?!
We have no regrets.
This is the way we live.
Damn… It’s uncomfortable going in.
Everybody in class probably
knows about my bald spot.
– The dressing’s coming off…
– You’ve already been treated…
They look like they’re gossiping!
Could it be about me?
I give up. I give up.
I’m going to rest in the infirmary!
Wasn’t that Harima just now?
He’s going home already? I wonder why…
He’s acting just like a bad school girl.
Could it be his head feels cool
and he can’t settle down?
What’s that?
Well, shouldn’t you apologize?
I told you I apologized the other day!
But it got worse, didn’t it?
Apologizing again would make things better.
I absolutely don’t want to!
You are really stubborn!
Charming girls are frank, you know.
Yeah, apologize, Eri-chan!
Aw, geez! Okay!
Hey, you!
Have you seen Harima-kun?
Harima-kun went to the infirmary.
Is that so?! Thank you.
Hey!
We’ll go with you!
Infirmary
Well, is she there?
Probably.
Okay, we’ll play rock-paper-scissors to see who goes first.
Why do we have to go in one at a time?
Don’t you know man-to-man is basic?
Really, what did they come here for?
You guys, too!
Hey!
You guys again? I told you not
to make noise in the hallways!
Damn, it’s Goriyama,
the guidance counselor!
R-Run!
Are you ninjas?!
What? What’s the matter?
That idiot, what’s she doing?!
Come!
Why?!
Tsukamoto!
Leave Tenma to me. I’ll get her back.
We can’t get in from the main entry…
If that’s the case, let’s try from outside.
A new nurse?
Yeah…
Now that you mention it,
there was supposed to be a change
in the second semester.
The last one was a
pleasant older lady, but…
I don’t want to be seen
apologizing to him.
Never mind. Hurry up and go in!
O-Okay!
Tenma-chan…
The window by the bed was left open.
Oh, there’s someone sleeping here.
Hario!
How have you been!
He knocked down the nurse?!
In the middle of the day?!
A delinquent does things
different after all…
I can’t ever go in!
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
This is a grave state of affairs.
A student attacking faculty!
It’s a good thing it didn’t
become an incident.
Katou-sensei… It’s true that Harima has
been known to be quite a delinquent.
However, he’s changed
since he entered high school.
Recently, it seems he’s found
something to devote himself to.
I can’t believe he’d do something like that.
Tani-sensei! An indulgent educational
posture like that is a problem!
Well…
Inﬁrmary
Anegasaki-sensei, we’re coming in.
Ah, yes, yes…
Hello. Did you want something from me?
Yes, well, Harima from my class
caused you great inconvenience.
Don’t let it bother you.
It was all my fault.
He’s not at fault at all.
Is… is that so?
Rather than that…
I made cookies for the teachers,
to serve as a greeting.
Faculty Room
Cookies?
Tani-san!
Yuripe, what’s the matter?
Tani-san. Is it true
you’re going to Tokyo?
There’s something I want to give to you.
These are cookies that I baked.
Yuripe…
I’ll eat them, later.
The next day, and the day after that,
Gon gathered chestnuts—
Yes, okay, that’s enough. Perfect.
Will you stop it already!
You’re the one who should stop!
Sorry, everyone. My class is being noisy…
Sensei, you’re wrong there!
We have been searching for opponents that can satisfy us!
When we meet them in the
upcoming athletic meet,
we need them to be violent beasts!
Ichi-jou!
That’s the way it is.
Is that so?
It’s over.
2-D gives me stiff shoulders.
Classes are easy, though.
Oh well!
Anegasaki-sensei’s cookies will heal me.
Can’t find them anywhere.
Have you heard, Tani-sensei?
It seems my 2-D class and your 2-C
are competing with each other
at the athletic meet.
Oh, is that so?
Well, between my superior class
and yours, we know which will win.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
It’s not me saying it, you know.
It’s the gossip going
around within the school.
Well, don’t be too harsh on us.
Yeah…
Oh, by the way, I had
the cookies on your desk.
They were sitting there forever,
so I thought you didn’t want them.
Well, excuse me.
Today’s class will be PE.
Change into your jerseys!
We’ll do some solid practice.
We will defeat Class 2-D.
Aim for the class championship.
Win… the athletic meet!
This is Tae Anegasaki.
Everyone, do your best at the athletic meet, okay?!
If you get hurt, I’ll be waiting
in the infirmary.
Next on School Rumble:
Time to Start the War!
Now the Cavalry Battle!
And the Great Uprising!
“Time to Start the War! Now the Cavalry Battle! And the Great Uprising!”
Hario? I’m watching you!
Introduction of the new characters.
Harry McKenzie
Masakazu Tougou, 2-D’s Chairman.
2-C’s rival, 2-D’s Katou-sensei
Don’t miss
the next
episode!