Coming up in…
School Rumble is coming up in 360 seconds.
When you watch TV,
keep the room lighted and don’t sit too close.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Dreams for Art!
Promises to God!
Wish on a Star!
Youko Sasakura, Art Teacher.
Itoko and Youko are old friends.
Here… Be counting on you
to get the AV room ready.
Yes, sir.
Sorry to put you to so much trouble.
It’s because your seat is the closest up front.
Oh, I like it. The expression, “Audio-Visual.”
You poor thing, Tsukamoto-san.
Did you have to go on another errand?
Oh… no, I don’t mind. Excuse me.
What a sweet girl.
You’ll find few old-fashioned girls like her.
She’s completely different from
the Osakabe-sensei of the past.
Forget that.
I’m only joking.
Oh, by the way, did you consider
modeling for me, like I asked?
Ugh. Here it comes. Okay.
I’ll do it, I’ll do it!
Or I’ll never hear the end of it.
Thank you very much.
I have new information.
What the…?
What’s happening?
War council.
So, Nishimoto, what’s today’s agenda?
Sasakura-sensei is going
to hold an art exhibit.
And she selected the model
for her paintings today.
According to my sources,
the model will be Osakabe Itoko-sensei.
And the theme is…
‘Nudity.’
This is, most likely.
Though it’s in paintings, we’ll get to see
Itoko-sensei’s beautiful body?!
Her seductive curves…
I can just picture them!
Praise the lord for Nishimoto’s network!
He’s undoubtly our class’s
number one Ero-Sommelier!
After all, his family runs a video store!
Settle down.
Gan
ji
Nishi
moto
Ganji Nishimoto.
Due to his gentle nature,
and because he influences the hopes
and dreams of the men in 2-C,
Buddha Nishimoto
he is idolized as “Buddha Nishimoto.”
Imadori-kun, what’s the size of the target?
D-cup! There’s no mistake!
Kyousuke Imadori
Kyousuke Imadori. “Hummingbird.”
One of the 5 Tiger Generals.
His “Video Store Pact” of blood
brotherhood with Nishimoto is famous.
Video Store Pact
Good.
Fuyuki-kun, the things I’ve asked for?
Leave it to me!
I have Itoko-sensei’s secret data taken with my camera.
Takeichi Fuyuki
Takeichi Fuyuki. “White Heron.”
Recognizing his intelligence-gathering talent,
Nishimoto recruited him with videos, “Three in Appreciation.”
Three in Appreciation
Nara-chi, help me pass these out.
Oh, yes.
Kentaro Nara
Underling
What idiots.
Why are all the boys
in our class like that?
But wouldn’t a nude painting of
Itoko-sensei be something to see?
Oh, I suppose. She has
a pretty nice figure.
C-Could Karasuma-kun be interested, too?!
Thank goodness. Karasuma-kun doesn’t seem interested.
His interests are different
from everybody else’s.
The others in our class that
aren’t creeps are…
Asou…
Umezu…
Harima isn’t interested, either?
Who knows? Maybe he has dark,
creepy thoughts deep inside.
What’s with that stupid overgrown beard?
A careless reaction can get you creamed.
You guys don’t know Itoko’s rage.
He doesn’t seem interested, either.
He’s, well… serious.
The first war conference is now ended.
Fuyuki, can I have these
top secret photos?
Sure.
Lucky!
The class representative
has finally arisen!
Hey, show them to me, Imadori-kun!
No way!
As class representative,
I must verify that data!
I guess he just wants to see them.
Yeah.
Yakumo-kun!
Me?
Yes, you’d make a pretty picture, too.
Will you do it?
Make a picture?
If I’ll do…
Thanks. It’s a big help!
N-No way…
Yakumo-kun is modeling nude?
I gotta see it… Yakumo-kun painted nu—
That means all the guys
who go to the exhibit will see
the nude images of Yakumo-kun!
Hey!
What should I do? The exhibit…
Nude…
What’s with him?
Harima
You’re helping Sasakura-sensei, too, Yakumo?
Yes…
That’s so cool.
Maybe I should help, too.
Really? Good. I’d feel
embarrassed by myself.
Don’t worry! I can pull it off.
N-No way…
Tenma-chan’s modeling nude?
I wanna see! Tenma-chan in the—
That means all the other creeps
who go to the exhibit will see
Tenma-chan’s nude pictures, too!
What should I do?!
So the satellite at point B which lines up with the trajectory of a larger size A,
will apppear to have twice the size.
What do you think about this, class?
Scratch, scratch
You seem to be concentrating
unusually hard today.
Don’t get indigestion!
Drool
The opening date of the exhibit
has been confirmed.
So when is it?
Next Saturday and Sunday, Yagami Gallery.
Roger. The next lab meeting is cancelled.
They’re works of considerable effort
and three-dimensional.
Th-Three dimensional?
Tsukamoto, you’re going
to help Ms. Sasakura?
Yes, it’s my… first… ex-per-i-ence.
Tenma-chan is so blank about it.
Tenma-chan, what the heck should I do?
Sis… You forgot your lunch again.
Thanks, Yakumo.
Yakumo-chan, you’re going to do it, too?
Yes…
Once she decides,
Yakumo doesn’t hesitate.
Unexpectedly aggressive, isn’t she?
“Aggressive”?
Yakumo-kun, what am I supposed to do?!
They’re going to sell pictures
at the exhibit, too.
Cool.
Oh, maybe I should buy one.
Don’t stop with one…
I see! That’s it!
I’ll get there first and buy up all the pictures!
This feels nostalgic.
Oh, that’s unusual,
hearing that from you.
Seeing them reminds me
of my school days.
It makes me think that
nothing really changes.
We’ve been through a lot.
Yes, we have.
Together.
Right. Good work.
This Saturday. We strike at 9!
But they’re only paintings,
aren’t they?
As someone said,
“We see with our souls.”
Commence the attack!
Cubism
Reception
Sasakura-sensei, congratulations
on your exhibit.
Thank you, girls.
Reception
Your name, please.
Yo, working hard, Tsukamoto?
I’ve never worked at a
reception desk before.
But Yakumo was too embarrassed
to do it by herself.
Your name, please.
She was only helping
at the reception desk.
I knew it’d be something like this.
I didn’t quite understand,
but this is what Osakabe-sensei said…
“Past and present, men are still the same, after all.”
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
A virtual wedding?
Yes. To advertise this church.
We’ll stage a wedding and use
the photographs in a pamphlet.
And you want me to play the bride?
Don’t you think you’d be perfect?
You’re going to be a bride,
Big Sister Yakumo?
I wanna see you in a wedding gown!
Do it, do it!
There, see?
But…
I know!
Who’s going to play the groom, right?
Don’t worry! My senpai at my
part-time job is perfect for the part!
Yo, Yakumo-kun!
I-I’m sorry, Yakumo.
My senpai couldn’t make it.
Do you want to call it off?
I wanted to see you in a gown, though…
O-Okay. It’s all right.
It is? Thank you! I’m sorry!
Hanai-senpai! Let’s see you
go with a serious expression!
Serious?
Like this?
Oh! That was just wonderful!
Even more so, when you don’t talk!
Don’t flatter me, Sara-kun!
Jasmine Restaurant
I heard, Asou!
You turned down the groom’s part?!
What?! You’re kidding!
I’ve got a previous commitment
after work today.
Who’d go to that one?!
You had a chance to be in a picture
with Tsukamoto dressed as a bride!
What a waste!
Just order, already, will ya?!
Your Oolong tea, sir.
No, I’ll have this after
I defeat the enemy.
Didja hear? Hanai’s gonna
be the bridegroom.
This is unforgivable!
No beardless jerk is good enough to play Tenma Tsukamoto’s bridegroom!
Only one can be the bridegroom… Me!
Beautiful…
You don’t have any idea
how I feel, do you?!
But! I’ll tell you now!
To tell the truth, I love y—
Stop the wedding!
Wh-Who’re you?!
Let’s go.
He doesn’t know
S-Stop!
What’s the idea, Harima?!
We’re switching roles.
Sorry, but get another girl.
Just like in olden days!
He came to steal the bride!
Wow! Get ’em!
I can’t do that.
Why? Because she’s the
most wonderful girl!
I know that.
You’re right.
Um…
Let me rephrase it, then…
You ain’t worthy!
Scram!
I-I can’t move… Is this the end?
It’s settled.
Harima-kun!
T-Tenma-chan!
Wha?! Y-You were out!
I’ll never stop coming back!
As long as I have love!
Go!
It’s over.
Hanai-chi!
Y-Yakumo-kun!
What?! You survived my fist?!
Love, oh, Love! Grant me a miracle!
Four-eyes, you love this girl so much?
Of course!
So we’re destined never to agree!
Then let us fight
until our souls give out!
Go! Hurricane Dragon!
Roar! Secret move, Flower Tiger!
The photo shoot is over.
Are you still fighting?
I’m Yakumo Tsukamoto.
I’m the groom now.
How could you ignore
your bride like that?
You were fighting so long, I asked
Takano-senpai to take your place.
Yakumo and I are going on a date now.
How nice! I’m next, okay?
Café El Cado
Well… anyhow… I’m… sorry, man.
Forget it, already.
By the way, why did you come?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Meteor shower?
Yes, it’s coming soon!
Really? When?
Saturday night is the peak.
Hey, let’s all watch it together!
Sounds good. Where?
Yagami Shrine.
I’ll ask Yakumo to fix us box lunches!
Oh, sounds great!
Meteor shower?
Yakumo-kun, you’re like a shooting star!
I’ve got to make a list.
For what?
Of wishes to make.
A wish comes true
if you repeat it three times before a star falls.
Japan has a custom like that, too?
Since it’s a meteor shower
I can make a lot of wishes.
Chanting three times is impossible, though.
Stars fall in an instant.
Oh, right. I’ll write them on poem cards, then.
This isn’t the Tanabata Festival.
Hey, what’s everybody going to wish for?
I hope it’s clear tomorrow night!
Yes!
Skies, stay clear!
Guess we’ll have to.
The forecast calls for continued rain.
Let’s call it off.
Too bad.
It would’ve made a wonderful memory.
You’ll catch cold, Sis.
What is it, Iori?
Is it something outside?
Amazing!
— I want to be smart. —
Sis… Sis…
It’s no use. She won’t get up.
— Help me become close to Karasuma. —
— Let me lose 6 pounds. —
— I wish they abolish English as a subject, Math too! —
— I wish I can eat a lot of delicious food! —
Let me be a dependable big sister
so that I can watch over Yakumo.
—
Please help Sis to be happy.
Cocklebur barrier…
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
I grew my beard long for Tenma-chan!
But when I woke up, it’d been cut off!
Who did it, anyway?!
Next on School Rumble,
“That’s Gone! This is Gone! Options, Gone!”
That’s Gone!
This is Gone!
Options, Gone!
Rich Girl, was it you?!
Kenji Harima, delivering manuscripts.
The boss, Masa’aki Mitsui.
Yakumo Tsukamoto, working part-time.
Costumes, all kinds.
Koji Yakushamaru, working on a film.
“The Three Slashed!”
Don’t miss
the next
episode!