Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next!
They’re finished!
Now, we’re all set to cheer
at the Athletic Meet.
Yay! Let’s practice!
Rah, rah, C-class!
Eri-chan…
Wow! Akira-chan looks so cute!
Pretty good, Sawachika!
Well, that’s about it.
Oh, my.
His beard!
Don’t scream like that.
Safe!
That sure came off clean.
Why? What have you got against him?!
It was unintentional!
But isn’t this dangerous?
Wasn’t Harima partial to his beard?
Yeah, he talked about
how he took care of it.
Well, I tried to fix it up.
It kinda doesn’t fit.
I mean, it looks creepy because
you can’t tell if he’s asleep or awake.
Should I take it off?
He’s waking up!
How cute!
Safe.
Beard! He’s reaching for his beard!
Awright!!
Safe!
What’s the big idea?!
Wasn’t this your fault
in the first place?
I wouldn’t know, but don’t
guys cherish their beards
as much as girls cherish their hair?
I have a feeling this case
is different, though.
How can I apologize to him?
How about pretending not to know?
Harima looks scary, but he won’t be mad.
He’s waking up again!
What’ll I do? I’m not ready yet!
Any ideas? Any ideas?!
A dream?
Safe!
What’ll we do?
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
That’s Gone!
This is Gone!
Options, Gone!
Pretty Kenji.
Uh-oh, storm’s a-brewing…
Beard fad arrives.
Apologize, anyhow. You did it.
Well, guess I’ll have to.
It’s hard to approach him…
Say, Beard…
I ain’t Beard no more.
What do you mean?
You’ve got a magnificent beard.
It ain’t magnificent no more.
Whaddya want, anyway?
Want? I came to apo—
Scram.
I don’t wanna see your face. Scram.
Hey, wait a minute!
That’s a mean way to treat a girl!
Aren’t you going to let me talk?!
Spare me your sarcastic comments!
Just go! “Get outta here!”
Oh, really?! Fine!
How can a man be so weak?!
I shouldn’t have come
to apologize! See ya!
I thought you came to
make fun of me again!
If you came to apologize, then it’s okay.
Rich Girl, you made a serious mistake.
You know that, right?
Of course, I do.
If there’s anything I can do…
That’s a good offer.
All right, from this moment on…
… you must bow to me.
It’s easy. From today,
you’re my right hand man.
What’s that?
My follower! Follower!
Learn some street talk, why don’tcha?!
So what do I do, specifically?
Well… For starters…
Buy me some tea.
She’s doing it!
Now she’ll probably stop bugging me.
Here.
What’s the idea, you?
“Tea” has got to be Uji Green Tea!
Go to Kyoto for it.
What’re you talking about?!
I can’t do that!
My chin sure feels bare. Wonder why?
How about this high-handed treatment?!
I’ll show her she can’t mess with me!
This is just what that stuck-up Rich Girl needs.
Fine!
It’ll take some time, but be patient.
I’ll have it delivered.
Oh, uh… that’s all right.
Crud! Never underestimate the rich!
And it highlighted my own pitiful
financial circumstances.
Hey, Rich Girl…
What?
I’ve got a hat that might look good on you.
Won’t you put it on for me?
I-It’s fine with me…
It looks great on you!
That’s the best, Rich Girl!
Tenma-chan… Will she be disappointed
that my beard is gone?
I’m scared to see her.
I’m a failure at apologizing.
Beard…
Are you going to keep lying here?
I just wanted to apologize to you.
I’m sorry.
I-It don’t matter!
No use staying mad at you.
Honestly! You’re so stubborn.
Why is that stupid beard
so important to you, anyhow?
It’s better without it… ordinarily.
It don’t matter what you think.
I’m gonna grow it out. Again, see?
Eri-chan!
We came to see how things were going.
I doubt it’s going well, though.
Good grief!
I’m glad you came.
There’s something I want to ask you.
High-school guys with or without beard?
Which is better?
Without.
You see?
Hey, are you listening?
Of course!
Hey, you’re clean-shaven, Harima!
I could fall for you!
S-Spring is here!
That’s right! Clean-shaven is the best look for a man!
Really? You like“clean-shaven” so much?
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Hmm…
Oh, I’m going to erase the beard later.
The story’s interesting,
but doesn’t it seem a little smug?
This development, somehow…
Is that so?
You should have a friend read it.
A “friend,” sir?
Yes. You could really polish it up.
I ain’t got no friends!
I’m a delinquent!
Crud! There’s a limit to
being a loner in school!
Friends… This is a big obstacle for me!
What about Itoko?
No, won’t work. I’d be too embarrassed.
Pyotr and the others?
No, they would never understand this beautiful love story!
Who else?
I can’t show it to them!
Crud…
It’s…
Mangoku!
He’s Koji Yakushamaru, who appears in “The Three Slashed!”
Mangoku! Wait!
Did someone forget this?
Mangoku—Koji Yakushamaru
I met the real actor…
He was even nice enough
to give me his autograph.
Damn, how lucky can I get?!
Let’s see the name…
Uh… um…
Did you see this?
H-Harima-san… Hello… Uh?
I never dreamed Younger Sister
would be working here.
Please! Don’t tell anyone about this.
A-All right.
All right, then.
Uh… um…
So what did you think?
Of my manga, I mean.
That page! Okay, laugh!
Wha—? Nothing! How come?
Uh… um…
No, it’s okay! It’s nothing!
I’ll turn around, okay?
The next page is the
highlight of the story!
Good, a reaction!
The pages are switched.
Page 6 is where Page 9 should be.
That’s crazy!
So what’d you think?
Uh… um… It was interesting.
That’s a lie! I know it!
She can’t fool me!
O-Only… this boy who’s the main character…
There! Finally, her true feelings!
He might be selfish and violent…
No good. It was no good, after all.
I’m just a thug, after all.
I should never forget my place.
Well, never mind.
I’ll just quit this and work hard from tomorrow on.
But… I don’t know
what others might think…
but I like this kind of boy.
And… doesn’t this boy need
someone he can confide in?
Uh… um… I’m sorry!
I shouldn’t have spoken,
when I know nothing about manga!
That’s it!
I can’t be wasting time. Gotta do rewrites.
Sorry, I’m going!
Y-Yes…
Thanks, Younger Sister.
When I’m finished, I’ll bring it back!
I’d like you to read it again, if you could.
Y-Yes.
I wish I could give you
something to thank you.
But this is all I have right now.
You want it?
Mangoku’s autograph!
Where’d you get this?!
It’s a secret.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
We have most of the competitors
for each event in the Athletic Meet.
The perfect lineup,
even if I do say so myself.
But we need people for
the class relay competition.
Five girls and five boys.
This shouldn’t take long.
Okay, who’s fast?!
Who’s good in the 100-meter?
Ume, for sure, probably.
Then there’s Hanai, Asou… Suga?
Akira! You sign up.
On certain conditions… plenty of them.
Never mind.
Oh, yeah, Imadori,
you’re pretty fast, right?
Hey, Imadori!
Hey, wifey! If you enter,
I’m sure Imadori-kun will, too!
Like I care!
I’m in!
Sorry, Miko-chan. I think he heard me.
Geez!
By the way, what about Harima?
He’s not here right now, though.
Imadori, give Harima a call.
Quit ordering me around.
In the first place,
I don’t know his cell number.
Oh, you neither, huh?
Or maybe he doesn’t have a cell phone?
No, he does.
How do you know?
Because I know his number.
Want it?
Not really… Give it to Hanai-kun, will you?
I’d like to, but I just
don’t feel like helping him.
He’s overzealous. It puts me off.
Where the heck is Harima?
I’m gonna find him and
make him participate!
Where the heck is he goofing off, anyway?!
Gee, sorry to call you out here like this…
It’s okay, my classes are over, anyway.
You must’ve been surprised,
though, to get my e-mail.
Oh… yes, that’s true.
So what do you think?
Please give me your honest opinion.
Uh… yes.
The problem is this scene.
See where the hero stops
the heroine at the climax?
Yes.
So Harima’s here, after all.
He’s with somebody?
It’s…
Would a kiss be okay here?
Yes, I think so.
Be quiet!
What’s wrong?
Uh… I thought somebody was there.
I’m sorry.
People might get the wrong idea.
You and me here together…
No, it’s all right with me.
It’s just… I can’t explain it,
but I sensed these strong feelings…
Feelings?
No… never mind.
Hanai never did come back to class.
I hope he didn’t get
into a fight with Harima.
R-Rats?! What the?
I’m going into training
for the Athletic Meet.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
My name is Lala.
As a child, I lived with my father,
a luchador, in Mexico, our homeland.
Note: luchador is Spanish for wrestler
Papa, did you lose again?
Stop drinking, Papa!
We have no more money!
Karen…
Whenever he got drunk,
my father would call out the name of my mother, who’d run off.
My father still loved her.
There was only one thing
that my father did for me…
He taught me everything
he knew about wrestling.
Look, Lala, beyond the sun
is a land called Japone.
It’s a rich land that
has everything, they say.
Let’s work hard and save our money.
And go to Japone together!
When we’re rich,
Mama will surely come back.
Right!
So in order to make my father’s dream
come true, I came to Japone.
To become the best luchador.
Lala!
Lala! What’re you dreaming about?!
It’s time for the match!
Don’t blame me if Ichijou trips you up!
Coach!
Do you think I would ever lose?!
N-No…
I can’t lose… For my father’s sake.
Doowah!
Th-This is a luchador?!
You Japones, making fun of me?
Fine.
One-second kill!
What the heck was that?
That Ichi-jou… she was practically a rookie.
Stop!
A fight?!
That mask… Ichi-jou?!
What’s she doing here?!
Wh-What strength!
Wait!
Where is she?!
Ichi-jou!
Why?! Why didn’t you
fight in earnest today?!
Answer me! With all your power,
why’d you fight like that?!
That’s… well…
You’ll pay!!
She’s gone?!
Ridiculous! How?
Sh-She’s…!
I’m sorry. It was just reflexes.
Who the hell are you?
Uh… I’m called Karen Ichijou.
Karen?
Could God be playing a trick on me?
To hear my mother’s name
in this faraway land…
So I transferred to
the class next to Karen’s.
Ichi-jou! Let’s have lunch!
Right…
Kenji Harima must be punished!
Besides committing many misdeeds,
he even attempted to deceive Yakumo-kun!
Next on School Rumble,
“Hanai Counterattacks!”
Hanai Counterattacks!
Karen Sparkles!
Reunion with Big Sister
With his Iron Hammer of Justice!
And who are you?
At present, his top-ranking friend,
Yakumo Tsukamoto.
Lala Gonzales has lunch with Karen Ichijou.
Jirou Yoshidayama
has been appearing since episode 1.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!