Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next!
Synopsis of the previous episodes
My name is Tenma Tsukamoto.
Today, I’m going to confess to the one I love!
… is the way it was supposed to start, but…
On top of not being able
to confess my love,
Karasuma-kun’s appearances
have decreased!
And in the story, for some reason,
we’ve accepted a challenge from Class D
and we’re entering
the athletic meet episode!
But don’t forget this
is a love-comedy!
… and so, a student’s duty
is both his studies and exercise.
Yagami High School Athletic Meet
Endless
Repetitive
Ladies and Gentlemen,
please keep this in mind.
Endless
Repetitive
Unlike 2-C, oops, I beg your pardon,
Endless
Repetitive
try not to get hurt like a certain class who acts recklessly and irrationally.
Endless
Repetitive
What does he mean by reckless?
Who’s going to get hurt!?
Shut up, Katou.
Next, I present Anegasaki Tae-sensei.
She is the new nurse,
so if anyone gets hurt, please be sure to have her check you out.
Everybody! I’ll be waiting!
I’ll get hurt to my heart’s content!
Wow, everybody’s getting pumped!
I kind of think it’s over the wrong thing.
All men are stupid.
Well, shall we get going?
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Time to Start the War!
Now the Cavalry Battle!
And the Great Uprising!
Sukuran… enters the age of civil war!
The advent of the goddess of military arts.
The advent of this one, too.
And this one… There are too many!
You’re not participating?!
STEERING
COMMITTEE
I can’t leave this position.
I guess if you’re on the steering committee, it can’t be helped.
Tsukamoto-san.
Do your best.
Yeah!
Oh, boy! 2-C and 2-D… A violent
battle from the beginning!
Harry, you’re doing good.
If they don’t hit you,
it’s no big deal.
Hey, everybody! The goal is
to get the balls in the basket!
Those are the hot girls from 2-C.
They’re the best!
Man, I want to join 2-C!
She doesn’t seem to be enjoying herself.
And she looks angry.
Japanese girls all cheer,
so Tougou forced her to do it.
If you don’t want to,
you don’t have to, you know.
Really?!
Infirmary
I can’t stand athletic meets!
Rather, Harima-san, what are
you doing in the infirmary?
Aren’t you usually on the rooftop?
Yeah, every once in a while.
Manuscript
Will you hurry up and disappear, you idiot!
I can’t continue my manuscript.
Manuscript
You can’t fool me.
You’re after Tae-chan, aren’t you?
There you are, Harima-kun!
You’re up next!
Sorry, Tsukamoto. Harima-san has
no time for the athletic meet.
Of course, I have time!
First!
Class C is overwhelming!
Everyone’s doing very well!
Okay, I’m going to do my best, too!
Three-Man Four-Legged Race
Hey, you know, don’t you?
I’m not happy teaming with you,
but I’ll give it everything I’ve got.
She’s really making an effort.
Next is the tug-of-war between
the second year C and D classes.
Neither team will give an inch!
We’re the top of our grade,
our class is terrific!
Huh? Where’s Lala-san?
She said she can’t eat with the enemy.
You actually like it, don’t you?
A one point difference.
The cavalry battle and relay are left.
That will determine the winner!
A thirst for blood?!
Tougou!
I, Haruki Hanai, declare that we…
… shall settle this with the cavalry battle!
He said it first again!
We are getting close to the climax!
The next competition is a tradition
at our school, the cavalry battle!
Three boys and one girl
make one horse team.
What will you do? Do you
want to change after all?
You’re supposed to team with Harima,
aren’t you? It could be a bit awkward.
Well, but, I doubt that it would
affect your performance, though.
It doesn’t matter to me!
In the first place, why should I have
to pay attention to his feelings?!
You’re hopeless…
Very well, each class, mount your horses.
I’m depending on you, Asou!
Right!
Well, then, shall we get it together?
I place my trust in you.
Leave it to us!
Hey! Hurry up and make the horse!
There’s still time.
Eri-chan! Harima-kun! Do your best!
What?
Don’t be so slow, stupid!
What in the world?
We’re going for the win!
Yeah, if we’re going to do it at all.
Let’s go, everybody!
Yeah!
Get them!
Gotcha! Leave it to us, Boss!
Ichi-jou…
Let’s have a look at your skill!
Ready!
If we’re going to do this,
let’s do it seriously!
And win! Got that?
Next is the second year cavalry battle!
Ready…
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
It’s a furious battle from the start!
A grand mêlée!
Got it!
– That was fast!
– Who was that?!
The team of greatest interest in this meet,
Harry and Lala, have made their move!
Attack! Attack!
They are overwhelming!
Is this triple speed?!
Watch for opportunity!
What shall we do?
Should we go after her first?
Leave them alone! We have to
wait until the numbers are smaller.
The others will get in our way!
Okay.
Wow, Ichijou has collected her
seventh headband already!
Come on! Do as I say!
No way, too scary.
Now, the cavalry battle has
come down to the three aces
competing for the most headbands!
Damn! At this rate, it’s a complete victory for Class C and D!
Our class will sink without
seeing the light of day?
No! The small fries have
a small fry’s pride!
We’ll do that!
Yes!
Thank you!
What’s that?
Super-ultra merging of bodies!
Well, what do you know! Second year
Class A has joined all its horses!
It’s practically a pyramid!
The riders are all at the top!
At this rate, they can’t be attacked!
What’s that? Isn’t that against the rules?!
The riders’ feet have not
touched the ground!
It’s not against the rules!
Let’s see, how about it,
steering committee chairman?
They have begun deliberations…
Approved.
It’s okay!
This year’s steering committee
chairman is very liberal!
That’s too liberal!
Get it if you think you can!
The headband is at the highest point!
Oops! One of the girls is
climbing up the pyramid easily!
Again, it is Ichijou!
Kare-rin, you’re so cool!
Don’t be careless! Counterattack!
Hey!
Did you consider what would happen after you left?!
Oh! It’s collapsed!
Good job, Ichijou-kun!
Thank you! Look how
many headbands we have.
That’s from one rider! Ichi-jou!
Ah… yes…
That won’t happen to us!
There’s Class B’s
gluttonous three brothers!
Such weight! The rider is buried among
the bodies and can’t be seen clearly!
They look like an Ashura demon statue.
No, more like a tumbling doll!
Let’s go, Suou!
Oh! Rider Suou resolutely
faces off with them!
Oh? They’re going to challenge that?
Bro! Enemy rider at 8 o’clock!
Eight?
We’re plunging in!
Wasted, wasted… We put on
30 kilos just for today!
How stupid are these guys?
Asou, go for their legs!
Here?
Turn 90 degrees! Head butt
from the right side!
They’re defeated!
Suou’s team of four’s combination moves
destroyed the wall of fat!
We did it, didn’t we?!
Idiot! Stop it!
Hey, Asou, how come you get
all the good parts!
Come on! Don’t just roam
around the perimeter.
We’re going to fight, too!
Too much trouble. Do it yourself.
What?! Are you still holding a grudge?
What are you talking about?
Do you have to ask? Of course, the bald—
You!
You’re such a small man to act
that way over a small thing like that!
You plan to wash over it
by calling it a small thing?!
You have some nerve!
In the first place…!
Oh, no, I mustn’t.
It’ll make things worse…
This baldy is totally incompatible,
and he irritates me no end, but…
But… I have to be the
adult here and give in.
Say, Harima-kun…
Hey!
Do your best, Hario!
I’m watching you!
Ah… yes…
Whoa, so affectionate, Harima-san!
Stupid, it’s nothing like that!
Ah… ah… hey, you, don’t grab that!
Face front!
Right now!
Hey! I’m not resisting—
Now, right!
Picking on a delinquent—
Now, left!
Are you having fun, hag?
Stop it already!
Oh, the cap is about to come off.
I’ll get you back!
They’re arguing. Now’s our chance!
Pincer attack!
Okay.
Don’t bother us!
Come on, run!
Shut up!
What the?!
What in the world happened here?!
Takano! Are you okay?
In the middle of dying in battle.
This is the end of them.
That’s the way it is.
B-Behind you…
It… it’s Class D’s Tennoji!
So… this is the end.
Don’t flinch! It’s just one team! Attack!
Okay!
Three teams with one hand!
What is he?!
This is outrageous!
With the appearance of Tennoji of 2-D,
every class is being annihilated!
Nara-kun, we haven’t fought at all…
If I stay behind a strong team
and last through to the end…
Your plan was brilliant!
I think I’m falling for you,
Nara-kun
Nara engrossed in a delusion
Tsukamoto’s in danger! Help her!
Okay.
Oh, no. I’m not letting you through!
I was getting bored
with all the weaklings!
Damn!
What’s with you?
Mikoto! I’ll take care of things here!
I’m depending on you!
I’m coming, Tenma!
I’m sorry… everybody.
Tenma!
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Tenma!
Nara-kun, are you alright?!
I’m fine… I’m fine…
You bastard! How dare
you attack Tsukamoto!
Hurricane kick doesn’t do anything?!
Rider Sawachika is ineffective!
Tennoji’s team has taken no damage at all!
Don’t give up, Eri-chan, Harima-kun!
Damn! I can’t kick with all my strength
while attached to the team!
Okay! Listen here, Rich Girl!
Do as I tell you!
Rider Sawachika is going around wide!
What do you mean?
Are you really going to try that?!
It’ll be the same no matter
how many times you try!
Can you do it or can’t you?
I’ll do it!
Twin Hurricane Kick!
I, Tennoji, won’t go down alone!
Hey, wait a minute.
If he takes that cap…
I’ll be embarrassed in front of the whole student body.
Hey! Harima-kun! Don’t give up!
And right in front of Tenma-chan.
It’s gone… my campus life full of love.
Sawachika-san!
Rider Sawachika has
fallen off her horse!
They struck each other!
What in the world happened?!
Hey, Rich Girl, are you alright?
It’s your fault we lost,
you bald mule!
Bald Mule
The crowd gives Sawachika a hand.
Thank you, but Harima-kun
and the others worked hard, too!
Ooh! At another place,
Rider Suou is in a pinch!
She’s surrounded by
two of Class D’s aces!
She’s completely open at her back!
Shit!
Banana boy!
Go… Miko-chin!
Imadori…
It’s enough for me… to be
etched in your heart like this.
A man who fought for
your sake… and fell…
Don’t act on your own!
Now!
If it’s one-on-one, I won’t lose!
She got it! Rider Suou
crushed the opposing rider!
Imadori, thank you.
You’re in the way!
Imadori…
Got it.
Can you believe it?! After getting tangled with her own ally,
Rider Suou is out of the
game in disgrace!
At this rate, we’re going to lose!
No… not yet.
Harima-kun…
He is still alive!
It looks like we’re the only ones left.
Focus everybody!
Right!
I was waiting for you, Ichi-jou!
Bring it!
This is tremendous!
Such offense and defense!
Lala-chan’s momentum is awesome.
No, she’s panicking.
She keeps attacking but her
every blow is deflected.
Are you alright, Lala?!
I can still continue!
I don’t want to lose to Ichi-jou!
This is a matter of pride!
Go!
Take this, Ichi-jou!
Rider Ichijou has been blown off!
Class D gets the win!
No! Not yet!
She hasn’t fallen yet!
Rider Ichijou is still alive!
What’s that? It didn’t work?
No… Hanai tossed her up for an instant!
In order to limit the damage to her!
Good job, Hanai!
This is going to be hard.
Hanai can’t fight back with that stance.
Like carrying a sandbag.
A violent attack!
He took a direct hit!
What?!
That won’t work!
What? Hanai repelled the kick!
Abs of steel!
What… what is with this guy?!
It looks like the fruit of the
training is finally showing!
The… old man from the mountain.
It’s been a while, dynamite sexy!
Who are you talking about?!
You know him?
If you want to get her, now is the time!
Hey!
Watch Rider Lala!
She’s running toward Rider Ichijou with tremendous speed!
I came to this country…
… to fight!
This is it! Thor Hammer!
She… disappeared?!
No.
An explosive display of supernatural skill!
Nymph’s Dancer, or Frankensteiner!
Huh? Are… are you alright?
I did it again!
Ichi-jou… You used a pro-wrestling move.
Ichijou-kun, won’t you come
to my dojo next time?
You’d make an interesting opponent.
Hanai-san, not you, too…
Ichijou’s the type that reacts unconsciously the stronger the opponent.
I never thought I’d meet a
natural in this island country.
The ones who won this
violent battle are Class C.
They’ve retained the number one position!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Well, put it behind you.
I can’t do that!
It all started as recreation, but I’ve changed my mind.
I’m going to beat them!
You were really cool, Kare-rin!
Okay, let’s for total domination!
To tell the truth, none of this matters.
I have to go feed Napoleon.
Farewell, my classmates.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Go out for the relay? No way!
Whether this class wins or loses
has nothing to do with me.
Next on School Rumble:
Women’s Battle!
Men’s Battle!
After the Battle…
“Women’s Battle! Men’s Battle!
After the Battle…”
Rich Girl, could it be that cavalry battle?
Rich Girl vs Infirmary Doctor.
Mighty rivals clash.
The composure of an adult.
The obstinacy of a high school coed.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!