Starting at last!
The gurugu mawaru love comedy, School Rumble...
Is starting now!
If you can read this, please install VSFilter or switch to the second subtitle track.
These feelings I want to tell you are so heavy
At this rate, I'll be flattened down
So many feelings I can't describe into words
It just won't reach, to that special person
This short yet very far distance
The sky is always blue,
But you just can't keep staring at it
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
You, who always pretend to be tottering
I just want to jump onto your chest
Round n' round, spinning Round n' Round
Rising softly into the air,
I am drifting above the clouds again today!
Heart Beating New Semester!
Struggles of a Love Letter!
Super-Sonic Bicycles!
Tsukamoto Tenma, sixteen years old.
A little bit silly.
Harima Kenji, a delinquent.
Definitely very silly.
su-ki
"Love"
What a wonderful word!
A magical word that changes the world as soon as it's mentioned...
I will definitely say it... to you.
We're going to be late, Nee-san.
Wait a sec, Yakumo!
Alright! The new semester starts today. I'll do my best!
Sorry to make you wait!
You're slow, Nee-san.
Sorry.
My name is Tsukamoto Tenma. I guess I'm an average 2nd year high school student.
Shouldn't you wake up a little earlier?
And like most other girls my age,
I have also fallen in love.
Hey, Karasuma!
Karasuma Ooji-kun...
Oh no! I just said his name out loud!
Nee-san, it'd be great if you two get to be in the same class.
No problem. We'll be in the same class for sure!
I've been praying for half a year, and the horoscope says my luck is the best today...
The tea stalks stood upright this morning, and I've succeeded in bending a spoon...
Note: Upright tea stalks are a sign of good luck, and note that psychically
bending spoons is Tenma's special power.
And the strap of my wooden clog broke!
Note: "Geta no hanao mo kireta" meaning "a wooden clog strap broke"
is actually a sign of bad luck, but given Tenma's intelligence...
That's dangerous...
Well, I'll go check out my class list.
Good luck and do your best.
su-ki
"Love"
What a wonderful word!
A magical word that changes the world as soon as it's mentioned...
I will definitely say it... to you.
I-I'll get even with you, Harima!
Alright! It's the new school term starting today. I'll do my best!
My name is Harima Kenji.
As you can see, I'm a high school delinquent.
But... there is a person who changed me.
Please let me be in the same class as Karasuma-kun!
Tsukamoto!
Ah, everybody!
Tsukamoto... Tenma-chan...
Hey you, what's with that sloppy...
I want to be in the same class as her!
Huh?
We're all...
In the same class.
Tenma, too.
Really!? Yay!
Eri-chan, Mikoto-chan and Akira-chan!
I'm so happy we're all in the same class!
And...
Hm? Is there something else?
Oh, n-n-nothing!
Look! It's Harima Kenji!
Tenma-chan is in 2-C class...
Why is he here?
Let's get away before he beats us up...
Mind Power! I will gather my concentration in 10 seconds.
I will also be in 2-C!
10...
Be in 2-C... Be in 2-C... Be in 2-C...
9...
8...
7...
Be in 2-C... Be in 2-C... Be in 2-C
6...
5...
4...
Be in 2-C! Be in 2-C!! Be in 2-C!!!
3...
2...
1!
Yo, I've already looked, Harima-san.
You're in 2-D.
Wha-What the hell?
Awesome power, huh? My concentration had nowhere else to go.
Damn it! I'm in 2-D?
Me, Harima Kenji?
HARIMAKKENJI    (Harry McKenzie)
It's a foreigner!!
You tryin' to be funny, punk-ass!?!?
Give me back my concentration!
Sorry for jumping the gun...
Sheesh! You're such a moron. Learn from me.
Ye-Yes!
2-C, huh? I'll find my name in one shot.
It can't be! My name isn't there!
Dammit!  Which class am I in?!
Huh? I can't find my name.
Harima!
What are you doing here?
Aren't you repeating a year?
Now I see...
How did it go, Nee-san?
I-I haven't looked yet.
If you're afraid, I'll take a look for you.
No way! I want to see it with my own eyes, just to be sure.
Karasuma Ooji
He's in the SAME CLASS!
Congratulations!
I'll be in your care for a year, Karasuma-kun!
You're the same class as me.
Yeah.
But I'm going to transfer schools...
...the day after tomorrow.
Just when I got to be in the same class as him!
It was a fleeting dream, wasn't it?
I'll do something about it!
Even when I say that...
I'll do some cleaning to calm down first.
I'll think about it after I do the laundry.
And after I do the dishes.
I haven't thought of anything at all.
Who cares. I'll go sleep!
Am I really ok with this?
To part with him without telling him my feelings...
Rather than regret doing nothing at all, I might as well regret after doing it.
Yes, I should confess my feelings!
All I have to write is
su-ki
"Love".
Well, that's so simple.
Karasuma-kun, I su...su...su...
I'd like to see how you ski!
Argh, what am I writing!?
Karasuma-kun, I su...su...su...
Skip
Calm down, calm down...
Karasuma-kun, I su...
Sukiyaki!! No...
Sukiyaki, a Japanese one-pot dish of beef and vegetables, which is cooked on the table.
Su-Suki ga nai kamae!
A stance without weakness
Su-Sukimani hasamatte!
To be caught off guard
Su-Skill Up!
No, I can't write it... What should I do?
Oh, whatever!
In any case, I'll just write my true feelings now.
In the end... somehow it became a scroll.
Karasuma Ooji
It'll be okay. I did my best.
H-He's reading it.
H-He's still reading it!
Ah, seems like he finished reading it.
Let's see...
Karasuma-kun reacted! Could it be a good impression?
There's no name written on it after all.
Oh, NO!
My first love is over...
K-Karasuma-kun!
Wasn't he supposed to get transferred?
Oh, him? I heard that he postponed his transfer.
He got permission from his parents to stay for another year.
Why? Why?
Well, I'm not sure... but it seems like someone asked him not to.
Please don't go!
Karasuma Ooji of class 2-C,
Tsukamoto Tenma's love interest.
Suddenly, when his transfer to America was discovered,
Tenma, who took the matter seriously, presented (not much of) a love letter to her target.
It became a prolonged battle, but the operation ended in failure.
However, somehow the situation changed for the better and Karasuma postponed his transfer!
Tsukamoto Tenma's battle is just about to begin!
I say... books sure are good. Maybe I'll borrow some...
The Psychology of Love
Having learned from the last time, I should first study more about love.
The Psychology
of Love
Karasuma-kun...
Stupid! Stupid!
Are your feelings for Karasuma-kun that shallow?
I'm not good at reading wordy books.
Ah, this is it!
"Know yourself and know your enemies, and you will win all 100 battles"
Whose essay is this?
Actually, the name is
Sonshi
Sonshi is the correct japanese pronounciation of "Son Zi"
(also known as "Sun Tzu"), the author of "The Art of War".
Sonko? Hmm, I guess it takes a woman to understand a woman's heart.
"Know yourself"...
What kind of a girl am I?
Tsukamoto Tenma, 16 years old.
Height, 154 centimeters.
Weight, 43 kilograms.
Both my looks and figure are normal... I think.
Blood Type:
Birthday:
Zodiac:
Height:
Weight:
B
November 30th
Sagittarius
154 cm
43 kg
I don't particularly stand out in class.
Sports... no good.
Studies... no good.
Cooking... no good.
I'm not good at anything...
But I won't give up.
I'll read something else.
A stripping... rabbit?
Here I go.
That's definitely wrong!
Excuse me, can you tell me what this means?
"Datto" - It means an escaping rabbit.
I see, thank you very much.
It's nothing.
HE... IS... HERE...
When in the world!?
Escaping Rabbit
DATTO
Yes, something like that.
No running along
the corridors!!
I'm sure he thinks I'm weird...
But I talked to Karasuma-kun for the first time.
Suki - Chance
But since I have the chance, I'm gonna make him read this next.
Ka-Karasuma-kun...
H-How do you say this?
Oh that? It's read as "suki".
And you're a high school student? How cute.
I remember there's a farming tool called "suki"...
Karasuma-kun, how do you read this?
Yes, say it!
sen-ba-ko-ki
"Farming Tool"
That's not it...
Well, I have to go home now.
Later, Tsukamoto-san.
Okay, see you, Karasuma-kun.
Sigh...I'm so useless...
Until only a short while ago,
I was but a conceited boy, hopelessly stupid and yet... a god.
Nobody could tie me down.
I belonged only to myself.
Harima, in love
I have fallen in love with Tsukamoto Tenma, the girl who changed me.
Why is Harima here?
And that's my seat over there too...
Could it be that he made a ruckus in the staff room and got himself moved up a year?
Please!! Please!! Please!! Please!!
Somehow I managed to get into the same class as Tenma-chan but...
How should I tell her about my feelings?
Note: It's supposed to be Hatashijou, meaning Letter of Challenge.
The idiot who wrote it used the wrong kanji.
ha-ta-shi bu-shi
"Kneel of Challenge"
Is this some kind of pun? To begin with, who uses a letter nowadays?
No wait! Instead, this will have a great impact!
This is it!
Take this! This is the world's best love letter.
"Meet me at 4pm behind the gym"
Tenma-chan, I wonder if you've already read it...
Harima-kun... well...
I also...
Man! I wish... it's about time!
Tenma-chan! She's already here...
Who the hell!?
Oh right! That "Kneel of Challenge" guy.
He's called Tennouji or something...
He fixed the same place and time?!
Damn it! Now I can't appear even if I wanted to!
Harima... I won't stop at just breaking 2 or 3 ribs.
Hello, miss...
I'm just wondering what you are doing here?
Eh, I'm waiting for someone.
Bastard! Who gave you permission to talk to her? You freaking beast!!
Oh, you have a letter...
Ye-Yes...
Please, let me see it.
Ah! N-No!
Bastard!
Oh, this must be a poem.
WAIT A SE...
"Thank you!" is what I want to say...
First of all, for raising you to be such a cute person, I want to say "Thank you!"
To your father and mother, I want to say "Thank you!"
Hah! What nonsense! What's the point if it's so funny?
Too bad it's anonymous.
I wish I could go out now and beat the crap out of him!
Really?
I may be thickheaded, but I can understand the feelings from this letter.
This is a warm and heartfelt letter, isn't it?
I love it.
I'm the happiest person to be in love with you.
To tell you the truth, I'm the one who wrote this.
I love you...
Huh? What the hell??! You're the one full of nonsense!
Thank you, but...
I love somebody else.
Don't cry! Such things happen.
Ha-Harima...
As if I'd say that to you!!
Asshole, how dare you make fun of my letter! It was my masterpiece!
He's out cold, so Harima
can say whatever he likes.
Time, huh? I need to spend more time with Karasuma-kun.
Besides school, where can I spend more time with him?
Ah, a butterfly...
The chance to spend more time with Tenma-chan will come. I have to make it happen somehow...
Ah! Karasuma-kun!
This must be it!
Good morning, Karasuma-kun!
Good morning, Tsukamoto-san! Today's a fine day, isn't it?
Yup!
Going to school by bicycle with Karasuma-kun...
Yo, Tsukamoto.
Good morning, Harima-kun! Today's a fine day, isn't it?
Oh, yeah!
Going to school by bicycle with Tenma-chan...
It will work!!
Tsukamoto has been acting strange lately.
Because she got into the same class.
Huh?
Well, you'll understand soon.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning, Yakumo-chan.
Huh? Where's Tenma?
Nee-san is going to school by bicycle from today onwards.
I see. I wonder why...
I hope Karasuma-kun comes soon.
Here he is!
Alright, I'll try greeting him naturally.
Karasuma-kun! Good morn...
Fast!
Eh... but that's a normal bicycle, right?
No way... wait for me! Karasuma-kun!!
Going to school by bicycle with Tenma-chan.
Oh, Tenma-chan!
Y-Yo! Tenma-chan... What a coincidence!
Eh? Wha...? What's the meaning of this?
Even if she's on a diet, that's just going way too far!
Wait a sec, Tenma-chan!
Karasuma-kun, wait!
Wait, Tenma-chan!
Karasuma-kun is keeping a cool face. He's so cool and wonderful!
Oh?
No way! Okay... I'm not going to lose!
Tenma-chan!?
But I'm also known as "the man with steel legs".
There's no way I'll back off.
Karasuma-kun!
Tenma-chan!
Kobayashi Tofu Store   [for private use]
Yagami Shrine
Yagami Hill
I sure feel good on days that I do my hair well.
Good morning.
Good morning...
F-Fast!
I can't believe he can go up Shisshin Hill so easily!
Tenma?
M-My hair... is all messed up...
What do you think you're doing!!
What's wrong, Sawachika?
Ah, Mikoto, Akira! You won't believe what just happened!
Tenma was chasing after Karasuma-kun's bicycle.
What do you mean?
That's what I mean.
Oh... I see...
Huh? What? What?
But, I think there's another person chasing after them...
Could it be that Tsukamoto likes Karasuma-kun?
That's what happens when you waste energy going the long way.
Tsukamoto-san, your eraser fell.
Thanks...
She missed out on such a good chance.
I guess that implies what lies ahead.
I love you, Karasuma-kun...
Boys are always, always...
...Chasing after girls.
All day long, always thinking...
...About girls.
But even so, boys are still so silly.
See? They don't understand at all...
...How the girls feel.
Hey there, you silly silly guy.
Shall I reveal it to you, you silly guy?
That's right! The most important thing is this world,
The thing you absolutely cannot take for granted,
I think it's the timing after all, isn't it?
That's right! When you say "I love you"
Or when you're on a date, or no matter what you're doing
Ooh, when you're kissing too
When you say goodbye too, no matter when it is.
That's right! The most important thing in this world is...
I think it's timing, isn't it?
Or is it so?
Oh no! There's a physical examination tomorrow!
I don't want to know mine, but I'm interested in Karasuma-kun's body information!
I wanna know! I wanna know! His personal information!
Next time on School Rumble!
The Test That Can't Be Understood!
The Toilet I Can't Leave!
The Unbelievable Physical Examination!
Uh! I've gained weight!
Sawachika Eri, returned from England.
Suou Mikoto, holds a belt in martial arts.
Takano Akira, her hobby is saving money.
Look forward to the next episode!