Coming up next!
I wonder if you remember that white bench.
Spring in all its glory.
“Spring has come!”
Could this be… Goddess of Spring?
Primavera!
Who can she be?!
Hey, isn’t that Tsukamoto-san of 1-D?
She’s a picture of beauty
even when she naps.
If we did that, it would look like
we were just dozing off.
Right?
Tsu for “tsume no aka” (dirty nails).
Ka for “kanashibari” (bound hand and foot).
Mo for “mogura” (mole).
To for “tokobushi” (abalone).
Tsu-ka-mo-to!
Note: Hanai was talking in “poetic” form, spelling Yakumo’s name with “memorable” phrases that start with each letter of her name. This is a popular teaching method for grade students.
Haruki Hanai, in the spring
of my 2nd year in high school.
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Cleaning The Pool!
Running Around The Pool!
War At The Pool!
Karen Ichijou, hard at work cleaning the pool.
Takeichi Fuyuki, camera guy,
devoting his youth to photography.
Pool cleaning!
Why should our class do it?
Hanai volunteered. He’s our class rep.
Faculty Ofﬁce
So, your class will be cleaning the pool during homeroom, got it?
Yes, sir.
Our class will clean the pool, sir!
But 1-D was assigned to it…
We’ll do it!
Pool cleaning is the dream of our youth!
Pool cleaning is love and passion!
I, Haruki Hanai, have a favorite saying,
“To ignore what is right
shows a lack of courage!”
Well, if you really insist…
He’s always been a workaholic go-getter.
Yeah. You were childhood pals?
I, Haruki Hanai, am a top student
in martial arts and scholarship!
Frugal and courageous!
Childhood pals, huh?
We both trained in martial arts together.
Tsukamoto-kun, in order to
rescue you from this difficulty,
I take on the burden
of everyone’s hatred!
Haruki Hanai has a one-sided
love for Yakumo Tsukamoto?
“Tsukamoto-kun,” he said?!
Yeah, that reminds me, that punk…
Hanai-kun is amazing.
Tenma-chan was impressed with him.
I can’t ignore this.
It’s Karasuma-kun!
Mossy smell.
Could this be his favorite scent?
You gotta be kidding.
I will do… this for… Tsukamoto-kun.
Yes, I’ll always remember us
under the blue sky.
Up there, I can see a swallow.
And there…
Tsukamoto-kun!
Tsukamoto-kun, wake up!
You’re too defenseless!
Aagh… She’s a sound sleeper.
What’ll I do? Let’s see…
I know.
The kiss to awaken you!
Conditioned reflex! I can think
of it as a conditioned reflex!
To be man enough for Tsukamoto-kun!
Didja see that?!
Harima missed that shot from Hanai!
That’s Hanai-kun! An amazing athlete!
I only meant to return
what you lost in haste.
Was it too fast for you?
Interesting.
I better make sure
I don’t lose it again, huh?
No, you don’t!
Wow! They’re locked in a dead heat!
Dead even?!
N-No, look!
My, my. For all his tough-guy act,
Harima-kun’s kind of a wuss.
No, Harima’s athleticism
is better than I expected.
He’s not even into sports,
but he’s keeping up with a student
of the Shorinji Kenpou style.
A martial artist can’t lose
to a thug! This is the end!
Sis?
Oh, Yakumo!
All right!
Rats!
That’s the famous freshman, Yakumo-chan.
Wow, so pretty!
My teacher sent me to see
how things were going.
Is our class so undependable?
Don’t worry, Yakumo Tsukamoto!
That was just an exhibition match!
For entertainment!
Huh? You know Yakumo, Hanai-kun?
This is more than mere play!
A real battle will start now!
To put on a show for the School Festival
with optional-participation Pool Hockey!
Wait a minute!!
I couldn’t decide between giving
a show or setting up a sales booth!
This will help us decide!
I don’t expect any objections!
The influence Yakumo Tsukamoto
has on him is so scary.
The most serious guys
are the most breakable.
That sounds like fun! I’ll participate!
What?! Okay, I’m in, too!
Ohh! Fine!
What an easygoing bunch.
Any other players?
What should we do?
It sounds like fun…
I’ll be watching for now.
Okay! I’ll play for the show!
I’m in.
I’ll do it for the sake of fun.
You’re in, right?
I’m playing for the booth.
Doesn’t matter.
Team for the booth!
Team for the show!
I won’t lose, Akira-chan!
Me, neither.
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Princess Aurora is here.
Princess Aurora pricked
her finger on a spindle
and fell into a hundred-year slumber.
But now, the Princess will be awakened by the kiss of the Prince.
“Sleeping Beauty,” huh?
Right! I’m the Prince!
Tsukamoto-kun will be Princess Aurora!
That’s why we need a show
for the School Festival!
I want a booth!
Want in, Asou?
Geez, everybody bet on Hanai, though.
I’ll go with Harima, then.
Yeah! Way to go, man!
Takano-san’s group always has such style.
They’re the top class
for beauty in my year.
As a girl, I can’t help
feeling a little jealous.
Okay, gang! All together!!
Go!
Go, go, Booth!
Again!
That’s it!
I’ll tell my teacher that the work
is progressing smoothly, Sis.
Yakumo Tsukamoto…
For your sake, I’ll win!
That’s going way overboard.
Announcers’ Desk
The match will now begin.
Wow! He’s gonna be head referee!
With stopwatch and everything!
Karasuma-kun is the head referee?!
I’ve got to make him notice me!
Tsukamoto-san, ge…
“Ge-?”
What “ge”?
Ge…Ge…
Note: “gekokujou” refers to peasants rebelling against their lord.
Gekokujou
“Gekokujo”?!
Game. I’d like to start the game.
Tenma-chan!
Karasuma-kun!
Tsukamoto!
It’s all…
In the name of love!
Yes! Love is a battle!
Game start.
Okay! Judging from
the participants’ shouts,
we can expect a high level
of play in this match!
An opening!
Right down the middle!
Little speed, too! Easy!
No, Harima! That’s a—
A c-curve!
Good, Sawachika-kun!
Excellent move!
That was a superb pass to winger Hanai!
Rats.
Now, a direct hit at goalie Suou!
S-She stopped it!
Owww!
Idiot! Ease up a little, willya?!
That’d only get me hurt.
I know what you can do, Suou.
Do Suou and Hanai know each other?
They both trained Shorinji Kenpou!
They’re both good.
Wow, Suou’s got such passion!
Don’t get lewd ideas, you wolves!
Stupid! It’s not like that!
It’s sheer admiration on his part. As a man!
As a man?
Yay, Suou!
We’re for you, too!
You’re great, Suou! Go for it!
Gee, this is kinda embarrassing.
But by myself, I can’t
hold them off forever.
I’m counting on you, Tsukamoto, Harima!
Here you are, Karasuma-kun.
Thank you. That outfit is becoming.
Here you are, Harima-kun.
Thank you. You look good like that.
Okay! It’s in the bag!
They’re really unraveling…
Even an impregnable
defense won’t win points.
Asou?
Oh, well. Guess I’ll help.
What?!
Harima’s gotta win.
Woah! A sudden entry!
Harima, cover center!
Huh?! Who the hell are you?
Just go!
I ain’t listening to you!
Tsukamoto’s gonna pass to you.
Center, right?! Gotcha!
Tsukamoto!
Right! Got it!
Take this pass and defend it!
Rats!
Great!
Now Harima can take it!
This is Tenma-chan’s pass to me.
This is Tenma-chan’s heart!
Her soul!
So I must pour all my feelings into this.
Flash of…
Love!
Kenji Harima, the man to be called
“Phantom Striker”, was born that moment.
Offside. No goal.
What kind of rule is that?!
No! You can’t argue with the head referee!
Phantom Striker, eh?
Tsukamoto-kun, where did you go?!
But even though you have gone…
I promise you a victory for love!
Eh? You’re still playing?
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
With more participants,
the battle heats to fever pitch!
Cheer against cheer!
Flying drops of sweat!
Man, they’re all embarrassing themselves.
That’s just fine!
Fuyuki, what’re you doing
with a digital camera?
Silly question!
To preserve our gallant figures
for graduation pics!
Get it! Super low angle!
What’re you doing, Fuyuki?
Oh… Nothing…
Damn, I missed it.
But I…
… won’t be discouraged!
I’m blessed as a photographer.
Lucky I’m in this class.
Fuyuki-kun’s really burning with passion.
Yeah. In the wrong direction.
Hold it!
What?
Bastard, you’re taking lewd
pictures again, aren’t you?!
Lewd?! That’s nasty!
In my case, call it “art”! Art!
Cut the bull, shameless fool!
I’m gonna punish you
in the name of justice!
Crap…
Oh, I know! I just took some
pictures of Yakumo-chan.
Wanna buy a set of ten?
You dirty… You’re even selling them?
How much?!
10,000 yen!
Too much!
Oh? It’s her summer uniform. Summer!
You still don’t have this, right?
Hanai-kun’s been buying them, huh?
Yeah. Seems so.
Should you let your fellow martial art
student embarrass himself like that?
Like I care.
Too expensive!
It’s too much for me, right now!
Good subjects are vital, to me!
During this match, I’ll get
the greatest shot of my life!
Gotcha!
Well, you’ve got good taste.
But will you be able to
capture that perfect moment?
I got a great shot of you, Tsukamoto-san!
M-Me?!
B-But I haven’t done anything, at all!
I see things differently from other people.
You’re… in love, right?
Right! That look! That’s fabulous!
Even Suou-san or Takano-san… Fabulous!
Am I being totally ignored here?!
You’re playing, right?
You join the Show side, then.
Uh… umm, but I’ve got zero athletic ability.
That doesn’t matter.
Work it and let the sweat flow!
I don’t want my blood to flow!
Is this enough?
Good work, Ichijou.
Shall we end here and fill the pool?
Yes.
Um… Let me try.
I don’t think you can do it.
Forget it, fool!
Crud! If it comes to this, I’ll just have to brace myself and…
Suou-san!
Cushion my fall with your big boobs!
A creep till the end, eh?!
Stay away!
She did it!
You jerks!
No! This was an act of god!
Magnificent…
W-Wait! Me too?
We couldn’t reach a decision today, but…
Tsukamoto-kun, I swear,
for the School Festival…
We’ll put on “Sleeping Beauty”!
Yakumo-chan’s an underclassman, so she can’t appear in any play of ours.
All right, don’t shove, folks.
Here’re photos of the babes from 2-C!
No more Suous?
There sure are!
Crud. Sawachika is sold out?
Never had any to begin with.
I’m just a passerby.
How much for this Tenma Tsukamoto?
I’ll take Yakumo Tsukamoto, three sets!
Hey, snappy choice, bro!
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Hey, Torimaru! You don’t
have lunch, either?
I’ll treat you! Do you like
curry or meat and potatoes?
Next on School Rumble:
“The First Shopping Trip! The First Box Lunch! The First Heartbreak!” Huh!? Me?
Episode Review.
Ichijou, on the wrestling team.
Wavy hair, Mina Yukino.
Council Chairman, Mai Otsuka.
The commentator was Ganji Nishimoto,
the play-by-play announcer was Ryohei Suga.
And the head referee was Oji Karasuma,
as presented to you.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!