Coming up next!
School Rumble is coming up next!
When you watch TV
Keep the room lighted and don’t sit too close!
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Please, Real Animal Divination!
Please, Tenma!
Please, God!
Big Sister, who Harima is sponging off of.
Tenma and Karasuma, a curry date?
What’s the matter, Suou,
are you sleepy?
It looks like you’re cramming
and studying hard.
Shut up!
See? I told you so.
It’s because your heart’s not in it.
In the first place, why am I
the partner in your practice?
I’ll be fine. This is nothing!
It seems that way…
It’s probably true that
my heart wasn’t in it.
Who would have thought
this pain would get worse…
It’s getting worse and worse.
What if I can’t hold a pencil?
It’s not like me to ask
the gods for help, but…
Please!
I… I want to go to
the same university as him!
I’m not that smart, though…
So, I can’t fail the test tomorrow!
I’m not asking for a good score!
At least let me hold a pencil
until the end of the test…
I can’t believe I’m doing this!
So unlike me!
Doing something like this…
It can’t possibly go the way I hope.
Is somebody here?
It can’t be…
Child, hold out thy hand and thy pencil.
How about that? You can
write with that, can’t you?
Set your mind at ease and go forth to thy school.
Th-Thank you…
Rather,
what are you doing, Harima?
What are you saying? I am
the god living in this area.
Your sincere plea touched me, so I especially—
No, you’re Harima!
Thank you, God!
And come to school already!
School…
Hey, did you hear about
the popular fortune-teller?
Fortune?
Ah, you mean the guy
with the black sunglasses?
The one who has a place
in front of the station?
Yeah, yeah. Have you ever seen him?
No, but… the rumor
is that he never misses.
Yeah, I’d like to give a try, too.
I love fortune telling, too.
But when I’m told something bad, it bothers me.
You can just listen to the good things.
That’s the inviolable
rule of fortune telling.
Oh… Is that so…
What about you, Takano?
Aren’t you interested?
No, not that much.
By the way, don’t you have
to hurry? It’s lunchtime.
Wait, Karasuma-kun!
Rice balls again?
They’re rice balls…
She is making no progress.
But she messed up the curry.
When things go this bad, it’s time
for the rest of us to make it happen.
Make what happen?
You’re going to help out,
aren’t you, Fuyuki-kun?
Yes!
This is some coincidence! We were just
talking about going to a curry restaurant.
when Karasuma-kun and Fuyuki were
already on their way to the restaurant.
It really is a coincidence.
Yeah! It feels like fate!
What’s the matter, Fuyuki-kun?
My stomach is a little…
I’m going to pass today.
Ah, I had to go someplace
on the way home.
Oh, yeah, I was on a diet.
Come to think of it, it was
my great grandmother’s last request
that we not eat curry
on her memorial day…
Sorry, Tsukamoto. See you later!
U-Umm, Karasuma-kun…
Let’s go.
Looks like it went well.
We did it!
Geez, what a troublesome couple.
Say, since we’re together,
why don’t we go for coffee?
If you’re treating.
Yikes.
Okay!
I really do have someplace
to go. Sorry, next time.
Well, shall the rest of us go?
What’s that? A fortune-teller?
It looks like it…
real animal divination
Thank you very much.
Now my company will recover.
real animal divination
No, I just relay what these animals tell me.
Right, guys?
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, I’d like you
to tell me my fortune.
Huh? Have we met somewhere?
I don’t think so. I have a common face,
so it’s probably coincidental.
Probably. I don’t have anyone
so strange in my circle of friends.
N-Never mind that, what did
you want me to forecast?
Well, I guess family fortune would cover it.
Can you forecast something like that?
There is nothing I don’t know.
I overcame great sorrow
and gained enlightenment.
Everything they say is the truth.
The animals do not betray.
Now, ask me anything!
O-Okay, then…
What is my father’s favorite food?
Ribbit
It’s curry.
Do a serious reading!
B-But Alexander the frog is a very good.
Well, whatever. Thank you.
And you, rather than fooling around here, come to school, okay?
School? It all seems like so long ago.
I feel like I’ve washed away
the filth from this world.
Now, I have these animals.
If I saw Tenma-chan now,
I probably wouldn’t be impressed.
Yes… I’ve been reborn!
Oh, look, look, Karasuma-kun!
A fortune-teller!
Calm down! Calm down, you guys!
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
real animal divination
This must be the one that Eri-chan and the others
mentioned whose predictions come true.
Please read my fortune.
Your fortune in l-love?
N-No!
We’re not seeing each other or anything.
I-I see, they’re not dating yet.
No, but since you mentioned it, if you will?
Fortune in love.
Al… right. I’ll read your fortune.
Yay!
Please!
What shall I do…
Maybe I’ll tell her their
compatibility is the worst.
N-No, I mustn’t! I’ve already given up this world.
I’ve decided not to let love bewilder me… But…
Let’s go for curry after this, okay?
After all, you love curry, don’t you?
I’m really looking forward to it.
I want to hurry and have that curry!
Say, which do you like better,
beef and potatoes, or curry?
Curry.
Ah… Umm… Then, which do you
like better, m-m-me or curry?
Curry.
Ah… Umm… Maybe I asked it wrong.
Which do you like better,
prepackaged curry or me?
He hesitated!
Karasuma-kun hesitated choosing between
me and prepackaged curry!
Wait a minute, you!
I won’t forgive you, Nijou…
I mean, Karasuma!
Maybe it’s none of my business, but…
When a woman cries right
in front of me, I can’t let it go!
The Angry Fist! I mean, Kick!
Go after her.
You’re telling me to go after her?
What… What in the world
are you thinking, Karasuma?!
I… can’t go after her.
Curry Shop
Everything Half Price
I understand!
Oh, he fell all the way down!
I wonder if he’s okay.
Wow, he left just like that.
All this time…
All this time… I’ve…
watched you.
Harima-kun.
No good… I… can’t run any further…
Is it all going to end here?
T-Tenma-chan?
C-Could… such a thing happen?
Hear me out!
I’ve… loved you since we first me!
I finally… finally said it!
I wonder if Tsukamoto was
able to be alone with him.
Sorry for all the trouble,
making you help us and all.
It’s okay, it’s okay.
Your set up was magnificent, Takano.
Just let me know and
I’ll help you out, too, Mikoto-san.
I don’t need it!
Who is it that you like, Suou-san?!
Do you know, Takano-san?
Of course!
What?! What are you
talking about, Takano?!
D-Do-Don’t you say anything! Geez!
I’m just joking.
I’m afraid you just might do it!
But you should do whatever you can.
Cowardly love will only mean regrets.
Come to think of it, I’ve never heard
that sort of story about Sawachika-san.
What?
She’s always with some guy or other.
Those are all the guys
who are after her, right?
I’ve never heard of her formally
seeing anyone in particular.
Well, I guess that’s true.
I was just wondering if she’s
ever fallen for a guy herself.
I love you.
Why do you laugh?
That image just seems way off the mark.
I mean, seriously!
In the first place, I can’t imagine
at all, what kind of guy it would be.
Shall we take another way home?
Yeah, good idea.
It’s Harima,
right?
Me?
Such strength.
I’ve never had a confession
of love like this.
What’s going on?
Huh?
He’s not really my type,
but… I should say no…
Oh, no!
I made a mistake!
I can’t tell her…
U-Umm…
Um… I… don’t know what to say…
Hario!
I looked all over for you.
Tonight’s dinner is my special
home-made beef and potatoes.
It’s really good.
Come on, let’s go home.
Wait, Harima-kun.
You said you liked curry!
You’re the lowest!
I don’t know what’s going on anymore.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Wow, it’s really swollen.
What was that girl so mad about?
I don’t know for sure,
but she’s from a very rich family,
so she doesn’t like people like me!
But, thanks to her,
I’ve snapped out of it.
Tomorrow… I’ll confess
my feelings to the one I love.
Then if she turns me down, I’ll quit school.
If it’s over, it’s over.
I’ll settle it once and for all.
Hario…
Love letter and resignation letter.
To Mr. Tani
Is that the only choice you have? Is it?
It’s alright. I entered the
school to be with her.
At this point…
Is that so… Then,
you’ll leave this place, too?
If you like, you can
stay a little longer.
Thank you for taking care
of me up until now.
It was nice having someone
here when I came home.
Thank you.
And keep working on your manga, okay?
After school today, on the rooftop, everything will end.
Tsukamoto
I did what I had to do.
That’s about it, I guess…
What shall I do until school’s out…
She loves me…
She loves me not…
She loves me not!
She loves me!
She loves me! She…
To Mr. Tani
Harima-kun.
I read it.
Finally… Finally, she knows.
What in the world will happen to me?
To you ~ Riding the wind ~
Song, Music, Artist: Kenji Harima
The ﬁrst time I saw you,
you stole my heart, didn’t you?
I saw only you all this time.
It is my ﬁrst confession of love.
The other day, I made a slight mistake,
but please don’t mind.
This is the ﬁrst and last chance!
For my love to ride the wind to you.
I love you.
Knowing my true feelings,
how will you react?
Ha-Harima-kun, umm… you know…
Here!
Your letter of resignation was for some reason in my shoebox.
I made a mistake!
I… I mixed up the contents!
Harima-kun, what’s the matter?
My love is over.
Say, Harima-kun, I don’t like it this way.
Come to school, Harima-kun.
Okay?
Yes.
Faculty Room
Tani-sensei
I found this outside.
From Harima? What could it be?
After all that’s happened,
I’ve come back.
Who are you?
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
I am Kentarou Nara.
I went to the pool with friends
and unexpectedly met up
with Tsukamoto and her friends.
Lucky!
Next time on School Rumble:
Nara!
Karasuma!
Harima!
“Nara! Karasuma! Harima!”
To tell the truth, Tsukamoto, I’ve always…
Kentarou Nara, was originally the main character.
Karasuma and Tenma, meet again in the rain.
Harima, finally returns to school.
Feels like Dostoyevsky.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!