Coming up next!
The school love comedy, School Rumble,
is coming up next.
When watching TV, please keep the lights on and watch from a distance.
A bit of Rumble
A special short anime
Three Part Stand!
Episode 1
Life is tough for the little sister
The Hu Family’s Vermicelli  Soup
Wow! Just smell the aroma of this noodle soup!
This restaurant uses tofu made from
That dish sure looks good, doesn’t it, Yakumo?
soybeans produced in Japan, so it’s healthy.
I’m home!
Oh, Sis, for dinner, I cooked noodle soup.
Amazing! How did you know
what I wanted to eat?
Yakumo couldn’t tell her that
was what they saw on TV last night.
Episode 2
Life is also tough for the big sister
Sis, what are you looking for?
I’m looking for my kappa.
Kappa? A raincoat?
A real kappa.
I want to give it to Karasuma-kun.
Sis…
Oh, here it is! This is it!
It looks awfully old.
It’s a real mummy of a kappa, it says.
Episode 2
Tenma’s Secret
As is natural for all girls,
Tenma fixes her hair every morning.
But depending on the day’s situation,
there are subtle changes in her hairdo.
Oh, Sis, good mor—
’Morning!
9 o’clock?
Correct!
There’s a drama I want to see tonight.
Now I won’t forget!
Fansub
Anıme
Mokkori
KickAss
Present
There’s something I want to tell you, but it’s too heavy
Just like this, it seems I must break
There are too many of these indescribable feelings
I cannot deliver them to you, though you are near, the distance is great
Forever only looking up at the blue sky is no good
Spinning around (spinning around)…
Unsteadily mustering strength, I want to try diving into your heart
Lightly floating, again today I am alone above the clouds
Save Me At the Beach!
Save Me Naked!
Just Save Me! For Real!
Whatever season it is in the world,
it’s mid-summer in School Rumble!
Hanai is a teaching demon.
Harima only thinks of himself.
Akira Takano is reading Twelve Kingdoms.
So is everybody here?!
Yagami Station
Ta-daa!
What do you think? I fixed my special box lunches for each of you!
Here, Takano-kun.
Thank you.
Here, Sawachika-kun.
Thanks.
Here, Tsukamoto-kun.
Wow!
Here, Suou!
Thank you.
Here, Nara, Imadori!
Gee, thanks.
And I made this one with
special care! Yakumo-kun, for you!
Deelish!
This is really good!
Really. Hanai-kun is a good cook.
That’s right. Don’t get depressed just
because Yakumo didn’t come. Okay, Hanai?
I forgot my own lunch.
Harima, give that back!
No, I missed breakfast today!
Gimme… gimme!
How pathetic can he be?
Travelling Dragon
Ohh. Nice!
The rooms are separated by sliding doors.
Urk! Are you serious?!
We’re gonna change. Got that?!
Sure, sure. I wouldn’t open the door, would I? Not me.
C’mon! Let’s change, too!
I’ve got my shorts on underneath.
Let’s see…
Imadori! Your promise!
You don’t expect me
to keep it, do you? Not me.
What’re you doing?! Shame on you!
Your suit looks so adult, Akira-chan!
Isn’t mine pretty daring, too?
Miko-chan’s boobs really
are big, aren’t they?
Your suit’s cute, too, Tsukamoto.
Yes. It’s a different color from Yakumo’s.
Yakumo’s?!
For Yakumo’s sake, I can’t
allow any shameful behavior!
The beach! So many people!
Tsukamoto is so cute.
Crud. Hanai made me miss it…
Yakumo, why didn’t you come?
Tenma, got any sunscreen?
No, I don’t.
I have some. I’ll rub it on.
I’ll get my own.
Hey, where’s Harima?
Still in the room.
He sure lacks socializing skills.
I was so sure I’d brought it with me.
A rugged spirit is calling to my wild side.
Wait for me, Tenma-chan!
But I got no time for foolishness now.
Okay, now… my trunks are?
Swimming trunks, swimming trunks.
Where’d I put them?
KickAss
Anıme
www.kickassanime.org
Wait! Don’t scream!
This is a perfectly innocent situation!
But if she screams, I’ll look like a pervert!
And Tenma-chan will think so, too!
Wh-What do I do?!
Why the hell did I grab her?!
Idiot! It came out all wrong!
She’s struggling like crazy, too!
I gotta explain! That I never
meant for this to happen!
A-Anyhow, first, I gotta calm her down!
How? Uhh…
Got it!
Keep quiet.
I made it even worse!
Now somebody’s coming! It’s all over!
You couldn’t find your swimming trunks,
but you went ahead and stripped anyway.
You still couldn’t find them,
and Eri walked in,
so you panicked and tried to explain,
but ended up pinioning her.
You’re a total screw-up, Harima.
What’s wrong? Did you find the sunscreen?
I didn’t have a chance to.
What? Did something happen?
I don’t want to talk about it.
Let’s split the watermelon!
Miko-chan! Let’s split the watermelon!
Miko-chan! Miko-chan!
Miko-chan’s drowning!
Hanai-kun!
Oh! Hanai-kun took off his glasses!
You thought you’d be forced to swim if you went farther out?
Are you nuts?
But…
You were just like a lifeguard, Hanai-kun!
I’m just used to saving her life.
Shut up!
Just calm down.
Have some hot coffee.
I’m sorry…
You’re lucky you can
swim like that, Hanai-kun.
None of us girls can swim.
Right, Eri-chan?
Shut up, will you?
What?!
Your wish is granted!
All right, let’s go all-out!
Swimming lessons start now!
Why does this always happen?!
Never mind. Let’s just
have him teach us.
Crud.
You’re a good teacher, too, right, Nara?
Eh? I-I am?
Fine! We men will be the teachers!
Now I’m feeling the enthusiasm!
Since Yakumo’s not here, I couldn’t
see any reason to come to the beach!
Oh, I see. By teaching her, I can
start talking to her naturally!
Okay. I’m gonna be the one
to teach Tenma-chan.
So first, I’ll have to…
Yo, Imadori, you like the flashy type,
so you teach the flashy rich girl.
Right!
Yo, Hanai, you seem to be friends
with Suou, so you teach her.
Yo, um… uh…
Nara.
You don’t really stand out,
so teach that quiet girl.
Okay, so draw up a chart.
Me?
You’re hopeless. Okay, I’ll do it.
Let’s see…
I’ll go here.
Hey, everybody!
We’re assigning our partners!
Sure!
Tenma-chan!
Now, let’s start the lessons!
Let’s go, Mikoto-chan!
I’ll be counting on your help.
Could Harima-kun be a complete idiot?
Missed by one line…
Wanna swim?
Over my dead body.
Mokkori
Fansub
www.mokkori.cz
Uh… If you’ll allow me,
I shall teach you.
So, Sawachika-san…
Hello?
F-First, give me your hand…
Uh, your hand…
Your han—
L-Like that. Do you understand?
Vaguely.
C’mon, c’mon…
Hey, how far do we have to go?!
Come on. Let’s go as far as we can.
Please teach me, Nara-kun.
Let’s do our best, Tsukamoto-san.
I’ll use this chance to really get close!
Let’s get started then.
Uh… S-Sure!
Smoosh
This softness…
Japan No. 1
Just forget it.
Listen. This is fair warning.
Just because you’re getting to
teach Ten—, I mean, Tsukamoto,
don’t get any weird desires or hopes up.
And… don’t fall for her!
R-Right. Gotcha.
But I like Tsukamoto, too!
Maybe I can get close to her
before he can complain.
I know! Maybe if I let go,
she might stick even closer to me.
I’m going to let go for a while, now, Tsukamoto-san.
Uh… Sure. All right.
H-Huh?! She’s swimming!
Stop! Stop! That’s enough!
I did it! I can swim!
I owe it all to you, Nara.
It was nothing.
Akira-chan! Aren’t you going swimming?
Hanai-kun’s worn himself out.
Hey! Quit staring, creep!
I’ll squash you, see?
S-Sorry.
It’s hopeless! Nothing’s working.
Harima-kun’s watching me like a hawk.
He really scares me.
Maybe all I can do is watch…
Help! Lost swimsuit!
Tsukamoto! Did it come off?!
I’m scared of Harima-kun, but if
I don’t go, I won’t be a man!
I love Tsukamoto!
Where is it? Tsukamoto’s swimsuit?
I’ll retrieve this swimsuit…
For you!
N-Nara-kun!
H-Here!
Thanks, Nara-kun.
Geeze, Harima-kun!
But wasn’t it lucky that Nara
found your trunks for you?
Wha…!
Where are we?
We’re marooned!
Sob
Well, it can’t be helped now!
We’ll never get home again!
Sob
Will you quit crying, Imadori?!
Anyhow, we can see the shore.
It’s too far away. No one will see us.
Rambling
Before that, we’ll starve to death!
It wouldn’t go that far,
but if this continues,
Rambling
something tragic might happen.
Panic
Don’t say that! I don’t
wanna die, Mikoto-chan!
Panic
I don’t wanna die, either!
And don’t use this as an excuse
to call me “Mikoto-chan”!
Imadori! You can swim, can’t you?
Can’t you swim to the shore somehow?
Th-That’s impossible!
Oh. You mean, stamina-wise?
No…
Things in the ocean. They scare me.
What did you come for?!
Just to hit on girls?!
You can’t swim, either.
If I could I would swim home
and leave you here.
There’s nothing else to do…
Let’s try to think of a way to get
help from the people on the shore.
Gotcha.
Thinking’s what I do best.
I’ll take care of it.
Well…
Smoke
A signal fire would be the best…
No fire, though. Nothing to burn, either.
We’ve got swimsuits!
Whose were you planning to burn?
We’d start with the one
that has two pieces, of course.
We might find something in this cave.
Let’s split up and look.
Okay!
Is that all he can think of,
at a time like this?
Mikoto-chan!
Look, look at this!
What’s this?
It’s a bottle!
I know that. What’s it for?
Look, we always see it on TV.
Put a letter in it and float it out!
BAM
That’ll take years!
Oh, I forgot. No pencil.
We should write in blood.
Forget it already!
Honestly! We can’t be
fooling around like this.
What?! Hey, I’m dead serious!
Now, what to do?
Plan A
Plan A — Make a raft.
But there’s no rope.
Plan A
Plan B
Plan B — Swim with everything we’ve got.
But if we could swim at all,
we wouldn’t be in trouble now.
Blub
Plan B
Plan C
Plan C — A human SOS signal!
S  !
O  !
But we’re short one human.
Plan C
S  !
O  !
Plan D
S  !
O  !
Plan D
S  !
O  !
Plan D
S  !
O  !
Plan D
Hya!
S  !
O  !
Hya!
Plan D
S  !
O  !
Hya!
Plan D
Plan D — Ride on the back of that idiot.
Hya!
D seems like the most practical way,
but I can’t place lmadori in danger all alone.
What’ll I do? I can’t think of anything else.
I-Imadori’s thinking astonishlngly hard?!
A-Any luck? Any good ideas?
I came up with four
possibilities, from A to D.
D.
Did he think of the same idea as me,
and come to the same conclusion?!
He even chose D, the most dangerous plan.
He’s a man.
I’m kind of… impressed.
It’s gotta be D.
You’re a D-cup, for sure!
Isn’t that right, Mikoto-ch—
Pow!
Will you be serious?!
Mikoto sure is cute.
The problem is, how do I suggest to her
that I’ll swim if she gives me a kiss?
Wh-What?
Say, Mikoto-chan, do you like any guy?
Ah… yes, I do.
Better forget the kiss, then.
She seems like the faithful type.
Oh… What’s he like?
Does he go to our school?
Um… He was an upperclassman.
When I was in my 1st year, he was in his 3rd.
He graduated and attends
a school in Tokyo now.
He’s a really smart guy.
I wanna get into the same college, but it’s really tough!
Oh… There’s still hope.
This arrangement won’t last.
What’re you trying to get out of me?!
I already heard.
Anyhow, that’s why I can’t
be wasting my time here!
There’s no need to
change the subject back.
We still haven't figured out
how to get out of here.
You’re right.
But you know… Did you forget?
We’ve got friends we can count on.
I know they’ll find us, for sure!
Before we go back to the inn,
let’s take a picture together!
A group picture?!
I’ll take it.
Come on, everybody!
Here, over here!
Here goes… What do mice like?
Huh?
What is it, Tenma?
I have a feeling that
we’ve forgotten something.
Here goes!
Ready, Akira!
Cheese!
They forgot.
And they’re in
a party mood.
They’re not coming.
Boys are always chasing after girls
All day long they’re thinking of girls
But those boys certainly are a little stupid,
They never seem to understand girls’ feelings
Hey, you really really are a big dummy
Shall I give you a lesson, Big Dummy?
So, the most important thing in the world is…
The thing that absolutely must be…
It’s definitely “timing”, you see?
So, if you wanna say “I love you”,
Go on a date, or do something…
Oh, kiss, or say goodbye, at any time…
Yes, the most important thing in the world is
definitely “timing”, I think, but…
Or something
Miko-chan! Where were you
and lmadori-kun all this time?
And Harima-kun’s in a horrible mood!
Could Miko-chan be the girl
that Harima likes?!
Mission 1: Confession of Love!
Mission 2: Night Offense and Defense!
Mission 3: Tweet!
Next on School Rumble:
Ugh! The subtitle is long!
Beach Trip continued.
The climax of Harima’s life.
And now revealed…
When Hanai was a child.
Don’t miss
the next
episode!