「I have-」
Just a bit more...
Look! I'm done with this part!
I'll be finished over here soon, as well.
An-chan!
Aniki, would you like some juice?
Sure. Thanks.
Senpai.
When you're finished, please rub some tanning oil on me.
Now you've done it!
「I have-」
「Lots of-」
Hurry up, Senpai!
Rub tanning oil on me!
「Friends-」
All right! He rolled over!
Leave it to me!
I cut his tail off!
Hey, he's running away!
Like I'd let him get away!
I'll set some traps!
We did it!
It's pretty nice to play co-op.
Yay!
I'm running low on healing items after that quest.
Could you spare me some?
Sure. Take some.
Kodaka, take mine.
Kodaka wanted mine.
No way.
「I have lots of-」
I'll get some from you next time, Sena.
That's a promise, all right?
Tell me anytime if there's something you want.
Sure thing.
Well, let's go on to the next quest.
One.
Two!
Three!
Four!
I am sure you will find something new tomorrow.
Let's draw a picture of the brightly shining sun.
They're really into it!
Senpai, you're so cool!
You've always been by me, haven't you? Thank you.
You're doing pretty well.
Let's stay together forever,
And draw a picture of a smile,
With a smile on your face.
「I have-」
Draw it like that.
You're amazing, Kodaka-senpai.
Way to go, Aniki.
Here, An-chan.
Let's eat it together.
Onii-chan, you can have mine, too.
Kodaka...
Kodaka.
「I have-」
All right!
I'm out!
You're too good at this, Kodaka.
Way to go, Kodaka.
Sorry.
You really are something amazing, Aniki.
You're great, Onii-chan!
As expected of my An-chan!
I know, right?
It's wonderful being a realfag!
Well, I'm getting hungry. Let's eat, already.
OK. The hot pot is nearly ready.
Why are we having hot pot?
You have to have hot pot at a summer camp, right?
It's just as Anego says.
Yay! It's hot pot!
Hot pot! Hot pot!
「Lots of-」
Senpai! Senpai! Please wake up!
Senpai! Come back!
What was I...
Shiguma
Ri
ka
Shiguma
Ri
ka
Taking a trip all by yourself and having it easy...
That's not fair, Senpai.
I was having a nice hallucination.
What kind of hallucination was it?
For example, Yozora and Sena were getting along and having fun together at the beach during the summer.
What an unscientific scene.
Yeah.
It's getting a bit difficult, isn't it?
Mikazuki   Yozora
Mikazuki Yozora
It would be best if you just give up now, Meat.
Kashiwagi   Sena
Kashiwagi Sena
Shouldn't you be the one giving up? You're panting pretty heavily, you bitch.
S-Spicy!
It's sweet! What is this?!
It's all sticky inside my mouth!
How did it end up like this?
All right. So that we don't mess up when we have a hot pot party with friends,
let's do a hot pot rehearsal.
Well then, shouldn't we do a dark hot pot?
Note: yami-nabe, everyone brings a different ingredient and they turn the lights off and put them all in having no idea what the other ingredients are.
That seems kind of fun.
Sounds good!
I understand.
Why do we need to have a dark hot pot to make friends?
Takayama   Maria
Takayama Maria
Onii-chan... There's a demon coming...
Hasegawa   Kobato
Hasegawa Kobato
An-chan, get out of the way! You can't kill her!
Kusunoki   Yukimura
Kusunoki Yukimura
Maria... Kobato...
Aniki... Aniki... Aniki...
Yukimura...
Searching the database of my memories for what this food most closely resembles...
It's antiseptic.
Rika! You, too?!
Well, then, next!
I know!
No! Don't!
This is a pathetic story where two of the heroines vomit right at the beginning...
A story of our very pathetic everyday lives.
I Don't Have Many Friends
笑顔のまま
egao no mama
With a smile on your face
描いてほら
egaite hora
Draw it like that
ああ、ため息なんかついて凹んじゃう時だって
aa tameiki nanka tsuite hekonjau toki datte
Ah, even when I feel down and sigh
君と話してるだけで
kimi to hanashiteru dake de
Just by talking to you
不思議に元気になる
fushigi ni genki ni naru
I strangely feel better
ほら写真に取ろう
hora, shashin ni torou
Come on, take a picture
思い出のたび
omoide no tabi
Keep it as a memory
はみ出しちゃう気持ちが
hamidashichau kimochi ga
So this bursting emotion
心に焼き付けよう
kokoro ni yakitsukeyou
Will be burned into your heart
いつも君が隣にいてくれたね　ありがとう
itsumo kimi ga tonari ni ite kureta ne arigatou
You've always been by me, haven't you? Thank you
未来へずっと一緒に
mirai e zutto issho ni
Let's stay together forever
笑顔のデッサン描こう
egao no dessan egakou
And draw a picture of a smile
どんな時も
donna toki mo
At all times
笑顔でいよう
egao de iyou
Keep a smile on your face
We must be able to build relationships with those
that are our neighbours, and so
while looking towards the day when we must part,
we work to forge healthy hearts and minds,
and all work in some way to support each other and become
people who can make friends with everyone.
Neighbour Club
We must be able to build relationships with those
that are our neighbours, and so
while looking toward day when we must part,
we work to forge healthy hearts and minds,
and all work in some way to support each other and become
people who can make friends with everyone.
It's the Neighbour Club.
We're recruiting
members!
mada mada zutto gyutto hajiketeru
Keep on pushing them away
angai nanka hamatte jan
It's working strangely well
hitomishiri shiteru kurai ha ji me yo u!
Let's begin getting to know people!
tomodachi tsukuchatte asonjatte yeah!
Make some friends, play around, yeah!
Miss Troublesome
Mikazuki Yozora
Meat
Kashiwagi Sena
Kusunoki Yukimura
Maid
Shiguma Rika
Girl Genius
Takayama Maria
Young Nun
Hasegawa Kobato
Crazy younger sister
Hasegawa Kodaka
Protagonist
kuuru ni miete jitsu wa chou sabishii
Though I look cool, I'm actually extremely lonely
This is a pretty nice song and video.
Yeah. It's not bad.
mousou nara baibaibai shinyuu nara inai nai nai
Bye-bye-bye to delusions, I don't don't don't have any friends
Although I would be able to make it absolutely perfect.
How?
nan no fushizen naku, dakedo tarinai
It doesn't bother me at all, but something's lacking
You don't know, Kodaka? It's simple.
I'd remove Meat from the song and video.
riajuu kara tooi tooi tooi shinyuu nara inai nai nai
I'm far far far from being a realfag, I don't don't don't have any friends
What the hell are you saying, Yozora?
Without me, its worth is zero.
ikemen doushi de atsumattara
If we just gather beautiful people
No, it's negative.
What's negative is your very existence, Meat.
There's no way a goddess like me could be a minus!
ah risou ja dekinai tenkai wo jirai wo funda-
Ah but it's not going ideally, oops, I stepped on a mine
In fact, this song and video should just be of me.
Then it would be perfect.
It would easily jump to the top of the charts.
A piece of meat like you taking the top of the charts is so ridiculous that it isn't even funny.
sowasowa zettai zutto nozokitai
I can't help it, I really want to peek
koukai nanka shitakunai tte
I don't want to regret anything
Keep this in mind and sit in the cold room.
tsumannai kuraiko nante surikicchae furikicchatte
That gloomy girl, just cut her off, shake her off
Why the fridge?
Don't you realise how kind I am being by trying to make your stench go away?
zannen dame shigumi kara angai nanka hamatten jan
It was a worthless plan but somehow it all worked out
There's not a single ounce of kindness in there!
itsudatte dokidoki atte mi tsu ke yo u !
Let's find something that gives us excitement
By the way, where's my part in this song?
Of course you don't have one!
tomodachi tsukuchatte asonjatte yeah!
Make some friends, play around, yeah!
I see.
zettai zettai nozokitai You!
I really really want to peek at you!
suteki chatte furikicchatte Yes!
It's amazing, shake it off, yes!
We must be able to build relationships with those
that are our neighbours, and so
while looking towards the day when we must part,
we work to forge healthy hearts and minds,
and all work in some way to support each other and become
people who can make friends with everyone.
doudai kyoudai sokontoko
How about it, brother, do something!
Meat.
You ended up doing nothing but playing games.
That's not true!