Hello. We meet again.
Ajin Sato is speaking.
Sorry, but I don't have any good news today.
We were cornered.
And that's why I was forced to make a decision.
We are going to use force to give
this country a chance for the fresh start.
So...
It's show time.
Don't let him resurrect!
Too late!
Our plan was
use the opportunity and ensure victory. Right?
This old man isn't human!
He is a monster!
Let everyone watch. We are fighting against humans.
Who are you betting on?
Tosaki-san!
We have found the whereabouts of Nagai Kei.
Sato-san...
You have ruined everything!
Rest till todays autopsy,
specimen 003, Nagai Kei.
Damn you...
Kuro-chan!
Get him! We won't have another chance!
Damn you!
Can't be...
He drastically differs from Hatter or Tanaka.
So, what's next?
Where are we running to?
We're done running. Let's stop Sato.
Well, well. For you to meet me personally.
Kouhai must always show respect to his senpai.
If they already decided on my
punishment then spit it out.
You will be forced to quit ajin research department, senpai.
What did you expect?
First you let the Hatter do as he wishes
and now you let Nagai and Nakano escape.
That's not...
Tosaki-san...
What will happen to me?
Didn't I tell you before?
Hell is awaiting you.
But the situation changed a bit.
They've decided to give you a thread to hang onto.
Let's go.
What has happened?
Hatter has made his second statement.
As of today, I have decided
to start the second wave.
Instead of looking for a compromise
humans chose to oppress demi-humans even more.
So the theme of the second wave will be cleansing.
Thanks to the information that Tanaka-kun
got while being imprisoned,
we've made a list of fifteen people.
If the government doesn't agree to our demands
then we'll kill those people.
He uploaded it to ajin.net
Kishi-sensei... And even minister?!
Hatter has demanded two things.
First was for the government to admit
the experiments on demi-humans.
and to reveal the profit made of those experiments.
And second, to recognize the rights of demi-humans in society.
That's bull! No one is going to accept such demands!
Exactly. That's why you must stop Sato
before he gets to the minister. At any cost.
This is your last chance, senpai.
As I see it, stating demands to humans while hiding inside society
is a cowardly act that should be responded to adequately.
So, you are not going to fulfill the demands that Sato made?
Statements that some kind of researches on demi-humans
are being carried out, do not reflect the reality at all.
The government isn't going to submit
to this kind of demands!
We are going to send forces to quickly
resolve this conflict instead.
These statements were made by the press secretary
of the cabinet at the conference two days ago.
The government is preparing to take extreme measures
after demi-human Sato declared the second wave.
They are also looking for any information that
can help to find him.
Ignore them. Act normally.
It's hard to tell most teens apart.
Most teens my age are acting exactly the same way.
Hey, Nagai! Let's go!
I've never met a bigger idiot...
Got some kind of towel?
We are showing you Sato and other demi-humans.
If you encounter them, then immediately report to police.
Huh?
Wasn't it the guy sitting here?
Then he was...
We better call police!
So, we aren't running away anymore.
What's next? Any ideas?
Sooo?..
I don't feel like doing anything...
Should've stayed with old lady.
Make the decision yourself.
Then let's go straight to Sato!
Are you really a moron?!
Listen, right now we don't stand a chance against them.
Even if we locate his hideout. Then what?
What two teens could possibly do to him?
How are we going to stop him? Trap in the cage?
And what are we going to do with it next?
So, we can't do anything at all?
Nothing. Not yet.
We have only two cards on our hands that we can play.
First is me. I'm smarter than most people.
We don't have tranquilizer guns and we have
no place to contain ajins, so we must improvise.
I once told you that I can leave you disabled
for the rest of your life. Remember that?
You said something like that?
I did!
For example. Not far from the village
there was a dried up well.
Point is, there was no air inside.
Soil bacteria consumed all the oxygen.
And if a human enters space without oxygen,
then he'll immediately lose consciousness.
And ajin will keep losing it forever.
Second card is that we already have
skills most suitable for the battle.
Which one of these three skill would
you like have on the battlefield?
First - strong body.
Second - strategical thinking.
Third one - immortality.
Strong body of course!
Exactly. Anyone would choose immortality.
You have considerably more possibilities to fight with it.
Then let's...
But Sato-san has way more
resources, people and experience than us.
The two of us fighting him?
Don't make me laugh.
So, what are we going to do then?
Lifting?
We'll search for an ally.
And he must be influential enough
to provide us with considerable support.
The hell are you speeding up?!
Aren't we looking for an ally? I have one on my mind!
Then explain it at first!
Come on! Leave it to me!
God damn it, not again...
...not here.
He said that he's going to conceal them!
What a fool you are. There's not a chance
he's going to leave them in the same spot.
Stop calling me a fool!
Well, you are one!
Not only were you driving like crazy, but you also
took us to the former Sato base! That's dangerous!
To hell with danger!
Finally! Took it long enough!
What's with the message?
After I've been found out, I ordered an investigation
at the detective agency to find some information
about demi-human research department.
And they found some quite interesting guy.
Him?!
At the moment searches are also going in other
prefectures, such as Kanagawa, Chiba and Saitama.
We haven't found any leads to Sato yet.
We've also sent guards to the young surgeon
that tops the list as a preventive measure.
Police units have been ordered to be on a stand-by.
Do you understand, Tosaki?
If I'm dead then your miserable life will end as well.
I do.
This is it, Nakano! He's quite an interesting guy!
He's loved one is in coma and he's paying all the expanses.
He certainly can't make this much money at the usual job.
He has a reason to stop Sato
and hang onto this seat.
And even better! His loved one is his weakness!
We'll use it.
What's so funny about it?
Tosaki-san...
The board meeting is about to begin.
Damned demi-humans...
Yu...
Come on, Yu...
Quit smoking tobacco.
That again?
Well, I want to be with you as long as I can.
I will never lose that chance.
Let's go, Shimomura-kun.
Turn on the tv.
Who are you? Where did you get my number?
Just turn on the tv. Faster.
What we are witnessing is the police chasing the stolen car!
Our sources say that demi-human,
Nagai Kei, is in the driver's seat!
Nagai Kei?!
Indeed.
You know where we are heading to, don't you?
Damn battery gone out!
Police asks citizens to free the road to avoid unnecessary accidents.
That's the road to...
Driver and his accomplice are heading toward central Tokyo.
That bastard!
Switch to the headphones and use fake IDs.
I'm going through the back entrance.
Understood.
Criminals are inside the hospital! Am sending the men in.
Cover both main and back entrances!
And who are you?
Glad to be of service!
Wait outside. We are going in by ourselves.
Have you gone mad, Nagai?!
What are you planning to do?!
Explanations later! Hide somewhere!
Where?!
Wherever! If they'll try to take me
by force then stop them with the ghost!
Ghost?! Are you talking about that black monster?
I don't have it!
This is not a funny joke!
I'm dead serious! It scared the hell out
of me when it first appeared, you know.
Anyway, hide! You'll only get in the way!
What?!
Let's go.
What are they trying to achieve?
Could it be revenge?
Or maybe Nagai is somehow
connected to Sato after all.
Isn't it dangerous?
Do you remember what's your job is?
My job...
Is to protect you.
You will have no future if I die.
Fight on! Fight for yourself!
Tension is hanging in the air!
Police surrounded the building and started hospital evacuation,
expecting some kind of terrorist act from demi-humans.
I'd prefer to never see your face again, Tosaki-san.
That's too bad, because we'll be seeing
each other quite often. Through the glass.
Let's not rush thing. All I want is to talk.
Then why not talk outside?
Weather is truly great.
If you try to catch me then I'll summon my ghost.
Without my orders he goes nuts.
He'll give you hell of a time even
if you manage to put me to sleep.
You won't escape easily this time.
And she...
...won't get away as well.
I'm going to kill you.
Wait! Don't shoot!
Nagai! What are you doing this for?!
Don't interfere, Nakano!
What are the orders? To shoot?
Just try to!
Do not open fire!
Have you gone crazy?!
Nagai!
Kill!
Wait!
I don't feel like doing anything...
He...
...is doing the opposite of what I order.
What are you planning to achieve?!
Summer.
Class room is filled with evening sun.
Drops of sweat are leaving traces on the text book.
Life was quite and boring, but stable.
This was never meant to happen. And to you as well.
Yes. It all happened because of you.
You're wrong!
It wasn't us who turned out lives into complete nightmare!
We're in the same boat here.
I came to make a deal.
Like hell I'm going to believe demi-humans word!
Hey, listen! I don't really get all that stuff, but I can say one thing.
We're definitely going to deal with Sato! Whatever it takes!
And for her as well! So please, don't...
We'll become your pawns.
Your immortal soldiers.
Exactly! So...
Wait, what?!
How's the situation?
Suspect captured. We're going to deal with him from now on.
Was it truly Nagai Kei?
No. Just a lookalike.
It came to an end...
Summer vacation.
Look, it's starting.
Hello. Glad to meet you again. Sato is speaking.
As far as I know, government
didn't agree with our demands.
So, I decided to start with...
...the young and perspective surgeon.
Specialist with a great potential.
And with that...
I'm starting the countdown.
As the second wave progresses,
we are going to prepare for the third one.
And third wave will be the last.
I will take over this country.
Perhaps you see my dream as an absurd one?
But I will make it come true.
Without a doubt.
Done from russkie subs special for anon.
Hope someone actually knowing shit picks up the releases.