"As for me—"
Just a little more...
Hey, this side's done!
This portion will be done soon as well.
An-chan!
Aniki,
would you like some juice?
Oh, thanks.
Senpai,
after you're done drinking, would you rub some suntan lotion on Rika?
Jeez, now you've done it!
"As for me—"
"I have—"
Senpai, hurry up and rub some lotion on me!
"a lot of friends—"
All right, it's stunned!
Leave it to me.
I've destroyed the tail section!
Hey, the enemy's gonna get away!
As if I'd let it!
I'll trap it.
Meat
Sena
We did it!
Multiplayer sure is fun.
Yay!
After that quest, I'm running low on healing items...
Could you guys share some with me?
Sure. Here, take some.
Kodaka, take some of mine instead.
Kodaka wanted some of my items.
What? No way.
"As for me, I have—"
I'll take your items next time, Sena.
All right, but that's a promise, okay?
If there's ever anything you want, just tell me.
Yes, yes.
All right, let's move on to the next quest!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four!
Tomorrow will surely be filled with surprises,
so let's go and find them.
The sun shines brilliantly in the sky.
Let's draw a sketch of it.
This is fun!
Senpai, you're so cool!
For always standing next to me, thank you.
You actually aren't that bad.
As we go towards tomorrow,
let's sketch our smiles together.
This smiling moment...
draw it for me, will you?
"As for me—"
Kodaka-senpai, that's amazing!
As expected of Aniki.
Here, An-chan! You should eat it with me!
Onii-chan, you can eat mine as well.
Kodaka...
"As for me—"
All right!
My victory!
Jeez, Kodaka, you're too strong.
That's to be expected of Kodaka.
Sorry, guys.
Aniki's existence truly is magnificent.
Onii-chan, that was amazing!
Just as expected of my An-chan!
Of course, of course!
IRL fulfillment
sure feels good!
Well, I'm getting hungry. Let's have some food soon.
That's a good idea. The hot pot's all ready.
Huh? Why hot pot?
When it comes to summer retreats, hot pots are a must!
It is just as she says.
Yay! Hot pot!
Hot pot, hot pot! Let's eat!
"I have—"
Senpai. Senpai. Please wake up.
Senpai. Please come back!
What am I...
Shikuma Rika
Tried to escape to your own private world, did you?
How unfair, Senpai.
I was having... such lovely hallucinations...
What kind of hallucinations?
For example, Yozora and Sena getting along and playing together at the beach.
Quite the unscientific scenario.
Indeed.
Haven't you started feeling the pain by now?
Mikazuki Yozora
Why don't you surrender for your own sake, Meat?
Kashiwazaki Sena
How about you give up instead?
Your breathing is getting heavier, woman-fox.
S-Spicy!
Sweet! What is this?!
The inside of my mouth is getting sticky!
How did it come to this?
All right,
to make sure we don't embarrass ourselves when we have hot pot parties with friends,
let's have a rehearsal hot pot party.
In that case, wouldn't Mystery Hot Pot fit the situation?
Seems kinda fun.
Sounds like a good idea!
Understood.
Yay!
Why would you have Mystery Hot Pot when trying to make friends?
Mystery Hot Pot!
Takayama Maria
Onii-chan...
the Devil... he cometh...
Hasegawa Kobato
Move away, An-chan...
You can't kill it...
Kusunoki Yukimura
Maria... Kobato...
Aniki... Aniki...
Aniki...
Yukimura.
The closest thing to this foodstuff in Rika's memory database would be...
rubbing alcohol!
Rika! You too?
On to the next one.
I know.
Idiots! Don't do it!
This...
is the story...
a story that starts with both heroines vomiting...
the story of an extremely pathetic everyday life.
I Don't Have Many Friends
egao no mama
笑顔のまま
This smiling moment,
egaite hora
描いてほら
draw it for me, will you?
a tameiki nanka tsuite hekonjau toki datte
あ、ため息　なんか付いて　へこんじゃう時だって
Ah, I let out a sigh - I'm just feeling kind of blue.
kimi to hanashiteru dakede fushigi na genki ni naru
君と話してるだけで 不思議な元気になる
But simply talking with you fills me with a mysterious energy.
hora shashin ni torou omoi de no tabi
ほら、写真に撮ろう　思いでの度
C'mon, let's take a picture, to mark our feelings.
hamidashichau kimochi wa kokoro ni yakitsukeyo
はみ出しちゃう　気持ちは　心に焼き付けよ
We'll burn these overflowing emotions into our hearts.
itsumo kimi ga tonari ni ite kuretade arigatou
いつも君が隣にいてくれたで あいがとう
For always standing next to me, thank you.
mirai e zutto issho ni egao no dessan egakou
未来へずっと一緒に 笑顔のデッサン描こう
As we go towards tomorrow, let's sketch our smiles together.
donna tokimo
どんな時も
No matter when,
egao de iyo
笑顔でいよ
let's stay smiling.
note: the paper is what he says out loud
Regardless, with the goal in mind
of accruing good relationships with those in our vicinity,
we will help and encourage each other
while developing our bodies and minds,
so that we may not infringe upon the trust of others
until we go toward ends of our own.
The Neighbors Club!
Now
recruiting
Still feeling so tight inside I'm about to burst.
まだまだぎゅっとぎゅっとはじけてる
mada mada gyutto gyutto hajiketeru
Actually getting pretty addicted to this.
案外なんかはまってんじゃん
angai nanka hamatten jan
So long as we're avoiding people and not doing anything,
人見知りしてる暇に
hitomishiri shiteru hima ni
let's get started!
は・じ・め・よ・う！
ha ji me yo u!
Make some friends, have some fun, yay!
友達作っちゃって遊んじゃって　イェイ！
tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte yay!
Ms. Trouble
Mikazuki Yozora
Meat
Kashiwazaki Sena
Shikuma Rika
Kusunoki Yukimura
Takayama Maria
Hasegawa Kobato
I Don't Have Many Friends
Hasegawa Kodaka
Main character
I may look normal,
but I'm really super lonely.
普通に見えて　実は超寂しい
futsuu ni miete jitsu wa chou samishii
Man, I'm really liking this song and animation.
Well, it's not bad.
My delusions can say bye bye bye.
妄想ならバイバイバイ
mousou nara bai bai bai
But I have a way to make it even more perfect.
Best friends? Don't have any any any any.
親友ならいないないないない
shinyuu nara inai nai nai nai
What are you gonna do?
I'm free to do anything,
but it's not enough.
なに不自由もなく　だけど足りない
nani fujiyuu mo naku dakedo tarinai
You don't know, Kodaka? It's simple.
Erase Meat from both the visuals and the song.
IRL fulfillment is still far far far.
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
riajuu kara tooi tooi tooi
What are you blabbering on about, Yozora?
Best friends? Don't have any any any any.
親友ならいないないないない
shinyuu nara inai nai nai nai
If I weren't here, this show would be worth nothing!
When all us pathetic people gather together,
残念同士で集まったら
zannen doushi de atsumattara
In fact, it would be worth less than nothing!
What's worth less than nothing is your own existence, Meat.
There's no way a goddess such as me could be worth that.
ah, nobody knows what will happen.
あぁ、予想ができない展開を
ah, yosou ga dekinai tenkai wo
Actually, how about having just me on screen and doing the singing?
Whoops, stepped on a land mine.
地雷を踏んだ
jirai wo funda
That's a guaranteed chart-topper!
A mere piece of Meat shouldn't joke about "chart-topping".
That's right, I have to have to have a look.
そうそう絶対絶対のぞきたい
sou sou zettai zettai nozokitai
I don't want to have any regrets.
後悔なんてしたくないの
koukai nante shitakunai no
Chill off in the cooler and understand your nothingness.
Take that worthless pride and
つまんないプライドなんて
tsumannai puraido nante
Why the refrigerator?
throw it out, shake it off!
捨て切っちゃって　振り切っちゃって
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
Do you not understand my graciousness in preventing you from rotting and stinking?
Looking from a pathetic point of view
残念からしてみたら
zannen kara shite mitara
I'm actually getting pretty addicted to this.
案外なんかはまってんじゃん
angai nanka hamatten jan
However you look at it, that's not being gracious at all!
As we bump heads in confusion
ぶつかって　ドギマギあって
butsukatte dogimagi atte
let's find out!
み・つ・け・よ・う！
mi tsu ke yo u!
Anyway, do I get a part in the song?
Make some friends, have some fun, yay!
友達作っちゃって遊んじゃって　イェイ！
tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte yay!
There's no way in hell you would!
I see...
I have to have to have a look.
絶対絶対のぞきたい
zettai zettai nozokitai
You!
Throw it out, shake it off!
捨て切っちゃって　振り切っちゃって
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
Yes!
Well then, well then, whatcha think of that?
どうだいどうだい　そこんとこ
dou dai dou dai sokon toko
Regardless, with the goal in mind of
accruing good relationships with those in our
vicinity, we will help and encourage each other while
developing our bodies and minds, so that we
may not infringe upon the trust of others until
we go toward ends of our own.
Regardless, with the goal in mind of
accruing good relationships with those in our
vicinity, we will help and encourage each other while
developing our bodies and minds, so that we
may not infringe upon the trust of others until
we go toward ends of our own.
So, Meat, you ended up playing games the whole time.
No, I did not!