Hello? It's me.
Oh, 2D-kun.
What's up?
I heard you're lonely.
Huh?
Ladies Talk
Aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na?
Ne, kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
Sonna koe ga kimi o ima demo kurushimete
Soba de te o kasanetemo
Kono omoi wa kienai kedo
Futari me o awasetara hontou no koto yuenakutemo
Kimi no kotoba, dare yori mo sekai o terashiteru
Tonari de kimi wa "Sayonara wa ai shiteru" tte, sou iu no
Sunao ni narenai
Watashi dake kodoku o utattemo
Egao ni narenai
"Arigato wa koi shiteru" tte sou iu no
Ai no world's end
Yana-san told me on the phone yesterday.
He said you've invited him to hang out several times,
but the timing's never right, and he felt bad turning you down.
Is that why you called me?
Yeah. I thought we could hang out.
You're so nice.
Aren't you busy with work, though?
No, I have the day off.
Don't you have plans to see Kaga-san?
I wouldn't call them plans.
She comes to my place almost every day.
So if you come over, the three of us can hang out.
Should I call Yana-san?
I tried calling him earlier, but he's busy again today.
I see.
That's too bad.
We haven't hung out in ages.
I wish we could at least meet up.
You know, I've been thinking... maybe he found a girlfriend!
What?
You mean like a romantic relationship?
Yeah.
He's been turning down our invitations since summer vacation started.
When I call him, he seems kind of flustered, too.
If you're right, it must be...
Huh?
What are you doing, Kouko?
It sounded like you were on the phone, so I tried to sneak in.
Who were you talking to?
H-hello?
Hello.
Oh, it's you, 2D-kun!
Good morning.
Huh?
Mitsuo has a girlfriend?
Is it Miss Ultrasonic?
You're kidding.
Yeah, we should definitely find out.
Find out?
It's all right.
I'm a professional.
I'm used to stalking Mitsuo.
Wait! What are you...
Now then, Banri...
Yes?
Today's going to be a busy day!
So that's Miss Ultrasonic's place?
Banri, I'm surprised you knew where this was.
I got her address before summer break, so I could send her a summer greeting card.
Is Yana-san really going to come here?
He will if he's seeing Miss Ultrasonic.
Knowing Mitsuo,
he should be devoted enough to walk his girlfriend home after seeing her.
Mitsuo is busy today!
Which means he has plans to go out with Miss Ultrasonic!
Which means we'll catch him in the act if we wait here!
My logic is flawless!
But... isn't it too hot to be stalking someone today?
I'm already kinda bored.
Why don't we go somewhere and get some shaved ice?
That sounds good.
Shaved ice?
We can't do that.
Why not?
Isn't today a perfect day for shaved ice?
It'll make you need to use the bathroom.
Wow...
You really are a pro.
We can't get a good view from here.
Anyway, why is she carrying opera glasses around like it's normal?
Sneak, sneak.
Sneak, sneak, sneak.
Sneak.
That's just how she is.
Eep!
What are you doing here?
Did you come to deliver your summer greeting card in person?
Ah, no, just...
It's summer break, so I thought
I'd drop by to visit unannounced.
What's with that?
You should've called me.
I'm free today. I've been lazing around since this morning.
You're free?
You don't have plans?
You're not seeing anyone?
Not at all.
So I'm glad you came to hang out.
Huh?
Kaga-san?
What is she doing?
Oh, that's... um...
A comedy routine!
Kaga-san.
You! What are you doing here?
This is my house.
What am I doing?
I'm living here, I guess.
That's not what I meant.
We thought you were with Mitsuo.
What?
Me and Yana? Why?
Actually, we thought Yana-san might have a girlfriend.
We thought if he was dating someone, it'd be you, so we came to check it out.
What? No way!
Not a chance!
I haven't seen Yana since summer break started.
Not even once?
Not even once.
Looks like you made a big mistake, 2D-kun.
It's my fault?
You're the one who was so sure
Mitsuo would come here!
And you were the first one who said Mitsuo had a girlfriend.
Well...
Now that you're here, come on in.
Thanks for having us.
Kaga-san.
The moment you step over that threshold,
I'll officially recognize you as my friend.
Wha...
Tell me before I step over it!
If I'd known, I would've willed myself to stop, even if an explosive blast were blowing me in!
Wow, Kaga-chan!
Your shoes are so cute!
If you call me that name in that tone again,
I'll self-destruct, expel my brain from inside my exploded skull, and become an urban legend.
Huh?
They're such idiots.
My room's on the third floor.
You guys go on ahead.
Does Miss Ultrasonic's family actually live here?
Thanks for waiting.
Thanks.
You shouldn't have.
Miss Ultrasonic, are you all right?
Huh?
This place looks abandoned.
We're in the process of moving out.
I'm the last one left.
My dad's moving back home because of work.
My mom decided to go with him.
In other words, they left you here?
We're originally from Fukuoka.
I can't attend school from there.
So, starting next month, I'll be living on my own.
I haven't found an apartment yet, and I'm kind of worried.
I see.
So that's how it is.
Oka-chan... you've been through a lot.
Thank you!
Fukuoka's far away.
I'm jealous, though.
You get to live alone.
I guess.
I wanted to try living alone,
but now that I'm doing it, I'm full of anxiety and fear.
Do you know where you're going to live?
Not at all.
I need to find a place soon, and I want to save money, too.
I was supposed to take the Okamera on a trip,
but this killed my plans.
I see.
That's sad.
The beach.
Huh?
Let's go.
You said you wanted to go, right?
Let's go with Oka-chan.
I'll bring a car.
You're right!
Let's do it! All of us together.
Miss Ultrasonic, do you have a swimsuit?
We're going to the beach.
M-my swimsuit should be around here somewhere.
When are we going?
I'll make proper plans.
Okay!
I'll invite Yana-san, and we'll all go together!
It's summer, after all!
Summer only comes once a year!
I think I'm hungry.
Let's go get something to eat, then.
I'll show you where the film club gets food.
There's a place that's cheap, but has good fried chicken.
I go there with the film club all the time.
Yeah, but we didn't have to come so close to the university for it, did we?
Now, now.
This'll be one of our summer memories.
We might run into someone from the film club.
There it is. It's already open...
And their fried chicken is great!
Yeah?
That was Yana and...
...Linda-senpai from the festival club, right?
What are those two doing together?
Huh? What?
Is Yana's girlfriend...
I thought Yana-san had unrequited feelings for Oka-chan.
Wh-what should we do?
Should we go to the same place?
Let's not.
I'm sure they have some reason.
Let's leave them alone for now.
I agree with Miss Ultrasonic.
Let's just...
...quietly watch over Mitsuo.
Yes?
Um, why are you dressed like that?
I'm engaging in espionage.
This is how I dress for stealth.
I think it makes you stand out even more.
Anyway, you'd better not tell anyone I came here today.
Why not?
Isn't it obvious?
I don't want anyone to think you and I are friends.
You're so shy.
Shy?!
As long as you're here, let's try to get along.
No! Way!
Oh, I have this.
Huh...
Anyway...
Did you figure anything out about
Yana and Linda-senpai after that?
Nothing.
I haven't even seen them since then.
Why? Is it bothering you?
Not really, but...
Wait, this isn't the time for chit-chat.
We have an important mission today.
That's why I'm here.
Well?
This is my first choice.
S-sure, why not?
But, who shows up at someone's house and immediately strips?
I told you we'd be choosing swimsuits today.
Well?
Think this'll charm Banri?
You want to charm Banri?
That's right.
I want to use the perfect swimsuit to make him fall completely in love.
I think he's already in love with you.
He's not!
I don't have nearly enough charm!
I feel like he's not even half-charmed yet!
What?
Why?
I just do.
That's why you have to take this seriously.
I brought all the swimsuits I had at home.
What?
Why do I have to change into a swimsuit?
Because I don't want us to match.
If we do, you'll have to change.
Oh, this suddenly became a lot of work.
Have you changed?
Yeah.
Here we go.
Ready, and... go!
Weird!
It looks weird, Kaga-san!
It's too erotic!
I was going for a healthy look.
Sort of a Latin American island style...
No, no, no. We're in Japan.
Turn around.
A thong!
There's no way you can pull that off!
I thought it was cute.
I'm glad you decided to show me before we went.
I stopped you before you had an accident that would remain in everyone's memory.
You're one to talk.
You're having quite the accident yourself.
What? You're kidding.
What is that?
What is it?
A swimsuit.
You look like a clay pipe.
What were you thinking when you put that on?
I thought it was cute.
Why?!
I don't like to dress too girly.
This even looks like something you'd wear around the house.
Right?
Dress girly?
You're dressing like a pipe.
But I think the designer was going for
a French enfant look.
enfant = child
No. We're in Japan.
Right.
We're in Japan.
Next!
I really don't think you have anything to worry about.
What are you talking about?
Banri's in love with you.
It's plain as day.
I feel like... Banri's afraid to try to get anything out of me.
Have you not even kissed yet?
We kiss!
Sometimes...
I see.
Are you sure you're not putting pressure on Banri?
What does Banri have to do to satisfy you?
I want him to know I love him...
So you're saying, "Get your freak on."
"Follow your sexual desires and attack me like a wild beast."
"Come on."
Is that it?
Wh-what's gotten into you?
Do you think you can say whatever you want if you use that voice?
Huh?
In that case... put politely, you're saying, "Make love to me," right?
You're terrifying!
That's not what I meant!
I just...
I'm actually pretty hurt.
What's wrong?
The other day...
Kaga-san, your boobs.
Huh? Oh!
So, what happened?
I went to Banri's apartment.
On the way home, the mood seemed right,
so I went for a kiss...
And then?
He seemed troubled and didn't do it.
It's like wrestling alone.
I managed to smooth things over, but I'm a mess on the inside.
How were things going at his place before that?
Well, I made air yakisoba...
Air yakisoba?
No, I mean...
I made Banri happy by cooking for him.
We relaxed enveloped in the smell of yakisoba.
Do you never feel in the mood while spending hours in your boyfriend's apartment?
That's the problem.
I don't at all.
I feel like I understand how Banri feels, though.
Really?
How do you feel?
That's just it.
It's that desperate face.
If you throw yourself at him like that,
you'll make him feel like a demon accepting a sacrificial virgin.
He's hesitating because he wants to show that he really cares for you.
What am I supposed to do, then?
I know he cares about me.
But it's like Banri thinks of me as a doll or something.
You're in quite a bind, huh?
This year, I have plans to go to Barcelona on my annual family vacation.
Uh huh.
But, secretly... I want to create a situation that will let me stay in Tokyo with Banri, at his place.
I see.
The beach is a prelude.
I want him to know I'm serious about our relationship.
Yeah.
I always feel uncertain.
Does Banri really love me?
Will Banri suddenly disappear one day?
Where is Banri, really?
What?
Is Banri still searching for himself?
What if he finds himself?
Is he going to leave me if he does?
Kaga-san?
Oh, come on!
I don't care about swimsuits!
I'm talking about what's inside!
About my feelings!
About fate!
That's what I'm talking about!
I'm going to wear the next one I grab.
I'll loan you the one I grab after that.
That'll settle it!
What the heck?!
My swimsuit is...
This one!
And your swimsuit is...
Why do you have two school swimsuits?
That one's from middle school, and this one's from high school.
They're not bad, though.
This might actually be kind of interesting.
What?
Really?
Yeah, really.
This calls for the Okamera.
I can't do it!
This can't possibly be right!
No, no. Some people will like it.
I want to charm Banri, not "people"!
This might inspire a new fetish in Banri.
That's not what I want!
Come on.
Say something.
Sheesh!
Ahem.
I'm Kaga Kouko.
Miss Ultrasonic talked me into wearing this.
I'm Oka Chinami.
Are you watching, Future Me?
Come on, Kaga-san.
I'm K-Kaga Kouko.
Are you watching, Banri?
I love you very much!
I'll love you today, tomorrow, and the day after.
I'll love you forever!
We're going to the beach soon.
We're going to have fun and make memories that will last a lifetime.
Right, Kaga-san?
Don't make that face!
You have two choices.
Choose whichever you prefer.
This is the innocent pair I bought in my third year of middle school.
This is the toxic pair the president gave me after the party the other day.
Did you think there was any chance
I'd choose the toxic pair?
I thought you might.
You seem like you might actually wear them.
I wish I could've invited Linda-senpai.
She said she's back home right now, so I didn't bother.
Really?
I wonder where Linda-senpai's from.
Dunno.
Chigau yo mou, chigau tteba
Aa, mada kizukanai no ne?
Ni san jikan mo mae kara sono ude ni furetai noni
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
Sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru noni
Doushite doushite chittomo aa satotte kurenai no?
Ne hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru?
Kosabayui kotoba wa iranai
Han eikyuuteki ni ai shite yo
Gosen-nen go nado kyoumi wa nai
Watashi endless de wa nai no
Itsuka wa shinu no yo
"Eien ni ai shiteru yo" nante yuwaretemo ureshikunai
Mazu wa watashi o shinu made
Ai suru koto dake o kangaete
Accident Beach
Summer vacation!
Yeah!
Yes!
Summer vacation!
Hey!
Yay!
Speaking of summer vacation...
Shaved ice!
The beach!
Charming Banri! The Eiffel Tower!
That's...
What are you talking about?