Ahem!
Y'all want Sensei ta hurry on back, right?!
Yes!
Well then, to welcome him back nice an' proper...
...let's get this place sparklin' clean!
Yeah!
Most of the mess here is because of Miwa-chan.
Kids? Don't let her fool you.
Now then, get busy and start workin' for Sensei!
Yeah!
I wonder when Sensei's gonna be back...
I wonder when...
Sensei!
Hurry on home!
"Should not go to the island"
That's...
Mother...?
What's this about...?
As you can see...
...it's my silent protest against your going to the island.
Silent?!
I already submitted my work to the exhibit, so I was thinking of going home to the island...
Going home?!
This is your home!
You're just a visitor on the island, you ungrateful kid!
Mother! Stop...!
No, I won't stop!
"I Won't Stop Until You
Say You Won't Go" Punch!!
Let's talk first! The punches just plain hurt...
What are you two doing?
Kawafuji-kun is with us.
What? Kawafuji-kun?
Kawafuji! You came at the right time!
I came to say that your work was safely submitted, but...
Sorry to bother you.
Of course it's not a bother!
Ah!
Let's go out and grab a bite!
Sei-san? Are you trying to run?!
There's no way I can let this go!
Let's all think together on this!
Help me convince him, Kawafuji-kun!
I was against it from the very beginning.
I couldn't do anything back then because the man next to me just went ahead with it.
From what I heard, it seems like you got sick and were even hospitalized.
I kept an eye on your cat allergies while you were here too.
Well...
Even if I told you not to go, you'd go anyways, right?
If so, then I'm not going to listen to your opinions!
I'll stop you, even if it means confining you!
Your mom is quite something...
So, finally resorting to force...
Well, what your mom is saying makes sense. Just give up.
Huh?! I thought you were on my side!
Now that I know you can write calligraphy in Tokyo...
...I'd rather have you work yourself silly than lie around on the island.
"The Opposition"
Is this the system?
Sure, a "remote island" sounds like a place so rural that there's no electricity...
But...!
That just means it's away from the mainland;
I can get everything I need to live there!
I was always the reclusive type, so I can get by well enough!
I don't have many friends here...
I'm happy enough writing calligraphy...
Wow... This is just depressing...
Do you think the location is all that worries me?!
What?
You've... been hanging around weird people, right?
Your attitude and speech have changed for the worse!
You weren't like that before...!
Am I that bad now?
Well, not so much bad. More like weird...
Bad company ruins good morals!
Use judgment in who you associate with!
Bad company ruins...?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What do you mean, "no"?!
You've been acting strange ever since you returned!
You keep eating pickles for some reason...
...and say strange things like "komonno" and "nusano"!
I didn't say that!
I'm not being influenced at all!
I think you are.
Sei-san never used to raise his voice like that!
If it's a matter of location and people,
I don't see any problems at all.
"The Supporters"
Dad's going to go with this system too?
I used to live on the island back when I was Seishu's age.
Nothing is wrong with the environment.
Huh? You lived on the island too, Dad?
I wouldn't have forced you to go there if I hadn't gone there myself.
Kido Yujiro's been taking care of you, right?
Kido...?
Village Leader!
Right.
I'm sure I had some photos in one of my old albums.
Oh, no! There's no way I'll let you show something that will help your cause!
This is just a walk down memory lane.
Pooh...
Wow...
I didn't know you kept such old photos.
Seimei-sensei, you look just like Handa.
My eyes aren't as harsh as his.
Here. It's a photo of me when I was on the island.
What?!
Whoa... Village Leader's so young!
I believe this was 35 years ago.
It was when I went fishing for hisanio with Kido.
Hisanio!
There! "Nusano"!
We caught a hisanio too, right?
Well, more like...
Hey!
Is this Kinoshita Shoten?!
Yes, I believe that was the name.
Is that the owner?!
So young! She was good-looking!
Hey! This river is still there too!
I got hurt there once.
Me too! I still have the scar here...
I've had enough!
You all are only thinking of going to the island!
No one understands my feelings!
Can't you tell I'm really worried?!
You're too irresponsible, Da-chan!
Can't you see our precious son is heading down the path of destruction?!
Da-chan...?
Now calm down.
If separation can help a child mature, that is for the best.
Aren't you on my side, Da-chan?!
"Mommy" "Mommy" "Mommy"
You're tossing aside your mother, who was there for you through all your sick days?
Impiety, as vast as the mountains!
Your mom is really a pain...
That's how you folks disrespect mothers!
She heard me?!
Undutiful, as quick as the winds!
You all don't know anything!
Wait! Missus! Ow! Ouch!
I'm sorry, Kawafuji-kun...
At this rate, I probably can't return for a while.
Seishu.
I was the one who told you to go to the island, but...
...the rest is up to you.
If you were able to write the calligraphy you wanted to write, you can always come back.
It's your call from here on.
Sei-san is such a meanie!
I keep wishing only for the best!
The calligraphy for the exhibit is done, and I think I know my way now.
Maybe there's no need for me to rush back to the island.
If you're gonna be reclusive no matter where,
I think it's more convenient to stay in Tokyo.
No matter how much I think,
Tokyo is still better...
Then why am I this troubled...?
Sei-san?
This parcel just arrived.
It looks like it's from the island residents.
Wait! Could it be?!
Your belongings, meaning to never come back?!
No, they wouldn't do a thing like that.
I asked them to send me
some documents I needed back when I was under the pressure of the exhibit.
What the heck?
Those kids...
They just threw in anything they could...
Teasing...
My son is being teased...!
That's not it!
This must be from Naru.
Who?! Who is Naru?!
She's a kid!
"To Sensei
I got a gold award. Next up
is the prefecture's exhibit.
Tama"
This...
"I got a silver award
Curse Tama"
They sent these too?
Sei-san...? What is that?
It's calligraphy written by the kids I'm teaching.
What?
"Visiting Old, Learning New
Yamamura Miwa, second year, class one"
Pretty good for only starting recently.
If the assignment results were going to come in so soon, I should have left after that.
"Visiting Old, Learning New"
I should have been with them for their results...
To congratulate and encourage them...
Sei-san...
"Should not go to the island"
Do what you please already!
Mother! Are you pouting again?
I'm not pouting!
If someone needs you...
...then you have to go back.
Mother...
But from now on, make sure you call us!
So... does that mean I can go?
I guess...
Are you okay with that?
Yes...
He was thinking of wanting to do something for others.
Any more from me, and it would have just been me being selfish.
I guess it wasn't only his calligraphy that matured.
That island is a wonderful place.
Let's go there before the cold settles in, shall we?
Yes.
Ahem. Now...
We just received word from the village phone keeper, Akki...
Sensei's gonna be coming home on a plane arriving this evening!
Yay!
So!
Let's get this place sparklin' clean for sure this time!
Yeah!
Sensei is going to get really angry if we don't clean up, so let's do our best!
So heavy...
Gotta hand it to Sensei, coming back to the island just as suddenly as he left...
They better be cleaning up the place.
"click-click-click"
I can't believe how much time we've wasted...
Hey.
Hiro-nii! When did you--?!
What's this?
Don't ask!
Now that we've settled down, we know it was a stupid waste of time.
Please don't hurt us any more!
"Duel!!"
I knew you gals couldn't pull this off by yourselves.
Ya didn't even clean the place up one bit!
--Whoops!
--Don't give me "whoops!"
Why'd you come, Hiro-nii?
It's only gonna get colder, so I figured I'd set the window slides up for the house.
Come to think of it, Sensei's place ain't got them window slides.
The glass broke in the hurricane, so I took 'em off and stored 'em at my place.
Well, I'll give the instructions, so you go and get the place cleaned up.
Aww...
Sensei's gonna be back, so we better hurry.
"(keep) flammable" "(discard) nonflammable"
Separate the trash!
Kenta! Use the broom and sweep the place clean!
Yeah!
You two wipe 'em clean!
It's a lot cleaner than before, Hiro-nii.
You gals clean too! Don't leave a single speck!
C'mon, relax a bit.
Everything is for Sensei.
For Sensei. For Sensei.
--For Sensei!
For Sensei!
For Sensei...!
Clean up...
Complete!
So clean!
Now we can dirty the place up all we want!
That almost sounds like you'd do it...
All we gotta do is wait for
Sensei to come back now!
I can't wait!
Neither can Naru!
Let's go home and bring back some snacks.
Hiro-nii, can you go and cook something for us?
You serious about dirtying up the place again?!
I'm back...
Village Leader was supposed to pick me up, but...
If I start walking, I'm sure I'll see him shortly.
"Evaluation Room"
Seishu-kun's calligraphy should be up shortly.
Yes. I haven't seen it, so I'm looking forward to it.
Kanzaki-kun's calligraphy was wonderful too.
It seems like it's going to be a duel between those two young ones.
I only wish that my son sees not just the results, but what lies beyond them.
I believe Seishu-kun is acting with a clear vision towards the future.
He's experienced more than his fair share of pain.
I'm sure his impulsive actions will fade away.
His impulsive actions will fade away...?
I can only hope so...
Village Leader... Not yet...
A vending machine!
"impulsive"
"pain"
Hurry... My wallet...
Wha--?!
Money...!
"pain"
Money... Money... Tea... Tea...
Ah...
"Hot-n-Lumpy Corn"
"warm"
"pain"
Isn't it too early to stock winter drinks...?
That's...
Hey! Sensei! Whatcha doin' 'round here?
Did you come to pick me up by any chance?
Nah! Just takin' a drive!
Where is Village Leader?
Sensei?
Wanna hitch a ride?
Come to think of it, this is just like when I first came.
That means...
The weather today is beautiful, so it looks gorgeous.
It's nothin' special. 'Bout like normal.
Normal...
Normal... is the best.
"A call from Kawafuji-san came in"
Hello! Kinoshita Shoten.
Ah, Kawafuji-san.
I believe Sensei is back already.
--Village Leader went to...
--Sensei, 'round here okay?
What?! I can't hear you!
--'Round here okay?!
--Please wait a moment.
--Huh?!
--Eh?!
Sensei!
When Sensei opens the door, we're gonna pop these!
Naru's gonna tackle him!
Yeah! You do that!
Here already?!
Oh, it's just you, Aki.
What do you mean by that?
Where's Sensei?
He's on the phone with
Kawafuji-san at the store.
Seems like the exhibit results are finalized.
Huh? That's quick.
Not good.
Right... If it's second place, he'll be down again.
C'mon, Sensei's an adult.
He won't say anything that'll make things worse.
Are you kidding, Hiro-nii?!
Don't underestimate
Sensei's childlike behavior!
Don't mess with the feelin' of getting second place!
Sensei's back, everyone!
--What?!
--Huh? Where's my popper?
You had it with you!
Hey! Where's mine?!
Who got mine?!
Found 'em!
I'm home...
That wasn't funny...
Ouch...
Sensei, you all right?
After being away this long, this is what I get?
Sensei!
Your hands... are kind of sticky...
Looks like he's in a good mood...
Should be okay, then.
Say, Sensei?
How was the calligraphy contest?
Did ya get first place?
Naru?
I told ya not to say that.
This is a delicate issue, you know?
Ya don't say...
Sensei? Don't worry 'bout what she said.
Are you girls... worried about the exhibit results?
Huh? Ya got good results?
Well, yeah...
--Yay!
--I'm so happy!
--Good for you!
Come on, cheer up.
The elder group was too good this time around.
"Results
5th Handa Sei (Seishu)
7th Kanzaki Kosuke"
Neither of you were even close to getting an award.
Bet they didn't want any youngsters having it their way.
But you could say this is how things should be.
You came, Kawafuji-kun?
Oh, Sensei!
You let Seishu know the results?
Yes, it seems like he wanted to know, so...
Do you think the results will disappoint him?
Well... Who knows?
But that is his first step towards writing his own calligraphy.
It'll be interesting from here on.
Cheers!
So, what kind of calligraphy did ya write, Sensei?
Yeah, I want to know too.
The subject isn't that amazing.
C'mon, don't hold back. It was good, right?
Not like it's gonna hurt anyone, ya know?
Right?
If you insist...
It's what I think is most important to me now.
"Arai Tamako" "Kotoishi Naru"
"Kido Hiroshi" "Yamamura Miwa" "Kubota Hina"
Important to you...?
--Could it be, Hiro-nii...?!
--Must be the calligraphy we wrote!
"Kotoishi Naru"
No.
You girls are so shallow.
People are what they eat!
"Kido Hiroshi" "Yamamura Miwa" "Kubota Hina"
Nothing to do with food.
Then... maybe a rabbit?
What are you talking about, Hina?
I thought it was a beetle!
I thought a praying mantis!
Then I say a scorpion!
Everyone, stop bothering Sensei.
Aki, you're acting like a pet again.
That's not true.
You're actin' too cool, Aki.
Oh, well...
Sensei?
Whatever happens...
...it's always fun bein' with everyone.
Looking at you kids having fun freely is... influencing me too.
Influencing...?
It just means this time now is what's important.
Understand?
Not really.
"Happy Yer Home"
"By Naru"
"Illustration by Tachibana Masaki"
Ready...
Thank you very much!
Yay!