Linda-senpai.
Huh?
Do you want to go back?
To that place where I used to be.
I...
I want to go back!
What did I just say?
Wow, you just fell asleep for a second...
Fell asleep?
Looks like you should get to bed.
Lack of sleep isn't good for you.
You'll become oversensitive and think things you shouldn't.
Good night, Tada Banri.
I still love Linda.
With You Again
If I can, I want to be with Linda forever.
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even it it's the long way around
Ah! Kaga-san, wait.
Banri, Kaga-san and I are leaving now.
Okay.
Thanks for waiting.
Kaga-san, you don't look well.
Really?
What? Kaga-san's sick?
Yeah.
She wanted me to tell you she didn't think she could make it to class today.
I see.
Well, I've got class.
Sure, thanks.
No subject
How's your cold?
Sending
Message
In our discussion of natural law,
Kaga-san didn't come to class for a while after that.
we cannot ignore the existence of an Englishman named Jeremy Bentham...
According to her texts,
her condition worsened, and she felt terrible.
How's
your cold?
Sending
Message
I didn't get to see Kaga-san over the weekend, either.
Then, on Monday...
Tada-kun!
Kaga-san!
Good morning, Tada-kun.
I'm sorry I couldn't go meet you today.
That's fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
You still look a little sick.
I can't stay home forever.
We have practice with the festival club today.
Kaga-san, you really shouldn't force yourself...
I'm fine.
Anyway, you should get changed.
Yeah, but...
You seem to be getting along well.
We heard you're dating.
I saw you holding hands and walking together the other day.
Didn't you say you were just friends?
I'm sorry!
I wasn't lying!
Okay, okay, okay.
Stop.
Don't bully the cute little underclassman.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks...
Hey!
Our outfits are here!
These are for the dudes,
and those are for the ladies.
Try them on.
Those are loaners, so make sure you don't lose them.
Kaga-san?
Take good care of them.
Let's go.
It might be a little tight.
Lose some weight before the performance.
Where did Kaga-san go?
It looks so good on you!
We look pretty nice in these.
Kouko-chan, you look great.
It's so cute.
Thank you.
Kaga-san, you look great in Japanese clothes, too.
I'm impressed.
Thanks.
Kaga-san, there's something wrong with you.
Maybe you're still sick.
Kaga-san, do you need a towel?
I haven't used this today, so it's still clean.
Kaga-san?
Do you love me?
Wh-why?
Of course I love you.
Do you really love me?
Will you love me forever?
When will you leave me?
Do you find it annoying that I'm asking you this?
Kaga-san?
Seriously, what's wrong?
Do you still love me?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Did I do something to you?
I'm...
I'm anxious.
I'm scared.
I keep thinking negative thoughts.
I want to stop.
I want to be cute for you all the time.
But...
No matter what...
No matter what I do, I feel anxious.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kaga-san.
I'm really sorry.
It's all my fault.
You don't need to feel anxious.
There's nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine.
It's perfect.
In the summer of my third year of high school,
I comforted Linda in the same way.
The current Banri doesn't remember.
Only I, a ghost, and Linda know.
U boj!
Note: Croatian for "to battle."
It's time to start running!
Let's burn as hot as the sun!
U boj!
Linda has an older brother.
He coached our high school's soccer team.
Linda and I both called him Brother.
Brother!
Oh, you guys are here?
Hey! Working hard?
Y-yes.
You seem to be working hard, too.
Yeah.
I'm trying to train them as hard as I can over summer vacation.
We've finished practice, so we're leaving.
Hang in there, Brother.
Yeah!
I'll introduce my fiancée to you sometime.
Okay. Can't wait!
She's beautiful.
She's kind and good at cooking, too.
I still can't believe I'm marrying her.
I hope I can meet her soon.
Look forward to it.
U boj!
He's amazing.
He works so hard at coaching, even though he doesn't get paid.
He's even using his own summer vacation to...
Linda?
Banri...
I need to talk to you about something important.
Huh?
An affair?
I saw my brother's fiancée leaving another man's apartment.
It must've been something else...
A friend, or maybe a brother.
They kissed when she left.
I haven't told my brother yet.
I have no proof.
I don't think he'd believe me if I told him.
He seems to really love her.
That's why I'm going to get photographic evidence and destroy their marriage!
What?!
Unless I send the pictures to everyone in both families and completely ruin her,
I won't be satisfied!
I'll make her pay so much in reparations, she won't be able to make a living!
I want her to live a miserable life, branded a cheater,
so she'll be lonely until the day she dies!
Linda...
Am I wrong, Banri?
Am I trying to do something I shouldn't?
I'm really angry right now.
I don't think I'm thinking straight.
That's why I want your opinion.
What do you think, Banri?
What would you do?
I...
I don't think you're wrong.
I don't want your brother to marry a woman like her, either.
I'll go with you.
Is that all right?
Banri...
She's here.
That's your brother's fiancée?
Yeah.
Let's go, Linda.
What's wrong?
I thought we were going to catch her in the act.
Just...
Just wait.
What do you want to do?
If we enter the apartment now,
we should be able to get even more damning pictures.
I told you, just wait...
I can't sit back and watch a nice guy like your brother be betrayed like this.
I know,
but let's try to calm down.
Hey.
Did you get a picture of them linking arms on your phone, too?
I did.
I did, but we need something more decisive...
Would you erase it?
What?
Erase all
pictures?
YES/NO
All pictures
have been
erased
Hey, what are you doing?!
I changed my mind.
Sorry.
What?!
Hey!
I'll wear the mask of an adult.
See you later.
Yeah.
What?
Nana-chan, what a coincidence!
I'd like to talk with you inside your car.
What?
I can't.
I'm busy right now.
Don't run!
What?
Who are you?
If you still want to get married,
please don't do this again.
I'll forget about this...
But please...
...please stop.
Don't drive until you've calmed down.
Be careful you don't get in an accident.
Don't turn around.
What?
That guy...
He's been watching us the whole time.
Seriously?
Scary...
I told her not to do it again.
And then?
"I understand."
That's all?
Yeah.
It's better than destroying everything.
As long as I pretend like I don't know anything, things will work out as they always have.
It'll be like nothing ever happened.
Is that really the right thing?
Well, I don't want to hurt my brother.
I'm afraid of making him sad...
It's for your brother?!
Do you really think pretending nothing happened is what's best for him?
It'll last forever.
She's going to be family.
Can you think of her as your own sister-in-law?
Imagine how your parents would feel.
Stop!
Everything you said is exactly right...
I know!
I may have been wrong!
But I can't help it!
I've already done it!
Besides, you don't need to be so harsh.
Sorry.
I crossed the line.
I've really done it now.
I wonder if I can endure this forever.
My brother's going to live a lie.
And I'm one of the liars.
I've hurt him.
What can I do?
What should I do?
This isn't good.
I did the wrong thing, didn't I?
What should I do?
What should I do?!
I...
I... um...
I saw everything.
So...
So you don't have to suffer alone.
I may be unreliable, and I may not be able to do anything...
...but I'm here.
I'll always be with you.
I'll never forget.
I'll always be by your side.
When you want to scream or cry, I'll be there.
I'll share your feelings and stay with you.
Even if you think I'm a nuisance,
no matter where you go, I'll find you.
How?
How...?
Well...
I'll find a way.
I'll always be listening for your voice.
When the rain falls, when the wind blows...
...when the flowers scatter, when shadows loom.
In every sign, I'll search for your voice.
I promise I will.
Really?
Can I really trust you?
I didn't have the confidence to answer her then.
But because of this incident,
my feelings for Linda became so strong,
I couldn't hold them back anymore.
The seasons changed, and winter came.
I was forced to clearly recognize my feelings.
Banri.
Linda... Senpai.
What are you doing by yourself?
Where's Kouko-chan?
Her cold came back.
She's not coming today.
I see.
She didn't seem to have much energy yesterday.
She rested all weekend.
She was acting weird yesterday.
I'm worried...
Well, well.
So, you were sad because you couldn't spend the weekend with your beloved Kouko-chan.
What about you, Linda-senpai?
What did you do this weekend?
Me?
Well, I went home.
Oh, to Shizuoka?
Yeah.
I didn't go home for Golden Week,
and my parents told me to come home now and then.
I'm kind of tired.
Did something happen?
It's nothing serious,
but I saw my big brother again, among other things...
Linda-senpai, you have an older brother?
Well, I need to get to my next class!
Banri, make sure you take good care of Kouko-chan.
What?
Always listen for Kouko-chan's voice.
When the rain falls, when the wind blows.
When the flowers scatter, when shadows loom.
In every sign...
...search for her voice.
Okay...
Kouko-chan is your girlfriend.
Later.
If I had looked her in the eye and answered her then,
would things have turned out differently?
Would I have not become a ghost?
Would I still be by Linda's side?
Really?
Can I really trust you?
I should have told her.
"I love you, Linda."
"That's why I want you to trust me."
I should have told her that.
It's too late for regrets.
Linda and I are hopelessly far apart now...
What?
I have a body...
I can touch.
I can move.
I'm not a ghost.
Linda!
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
In The Mirror
U boj!
Working hard, Banri?
What? Is that, like...
...the Eiffel Tower?
What? It's the Awa dance!
Oh!
Yes, I'm working hard!
I'm Awa dancing!
What did you mean by the Eiffel Tower?
Well, that's, er, it's... I can't tell you.