I have a body...
I can touch.
I can move.
I'm not a ghost.
Linda!
I can see Linda.
What... was that?
I wasn't myself just now.
That was...
Linda...
I want to see Linda.
How?
Why?
My memories didn't return,
but my desire to see Linda is still there.
What happened...
In the Mirror
...to me?
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
It's not a serious injury.
Why do I feel like this?
I still didn't clearly understand what had happened the previous night.
But I knew I was the Tada Banri that loved Linda,
and that feeling still hadn't disappeared.
Huh?
The photo's gone.
I know I put it here.
Why?
Why is it missing?
Did Kaga-san...
I need to go to the hospital.
I can't...
I can't walk.
I might really die.
Kaga-san...
What's wrong with you? It's still early!
What are you doing?
I'm... in distress...
I'm really sorry.
You have a fever. Don't talk.
All done?
Yeah, I think so.
Nana-senpai...
What?
Nana-senpai, you seriously, really are a super nice person.
Your face is pissing me off.
I seem to have had the wrong idea about you.
How so?
I thought you were an over-the-top cosplayer from Kawaguchi,
putting on a brave front so you wouldn't be taken lightly in the big city,
until the harsh Tokyo life changed you and you forgot neighborly love for real...
I'm not from Kawaguchi, and this isn't cosplay.
Um... was it Kaminakazato?
Warabi.
Get in.
You're so mean.
Just when I thought you were really nice, suddenly you're being cold...
Are you trying to drag me around by the nose with your tsundere-ness and break my spirit so...
Shut up.
I'm sure Linda-senpai would be nicer to me.
That's great, then.
Huh?
Pass.
Oh, my.
What happened to you?
Nana-senpai, did you take out your rage on Tada Banri and beat him up?
I'm not interested in him like that.
The idiot ended up this way himself and came to me for help.
Anyway, I'm out of smokes.
Ah... wait, Nana-senpai!
You should really quit...
She's not listening.
Are you sure you're okay?
Hey, what are you looking at?
Can you walk?
I'm back.
How are you feeling?
A little better.
I bought some stuff you might be able to eat.
Well?
Think you can eat this?
Are you listening?
What about this?
I-it's fine.
That'll be fine...
Your face is red.
Maybe your fever came back.
Thanks.
Linda-senpai, what are you doing here?
Nana-senpai sent me this text.
NANA-senpai
No subject
Tada Banri's going to the hospital
It surprised me, so I called her back, and she told me to wait at her apartment.
So, I came.
Drink up. Here.
Good. Let's try this next.
It's a little weird, but no one's watching.
Think you can eat bread?
Okay, you can take your medicine after this.
Now, where did I put it?
Thank you, Linda.
There it is.
Huh?
Did you say something?
Um... well...
Thank you, Linda-senpai.
For taking care of me, I mean.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry about it.
I told you the other day that
I'd support you in any way I can.
But I made you skip your lectures.
It's fine.
I'm Linda.
It's only natural for me to do this.
That's all you need to know.
So don't worry about it.
Just let my kind self take care of you, Banri.
Thanks.
No...
The one she calls Banri... isn't me.
To her, Banri is the high school Banri
who was in the same class and the same track and field club as her...
Here.
Thanks.
Good.
Okay.
Um... where's your burnable trash?
In the kitchen.
How's he doing?
He's fine now.
He took his medicine, and he's eaten a bit.
I see.
Nana-senpai's nice, isn't she?
She really is.
If she hadn't helped me,
I really would've been in trouble.
Despite how she looks, she's actually very caring.
I don't even know how many times she's saved me.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I let Kouko-chan know.
Kaga-san...
I miss her.
She is your beloved girlfriend.
I don't know what happened to me.
I don't know what will satisfy me.
I don't know what I want.
The only thing that's certain is that...
I want to be with Linda.
Being with Linda...
...makes Kaga-san seem like someone I met in a dream.
I feel like the world with Linda is reality,
and Kaga-san is fading like a dream.
If the world with Kaga-san is reality,
I want her to appear in front of me.
If she doesn't,
she'll fade into the scenery that's all blurred together by this fever...
She should be here soon.
She's probably coming here as fast as she can.
Ah... But Kaga-san's still resting with a cold...
You're cheating!
Kaga-san!
Good morning, Tada-kun.
You're alone in your apartment with another woman, despite having a girlfriend.
That's the very definition of cheating.
I've said that before!
Uh... but this is...
Kouko-chan, calm down.
Just kidding.
Honestly, Tada-kun.
What happened to you?
Oh, my...
You shouldn't be so reckless when I'm not watching you.
Bad.
In any case, now that I'm here, there's nothing to worry about.
I, your girlfriend,
will restore you to perfect health!
Hey, let go!
You let go!
I'm the one who caught the bouquet!
No, I caught it!
Yana-san, 2D-kun.
I'm going to get married next!
No, I'm going to get married!
Did you come to do a comedy routine?
I'm really kidding.
I just thought it'd be funny if I said you were cheating.
After all, there's no way my Tada-kun would cheat on me.
Tada-kun, you totally love me!
I know that, of course.
I'm loved!
That absolute confidence makes me stronger and stronger.
The power of being loved runs through me and makes me feel even better,
and that in turn makes you...
You looked pretty serious.
Seriously, cut that out.
You really scared me for a second.
You're imagining things.
Oh, but I had no idea.
So Nana-san is your neighbor?
She's acquainted with Linda-senpai, too.
Why didn't you tell me?
There are no secrets between lovers.
I wasn't hiding anything from you.
I just forgot to tell you.
Okay, I forgive you.
Linda-senpai, thank you again.
As his girlfriend, I'm truly grateful to you for taking care of my Tada-kun.
You're a frighteningly good liar, aren't you?
That's completely different from what you were saying earlier.
What?
Earlier, you were saying, "He's cheating, cheating, cheating!"
"Tada-kun is cheating!"
"He must be cheating!"
...and making a big fuss.
That's why you dragged us along.
"Restrain me!"
"If it comes to it, restrain me by force!"
...you said.
Right?
Wh-who knows?
I don't really understand 3D girls.
What?
3D?
Oh, yes.
I've abandoned the third dimension, so they call me 2D-kun.
My real name's Sato Takaya.
Sorry I didn't introduce myself earlier.
I'm Linda.
I'm a second year in the Festival Club with Tada Banri and Kouko-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Oh, I'm so happy.
My first vertical relationship.
Linda-senpai, please forgive Mitsuo.
What?
Mitsuo is sick.
Actually, he's really stupid.
What?!
I know he seems normal, but he's a compulsive liar.
Poor boy,
he doesn't even know what he's saying.
Don't be ridiculous!
You wouldn't shut up about us coming, so we skipped class to-
Then...
...go along home.
The door's right there.
Mitsuo, go home!
Why, you...
Hey, don't fight.
Don't make such a fuss in front of a sick person.
Sorry, but she...
I'm sorry, Tada-kun.
Anyway, it's true.
I really don't think you were cheating...
But, well...
...another girl came to take care of you before me.
I can't deny that I may have been upset.
Then you should feel more threatened by Nana-senpai than by me.
Nana-senpai's the first one who saved Tada Banri.
What's Nana-senpai like?
Like this.
What the heck?
That's terrifying!
She really does look like that!
She does! That really is her!
Are you guys going anywhere over summer vacation?
I haven't thought about it much yet.
Do you have any plans, Linda-senpai?
Like traveling abroad?
I don't have the money to go abroad, but I do want to travel.
Besides that, it's just the Festival Club and visiting home to see friends.
You're not from here?
Where's home?
Anyway, the beach!
It's all about the beach!
Do you have any plans like that?
"Let's all go to the beach together!" or something like that?
That's a good idea.
I really want to go to the beach.
I have a license.
It'd be fun to rent a car and go together.
You know, we should all go together.
We could go somewhere close, like Shonan, or go all the way to Izu!
You should come with us, Linda-senpai.
You're inviting me?
Of course.
It'd be boring if Kouko were the only girl.
Then I'll invite Nana-senpai, too.
What?
Nana-senpai doesn't seem like the type who'd like the beach.
We should invite Oka-chan, too.
We made that promise the other day.
What?
If you invite Miss Ultrasonic, we won't have enough seats.
As long as we rent a big car, it won't be a problem.
Who's Miss Ultrasonic?
Mitsuo confessed to her and was rejected instantly...
Don't tell her about that!
Kaga-san.
You're awake?
Yeah.
I guess I fell asleep.
How are you feeling?
A little better.
Where did everyone go?
They left around noon.
They could still make their afternoon classes.
You've been here the whole time?
Yeah.
Do you need anything?
Want some water?
No, I'm fine.
Kaga-san, you don't need to go?
You haven't eaten anything, have you?
I ate the bread Linda-senpai bought.
Tada-kun, I'm sorry.
For what?
For barging in with everyone when you're not feeling well.
For not taking care of you properly.
For making a fuss...
You didn't get any rest, did you?
I shouldn't have come.
That's not true.
It is!
It's not.
It is...
I want to be a good girlfriend,
but I can't seem to do it.
A piece of junk like me isn't...
That's not true at all.
It is!
I really thought so today.
Instead of me,
someone like Linda-senpai would be much better...
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Anyway, Kaga-san, are you sure you're okay?
What?
You're not over your cold yet, are you?
I'm fine.
Honest, I'm okay.
If I had a cold, I couldn't have come to see you.
You're still hot.
Getting a fever like this when you're living on your own makes you anxious, doesn't it?
But I'll stay by your side.
I'm your useless, piece-of-junk girlfriend,
but I have more love than anyone.
I'll do anything I can.
Hey, Tada-kun.
Earlier, I thought...
I want to go to the beach.
Not with everyone... just with you.
When you get better, will you take me?
Really?
You want to go, just the two of us?
Yeah, I do.
It doesn't have to be Paris.
I want to go to the beach with you.
What?
You mean...
Let's go to the beach.
Just the two of us.
Really?
I promise.
Once summer vacation starts,
I'll take you to the beach.
Yeah.
It's a promise.
A promise.
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
Trouble Party
Come on! Walk, you pig!
Did you get that injury when someone hit you?
No way!
From me, from me!
Shut up.
Whatcha gonna do?
Shut up. I'll kill you.
Oh, Nana-senpai,
you're so distant... and you reek of cigarettes.