Yeah, it's done.
I'll send it this week, so make sure you watch for it.
I'm glad I finally wrote an outstanding calligraphy piece.
Ever since I've been here,
I've been tingling with inspiration.
"Narukain Exhibit Application
'Stars'"
Got to hand it to Mother Nature.
I'm actually enjoying writing, compared to when I was over there.
Hey, are you listening, Kawafuji?
Hey!
You're early, Director. I'm sorry to have put you to the trouble of coming here.
How is his work going?
He says he's doing fine.
Instead of writing beautiful calligraphy like others...
...I'd prefer that Handa-k u n master writing calligraphy of his own.
A calligraphy that represents his very self...
I don't know about that.
Personally, I'd rather like him to hurry on back here,
but he seems intent not to return until he gets results from the exhibit.
Has he... repented for punching me?
Well, I can't answer that...
If my forgiveness will bring him back...
...let's have him come back soon.
"Dacchi Ikode"
"Translation: Let's go together"
Damn that Kawafuji...
He doesn't care what I have to say.
I expressed myself strongly to Kawafuji, but...
"Narukain Exhibit Application
'Stars'"
...was that calligraphy really okay?
"Stars"
I think it looks good...
You can tell it was written in the heat of the moment...
Can I really say this is my calligraphy?
This is something I was able to write because I was on the island.
If I was told to write the same in Tokyo, I probably couldn't.
Dang it... Now I'm getting worried.
Is it okay to submit something I wrote on a whim to an exhibit I can't afford to lose?
Positive... Positive thinking...
It's no use thinking about it now.
My only weapon now is my inspiration from nature.
Worrying about my calligraphy would push the schedule...
Naru, what do you think?
Huh? What?
Never mind that. Whatcha wanna play today?
Never mind...?
I'm not going to play with you.
Here I was trying to open up to you in a rare moment of vulnerability...
Better watch what ya say...
--Peek...
--Tch!
"'I'll do anything you say' ticket
1 time"
I should have made a "free shoulder massage" ticket instead.
As long as I got this, ya gotta listen to what I say forever!
It says "1 time" on there, got it?
Hey!
Grandpa!
Oh?
Naru!
Hm?
What are they doing?
Ya stack them stones ta make a wall to protect against hurricanes.
Ya gotta stack 'em perfect, or else it'll just fall apart.
It's like a puzzle.
Then can ya bring me that stone over there?
He's trying to make it so
I just naturally start helping!
Naru's gonna make Sensei take her toad huntin'... using this!
Toad hunting?!
--'Kay, then...
--Hey!
I'll use this, so help me out, will ya?
--Wha--?!
--Well, if that's the case...
Aww! That's Naru's!
C'mon, I'll give ya somethin' else, Naru.
Somethin' else? Whatcha mean by that?!
--Here.
--Hm?
What's this?
It's a rock that'll skip good on water.
Aah... Aren't you happy, Naru?
Don't want it...!
Pretty good.
C'mon and help, Sensei!
S-So heavy...
Take it there.
Phooey...
Let's put this...
...here.
It feels good when it fits in perfectly!
Ya don't say?
Yer really good.
I think I'm good at handling exacting tasks.
I thought I stacked mine well, but this here's rickety.
Pfft...! You've got no skills, Grandpa!
You're so honest, Naru!
Why not have Sensei handle that shrine thing?
Oh, yeah, that thing.
That thing?
Go on in.
Excuse me.
What is it that I have to do in this shrine? Purification?
Look at that there.
Them's the names of the people who helped when the shrine was built.
Well, it's got all of us villagers' names there.
We're thinkin' of getting it rewritten.
Here ya go.
A list of names.
We were gonna hire a pro from the city to rewrite it, but...
...you're better, right, Sensei?
Here.
Wow... This is amazing. So old...
It ain't much, but we'll pay, y'know?
Ah, I'm not worried about the pay, but...
Don't feel like it?
That's not it.
It's just that it's been a while since
I wrote such well-ordered characters.
Write 'em good, 'kay?
Ya see here? Got space here for one more person.
Sensei, can ya write yer name down here, so we know who did the writin'?
Are you sure? I didn't contribute at all.
Shh...!
Keep it secret.
Uh, that's not good...
--Sensei.
--Hm?
There was a call from
Kawafuji-s a n for you at the store.
That guy... And after ignoring me too...
You kids go and take this back to my place.
Okay.
Why'd Kawafuji call?
He said he had something important to talk about.
Whatcha mean, important to talk 'bout?
Adult talk.
What's the matter, Naru?
I didn't get to ask for anything with my "I'll do anything you say" ticket...
Grandpa used it up!
That's too bad.
What were you going to ask for, Naru?
Lemme see...
I wanna go to the festival with Sensei, and...
...I wanna go to the sea again too!
I wanna go to a sports event too!
Hey, the mountains, too!
And...
I bet he'd take you to those places without a ticket.
Oh, yeah!
I can't wait!
C'mon, let's plan for goin' to the festival!
Hina wants to wear a kimono!
Then let's ask Miwa-n e e and Tama to come too.
It'll become a hassle if you invite those two.
You're gonna come too, right, Akki?
Yup.
Yeah... I see...
Yeah, I got it.
I'll return.
Okay! I'll choose this one!
I'll use this.
Good! You've both done well, improving yourselves through all the lessons.
As your mentor, there's nothing more I can teach you.
You both better get a gold award!
"Visiting Old, Learning New"
Yes, sir!
That's 'bout it for bein' eager.
Is this really gonna be okay?
With all that spirit we put into it, if we don't get awarded...
I feel sick about submitting this...
You idiots!
I taught you two!
Your calligraphy won't lose to anyone!
Ya really think so, Sensei?
I'm the one who should be worried...
I'm not even sure if the work I'm going to submit is good or not...
Sensei!
Sensei! Take us to the festival!
You promised!
Here you go.
Sensei, I didn't know you could tie a yukata sash.
That's amazing.
It's cute!
This is nothing.
If I wanted to, I could tie a kimono sash too.
Sensei, you're going to the festival too, right?
Yeah.
Yaaay! Let's hurry!
Festival! Festival!
'Kay, we're gonna go too, so see you there.
--Thanks for the calligraphy.
--Sure.
Sensei, let's hurry and go!
--Hurry...!
--I got it!
A festival...
I guess I'll go with them for a change of pace.
Sensei, you look happy.
I-I'm not happy at all, you know!
Hey!
Festival!
Oh, well...
This'll be the last...
"Goto Bus Center"
Yay! Festival! Festival!
"Tonme Festival"
Sensei! Here! Over here!
So this is what a festival is like...
Come to think of it, I hardly went to any when I was in Tokyo.
"Elementary School"
Sei-s a n? How would you like to go to the festival?
No. He has an exhibit to attend to.
"High School"
Handa, let's go to the festival.
I'm sorry. Sei-s a n has an exhibit to attend to.
"College"
Handa-k y u n, let's go to the festival!
Handa's got an exhibit he has to attend to, so I'll go in his place.
Hey!
Sad memories to remember... and even now, it's before an exhibit.
Sensei!
"Goldfish Scoop"
Sensei! Goldfish! Goldfish!
Oh! That's the famous goldfish scoop!
Oh! Yer here too, Sensei?
Yakuza--! No, you're Miwa's dad.
I'm just helpin' out the association.
Wow, you must be busy.
Here ya go... 100 yen.
A pastry shell?
You can scoop with this?
Do yer best, Sensei!
Your best!
Now!
--Huh?
--You're bad at this, Sensei.
Pops, this has got to be defective!
Course it ain't. Yer just bad at it.
Damn it... Once more...
Excuse me, Sensei. Can you move over a bit?
Ah, Nurse?
Hey! Iku-n e e!
You're not supposed to scoop with force.
Keep yer eyes on Iku-chan's scoopin' skills.
Wh-What?!
It's as if the goldfish are coming in to be scooped!
Hey... It's Iku!
Amazin' as usual. She's gonna put us in the red.
I'd like ta know what she's gonna do with all of 'em.
True...
--Here's the last spurt...
--Iku!
Whatcha doing, Aiko?!
Too bad, Iku-c h a n.
Aww... And I was so close to making a new record!
Ikuko tries to make a clean sweep at the goldfish scoop every year.
Huh? Head Teacher?
Thought I taught her the importance of moderation back in branch school...
Huh, is that so?
He wants me to call him out, but I'm not taking the bait.
We didn't catch any goldfish.
Raising living things is a pain, so I purposely didn't catch any.
They're doin' somethin' over there.
Wonder what.
It's a free throw competition.
--Hey, Akki!
--A-Akki?
You shoot for points as a four-person team for coupons.
We're gonna enter too!
You brats!
We're on the same team.
If it weren't for the middle school students so serious about the coupons,
we would have had a solid chance for first place.
First place is 5,000 yen...
Let's show everyone that the softball club is invincible.
Okay, Miwa-c c h i.
The air there is stagnant...
Hey, isn't Tama with you?
Oh, Sensei.
Tama went to buy today's manga release.
We gotta have four people, so I want her to come back soon.
It's the rumored Sensei!
Wow, he's handsome!
Nice, Akki!
Akki's actin' sassy for a sixth grader.
Contrary to his appearance,
Akki is pretty high-spec.
It's our turn next, but where in the world is Tama?
So late!
"Tama at the time"
Why don't you have it on sale on the day of release?!
It's always been like this.
Next up, "Softball Club Eyeglasses Team"!
This isn't good, Miwa-c c h i...
Hurry and come down!
Why, that rotten four-eyes...!
Sensei! Please!
--Huh?!
--You just have ta make a shot in!
--Just make a shot in?! It isn't that easy!
--Okay, first shot!
Alley-oop!
Second shot!
Third shot!
You girls are too good!
Aren't you in the softball club?!
We sometimes help the basketball club too.
None of the clubs have many members, so we give an' take, y'know?
The club situation in the countryside is astounding...
Here! Now do it, Sensei!
Huh? Seriously?!
I guess I don't have a choice...
Sensei! Do yer best!
Who'd have expected a day to arrive where I would have to display my undisclosed talent...?
That's right... I used to...
...read basketball manga!
The winner, "Team Akki"! They did great, even as elementary students! So moving!
Sensei? Lift yer spirits...
Well... I thought I could do it...
Here, Sensei!
It ain't much, but we got some coupons for second place.
Even split fer 300 yen a head.
You sure I can have these, even when I missed?
Should've been Tama's, but she ain't comin'.
"Tama at the time"
I asked you to put the book on hold!
Why'd you sell it?!
We'll get more soon.
To heck with it!
"Takoyaki 400
Yakisoba 300
Cotton Candy 100
Juice 150"
What do you want to eat?
I'll buy you anything now.
Yay!
Then, t a k o y a k i!
Ya k i s o b a!
--Cotton candy it is.
--Huh...?
--Cheap!
--Ya said anything we want!
Don't think that all adults have money with them.
It's okay, then. I'll just buy it myself.
Hina too.
You girls had money?!
I showed off for nothing!
If ya want something, lemme know.
I'll buy it for ya.
Stop it! No way I can be treated by a seven-year-old kid.
Just let her treat you.
Hiro!
Wanna buy some y a k i s o b a?
It'll help fund the baseball club.
Not that I don't have money, but...
I'll have three cotton candies, using these coupons.
So cheap...
Here, super-sized.
Yay!
--Here.
--Yay!
--Here, Sensei.
--Thank you.
Thanks, Sensei!
So this is cotton candy...
Where am I supposed to bite into it?
Here? Over here?
Wait, here? No, here?
Is Sensei going to be all right walking into the crowd?
Hope he doesn't get cotton candy on someone's clothes,
or poke himself with the chopstick...
Hiroshi! We got more y a k i s o b a!
Them drums are so loud!
So loud!
The fireworks display will begin at nine o'clock.
Fireworks, Sensei!
Yeah.
Both of you, don't get lost.
Hey!
Sensei! Over here!
Already...?
Naru!
Hina!
Damn it! It's so dark...
Sensei...
Tama? What are you doing here?
I was reading the manga I bought.
I don't like being in a crowd.
I'm pretty much like this every year during the summer festival.
Not that I'm fit to say this, but you're wasting your youth badly.
Did you see Naru and Hina--stop it!
They went through here, so they must have gone to the beach.
It's almost time for the fireworks, so let's go.
We know a perfect place.
Hey, it's Sensei!
Tama, where ya been hiding?
I'm really sorry. I was just reading manga.
Huh? Where are the girls from the softball club?
They're gonna watch the fireworks with their boyfriends.
Oh? If only they'd explode...
--Tama?!
--Hey! Naru and Hina're here too!
Hey!
You're here too, Hiro-n i i?
Where's yer girlfriend?
You think I'd be cooking y a k i s o b a if I had a girlfriend?
Sorry, I was just pullin' yer leg.
Well, I guess it's the same group as usual.
Yup.
So, summer vacation is about to end...
It was fun this year.
Once school starts, we won't be able to play so much.
Hiro-n i i, you gonna study for the exam?
I'm gonna look for a job.
Does that mean you're gonna stay on the island?
--I'm leaving.
--Aww... That's going to be sad.
Well, I still got some time.
I guess, and even if Hiro-n i i ain't 'round, we still got Sensei.
You think Sensei can take my place?!
Hey...
There's something I need to say...
It's starting!
Yikes! It's so bright!
--Wow!
--Super!
Hey.
What was Sensei trying to say?
--Beats me...
--Both of ya, look at him.
Even without words, Sensei's back says it all...
Sensei! I'm here to play!
Huh?
Sensei!
Sensei...?
No one's a comin'...