What happened...?
P-R-E-M-I-U-M...
C-H-O-C-O-L-A-T-E...
Hey, you read it!
That's great, Naru!
Mmm... "Mandom"...
Mandom?
By mastering the katakana I'm supposed to learn after summer...
...Naru took a step towards adulthood.
Everything in sight is so beautiful...
--So this is what it means to mature...
--Congratulations! Congratulations!
--It is as if the birth of a new me is being blessed...
"Mandom"...
Where did you learn that...?
Let me find something a bit more difficult.
Here, can you read this?
It says... "open square."
That's amazing!
You learn this kanji in your third semester...
No, in your second year!
You read it right, so I'll give you this milk as a reward.
Thanks...
Make sure you tell everyone that you read that!
Kids mature fast, don't they?
I didn't think she was that studious...
I wonder what struck her.
There's only one explanation...
Oh, yeah...
You... What happened...?
Sensei, can you read this?
It says... "opening."
Huh...?
"Hitonmochi"
"Translation: Rice cakes thrown in celebrations"
Yeah, I just sent it.
Submit it to the Tokyo Kasho Exhibit.
So, pretty confident in it?
That's my calligraphy now.
"Mind at Ease"
I wouldn't send it if I wasn't confident.
I can't wait for it to come.
Oh, that's right...
I ran out of ink.
Hiro? Where can I buy ink?
Kinoshita Shoten?
Welcome.
Ah, thank you for helping me move in.
Feel free to look around.
The store is pretty well stocked.
Hey, candies...
Hardly ever ate candies, with my parents saying they weren't good for me.
Naru's probably going to come over, so I better buy something.
Naru loves them Kanro candies and Choco Bats.
She read my mind?!
Wow... Maybe I should buy in bulk...
Other little ones come too, y'know?
What's this?
Let me take a quick peek...
Whoa! Shoot!
What are these?
Needles?
I-I'm sorry! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Um, this should be all of them. I'll buy this.
Don't you worry.
You cleaned the floor for this old lady.
My back hurts, so I can't bend, y'know?
Mighty kind of ya.
Maybe it's because you're carrying a poodle.
Well, not that I could say that...
Coming in.
Oh, hello there.
My, the day's a burnin'.
Welcome.
How's your back?
(Dialect)
Anything you need?
Do you have any strings?
(Dialect)
Yes, it stings.
Do you have any strings?
(Dialect)
Yes, it stings.
Do you have any stings?
(Dialect)
Yes, it stings.
Um, "strings" as in this?
My, yes, that's it.
I've been asking for that, but she kept saying "it stings."
(Dialect)
That old bag's ears went bad.
I don't understand a word you're saying.
Ol' baggie there seen better days.
Should just clam up and take a breather.
Why is doggie so mad?!
That's right, ink!
Thank you for letting me have the ink.
Don't worry. I'll just get it from the inkstick.
This really helps, especially with my deadline.
Speaking of, I heard you were writing manga.
It's nothing special or anything!
No need to be shy about it.
We both found enjoyment in writing, so let's get along.
Um...!
Can you... read my manga?
I was thinking of submitting to a shonen magazine...
...but I wanted to get candid feedback from someone first.
I'm no professional, so I can't give good feedback.
That's fine! I asked because it's you, Sensei!
I want someone who found enjoyment in writing to read it!
Please!
Well, if you say so...
Pretty alluring intro, isn't it?
Were... you sending this to a horror magazine?
A shonen magazine.
Is there something wrong?!
Um... Not wrong, but...
...maybe you should keep the concept of "shonen magazine" in mind more...
"Whoever's name is written explodes to bits"
"I'll call this the 'Keth Note'"
Like something with friendship and effort...
What are you saying?!
No one will read a manga that professes the ideal of common justice!
The heck?!
Blood, flesh, splattering gore!
The demise of justice!
A dark-sided hero!
A complex male friendship with a friend who is also a foe!
A heroine who naturally fades out of the story after the first episode!
But children read this...
The world seeks something never conceived before!
Yes! The heroine's friend's grandfather can be the last boss!
I... I think the manga captures the current trends...
Please read to the very end.
I seek your opinion!
If it isn't good, say so! Sharply!
So sharply one can never recover! Yes!
No way she's going to listen...!
Please read these and learn what manga is about.
I'm never going to get myself involved with manga writers.
Miwa-chan was about the only one
I ever told about me trying to be a manga writer...
I got carried away there, and even showed him my draft.
What am I going to do if Sensei tells the others about this?
--Naru saying...
--"Tama's a manga writer!"
...may not have credibility, but Sensei's word would!
Everyone in the village will find out that I'm an otaku!
A complex male friendship with a friend who is...!
A heroine who naturally fades out of the story...!
If things go bad, they'll think
I'm more a fujoshi than an otaku!
"Fujoshi: Females who find a liking towards
novels or manga portraying love between males.
<Related> BL (Boy's Love), Yaoi, Fudanshi
<Official>, Females who like manga ≠ Fujoshi"
This can't happen!
"Aaaaaah!"
I just have a pure love of manga!
In general terms, I'm a fan of fine arts!
I'm no low-life fujoshi!
I need... to fix this...
Here, this is for today.
Yeah... thanks.
What's the matter? You don't look well.
I was thinking of how girls nowadays are so passionate.
--Huh?
--And I need to make some ink now.
Yeah, I'm not well...
Oh, so you weren't able to buy ink after all.
After all?
It sells out quick with the calligraphy homework during summer vacation.
I figured as much, so I brought you an open one I had with me.
I need to fix this!
I can't live in this village if people claim that I'm a fujoshi!
I'll say that I wanted to be a novelist, not a manga writer.
Did I mistakenly lend him my "special book"?
"overtime work lovers
What?! Overtime, again?"
That was when I was in the first year of middle school...
Tama, I got some manga from your relative.
Yay! All right!
You really like manga, don't you, Tama?
What's this?! Guys on guys?! Eew!
This is going to traumatize me!
So filthy, and stupid...!
Adults are all so dirty!
Peek.
I kept my "special book" so I wouldn't forget about that fateful day!
I kept it separate from the others so I would never mistakenly lend it!
Whatever I do, I'm going to keep my position as a girl of literature!
Sensei!
Whew, you saved me...
I didn't expect to slip...
Whatever! Just hurry and get yourself back up!
I got dizzy with joy from seeing the ink.
At this rate, you're gonna bang your head somewhere and die!
Hey, wait! The champon!
What?!
--Huh...? What...
--It's been champon every day.
--...am I doing here?
--We got noodles as a midyear gift.
I need to work on my draft...
Draft... Draft...
Draf...
Dra...
Curse my freaking youth!
Huh?! What do you mean?!
That calligraphy was my masterpiece!
There's no way it could only get second place!
You've got to be kidding...
Sensei! Let's play!
--Huh?
--Hm?
What's with the bad vibe in here?!
Look!
Wha--?! What's that?!
What's the matter, Sensei?
You've got stuff coming out of you.
...mumble, mumble, mumble...
--Hm?
--Huh? What's he mumbling about?
Sensei said he took second place in the calligraphy competition.
Oh, yeah, he did say he sent his work to a calligraphy exhibition.
Second place is amazing.
...mumble, mumble, mumble...
Hm?
First place was some eighteen-year-old punk.
Wait. You're pouting because you lost to a younger person?
--Is that it...?
--"Is that it"?!
Do you girls have any idea how much I put into my work?!
The work I spent my nights on was beaten by some rookie calligrapher!
I thought moving here would make me write better...
...but now my lazy approach is finally taking its toll!
I shouldn't have come here in the first place!
Hey, Sensei!
Miwa-chan!
I'm sorry, Sensei.
I think we caught you at the wrong time.
We'll come again.
Why didn't you just give it to him?!
He made it sound like we're the ones dragging him down!
Sensei thrives on pride...
...so speaking logic is just going to make matters worse.
Let's just leave the rest to Naru.
Sensei?
Miwa-nee and Tama didn't leave because they don't like Sensei.
I know that.
I made middle-school students worry.
This is just pathetic...
But I can't bring myself to face the facts...
If you take calligraphy away from me, I'll have nothing left.
I need to be number one...
Sensei, are you happy now?
If you're not happy, let's go out and play!
Everyone's bringing grocery bags...
What's the event?
Mochi catching! Sensei, you don't know that?
Boy, you outsiders.
It's that thing where people toss mochi when building a house, right?
I never participated in one, but I at least know about it.
House?
We're gonna catch mochi from a boat today!
Let's grab em' all!
My, Sensei, you're late.
Hurry, the toss is about to start.
Um... This is for...
Its Kenta's new boat.
Kenta's?
Hey! Naru!
Kenta! The boat's so cool!
Right?! It's called the Kenmaru!
--"Kenmaru"?
--Using an older sister's name is considered lucky...
...but we don't have a daughter.
--I'm gonna toss a lot to your side, Naru!
--Sensei! Over here!
Darn it!
Naru! Look, mochi!
The heck ya doin', Kenta?!
--But, but...!
--Never mind! Hurry and scoop them up!
Hey, if it isn't Sensei.
So, feeling a bit better now?
Hiroshi's here too?
Yeah, I was forced away from my studies...
Sure, so how do you explain that glove you got there?
If we're gonna do this, might as well go serious.
Well then, you're on!
Hey...
About earlier... Well...
What? You still haven't recovered?
Don't worry about us.
Let's just think of getting those mochi.
To get a lot, you need to get away from the two professionals.
Professionals?
The first is "Yasu-ba"!
She's participated in a lot of mochi catchings,
so she always goes home with the most.
The other is "Panchi."
She grabs mochi away from others, so don't go near her.
The rest is up to each of us doing our best!
--Sensei!
--What?! I'm doing this, too?!
All right! Ya ready?!
Let's go get 'em!
Yeah!
Yeah...
Here ya... go!
I got out of the gates late...
I better go to the front and catch them.
What the heck...?
Damn it, one more time!
Good. Now's my chance...
Whoops, sorry, Sensei.
You... That's my mochi...
Tch... Are the gods testing me...?!
Tama?
Don't just lie there, Sensei.
Show your spirit like you usually do.
What do you mean, "usually"?
I guess it's the same here too...
There's those who can get what they want and others who can't.
Instead of struggling for something you can't get...
...maybe it's more acceptable to give up trying.
Maybe I should quit calligraphy...
Ouch!
Damn that Panchi...!
Sensei, did you get any?
No.
Maybe you're not good at this, Sensei.
I'm really not good at all...
Well, of course, you only look up.
Wait a wee bit and pick up the ones on the ground.
Your chance could be lyin' there on the ground, y'know?
The ground...
Only got a little more left, so give it your best.
Ah, Yasu-ba! What should
I do if I still can't get it?
Like, I can't get it because there's someone better than me.
Hm?
Um... No, well...
Well, then...
Be my guest.
Let them have it, and you go lookin' for a bigger mochi.
You be mindful of giving and getting.
See? Look at this.
Sensei!
C'mon, hurry. They'll all be gone!
All right!
Let's do this!
Let's do it!
G-Go ahead...
Was this the right thing to do?
How many did you get, Sensei?
Don't ask, Naru. He didn't get any.
Naru got twenty-eight of them!
Wow, a grown adult got zero.
Not true! I actually got one, but Panchi...
Liar.
What's that?
Mochi and red bean soup?
Yeah, it must be from Panchi.
She's always serious,
but after mochi catching, she goes around sharing what she makes.
She gets a lot of mochi to share with the others who couldn't come.
Whatever the reason,
I'm not gonna lose next time!
Yikes, this mochi is wet!
Must be the one that Kenta dropped.
Ew, I got one too!
You know what...?
I had fun today.
Thanks.
See?
So, you folks fishing for crayfish too?
Hey! Head Teacher!
I don't see a single quality of a teacher there.
Is Head Teacher gonna raise crayfish too?
Of course not.
I'm gonna use them as bait for striped beakfish.
Why'd you do that for, Naru?!
You're so mean, making the crayfish into bait!
Huh?
Naru? If you let this go, you can eat beakfish.
Really?!
You want to eat, right?
Then let's catch some crayfish!
Yeah! Gonna catch them!
Head Teacher! How do you make them into bait?
Um, well...
...you just pull the claw off like this...
Hey, Naru!