And then I suddenly saw my past self.
I tried to save him, but he made himself fall.
Has anything like that happened since?
No, it was just that one time.
I see...
Doctor, what's going to happen to me?
There's nothing I can say for sure now.
I'll prescribe you a sedative.
Take it if you feel unstable again.
My past self returned once before.
While he was here, I was unconscious.
And while I'm conscious, he's not here.
It's as if I'm fighting with my past self over the person called Tada Banri.
But he chose to disappear into the darkness.
In other words, he won't try to take over my body again...
Night in Paris
Can I believe that?
Ah, if we could meet in a dream, could I say it?
Say, if sadness alone floats down from the sky
If that kind of voice pains you even now
Even if, off to the side, our hands are placed on each other's
This memory wouldn't fade, but...
Even if, when our eyes meet, I can't say the truth...
Your words illuminate the world more than anyone else's
Next to me, "Goodbye means I love you," you say
I can't be forthright
Though I alone sing of loneliness
I can't smile
"Thank you means I'm in love with you," you say
The world's end of love
In the middle of September, I returned to Tokyo.
I brought with me a ring my mother gave me.
Banri!
What is this?
I wore this ring when I was younger.
You have a girlfriend in Tokyo, don't you?
Give it to her.
But this looks pretty expensive.
It's fine.
I'm sure the ring will be happier being worn by a young lady.
Banri!
Kouko!
BANRI!
Banri!
It's been such a long, long, super long time!
Hey, you're looking well!
When we heard from you, we decided to come meet you!
Welcome home!
It's been way too long!
Things just aren't right without you!
Why are you people welcoming him home before me?!
Know your place!
This is the moving reunion of two lovers!
Banri.
Who are you?
What?!
I'm just kidding.
That joke totally wasn't necessary!
I'm home, Kouko.
Welcome, welcome, welcome home!
Now, a toast to Tada Banri-kun's return to Tokyo.
Cheers!
Oka-chan, you cut your hair.
Oh, right. This is the first time you've seen it.
What do you think?
It looks great on you.
But wasn't it kind of a shame to cut it off?
Hm... you agree with Yana and 2D-kun, huh?
Maybe cutting it was a mistake...
I don't think it's a shame at all.
After all, it looks great on you.
Aw, shucks.
Anyway,
Banri and Kouko, I need a huge favor from you guys.
What is it?
Do you think I could check out your club?
I want to make a film about the festival club.
A film?
Yeah.
You know the school festival in November?
I want to produce something to show there.
I was thinking of editing you guys dancing into a short film, like a music video.
Huh...?
Oka-chan, are you helping him?
No, I've got other plans.
We'll have to ask the senior members about letting him film us.
Yeah.
Why the festival club, anyway?
Well, to be honest, there's someone in the festival club I'm interested in.
I want to film...
I mean, I want to see Linda-senpai.
I was hoping this would give me a chance to get closer to her.
We've actually gone out to eat together a few times,
but it's completely one-sided.
I panicked and did some weird things.
I don't know what to do anymore...
I get it, I get it.
Whatever the reason, we'll talk to the senior members about it.
You just hang on to your one-sided crush and wait.
Thanks, guys.
I'm counting on you.
What?
So you knew?
Yeah.
We all saw you with Linda-senpai before.
What the heck...
You weren't all making fun of my one-sided crush, were you?
No, no.
We thought it'd be better if we didn't interfere.
But it was wrong of us, wasn't it?
Sorry.
I didn't tell you guys about Linda-senpai
because there was something else on my mind that wasn't easy to explain.
I guess you could say...
I actually felt kind of jealous of you.
You were jealous of me?
To me, it looks like you and Linda-senpai aren't just in the same club.
It seems like there's something else to your relationship.
When you got injured,
Linda-senpai was really worried.
And you're both from Shizuoka, right?
Once I started thinking about it, everything started to bother me.
I even thought...
you might be hiding something important from me, too.
I started to suspect that you didn't really accept me.
This'll be the only time I ask, so give me a straight answer.
Banri, is there something you're not telling me?
Why don't I just tell him?
I should be honest.
I shouldn't hide anything.
Linda and I were classmates in high school, and I was in love with her.
But I lost my memories, and didn't recognize her when we met again.
I've hurt Kouko before because
I was confused about my feelings.
But now my mind is clear...
...Linda and my family respect who I am now...
...so everything is fine.
There's no problem.
U-um, well...
Sorry!
There must really be something wrong with me.
I'm sorry for suspecting you of weird stuff like that.
No... you weren't...
Forgive me.
I still want to be your friend.
S-sure...
Don't worry about it.
I'm just glad you didn't hurt yourself, Banri.
I'm really sorry.
I'll give you something next time...
Oh... right!
My mom's ring!
Wait.
Is that something I should give her so casually?
Wouldn't giving her a ring mean... proposing?
If Kouko and I got married,
I'd be ecstatic, of course!
But if we did,
the Kaga family fortune and her ramen-eating dad would come with it...
Plus, I wouldn't fit in as a member of the Kaga family. I just don't match.
Maybe proposing to Kouko just because I love her is a bad idea...
Hey, Banri.
What do you think this is?
Uh... um...
It's my present to you.
Open it.
I hope you like it.
Wh-what is this?
We were apart for a while, weren't we?
I missed you so much.
I thought of you all the time,
but that made me love you even more.
O-okay...
I thought I'd try to express my love artistically, so I made this.
Well? What do you think it is?
Um... a club?
It's not? Then, um...
It's the Eiffel Tower.
What?!
This thing?
Wh-wh-what I'm saying is... you know...!
I decided that when you came back,
I'd f-finally... make you let me get you to become one with me.
Huh?
Tonight, we'll finally climb the stu-ste-stairs to ada-ado-adulthood!
What?!
Just... understand!
Understand what I'm saying!
K-Kouko, just... Wait a minute!
I won't wait!
I'm asking you to understand... please...
No?
Kouko...
Wh-what?
It's nothing. I'm fine. Fine, fine.
Kouko...
Wh-what's wrong?
I had too much to eat...
It's okay.
I swallowed it.
Swallowed what?!
I'm fine now, so...
Kouko!
Why did it turn out this way?
Who cares?
It's the kind of thing I'd expect from us.
This is what you expect of us?
No way!
I want it to be more romantic!
But this is how I really am.
You keep drawing this side of myself out of me.
This is the one place where I can truly be myself.
I belong here more than I belong in my own room at my own house.
Me, too.
You're the one I want to come home to.
I feel like I've been searching for this place for a long time.
Banri, you've finally fallen for me.
I have, I definitely have.
Let's take things at our own pace.
We have plenty of time.
Okay.
Our second semester classes started.
It was autumn.
The festival club had begun practicing for its next festival.
Yanagisawa Mitsuo-kun!
He's apparently Banri and Roboko's friend.
Thanks for having me.
Any objections or questions?
Here!
Yanagisawa-kun, do you have a girlfriend?
N-no, I don't...
Seriously?
We might finally have a chance!
What'll we do? What'll we do?
Hey, guys, I don't have a girlfriend, either. What'll you do?
We know that!
We're not doing anything!
Okay, looks like no one's opposed.
Try to work with Yanagisawa-kun, everyone.
Okay!
There's a lot going on this fall.
First, October.
There's another Awa dance festival.
After that is the school festival in November.
We'll be asking people from other colleges for backup there.
Give it everything you have.
Yeah!
Okay, start warming up!
It's great that you got permission, Yana-san.
Yeah, but...
Did something happen?
I made Linda-senpai mad the other day.
What?
Kouko-chan, let's warm up together.
Okay.
That's all for today's practice.
You're dismissed.
Good work today!
It didn't work.
I didn't get the chance to say a single word to her.
You're just getting started.
There are almost two months before the school festival.
I feel like I've been summoned to a really secret conversation.
About Mitsuo?
Probably.
Got it.
Leave Mitsuo to me. I'll stall him.
Hey, Mitsuo, why don't we get some tea?
Huh? With you? Why?
And where are you going, Banri?
I need to go get something I forgot on campus.
I'd feel bad making Kouko come with me.
Why don't you hang out with her?
Let us come, too!
We want to know more about you!
Yeah, we want to know every last thing!
Let's go!
Pick up after
your dog.
Linda!
What's gotten into you?
Why didn't you say anything?
Wh-what, specifically, are you talking about?
Wait, wait, wait!
I really don't know what you're talking about!
Figure it out.
Don't be unreasonable!
When you say that to me with that look on your face...
What?!
You kicked me!
Yeah, I kicked you!
Anyway, I really don't know what you meant!
Why are you so pissed about Yana-san?!
What?
Nobody's mad!
Would you kick my butt on the street if you weren't mad?!
See? Those eyes...! You're mad!
Why?
I don't understand!
I said I'm not mad!
I really don't understand!
I s-s-s-s-seriously don't get it!
Pick up
after your dog
What are you doing, you idiot?
Shut up!
What am I going to do about this?
I can't believe how stupid you are.
Seriously, it's unbelievable.
Right now, I'm thinking from the bottom of my heart that you're a major idiot.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
So this is what campus is like after classes are over...
So?
I'm not mad.
I was just really surprised.
I got flustered.
That Yana-san came?
Yeah.
You should have told me.
Why do you want to avoid Yana-san so badly?
It's not that I want to avoid him.
I mean, you might have heard from
Yanagisawa Mitsuo, but...
He treated me to dinner a few times over summer break.
Yeah, I know about that.
I saw him a few times working at the club,
and I thought it'd be fun to spend time with a younger guy now and then.
But one day, I suddenly wondered, "Why?"
Why what?
Why did he seem so happy having dinner with me?
Maybe I'm being self-conscious, but...
Heck, it doesn't matter what you think of me.
I felt like Yanagisawa Mitsuo saw me as something really precious.
I guess it was kind of scary.
Scary?
A big, sweet, pedigreed dog of a guy like him?
Well, I couldn't tell what about me he was interested in.
If it was a fantasy, a misunderstanding, or an assumption...
There's no way to tell.
Maybe he just likes you because you're attractive.
That's not possible.
He's got a prettier face than mine,
and I don't think I've shown him enough of my personality for him to fall in love with me.
Besides, I don't want him to think he knows me after spending so little time with me.
So, I thought I'd keep my distance for a while.
Then, today...
Kouko and I brought him to the club.
It really threw me off.
Anyway, why didn't you tell me?
I'll start by killing you.
Then... I'll send Kouko after you.
That's what I was thinking during practice.
I distinctly felt that.
But I'm just taking out my anger on you.
I'm sorry about kicking you in the butt earlier.
Did it hurt?
No, I'm totally fine.
Man, I'm hopeless.
Why do I always get so weird?
So basically,
you're actually kind of interested in Yana-san.
Hold up.
I'm really pissed at you right now.
Why are you making that face?
Just because you have a girlfriend, you think you can say whatever you want?
Ow! I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
You and Kouko-chan seem to be getting along as well as ever.
Was she lonely while you were in Shizuoka?
Yeah, she was.
Oh, right.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
You did?
What is it?
My mom gave me her ring.
Her ring?
She told me to give it to my girlfriend.
If I'm going to give it to her,
I thought I'd wait for the right situation.
I haven't found the right time.
Is that the ring you were supposed to give me?
What?!
I'm kidding.
Hey!
Ow! I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry!
I can't believe you.
But your mom must be happy.
You've got a girlfriend out here, and you're doing well.
I hope I am.
What?
Of course you are.
Have some confidence in yourself.
But I haven't been able to tell my friends yet.
About my past... including you.
Yanagisawa Mitsuo doesn't know about us either, does he?
I'm not trying to hide it.
But you didn't say anything, either.
I wouldn't want him to feel weirdly about you, too.
Don't worry about me.
Tell him.
Tell him everything.
Everything, huh?
Guess that's impossible.
Um...
Oka-chan.
What are you doing out so late?
Are you Linda-senpai?
Yeah. Are you Banri's friend?
Yes.
My name's Oka Chinami.
Banri, do you have a minute?
Sure...
I'll head back, then.
Oka-chan, I hope we can talk sometime.
Yes. I'd love to.
Oka-chan, what's wrong?
I was helping some upperclassmen from the film club.
Anyway, Banri, what was that about?
What?
It's not right.
Why are you so close with Linda-senpai?
Wh-why?
We're in the same club, and we have a lot in common...
Well, stop.
That's the girl Yana-san likes.
It's not right for you to be so close to her.
Wait, sorry...
Don't you think you're acting a little weird?
There's no reason for you to be so upset.
You're the weird one!
Besides, I think Kaga-san would feel bad if she saw you two just now.
Don't you feel bad for Kaga-san?
You're the worst.
You're wrong, I'm telling you you're wrong
Ah, you still don't notice, huh?
Though I've wanted to touch that arm for the past two or three hours
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
The urge to scream is so great that, look, I can't stand it
So why, why won't you notice even a little?
Are you really, really in love with me?
I don't need words of flattery
Love me semi-eternally
After 5,000 years or so, I won't be interested
I'm not endless
I will die someday
Being told "I'll love you forever" won't make me happy
First, think only that
You'll love me till I die
His Chasm
Kouko, what's wrong?
W-we'll finally climb the ste-sto-stairs to adulthood...
Don't worry.
It's only a little sour.
This is...! The spice...! Of love...!
Banri, smooch!
I... I'll have some of that spice!