When Kaga-san and I were lost in the mountains,
Linda-senpai happened to show up and help us.
Linda-senpai had come to the university's seminar house
for an overnight trip with the festival club.
We had somehow ended up near the seminar house.
Blackout
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
Tada Banri!
I'm glad you're okay.
I was so worried about what might've happened to you and Kaga-san, Banri!
I was relieved to hear from you.
Sorry to make you worry.
I'm so glad you're all right!
Tada-kun!
Banri.
Yana-san, Oka-chan.
I see.
So you went on the same trip with them.
It sounded like a rough time.
It was.
I couldn't stop worrying about Banri and Kaga-san.
I was worried, too.
I texted you and Kouko a few times, but you didn't answer.
You texted Kaga-san?
I couldn't help worrying.
We're old friends.
I see.
I'm sure Kaga-san must have been overjoyed.
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
An overnight trip?
You sure you'll be okay?
Well, I've got class. I'm going to go.
Bye bye, 2D-kun!
Sure, see you later.
Kaga-san did a lot of introspection.
She said she's done a lot of things to make you hate her.
Ah... youth.
Hey, Chinami, don't you have class?
Nope! I'm free until this afternoon!
Hang out with us, then.
All right!
What are you doing, Mitsuo?
How is that your business?
K-Kaga-san.
It is my business.
I don't want my boyfriend speaking to other girls.
I'm not your boyfriend.
How many times do I have to tell you that talking is cheating?
How many times do I have to tell you that I'm not your boyfriend?
I don't want you to do things I don't like.
Why are you not even hearing me?
Because I didn't ask for your opinion.
What's going on?
What is that thing?
Do you mean me?
Where are you speaking from?
M-my mouth...
Your mouth!
That voice is coming from your mouth?
How does that work?
Hey.
I don't care how mysterious creatures do what they do,
but keep your hands off Mitsuo.
That's not a request. It's an order.
Mitsuo isn't just my boyfriend.
I plan on marrying him.
It's been decided by fate.
Anyway, we live in a different world from you.
Do you understand?
I insist you understand here and now!
Kaga-san.
Stop it, Kouko.
What's your name?
O-Oka Chinami...
What kind of name is that?
I don't know what that's supposed to mean, but call yourself whatever you want.
Live however you'd like. Do what you want.
Um, my foot...
But do it in a world that has nothing to do with ours.
Don't butt in, don't get in our way, and don't come near Mitsuo.
I just wanted to warn you.
Next time, you won't get off so easily.
That's enough.
Just go.
Mitsuo, you texted me.
Thank you.
Listen, about that...
Chinami.
Banri.
Um...
I want to talk to Kaga-san about thanking the festival club.
Fine.
Kaga-san, did you really have to...
And do you really have to do that?!
Are you hiding your armpit sweat?
You realize you went too far.
You look like a toad.
Are you okay?
I think I should wipe my sweat in the bathroom.
Ten minutes.
Thanks for waiting.
Are y-
Don't ask me if I'm okay.
I'm fine.
But-
Don't "but" me.
I'm fine.
Kaga-
Don't ask me what I was doing.
Don't tell me I'm being stupid.
I know I'm dumb.
Yes, I made a huge mistake.
I made him hate me again today.
I've been doing the same thing for years.
But I couldn't stop myself.
I couldn't turn back.
After all, I'm an idiot!
I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
You wanted to thank the people from the festival club, right?
Yeah.
I texted Linda-senpai.
I thought we could go see her during lunch.
You're right.
I'll go with you.
I told the student affairs office about yesterday.
I said some weird organization had infiltrated the school.
Thank you for taking care of that.
The people who tried to recruit you have been causing problems at other schools.
They make you buy really expensive accessories and charms.
They even run pyramid schemes.
Whoa.
I'm glad you got out safely.
Thank you so much.
I'm sure this is more than a coincidence.
Why don't you join our club?
Um...
I'd like to check it out before I decide.
I understand!
Well, we'd be glad to have you.
We didn't get too many new members this year.
The festival club usually practices in that ward assembly hall.
Make sure you remember.
Don't forget, Tada Banri.
What's wrong, Tada-kun?
Nothing.
What brought that on?
I almost remembered something just now.
I brought the kids from yesterday.
Oh, good work.
Excuse us.
Thank you for yesterday.
I'm glad you're all right.
I'm the president, Koshino.
Third year.
Everyone calls him Kosshi-senpai.
As long as you're here, why don't you jump in?
We were just practicing our Awa dance.
I had no idea Awa dancing was so difficult.
Kaga-san, you looked like you were dancing the robot.
Are you joining the festival club, Tada-kun?
Hmm... It seemed fun.
I might.
I can't.
I'm not confident enough.
Besides, I intend to join the same club as Mitsuo.
Kaga-san.
I won't give up.
I'll win Mitsuo over!
I'm going home.
Thanks for everything.
Bye.
As first year law students,
Is Chinami-chan
your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional,
but she's cute.
you'll spend the next four years studying law.
Is Chinami-chan
your girlfriend?
She's three-dimensional,
but she's cute.
She's not my girlfriend yet!
It'd be nice if it worked out.
While we call it the study of law,
it actually encompasses a variety of studies.
She's more than just cute.
She's funny, has a good personality,
and she's smart.
She's everything I want!!!!
For example, there is positive law, basic law, the philosophy of law,
legal history, and comparative law.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO
ABOUT KAGA-SAN?
Fields of study are further subdivided within these categories.
Wasn't Kaga-san
a childhood friend?
As you advance in your studies,
KAGA-SAN
IS IN LOVE WITH
YANA-SAN.
you will be required to choose a specialization.
What?!
Without becoming too attached to your specialization,
I'll make it clear to Kouko!
I'll make sure she understands.
I want a serious relationship
with Chinami!!
we hope you will approach law with a broad perspective.
Laws are the rules of society, and...
Kaga-san didn't come to college once that week.
Yo!
Even when I texted her, she only told me not to worry.
Hey!
Kaga Kouko
No subject
Don't worry.
On Saturday, Kaga-san invited me out.
You must have been lonely without any contact from me for four days.
I had to prepare for something.
I intend to settle things once and for all today, too.
Listen, should I really be here?
Stay.
You're our witness.
I'm about to prove that Mitsuo and I should be together.
Sorry, but we need you to stick around.
Why is the mood so combative?
First, our birthplaces.
Kaga Household
Yanagisawa Household
This is the Kaga household.
This is the Yanagisawa household.
They're 800 meters apart and in the same school district.
Even if we had attended public school, it was highly likely we would meet.
In other words, it was inevitable that we would meet.
This is the entrance ceremony.
This is a picture of our field trip.
The sports festival, camp school, graduation.
They're all pictures of us together.
So?
We've been together since we were children.
Do you remember how I confessed my feelings for you in first grade?
You said you liked me, too.
You said you loved me and asked me to be your wife.
We were just acting for our Christmas party.
You're embellishing facts to suit yourself.
That was when I decided to marry you.
I've told you over and over,
I don't intend to marry you.
Listen, Kouko.
We've never even dated.
We played together when we were little,
but we're not kids anymore.
"I like Mister Giraffe, I like Mister Elephant, and I like Kouko-chan."
I'm past the age of saying that.
That's not true at all.
Our relationship is destined, eternal, and absolute.
I'm sick of your assumptions!
I want to go home.
There's a girl I like.
It's me, isn't it?
You met her on Monday.
Oka Chinami.
If you bother Chinami again,
I'll never forgive you.
Why?
Kaga-san.
But...
I don't understand.
Am I not special?
Who cheered you up when you cried because you didn't win a gold medal in calligraphy?
Who baked you a cake to congratulate you
when you were chosen to run in the relay race at the sports festival?
You did.
I was chosen to be the anchor for the girls, and we took first place.
I ran faster than everyone else because I thought you were watching,
and I could hear you cheering for me.
The reason I can run fast, the reason I want to be beautiful,
and the one I want to love... It's all you, Mitsuo.
I should be with you.
That's why I tried so hard to be perfect.
So why... am I not special?
Am I not important to you at all?
You're an idiot.
You've never tried to understand me.
You were always about yourself.
That's why you don't get it.
Of course you are important to me.
That's why I can't date you just for the sake of it.
You're special, but you can't be my girlfriend.
I can't think of you as my soul mate.
Even if I dated you out of pity,
I don't think it would make you happy.
If I'm important...
If I'm special, how is that different from loving me?
Can't that be part of loving me?
Can't you...
...fall in love with me and marry me?
Is it because of everything I've done to make you hate me?
Do all our memories count for nothing?
If that's the case...
Kaga-san.
I don't need you anymore!
Forget everything!
Act like it never happened!
If there's no fixing it, just forget everything!
What have I done?
I'm sorry, Tada-kun.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Kaga-san?
I'm sorry!
The old Tada Banri disappeared from this world.
It's okay, Kaga-san.
I'm sorry.
It's really okay.
You don't need to worry about me now.
I'm sorry, Tada-kun.
Kaga-san, we should get going.
I want to die.
Kaga-san...
Here.
I'm performing in that concert tonight at nine.
If you're going to die, die by music.
Um, who are you?
I'm NANA.
What? NANA?
Come and die.
I will.
Hey, are you really going?
If I can't be perfect, I'm better off falling apart completely.
But...
You don't need to come with me, Tada-kun.
I'm going with you.
Thank you.
I'm falling apart!
Kaga-san!
Mitsuo's a moron!
I'm going to die!
Don't screw with me!
Ow...
Take her away.
This stage is mine.
Kaga-san, are you okay?
I can't move.
Oh, wow.
This room is filthy.
Kaga-san.
You heard what Mitsuo said.
He won't date me because it wouldn't make me happy.
When he said that,
I realized I've never thought about Mitsuo's happiness.
I've just been telling him
I love him and pursuing him.
I just wanted to do things according to my plan.
If the person you love doesn't love you back,
you're worthless.
That's what I told myself.
I only insisted Mitsuo love me, accept me, and not reject me
because I was forcing that conviction on him.
Took me long enough to notice, huh?
I think everyone's like that to some extent.
Really? Even you, Tada-kun?
Accepting the new me that everyone rejects is really difficult for me.
I mean, my amnesia...
When I'm with my family,
I can tell.
They're waiting for the old me, the real Tada Banri, to return.
The personality that disappeared might simply come back one day.
If that happens, my current self will vanish.
But that would make everyone happy, right?
If I stay the way I am,
everyone will continue to be disappointed.
I...
I'm not disappointed.
What?
I'm not.
I'll never be disappointed.
After all, if you disappear,
who am I supposed to share my disgraceful self with tonight?
There's no one else.
There's only you, Tada-kun.
So don't disappear.
I...
I know I'm an idiot, but...
Don't forget about me.
I won't forget.
There's no way I'd forget.
Because... I...
I like you, Kaga-san.
I like you, Kaga Kouko.
I really do.
But, it's not fair for me to confess to you now, is it?
Sorry.
I won't ask you to forget, though.
Anyway, tomorrow...
T-tomorrow?
Wh-what's happening tomorrow?
We left our bags in a locker.
O-our bags?
We're always running away without our bags, aren't we?
You're right.
I actually enjoy it, though.
It seems everything turns out fine no matter what I leave behind.
I seem to be surprisingly strong.
You know, I lost my shoes again.
I'm going to go.
Do you know the way?
Should I go with you?
No, I'll be fine by myself.
Besides, I don't want you to see how I look now.
You can use my sandals.
Thanks.
Kaga Kouko
Worrying about rejection may be the same as rejecting yourself.
No subject
Worrying about
rejection may be
the same as
rejecting yourself.
I'm home.
What are you doing?
I didn't have anything to do, so I came home.
You did what?
If you're coming home, you should have called.
Are you hungry?
Do you want something to eat?
Yeah, sure.
Tada Banri in high school...
Tada
Banri
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
What? What is this?
Linda-senpai?
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
Make sure you remember.
Don't forget, Tada Banri.
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
Body and Soul
Mitsuo here.
Despite everything,
Kouko's my childhood friend,
and I worry about her sometimes.
Hey, wait! Kouko!
Back to your house! Your house!
Not that way!