Congratulations!
Springtime
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even if it's the long way around
No, no, no, no...!
Fukurai University Entrance Ceremony
Excuse me. I'm Tada Banri of the law school.
And I'm late!
Show me your student ID.
And tell me why you were late.
I'm not used to living in Tokyo, so I got lost...
I got on the wrong train, and when I finally reached the station,
I couldn't find the exit and was running in circles...
Student ID
Name: Tada Banri
Affiliation: Fukurai Private University
Law School
That concludes this year's entrance ceremony.
New students, please head to your department's building for orientation.
What...?
This spring, I moved from my home in Shizuoka to Tokyo.
I made my long-anticipated college debut,
Tokyo debut, and solitary living debut...
But I started it all by being late to the entrance ceremony.
I wonder if I can really do this...
A lot of parents are here...
So we head to the college now?
It's one stop away on the subway, or a fifteen-minute walk...
How should we get to the college?
Want to take the train?
Won't the subway be crowded?
It's not that far if we take a shortcut. Let's walk.
You're right. I'm in!
Hey, have you decided which club you're joining?
No, not yet...
Me neither.
I wonder what kinds of clubs there are.
Even I think I'm being suspicious.
It's so hot today.
Want to get some ice cream?
I think there's a convenience store up ahead.
Seriously?!
Excuse me.
Who is that?
Keiko.
She said, "let's meet in front of the college."
What? We'd better hurry, then.
Thanks for waiting.
Oh, go ahead. We're not buying anything.
Huh?
She said she'll be there in five minutes.
Let's hurry.
But...
Wait...
That will be 150 yen.
Huh? Oh... um...
What the heck?
Huh?
Are you a law school student?
Yeah.
Actually, I don't know the way to the college...
Same here.
"I followed those girls because they seemed to know the way,
but they went into the convenience store..."
"I thought I'd better follow them, and bought ice cream, too..."
I'm Tada Banri.
You can call me Banri.
I'm Yanagisawa Mitsuo.
You can call me Mitsuo or Yana or whatever.
You from Tokyo?
Shizuoka.
What about you... Yana... Yana-san?
Tokyo.
I'm living on my own, though.
Me, too!
Looks like this is the right way.
This must be the building.
You know... I was late this morning.
I didn't have anyone to talk to until just now, so I was kinda discouraged.
It seemed like other people were already making friends,
so I felt even more alone.
Me, too.
I attended the same university affiliate since elementary school,
so I've never felt so out of place before.
An affiliate? To a different university?
Yeah, from elementary to high school. Dainohara's.
You're kidding!
That's a really prestigious school!
Why did you come to this college?
You definitely should've kept riding the escalator there!
Was there some reason...
Yeah, well...
Sorry! I shouldn't be asking someone
I just met so many insensitive questions.
Not at all. It's fine.
It's just a long story...
The short version is,
I got into some trouble with the opposite sex...
The opposite sex?
I just got sick of people living in narrow worlds.
I wanted to turn over a new leaf in a new environment in college.
Huh...
So basically, you had an argument with your girlfriend...?
She wasn't... my girlfriend.
She was, well...
a disaster...
Yeah, like a calamity...
A calamity...?
Congratulations.
You're a college student now, Mitsuo.
I removed the thorns.
You're an idiot, Mitsuo.
Did you think you could run away from me?
You'll be mine forever, Mitsuo.
Yana-san, hang in there!
Who was that? What was that about?
A lovers' quarrel right in front of the college?
That guy with the roses is a new student.
What is he doing right after the entrance ceremony?
It's over.
My college life ended on its first day...
Hey, Yana-san!
Um...
Here. Take one if you like.
Huh? Is this for me?
Take one, take one!
Th-thank you...
What are you doing?
I thought we might be able to play it off like this.
Oh, here.
Take one. There's plenty more.
Take two.
Thanks. I'll do it, too.
Take one.
They're free.
We're handing out roses.
Take one.
In college, you have mandatory courses and electives.
In law school, many electives will be available to you starting from your first year,
so be sure to choose carefully.
Please turn to the first page of your documents.
Kaga Kouko?
Your mandatory courses are general education courses and physical education.
Yeah,
we've known each other since we were kids.
Even if you have enough elective credits,
Her dad runs a huge hospital.
if you do not have sufficient credits from mandatory courses,
He knows my parents.
you will not be able to move up or graduate.
Heiress of a big hospital, huh?
Because of this, we strongly recommend you take as many credits as you can in your first two years.
We attended the same schools from kindergarten to high school,
we were supposed to attend the same college...
In general, your deadlines for reports and papers will be stricter than they were in high school,
So you came to this university because you didn't want that?
so be sure to turn things in on time.
I'm arguing with my parents.
Yeah. And because of that,
Mandatory courses have already been scheduled,
They won't send me any money, and I'm having all kinds of trouble.
but electives will be scheduled according to the academic programs you set for yourselves.
You must have really wanted to get away from Kaga-san...
Terrifyingly enough,
she decided we'd get married
when we were kids.
We have also distributed documents explaining the courses,
Without consulting me! On her own!
so please consult them when considering which classes to take.
That just sounds like a typical romantic story to me...
Additionally, the registration period is at the beginning of the term, and each class will hold guidance sessions.
You don't understand!
You don't understand at all!
You saw what happened earlier, didn't you?
Just because I wouldn't go to college with her,
You may attend these freely.
she's the kind of girl who'll wait for me at my entrance ceremony
Class sizes are limited,
so she can slap me in the face with roses.
and students are sometimes unable to take the courses they want due to over-enrollment.
She really is a calamity...
I don't know about a calamity...
Kouko has her own perfect plan.
In these cases, students who registered first are given priority,
so we recommend you sign up for courses you wish to take early.
The only reason she attaches herself to me
is because she wants her life to go according to that plan.
If I try to do anything...
However, if you sign up for too many courses in an attempt to take as many credits as possible,
"Mitsuo, that's wrong!"
"Mitsuo, that's not in my plan!"
you will experience great difficulty during exams and when reports are due,
"Mitsuo, do as I say!"
leading to problems acquiring your credits, so please be careful...
"Mitsuo, blah blah blah blah!"
"Mitsuo, blah blah blah!"
"Mitsuo, blah blah blah blah BLAH!"
It's like that.
What? She wasn't like that.
She was more like...
"I removed the thorns!"
Like that.
You're wrong!
"Mitsuo, do blah blah blah!"
"Mitsuo, don't do blah blah blah!"
"Mitsuo, don't you think blah blah blah?!"
She's like that!
What? She's not like that!
You two!
Stop chatting!
Unbelievable.
This concludes your orientation.
Starting today, be sure to act with the awareness that you are students of this department.
That's all!
Kaga...
Kouko-san...
What are you doing here?!
What's going on?!
What are you doing in this university...
...in this department...
...in this orientation?!
Those are the guys who were handing out roses.
They're standing out a lot on their first day...
Yana-san, you're being too loud!
I'm conforming to your desires, Mitsuo.
I'm attending this university, as well.
My, you look so happy.
We'll be able to study together for four more years.
Wh-what about your plan?
According to your life plan,
weren't you going to stay on the escalator,
study French literature, and spend your third year studying abroad in France?
Then you would build a career in fashion...
It's true I did need to make some modifications.
But it was no big deal.
If I don't enjoy my college life with you,
Mitsuo, there's no point.
How did you know I applied to this school?
You know my father makes donations to various universities, don't you?
It was easy enough to figure out where you wanted to go using my connections.
Mitsuo, aren't you happy that I'm so devoted to you?
I'm not happy...
You're happy, aren't you?
I'm not happy at all.
But you're actually happy, aren't you?
I SAID I'M NOT HAPPY!
I applied to a different school to get away from you,
and now it's all ruined!
Don't let it bother you.
Mitsuo is one of those famous types.
Tsu-
Tsun-
Tsunde-
Tsundere.
Are you Mitsuo's new friend?
Um... ah... I'm Tada!
I'm from Shizuoka, and I just met Yana-san.
I'm Kaga Kouko.
Nice to meet you.
Wait, Mitsuo!
Hey, Yana-san! Kaga-san!
Oops...
Let me help you pick those up.
Huh? Uh, thanks...
Is she really a college student?
Were those your friends? That was pretty crazy.
Yeah...
It certainly was.
They're both so beautiful!
Oh, that's what you meant?
I wonder if they'll be friends with me.
Looking at pretty people makes me happy.
Whether they're boys or girls.
Really? I guess Yana-san's pretty handsome...
I guess she's a little unusual.
I'm Oka Chinami!
I'm Tada Banri.
Hey, Chinami!
See you, Tada-kun, I hope we can be friends!
Me, too.
See you later!
What's up? Who was that?
That's Tada-kun! We're friends!
Friends, huh...
Shogi Club
Tea
Ceremony
Club
Wrestling Club
Daytime Napping
Association
You, there!
Congratulations on your admission!
I can't, I can't!
Are you interested in comedy?!
We put on student shows!
We are the glee club!
You look like you enjoy sleeping outdoors!
The outdoor club's this way!
We're the tea club!
We're especially recruiting boys!
Drink some, drink some. Drink, drink, drink.
O-okay.
Way to drink!
Amazing!
That was so bitter...
Hey, you. Would you like to join the Latin music club?
No, I'm not...
You won't get away that easily.
If you want to run, you'll have to get past us.
Come on, come on. What's wrong?
Ouch...
Are you okay?
Oh, sorr-
Ow...
Sorry. Was I too rough?
N-no... Um, thank you.
Are you a first year?
Uh, yes. I'm Tada Banri from the law school.
I'm Linda.
"Linda"?
My actual name is Hayashida
It's written as "forest" and "rice field."
But "forest" is also written as "Rin," hence Linda.
The club recruitment is a war zone.
I always carry these just for that.
I'm sorry. Really, I am.
It's fine. It's a senpai's job to look after younger students.
Linda-senpai, which club are you in?
I'm in the festival club.
But I won't try to force you to join, so don't worry.
This must be more than a coincidence.
If you ever need anything, you can come talk to me.
I'm in the law school, too.
See you later.
Excuse me...
Your lipstick... It's beautiful.
I'm in Tokyo... I'm really here...
I feel like I can be reborn as a new person here.
I can meet new friends,
TADA
stay in a new place,
and live in a new world.
It's so much fun, and I'm so happy and satisfied.
Even if I'm sad or lonely or make mistakes,
everything shines like gold.
I feel like I can lead a blindingly bright life.
If I keep living life like that,
I'll probably fall in love eventually.
I want to fall in love...
I want to feel like I could give my whole heart to someone.
I wonder if I can have that...
If I can have that love...
Oh, you're that boy from earlier.
Um...
T-Tada Banri.
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for Mitsuo.
He should come by this way.
Why don't you just call him?
He won't answer his phone.
Mitsuo's never honest with himself...
But that's what makes him cute.
Hello?
Banri? Sorry about earlier.
Where are you?
I'm still at the university.
Listen, about those documents I threw...
Oh, those. I...
Huh?
Mitsuo! You're still at school?!
Kouko?! What are you doing there?!
I'm heading there now! Don't run!
I need to talk to you!
Wh-what?
I'm sorry.
I forgot to return your phone.
Thank you. I hope we can continue to be friends.
Sure!
Goodbye.
Mitsuo, I'm coming!
Received Call:
Hospital
I shouldn't have said I'd wait...
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
Lonely Girl
You're so stupid, Mitsuo.
I would never say, "Blah blah blah blah."
I found Mitsuo! Wait, Mitsuo!
Blah blah blah blah blah!