All right! I'm better now.
Good morning, Tada-kun.
Good morning, Kaga-san.
"Roboko"?
Yes, Roboko.
People have been calling me that lately at the festival club.
You know, because I look like I'm dancing the robot.
Ah... yeah, it's true. Your Awa dance is like this.
What?
I'm not that bad.
I was holding back quite a bit with my impression, too...
Once summer break starts, there's the Awa dance festival.
And...
And the beach. Right?
Kaga-san...
Thanks to Kaga-san coming to see me every day,
my injury has mostly healed.
But...
I still can't ask her about the missing photo.
Did Kaga-san find out that Linda and I used to know each other?
And... that I still have feelings...
Trouble Party
...for Linda?
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even if it's the long way around
Hey, Banri, Roboko.
President, come on!
Now, now.
He calls you that with love.
Hey, Tada Banri, has your fever gone down?
Yeah...
Thanks to you guys, I'm back to normal.
Thank you for everything you and Nana-senpai have done.
Tada-kun scarfed down his oyakodon at lunch today.
He's doing fine.
Right?
Um... Don't say that in front of others.
Annoying.
So annoying.
Fine. Yeah, yeah.
Stop feeling sorry for yourselves.
Let me explain the festival we'll be participating in over summer break.
Here.
Thank you.
AWA DANCE
Make sure you're aware of the date and time,
as well as your costumes, clogs and accessories.
We actually only have two more days to practice together.
What?!
I couldn't reserve this room.
Even if we're not that great, don't worry about it.
I'm sure Linda and I will stand out, though.
Stand out?
What do you mean?
Kosshi-senpai and I are going to be at the front.
Our outfits are fancier than yours.
That's great!
Your dancing is beautiful.
I'm sure it'll be wonderful.
Want to switch with me?
Let's do our best, Linda.
Yeah.
What am I worried about?
I don't have any reason or right to feel jealous, no matter who Linda-senpai is friendly with.
All right, dismissed!
If you're unsure of your dancing, practice on your own.
That's all!
See you guys!
Tada-kun, let's go to a café.
I'll treat you to celebrate your recovery.
Ah... Sorry, you go on ahead.
I need to talk to the seniors.
Um, Kosshi-senpai...
What's up, Tada Banri?
Ah... there's something I want to ask you.
Do you have a minute?
What's wrong?
Um, my girlfriend...
You mean Roboko?
I promised I'd take her to the beach,
but I'm not from the area, so I don't know where to go.
Oh... is that right?
Ow, ow, ow!
First, spray Roboko with an anti-corrosive so the salty breeze doesn't make her rust.
Are you staying overnight? Huh?
One night, huh?
Why would you say that?!
Of course you'd want to stay.
Going to the beach makes your hair and skin all gunky.
Those beach house showers aren't enough for two young bodies.
She's likely to say she wants to take a bath, or that she's tired.
That's what overnight facilities are for.
And that's your chance!
That's not what I wanted to ask!
I wanted to know where I should go, and what train I should take.
Huh?
You're taking the train?
Don't you have a license?
A car?
No, neither.
Going to the beach by train is hard.
Yeah.
It's fine if you're going with guys, or with some normal, active girl.
But taking a classy girl who wears heels all the time on a train
where she might not even get to sit...
You can't do that in college.
It'd be torture for Roboko.
Actually, show her what it really means to date an ordinary guy.
She might end up saying,
"Roboko can't take this! It's too much!"
Don't you have any money?
Huh?
Of course I don't.
Maybe you should start by making some, then.
You're not working, right?
No.
You really should be.
Without money, you can't go anywhere.
If you let a pretty girl like her go, you'll never meet one like her again.
Work like your life depends on it!
You don't give the impression that you're working very hard.
Oh, I was thinking the same thing.
You might think you're working hard,
but there's no point if you don't show her that.
You've got to show her you're a man sometimes.
Right, Tada Banri?
No.
No?
No way. You can't get a job.
Yeah, but...
No way! I wouldn't get to see you as much.
Absolutely not.
I'll never allow it.
No way.
But I need money before
I can take you to the beach.
I'll pay for myself.
No, I don't even have my own spending money.
I think it's normal for students to work part-time.
I'm not working.
But you're from a rich family.
Let's do this, then.
I'll take you to the beach.
That's fine, right?
That solves it, doesn't it?
Are you saying you'll pay for me?
Ahem...
Do you actually understand, Tada-kun?
U-understand what?
I want to see you more.
Do you understand that?
I want to spend a lot more time with you!
But I don't want you to think I'm annoying, so I'm holding myself back.
I'm actually pretty desperate.
You are?
When you're away, I always wonder what you're doing and thinking.
The truth is, I wish I could be with you 24 hours a day.
The things you see, hear, eat, feel...
I want to know everything.
I want to share it all.
Everything, completely.
But I know I'm awkward, overbearing, and annoying when I'm like that.
I know it's stalker-like and scary.
I've learned, haven't I?
You're right.
So if you work, I won't be able to hold myself back anymore.
What?
It makes me wish you were smaller.
About this size.
Then I could keep you with me all the time!
I'd feed you, put you to bed, change your clothes,
hide you from sight to protect you,
and keep you in my bag so no one could steal you!
Ultimately, I'd put you on a sushi roll and eat you up.
What?!
This is a shocking development...
Ah! You're flirting while it's still light out!
Miss Ultrasonic!
What are you doing here?
I saw you as I was walking by.
I heard from Yana.
Your injury must have been awful.
Thanks.
I'm fine now, though.
Tada-kun, let's go.
Miss Ultrasonic's exuding an extremely perverted aura.
I never thought I'd hear the words "extremely perverted" from your mouth...
Oh, I've gotta get to work, anyway.
See?
Oka-chan works, too.
Everyone does it.
Huh?
Well...
I'm thinking of working part-time, but Kaga-san won't let me.
What?
It's normal to work.
In fact, we're looking for part-timers at my job right now.
Do you want an interview?
What?
What? Seriously?
Really, really.
It's a café in Daikanyama.
Daikanyama...
...café?
This burlywood sofa is just like the one in my studio.
Really? Sounds nice.
Well, Banri?
It's a nice place, right?
Yeah, it is.
Excuse me.
Coming!
I'll see you later.
Tada-kun.
You definitely can't work.
What?
Um, thanks to you, I'm feeling better.
I thought I'd pay you back for the taxi.
Oh.
Bye.
A-also...
What?
I'd like you to have these.
They're cookies from a café I went to today.
I'll take those.
They'll be my dinner.
Um...
You're just having those cookies for dinner?
Got a problem with that?
I should've brought you a real meal.
Like bread or a boxed lunch.
I don't want you feeding me.
Of course you don't.
Is that funny?
Sorry...
Is that better now?
Ah... I'm fine.
I'm still taking my medicine, though.
Really, thank you.
If you hadn't helped me,
I really would've been in distress.
Make sure you thank Linda.
You owe her, too.
What's with the face?
Something wrong with Linda?
Ah! No, nothing!
Um... well...
I'm kinda broke right now...
You can pay me another time.
Huh?
No, no, no, no.
That's not why I said that.
I'm looking for work now.
Work?
Yes.
This weekend...
I know a job where you can earn a ton in one night.
Wanna be a waiter at a party?
That sounds great.
Is there an interview?
With my introduction, you'll be fine.
There's one condition, though.
Condition?
Can you bring Yanagisawa?
He's pretty good-looking, right?
A job?
Yeah. Want to join me?
I heard it's pretty good money.
Really...
Nana-senpai said something curious, though.
The job might be too much for you.
What do you think that meant?
It better not be some sketchy job!
Something illegal or for adults only.
Hey!
It's Tada Banri and the hot sumo wrestler.
So, you're looking for part-time work?
Sao-chan Senpai and...
Shi-chan Senpai.
Want us to get you a job?
There's really well-paying work through the tea club.
Wholesome and healthy manual labor.
Our male members work daily, morning to night, drenched in sweat.
You'll stay in the mountains with fresh, clean air.
As an added bonus, you'll feel like you're on a trip.
However, you'll have to join the tea club.
It's 70-30, with 70 going to us.
Anyway, sign here.
Sign, sign! Sign here!
Contract
There's no way that's decent work.
We're fine.
We've already found jobs.
Bye.
Hey! Don't run!
If you don't like the mountains, there's a beach option, too!
That was close.
They always try to capture us at every chance they get.
I'll do Nana-senpai's job.
Anything's better than whatever the tea club's offering.
Got it.
Oh, one more thing.
Huh?
Don't tell Kaga-san.
Hey.
Did you get any sleep?
I tried, but I couldn't.
Me neither.
New Message
Kaga Kouko
Nana-senpai?
Kaga-san.
Give me a minute.
She gets mad if I don't respond right away.
Oh, I can imagine.
She wanted to come over today,
but I finally got out of it by saying
I wanted to focus on my report.
Let's see...
Currently writing my report...
Kaga Kouko
No subject
Currently writing my
report. May not be able
to respond for a while.
May not be able to respond for a while...
Sending Message
Kouko's clinginess is annoying, isn't it?
Actually, I don't mind it that much.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Kouko's lucky she met you.
Why?
Because, you know...
Not many people would accept her overflowing stalker tendencies.
I love Kaga-san.
I really love her, so it's fine.
You're gushing about your girlfriend again.
It's so gross when you do that.
I want to go back to Linda.
There's a part of myself that feels that way.
Because I feel guilty over that, I can forgive or endure anything Kaga-san does.
If that's how I feel, I must be pretty awful.
Whoa...
This is my second time here.
Seriously?
You're Yanagisawa, huh?
Nana-senpai!
Nice to meet you.
I look forward to working with you.
You pass.
Let's go.
So! Which'll it be?
Choose quickly and put it on.
Are you ready?
Yes, ready!
Ugly!
What?
But kind of sexy, too.
U-um, no one's really told us yet.
What's happening today?
A birthday party.
What?
It's my friend's birthday party.
She rented out this place for a masquerade.
I'm running it and paying for it,
so I can't have you wearing half-assed costumes!
So, which'll it be?
I really can't decide.
Damn it.
I never thought the day would come when I'd have to worry about this...
By the way, if you wear this one,
I'll pay you ten thousand extra.
If you can't decide, why don't you choose that one?
They're both embarrassing anyway.
I'm surprised you're not embarrassed.
I'm a little impressed.
I'm used to it.
I've accepted who I am.
Now, Yana-san, get changed.
The party's about to start.
Got it.
I'm ready.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Thank you for coming to my dear friend Tesshi-chan's birthday!
I've pumped this party full of love and passion!
I'm gonna make you fall in love, so be ready!
Do we have to keep this up all night?
It'll be fine.
You look fantastic, Yana-san.
If Chinami saw me like this, I might die.
Oka-chan would probably accept it.
She'd laugh and say she wants to film you with the Okamera.
No way, no way, no way!
I couldn't take it!
Anyway, could you let Kouko see you like that?
I don't think Kaga-san would be opposed to this.
I'd be able to show her.
Seriously?
You really are amazing.
Well, I can't have her finding out I'm working, though.
Move your bodies, not your mouths.
Y-yes, sir!
Yanagisawa-kun, come here.
Entertain the guests.
Wh-wha-
Good luck, Yana-san.
He's so strong!
I see you've changed, Tada Banri.
Huh?
You're Nana-senpai, right?
Who did you think I was?
Anyway, you look ridiculous.
You look pretty crazy, too.
Are you supposed to be a devil?
Apparently.
A devil twin.
Twin?
Hey, Little Sister.
Come here.
Banri!
Linda-senpai?
What are you doing here?
And why are you dressed like that?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
No one told me Linda-senpai would be working here.
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Well, not that it matters.
Nana-chan, come here.
Okay.
Work hard.
Don't look at me like that.
No, no, no. Don't stare at me, Linda-senpai.
You two!
Stop playing around and get back to work!
Yes, sir!
Kaga Kouko
Incoming Call
Calling...
You are being connected to an answering service.
Please leave your message after the tone.
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
Don't Look Back
Sao-chan here!
Shi-chan here!
The tea club is recruiting strong young men
to work like horses for our female members.
You, there!
Why don't you join the tea club?!
And have a good gag ready!
Hissss!