The night I returned home from the Awa dance festival,
I still hadn't collected my thoughts.
For a moment, my consciousness had rewound to the day after graduation.
It felt as if the world I'd been living in until now was a dream,
and I'd just woken up.
As if the person I am now was a lie.
Could... my memory be returning?
Will my current self disappear?
Will I have to start over from the day after graduation?
If that happens... my current consciousness, my current mind...
will disappear soon.
Without anyone knowing.
I'll Be Back
Before I can even say anything.
Ah, if we could meet in a dream, could I say it?
Say, if sadness alone floats down from the sky
If that kind of voice pains you even now
Even if, off to the side, our hands are placed on each other's
This memory wouldn't fade, but...
Even if, when our eyes meet, I can't say the truth...
Your words illuminate the world more than anyone else's
Next to me, "Goodbye means I love you," you say
I can't be forthright
Though I alone sing of loneliness
I can't smile
"Thank you means I'm in love with you," you say
The world's end of love
We're not allowed in?
That's what the committee officer who lent us our costumes said.
Is this because we messed up yesterday?
We stopped dancing and put a damper on the festival.
Some of us clearly hadn't practiced enough, either.
They said they couldn't continue dealing with the Fukurai University festival club.
The other groups apparently agree.
I'm sorry!
It's my fault!
You didn't do anything wrong.
You were sick. You couldn't help it.
But...
It's our fault.
If we had practiced more...
So, if the other groups won't help us,
does that mean we won't be able to borrow costumes or music?
What about next month's school festival?
Oh, no...
But we practiced so hard for it...
But without costumes or music...
Well, why don't we do something?
I don't know what we should do, either,
but if we don't do anything at all, it'll mean the end of the festival club.
You're right.
It's too soon to give up.
Let's start by doing whatever we can!
Yeah.
He's right.
We've got to try.
Hey, this is no good, Banri.
You didn't sort your garbage.
I'll do it later. Just leave it.
Running?
Yeah... I was thinking of starting up again.
I mean, apparently, I was in the track club in high school.
What brought this on?
I can't sleep lately.
You know, the festival club's in trouble because of me, and all.
I thought I'd be able to sleep if I got some exercise.
Hey... Banri.
Isn't there some other reason you can't sleep?
Huh?
There's nothing...
You're lying!
There's nothing, really.
I'm fine.
Don't run away, Banri.
I'm not running away.
You want to run away.
I can tell that much.
It seems like you're about to run off somewhere at any moment.
That's not true!
It is!
No, it's not!
Banri...
Before I know it, maybe no one will know who I am.
Without anyone realizing it, maybe I'll just disappear.
I keep having these scary thoughts.
I still haven't told Yana-san or anyone else about myself.
Banri, is that what you're worried about?
That you haven't told everyone about yourself?
You're worried that Miss Ultrasonic doesn't understand,
and that you'll affect Mitsuo's relationship with Linda-senpai?
I haven't been able to sleep because I'm afraid.
There's nowhere for me to run... and I don't know what to do!
It's okay.
It'll be fine.
I'll make everything fine.
Leave everything to me.
After all, I'm Kaga Kouko!
Let's tell everyone.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm with you,
you could even conquer the world.
It scares me that I feel like I really could do that.
Beef!
What?
What?! What are you talking about?
I'm asking if you want to come to my place tonight for dinner!
Huh? Is something going on?
B-e-e-f is going on!
That's right!
Lady Kouko right here has...
Beef.
I received a huge chunk of Kobe beef as a gift.
Are you serious?
Kobe beef!
If they listen while eating delicious food,
they can keep calm, no matter how serious the discussion.
Nice idea!
Well, then. Mitsuo's next.
I'll contact him.
You've got class soon, don't you?
Oh, right.
See you later, then.
Okay.
Hello, Yana-san?
What are you doing?
Volunteer work?
An upperclassman in the film club asked me to gather dried leaves for a shoot.
Huh...
Okay. I'll help you.
Actually, I meant to ask if you wanted to come eat at my place.
I hope you'll come.
What?
Hold on.
I don't have a bag to put these in...
Lucky.
You thief.
That's mine.
Give it back!
Oh...
This was yours?
Sorry about that.
Are you gathering leaves, too?
I'm helping Yana.
I... I see.
Let's gather them together, then.
What are you doing?
I gathered these leaves.
They have nothing to do with you.
I never thought you'd do anything so ill-natured.
I've known for a while now.
Why are you acting like this?
You've been like this ever since that night.
I don't want to associate with people who do things behind Yana's back.
Look, just hear me out...
Over beef!
Listen while eating beef at my place tonight!
Beef?
Yeah!
There's something I really want you to know!
No!
Kouko's bringing Kobe beef!
Are you sure you want to miss that?
Are you sure you don't want to associate with me?
It's not that I'm avoiding you.
You're clearly avoiding me.
I just...
I just think...
...it was a mistake to cut my hair!
Oka-chan.
Uh... W-well, come on in.
No one else is here yet, though.
Listen...
Huh?
There might be something I want to tell you, too.
That's why I came a little early.
I wanted to talk to you before everyone else came.
That's what I meant to do, but...
Linda-senpai?
Oh.
What are you doing here?
Are you on your way to Banri's place?
What's your relationship with him?
It's super suspicious!
Huh?
What are you doing?
You want something with my guest?
Huh?
Actually, I just came to hang out with Banri's neighbor...
With this girl here. This is Nana-senpai.
What?
What's wrong, anyway?
Did something happen?
No... uh...
If you want to talk, I'll listen.
Linda-senpai was really worried about me.
Even though I jumped to conclusions and tried to pick a fight with her.
I see.
The other night, when I saw you being friendly with Linda-senpai on campus,
do you know what I thought?
Well...
That I was having an affair with the girl Yana-san loves-
No!
I was thinking, "Yes!"
"Yes"?
"Yes!"
"All right! Lucky me!"
"Now Yana will be rejected!"
"And then I..."
"I can..."
Oka-chan...
I...
I like Yana.
I realized it the moment I learned
Yana was in love with someone.
It's stupid, isn't it?
I really, really regretted it.
I actually didn't want anyone else to have him.
I pretended not to be interested,
but it was because I thought Yana would like that.
I got complacent fighting imaginary enemies, and got stuck.
The world was chugging along, tens of thousands of light years away.
But I pretended I didn't really care, and cut my hair.
After cutting it off, my appearance suddenly changed so much, and I...
Oka-chan.
I didn't understand why I was so hurt that I'd cut off the hair I'd kept long for years...
And I really, really regretted it!
I'm the one who's awful.
But instead of blaming myself, I lashed out at you.
I'm really sorry.
I know I made you feel bad.
I...
Oka-chan, that's enough.
Banri.
Will you film my face right now?
What?
I want to keep a record of how stupid I'm being right now.
So please...
There's something I've been wanting to tell you, too.
I was going to wait until everyone got here, but...
Everything, huh?
I can't do that.
Who... are you?
Huh? What?
Where am I?
What is this?
Banri, what's wrong?
Linda!
Help me!
Come quickly!
Linda!
Linda-senpai!
Linda-senpai, come quickly!
Banri... It's Banri!
What's wrong?
I don't know!
But Banri keeps asking for you!
Banri!
Linda!
Banri! What's wrong?
I don't know! I don't know!
What am I doing here?
Banri, are you okay?
Should I call Kouko-chan?
Or would you rather go to the hospital?
Kouko?
Kouko...
Oh... that's right.
I'm in college now.
This is where I live.
It's been a year and a half since then,
and I'm dating Kouko now.
If I left, Kouko would be all alone.
She'd cry.
Banri?
Don't tell Kouko.
What?
Please! Don't tell her about this!
Don't tell Kouko my memories returned!
Wait, Banri!
Please! I'm begging you!
Nana-senpai!
I don't know what's going on,
but that's what you do to someone who's lost his senses.
Banri...
Don't... Don't tell Kouko.
No...
No, no, no!
I want to live with Kouko!
I don't want to die.
I don't want to disappear.
It's fine!
I want to pretend it's fine!
So don't tell...
Banri!
Is it my turn now?
I'm going to disappear like he did.
I'll forget everything that happened in the past year and a half.
It'll be like everything I did with
Kouko never happened.
Huh? Banri?
Hey!
Banri, what's wrong with you?
You little...
Wait, Banri!
Hello?
Target found!
Banri?
You idiot, you overdid it!
But you told me to cut him off and catch him!
Are you okay, Banri?
Come on, let's sit down, okay?
I'm really sorry.
I'm fine.
There's something I wanted to tell you guys today.
I've been thinking for a while that I needed to tell you...
but I just couldn't bring it up.
I didn't want you to think I was a liar, or that I didn't trust you.
I thought up all kinds of reasons not to tell you...
But really, it's not any of that.
I couldn't tell you because I was afraid to know
how truly deep, wide, and permanent the damage was.
That doesn't make any sense, does it? Sorry.
It's fine.
Right?
Yeah, yeah! It's totally fine.
Besides, it's not as though we had no idea.
You mentioned a lot of things at the cult's overnight trip.
If it's not easy for you to say, don't force yourself.
Just skip over it for tonight.
Something terrible happened.
Something truly terrifying.
It was probably the same as dying.
I came back to life and made it this far,
but nothing is going right anymore.
I'm so scared, I can't take it.
I tried running, but all I learned was that I couldn't run from it.
I see.
Well, then, what are you afraid will happen?
I'm afraid... that I'll disappear without anyone noticing, I guess.
What do you mean, "disappear"?
If I disappear now,
I don't think anyone would be able to find me.
Hmm... I see.
Yeah, I don't really understand.
But let's do something about it, then.
All of us.
Right, Yana-san?
Sure.
I don't know what's going on, but leave it to us.
If it comes to it, we'll find you.
I don't think you'll really disappear,
and honestly, I don't really understand...
but if that's how you say it is, we have no other choice.
Right. We accept your challenge.
Anyway, you've got Kouko.
No matter where you go, she'll find you.
That's so true.
While screaming, "Banri, where are you?! I love you!"
Kaga Koko
No subject
Miss Ultrasonic told me not to ask, so I won't.
We ate all the beef together next door.
Goodnight.
You told me not to tell Kaga-san, so I didn't.
After that, Kaga-san brought the beef,
and I just told her you ran away.
What'd Kouko say?
"I see. He ran away?" That's it.
Banri?
Hey... I want you to film what
I'm about to say with the Okamera.
What?
I want to leave a record of it.
Saying that I was here, and alive.
I want our future selves to know that I lived here.
I want to leave a mark... so that I won't lose my old self again when I look back.
Sure.
Go ahead.
I'm...
My name is Tada Banri.
I don't know how much time I have.
In the next moment, I might disappear.
I may stay the way I am for ten or fifty more years.
But it won't do any good to worry about it.
I want to do what I can, while I still can.
That's what I thought.
This is the light that will help me find Kouko.
Even if I lose my way... with this light,
I know I can return to her.
If we meet again, I'm sure our love will come back to life again and again.
That's why I want her to trust me and wait for me.
No matter how many or which paths I take,
I will always return to her in the end.
That's what I was going to tell Kouko.
I can't accept that.
I can't promise a future with you.
I hadn't said anything until now, but I think this is the time.
I only came to college to follow Mitsuo, after all.
That was always my plan, from the start.
What?
Goodbye.
You're wrong, I'm telling you you're wrong
Ah, you still don't notice, huh?
Though I've wanted to touch that arm for the past two or three hours
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
The urge to scream is so great that, look, I can't stand it
So why, why won't you notice even a little?
Are you really, really in love with me?
I don't need words of flattery
Love me semi-eternally
After 5,000 years or so, I won't be interested
I'm not endless
I will die someday
Being told "I'll love you forever" won't make me happy
First, think only that
You'll love me till I die
Paradise Lost
Beef?
Real Kobe beef?
Seriously?
Kouko, right now, you're the most
awesome you've ever been!
Beef!
Beef, woo!
Wait... Didn't we miss our chance to eat Kobe beef?
Why?!