86th
FUKURAI UNIVERSITY FESTIVAL
Banri?
I'm back.
Banri.
I'm... Banri.
I... I finally made it home.
His memories returned.
Are you sure?
You won't regret this?
Hello to everyone watching
Oka-chan's co-ed diaries.
I was just dumped.
I feel really awkward.
I don't know what I should do now.
I know how you feel.
You're even in the same club.
Three, two, one...
Goodbye.
Where's Banri?
His mom and Linda-senpai took him home.
They're heading straight to a local hospital.
Does he really not remember us anymore?
Looks that way.
I can't stand this.
Banri forgot this.
It probably fell out of his luggage.
Golden Time
Aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na?
Ne, kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
Sonna koe ga kimi o ima demo kurushimete
Soba de te o kasanetemo
Kono omoi wa kienai kedo
Futari me o awasetara hontou no koto yuenakutemo
Kimi no kotoba, dare yori mo sekai o terashiteru
Tonari de kimi wa "Sayonara wa ai shiteru" tte, sou iu no
Sunao ni narenai
Watashi dake kodoku o utattemo
Egao ni narenai
"Arigato wa koi shiteru" tte sou iu no
Ai no world's end
Horai
Bridge
I'm back here again.
My name is Tada Banri.
The day after I graduated from high school,
I fell from this bridge, and apparently lost my memories.
While my memories were gone,
surprisingly, I was attending a college in Tokyo.
But now that my memories have returned,
I've forgotten everything that happened in that time.
So cold...
I should head home before I catch a cold.
What was that?
It looked like a ring.
I feel like I've lost so many important things
beneath this current.
I submitted a notice of leave of absence to my university.
I'll probably end up dropping out.
I found notes to myself in my luggage.
I ran into Linda again there.
We were in the same club.
IMPORTANT PEOPLE WHO MUST NOT BE FORGOTTEN
KAGA KOUKO = EX-GIRLFRIEND
PROMISED TO PRETEND I FORGOT EVERYTHING BETWEEN US
YANAGISAWA MITSUO A.K.A. YANA-SAN,
GOT MAD WHEN I LIED, DOESN'T LIKE ME ANYMORE
(NEED TO APOLOGIZE WHEN I SEE HIM NEXT)
I even had a girlfriend.
But she dumped me. All of this was written there.
But there's nothing I can clearly recall.
I wonder what my girlfriend looked like.
Maybe I'll find a photo or something if I look.
But I don't think there's any point in seeing the face of the girl who dumped me.
Besides, I don't remember her anyway.
Inbox
It's all spam.
Folders:
Inbox
Sent messages
Spam
Inbox
December 20th
This is from yesterday.
It's to...
From: TADA BANRI
To: KAGA KOUKO
Kaga Kouko?
I knew the name, of course.
She was the first person mentioned in my notes.
The ex-girlfriend who dumped me.
"Dear Kouko...
I'm e-mailing you again believing you'll read it.
It's almost Christmas.
I would be truly happy if we could spend Christmas together.
What do you think?
If you still have any feelings for me at all, please respond.
Don't forget the man you're destined to be with."
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What is this?
I never sent this e-mail.
Kaga Kouko: To Kouko
Kaga Kouko: Don't forget me
Kaga Kouko: Destined to love each other
Kaga Kouko: Please message me back
Kaga Kouko: Awaiting your response
Kaga Kouko: I'm really worried
What?!
Gross!
No responses from Kaga Kouko.
"I don't know who you are, but stop sending out e-mails.
You're a nuisance."
He's pretending to be me and trying to get back with a girlfriend I don't remember.
It makes no sense.
From: Tada Banri
To: Me
I won't stop.
You broke your promise first.
Christmas passed, and Linda came home.
Oh, my.
It's good to see you again!
Banri, Linda-chan's here!
Things got busy, and I forgot about the e-mails.
Hey!
Hey.
And then...
It's been a while.
Horai
Bridge
...the last day of the year arrived.
Are you sure you should be here on New Year's Eve?
It's fine.
I don't want to help clean the house, anyway.
Hey, is the Tada family pounding mochi this year?
Yeah, we are.
My dad's been getting stuff ready.
Your dad's going all-out, huh?
All right! I'll come eat some.
I still love Linda.
My feelings haven't changed since the day
I waited for her on that bridge.
But Linda hasn't changed, either.
What?
Oh, nothing.
If you're coming over to eat,
I'll tell my parents to make extra.
Tell them Linda-chan's looking forward to the ones with red bean paste.
Because Linda-chan puts toasted mochi with red bean paste in her New Year's soup.
I don't know what happened between us
while my memories were gone,
and Linda won't tell me anything.
I do that, too.
In fact, isn't that normal?
Lots of people find it gross.
I'm still waiting on the bridge for her answer.
What?
My family loads ours with seaweed and stock powder.
maintaining this balance.
She leaves me in the middle of the bridge,
You're kidding.
Even I think that's gross.
Why?
Maybe that's Linda's answer in itself.
Ack, that's sour!
Maybe that's Linda's answer in and of itself.
Yes?
Hello.
It's good to see you again.
I came to return the DVD I borrowed from you.
DVD?
I know who you are!
You were in my notes!
You're her, right?
The Okamera girl!
Umm... Oka...
Oka Chinami!
You're Oka-chan, right?
Linda!
Oka-chan came from Tokyo!
It's Oka-chan!
Oka Chinami-san!
Huh? What?
Who did?
What's with that reaction?
It's good to see you again, Linda-senpai.
Don't mind me.
I'm fine with this.
I just came to return this DVD to Banri.
I'm glad you were home.
Why don't you come in?
Not that it's my house...
No, thank you.
This is all I came for.
I can see Banri's doing well.
I'm glad I came.
I have a taxi waiting for me,
so I'll be going now.
But...
Here.
It's in your hands now, Banri.
Thanks...
But...
Don't forget this.
This is yours, right?
REMEMBER
Oh... right.
I wanted to cross that bridge...
the famous wooden bridge, on my way home.
Oh, the place where I fell?
Y-yes.
How can I cross that to get home?
You can't cross by car,
so you should have a taxi let you out by the bridge.
You can ask him to pick you up on the other side.
Got it.
Thank you.
If my parents were here, we could've given you a ride.
Sorry.
They're out shopping right now.
It's fine.
I'll be leaving now.
I'm sorry I couldn't help much after you came all this way.
Thanks for the DVD.
It's fine.
I just wanted to come here.
I got to see your face again, Banri.
Well, goodbye.
Banri... look...
Oh, right.
What's up?
What are you looking for?
This isn't mine.
Banri! Where are you going?
After her!
Remember. Remember, Banri!
This is who I am.
I'm broken, shattered, not even close to perfect,
and always lacking something.
But this is who I am!
I am who I am!
So I can go after her if I want to!
Ow...
Oh, come on! Damn it!
Banri!
Here!
Don't forget these!
I must've given them to you just for this moment!
You must have!
Three, two, one...
Zero!
Go, Tada Banri!
Run!
Horai
Bridge
What's going on?
How come you can see me?
Why are you so wet?
How come you can talk to me now?
I've always been with you!
How dare you pretend not to notice?!
I couldn't help it.
You have no idea how frustrated I was!
You never listened to anything I said!
You never even noticed!
That's why I gave up on everything and decided to stay hidden.
What now?
Is this how it ends?
I can't accept this.
Now, now.
We'll all end up in the same place eventually.
As long as they're alive, everyone's present becomes the past.
I'm leaving.
Maybe I'll see you after the very end.
Banri!
Banri! Wait!
It's... "yes"!
Yes!
Linda...
It's "yes"?
It's "yes."
I love you, Banri.
I'm saying "yes" to all of you!
Really?
I'm glad I heard your answer!
I'm glad I waited all this time!
You dropped something, Tada Banri.
Later.
"Yes."
To all of you... my answer is "yes"!
It's "yes" to your love for Kouko, too!
So...
So I can say "yes" to myself, too!
I'm going!
There's something I need to take care of!
Sure! You can do it!
Kouko!
You called my name, didn't you?
I did.
You didn't forget me, did you?
It was close, though.
Then, what about our promise?
Do you remember that?
You remember, right?
You remember, don't you?
Do you remember?!
Tell me you remember.
I want you to remember.
I remember.
If I don't forget you,
we'll be together for the rest of our lives.
You know, once this promise is in effect,
it can never be broken, no matter what.
I hope not.
If you ever forget me again,
I won't show you any mercy.
I won't be nice to you.
I won't hold back like I've been doing.
I won't forgive you until you remember.
Are you still sure?
I'm sure.
It's for the rest of our lives.
I'll never leave you again.
Okay.
Banri... I love you!
Stop laughing out loud.
I love the time I spend with you.
I love who I am when I'm with you.
Banri, I...
really love you!
Whether you remember me or not.
Wherever I go, wherever I fly,
I need you to be there.
Without you, I don't know where to get off.
I need you, Banri.
I'm sorry, Banri.
I made a mistake once.
It's fine now.
I thought I just had to bear it.
I thought I was holding you back and making you suffer.
I thought you'd be free without me.
I thought you'd be able to change painlessly and naturally without me.
Yeah. I know.
But... I couldn't forget you!
Injured, scattered, and incomplete Banri.
And also... my Banri.
I want to live by your side forever.
Is that okay?
Are you really sure?
Yeah.
My heart will always look toward you.
You know, a lot happened while you were gone.
You can tell me when we get home.
Will you come to my place again?
Yes! Let's go home!
To your place!
This is yours.
What?
You're right.
This is my ring!
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
I can't stop my heart from dancing
responsible for all those e-mails.
According to Kouko, 2D-kun was
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
In an attempt to bring me back to Tokyo,
2D-kun tried to get Kouko to move first.
He learned my address and
password from my notes
while helping move my things,
and sent Kouko e-mails under my name.
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Finding your true self
Kouko didn't notice until just yesterday.
Otona ni narutte taihen de
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Yana-san and Oka-chan's protests
Kouko and 2D-kun ignored
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Maybe I can forget now
and got into a huge argument.
Yoru ga matte iru kara
The night is waiting
I abandoned Banri once at that cult's overnight trip!
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
As our hearts beat exactly in rhythm
I won't give up on him this time!
Hashagi mawareba
And if we frolic about
Isn't that what you want to do, too?
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
I nearly realize
Aren't you Kaga Kouko?
Kizuite shimaisou de
The feelings I want to tell you
Once you fall in love with someone,
in your single-minded pursuit?!
don't you go out of control and drive him crazy
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Even if we are afraid of the past and the future
Why aren't you going out of control now?!
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
You cannot move if you remain empty
That apparently got Kouko going again.
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
Film Club
Oka-chan chose to exercise her own rights.
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
If I forget all my troubles and dance the night away with you
I said she could use as she pleased.
She decided to really use the film
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
What are you going to do with that when you finish editing?
I'm sending it to Banri.
Kaga-san will be my messenger.
Owaranai Golden Time
The endless Golden Time
If you're watching this, Tada Banri,
Gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
The distance between us as you approach
Kouko is probably next to you.
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo
Neither closes nor widens
At least, that's what I'm hoping.
Taisetsu ni shitai
I'll treasure this even if it's the long way around
I sure hope she's there.
It'd be great if she is.
I've asked everyone for help,
so I know you'll be fine.
Yume miru jibun wa doko ni iru toka
I don't know where my dreaming self went
I guarantee it.
And, Kouko...
Mirai nante wakaranai
I don't know the future
Uh... No, sorry.
Aru ga mama de ikitai no!
I want to live as I am!
Forget I said that.
Tell her yourself.
Yoru wa matte kurenaindakara
Because the night will not wait
Kouko, Kouko.
Suki to kirai osorete ite mo
Love and hate, even if I'm afraid
Kokoro wa ima uso wo tsukenai
My heart cannot lie now
I'm not asleep.
Tsutaenakya never give up hajimeyou
I must tell you and never give up, so let's begin
Listen... thanks for being here.
Yeah.
Yana koto zenbu wasurete hazukashisa wo kanaguri sutetara
If I forget all my troubles and cast off all my shame
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
Hajimari wa Golden Time ano toki tsumugi atto kotoba
It begins with a Golden Time, the words we've spun together
Sora wa tashika ni eien ni mieta yume no tsuzuki ne
I am sure they were the continuation of an eternal dream
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Kore kara no koto mo
Everything going forward
Kore made no koto mo sukoshi zutsu
And everything until now, little by little
Chanto subeto wo ukeirerareru
I can learn to accept it
Shinjirareru kimi ga iru nara
I can believe, as long as I have you