This should be the right way...
Ow...
I'm Kaga Kouko.
Nice to meet you.
Lonely Girl
Kaga-san...?
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
It's been a week since I started college in Tokyo.
Kaga Kouko-san...
Hey, who's that hottie?
A first year named Kaga.
I hear her parents are filthy rich!
Oh, my.
Good morning, Kaga-san...
What were you looking at on your phone?
Pictures of Mitsuo.
These are all of Yana-san?
That's right.
Mitsuo and I have been together since we were this small.
Kindergarten, elementary school,
middle school, high school,
cram school, and calligraphy school.
We did everything together.
Mitsuo and I have always been together, and we will be forever.
That's how it should be.
Don't you agree, Takada-kun?
It's Tada.
Tada Banri.
Hey, can you get in touch with Mitsuo?
He always runs away when he sees my face.
I've been waiting for him for half an hour...
I don't know why we're attending the same university if he's going to be like this.
A-anyway, Kaga-san, have you already established your schedule?
What do you have first period?
Sports science.
Oh, really? Me, too.
I actually wanted to take the same classes as Mitsuo...
but he won't tell me anything.
So I want to use your phone again to...
Mitsuo!
Wait, Mitsuo!
Wait, Kaga-san!
He got away from me again.
L-listen, Kaga-san...
I don't think you need to chase him at full speed like that...
That's it, Takada-kun!
My name isn't Takada...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Tanaka-kun?
Your hint is: it's two syllables.
Two syllables...
Kaga-kun?
That's your own name.
Listen, if you figure out Mitsuo's schedule, will you tell me?
Oh, and his club!
Shouldn't you ask him about that yourself?
Even if I did, I'm sure he wouldn't tell me.
I want to know everything about Mitsuo.
I want to know how he's living on his own, and what company he keeps!
Yeah, but...
I won't ask you to do it for free.
I'll pay you...
...in cash!
What?
That was a joke.
Forget it.
Go ahead.
That girl's always wearing brand name stuff from head to toe.
Her parents must be rich.
Some of you may not be familiar with the term "sports science."
Sports science is...
Wow!
Your mom made some nice choices!
Look at this ramen and instant yakisoba!
Are you sure I can have these?
Yeah, she told me to share them with my friends.
Seriously?
Anyway, are you listening to me?
I'm listening.
Kouko asked you for my schedule, right?
You didn't-
No, no, no! There's no way I'd tell her!
I know you're avoiding Kaga-san.
But I've seen Kaga-san here and there this past week.
She doesn't seem to have any friends yet.
She sits alone in her classes, and she never gets to see you.
I kind of feel bad for her.
What... You're sympathizing with Kouko?
A little.
Just a little, really!
Attractive girls really do have it easy.
No matter what they do, as long as they put on a pretty face, everyone feels so bad for them.
Even in high school, no one cared about me.
They all said the same things.
"Just be glad she's so hot.
I'm jealous. I wish I were you."
They should put themselves in my shoes.
What are you talking about?
I never said any of that!
I won't tell you not to ignore Kaga-san.
That's your choice.
But feeling bad for Kaga-san is my choice, too!
Well, you have a point.
Me avoiding Kouko has nothing to do with you.
Let's not do this.
There's no point in us fighting over Kouko.
Oh...
It's almost time.
Huh? Is something happening now?
The film club's welcoming party.
Want to come with me?
Huh?
GOLDENTIME
I see! You were in a film club in high school, too?
Yes.
You'll make a great club member!
You want to be a cameraman?
Have you used one before?
I feel kinda out of place.
Just checking it out can't hurt.
Yana!
Tada-kun, you came, too.
Huh? Oka-san, you're in the film club?
There.
Hey, Chinami.
Wait, huh? You two know each other?
Since when?
We're in the same mandatory English class.
Oh, don't call me "Oka-san."
That's what people call my mom.
Note: Okaa-san ( ) means "Mother" and sounds very similar
to Oka-san ( )
Oh.
In that case, Oka... chan?
Yeah, that'll do!
So, what do you think?
Do you feel like joining the film club now?
Well, the upperclassmen seem nice.
That's what I like to hear.
What about you, Tada-kun?
Oh, I was thinking of checking out a few other clubs before I decided.
I see. Okay, okay.
Senpai, Yanagisawa-kun here has decided to join!
New first years are totally welcome!
You've got a nice face!
You can be an actor!
Thanks...
Oka-chan, you're in the film club?
Yeah. Anyway, that pretty girl who was with Yana the other day...
Oh, Kaga-san?
Yeah, Kaga-san!
I wonder if she's already joined a club.
I don't know.
I don't think she's chosen one yet.
My senpai told me the club recruiters have a hard time talking to her.
She's kind of...
Overpowering! Out of reach!
She has an aura like that.
I wish you and Kaga-san would both join the film club, too.
Well, Yana-san is avoiding Kaga-san.
Kaga-san seems to really like Yana-san, though.
Yanagisawa-kun, do you have a girlfriend?
No, not at all!
I see.
I can't explain why, but that's youth for you.
They seem to be having fun, too.
I wonder if they're throwing a welcoming party, too.
Wait, don't open that!
Beyond that door lies the realm of demons!
What?
Ta-da!
I'm Sao-chan of the tea club!
I'm Shi-chan!
Oh, it's the film club!
You're throwing your own party?
Hey, you're the new student who drank our tea on the day of the entrance ceremony.
Huh?
You can't get away from us now!
Come party with us!
Huh?
Hey, wait.
I'm not joining the tea club!
There!
Hey! Help me, Yana-san! Oka-chan!
Banri!
Tada-kun!
Don't go!
You'll get sucked in, too!
BANRI!
Tada-kun!
Go get the pitcher.
Yes!
You, pour!
Yes.
Serve up the fish!
I-immediately!
Choose a location for the after-party!
On my way!
Dance, dance!
We're out of sake!
Tea club bowling!
Roll, roll, roll, roll...
You smell so nice.
Come on! Drink up, drink up, drink up!
Oh, I don't...
Then you'll fight!
Wrestle with him! Sumo!
What?!
Come on!
Take it off, take it off, take it off!
Put on your loincloth!
Ready... fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Why is this happening?!
Like I know!
It's a tie!
Why is this happening?!
Like I know!
This is why I hate three-dimensional girls!
You're all weird, you jerks!
From now on, I'm going to live in the world of 2D!
I see!
Then from now on, you'll be 2D-kun.
Fine! Call me 2D-kun!
What about you?
What's your name?
It's T-Tada Banri...
Um, I need to go back to the film club...
Now, now.
Don't be like that.
Hang out with us.
All right! We'll party all night long!
Yeah!
I'm in Hell.
The number you are trying to reach is currently outside the service area or-
Hey, Banri.
You're alive, huh?
Yana-san...
Didn't get enough sleep?
Yeah...
I ended up going to five parties with the upperclassmen in the tea club...
Huh?
Kaga-san?
I'm going through the rear entrance.
Don't tell her you were with me.
O-okay...
Also, make sure you don't tell her
I'm joining the film club.
I won't.
I won't, but...
She waits for you every day.
You could talk to her.
It may just be a ploy to get sympathy.
You think so?
In any case, no one knows what she'll do.
You should be careful.
Later.
I can finally go home...
I'm with the social dance club.
You're a first year, right?
Have you already chosen a club?
Not yet...
Join us, then!
No, join our club!
At least come check it out!
Stop!
Sorry, but this kid's joining the festival club.
Come on, get out of here.
What, he's already been bought up?
Hey, you, have you already joined a club?
Oh... um...
Linda.
You're Tada Banri-kun from first year, right?
Yeah... Thank you for saving me again.
What's that club you mentioned earlier?
The festival club.
I'm in it.
Its formal title is the Society for the
Cultural Study of Japanese Festivals.
I see...
You can't just wander around like that.
They pounce on defenseless first years immediately.
I'm sorry. I didn't get enough sleep...
Are you not feeling well?
Should I go to the nurse's office with you?
No, you don't need to do that.
You're a really nice person.
Not really...
Hey, after this...
Kaga-san?
She's alone again...
You know her?
Is she your girlfriend?
N-no!
Kaga-san likes someone else, and she's from a wealthy family!
You might say we're too different...
I don't need to hear all of that.
Well, whatever.
See you later.
Did you see her?
What a hottie!
She looks like a model.
Isn't she the heiress of that famous major hospital?
That's a little out of our league.
I bet she'd just ignore us.
Kaga-san!
Oh! Um... Yamada-kun?
It's Tada.
Tada Banri.
I was wondering what you were doing by yourself.
Hey, do you know where Mitsuo...
Even if you did, you wouldn't tell me, would you, Tada-kun?
Or have you changed your mind?
No, I haven't.
I thought so.
Tada Banri!
So whose welcoming party are you going to today?
Are you cheating on us?
We're throwing a party today.
You're coming, right?
No, I don't think I can do two days in a row...
Don't give me that!
You should just make up your mind and join the club!
Ow, my butt...
Oh, I'm sorry.
You had someone with you.
If you change your mind, text us.
We'll be waiting.
What was that about?
Huh?
They're in the tea club.
I think their names are Sao-chan and Shi-chan...
That's not what I meant.
Tada-kun, what do you think of them?
What do I think?
Tada-kun, how many clubs have tried to recruit you?
Who knows?
I couldn't count all of them.
I think that's true of all new students...
I've had zero.
Zero?
I only took this flyer because it was lying around.
I wonder why no one tries to talk to me.
It's not as though I'm interested in clubs.
If it's not with Mitsuo,
I don't want to join any of them.
We went to school and cram school together, and I can't imagine myself without Mitsuo...
But since coming here...
I...
I feel like I've become invisible.
It's like everyone around me is ignoring me.
Am I really that strange?
Maybe that's why Mitsuo won't talk to me.
Is this an act to make me sympathize with her?
Or is she serious?
Maybe you should try talking to not just
Yana-san, but to a lot of different people.
Try starting a conversation.
You might be right...
You could try going to the welcoming parties of various clubs.
I'll even go with you.
Oh?
Are you interested in our club?
Sorry, I had just stepped away from the booth.
We do all kinds of things...
Simply put...
We view flowers and drink in the spring,
barbecue and drink in the summer, pick leaves and drink in the fall,
and snowboard and drink in the winter!
It's a laid-back club!
If you're interested, there's a great cafe nearby.
I can tell you more there!
They serve cafe au lait in bowls.
It's a cafe au lait bowl!
Oh, I'll pay, so don't worry.
It's decided, then!
Come on, let's go!
Whoa!
Tada-kun, my bag!
Huh?!
Oh...
I see.
You haven't joined any clubs yet.
In that case, you should definitely join ours.
We get lots of information about lectures and exams.
And we have lots of alumni who can help you find work.
Ah...
I highly recommend it!
You'll also get a lot of privileges if you join...
The truth is, I'm from a different university.
Talking to people from other universities is mentally stimulating.
Some questionable clubs won't let you quit once you join,
but we're not like that!
Every year, we hold our welcoming party at a seminar house.
It's three days and two nights.
We leave Saturday afternoon, get there in the evening, have dinner,
and party!
Oh, we come back early on
Monday morning, so don't worry.
We don't ask new students for money, so you can take it easy.
You'll come, right?
It's decided, right?
Meet us in front of the main entrance tomorrow!
You'll have tons of fun! Look forward to it!
Okay?
I guess we're going.
Yeah, she was really intense...
Trying stuff like this isn't so bad, though.
We can decide if we want to join later.
You're right.
We have this opportunity, and everything is an experience.
Well, this is as far as I go.
I'll see you tomorrow, Tada-kun.
Okay.
She feels she's become invisible, huh...
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
Night Escape
Three days and two nights with Kaga-san...
With Kaga-san...
It's not like I'm excited about that!