♪ Fishing for fishies! ♪
--Yahoo!
--I ain't satisfied, Handa-kun.
Huh? About what?
After spending five days of my vacation on this island...
...all I did was look for your place...
...and get a hangover from a bunch of geezers I never met before.
--Gimme back my vacation.
--Serves you right.
We're fishin' 'cuz you said you wanted ta enjoy your last day.
Listen, middle-schooler...
What I meant by "enjoy" was that
I wanted to go on a tour. Got it?
Like I'd know. I dunno anything 'bout tourist spots and stuff.
I'm not satisfied either!
This was the perfect chance to see Sensei's writing up close!
I can't believe we're spending time outside!
Guess he wants to be holed up even on a trip...
What's the matter, Hiro? You look tired.
He was talking to me the whole night about his ideas on calligraphy...
--I started when I was in elementary, and...
--There's a U23 exhibition, and...
--I have a preference as to what brush I use, and...
--I didn't get a wink of sleep...
Aah...! I want to stay indoors!
"fake bait hook" "bamboo fishing rod"
Here's the fishing gear.
What can you fish for using this?
"bait basket"
Mackerel.
I guess there's more to fishing than just putting on bait...
It's the first time I've seen this too!
--Huh?! Is this your first time fishing?
--Wow! A fishing rod!
Yeah.
How 'bout you, Kawa-san?
Don't lump me in with those city boys.
My target: the bass...!
Nah... Bass know-how won't help you catch mackerel.
A large blanket can cover a small hole!
But it wouldn't keep you from falling in...
G-Get it off!
--Naru?
--Hm?
Put some bait in here.
I don't want to touch it.
Okay!
Huh? There's bait already on the hook...
Fake bait...?
--Come on! Get a hold of it!
--The rod is so stinky! I don't wanna touch it!
--Too high! Down here!
--Zip that there mouth of yers an' stay put!
--Speak in Japanese!
--Sure isn't worth bringing city folks fishing...
Well, I'm gonna fish up over there.
Good luck, Miwa.
Wha--?! Hiro-nii, you ditching me?!
I'm a man of the sea.
I ain't goin' for something small-time like mackerel...
My target...
The hisanio!
The hisanio...?
--Hisanio!
--The hisanio...?
--That's super, Hiro-nii!
Do yer best! I hope ya catch one!
The heck is a "hisanio"?
Beats me...
Maybe it's a "miserable fish"? [hisan = "miserable"; o = "fish"]
"Hisanio"
"Translation: An expensive fish"
First you toss some bait...
Thanks.
Then you drop the line where you tossed the bait.
When the tip of the rod bobs...
See?
Whoa, that's amazing!
Grandma was sayin' that they'd bite good today.
--All right, fishing time!
--Yeah!
We'll have deep-fried mackerel tonight!
Whoa! I think I got something!
Bring it up! Bring it up!
Whoa!
I got two of them...! What a catch!
--Naru?
--Okay!
Usually it's the other way around...
Look, Handa! I got three of them!
What? I can't lose to you!
I got something too!
The pull's so strong! It's got to be big!
"Ahahahahahahaha"
I'm a genius of calligraphy and fishing!
I'll show you common rabble that I'm in a league of my own!
You caught the shoal...
Shoal?
Gotta hand it to ya on catchin' the Earth.
--Hey, wharf roaches!
--This can't be...
Wow! There's plenty of 'em!
"Naru obtained slightly long stick!"
Gotcha!
Hina, gimme your hand...
--No!
--Don't worry...
--No...!
--C'mon, don't worry...!
No...! They bite!
I give up...! It stinks, I can't catch any fish, and it's hot! I wanna go back!
There's no need to go back with all the fish we're catching.
I want to write calligraphy with you, Sensei!
H-Hey, wait!
You don't like outdoor activities like this either, right, Sensei?! Let's go home!
No way am I going to write calligraphy with you around.
Why are you saying such a thing?!
You're probably just going to say I lost my touch again...
--Huh?
--What?!
Kosuke! Did you really say that?!
Well...
...it is true.
So, you gotta see things only your way, eh?!
That's why you're in a slump!
Slump...? You're not writing?
Not since he saw the work you sent in the last time.
Handa, you haven't lost your touch.
If that was true, you wouldn't be recognized at all.
Kosuke's been writing with your calligraphy on his mind all this time.
That must be why he got anxious--
he lost his point of reference when you changed your style.
Look at them.
That's what I want to say.
Huh? What's this about?
See how the kids are mimicking her?
Handa, have you ever seen
Kosuke's calligraphy?
No. Why would I?
Figured as much.
His calligraphy looks just like yours.
Handa, yours looks just like your dad's.
Both of you are just true to fundamentals.
I got first place with it, so fundamentals should be number one...
You just dissed my old man too, didn't you?
The role of you young ones is not to fear failure, but to seek new frontiers!
Director...!
Instead of setting records, be remembered!
Lose the match, but win the battle!
Instead of being number one, aim to be the only one!
Instead of winning awards, strive to make works that sell!
That last one is your desire!
Give me... money...!
He's being taken away!
Sensei.
I learned this from Miwa-nee.
Use this.
Wow, you tied that?
Sensei, use Naru's too!
You made one too?
Naru's is super ultra...
Catch 'em all with this!
No way you can fish with that!
So, is this the "new frontier" you were talking about?
Well, I guess...
It's like the epitome of failure!
C'mon, don't laugh so much. She's only a kid.
But she's so straightforward and simple...!
Taaackle!
You... brat...!
I'll let ya go with that for today.
Looks like they're having fun down there...
Hiro-nii, you got more bait on you?
What? You're out already?
Hina spilled 'em all.
Are Sensei and the others fishing at all?
--I found my glasses...!
--All they've been talking 'bout is calligraphy.
Something 'bout losing his touch, or not.
If you're good, you're good.
Isn't that all there is to it?
If everyone became masters, there'd be nowhere left to go.
I'm probably not gonna catch a hisanio today either...
Guess I ain't got a chance this close to land...
Head Teacher said that he saw someone catch one around here.
Hey, Hiroshi! Did ya catch a hisanio?
Not a single bite. Best we start heading out.
Hiroshi, how about this?
What the...? It looks like some cursed tool.
Sorry.
Okay, this'll be my last cast, so I might as well use it.
Make sure you say "Ebisu."
I know, I know.
What are they talking about?
Good mojo.
They say that if you say "Ebisu" when you cast the line, you'll catch a hisanio.
Hm? "Ebisu"? You mean from the Seven Gods of Fortune?
Ebisu carries a hisanio with him, you know?
So a "hisanio" is a "sea bream"!
To be specific, I'm fishing for a striped beakfish.
Don't you catch them offshore?
If you could catch one here, anyone could become a fisherman.
Wow, you're so negative.
But, if we can catch one, we could have sashimi for dinner...
Ebisu!
Serious now...?
Of course! There's no way I'm leaving here without eating something good!
No bites...
Yeah...
In the first place, you're all forgetting we're trying to catch one with that hook.
All right, time to leave.
Aww...
I'm going to clean up, so can you hold this?
Huh? Me?
You haven't caught anything anyway, right?
H-Hey...
Come on...
We... We've got a hit!
What?!
--Miwa, the net!
--Got it!
--Okay, we'll help too!
--Is it because of Ebisu? Is it because of Ebisu?!
Wha--?! You're in the way!
You crazy?! No way you can reel in the big one alone!
I can! I bet you guys are gonna take the credit!
--Ebisu! Ebisu!
--Be quiet over there!
All right!
We got it!
Huge...!
Ah...
The heck was that?! That was freaking huge!
There actually was one like that?!
Did you see it drop?! It just plopped back in!
I can't breathe...
The hook just fell apart in midair!
Let's go home.
Well, we did catch a lot of mackerel, so all's good.
I'll deep fry them at my place.
I heard pickling them is good too.
Sensei, let's go.
You know...
Since coming to this island, I sometimes get this urge to write calligraphy...
Something rises from inside me...
...and my hands start to shake.
I feel that now, too.
Sensei caught 'em!
Um...
Today, I'd like to celebrate our visit to the island, and...
Cheers!!
Don't ignore me!
Time to eat!
What's with the fish covered in ink here?
That's the remains of the new frontier...
It would've been better if it was a sea bream.
You guys do your best and get better, and make me rich.
That sure sounds like you...
So I guess we're just products in Kawafuji-san's eyes...
What's this 'bout "new frontiers"?
Beats me...
The other room...
Ah...
Snooping around again?
Let me see.
Lookin' good.
I always liked your writing, Sensei.
This one's the best!
"Sea Bream"
"Fukue Airport"
Fukuoka flight 635 will start boarding at 10:20...
C'mon, you folks didn't need to come and see us off.
It's only a three-hour flight to Tokyo.
--Well, I know you're all sad to see us go,
--What's this?
--Kankoro mochi ["sweet potato rice cakes"].
--but you really don't need to worry...
--It tastes good when ya grill 'em in the toaster oven!
Look, Kawafuji!
It's written as "Eight Lightning" to read "Hacchikankan."
--TV rock's the revolution of rocks!
--Really, why'd you come?
Huh? What's that?
Why are the locals so excited to be here?
There's time before the departure, so you should go and buy some gifts too, Kawafuji-kun.
Huh...
Thank you for your generosity.
Don't worry 'bout it.
Sensei's friends are always welcome here.
The kids usually only interact with people nearby,
so it looks like they had fun with you city folks.
--Look at it! Awesome, right?!
--Hey! They got somethin' here!
Whoa...!
Look at all them toys!
The airport's so neat!
It's like Santa's house!
You wanna take one with you?
Nah, I'll pass.
Say, what's this island's specialty?
Let's see...
Kankoro mochi, camellia candy...
...oval squid... sea urchin...
...Goto udon... Goto beef...
There's no way I can bring that much with me...
Is there something besides food?
How about a mobile strap?
Pretty standard gift.
"Goto Specialty
Baramon-kun"
Wow, not cute at all!
It's "Baramon-kun." Buy plenty, and make 'em popular in Tokyo.
I don't have friends, so I'll just buy one for myself.
Wha--?!
Well, uh... sorry...
For what?
I'll buy one too.
Naru's gonna buy this!
"Buy"? As in you're going to make me buy it, right?
C'mon, Sensei...
For heaven's sake...
Don't stake your afterlife at your age...
I really wanna give this to Kawafuji as a gift...
Darn... I tell you...
How did you know what he'd like?
I don't like that!
You sure bought a lot of gifts.
I bragged to the guys at work that I was going to Goto...
I gotta look good, you know?
Fukuoka flight 635
--will now begin boarding.
--Oh? It's time.
--Please come to Gate 1 for boarding.
--Sorry for not doing anything special.
I know you're not good with stuff like that.
Well, it was nice seeing you managing yourself.
I can put in a good report to Handa-sensei too.
You've been... seeing my old man?
Every so often, for work.
He was pretty worried about you, despite being the one who sent you here.
I see...
Hm? What's with that surprised look of yours?
Well, the way you are,
I figured you'd say rebellious stuff like, "He wouldn't worry for me."
I've been thinking recently...
Maybe my old man doesn't dislike me the way I thought.
You're... just figuring that out now?
Being strict and not liking someone are two separate things.
If you ask an outsider like me, you've got a doting parent.
What?! No way!
Call him some time.
Kawafuji...
Aah...! Did Kawa-san board already?
No, not yet. He's going through now.
It's his glasses! His glasses set it off!
I knew he'd be caught!
You both came here just for this...?
Not my glasses, my belt!
Ah, this is golden! He's sayin' something.
I bet he has a knife rigged into those glasses of his.
As your friend, I'm embarrassed, Kawafuji.
Sensei.
Thank you very much.
I've been rude this whole time, but...
I'm happy to have met you.
I learned a lot from you...
Learned from me? This wasn't a school field trip or anything...
If we walk the same path,
I'm sure we'll meet again.
And the feeling's mutual.
I'm happy to have met you.
Sometimes, meeting someone face to face
makes you feel better than being jealous from afar.
Come again any time.
Yes! I'll come again, for sure!
Definitely!
I can't take this! Are they trying to kill me or what?!
Check out the nabbing power of the metal detector!
Why am I feeling embarrassed?
"I've done it this time!"
I forgot to give 'em the gift that Grandpa told me to!
You still have time. Go, Naru!
Yup!
Wait a minute... She doesn't have any metals on her.
Hey, there they are.
Looks like Kawa-san noticed.
He's waving to us.
Kind of sad, isn't it?
We only just met them, and we're feeling sad already.
Sensei must be...
No fair! Gimme some juice!
Jealous?
--He sure can adapt quickly.
--Gimme...!
Tokyo, eh...?
What's the matter? You wanna go to Tokyo too, Hiro-nii?
Not like I wanna go to Tokyo, but...
I was just thinking that, one day, we're gonna leave the island too...
I'm in my third year of high school, so I gotta start thinking seriously 'bout stuff like that.
Thanks for ruining my serious scene there!
Huh?
They're off.
Bye-bye!
--Bye-bye!
Bye-bye...!
We're over the passenger limit.
Kawafuji-kun's rental car was returned, so come home by bus.
Bye-bye!
--Hey! There's gotta be room for us somewhere!
--Wait up...! Don't leave us behind!
It's sad seeing your friends go, right?
No...
I can't wait to see them again.
What was Naru's gift?
So this is what was detected...
"Naru"
Let's come again.
Yes...
Next time...
...I'll come alone.