I'm glad the sun's out.
Yeah.
It's a perfect day for a dip in the sea.
Are you wearing your swimsuit under your clothes?
Of course.
It's a bikini.
What about you, Banri?
Are you wearing a jockstrap?
It's a swimsuit.
I'm wearing a speedo.
Wow, a speedo!
Wait, really?
I am, in place of a jockstrap.
Oh...
Anyway, I'm more worried about something else...
Oh, good.
The innocent pair's in here, too.
Isn't that Mitsuo's swimsuit?
Just from one look?
She really is a professional stalker.
Hey, did Mitsuo say anything?
Like what?
You mean about that time?
Yes, that time...
We decided to just keep quiet and watch, right?
Yana-san didn't say anything, and neither did I.
You're right.
I know.
I know, but...
It just doesn't feel right...
Just so you know,
I don't feel that way because I still have feelings for Mitsuo or anything.
I wasn't thinking that.
I'm actually more worried about how Miss Ultrasonic feels.
Mitsuo and Linda-senpai becoming an item must make her feel something.
Who knows?
I don't like Miss Ultrasonic at all.
In fact, I hate her...
...but I can imagine how she feels.
She rejected him once,
but just when she thought she'd tolerate his presence
or smugly thought she had room to breathe...
...this happened!
That's what Oka-chan is like in your mind?
Because she was slow,
a mature older woman stole him away.
That has to hurt.
Maybe she didn't think someone like
Linda-senpai would appear before Mitsuo.
Linda-senpai is a wonderful person.
Anyone would fall in love with her, right?
Listen, just so you know...
...you're the one I love, Kouko.
That's the one thing I'm sure of.
Yeah, I know.
Accident Beach
Ah, if we could meet in a dream, could I say it?
Say, if sadness alone floats down from the sky
If that kind of voice pains you even now
Even if, off to the side, our hands are placed on each other's
This memory wouldn't fade, but...
Even if, when our eyes meet, I can't say the truth...
Your words illuminate the world more than anyone else's
Next to me, "Goodbye means I love you," you say
I can't be forthright
Though I alone sing of loneliness
I can't smile
"Thank you means I'm in love with you," you say
The world's end of love
2D-kun's late.
I wonder what happened.
Who knows?
He said he'd meet us at the bus stop.
This should be the right place.
I'm going to go look for him.
I'll go with you.
Pedestrians
and
Bicycles
Only
2D-kun!
I finally found you.
I meant that one.
The shuttle bus stop.
Who doesn't check voice mail when it's 20 minutes past the meeting time?
I called you over and over while driving around looking for you.
Sorry.
My phone was in my bag,
so I didn't hear it.
And why are you sitting like you're in a taxi?
Huh?
You guys can be like that sometimes.
I feel like you don't show me any consideration.
Sorry.
There, there.
You can have these.
Crispy
Non-Fried
Potato
Sticks
What am I, a kid?
Open wide.
Kouko?
I felt like I was hit in the face with a blast of hot air!
The air conditioning is messed up.
Hello?
Oka-chan?
Some stuff came up.
We're going to be about 30 more minutes.
Okay, I'll pass the time in a cafe close by.
Call me when you get here.
Got it.
Later.
There you go.
I wonder if we'll get there in 30 minutes.
The number you are trying to reach is currently outside the service area...
You can't reach her?
Yeah...
Maybe she doesn't realize her phone's out of service.
Man, what the hell?!
We know she's around here, right?
I'll go look for her.
This is why I hate the 3D world.
Uh...
Want some?
They're taking forever...
We still have to go to Yana-san's place, too.
Why did Yana-san have to go back home today of all days?
We have to go out of our way for him.
He said it'd just be while his dad was on his business trip.
His timing sucks.
We haven't been cursed by something, have we?
Come on, try to think positive!
After all, we're going to the beach!
Thanks for waiting.
Scoot over, Banri.
Good morning.
Sorry.
I was seated downstairs and didn't realize I didn't have service.
Basements have so much junk blocking the signal, right?
Yeah.
Again, why are you sitting like you're in a taxi?
Oka-chan, you're wearing a skirt today!
Yeah, so it's easier to change.
I'm wearing my swimsuit under my clothes.
All right, let's go!
I see...
You're wearing a swimsuit under your skirt, huh?
That's right.
So-tell-me, Chi-na-mi.
Are you wearing a school swimsuit?
I thought about it for a second,
but I ended up wearing a normal one.
So-tell-me, Chi-na-mi, are you worried because you forgot your panties?
I never forget to bring anything.
I see, I see.
That's a shame.
Why?!
What time is it?
10:30.
We're two hours behind schedule.
My luck's really off today.
Hey. You guys took a while.
All right! I get shotgun!
Not a word about Linda-senpai.
I know.
My lips are sealed.
Shall we go, then?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I saw Banri the other day, though.
Y-you're right.
It's been a while, Yanao.
I mean, Mitsuo.
What's wrong with you?
You're kinda stuttery.
What? N-no, I'm not.
Come on, Miss Ultrasonic.
It's been a while since you've seen each other, right?
Right? Right?
Uh...
Chinami, I heard you're having a rough time.
You've got a lot on your plate?
Well, I'm sure you can handle most things,
so I'm not too worried.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Banri told me the other day.
What?
Nothing's going on.
But he said you're moving soon, and next month you'll be living on your own...
Oh! I didn't think it was anything worth telling you. Don't worry about it.
Hey, Kaga-san, could I have some potato sticks?
Uh, sure.
What's with her?
She's kinda standoffish.
Right?
Don't you think Chinami was being cold to me?
Not at all.
It was totally normal.
That's what I think.
Don't you think so?
Because you should!
I don't think so.
It's raining.
Seriously?
Why?
Why won't anything go well?
Yokohama Machida-Atsugi
Traffic next 10 km
Wouldn't it be faster to take side streets?
We can't for a while.
The exit's way ahead.
There's no telling when we'll get there now.
Should we turn back?
But we've come this far...
Yeah.
The rain might stop by the time we get there.
The weather report said it'd be sunny.
Hey... seriously, are we sure one of us isn't cursed?
That's really not...
...funny.
I guess we should've turned back, after all.
Yeah.
Are you awake?
Banri, what should I do?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Is it a phantom urge?
No. It's real.
There seems to be a bathroom over there.
Do you have an umbrella?
No...
Me, neither.
Neither do I.
You're wearing your swimsuit, right?
Yeah.
Huh?
Banri?
All right! Let's go!
What?!
You're kidding!
If you go now, I can go with you!
Huh? Huh?
Take it off, take it off, take it off!
Hurry up and take it off!
You've got three more seconds!
Three, two...
Wait a minute.
Underneath my clothes is...
...the toxic speedo...
There!
Wait, wait!
I'll go with you!
Go! Sprint!
I'm going to drown!
No!
What are we even doing?
Awesome!
Yay!
"Awesome," nothing.
Stop acting like an observer and come with us.
What?! Hold on!
Not the Okamera!
Sheesh!
And on top of everything, it's cold!
You two must be idiots!
Wh-what is that?
Oh, no!
Banri's not wearing a jockstrap under his swimsuit!
We have no choice!
Let's go, 2D!
Yeah!
No, Mister Tada!
Your outline is clearly visible!
Uncle!
2D!
You did this for me?
Of course we did.
By swiftly taking possession of your dangling bits,
the crime-constituting conditions of embezzlement have been completely met.
Also, why is Yana-san your uncle?
He just is!
What's wrong, Kouko?
Did you wet yourself?
I just slipped, you idiot!
That's the first time she's called me an idiot.
Thanks for the food!
Banri, your ramen looks delicious.
Really?
Look, the Okamera.
Yay!
Whoa! Oka-chan, what was that?!
There it is!
Miss Ultrasonic's weird face!
Here we go!
Look, a shell.
Open wide.
Brain freeze!
Okay, Yana-san. Open wide.
Here, Kouko.
I'm good.
Of course you are.
Brain freeze!
Fireworks!
Yay!
Kaga-san and 2D-kun have a sparkler in each hand!
Okay, let's light this one.
Sounds good!
I'm glad the weather cleared up.
Yeah.
The stars are so beautiful.
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
Yana-san, talk to me while I drive.
If it gets too quiet, I think I really will lose consciousness.
Are you okay?
In that case, do you want me to drive instead?
You have a license?
Yeah.
See?
Are you sure?
It'd be a huge help.
Leave it to me.
You drove all the way here.
It's no wonder you're tired.
Kouko, are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
You can't be that used to driving.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
I'll ride in the passenger seat, then.
2D-kun, you can sleep in the back.
Yeah, I totally will.
I'm so sleepy, I can't take it...
Okay, everybody... Let's go!
You're a good driver, Kouko.
Aren't I?
Don't worry.
I'll drive really safely.
Everyone's asleep.
That really was fun, though.
I thought we were done for when it started to rain.
I know.
It ended up being so fun.
I'm glad we got to go to the beach together.
Yeah. Me, too.
As of now, this feels like the best summer of my life.
Surely you're exaggerating.
It's true.
It is.
When are you going to Barcelona?
Next week.
But... I want to stay with you.
We talked about this before.
You should go.
Bring something back for me.
I really do wish I could stay with you.
No... I can't.
I need to keep talking to Kouko...
Wake up!
This can't happen!
I didn't want things to go this far!
No! Not this!
This isn't what I want!
I didn't want this to happen!
Someone, help!
Someone!
Please! Anyone!
Tell him, "You can do it."
Oh...
I'm not supposed to say that kind of thing.
Just press on!
You're wrong, I'm telling you you're wrong
Ah, you still don't notice, huh?
Though I've wanted to touch that arm for the past two or three hours
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
The urge to scream is so great that, look, I can't stand it
So why, why won't you notice even a little?
Are you really, really in love with me?
I don't need words of flattery
Love me semi-eternally
After 5,000 years or so, I won't be interested
I'm not endless
I will die someday
Being told "I'll love you forever" won't make me happy
First, think only that
You'll love me till I die
Wake Up Call
It's not here! It's not here!
I forgot a change of underwear!
What's this?
You forgot your underwear even
though I asked about it?
I see. That's not good.
You've got a criminal record now.
What's wrong, 2D?!
Are you broken?!