Linda's late.
What...? But you and Banri-senpai are so close!
You always go home together.
We were convinced you were dating.
Cut it out.
I mean, are you guys stupid?
I look out for him.
You know, Banri's unreliable.
I just can't leave him alone.
I see.
You're saying you can't leave
Banri-senpai alone because you like him.
No!
I don't even see him as a guy in the first place.
There you go again.
You actually like him, don't you?
No! No!
I don't like him at all!
Come on. Let's go home.
Banri, wait!
Hey, Banri!
Wait, Banri!
Hey, Banri...
Banri, about the other day...
I don't like him at all!
It's so cold.
It's all the opposite, Banri.
Sometimes I'm really stupid.
Forgive me for being stupid.
I won't.
I don't like you at all, either.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Banri...
Forget it.
Let's go home.
Okay.
In this moment, I think a fire was lit in my heart...
Linda said she didn't like me at all.
If those words were the opposite of how Linda really felt...
Reset
...then maybe she...
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
What?
Yana-san left early?
Yes.
So, Tada-kun, will you go check on Mitsuo for me?
I mean, there's no way I can go.
Why not?
I can't go to another man's place when I have a boyfriend.
Going behind closed doors with a member of the opposite sex is cheating.
Y-you're right...
I'm going next door.
Later.
Tada-kun, are you listening?
I'm listening.
Okay.
I'll go check on him.
Yeah...
I haven't forgotten my feelings for Linda.
Got it.
I'll call you later.
Not even now, as a ghost.
Okay.
But that has nothing to do with the current Tada Banri.
Bye.
The current Banri... is dating Kaga Kouko.
Let's see...
Is this it?
Come on, Yana.
Let me in.
No, seriously.
I'm not feeling well today.
You shouldn't push yourself so hard.
Um...
I thought I'd make you dinner.
Do you like meat and potatoes?
No... I really...
I don't have anything to do today.
I was thinking I could stay over.
Seriously, seriously, seriously, seriously...
Hi, Yana-san!
What?
Banri?
My boyfriend!
Wait, what?
He's my boyfriend.
No one can come between us.
We're lovers from a past life.
Right?
Yeah!
I was a shepherd in a past life.
And I was a nun at a convent.
Gross!
There's something wrong with you two!
Y-you saved me.
Who was she?
Reina-senpai from the film club.
I was so scared.
She was shoving her cleavage in my face.
Right...
Whoa...
This room is a mess.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming over.
Kaga-san told me.
Something happened with Oka-chan again?
Yes.
Hey, Yana!
You won't get away today!
Chinami, wait...
Sorry, but could you not talk to me?
A lot of people know about what happened at the party.
Do you mean forever?
Forever.
If that's what you want, then fine.
H-hi...
When did you get here?
You're the one who just came up next to me...
Hey, that's...
It's the guy who confessed to Chinami at the party and got shot down on the spot.
Ouch...
Yana-san?
Everyone around me seems to know that Chinami rejected me.
No matter what I do, I feel so self-conscious...
I see...
I know.
I should act normal around Chinami, like nothing ever happened.
But I freak out every time I see her.
I feel embarrassed and sad.
I'm the worst.
I understand how you feel.
Yana-san, look at yourself!
I've got seaweed in my teeth.
From that sushi I bought at the convenience store...
That's not what I meant!
You're attractive! You should be more confident in yourself!
In any case, you can't keep acting like this.
Just like Linda-senpai helped me, it's my turn to help you.
What did Linda-senpai do?
Hello, 2D-kun?
Listen, I want to throw a party to cheer up Yana-san.
Hey! Tada-kun, you're fifteen minutes late!
Sorry.
Just kidding.
I'm not mad.
I'm happy to see you, Tada-kun.
I'm happy to see you, Yana-san.
I'm...
...not happy.
That's cold!
Look, I appreciate what you're all trying to do, but...
I don't get why she's here.
When Banri called me, I had just left class with Kaga-san, and she overheard.
I just want to be with Tada-kun all the time.
I don't care about you.
Going to an amusement park was my suggestion.
If you don't like it, why don't you go home?
You're just getting in the way here.
Wait, wait, wait!
Kaga-san!
Oka
Chinami
Wh-what should I do?
It's Oka-chan.
Should I answer? Should I answer?
Yana-san.
I...
I... I...
It's me.
We're throwing a party to cheer up Mitsuo.
You should come, too.
I don't want you to come, but I'm reluctantly inviting you for Mitsuo's sake.
You...
Hello?
Yeah, that's right.
I used up some of my kindness on Mitsuo again.
We're at...
Replenish...!
You...! What did you just do?!
You heard me.
So, what are you going to do?
Leave? Or stay?
Hello, Oka-chan?
Yeah.
We'll be waiting at the ticket gate.
Bye.
I wish I could've come with just you.
Let's come back together sometime, then.
The pool will be opening soon.
Or would you rather go to the beach?
Oh, my! The beach with you!
What should I do? I'm so excited!
Banri!
Kaga-san, you came to meet me, too!
Thanks!
I was so surprised by that phone call!
I was shocked when Kaga-san suddenly answered and said Yana was there.
I knew I had to go.
I was pretty flustered.
See?
I brought this.
Noodles?!
I see...
You really were flustered.
Oh, yeah! I heard you two are dating now!
Oh, you knew?
2D-kun told me the other day.
I've seen you holding hands, too.
You saw that?
I sure did!
I didn't actually want you to come.
I want you to stay out of my sight.
Kaga-san, you invited her.
I just pitied Mitsuo because he's hurt.
He's my childhood friend, after all.
You can see him,
but don't hurt him any more.
If you can't do that, leave.
Why would you say that?
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
Whatever happens between me and Yana has nothing to do with you.
You're dating Banri, right?
Why don't you pay more attention to what you have?
Give me back my noodles.
A-are you okay?
No way...
It's okay.
It's not broken.
I wonder if it still works.
This is Kaga-san, Kaga Kouko.
This is my first time filming her with the Okamera.
Hello.
Hey, Kaga-san... it's hard for me, too.
I know it may not seem that way.
After all...
After all, Yana said...
He told me to never speak to him again.
No!
I'm the only one who can act cute and cry in front of Tada-kun!
Suck it up!
I'll keep doing this until you stop crying!
K-Kaga-san!
You're suffocating Oka-chan!
Let me know when you're done crying!
I'm going to keep doing this until you do!
You're going to kill Oka-chan!
Are you done crying?
A-are you alive?
Hey, Banri... don't I look really funny right now?
What? You want me to film you? Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
Okay.
Kaga-san, could you try letting go?
It feels really stable right now.
Here we go.
What am I doing?
W-well, then.
What should we ride first?
A roller coaster!
HAUNTED
HOUSE
Have they made up?
Tada-kun, look only at me.
Cheers!
Oh, that's called Face Yakisoba.
Face Yakisoba?
Yeah.
What kind of name is that?
Is it good, Yana-san?
Have some.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's good.
Hey, why don't we make a pact?
A pact?
Yeah.
If any of us ever decides to hang out or go drinking, like today, we'll all try to go.
That way, we'll always have a few people to hang out with.
I'm in.
If Tada-kun's in, I'm in.
I don't like that Mitsuo's involved, though.
I could say the same about you.
Count me in, too!
Ready, and...
Yeah!
Is anyone awake?
Linda-senpai
No subject
Are you awake?
Sending
Message
Linda... Senpai.
Banri.
Can I speak casually with you, just for now?
It just feels more right that way.
You guys were noisy.
Were you in Nana-senpai's room this whole time?
I was just reminiscing about you.
So I really freaked out when I got your text.
How did you know I was awake?
I don't know.
I just felt like you were.
You've always been like that.
Sometimes we'd go on trips with our club.
Whenever I couldn't sleep,
you'd come into the girls' room and ask, "Hey, Linda, are you awake?"
What? So I was a pervert?
You did cause trouble doing that, but you'd nervously tell me,
"I can't sleep. I'm going to be exhausted at practice tomorrow."
Whoa...
Yeah, I definitely had some naughty intentions.
Seriously?
Then when my panties went missing, could you have...
Huh?
I'm kidding.
You know... for some reason...
What?
I think I used to like you then.
Saying I couldn't sleep was just an excuse.
I think I had a sort of perverted desire to watch you sleep.
So... sorry about that.
We should've talked about the past like this from the beginning.
Once you miss the opportunity to say something, the words become increasingly toxic.
The best thing to do is to just say everything.
There's nothing between us that we can't say anymore.
We haven't changed.
We're still alive.
We're looking at the same sky.
That hasn't changed at all.
Banri?
There's something I haven't asked you yet.
What?
I was wondering...
...what your answer to my confession was the day after graduation.
That's obvious.
It was "no."
I just couldn't think of you romantically.
I was going to tell you we should stay friends.
I see...
Linda... Senpai.
Do you want to go back?
To that place where I used to be.
I...
I want to go back!
What did I just say?
Wow, you just fell asleep for a second...
Fell asleep?
Looks like you should get to bed.
Lack of sleep isn't good for you.
You'll become oversensitive and think things you shouldn't.
Good night, Tada Banri.
I still love Linda.
If I can, I want to be with Linda forever.
But I can't leave you.
If I do, I'll disappear.
I feel like I will.
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
With You Again
Oh, wow!
Tada-kun, you're so good at impersonating me.
Mitsuo, your room is filthy and your feet stink.
Grrrr...!
Butt chin!
Yana-san, back to your house!
Your house!