STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
HORAI
BRIDGE
This is where I lost my memories.
Why...
Why don't I...
...remember anything?
What was my relationship with Linda-senpai?
Banri?
Yana-san.
Listen...
Can I come over to your place?
I'm... not there.
Huh?
Body and Soul
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even it it's the long way around
Until I was 18, I was Tada Banri.
The day after my graduation,
I fell off a bridge and left my physical body.
I was ejected and became a lifeless spirit.
Meanwhile, the soulless and empty Banri has been living in body only, as an amnesiac,
and somehow became a college student.
Meanwhile, as a ghost,
I've been watching over the newly reborn Tada Banri.
But...
Banri can't hear me.
New Message
Kaga Kouko
Let's go get our stuff
from the club.
I want to talk to you
afterward.
Oh, right.
That happened.
We've just met...
But being with you is so much fun.
That's the truth.
So I hope we can be good friends!
Tada-kun?
Oh... It's nothing.
Anyway,
I want you to have this.
Huh?
Now we'll match.
See?
It's a survivor's mirror.
I had mine when we escaped from that cult the other day.
I see...
I left my stuff behind, remember?
But I had this in my pocket, so I took it with me.
Since then,
I've thought of it as a symbol of our friendship.
I wanted to give you the same one, so I bought this.
Please accept the gift!
Thanks.
Good friends, huh?
To commemorate the
anniversary of our escape!
From your friend,
Kaga Kouko
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
What was up yesterday?
You sounded weird over the phone.
Oh, sorry.
Did you need something?
I thought I might have been a little hard on Kouko.
So you're worried about Kaga-san.
Yeah.
And about Chinami, too.
Oka-chan?
My!
My! My!
Why, if it isn't my dear friend, Tada-kun.
Good morning.
Now that I've run into you this morning,
I'm sure this will be a splendid day.
We must have been destined to be great friends since a previous life!
G-good morning, Kaga-san.
Tada-kun, your voice is amazing.
Hey, have you ever thought about our previous lives?
What?
I have!
I was a postulant at a convent.
You were a shepherd living deep in the forest.
Every morning, you delivered cheese to me, right?
That's what I believe.
Hey, isn't that so romantic?
Thank you.
Thank you for everything in my life!
I'm so grateful to fate for allowing me to see you again.
Uh...
My, Mitsuo.
Ah... Good morning.
Mitsuo, you must have been a solitary hunter wandering through the wilderness.
I can tell by looking at your face.
Given my quiet days of prayer in the convent, perhaps we were never destined to meet.
Um... what should I do?
Ignore her.
That's what I did.
Hey!
Let's get started, Kouko-chan!
Sorry.
Linda-senpai was helping me register for classes.
This girl doesn't know a thing about mandatory courses.
I was telling her about some she could still take.
Tada Banri, what about you?
Have you already registered?
Huh?
Er, yeah, I guess.
Oh, let me introduce you.
This is my friend Yana-san.
This is Linda-senpai from the festival club.
She rescued us from the cult's overnight trip.
Nice to meet you.
I heard my friend caused you some trouble.
It was no trouble at all.
Anyway, is your registration going well?
Yeah... I suppose.
Who's your civil law teacher?
Uh... Tsukamoto-sensei.
What?!
You're taking Tsukamoto's civil law course?
That's not good!
Tsukamoto makes really tough exams every year!
Previous exams are no help,
and he's really strict about attendance!
Seriously?
Oh, my.
Mitsuo, you seem to have a problem.
How... sad... for... you!
I'm going to ask some other civil law professors if it's not too late to register!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Fail all your classes!
Stay an extra year!
And cry!
Stupid, stupid!
What was that?
Mitsuo is such a child.
Oh... right.
Have you guys decided whether you're joining the festival club?
We still don't have any new members.
Of course.
We'll both join.
We're great friends, connected by a powerful bond.
We do everything together.
Right, Tada-kun?
Um... well...
Great! That's two new members!
I hope we can be friends.
Right!
R-right.
Linda-senpai...
You must know who I am.
Is there some reason you won't mention it?
Kaga-san, didn't you say you weren't confident in your dancing?
Yes...
But I figured that's no reason to shy away from it.
Pedestrians
and
Bicycles
Only
A lot has happened recently.
After overcoming all of it, I'm feeling really positive.
I see...
That's good.
It's thanks to you, my friend.
I want to try new things.
You shouldn't be indecisive.
It's a waste of life.
Make progress every day.
I'm going to run myself to death with a super-positive lifestyle!
Why are you being so proactive?
You should be more positive, too.
No... you have to be.
If you're not as positive as I am, you won't be the perfect friend!
Just because I rejected-
Would someone normally say that?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
But you were about to say it.
I wasn't, I wasn't!
I really wasn't.
Then take control of this awkward pantomime act.
Fine, I'll handle it.
A-anyway, that's that.
Let's give the festival club everything we have.
Y-yeah.
I'm first year law student Tada Banri!
Nice to meet you.
I'm first year law student Kaga Kouko.
Okay.
This'll help build momentum for our summer event.
What's happening this summer?
We're participating in an Awa dance event.
Let's start practicing.
Music.
Start by imitating the people around you.
O-okay.
It's all right.
I'm confident that I'll dance well today.
Looking forward to it!
Let's give it a shot!
You were actually pretty good for beginners.
You'll get better.
Tada Banri and Kouko-chan, see you later.
Thank you.
I can't do this.
You're supposed to be my friend!
It's not fair that you can dance!
You're so mean!
Traitor!
What do you want me to do about it?
I'm sick of this.
I wanted to be positive.
Why does this have to happen?
It's nothing to cry about.
B-but...
Tada-kun, I'm sorry!
I know I'm just... lashing out at you!
Kaga-san...
You'll still be my friend, won't you?
I know...
I know you're just being nice to me.
You joined a club with me,
danced with me...
You listen to me complain,
and worry about me.
I'm just taking advantage of your kindness and causing you trouble.
You must hate me, too.
Well, um...
Why don't you stand up?
She's been pushing herself really hard.
It's only been two days since Yana-san rejected her.
Is that drink crazy enough?
A latte with espresso, vanilla syrup, whipped cream, caramel,
and chocolate.
It's the greatest combination.
You seem to be feeling better.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
It was ridiculous of me to cry.
These days, I've just been...
...so hopeless.
Actually, I may have always been easily confused.
I'm stupid, hot-headed, and irredeemable.
I don't know what to do.
I thought I had to put my mistakes behind me as soon as possible.
And so... I panicked.
When you say "mistakes", you mean...
Yes.
I wanted to deal with my feelings for Mitsuo.
It's not as though I still love him.
It's just...
It's like my emotions are still paralyzed.
Oh, no! My nose!
Just a second.
Tada-kun... you're using it.
Of course.
They're matching mirrors of friendship.
Tada-kun, you understand my worthless self.
You forgive me despite my worthlessness.
And I took advantage of that and cried.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'm a year older than you, after all.
Oh, right.
You're the same age as Linda-senpai.
I want to be like Linda-senpai.
I admire her.
Do you?
She's so open, and she seems to be positively enjoying life.
She's cool no matter what she's doing, and she's pretty.
Hey, do you think Kosshi-senpai likes Linda-senpai?
Wh-why would you say that?
They seem close.
They don't seem to be going out, though.
Maybe Linda-senpai has a boyfriend!
After all, she is wonderful!
I bet she's really popular!
Linda-senpai.
Hayashida Nana...
Your temperature is normal.
Is there something bothering you?
Well... it's not about my health.
Every day in the middle of the night,
I see a flickering light on that hill.
Do you know what that is?
A light?
At night?
Are you saying you're having trouble sleeping?
You should have said something.
But I'm not tired yet at 11:00...
It's lights out at 9:00 in this hospital.
You need to sleep according to the schedule.
I know they're worried about me.
After all, I have amnesia.
But...
I've been hospitalized for almost two months.
I feel like I've been confined for observation.
When can I leave?
There it is.
Could it be some kind of signal for me?
Yahoo!
I think it was this way...
Ouch...
G-give me a second.
I mean no harm.
Um... I'm a patient in the hospital down the hill.
If you're wondering what I'm doing here,
it's because I can see that light from my room, and I wondered what it was.
So I came out here to find out.
A-are you okay?
Sh-should...
Should I get someone from the hospital?
No, don't worry about me.
Anyway, as for the rest of my story...
I thought...
someone was trying to signal to me with that light.
I thought they were signaling for me to escape.
Like it was saying, "Come with me, come with me!"
Like I was being led here.
Like I should run this way!
Escape?
In the hospital,
I'm under observation all the time.
It's suffocating and boring.
So today, I couldn't take it anymore,
and now I'm here.
Yes! I am clearly stupid!
I see.
So, what about you?
What have you been doing alone every night?
I've been coming to see the hospital.
My friend's been hospitalized.
I can't see him, though, for... reasons.
But I thought I could at least drop by.
Is he from around here?
He's from Tokyo.
I go to college in Tokyo.
I'm home for Golden Week now.
Oh...?
Tokyo sounds nice.
If I got into a college in Tokyo,
I could say goodbye to this prison.
I feel like I could escape.
Prison? You mean the hospital?
That... and the human relationships restricting me.
All my ties.
All of that stuff.
Come to Tokyo.
What?
It's fun.
Come with me.
Yeah, you're right.
I should go to Tokyo.
I'll leave the hospital, study,
and get into a college in Tokyo.
Thank you!
Thanks for your signal.
I know your signal wasn't meant for me...
but to me, your light was a sign for me to break free!
I'm going to Tokyo!
That was Linda-senpai.
Why hasn't she said anything, though?
About going to high school together,
or meeting me while I was hospitalized...
I don't get it!
Even though you have a body,
you have no memories from before you were 18.
Even though I have memories, I have no body.
I want to tell you...
...what Linda...
...meant to me.
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
Yes No
Whirr, clunk. Whirr, clunk. Whirrrr, whirrrr...
Kaga-san, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Wh-whirr, whirr, whirr...
Boom!
Kaga-san broke!
Yana-san, what am I supposed to do now?
Ignore her.
That's what I did.