"Should not go to the island"
"The Opposition"
"The Supporters"
"Mommy" "Mommy" "Mommy"
"To Sensei
I got a gold award. Next up
is the prefecture's exhibit.
Tama"
"I got a silver award
Curse Tama"
"Visiting Old, Learning New
Yamamura Miwa, second year, class one"
"Visiting Old, Learning New"
"Should not go to the island"
"click-click-click"
"Duel!!"
"(keep) flammable" "(discard) nonflammable"
"Evaluation Room"
"impulsive"
"pain"
"Hot-n-Lumpy Corn"
"warm"
"pain"
"A call from Kawafuji-san came in"
"Results
5th Handa Sei (Seishu)
7th Kanzaki Kosuke"
"Arai Tamako" "Kotoishi Naru"
"Kido Hiroshi" "Yamamura Miwa" "Kubota Hina"
"Kotoishi Naru"
"Happy Yer Home"
"By Naru"
"Illustration by Tachibana Masaki"