They're finished!
Let me see.
They're finally here?
Hurry up.
They're so cool.
Nice.
My name is missing...
Why is mine the only one missing?
Our graduation shirts are supposed to stay with us for the rest of our lives...
Did they all hate me?
They're so cool.
Or something...
The material's pretty nice.
The color's not bad, either.
Banri?
What's wrong?
My name...
Your name?
My name is missing!
It's true!
Banri's name is missing!
What? Really?
That's awful.
They'll replace them for free, won't they?
Come on, we'll get them replaced.
Cheer up.
F-for a second, I was afraid it was intentional...
No way.
Just how stupid are you, Banri?
I'm really worried about you.
After we graduate, we won't be together anymore.
Will you be okay?
Can you make it on your own?
Karaoke
Whew!
That was exciting.
Everyone cried way too much.
It made me cry, too.
Banri, good luck on your entrance exams next year.
I'm going to Tokyo,
but I'll help you study when I come back.
Yes or no.
Huh?
I want you to tell me.
This will be the first and last time.
I want a simple answer.
I don't want to be apart from you.
I want to be with you all the time.
I love you.
If you feel the same way,
I'll go to a prep school in Tokyo.
Yes or no.
Tell me your answer.
Could you wait a little bit?
Can I think about it overnight?
Fine.
I'll wait for you on the usual bridge tomorrow.
In high school, I was in love with Linda.
I was serious about her,
but the people around us saw us as siblings or friends.
Linda only thought of me as a friend, too.
The same way that Kaga Kouko...
Yes No
...calls Tada Banri her friend now.
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
They fit perfectly!
My feet feel so light.
They fit someone?
They didn't fit any of us.
Could he be Cinderella?
Note: the white-eyed expression of shock are iconic of
the stage-drama, anime, and manga story, Glass Mask.
Are his feet the ones that fit the glass sneakers?
This kid with the aura of a seedy and unpopular comedian saturating his genes?
Terrifying!
So, where did these come from?
Someone wants to sell those sneakers.
She said she'd sell them for five thousand yen if they fit.
Brand new and unused.
They'd probably normally cost over twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand...
I'll buy them!
Ah, Tada-kun! Hey!
Kaga-san...
...and Linda-senpai.
Linda, Tada Banri said he'd buy these sneakers.
Really?
Linda-senpai, are these yours?
Yeah.
How do they fit?
Perfectly.
Really? Okay, then.
For Tada Banri, they're free.
You're "tada" Banri, after all.
("free")
Seriously?
That's not fair.
Well, he's our junior.
A sweet, precious first year.
I can't take his money.
But...
They weren't my size, but it was love at first sight. It was an impulse buy.
You should wear them instead.
Okay...
Thank you, then.
All right!
Hey.
Are you guys Awa dancing?
Senpai.
Long time, no see.
They're fourth years.
The former club leaders.
How's the search for work going?
Have you already found jobs?
We're just getting started, you idiot.
None of us have any offers yet.
It's not easy.
You'd better prepare yourselves.
Anyway, did you bring us any goodies?
Don't worry.
We brought something.
You need these for the Awa dance, right?
Yeah, but...
The fourth year students pooled their money to make these.
He designed them.
Come on, smile!
Don't you like them?
No.
I hate you guys!
Tada-kun, did something happen with Linda-senpai?
Huh?
Things just seemed a little weird earlier.
Why would Linda-senpai and I...
You're imagining things.
Oh?
If you're worried about something, you can tell me about it.
After all, we're friends.
Yeah.
Friends...
Banri, Kaga-san!
I finally found you!
Okachi Nami...
You split it up wrong.
It's not Okachi.
It's Oka Chinami.
Why don't you come to our welcoming party today?
We're going to have a blast with all of our friends.
I'm the one who suggested it, so I'm organizing it.
Yeah? Where-
I'm not going!
There's no way I'd go!
What?
Tada-kun, I'm going to class.
I knew she'd turn me down.
Why do you want Kaga-san to go so badly?
Most people wouldn't, considering what happened the other day.
You think so?
Unless you're actually a really malicious person.
Maybe you invited Kaga-san because you hate her,
and you're planning to swallow her and chew her up like a Rafflesia enshrined deep in the jungle.
What? Why would I do that?
What kind of creature am I?
Well, I just...
There's something I find irresistible about Kaga-san.
And she's really pretty.
She's definitely really pretty.
Yana's missing out.
Not being acknowledged by the person you love must be hard.
Since they attend the same college, they can't avoid each other.
Are you sure Kaga-san won't come?
Well, I'll try inviting her.
Bar
GOLDENTIME
I'm so happy you're all here!
This'll be a great party!
I'm your organizer and host, Oka Chinami!
Cheers!
CHEERS!
Wow.
So these are all Oka-chan's friends.
It's not just first years here.
There are some older students, too.
Just how many people does she know?
So, what are you doing here?
My friend Tada-kun convinced me to come.
He said we should dive into all kinds of new things.
Aren't your friends from the film club here?
Why don't you go hang out with them?
Don't order me around.
L-look, why don't you try to get along just for today?
What happened?
It's complicated...
Don't tell me...
It's Hell in there!
We didn't see anything!
Why don't you learn from Chinami?
What does that mean?
I'm saying you should change seats and try talking to different people.
You still don't have any other friends, do you?
I do!
The seniors in the festival club are nice to me.
Linda-senpai is really nice.
I don't need to copy Miss Ultrasonic.
Don't call her that!
You'd never be able to gather this many people!
Well, neither could you!
Besides,
you're only pretending to like
Miss Ultrasonic to spite me!
That's not true at all!
It's definitely true!
I don't know what happened,
You just think it will hurt me!
but shouldn't we separate them?
It has nothing to do with you.
Yeah.
Just how overconfident are you, anyway?
H-hey, Kaga-san...
You'll never be able to confess your feelings to her!
Can you-
You don't have the resolve!
Don't assume I can't!
If I'm wrong, why don't you prove it?
Oh, I will!
Hey, Chinami!
Oh, Yana!
And Kaga-san, thank you for coming!
I'm so happy.
Chinami.
Yes?
I love you.
I want to go out with you.
What?
I love you.
I want to go out with you.
What?
Don't be stupid.
He's done it now...
What should we do?
Don't ask me...
K-Kaga-san?!
H-he really did it...
Ladies, I have tribute for you!
Tada Banri, you're here?
Tribute? What tribute?
He's so hot!
Thank you!
Take her, too.
Ah! It's that girl!
Her skin is so smooth and beautiful!
It looks delicious!
She's so cute, I just want to torment her.
You're a monster, Banri.
Am I?
He sprung it on you...
I know!
Ta-da!
It's the Oka Chinami Camera!
The Okamera for short!
I've been filming everyone with this.
I'd like to put it all together in a single film eventually.
Oh, right. You're in the film club.
This is the only time we'll be new students at a university.
These moments are precious.
Anyway, say something funny.
Uh... um...
I'm 2D-kun, Sato Takaya.
I'm nearsighted.
Next, Banri.
I-I'm Tada Banri.
I'm alive, I guess.
I can't think of anything funny!
That was fun.
Can I have your email address?
The tea club's going out for a second round.
This way if you're coming!
I don't think I can...
They met the same fate we did...
Pedestrians
and
Bicycles
Only
Come on, Kaga-san. Walk.
I've got it.
Come on, catch me.
Seriously, that's enough!
I don't feel so good.
I'm going to be sick.
Do it in here.
Let's go home.
Kaga-san, please. Take a taxi.
I want to have more fun.
You're my friend. Come with me.
It's late, and I don't have any money.
Then let's go to your place.
Let's talk all night.
About friendship and youth.
Let's badmouth Mitsuo, too.
Can we stop?
What?
I don't want to be friends anymore.
Okay?
Say "yes".
I don't want to be friends with you anymore.
Yana-san is still all you think about.
Have you thought about how it makes me feel to see that?
It's too hard for me to be with you.
I'm not your friend anymore.
Okay?
Do you still want to be friends with me?
Is it because you feel comfortable being with me?
Because I understand your awkward and useless self,
and still love you?
Quit acting so spoiled.
When you rejected me, you lost the right to want those things!
I shouldn't have tried to be your friend.
I can't associate with you anymore.
I don't want to.
Wait.
I won't wait.
I won't wait for anyone anymore.
Tada-kun...
I...
She's riding.
Tada-kun, don't do this!
Please, listen to me.
No.
Goodbye.
Clean up!
The next group is coming in to use this room.
Let's clean this place up and get out!
Okay!
What's wrong, Tada Banri?
You seemed down today.
Yeah...
Let's go.
Did you have a fight with Kouko-chan?
Okay.
Linda, we're leaving.
Kouko-chan was looking at you.
You shouldn't make your girlfriend so sad.
Linda-senpai... do you think we're dating?
Well, you're so close.
We're not.
I see...
How can she act like she doesn't know anything?
Oh, I know.
You're more than friends, but not yet dating?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
What... about me?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Maybe someone you've been dating since high school?
Even if I ask...
I'm sure you'll tell me you don't!
No one. You'll say there's no one!
You've erased him!
How can you do that?
Don't you think it's cruel?
Don't you feel bad for me... for the old Tada Banri?
I'm doing the same thing.
I act like I don't know them.
Not Linda-senpai, not my parents, not anyone I knew...
The same goes for me.
Banri...
Banri!
Banri, wait!
I'm the worst...
Banri! Banri!
I don't know that name!
Who is it?!
You were like a bomb.
One wrong move, and I might have lost you again.
I didn't know what to do...
I forgot everything.
I'm afraid!
I'm so afraid, I can't help myself!
I don't know what I'd do if it was my fault...
Your fault?
The day after graduation,
I went to tell you my answer.
But I didn't make it in time.
Is it my fault?
Is it my fault because I wasn't there in time?
It can't end like that...
It can't!
Linda-senpa-
Tada-kun?
Hey... What's wrong?
Did something happen with Linda-senpai?
The answer...
The answer is "yes"!
Tada-kun, wait!
No!
Why are you running?!
Please! Wait!
Tada-kun!
Let me borrow that!
I don't know where this path leads.
I don't know which paths I've chosen until now.
Right and left, yes and no.
We must continuously choose which path to take.
Yes and no are tangled in an endless web,
and I don't know which is the right path.
If I did...
If I could correctly trace back all of
Tada Banri's decisions until now...
I'd find Linda-senpai there.
But...
I can't turn back.
I can't find the past I've lost.
If I fall again...
...can I do everything over?
What's the answer?
Tada-kun!
I caught you.
K-Kaga-san?
Don't run anymore.
Don't go where I can't reach you!
Stay with me forever!
What?
I love you, Tada-kun.
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
Masquerade
Ta-da! It's the Okalesia!
Ugh, it's her.
I'll eat anything.
I'm a healthy girl.
Huh? The flower under me?
It's a carnivorous flower.
Oka-chan's being eaten!