So young...
...yet already writing in monotony.
What?
Very textbook-like, or rather...
...written for the sake of winning.
Did you try to overcome the wall of mediocrity?
"Award Celebration"
Excuse me, Director, but...
When you've been in the business as long as I have, you can see true value.
What an uninteresting piece.
Hey, about the picture we took earlier...
Hey, Handa!
What's so wrong with my work?!
Are you crazy?! What the hell are you doing?!
Let me go! Damn him for saying that!
He doesn't have a clue what I had to go through!
Ouch!
"From: Kawafuji
Sub: None
How's the island?"
Like I'd know...
"Taxi"
"Airport
Goto Bus"
"Buses 1-7 operate 6/14-7/31
If flights are canceled, operations may
be put on hold, so we ask for your
understanding in this matter."
Where is everyone?
"Barakakodon"
"Translation: Spirited Child"
"After you land at Fukue Airport,
use the taxi, and once you arrive, contact
the Village Leader, who will be taking care
of you. Be sure to mind your manners."
You sure are a lucky one, y'know?
Heck, if I hadn't passed ya,
it would've taken ya half a day to get to Nanan'dake.
What?!
Would've hadta walk half a day...
Um... I can't understand what you're saying.
Eh?! What'd ya say?!
--Huh?!
--Eh?!
Hey, I can't make out a word yer sayin'...
Never mind. I'll just ignore him...
There really isn't anything here...
Well now, lookie there! It's the ocean!
The what?
Oh...
How 'bout it?
My little tyke is crazy 'bout the ocean,
an' hollers just lookin' at it.
How about it...?
It's just like any old ocean...
Maybe it doesn't look nice
because my mind isn't at peace.
M-My ribs...!
'Bout as far I'm gonna take ya.
I got my fields a waitin'.
Okay...
Young man, it's not 'cause you ain't calm or nothin'
that the ocean don't look nice to ya.
It's gonna be cloudy in the afternoon.
Ah... I see...
Ya gotta watch that there ocean when it's rough and tumblin'.
Ya don't get it, do ya?
"Kijima Transport"
Handa-san!
Handa-san?
Handa-san! Kijima Transport here!
Coming!
Huh?
I'm from Kijima Transport!
This should be all of it.
Um, aren't you going to help me carry these in?
Oh... We don't do that.
'Scuse me!
Service sure takes a nosedive without any competition.
I've been waiting for you.
Wha--?!
Um, you're... the Village Leader?
It must have been tiring coming from Tokyo.
Here, the key.
Aren't there any buses or taxis here?
There's a bus running once a day.
You can call a taxi, but there aren't many here.
If you need to go to the shopping district,
I'll lend you my car.
Well, can you please leave me alone for a week?
I want to concentrate on my calligraphy.
Yes, no problem.
Here, pass me the key.
Take all the time you want.
No need to worry about food, either.
Huh? That was quick.
Um, no one is supposed to be living here, right?
Yes, that's right.
The place feels like it's been lived in...
Huh?
It's... It's just your imagination.
--A seal?!
--Oh, don't worry.
It's just a plain old seal.
A squat toilet...
What is this?!
Oh, never used a balanced flue before?
You crank it like this to turn the fire on.
See?
So, this is where I'm going to live...
Are you okay?
I... I'm fine.
There has to be something in here.
You found me!
Village Leader! Who is she?!
She's one of the village brats.
Looks like they used this place as a base.
--Base...?
--Oh, a colony. Colony.
Uh, that's harder to understand...
I'm sorry. I did tell her to leave.
Hey, Nii-chan, you a Junon Boy? [Junon Boy: "a cool, handsome man"]
--Huh?
--Hey, Naru! It's rude to speak like that!
Miwa-nee said that a Junon Boy is cool.
Nii-chan is cool, so he's a Junon Boy!
Maybe so, but he's actually a master calligrapher.
Okay, Village Leader!
A Junon Boy who can also write!
That's not it.
Naru thinks he's a Junon Boy.
Well, to start with, he's not young enough to be a "boy."
Hey.
But the people on TV fake their age, right?
--That's what Miwa-nee said.
--Hey.
Well, I'm sure faking their age is part of their work.
Hey! Cowboys can be "boys" even if they're middle-aged!
I'm sorry about that.
She's really hard to reason with.
Um, can you please get out?
Locked...?
Damn it...!
This place, a "base"? What a joke.
But I guess I'm lucky that the place was ready to live in.
Wow...! Naru wants to write too!
How'd you get in...?!
Who does he think he is?
Just because he won...
He spat on the Director.
He's basically dead in the world of calligraphy.
He's so rude...
Don't talk to him.
Everyone will think you're like him.
Don't get involved with him.
"Four Seasons
Perfect Indifference
Self-Respect
Amidst Enemies"
Damn it! I can't concentrate!
Is there a kettle in this house?
Yup, you need to eat the corn treats stacked!
Well, I'm overweight, so I'm fine eating them one by one.
--Hey.
--Wha--?! Handa-sensei!
Want some finger-corns?
Rolly-rolly!
It's a new move! A new move!
That's amazing, Naru!
--Show me how you did that!
--I can't work like this...
Focus... Focus. Focus!
What the...?!
"Kotoishi Naru"
Hey, look! Pretty good?
Who said you could write?
Come on, loosen up, Junon Boy.
I'm not a Junon Boy.
Like your name, "Kotoishi Naru,"
I have a name too.
How'd you know Naru's name?!
You must be one of them mind readers!
Do you think I'm stupid? Or are you just stupid?
Naru knows, too! Junon Boy's name!
Well... good for you.
Um...
Um, let's see...
The Village Leader was sayin'...
Got it!
That's one archaic effect...
Junon Takeo!
"Handa Seishu"
Handa Seishu.
Junon aside, where'd you get the "Takeo" from?
Sounds like a middle schooler's pen name!
It's a pseudonym!
Wow... Sensei writes so neat. You're so good.
Of course it's good.
It looks like the school teacher's writing.
Already writing in monotony...
Very textbook-like...
What an uninteresting piece.
Oh, that's right! The Village Leader is gonna bring dinner...
Hey! Why're you doing that?!
It looked so nice, too!
Be quiet!
Like you'd understand!
Don't try to make it seem like you know!
Ouch!
Wait up!
I'm such a loser...
Getting all mad because she was right...
That was so immature...
What? Going to the island? What for?
My old man said for me to cool myself off.
Said I'm lacking something as a human, never mind a calligrapher.
The heck are you laughing about?!
"Kawafuji Fine Arts"
You punched an old man who uses a cane.
I've got no condolences for you.
You should just apologize.
Hell, no!
That geezer and my old man know nothing.
What's wrong with being true to the basics?!
Hey, is doing calligraphy fun when you feel that way?
The fundamentals are the most beautiful.
I've done nothing wrong.
♪...the most important thing... ♪
What's the "most important thing"?
She heard me singing...!
What? What's the most important thing?
What? What? What?
What are you doing here?!
I'm not going to apologize!
Why would Sensei say sorry?
I was the one who said something that Sensei didn't like.
So I tried to write it again, but...
I can't write like Sensei.
I'm sorry!
H-Hey...
You've done nothing wrong.
So you're not angry?
No...
There's nothing to apologize for...
So happy...!
Huh?
I'm so happy you're not angry.
Saying sorry is so scary.
But I'm glad I said sorry!
Sorry for yelling at you.
Hm?
Nothing...
Hurry and get up.
Okay!
You did really good writing this.
Yup. It was easy to copy.
Sensei's writing is just like a textbook.
Why'd you do that for?!
Sorry, natural reflexes.
You don't even know why I got mad, do you?
This was just for practice, so you could've thrown...
You did it first to me!
Huh?
Sensei?
Sen--
Don't scare me! I thought you croaked.
With how heavy my clothes are, I will!
C'mon, you city folks don't know a thing!
See, you have to do this.
Whoa! What's that?!
First, close the neck part of the shirt.
Then get air in through the bottom.
Now swim!
Whoa! I can't believe I'm surprised over this...
Do you swim in deep waters like that all the time?
Yup!
The fearsome power of kids...
Sensei! I'll show you something neat!
What?
If you climb that wall, you can see a super-duper sunset!
Wait a minute. You're going to climb this breakwater?!
Yup! Gotta climb to see it.
Never mind the sunset.
Look at the skies.
You won't be able to see a thing through all these clouds.
You gotta climb to find out.
If you don't try, you won't find out.
Watch it!
No problem, I'm okay. I just rushed.
I'm here!
Hurry on up, Sensei!
If you don't climb this wall, you're not gonna see a thing!
Did you...
...try to overcome the wall of mediocrity?
See? Pretty, right?
Yeah...
It sure is...
Hey, yer back, eh?
--Hey!
--The first villager...?
Grandpa!
Grandpa? Your grandpa?
Yup!
Hey, Sensei!
Better hurry or we're gonna break open them boxes for ya!
Huh?! Why?!
Ya just moved here...
...so we're here ta help ya!
Help?
Tokyo, eh?
Mighty far place you came from.
I'm going in, 'kay?
Uh, yes.
C'mon! Hurry, Sensei!
Did your grandpa call for everyone to come?
Huh?
Nope.
Everyone saw the mover's truck and came here.
Not like we get plenty of folks moving here.
But I don't know everyone...
...and I can't have them...
My, what a handsome man.
Sorry that I'm late.
Hina!
Look, Sensei!
This is Naru's friend, Hina!
Nice to meet you.
Huh?
Hina's super shy!
Oh... So I shouldn't talk to her too much, then?
Huh?! What now?!
Hina wants Sensei's attention.
I-I see... Sorry about that...
Huh? Why...?!
Hina cries when she's happy too.
Wow, she's hard to handle!
Butt... stab!
You were wide open!
Hey, Kenta!
We said at the class meeting that butt-stabbing isn't allowed!
Shut up, smoke face!
So sorry, there.
You just can't get through to brats like them.
You okay?
I'm fine...
And this here is...?
He's the head teacher for the school branch.
Hi there.
Heh, there's nothing funnier than seeing a handsome guy being shamed.
Why, you...!
So, we can just put them in the house?
Ah... yes.
Sensei! See you again!
Yeah.
What is it, Kawafuji?
Yeah...
Now I kind of get why my old man sent me to this island.
If I come up with something good, I'll submit it.
I'll ask for your help then.
Also... can you apologize to the Director for me?
I was wrong too...
Do it myself? I can't do that yet...
Hm? This island?
Yeah...
"Ease, Comfort, Relief"
I think I'll manage.
Um... I brought... champon noodles.
Freaky.