Hey, y'all! C'mon up to the seashell shop!
"20 Yen"
C'mon up!
Should be around here...
Please search carefully today.
I don't want to stay at the camping site anymore.
Sure, sure.
The heck is this?
It's the seashell shop. C'mon up!
Wha--?!
Grandma!
She's back.
Hey! C'mon up!
What's with the competitiveness?
Are you playing shop? What are you selling?
Seashells.
Well, can I get one?
Sure, here you go!
I didn't know you liked kids.
--Officially, anyway.
--You're pretty terrible.
What about you, Kawafuji-san?
Give this one another ten years, and I could like her.
That's not liking kids. That's liking women.
Specifically, I like my women--ahem--mature.
Eew! Gross!
--The heck?! You trying to break my glasses?!
--Eew, yuck! Something got on me! So disgusting!
You use a toothpick to dig 'em out like this, and eat 'em.
Eew! Gross, gross, gross!
"*Good kids don't eat them raw!"
--Little girl...
--Hm?
Is there a person named
Handa Seishu living around here?
Handa... Seishu...?
Nope.
Huh? You're kidding.
But there is a sensei with a fancy name like that.
Sensei?
A calligraphy sensei.
That's him! Do you know where Handa-sensei lives?
I'll tell you if you buy a seashell.
Pretty shrewd.
Ah, then sell me that one.
Oh... Quite an eye to choose this one.
But only a rich person like an IT prez or a major leaguer can buy this.
What? Well, then...
...how's about a card payment?
C-Card...!
So, how much do you want?
I want you to be my guide too, so I'll pay you good.
Mi... Mi...
A million yen to you, ya thief!
Don't treat me like a thief when
I haven't bargained a single yen!
I never saw one before... So this is a card...
Here.
All right, little girl. Take us...
Just a sec! I'm gonna show this to grandma!
Now just you wait! My stuff is first.
Stop it! Lemme go!
Hurry and take us--
Where'd ya come from?
Huh? Well...
What's the matter, Head Teach?
--We got some weird folks here.
--Kidnappers?
Look at them tattoos he's got.
--Ah, well, it's not what you...
--Call the fire squad.
We're gonna go to the village meeting.
Let's hear what ya have ta say there, 'kay?
--Huh?
--C'mon!
Huh? Well, hey...!
Kawafuji-san--!
"Yosonmon"
"Translation: The guys from Tokyo"
Let's eat.
Let's eat...
Time to eat!
Wait, why are you two eating at my place?!
Dad and Mom went to the village meeting at the community center.
Grandpa too!
It tastes better than eating alone, right?
Right!
I don't mind eating alone...
Sensei, you got fat since you came here.
No way!
Seriously.
The country's loose atmosphere is spoiling me.
Men with a little meat are just right!
By the way, it's been bothering me for a bit, but what's with the scribbles?
I met a guy who had scribbles on him too.
Probably not a "normal" guy...
Scribbles? More like tattoos, right?
A flower... Dog... What are those dots?
"Dog"
Marble chocolates.
Did that guy's tattoo look like an eagle?
It was all messy and I couldn't tell.
I've actually gotten a ton of emails from him since yesterday.
Huh?
"Kawafuji"
That may be my friend.
After falling in the sea a number of times, the keys were acting up and I couldn't reply.
Forget the mobile,
I'm surprised that you have a friend.
--I'm gonna beat you.
--Sensei.
Miwa? What's the matter?
Whatcha mean, "What's the matter?"
Those two...
Hey, guys, come in from here!
That's the entrance.
Um, I'd prefer you use the entrance...
Do we have guests?
They're saying they're your friends, Sensei.
"Drunk"
Yeaaah...
Kawa... fuji...?
Why's he so out of it?
Something like, he was gonna kidnap some kid,
so he was being lectured until now at the village meeting.
You're exactly righty...!
But with all the people, it just became a drinking get-together.
--I'm sooo sorry...
--Ah, I see...
Heeey, Handa!
You... Do you even know how worried I was for you?
A city boy like you living in the country like this...
Great, so now you're going to cry?
I was just so worried, and worried...
Kawafuji...
You were this worried for me?
My friend Handa!
My friend Kawafuji!
My friend forever!
Kawafuji!
Handa!
Crane-style!
How dare you freakin' ignore my calls?!
Are you fake?! Are you a fake friend?!
Sorry! My mobile was acting up, and...
Screw you! Do whatcha need to do to call me back!
W-Well, I figured you would find your way.
Dammit! Don't underestimate the inconvenience of the rural!
Wha--?! The hell are you doing barfing here?!
It must've been a pain coming from Tokyo.
It took about three hours by plane with connections.
Wow. I'm still not sure how to ride a plane.
I haven't even been on one before.
You kids never went to Tokyo before?
--Nope.
--Only as far as Nagasaki.
For me, Hyogo.
Seriously? I don't believe it.
Ah, Sensei? We're outta konomon["pickles"].
Can ya get more?
Get more? Are you asking an elder to do stuff for you?
This is your house, Sensei, so c'mon, hurry.
--You're all like friends.
--Middle schoolers nowadays...
You don't seem like Sensei's friend, but...
...did you just come along with the drunk over there?
I really wanted to meet Handa-san.
Here's my card.
"Kanzaki Kosuke"
I'm a calligrapher, Kanzaki Kosuke.
--Naru wanna card too. Naru too.
--I was drawn to calligraphy through my admiration of Handa-san.
--Naru too. Naru too!
--Huh... But you look super young.
--Naru too!! Naru too!
--I'm eighteen. I get mistaken for a middle schooler a lot.
--Yay!
--An eighteen-year-old calligrapher?
Where'd I hear this before...?
Last time, I mustered the courage to challenge the Tokyo Kasho Exhibit...
The same exhibit that Handa-san submitted to.
--What?!
But I'm so bad with sensing the mood of things.
I actually took first place from the person I admire.
I suddenly felt closer to Handa-san, who I thought was unreachable.
Well, I guess Handa-san wasn't serious back then.
Isn't this the guy he was talkin' about?
Y'know, the mochi toss?
Yeah, the "second place" incident...
The heck is he planning to do, coming to see Sensei?
Maybe he came just to see him bitter.
If Sensei finds out who he is...
Is this much konomon enough?
Ah, Handa-san, here's my card...
--Nooo!
What do you mean by "no"?
Don't you normally eat this much?
No, it isn't about the amount!
Wait, that's too much! How hooked are you?!
You're the funny type, aren't you, Handa-san?
Aw, man, if he finds out he lost to this tacky guy...
And with how much pride Sensei has...
...he could commit suicide.
Handa-san, about the last exhibit...
Aah!
Hey, hey, look at the time!
Yeah! You gotta go soon!
You're staying at an inn, right?!
We stayed overnight at a campsite yesterday.
Oh, really? Then ya gotta go back to Camp Village, then!
Walking the road at night's dangerous!
Kawafuji is sleeping, so why don't you stay here tonight?
--Huh?!
--Huh? Really?
Thank goodness. I didn't like the campsite with all the bugs.
Plus, there's a lot I wanted to talk about.
So what now? He's all into staying over here!
Well then, we better stay over too and stop him.
I've got a career advising
I gotta be at tomorrow.
What is it?
Sensei's friend is Naru's friend, so here's a sign of friendship.
What's this?
A dirty Monster Ball!
--What the heck did ya do?!
--Naru's precious buggies!
Don't keep weird pets!
--Be quiet...
--Damn it! Get out!
No, Sensei! Don't agitate them!
Wha--?! Stink?!
See?! I told ya!
--Hiro-nii!
--'Kay!
Here!
If you use this, you can catch 'em without 'em stinkin'.
You guys know the strangest stuff...
It's super useful, so don't call it "strange."
No more... I wanna go home...
You should just go back for tonight.
The smell is gonna attract more of them bugs.
What?!
We'll be back again tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll be waiting.
Oh, Handa-san.
Hm?
Can I... call you "Sensei" too?
Sure, whatever.
We made it through...
Hm, so that's Kanzaki Kosuke...
He doesn't look the type to be doing calligraphy.
The dirty side of him was coming out, though.
--Wait a sec! You knew him?!
--Wait!
"From: Kawafuji
Sub: Answer the phone!"
Not personally, but I did get an email from Kawafuji.
"I'll bring along the brat, Kanzaki Kosuke, who won first place at the exhibit."
"He's a bit unique, so be prepared."
--See?
--Not "see"!
Couldn't ya tell how stressed we were back there?!
Huh? Really?
Well, it's not that it doesn't bother me, and I am envious, but...
...I feel more at ease than before.
Sensei...
Now, let's go and catch the remaining bugs.
Yeah!
I'm lost...
I'm sorry to bother you again today.
Is tea okay?
Ah, you're too kind.
Kawafuji isn't coming today?
"Sun Sun Camp Village"
He has a major hangover, and can't even get up.
Yeah, he can be like that at times...
Like, he always does things at the wrong time.
--Tea in this heat...?
--Tea has got to be black bean tea...
Did you hear anything about me from Kawafuji-san?
Something about you getting first place, and it went to your head.
That's pretty harsh.
I have a lot of respect for you, Handa-sensei.
Look at my collection!
I collected all the publications
I could that you appeared in.
"All You Need to Know About Calligraphy"
"Learning from Scratch:
Introduction to Calligraphy"
The talented calligrapher with a master calligrapher as a father.
All the publications give praise that Sensei's words are true to fundamentals, and beautiful.
See the smug look on the gravure?
"Calligrapher
Handa Seishu"
You can't make an expression like this without confidence!
In this one, you're in a black suit.
Was it black to represent ink?
"Handa Seishu"
What? This is just embarrassing...
Can you see? Sensei, you're the one who I want to be!
Speaking of, I love this comment the most.
"...breathe in the refined air, and when
I speak to the paper and brush...
--...they listen, and answer back to me.
--Stop it! Don't read it out loud!
To me, calligraphy is a cathartic activity."
What's karuta-sushi?
"Karuta" "Sushi"
Be quiet.
Don't console me in silence!
This is even more wonderful.
Stop the disgrace! Take this!
Hey, that's mean!
Who's meaner here?!
You did come to mock me, didn't you?!
N-Not at all!
I wanted to hear Sensei's neat lines!
I even brought a voice recorder for them!
What kind of a fan are you?!
The reason I entered the Kasho Exhibit was to meet you, Sensei!
What are you doing in the country like this?!
Sensei, the calligraphy that was entered in the exhibit...
...was what you wrote after you came to this island, right?!
Sensei! Let's go back to Tokyo together!
Ugh, my head...
Hm? What is it?
Thanks for yesterday.
We came to see Kanzaki-kun, but where is he?
Ah, he's at Handa's place now.
Huh, already?
What? You came to warn him not to shoot his mouth off to Handa?
Well, yeah.
Good luck on that.
It isn't easy keeping watch over an adult, right?
It's not like we're takin' care of him!
Don't say any more.
I know exactly how you feel.
Despite how he looks, he's quite a handful, so someone's gotta support him from behind.
Me and Handa are friends from back in middle school.
--He always had the hardest time being social...
--Are you stupid?
...and each time he opened his mouth, he only spoke high-handedly.
--He gets depressed easily,
--I'm such a loser...
--and closes himself off from others.
--A barrier...?
In the end, he even raised his fist against the Director.
You can't imagine the pain of cleaning up after that.
I can actually imagine that easily...
I thought being in the country required being social with others...
...so I thought he was going to give up right away and come back.
He must really be enjoying his life here.
Can you keep an eye out for him a bit longer?
If you know so much about Sensei, why'd ya bring Kanzaki-kun here?
Sensei was super depressed when he lost first place to him.
Ah... Another headache...
Don't change the subject!
I'm an art dealer.
Handa's my golden goose before he's my friend.
Golden goose?
I need to have him write quality works or I'd be in trouble, right?
He's gotten close to finding something since he came to this island.
He probably just doesn't know what, which is why he's lost.
A person needs a rival to become better, right?
Now, then.
I still got a hangover, so I'm gonna sleep it off today.
Let Handa know I'll stop by tomorrow.
That sure is Sensei's friend, all right.
Is this like a "sparing the club and spoiling the child" thing?
Before that, is calligraphy about winning and losing?
Not like it's martial arts...
Please return to Tokyo and face calligraphy seriously like before!
Just a second.
I came to this island to raise my skills in calligraphy.
I can't go back until I see results.
Results?
What do you mean by "results," Sensei?!
I'd been doing calligraphy since elementary school, but...
...every day was just more boring practice, and I was thinking of quitting.
It was then that I reluctantly went along to an exhibit and saw your work.
And what a beautiful work it was...
But now, before even getting results, you've lost your touch!
Lost my touch?!
Can't you tell?!
Sensei, your calligraphy is trying to be too unique, or rather...
...just being written by inspiration, and it isn't like you, Sensei!
Really?
Losing to me is proof of that!
I thought you'd be bitter, but you aren't noticing that you've gotten worse!
This environment is ruining you!
Hey, wait...
Let's go back to Tokyo!
Like I said...
You're the one who said that writing to be recognized by others is everything!
What an uninteresting piece.
So young, yet already writing in monotony.
Very textbook-like.
--Did you try to overcome the wall of mediocrity?
--Sensei! Listen to what I have to say!
--I just wanna have fun writing without worrying 'bout that.
--Let's go back, Sensei!
--Recognized by...?
--Staying here isn't good for you, Sensei!
Sensei! Sen--
Shut up!
Aah! What the hell?!
After winning first, but being told that my calligraphy is uninteresting...
...I then write something good, but don't get first.
I'm so confused...!
I've got no clue what's right anymore...
A paper airplane?
That's from my collection!
Who did this?!
Wow! Naru, your airplanes fly so far!
They fly when the wind blows!
Sensei! Look at 'em fly!
Screw you brats!
What the heck! Sensei, say something to...
Be my guest.
The beautiful words you saw
are well-behaved words written exactly how my father told me to write.
I'm fine being reprimanded, as long as...
...I write words that only I,
Handa Seishu, can write.
I don't know what's right, but...
...I feel it isn't right for me to rush back to Tokyo because of what you said.
I want to change...
...here.
You girls, it's dangerous up there. Come down.
--Okay!
--Yes!
You go on ahead and wait for me.
I'll ride the wind, and get to you quick.
Sensei! Can you say that line one more time...!
Ah, shoot! That worked better than I thought!
Naru! Bring the Village Leader over!
Hina! Go and get some ice!
Okay!
Too bad.
He's still going to get better...
I need to do better too...
Why's he here?
Stuff just happened.
It feels better making dinner with young folks around.
An old hag like you shouldn't be actin' like some tween...
"(Dialect) I'm going to beat you
until your jaws come off"
I'm gonna wallop ya an' crack them jaw bones of yers until ya lose 'em!
Oh, by the way, Sensei.
Naru was passing out mags like this to everyone in the village.
Sensei, you're really famous, aren't you?
--Ah, um, eh...
--Ah!
Can you autograph this?
Does your mom have a grudge against me?
Sorry, man. In the first place, asking for an autograph...
You have one?
Um, you said earlier that everyone in the village...
Sensei, I read it!
Aah... Go figure...
--That's really somethin', bein' published in Tokyo!
--Can I get your autograph?
I don't have an autograph sheet, so can you write on my shirt?
Ya ain't a sensei fer nothin'!
To me, calligraphy is to breathe in the refined air...
--Aah...! Stop!
--...a cathartic activity...
I'm going home to Tokyo--!
A dirty Monster Ball!
Good evening.
Don't keep weird pets!
--They went there!
--Be quiet...
No, help me! I wanna go back to Tokyo!
Ah, Hiroshi!
Hiroshi!
That's dangerous... Dangerous...
Sensei, can I let it go...?
The combatants...
They've multiplied...!