Banri!
Linda-senpai?
What are you doing here?
Why are you dressed like that?
What about you, Linda-senpai?
Composing Message
Tada Banri
No subject
Why
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
Don't Look Back
Hand in hand let's go party night!
Kokoro odoru tomerarenai no
Naite waratte kimi to no kioku zutto wasurenai
Hontou no jibun wa doko ni iru toka
Otona ni narutte taihen de
Ima wa wasurete mo ii kana
Yoru ga matte iru kara
Kokoro wo hazumase aeru toki wo
Hashagi mawareba
Tsutaetai omoi ni ima
Kizuite shimaisou de
Kako to mirai osorete ite mo
Karappo no mama ja ugeokenai
Tanoshimeba it's all right hajimeyou
Yana koto zenbu wasurete kimi to issho ni odori akaseba
Motto suteki na jibun ni nareru sonna ki ga suru no
Owaranai Golden Time gyutto chikazuku kimi to no kyori wa
Tsukazu hanarezu mawari michi demo taisetsu ni shitai
Yes!
Hey, you.
Yes?
That's quite the getup.
Do you always dress like that?
No.
It's for my job.
Hey, take a picture with me.
Me, too.
Just the two of us first.
Yanako's working hard.
He is attractive.
I'm so cute!
I'm cuter!
What? Linda-senpai?!
Nana-senpai offered Linda-senpai a job, too.
I just found out, too.
Don't be embarrassed.
You wear that look pretty well.
Linda-senpai, you look cool, too.
In fact...
You look seriously hot!
I told you not to stare!
I have a message from the boss.
"It's a waste for you to be a waiter.
Get on the stage."
What?!
He said he'd pay you ten thousand more if you do it.
Do it, Yana-san!
Earn funds for your summer vacation!
You talk like this doesn't concern you at all!
Come on. Just do it, Yanako.
Everything's an experience.
It's an order.
Come on!
I'll do it!
I'll do anything for money!
Go for it, Yana-san!
We'll be watching your display of bravery!
You don't have to watch!
Hey, do you have a girlfriend?
Huh?
What do you think of one night stands?
Um... I...
Excuse me.
We need to borrow him over here.
Huh?
Thanks. You really saved me.
People take advantage of you because you get flustered.
Keep it together.
I've never experienced anything like this before.
I got a little overwhelmed.
What you need is spirit.
Throw your chest out.
Right...
What are you looking at?!
Sorry, sorry.
Sheesh...
TADA
Tesshi-chan, congratulations!
Thank you.
Working hard?
Yana-san.
You seemed to be having fun.
You might be good at this kind of work.
What? You can't be serious.
The guys around me told me to just copy them.
That's all I was doing.
You didn't seem uncomfortable with it, though.
Don't you think so, Banri?
Yes.
Linda-senpai's right.
Hey, now...
Hey, Linda.
Lend me a hand.
Okay.
You really seemed to be into it.
You even got all oiled up.
Are you sure you didn't actually have fun?
You're right.
It doesn't feel that bad.
You know, being a device that heats up the party.
I think I know what you mean.
Yana-san was right.
On this insular night in the life of Tada Banri,
I actually found myself enjoying being in this environment I wasn't used to,
dressing as someone else and becoming a working machine.
Linda-senpai really does look great.
Maybe I'll get a picture with her, too.
Incoming Call
Kaga Kouko
Are you tired?
Doing okay?
I'm actually having fun.
I might even get into this.
I know what you mean!
This is actually my fourth time working one of the boss' events!
You two are so cute.
Can I get a picture?
Sure.
That's great.
Take some with this next.
This isn't what it looks like, Kouko-chan!
You're mistaken!
It's me! Me!
It's Linda!
Hayashida Nana...
I know that.
I'm so sorry!
I got carried away!
It's my fault!
I'm really sorry!
Don't make a fuss in front of the guests.
Come on.
Kaga-san, this way.
I'm working right now.
I'll explain everything later.
Wait until I'm done with work.
Okay?
You can't stay here, though.
I know. My apartment.
Use this to get in.
I'll go there as fast as I can when I'm finished.
Work.
Sorry.
Yes.
Next: Tada Banri-kun!
Good work.
Thank you.
There's a lot in here!
Now I can make it through summer!
Mine may have lost its use...
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
I should text Kaga-san!
You have
63 new messages
Inbox
No subject: Kaga Kouko
Kaga Kouko
Received Message
No subject
Where are you?
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Has your injury worsened?
I'm going to your place.
I'm here. Why aren't you?
I'll try the convenience store.
I'll try the family restaurant.
Did you get in an accident?
I tried calling the police.
Are you at Mitsuo's apartment?
Are you on campus?
I'm going to the festival club's training room.
TADA
Kaga-san?
Kaga-san...
I'm really...
I'm sorry for throwing a drink at you.
For hitting you, too.
That's-
Your injury hasn't even healed yet.
I'm sorry.
Kaga-san.
I wanted to be a good girlfriend who wouldn't do those things.
I failed again.
I just can't do it.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Sorry!
I wanted to take you to the beach.
I didn't want you to pay for me.
I wanted to be a cool boyfriend.
That's why I lied and secretly took a job.
I didn't know Linda-senpai would be working with me!
I got carried away by the atmosphere there.
It put me in a weird mood.
That's why I did it.
That's all. Really.
I'm sorry for making you worry!
I'm sorry for lying, too!
I'm really sorry!
Then...
Why do you...
You said that was all.
Don't lie.
I'm sorry.
Linda... Senpai was a classmate before I lost my memory.
We were in the same class and track club together.
We were friends.
I had forgotten about Linda before I ran into her at college.
Linda recognized me right away, but she didn't want to confuse me.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want you to know.
Why?
Before I lost my memory...
I was in love with Linda.
I didn't want you to worry about that.
You mean because I'm an annoying woman?
No.
Because you thought it'd be a nuisance if I made a big deal about it?
Because I felt guilty!
What?
My feelings sometimes return to me.
Out of nowhere, like flashbacks.
What do you mean?
I can't do anything about it.
Sometimes my soul screams like a storm that it wants to go back to Linda.
My memories don't return, but my feelings...
My desire to see Linda suddenly returns!
I don't know what to do!
Why would you say that?
Kaga-san?
I wanted to be a good girlfriend.
When I found the photo,
I decided to wait for you to tell me.
I wanted to stop interrogating you and becoming mentally unstable.
I worked hard! I did!
I was doing my best!
Kaga-san-
But if you say that, I...
What should I do?
It's all for nothing!
Everything's ruined!
Just look at me!
This is what happens to me!
What should I do?
I don't want to be like this!
I don't!
I really don't!
Why would you say that?
Why? Why did you tell me?
I wanted to be honest with you...
I didn't want to know!
Kaga-san, wait-!
You're a storm.
You rile up my heart like a storm.
Don't remember anything else.
Please, don't remember the past!
That's the only thing I want from you.
Please.
I understand.
I won't.
Can I call you Banri from now on?
Yeah.
Will you call me Kouko?
Yeah... Kouko.
I love you.
I love you so much,
I don't know how this happened.
But I really do love you.
I love you too, Kouko.
I must look terrible.
It's okay.
I don't think I got all my makeup off-
Why don't we get some makeup remover in the morning?
Huh?
We can leave it here.
Maybe I can use it when I stay over.
Ka...
Kouko.
Hey, Banri.
I feel uneasy.
Do you understand?
Will you understand?
I can't help but feel uneasy.
After all, we don't have anything.
We don't have a lot of time spent together.
We don't have experiences together.
We don't have any memories.
We don't even have any pictures.
In that case...
Shall we take a picture?
What?
I want a picture with you, too.
Let's start from there.
We don't need to rush anything.
I don't want to push you too hard just because I'm spineless.
Okay.
Tada Banri!
Did you wait long?
Anyway, sorry about last night. I'm really sorry.
What should I do?
Kouko-chan was angry, wasn't she?
Of course she was.
I'm the worst.
Don't worry about it.
Kouko's fine now.
Really?
Why'd you come out to my place, then?
I wanted to talk about the past.
We weren't dating.
That's what you said, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I liked you, but you, Senpai...
Linda... you didn't like me.
Yeah, not in a romantic sense.
You were my friend, but I wasn't in love.
I didn't like you that way.
I wanted to confirm that.
Did you hear?
You can't go back to Linda.
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
No matter how strongly you feel,
that's a one-way street.
So just forget about her!
Disappear!
No!
I love Linda!
I want to be with Linda!
The truth is...
The truth is, I've been searching for Linda.
I've wanted to go back to Linda!
Thanks for everything.
But from now on, I want you to pretend we didn't know each other.
It's stressful.
I don't want to think about my amnesia.
I want to cut ties with my past.
You're not my former classmate anymore.
From now on, we're just a senior and junior in the same club.
You don't need to worry about me.
Honestly, Kouko's a little bothered by you.
So I want to put a clear distance between us.
I want to treat my girlfriend right.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I understand.
Yeah. That's what you should do.
We're doing the right thing, Banri.
It's all the opposite, Banri.
You're posing again.
It looks unnatural. Don't do it.
What? I wasn't posing.
You were.
I wasn't.
Hey, Kouko...
Why don't we take some outside?
Sure.
Let's go.
Banri, hurry up.
Okay, okay.
Katate ni wa amaku shita okiniiru no cafe latte
Hohoenda shunkan ni koi no kaori
Kanpeki ni kimetai no cherry iro no one-piece
Sasayaka de tokimeite kimi e isogou
Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry
Ki wo tsukete amai wana
Yes sasayaite ageru kara
(Nee chotto doki doki)
Aa machidoosii kedo
Donna egao de aeba ii
Pretty love, pretty love
Kimi ga itoshikute
Under the sky, under sunshine
Te wo tsunagou
Sunao ni narenai sonna watashi no te wo
Hippatte ite ne
Summer Has Come
Wahoo! Money!
That underwear was unbelievable, but as long as
Linda-senpai's there, I don't mind doing this job.
Kouko!
Banri!
BANRI!
Actually, sorry. That's seriously annoying.
Kouko!
Banri!