The role of you young ones is not to fear failure, but to seek new frontiers!
New frontiers...
"feather"
How about...
"china spoon"
Sensei.
"bowl"
Whatcha doin'?
Naru's birthday?
Shh...! If Naru hears this, it won't be a surprise.
We were thinking of having a party for her.
Sensei, you're an adult, so a thousand yen should do.
You're charging fees for a kid's birthday?!
Not fees. It's to buy the cake.
With our allowances, we can't buy a whole cake.
Hiro-nii will be bringing food in the evening.
Sensei, get a present ready too, 'kay?
Present?
--Cake! Cake!
--Hey, I've got to write today...
"feather" "bowl" "china spoon"
Well, I guess it's okay for today...
"Onde"
"Translation: Buddhist chanting and dancing"
I got you a teddy bear for your present.
Yaar! A punching bag!
I got you a ribbon.
Yahoo! Perfect fer wrappin' 'round my waist!
Here, a mirror.
Yay! Laser beam!
So bright!
None of them feel right...
What would make her happy?
Dang, that cicada is noisy!
Got it.
All right! I got the cicada!
Yay!
Kenta, you got a minute?
Hey, Sensei. What's the matter?
Well, I have a favor to ask.
This is about all I could come up with for a present.
--Can you give me one of your beetles?
--Nope.
Just one! Only one! I'll give you ten yen for it!
That's a lot of money to you kids, right?!
Yer so pesky, Sensei!
Yer talkin' bout a present fer Naru, right?
I'm gonna be the one to give beetles to Naru!
Come on, just one!
Nope! I'm gonna give her a hundred of these, and make a bed out of 'em!
"scuttle-scuttle"
That's just torture.
I don't wanna give her the same present as someone else!
Well, I can see that...
Ichiro, Jiro? What are you guys bringing?
Those aren't our names!
We're gonna give her candy!
I guess you kids are all set...
You better think of what to get too, Sensei.
I'll get her a stag beetle!
If you can catch that many rhinoceros beetles, then stag beetles must be easier.
Hand me your net.
Sensei's not takin' beetle catchin' seriously.
More like Sensei ain't takin' life itself seriously.
Easy fer you to say!
They're hard ta find, y'know?
That's because you're kids.
If you're as tall as an adult, you can see from above, so it'll be a cinch.
Sensei can really get on your nerves.
Found one!
Shoot. A girl.
Hey! I'm the one who found it!
Yer too slow! Finders ain't keepers!
Why, you...!
Naru's gonna be so let down if ya can't even catch one beetle!
What a letdown...
Not that I care, but that's irritating.
Kenta! There's another one over here!
It's mine!
I won't lose ta you!
Good!
I did it! I got the beetle--
No, it ain't! The heck is this?!
Lame! That's a drone beetle!
--Sensei ain't gonna catch any!
--Let's go over there!
Yay!
Those brats! No way am I going to lose...!
Hey! A giant stag beetle!
It's pretty high up.
Okay, then!
Formation... Beta!
Just a little... more...
S-So heavy...
Nooo...!
Oww...
Where's Kenta?!
What are you kids doing?
Sensei, I thought ya went home.
First, say "thank you."
How can I leave without catching a single beetle?
It'll be a cinch with this.
I can catch any bug, no matter how high it is.
All right! Got the present!
Sensei?
Can you lend me the net...?
Yer trying to catch 'em, and ya can't even touch 'em?!
Are you stupid?! They could bite or be carrying diseases!
They don't bite and they ain't diseased!
Apologize to the beetle!
Up close, it looks creepier than I expected!
Why's it so glossy?
It's no different from a roach!
It's not a roach, stupid!
Just hurry and hand me the net.
Nope!
I kinda think it hurts!
Is he gonna be able to catch beetles?
Nah.
Whoa!
Look over there, Kenta!
It's a Hercules beetle!
Why's it here?!
Musta got loose from a cage!
No way you could find one here!
What? Is it that good?
Super good!
They said on TV that it's worth twenty thousand yen!
Twenty thousand for a bug?
Sensei! Can I borrow the ladder?
--Huh?
--Let's work together to catch it!
Naru's gonna be so happy if we get her something super like that!
Yeah!
A kid's present worth twenty thousand...
Slowly...
Slowly, Kenta...
Yeah.
No... Can't reach it...
--Sensei!
--Me?! N-No way!
Sensei!
We'll hold the ladder!
I'll tell Naru how great ya did!
Let's give her a super present together!
C'mon, Sensei...!
Sensei! Do your best!
--Your best!
--Do it, Sensei!
Gross...
Big deal, just catch it!
Got it!
All right!
Banzai!
--H-Hey, wait! Don't let go!
--Her-cu-les! Her-cu-les!
How can ya fall twice in one day?
Being this big a klutz is almost like a talent...
I'm never going to trust you kids again.
Where's the Hercules beetle?
Didn't want it to get away, so I had the net clutched tight.
Yay!
--Huh?
It's... not movin'...
Is it... dead...?
That can't be!
You squished him!
No, I didn't...!
I can't believe you squished a Hercules beetle!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Repent with yer life!
Do I deserve this...?
Come on, it's just a bug.
I was gonna give it to Naru...
C-Come on! Stop crying!
"Hercules"
Seriously, I'm sorry...
It's okay already.
Here, Sensei.
I'll give ya one that I caught!
Are you sure?
Yup. Cuz you did yer best for Naru.
You're the first adult who ever played with us so seriously, Sensei!
I've had a blast this summer!
--Me too!
You kids...
Hold it from the back.
--Like this?
--Yup!
Yes! I can hold it!
Now I'm one step closer to you kids!
I wasn't playing with you kids.
I just didn't want to lose to you.
I'll be serious again, so be prepared!
Are ya stupid?! Whaddya think yer doin'?!
Hey... The place looks like it's ready for the party.
"Naru's 7 years old"
"Happy Birthday Naru-chan"
Sensei, you're late!
How did you girls get in?!
Easy.
How long ya think it's been since we've used this place as our base?
You can have this one, since I've still got one more.
Don't tell me...!
A spare key.
I was getting my bicycle key copied,
and since it was so cheap,
I got five spares made for this place.
I have one too!
Huh? The door's open today...
You too, Hiro?!
Wait... If there are five, then who got the other one?
I lost it.
Maybe it was when I was playing in the mountains.
Sensei? Did you get a present?
That's right... Present...
I brought her some bubble wrap!
I picked up some peacock feathers.
You girls sure know what'll click with Naru.
Miwa-chan, you brought bubble wrap?
I was thinking about that too...
--But those feathers are good too.
--Really?
--Yup.
--Well, I actually found these on the side of the road...
Naru's here!
Yikes! Everyone, get ready!
I've never thrown a birthday party before.
If it weren't for you, we wouldn't have done this, Sensei.
Huh? Me...?
Let's have one every year from now on.
Did I do anything?
Get your crackers ready for when Naru comes in.
--Ah... Ah...
--Hey!
Ah... Ah...
Ah-choo!
Uh...
Naru! Congrats!
Congrats!
Oh, yeah! My birthday!
First, a present from Sensei!
Ah, well, I'll go later...
C'mon, just show it!
H-Hey, wait! Stop it!
Got it!
Here. From Sensei.
Whoa...
"'I'll do anything you say' ticket
1 time"
The heck is this?! An elementary student's Mother's Day gift?!
And only one?! So cheap!
Why, you...!
C'mon, Naru. Go ahead and be angry.
Yaaay!
Your happiness is starting to scare me...
Isn't this great, Naru?
Look at me, earnestly watering the sunflowers, not knowing who planted them.
They'll probably grow even if I don't do anything...
Boo!
There you go again, climbing up there. It's dangerous.
Grandpa's goin' grave visiting, so he said to bring you, Sensei.
Grave visiting?
Yup!
Sensei! Over here!
That's right... It's already the Bon Festival period.
Sensei!
Sensei! Over here!
Nice of ya ta come!
Are you sure it's okay for an outsider like me to be here?
I've gotta go ta my fields...
...so I was hopin' you'd keep watch over this grave.
Huh...
Firecrackers?! That's so tasteless!
That's normal 'round these parts!
A custom?
'Kay! I'll leave ya to it!
See ya!
Huh?! You're going already?
Naru's used to it, so just listen to what the kid has ta say!
Now, the fields're waitin'!
How irresponsible...
"Kotoishi Family Grave"
I've never really properly visited a grave before...
I don't know who's at rest here, but please look after us for today.
Sensei, we gotta light the t o r o first.
--"Light the t o r o "?
--Ya know, those.
Ah, you mean the paper lanterns?
To r o!
Come to think of it, it looks like every family has them up.
We can't leave the grave until the fire on this goes out.
Isn't that a candle meant to last for two hours?
We have to stay here that long?
If we get bored, we got these!
You too, eh?
Going to pay my respects, okay?
Hey! Yasu-ba!
Let me go and offer an incense stick.
I was friends with Naru's grandma, after all.
Look at me. I managed to get through another year.
That sounds so glum...
Thank you, dear. Must be tough in this hot weather, Sensei.
No, but having an unrelated person like me here must make Naru's grandma uneasy.
Not at all.
Look at this candle here.
The flame's bobbing up and down, right?
You're right...
Just means Grandma's looking at ya happily.
Don't you worry, ya hear?
If it'll make the owner of the grave happy, I'll do my best.
Yeah!
You got a lighter with you?
I got matches.
Fireworks, again?!
Hey, parachutes!
Chutes!
Hey, they're coming down here!
All right! Midair catch!
That's my Miwa-chan! Running wild without thinking about others!
Gotta say, its hard running in a yukata.
Naru wants ta do it too!
Sorry! That was the last of them chutes.
Let's do something else!
Hey, Sensei? C'mon, react a bit here.
Ignoring us is against the rules, you know?
I guess he wants us to help...
I got it! I'll help! I'll help!
Stop with those eyes!
I feel like I'm going to be cursed!
So, is this different from the
Bon festivities in the cities?
Completely different. In the first place, we don't pay a visit in the evening.
And no rice grains are offered.
No fireworks. No yukata.
No lining up lanterns.
Huh?! None of 'em?
Isn't it weird having the gravestone etched in gold?
You're kidding! I thought gold was used everywhere!
Well, I rarely pay my visits, so I can't speak proudly about customs.
Us either. We only ever come here during the Bon Festival.
And we basically only come to play with fireworks.
And to see the Onde.
--The Onde?
--'Scuse me.
Ya mind if we pass through here?
This is the Onde. People dance in front of graves less than a year old.
That sounds scary...
What does that translate to in Japanese?
It isn't a foreign language.
What? Why stop?
Am I being stared at?
I am being stared at! Did I do something?!
You should look at your face!
You freak out too easily, Sensei.
Hiro!
Are you part of that group?!
I just came to assist, since they didn't have enough guys.
Hiro-sempai!
Let's hurry on to the next one.
My feet are killing me.
We only got three more left. Stick it out.
I'll see you, Sensei.
I need to dance a bit longer.
Okay, keep it up.
Don't follow me!
Come on. I want to see you dance.
Sensei is really getting used to living here.
He's acting like Naru's guardian too.
I've tried not to think too much about it, but...
...Sensei is on this island because he punched a prominent person in calligraphy, right?
That means when he's forgiven...
Tama...
Did ya finish your summer assignments?
Well, pretty much...
Mind letting me copy 'em?
Miwa-chan...
C'mon, Sensei, you're late.
Fireworks, fireworks!
Smoky...
Hey there, Sensei.
Can I offer an incense stick?
Village Leader.
Naru's grandma took good care of me when she was alive.
Ah, the Kinoshita Shoten lady...
You mind if I offer an incense stick?
Please go right ahead.
Hey, Miwa!
The hell ya doin', foolin' 'round here and leaving our family grave?!
Ugh! Dad!
Sensei, please tell him that you forced me to come here!
Are you stupid?! Hell, no!
Nee-chan, what are you doing here?
Mom was looking for you.
Aki... How'd you know I was here?
Mom told me to give incense to Naru's grandma.
Can I offer an incense stick this year too?
Sure!
Naru's grandma sure is popular.
Yes, people keep coming here every year.
Gramps is always busy, so Naru's been keeping watch by herself all this time.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Naru's parents yet...
Sensei! Pinwheel firecracker!
Hey!
Today is so fun!
Stop fooling around, brat!
It's usually boring waitin' for Grandpa, but tonight I don't wanna go home.
Just sleep here tonight!
Ya know, it must feel like this because you're here, Sensei.
Aah! Naru wants ta play too!
She's always around other people when
I see her, so I never realized it, but...
...I guess she must get lonely like anyone else.
She'll probably grow even if I don't do anything...
...but I'll stay with her while I still have the time.
Ah... The fire went out...
Time to go already? Feels so early.
You gonna go already?
Gramps hasn't come back yet...
We'll stay longer.
--Yippie!
--You're so kind, Sensei!
--Zip it!
--Grandma!
Naru's gonna keep playin'!
Are you that happy?
Sensei, take a look!
Grandma's happy too!
Hey there, Sensei.
Puchi-san...
Did you come to fish for dinner?
Dogs don't eat crayfish.
You're looking natural there, fishing at this here hole.
Nah, I still need work...
The people in the village seem to like you.
How about just living here permanently already?
Well, that I can't do.
I see.
Well, as long as you have a place to call home, you're free to do as you desire, right?
Puchi-san...
If you become a big-time calligrapher, then treat me to lobster.
So you d o eat them!
Keep this secret from Granny, okay?
That's what I saw in my dream.
I was still happy, even if it was a dream.
Huh...
Puchi is a female.
What?!