Excuse me.
Um... I made reservations for Fukurai University's
Japanese cultural research group...
GOLDENTIME
Return to Yesterday
Ah, if we could meet in a dream, could I say it?
Say, if sadness alone floats down from the sky
If that kind of voice pains you even now
Even if, off to the side, our hands are placed on each other's
This memory wouldn't fade, but...
Even if, when our eyes meet, I can't say the truth...
Your words illuminate the world more than anyone else's
Next to me, "Goodbye means I love you," you say
I can't be forthright
Though I alone sing of loneliness
I can't smile
"Thank you means I'm in love with you," you say
The world's end of love
Hey.
Huh?
Everyone's already here?
I'm so sorry.
I'll help!
It's Tada Banri.
Tada Banri.
It's Banri.
Oh, my.
Huh? What is it?
What's going on?
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's nothing.
Come over here, Tada Banri.
Let's do this together.
We're hanging up these lights before the fourth years arrive.
Don't forget about these lanterns.
N-no! You're scaring me!
Why?
We're not scary.
Yes, you are!
You're acting weird!
There's nothing weird about us.
We didn't get to go on our overnight trip,
but let's have fun today to make up for it.
The president's connections got us this place, too.
Isn't it great?
Right? Isn't this fun?
The festival club is so much fun, isn't it?
Hey, Tada Banri!
It's been a while.
I've really, really missed you.
What have you been up to lately?
Well... lately... I... just, um...
"Just..."?
Well, you can't help that, can you?
I guess you could say we see you and Roboko as... well...
Sort of like a fertilized egg.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Two life forms have become one.
That's what I mean.
It's like you and Roboko were always one.
You're the genes that will carry our souls on to the next generation.
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
Is Linda-senpai not here?
Her?
She said she'd come here from home.
But forget about that.
Oh, she went home to Shizuoka?
Don't talk about it right after I told you to forget it.
Anyway, what about you?
No, I mean you guys.
Um... I really don't understand.
What I'm trying to say is...
We all want to include you and Roboko.
You get it, don't you?
No, I don't.
You don't?
In any case...
It's that! Get it?
I don't get it.
In other words, just because you broke up with Roboko,
neither of you should quit the club.
What?
You don't have to tell us.
We understand.
We've been calling and texting Roboko lately,
but we can't get in touch with her.
Even when we called you,
when we asked about Roboko, you gave vague answers.
Isn't that what it means?
Actually, I...
But!
Even if you're not a couple anymore, that doesn't mean your bond with us is lost.
Right, guys?
That's right!
We'll soothe the pain of lost love!
Come on! Let's cheer up Tada Banri!
Tada!
Banri!
No, no, no!
Why would you assume that?
Tada! Banri!
Kouko and I are...
Sorry I'm late.
Roboko!
Roboko's here!
Roboko's returned from the heart repair factory!
Let's give a warm welcome to the nearly broken Roboko.
Roboko!
Huh? Huh?
What's going on? What?
It's not like that! You've got the wrong idea!
You don't have to tell us.
We understand.
No, you don't understand!
We didn't break up!
What?
Well, this is stupid.
We wasted our time trying to be nice to them.
We were really worried about what we'd do if you quit.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Aww, don't blame them.
It's not their fault.
Yeah, you're the one who's most at fault!
You were the first to assume they broke up!
You guys said you were sure about it, too!
Are you trying to blame us?
It's your fault for jumping to conclusions!
We might have come dangerously close to it, though.
That wasn't close at all.
That wasn't even within the range of "close."
What?
Nothing.
I just thought you look good in your yukata.
This? I made it this year.
I decided I would go and see fireworks with you this summer!
It rained the other day, though.
Yeah.
Listen up, everyone.
I just got word.
Mind if I come to
today's fireworks
extravaganza?
It's okay, right?
Of course it is!
See you later!
Former president Hoshino-senpai is coming here today.
Seriously? Hosshi-san's coming?
He said he wouldn't come if he couldn't find a job.
Which means...
He found work!
That's great.
He'd been looking really gloomy.
Okay! Let's celebrate with everything we have!
Yeah!
Hey, it's been a while!
Hosshi-san!
Your legendary pirouette is so cool.
Isn't it? Isn't it cool?
Wow, this place is awesome.
Sorry, guys.
We should have helped.
Don't be ridiculous.
Anyway...
Hosshi-senpai.
Congratulations on your employment!
Congratulations!
Yeah.
Now all the fourth years have found jobs.
Congratulations!
Huh?
Oh... yeah...
Sorry.
I haven't actually found a job yet... you might say.
I wanted a change of pace.
That's why I came.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh?
What's this mood in the air?
What's wrong with me, huh?
Those guys out there in the world are lousy judges of character!
I know what you mean.
It's not your fault.
Come on, drink more.
In any case, I'm glad you're all okay.
Oka-chan's injury is better now, right?
Yeah, completely.
I'm really sorry for making you worry.
It's fine.
Even though I was at home, I felt so uneasy.
Actually, how did you hear about the accident?
Oh, you know. From people.
I'm so relieved, though.
I was worried until I finally saw you.
It was worth coming back just to see you two.
Linda-senpai.
Huh?
Did we ever light fireworks together before I lost my memory?
You were in the same class for all three years of high school, right?
That's right.
Before I fell off that bridge.
You were both on the track team, weren't you?
You must've looked so cool, Linda-senpai.
About those fireworks...
Take a look at your left leg, Banri.
My left leg?
That's a burn scar.
In the summer of our second year, when we lit fireworks on the track team's overnight trip,
a bottle rocket fell over and struck you.
What?
Now I remember!
I hurt myself protecting you!
This scar is a badge of honor!
No, no.
I ran away quickly, but you were stupidly slow to run away.
We got in a lot of trouble with our adviser afterward.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
It's all in the past.
By the way, Banri...
You're not going home for summer break?
I will.
My parents have been pushing me to go.
Linda-senpai, that's how it is.
If you happen to see Banri while you're back home,
I hope you'll hang out with him.
Please.
Listen, I wasn't going to bring this up, but...
...can I say something?
A high school class reunion?
Yeah, next week.
Our class is holding a reunion.
I was sure you wouldn't want to come, so I wasn't going to tell you, but...
Do you want to stop by?
Oh, I won't force you.
It's just... everyone's worried about you.
If you show them you're fine,
I think they'll be really happy.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Senpai.
Banri will attend.
What?
You will, won't you?
What? You won't?
You will, right? Of course you will.
Yeah. I'll go.
I'll go to the class reunion.
Did I do something I shouldn't have?
I'm sorry for making the decision for you.
Did I cause you trouble again?
No, it's fine.
I decided to stop running from my past.
I'll go.
Honestly, I'm anxious.
The person everyone wants to see is the
Tada Banri from before I lost my memory.
He's a completely different person from who I am now.
When they see me, they might think, "Who is this guy?"
"You're not the one we want to see."
"We want to see the old Banri."
They might think something like that.
You told me the other day that I abandoned my friends and family and ran away.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry about that.
I know you don't remember them.
I shouldn't have...
It's fine.
I'm glad you said it.
It helped me decide to face my past.
I'll go see my classmates.
I can't help what they think about me.
I'll apologize for making them worry, and thank them.
I wonder why it is.
I feel like I'll finally get to see the whole Banri.
The whole me?
I think I couldn't really accept you before.
Maybe I only saw the Banri I wanted to see.
I couldn't accept that there were people who knew a Banri that I didn't know.
I must have been jealous.
But, what you said...
"I'll do my best, so you do your best, too."
"Don't get out of the car."
When you said that, I realized I loved you.
I realized it was fine for me to keep loving you.
I love you because you're you.
I'm happy that you're whole.
I don't care if there are sides of you
I don't know, or don't like.
If that's who you are, that's fine.
As long as you're whole, that's enough for me.
But I'm struggling because
I've lost sight of my whole self.
That's part of who you are, too.
So go see your past with your own eyes.
See for yourself the Banri you've forgotten, who you were before you met me,
and then tell me about it.
Can I open this box?
Sure!
Oh, but could you take that box to the corner over there?
It's full of fragile stuff, so be careful.
You're a real slave driver, aren't you?
That's not true.
Kaga-san, you're staying here tonight, aren't you?
What?
It'll take until nighttime to finish putting things away.
Wait, you're going to make me work until then?
What?
But isn't that why you came here?
No!
I had no intention of helping you move.
I was a little curious, so I came to take a look.
When I heard your apartment wasn't what you imagined,
I thought I'd come laugh at you.
Is that why you brought an apron?
In any case, let's get this done quickly.
You'll be the first one to stay over!
I'm not staying!
Absolutely not! Not even if it kills me!
I won't stay over even if the world ends!
Kaga-san?
What?
Do you want me to guess what you're thinking about?
Do whatever you want.
You're thinking about Banri, aren't you?
You're wondering what he's up to in Shizuoka right now.
You're amazing.
Once you fall in love, you really love that person through thick and thin.
Isn't everyone like that?
No, they're not.
I have a lot of respect for you.
What?
Hey, what did you...
I know you're just pretending to sleep.
I knew it!
Linda-senpai, you're not leaving yet?
Yeah. I'm staying until the first train.
Once the trains start running,
I'll get on a bullet train.
You're going home again?
I meant to head right back home in the first place,
but I was suddenly asked to work here, and that delayed my plans a day.
I got to see the two underclassmen, too.
Um... Did I do something I shouldn't have?
I made you worry by telling you about the accident.
Not at all.
I'm glad you told me.
Thanks.
I see.
Um, do you need some help?
No, that's okay.
I'm finished.
Um... how long are you going to be at home?
Until the end of summer break, I think.
I've got a class reunion,
and I have plans to hang out with some friends after that.
A reunion, huh?
Sounds fun.
You don't have any plans like that?
None yet.
Banri's gone home, too.
With fewer friends around, I don't have much to do.
Shizuoka
Tokyo
Linda-senpai, you're from Shizuoka?
Yeah.
Banri said he's from Shizuoka, too.
Maybe you'll run into Banri somewhere.
That won't happen!
Shizuoka's a big place.
Hey! What are you doing?
Give it back!
What?
Give it back.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you think I'm doing this?
Actually, I'm going back to my apartment first.
Later.
Three is fine, thank you.
Oh, but make them all different flavors.
Very well.
And where's the restroom?
This way.
I'm so glad Kaga-san's feeling better.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
I wish I could have seen Oka-chan, too.
I guess she can't help it.
She said she's not done unpacking.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you today?
I wouldn't say it's bothering me, but...
Listen, Banri's from Shizuoka, isn't he?
Do you know what high school he attended?
No.
You know he doesn't really talk about his past.
Now that you mention it...
Maybe he doesn't want to remember because of his accident before.
Accident?
You mean the one the other day?
No, not that.
Huh?
You haven't heard, Yana-san?
About when Banri fell from a bridge and got badly hurt?
Badly hurt?
We were tricked by some weird cult and taken to their campsite.
Banri told us about it then.
He fell from a bridge and was hospitalized for a while.
Anyway, he said, "I'm interested in religion because I've had that experience."
"No one else is interested, so let them go."
Is that really true, though?
I thought it was a lie, too.
I assumed he made something up so we could escape, but...
When we went to the beach the other day, I saw a faint scar.
Around here.
I pretended not to notice,
but maybe what he said at that camp was true.
He said a bunch of other things, too.
What do you mean, other things?
Well, I don't know how much is true and how much is false.
Besides,
we shouldn't look into it too much if he doesn't want to talk about it.
Thank you for waiting.
These look delicious.
Take whichever one you want.
It's on me.
Since I made you guys worry.
You're so big-hearted, Kaga-san!
What?
What are you saying about my nice body?
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
You're very thin.
Kouko, did you know?
Know what?
That Banri was hospitalized.
Hey, Yana-san!
Who knows?
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
Here, take a spoon.
Thanks...
You, too, Mitsuo.
I guess I'll dig in, then.
Go ahead.
Oh, right. Kaga-san, how was Oka-chan's place?
You stayed over, didn't you?
I did.
In fact, she even made me help her move.
You, doing work? Sounds cool.
Right?
You're wrong, I'm telling you you're wrong
Ah, you still don't notice, huh?
Though I've wanted to touch that arm for the past two or three hours
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
The urge to scream is so great that, look, I can't stand it
So why, why won't you notice even a little?
Are you really, really in love with me?
I don't need words of flattery
Love me semi-eternally
After 5,000 years or so, I won't be interested
I'm not endless
I will die someday
Being told "I'll love you forever" won't make me happy
First, think only that
You'll love me till I die
My Hometown
I want a job.
It's okay!
You'll find a job before Jack Frost arrives.
Yeah.
You'll be fine, Hosshi-senpai.
Hey there, future prime minister!
Jack Frost, huh?
I wonder if he'll come.