Oka-chan, what's wrong?
I was helping some upperclassmen from the film club.
Anyway, Banri, what was that about?
What?
It's not right.
Why are you so close with Linda-senpai?
Wh-why?
We're in the same club, and we have a lot in common...
Well, stop.
That's the girl Yana likes.
It's not right for you to be so close with her.
Wait, sorry...
Don't you think you're acting a little weird?
There's no reason for you to be so upset.
You're the weird one!
Besides, I think Kaga-san would feel bad if she saw you two just now.
Don't you feel sorry for Kaga-san?
You're the worst.
His Chasm
Aa yume no naka de aetara yueru ka na?
Ne, kanashimi dake sora kara maiochite
Sonna koe ga kimi o ima demo kurushimete
Soba de te o kasanetemo
Kono omoi wa kienai kedo
Futari me o awasetara hontou no koto yuenakutemo
Kimi no kotoba, dare yori mo sekai o terashiteru
Tonari de kimi wa "Sayonara wa ai shiteru" tte, sou iu no
Sunao ni narenai
Watashi dake kodoku o utattemo
Egao ni narenai
"Arigato wa koi shiteru" tte sou iu no
Ai no world's end
I see.
So Linda-senpai is uncomfortable with it.
I had sort of suspected it from the way she was acting.
But what really surprised me was Oka-chan.
She didn't seem like herself.
Yeah...
I'm sure Miss Ultrasonic has a lot of feelings on the subject.
I'm sure she said all that because she does,
but wasn't that a little one-sided of her?
She doesn't know that you and
Linda-senpai were classmates.
I know it's my fault that I haven't told her yet, but...
Anyway!
I'm shocked you were being so friendly with Linda-senpai
that Miss Ultrasonic got upset!
Huh?!
No, no!
That was her mistake.
We were just having a frank conversation as friends.
We weren't doing anything inappropriate.
Really?
It's true!
I feel like I've been able to put a lot behind me since going to the reunion.
I was fine when I heard that Yana-san likes Linda.
If anything, I want to support him from the bottom of my heart.
Yeah, same goes for me.
I feel like just a normal friend, praying for my friends to be happy.
Exactly.
The person most important to me right now is...
Oh, right.
Isn't this the right time to give her the ring?
It'd follow naturally from this conversation.
The location is beautiful, too.
What's wrong?
Hold on.
Huh?
Oh, no!
I didn't bring it!
I always screw up at times like this!
Did you forget something on campus?
If you're going back, I'll go with you.
Uh... no... it's nothing.
It's from Yana-san.
"Stuck with senpai girls. Can't get away.
Requesting immediate rescue."
So he says.
Ah... I also bailed on him, saying I was going to meet you.
I guess we should head back.
Yeah.
When is the best time to give it to her, I wonder?
I can't possibly wait until Christmas.
I wish I could ask Oka-chan for advice.
I wonder who else I could talk to...
Huh?
Good morning, Nana-senpai!
Uh... um...
Huh?
It's unusual that we end up on the same train in the morning, huh?
Yeah.
So even you go to college in the morning sometimes.
My attendance.
I can't afford to miss much more.
Oh, I see...
Did you not get enough sleep?
And I'm hungry.
Oh...
Doesn't seem like a good time to ask her about the ring...
Your girlfriend.
What?
She's not with you today?
No, Kouko has a first period class.
She's funny.
Oh, I heard...
She visited your apartment while I was gone.
Yeah, when she did the exorcist.
Huh? What is that?
She didn't tell you?
No, she didn't.
What's the "exorcist"?
If she didn't tell you, never mind.
But... I have no idea what you're talking about.
Did Kouko rotate her head 180 degrees or something?
Hey... Nana-senpai!
I see.
So Yana-san really started filming the festival club.
Yeah.
He's apparently going to keep coming until the school festival next month.
In other words, if he can't get closer to Linda-senpai before then, he fails.
But the festival club doesn't even practice every day.
Oh, Mitsuo's here!
Thanks for waiting.
You guys got here early.
Did you skip class?
No, no!
Our lectures just ended early.
Hey, Kaga-san, let's go to the convenience store.
Now?
What for?
Their limited-time Belgian chocolate soft serve is on sale now.
Wh-what did you say?
The Belgian chocolate I've been waiting since last year to see on sale again?!
I don't have class this afternoon, and I've got work after this.
Without Belgian chocolate,
I just don't feel like working.
If I don't work, I won't be able to pay my taxes.
I'll fail as a cog in the machine of society!
You're kidding! That's awful!
We'd better go, then!
I've got to do my part, so you can do your duty!
This is what you call noblesse oblige!
Banri, I'm going to go eat Belgian chocolate with Miss Ultrasonic
to secure our nation's financial resources!
You're done with classes, right?
Right!
I'll be waiting for you somewhere.
Call me when you get out.
See you tomorrow, everyone!
They've really grown close, haven't they?
Nothing good comes of those two getting together, though.
They left the three of us to go have fun on their own.
Oka-chan didn't even look at me once.
So, how's it going, Yana-san?
Are your visits to the festival club paying off?
Not in the least.
What? It's not working?
Don't tell me you still haven't had a real conversation with her.
Well, we've talked a little bit, but...
When I asked if she wanted to see what I'd filmed,
she said, "No, that's okay."
That's all?
That's all.
Maybe she's still mad at me for the other day.
We've grown farther apart than we were before.
She left so quickly yesterday, too.
What am I supposed to do?
This so hopeless, I could die.
Don't die over that!
You and Kaga-san aren't doing enough, Banri!
Huh? It's our fault?
You're always there with him, right?
You're not helping your friend enough.
But Yana-san's free to come and go as he pleases at the festival club.
The rest is up to him.
No! The festival club's defenses are pretty tough to breach.
Huh? They don't have any defenses.
If anything, those second year girls are kicking down all defenses themselves.
I mean their defenses around Linda-senpai.
Specifically, the president, Koshino-san.
Why him?
Kosshi-senpai's a really nice guy.
I can tell he's a really nice guy,
but he's always watching Linda-senpai.
Whenever I try to approach her, he casually leads her away.
He's obviously trying to protect Linda-senpai from me.
What?
Are you sure?
Crap! Class is starting!
Huh?
Whoa, you're right! Damn!
Banri!
Kouko!
Sorry. My class ran late.
It's fine.
I enjoy waiting for you.
We don't have practice with the festival club today.
I thought about where we could go and what we could do together.
So? Where should we go, Banri?
Oh, right.
I forgot to ask.
What's the "exorcist"?
What?!
The exorcist?
Nana-senpai mentioned it this morning on the train.
Wh-wh-who knows?
I have absolutely, totally no idea what you're talking about!
But Nana-senpai said...
Oh, right!
Don't you want to go see another one of Nana-senpai's concerts?
Let's go with Linda-senpai, Mitsuo,
Miss Ultrasonic, and 2D-kun next time!
Uh... sure...
We'll be busy with the Awa dance and school festival for a while...
But once those are over, let's have lots of fun.
We can go to all kinds of places and see all kinds of things.
Sounds good.
I hope our days stay like this forever.
Yeah.
I need to give her that ring soon.
The problem is that I'm just thinking about this too much.
I should just casually give it to her.
I'm Sao-chan from the tea club!
I'm Shi-chan!
Tada Banri!
It's been so long!
What'd you do over summer break?
Everything going well with your beautiful girlfriend? You rascal!
Y-yes, very well, thank you.
What's that?
D-don't!
It's a ring!
Are you giving it to your girlfriend?!
You're proposing!
Uh... is that what you think?
Of course!
Tada Banri, what are you talking about?
When a man gives a girl a ring,
it means he wants her to marry him!
Generally speaking, giving a ring equals a proposal.
But what's with this thing?
It's not even wrapped. It's just there.
That's not good?
Did you find out her size?
You wouldn't want the ring to be too small.
But it's really not that big of a deal...
My mom wore this ring when she was younger.
She told me to give it to my girlfriend.
Your mother...
...wore that ring...
...when she was younger?!
What's the overreaction for?!
That's meaningful.
That's way too meaningful!
What?
It totally means she wants you to bring her home and show off the ring on her finger.
No, no, no!
I really don't think my mom put that much thought into it!
You're so dense!
So dense!
Immature.
You're too immature, Tada Banri.
Maybe you should join the tea club and cultivate your mind.
Why are you bringing that up again?!
Well, see, all the boys we dragged into the club in April ran away.
We're currently recruiting male club members.
Want to come check us out now?
Actually, I've got festival club practice now.
Oops, Shi-chan, we're going to be late ourselves.
You're right.
Tada Banri, you should hang out with us sometime!
I feel like they just raised the bar as high as it'll go...
Thanks for waiting, Banri!
Whoa!
Sorry. My lecture ran late.
Let's go.
We shouldn't keep everyone waiting.
Okay.
So, it's been decided
that the fourth years will be participating in this Sunday's festival on short notice.
Thanks for having us!
Today's our last day to practice.
Make sure you all work together!
Okay!
I wonder what happened.
The former president still hasn't found a job.
He wants to take another break for a change of pace.
Oh...
All right! Let's start with some stretches!
Um... Linda-senpai...
Linda! Help the fourth years with their dancing.
You're the best at it.
Okay.
Oh, my.
So that's what he meant.
Do you remember how to put on your costumes, and the choreography?
No.
We were away for a long time.
I haven't danced at all since becoming a fourth year.
I'm worried about Mitsuo,
but I wonder if Hosshi-san and the other fourth years will be all right.
They only had today to practice.
I'm a little worried about them, but festivals are a place to have fun.
If this'll cheer Hosshi-san up, what does it matter?
Yeah, you're right.
Listen, have you talked to Oka-chan since then?
Whenever I try to talk about you,
she says she has something to do and runs off.
It might be best to leave her alone for a while.
Let's focus on the festival for now.
We can talk about everything else later, together.
I'll help you think about what we should do.
A lot of people will be coming, so you should secure a spot to film early.
Yeah.
It'll probably be difficult to film from the starting point.
I'll move off a bit and wait where the crowd starts to thin out.
There sure are a lot of people here, though.
They're all really pumped up.
No one wants to look bad or embarrass themselves.
Huh...
Okay!
Today, I'll abandon my personal feelings and focus on filming!
Banri, I'll be filming you, so make sure you look good!
Got it!
I'll go find a spot to film.
Okay.
Hey, Banri.
Look at that.
You don't need to be nervous!
You've got far more experience than I do.
Yeah, but it's been so long...
Um... how do we start?
For that... Kosshi-senpai!
Huh?
Good.
Kouko doesn't seem to be too nervous today.
She's so focused on taking care of the fourth years,
she can't afford to be nervous herself.
Golden
Time
Today's the day.
This is the time for us to show the results of our practice!
All right!
Let's go, festival club!
Yeah!
It's amazing.
The world's shining.
Everything's bathed in a golden light.
Where am I?
What?
Just a second ago, I was waiting for Linda on the bridge...
What was that?
What's wrong, Banri?
Hey, what are you doing?
Dance! Dance!
Banri?
What's wrong with him?
Come back, you idiot!
Banri!
What are you guys doing?
Dance! Dance!
What is this?
What's going on?
I thought I was waiting for Linda on the bridge.
Why was I suddenly thrown into this place?
What happened?
Banri.
Linda.
What's wrong, Banri?
Are you not feeling well?
Kouko-chan's looking for you somewhere else.
Kouko...
We should head back.
Can you dance?
Are you okay?
Kouko...
Oh, right! Kouko!
I was just dancing with Kouko until a minute ago.
But... why did my memories up to the day after graduation suddenly come back?
Hey, seriously, are you okay?
I'm... fine.
Sorry.
I need to go back to Kouko and the others.
Banri.
I'm fine.
I need to go to Kouko...
Why did this happen?
I thought he was gone.
Why did my memories suddenly return?
Is he trying to take over my body...
...my memories...
...my existence again?
Chigau yo mou, chigau tteba
Aa, mada kizukanai no ne?
Ni san jikan mo mae kara sono ude ni furetai noni
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
Sakebitai kimochi wa hora komaru hodo aru noni
Doushite doushite chittomo aa satotte kurenai no?
Ne hontou ni hontou ni watashi ni koi shiteru?
Kosabayui kotoba wa iranai
Han eikyuuteki ni ai shite yo
Gosen-nen go nado kyoumi wa nai
Watashi endless de wa nai no
Itsuka wa shinu no yo
"Eien ni ai shiteru yo" nante yuwaretemo ureshikunai
Mazu wa watashi o shinu made
Ai suru koto dake o kangaete
I'll Be Back
How dare you act so happy?!
You're so impudent, Tada Banri!
Happiness won't come to us!
That's why we go out searching for it!
Come on, bring it on!
Yeah!