It's not often I can write on a ship, so this was a great experience for me.
I also found out that I can ease myself thinking I'm dirtying white paper.
The brushing is a lot easier now...
Just one more month until the Narukain Exhibit.
With one month, I'll...
Here, eat!
What is that?
Konomon. ["pickles"]
Konomon?
This much?
If'n ya finish 'em, I'll bring some more.
So they do go out from the back...
There's no way I can eat this much.
Delicious...
I have to concentrate on calligraphy now...
I'll write an innovative and artistic konomon--
Not konomon!
Write... I'm going to write on the konomon--
Not konomon...!
The Konomon-in Exhibit is next month--
Not Konomon-in Exhibit...
Konomon. Konomon...
Konomon!
"Konomon"
"Unnioegi"
"Translation: Going to the sea to swim"
Konomon. Konomon...
Konomon?!
If'n ya finish 'em, I'll bring some more... more... more...
Konomon!
Teach me calligraphy!
It's you girls...!
"You girls"? That's rude.
Ah, sorry.
Here!
Grandpa told me to bring them, since ain't nothin' wrong with having them.
Thank you.
Sensei, can you help with our subject?
First, hold the brush with your right hand.
--This is my right hand!
--Correct.
You have to be right-handed to do calligraphy?
No, but it's easier to write with the hand closer to the inkstone.
And what's the subject?
Um... This.
"Visiting Old, Learning New"
Okay, I'll write an example, so watch carefully.
Out of my way.
Aww... You're not gonna slap it on like usual?
"Visiting Old, Learning New"
What do you mean, "slap it on"...?
Everything starts with fundamentals.
I wanna write 'em like that!
It's flashy!
Ah... That's still in the works.
Once it's done and recognized,
I'll teach it to you.
Recognized by...?
When I get first place in next month's Narukain Exhibit...
You're good enough without getting an award.
I just wanna have fun writing without worrying 'bout that.
Have fun...?
You girls are such kids...
Here, Naru. Write this.
"Cat"
Yay! Cat!
All right!
Now that I'm teaching,
I'll make sure you're both awarded.
With results, you'll know firsthand why I'm so fixed on getting an award...
Now, start writing for the next hour like there's no tomorrow!
Focus.
Don't ink your brush twice.
The line here is wrong.
Stop your brush once.
Wake up.
I can't take this no more!
You girls! Stop being lazy!
You girls were the ones who asked for help on the subject.
I won't let you take anything less than first.
Yeah, but how many times are ya gonna make us write the same stuff?
Aren't there any tips for writing better?
Are you girls kidding?!
Do you think professional calligraphers write beautiful characters easily?!
Feel the emotions being written into a single piece of calligraphy!
Thousands upon thousands of our predecessors
have written on paper millions upon millions of their emotions!
--Who?
--Beats me...
Physical fatigue... Mental breakdown...
Constant solitude...
Yes, the limits. See the limits!
Limits...
Just a step... Just a step closer to completion...
Yet ahead is an eternal desert.
You can't walk... You're tired of writing...
It's at that moment you see...
...the god of calligraphy!
But that god is also a mirage from the desert!
I've never seen someone hallucinating on calligraphy before...
We don't wanna reach that point over a simple middle school subject!
Before you go on, buy us some juice!
You girls aren't into this after all!
We are! We are!
We're into this, so please let us take a break!
All right, but you better be writing when I return!
We got it!
Sensei is really a calligraphy nut.
Sei!
At this rate, he probably can't get a girlfriend.
Who knows?
Maybe he's in a platonic relationship or something.
Girlfriend?!
Lemme check the room out a bit.
Stop it, that's tasteless.
Oh?
Kawafuji-san?
Maybe it's his girlfriend.
Miwa-chan, just stop...
Shucks, a guy.
Huh?! Let me see!
What's with the interest?!
A commemorative picture?
Maybe he's going out with one of 'em!
How 'bout her?
She's good-looking, but she's not standing close enough.
How about her?
Isn't she rather plain to be Sensei's girlfriend?
I don't think looks matter.
He's satisfied with anyone as long as they talk about calligraphy.
You think any gal's gonna listen to his delusions?
--Got it!
--Anyone can listen, even monkeys.
--This.
--What's the matter, Naru?
Sensei said this was his treasure.
--What's this?
--A picture stand?
Sure feels like he's got his "special someone" in here.
What's the matter?
Sensei was someone's wife...
Naru? You're using the word "wife" wrong.
Well, Naru likes Sensei a lot.
Don't worry. It's weirder to have someone his age not go out with anyone.
Wait ten more years and you'll be prettier, Naru.
Go and plunder him.
Plunder...?
Come on, let's have a look...
...at Sensei's girlfriend!
I bought some juice.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Get serious, or else you're not even going to get an award!
Sensei, you're twenty-three already, right?!
Look at things other than calligraphy!
Whatcha thinking, fallin' in love with some historic figure?!
C'mon back to reality!
Sensei, just go out with Naru already.
--Right! I'm gonna plunder you!
--Plunder?
Hey! You! Stop it!
At this rate, you're gonna die alone!
What is this all about?!
--Plunder!
--What the heck are you saying?!
Swimming?
The kids said they were going swimming, so I was hoping you could monitor them.
I actually asked the Head Teacher, but...
I'm gonna go fishin'!
Everyone can swim, right?
If it's just watching them...
Well, but it looks like Miwa and
Tama are going with them too.
Can you keep watch so that they don't mimic anything dangerous?
I'll have Hiroshi go along too.
Something is bound to happen...
--Sensei! Let's hurry up!
--Okay.
--C'mon, hurry!
--Hey, wait a sec.
--Sensei, hurry, hurry!
--I got it, I got it! Let me get ready!
--Butt...
--Stop it!
Stop running around.
Hey, it's Miwa-nee and Tama!
Hiya, Naru!
You're late, Sensei.
Thanks for today.
Huh? What's with the gym suit-like wear?
Not "like"--these are our gym suits.
It's easier to swim in these.
What? You're swimming in those?
Well, yeah...
It should be a pain swimming with your clothes on.
Hm? Then you take yours off, Sensei.
Well, I don't have a swimsuit...
C'mon already!
Hey, wait! Hiro isn't here--
All right, let's go.
You ready, everyone? Follow Hiro-nii!
Okay!
He's only thinking about playing...
Let's go, everyone!
I'm gonna master backstroking!
Hey, don't go running around too much!
Don't worry. We go to the beach every year.
Beach? More like rocks, isn't it?!
Play somewhere safe, like a real beach!
A beach is where kids play.
That's where we should be!
The ground... is so slippery...
Sensei, what did you do?
You city folks are such a pain...
Sensei? You okay?
He'll be fine. Everyone goes through this once.
All right, jump in!
--Yeah!
Huh?
--Super huge!
Sea urchin.
Sea urchin...
Stop it already, Naru!
Hey!
Hina! You found any fish?
Yeah, but my goggles were clouded, so I couldn't see well.
Then use mugwort to wipe 'em.
I got some mugwort leaves in there.
The mugwort sap stops it from being cloudy.
Wow. Naru, you know so much.
You're like a grandma!
Whatcha mean, "grandma"?
Whoops, sorry. You don't like it?
Of course I don't like it!
I'm only seven years old!
Look at them kiddies...
They don't know a thing about how to enjoy the sea.
I see ya! Take this!
Hiroshi Critical!
Whoa! An octopus!
I got 'im!
You're so cool, Hiro-nii!
So uncool, Hiro-nii!
Look at them guys. They don't know how to enjoy the sea.
Sorry, Miwa-chan. I'm a bit tired...
You okay? Don't overdo yourself.
I'm going to go rest where Sensei is.
Hey, you okay, Tama? Your face is all red!
I'm sorry. I'm an indoor kind of person...
If you're an indoor person, stay still.
First, water. Can you drink now...?
Uh, yes...
Good, you're doin' great!
What is it...? I feel like she's staring at me.
Sensei...?
Have you ever been troubled to the point where you couldn't sleep at night?
What's the matter?
Is something bothering you?
No, not so much bothering, but...
To be blunt, what do you think about Hiro-nii?
Hiro? Why all of a sudden?
--You ready?
--What do I think?
--Here... you go!
--He's about my age and easy to talk with, so he is like a younger brother.
No... We're not that close.
He's more like someone who just brings food over...
"Jitter" "Jitter"
In the first place, why is eyeglasses girl asking me this?
I get it...! She must like Hiro!
I see. So that's why she's been acting strange lately.
Somehow, she came to ask me for advice as an elder.
Now, isn't she cute?
Sensei?
I should do my best to support her.
Hiro's a great guy.
He pays attention and can cook.
He's the sort that you don't come across too often.
He's the perfect guy to go out with--
I've had enough!
Who do you think is the reason
I'm having sleepless nights?!
What?!
I'm no fujoshi...!
Huh? Fujoshi? What are you saying?
It's dangerous running...
Sen... sei...?
You're kidding me...
Ta-da! Look, Naru! A sea cucumber!
Ew, I can't believe you can hold that thing.
Naru, you try holding it.
If you can hold this, you're an adult!
Adult...
Boo!
You're so mean, Miwa-nee!
I don't like ya!
I'm sorry 'bout that.
It looks gross, but you'll be fine once you get used to it.
It's so pudgy...
I'm okay now.
Good. You're an adult now.
Hiro-nii? Where's Sensei?
Ah...
--How much of a wimp are you?!
--Looks like he's still out...
Good, then it's okay.
Naru!
Let's go someplace more fun.
Someplace fun?
Yup! Someplace only for adults...
Ugh, damn it...
I was out again...
We better be going back.
Haven't eaten lunch yet either.
Hey, everyone! Start packing up!
--Aww... Is it already time?
--I don't wanna... Still wanna play...
Knew this'd be difficult...
Hey, where's Naru?!
She was with Miwa-chan a while ago...
Over there.
Here I go!
Miwa?!
That's dangerous! Stop!
So fun!
Hey, Miwa, looks like
Sensei is sayin' something.
Really? Wonder if it's time...
Let's jump once more, then go.
Yeah, but before that...
Hey, Naru!
Jump in!
Hey, wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Why are you...?!
Stop! Naru!
Naru...!
That was fun!
Good job! Now that's my young gal!
I geard Sensei cheerin' for me, sayin', "Naru!" when I gumped.
Ghat's why I wasn't sghared at all.
Cheering?
Yeah, I guess he was sayin' something.
Sensei?!
Hey... Sensei!
Damn it! Doing such dangerous things...!
Sorry, Sensei...
We won't do it again, so cheer up already.
C'mon!
Sensei...!
This is the first time...
Until I came to this island, all I needed to do was think about myself...
This is the first time I've ever worried this much for someone else!
Damn it! I'm going!
Sensei!
H-Hey...
Sensei! I won't make you worry!
--Me either!
Me either!
You kids...
Sensei! I won't do anything dangerous anymore!
I won't ever do anything dangerous either!
Sensei! Sensei! Sensei!
Guess the outsider really got his roots in...
Stare...
Don't expect me to join in.
Aww...
"Sigh"
Stop it!
"Cool breeze"
"Call received" "1 call"
"Kawafuji"
"Fukue Airport"
It's no good. He's not answering...
"Out of area"
What? Out of area again?
What to do...
Dang, what an inconvenient place.
Well, I like the place.
Everything is like a miniature set. So tiny.
Kosuke, you're making fun, aren't you?
It's okay... The "where" doesn't matter.
As long as I can meet Handa-san.
Miwa-chan! Miwa-chan!
Huh?
Your hair's a wreck.
Ah...
Been super humid recently, so...
Well, you do have kinked hair to begin with.
"Shaggy"
Found a colleague!
Hey, you girls came to fish too?
Sensei, your hair's quite something...
Really? When I'm feeling good, it's usually like this.
Nah, that's because of the humidity.
You both have similar hair types.
Pretty much the same cuts too.
Don't copy me, Sensei!
"Copy"...?
Why not just crop it down short?
No, it wouldn't match me...
Hey, got a lot of people here.
Can Head Teacher join ya?
"Shaggy-curly"
Tell ya, this humidity is such a pain!
The same as Head Teacher?!
Thank goodness I have straight hair!
Short hair isn't the thing, ever.
It's tengusa head!
What?
"Tengusa" ["seaweed"]