Kaga
Kouko
But since coming here,
I...
I feel like I've become invisible.
Kaga-san.
Hello, Tada-kun.
Where is everyone else?
Not here yet.
It's nearly time, too...
Tada-kun, did you tell Mitsuo about today?
I texted him.
He just sent me this reply.
Yanagisawa Mitsuo
No subject
An overnight trip?
With which club?
He's thinking about me!
Huh?
Tada Banri!
2D-kun?
Are you here for the trip, too?
"2D-kun"...
Is "2" his name?
Let me introduce you.
I met him the other day at the tea club's welcoming party...
Um, I...
Are you okay, 2D-kun?
Y-you're Kaga Kouko-san, right?
I've seen you in our civil law class!
Yes, I'm Kaga Kouko.
Nice to meet you.
My real name is Sato Takaya!
I was named 2D-kun at the tea club's party!
Okay, everyone!
Sorry we're late.
Gather 'round.
Our three-day, two-night trip begins!
Thank y-
Why don't you start...
by writing your name, address, and phone number on this.
Oh, you can fill them out in the car.
Get in.
We're a little behind schedule, so we'll have to hurry.
Okay, you're in this car.
You're in this one.
You're over there.
Night Escape
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even it it's the long way around
PERSONAL INFORMATION FORM
University/Department:FUKURAI UNIVERSITY LAW
School Name:TADA BANRI
Residence:TOKYO SUGINAMI
I'm so glad the weather's nice today.
Oh, let me know if you want a drink or anything.
We won't be making any stops, though,
so maybe you shouldn't drink too much.
Oh... Your name's Kaga Kouko?
What a beautiful name.
Yes, thank you.
Why are you looking around like that?
Hurry up and fill in your form.
O-okay...
Fukurai University
Fuji Seminar House
Excuse me, but didn't we just pass the seminar house?
Didn't we just pass our university's seminar house?
What? I can't hear you!
Didn't we just...
Hey, wait.
That tickles.
Don't do that.
Where are we?
We're almost there.
Get ready to go.
Carsick...
Okay, I'm going to collect your forms now.
Give me your completed forms.
PERSONAL INFORMATION FORM
University/Department: FUKURAI UNIVERSITY
LITERATURE DEPT
Name: TAKAHASHI SHU
Kaga-san!
Tada-kun.
Oh, good. I can finally talk to someone I know.
Is this really the university's seminar house?
My phone has no service.
I don't think it is.
The place was the training facility for a religious organization I had never heard of.
We'll keep all your luggage in here.
Bring your bags on in.
For the next five hours, maybe longer, we were shown films...
and indoctrinated with lectures on the universe and souls.
This is bad.
I can't handle being trapped here another two days.
Well...
Let's have some fun.
Lift your glasses, everyone.
To the awakening of our new children,
to the excellent full moon tonight,
and to our reunion ten thousand years into a future century!
Cheers!
Hello, Neo-Children!
Hello!
What am I going to do?
They made us write down our addresses.
Come on.
We're throwing a party for the day of your awakening!
Try to have fun.
Right.
You must begin by loving the Earth.
I see...
Have you ever loved the Earth?
What should I do?
I'm responsible for bringing Kaga-san here.
I need to at least get her home safely.
What should I do? How can I...
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm not doing this!
Ten thousand years into a future century?!
You tricked us by calling yourselves a club!
Anyway, aren't you detaining us?
That's a crime!
Do you think you'll get away with this?
Take us home immediately!
We don't want to be here any longer!
We'll sue!
That's what everyone says at first.
But don't worry.
You'll understand soon.
After spending all day tomorrow speaking with us,
I'm sure you'll awaken, as well.
Are you people serious?
If you want to leave, then leave.
I don't want to go, though.
Wh-what are you talking about, Tada Banri?
Your whining is bringing everyone down!
What do you not like about this?
Having difficult people like you around just makes trouble for the rest of us!
I want to have fun here!
Quit complaining over little things!
Senpai, they're in the way.
If they want to leave, you should let them go.
When I saw that film earlier, I was really moved.
I'd like to listen to what you have to say in earnest.
The truth is...
In high school, I suffered a serious injury in an accident,
and lost all my memories.
It's what you'd call amnesia.
When I awoke, I was in a world full of strangers.
I had no parents.
No friends, no acquaintances... no one.
I was so lonely...
...and so insecure.
I was in such pain...
It must have been hard.
But you don't need to worry anymore.
The moment of your salvation has come.
Listen, everyone!
I believe we should allow the kids who are not interested to depart,
and instead spend time getting to know this boy.
Go back with us.
I've already decided to become a believer.
Thanks to you, Kaga-san,
I met some good people.
Thank you.
If you're leaving, get in the van.
Well, let's head back.
Okay.
I decided to stay after all.
I was impressed by the lecture earlier.
Even though I'm beautiful, I'm not very popular.
I have abandoned this century.
I long for the new century!
Well...
We somehow managed to meet our quota.
Now we can save face with the district leader.
What are you doing?
You're ruining the whole reason I stayed.
I knew that was it.
You wasted your chance to escape.
I couldn't leave you here.
It's my fault you're here.
Let's escape together.
Come on, you two.
The stars shouldn't be waiting in the wings.
Come here so we can tell you more.
We'll be right there.
Oh, but first...
We'd like to put her luggage away.
Could we borrow the key?
The key?
Sure.
Here.
We'll be right back.
Wait. I'll go with you.
Stop!
Somebody! Stop them!
Open this door!
What's wrong?
They locked the door from the inside!
What?!
I think we can get out through here.
Hey, open up!
Let us in!
Hang on.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Open the door!
The forms.
They're trying to escape!
Hey, someone bring the spare key!
Oh no!
Can we leave everything except your valuables?
Yeah!
They should be heading towards the station!
Split up and search!
We passed our university's seminar house on the way here.
If we can make it there,
I'm sure the rest will work out.
We seem to have lost them.
Yes.
OUT OF
SERVICE
I still can't get any service.
What about yours?
Mine's not working either.
Kaga-san, aren't you cold?
Kaga-san?
It's my fault this happened, isn't it?
Come on...
Don't say that.
It's my fault.
I'm the one who had the flyer, and I'm the one they approached.
You just came along with me.
I think it's my fault.
It's not!
I thought it would be nice if you could make friends in this club.
That's why...
It's my fault.
It's not!
It really isn't!
It really isn't your fault, Tada-kun!
I thought you would tell me about Mitsuo if I became friends with you.
I've never cared about clubs.
It's true no one tried to recruit me.
It's true everyone at college ignores me.
But it didn't bother me.
I was only trying to win your sympathy by appearing depressed.
I wanted information about Mitsuo.
So you really were after Yana-san.
Yes, Yanao...
I mixed them up. Mitsuo...
It was for Mitsuo.
90%, anyway.
What about the other 10%?
I don't know myself.
All I know for sure is that you're the only one who talks to me at college, Tada-kun.
I was happy you talked to me.
That's the truth.
I bet Yana-san's worried about you right now, Kaga-san.
I didn't tell him any details.
You think so?
You know how it is!
His uncertain feelings will change to a passionate possessiveness,
and you'll be sitting firmly in Yana-san's heart!
No way! That sounds great!
Will that really happen?
Yana-san will realize just how important his childhood friend is to him!
Yeah.
"I thought she was annoying."
"I even suspected her of being a stalker!"
"However, this girl truly is the one I'm destined to marry!"
"Kouko!"
"Mitsuo!"
Does Yana-san know that side of you, Kaga-san?
What do you mean?
Well...
You seem a little different when Yana-san isn't around.
Yana-san hasn't seen you laugh that much, has he?
If you think I seem different...
I'm complete when I'm with Mitsuo.
Think of that as the real me.
What do you mean, complete?
I'm nothing without Mitsuo.
I wake up, go to sleep, go to school, dress up, cry, and laugh because of Mitsuo.
Without Mitsuo, I can't do anything.
There's no reason for me to live.
Kaga-san, you really are all about Yana-san.
It's how I've always lived my life.
I have nothing better to do than chase a man who ignores me.
You must think I'm stupid.
It's fine, though. I really am stupid.
You shouldn't do things that upset him, then.
Like hitting him with roses.
That was...
Mitsuo's fault! Yeah!
It was clearly your fault.
No, it wasn't!
There was a reason for that!
Four months of rage exploded!
The truth is, I meant to congratulate him and hand over the roses with a smile.
That was my perfect plan...
What did you think would happen?
I thought for sure I'd knock Mitsuo out this time
with my bravery in following him to the same university!
Seriously?
Seriously!
Mitsuo always told me he would apply to our affiliated university.
I knew it was a lie,
but I pretended to be deceived, and secretly applied to the same school as Mitsuo.
I hoped he would eventually tell me the truth.
But even after we graduated, he didn't say anything.
I still meant to forgive him with a smile...
But on the day of the entrance ceremony, when I saw him happily walking up with you,
I just couldn't take it anymore!
That's why you whacked him with the roses?
That's right, wham!
I regret it now.
You're right. I keep giving him reasons to hate me.
When it comes to Mitsuo,
I can't keep a cool head.
I lose sight of everything else.
Anyway, let's not talk about me.
Tell me about yourself, Tada-kun.
Let's see...
Tada-kun, are you going out with anyone?
I wouldn't know.
I really did lose my memories.
What are you talking about?
My amnesia.
That was true?
The day after I graduated from high school,
I apparently fell off a bridge in the neighborhood.
I lost my memories after that, and here I am now.
I forgot everything I knew about myself before then.
My relationships with parents, friends, classmates, and teachers.
What I liked and didn't like.
In other words, I lost what you'd call my identity.
Even a year in the hospital and rehabilitation didn't help.
I was afraid to meet my old friends.
I thought the one they wanted to see
was the former Tada Banri they knew before I lost my memories.
I felt like they didn't need who I was now.
So I refused to meet anyone.
But if I had a girlfriend, I'm sure she'd have come to see me anyway.
Yeah, maybe.
I can't remember anything, but sometimes these emotions come back to me.
Sort of like nostalgia.
Like I can almost remember something...
But when I try to pursue those feelings, they disappear.
It's like there's something written on a piece of paper,
and when I try to read it, the sentence disappears.
Those vague hints of memories
I can almost recall are just eaten away.
It's actually quite terrifying.
Um...
Sorry! That must have been weird.
No, that's okay.
It's just...
I don't know what to say.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm perfectly healthy now.
If you have any questions, ask away.
In that case, um...
Do you want to return to your past self?
I don't know.
The only self I know is the person I am now.
I understand why my parents and other people want me to return to my old self, though.
Sometimes I want to try returning to my old self.
That is, I wouldn't mind adding my past memories to my present self,
but to lose my current identity...
If my present self had to disappear and be replaced by my old self, I wouldn't want that.
The old Tada Banri disappeared from this world.
The person here now is a new and different Tada Banri.
I see.
I wonder if the old Tada-kun is watching over you from somewhere.
Like a guardian angel.
That might be a little scary.
Tada-kun, look!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Now that I think about it, this is just like that time...
Wait, Tada-kun!
Something's wrong with those people.
Maybe it's those believers.
If it is, we've got trouble!
Banri?
What?
It's me.
Can't you tell? Here.
Huh?
Barbara?!
It's Linda.
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
Blackout
Oh! Tada Banri?!
What are you doing wearing slippers
way out here in the mountains?
Oh, are you on a date?
Who, me?
I'm...
What was I doing?
Anyway, who's Barbara?