Sensei! I'm here to play!
Huh?
Sensei!
Sensei...?
Hey, you're early.
Did you get my calligraphy?
Got it a while back.
"Stars
Seishu Handa"
With its size, it's quite a piece to look at.
Yeah...
Are you saying it wouldn't look good if it was small?!
That's not what I meant!
Even if he's learning,
Kawafuji is technically an art dealer...
Is it just technical, and that's why he only praises size?!
Or is size the only thing about it worth praising?!
Bothersome as usual...
Now calm down. The Director should be here shortly.
C-Can I get a glass of water...?
You look pale...
You sure you're okay?
"I'm in Tokyo"
"Translation: Yoseo"
What am I supposed to say to the Director?
What do you mean "what"? Just apologize.
You're back because the
Director said he'd forgive you.
The rest is just a matter of how you feel about this.
Well, I did buy these cell straps as a gift...
Straps? He isn't a high-school girl...
"Baramon-kun"
It's not cute at all...
Your sighing is starting to depress me, too.
The Director is going to be looking at my calligraphy shortly...
What am I supposed to do if he criticizes it before I submit it to Naruka?
I wouldn't be able to recover from it...
I don't think it'll be criticized.
You sent this over because you were confident in it, right?
We've known each other for a while.
What's your take on it?
Would you have known it was something I wrote?
Now that you mention it,
I'm not sure how to reply, but...
...the calligraphy is bold and draws attention. I think it's good.
I wouldn't have expected this based on your previous style.
That's the problem!
Huh?
I don't... write this kind of calligraphy!
It's too good!
Ah, sorry, but I don't get a word you're saying.
How can I word this...?
This "off" feeling... I mean...
Okay, it's like, it's their fault I wrote it, know what I mean? Like, it just happened, like...
"10 minutes later"
So you mean it was a fluke?
Way to cut down on the details!
But you're right.
Damn it... Anyone can write calligraphy like that if they go to the island.
It's nothing to be worried about.
Stop questioning yourself just because your style is different from before.
Just say you adventured a bit, and get it over with.
If I do that, I'll never be able to write my own calligraphy.
An aspiring farmer can't become a fisherman
just because he casually went fishing and caught a hisanio!
I want to find my own one-of-a-kind flower and nurture it until it blossoms!
I want a special flower that's the only one of its kind!
Huh? So what?
Are you implying that you don't need to be number one?
A farmer can't become a fisherman...
Quite an interesting comparison, Handa-kun.
Director.
Successful calligraphers and artists master their arts in like manner.
I'm sorry I didn't greet you.
Never mind that. I'm the one who wanted to meet Handa-kun.
No formalities are needed.
Now, then... How have you been?
Yes! Fine! And well!
No need to be so tense...
You spoke more naturally before.
No! I just got carried away back then!
Calm down... Calm yourself...
Today's the day I'm going to apologize and get forgiven...
A cane?
The Director must have an ailing back...
Thank you, Handa-kun.
Not at all.
Even if I was angry... how could
I have punched a person like this?
I'm such a lowlife...
I'm truly sorry...
I should have apologized earlier.
For my violent behavior, and for only facing you after hearing you would forgive me...
I'm truly...
...truly sorry...
Director...
In all honesty, I wasn't going to forgive you.
I used my forgiveness as bait to bring you here, so that I could lecture you on morals, but...
...it seems that wasn't necessary.
Don't ever act on impulse again.
I forgive you.
Handa?
What a relief...
I was worried about what to do if I wasn't forgiven...
Thank you...
...so very much.
Good for you, Handa.
Go and give him that strap now.
This isn't the right time to bring that out!
Now then, Handa-kun?
Yes!
I'd like to take a closer look at your calligraphy.
Do you mind lending me a hand?
Y-Yes!
Oh? So this is your style of calligraphy now?
Yes...
Uh, um... This is...
Um...
Handa-kun?
This calligraphy...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!...
I thought I just told you not to act on impulse...
Don't laugh... Don't laugh... Don't laugh...
This work is just a sketch! Right!
Something I wrote for practice!
I packed my work for the exhibition, so I... uh, didn't bring it with me.
I see.
It is unreasonable for me to have wanted to see your work so close to the deadline.
Y-Yes. I'm so sorry to have shown you my terrible calligraphy!
Hey... Handa...
Very well.
Let me evaluate this based on the idea that it is just a sketch.
Your writing has become very interesting, unlike anything before.
The character is reminiscent of an elementary school subject,
and yet I can see stars amid the night.
There's the loneliness of being abandoned in darkness,
but also the light that only darkness reveals...
I'm not the only judge on the panel, but I think this is grand prize-worthy.
Thank you very much!
Well, now I can't wait.
If this is just a sketch, then I can expect something better at Naruka.
What a wonderful day it has been.
I'll come again.
Ah, Director? I'll call a taxi.
I've really done it...
"Kawafuji Fine Arts"
Director?
No need for a taxi.
My ride is here.
I see.
Thank you very much!
Someone drove him here?
Huh? That car...
It seems sending Seishu-kun to the island was the right move.
He still has a lot to improve on...
Wh-What happened?!
I'm sorry, I stalled the engine.
I'm not very good at starting the car on an incline.
We're just awkward.
Both me and my son.
Ah! Y-You're scaring me!
Hey, Handa! Looks like your dad was here...
What the hell?!
Send me back to the island...
Hello.
My, it's been a while, Kawafuji-kun.
Handa.
I'm coming in.
"Naru" "flight" "island" "konomon"
"island" "stars"
"Tama"
"Hiro"
"things will be
"Naru"
"island"
fine as long
as I return to
the island"
You're late...
--I better leave...
--Don't leave... you jerk...
From the looks of it...
...you haven't finished, have you?
No...
That hair of yours...
Is that to get back into the groove you were in on the island?
Yes... I was hoping for a sliver of inspiration...
The deadline for the exhibit is tomorrow.
This is no time to be doing stuff like that!
No need to get so angry...
Well, I did write the "Stars" character like before.
Oh? If you write in that style, you can shoot for the grand prize!
If you wrote it like before, then you're set!
"Stars
Seishu Handa"
Looks like something an elementary school student would write.
I knew you'd say that!
I've been trying to write the same as before, but I just can't!
I tried staring at the stars, but the bright city lights don't allow me the needed anxiety!
Can't write! Can't write! I just can't write...!
Still, the difference is astounding.
I'm just the type who gets swayed by the environment more than others...
That means your stability up to now was just because your life was so calm and placid...
You've submitted to a number of exhibits before, right?
Then do something.
Easy for you to say! If I could do this,
I wouldn't have called the likes of you!
"The likes of me"?
I'm the only friend you have...
There's nothing I can do--
No!
There is one thing you can do...
Sei-san? I brought tea.
--Is there any meaning to this?!
--I can't bind you well. Stay still!
Sensei, who am I supposed to be?
I don't really like kids.
Shut up already!
Just shut up and cry!
B-Bondage!
--B-Bondage...
--Are you his mother?
Sorry for the bother!
Wha--?! Mom?!
Sei-san... What are you doing...?
Ah! No, it's not what you think!
This is for my writing...
--This really isn't what it looks like, Mom!
--By the way, Kawafuji-san is Naru-chan,
--Mom...?
--and I'm the crybaby first grader.
He was such a good child...
He may have had a cold attitude,
but he was kind at heart, and loved by everyone as a tsundere...
But now, he's more like a tsun-dummy!
There's no "moe" involved whatsoever!
This is all because he went to the island!
Hey, Mom?!
No...
You all right?
Not really, but this is seriously bringing back memories of the island.
But don't you think it's too simple to expect that you'll be able write calligraphy well...
...by mimicking what happened on the island?
Get out of my bed.
Just forget about calligraphy you can only write on the island, and hurry back to Tokyo.
Hey! Stop searching!
I knew it! A dirty mag!
--Hey!
--Seriously?!
Don't toss it!
I don't feel like submitting if
Sensei isn't going to submit.
It's not like the prize money is great or it'll make you famous.
Maybe I should just write a bunch and open my own exhibit.
Are you kidding? Do you know how much I'm staking on this exhibit?
Sure, it's not a major exhibit.
But for me, this is an important step towards being reborn anew...
I'll take that step no matter what...
Sensei...
Hey! Stop recording me!
My famous quotes!
Why'd you bring him here?!
--I figured Naru alone wouldn't be enough to lift your spirits.
--S... Sensei!
He's just a nuisance!
Well, at least...
...your seriousness was answered.
Let me help you.
A call?
"On Hold"
Hello?
So did we get through?
Sensei?
We got through?
--Sensei!
--Sensei, how ya doin'?!
--Hey, lemme speak too.
Why are you kids...
Ah! He's on!
Hi there, Sensei! How ya doing?
Sensei? Kawafuji-san told me that you were lonely, and he wanted us to call.
Hey, Aki! Ya finished yet?
So I gathered everyone at the store.
Sensei! Are you okay?!
Kawa-san is so kind! But Hiro-nii is also really worried about you!
Why are you saying that?
Hello.
--You sure did cause problems,
--My turn!
--leavin' without a word like that.
--Hand it over!
I see. Sorry about--
Sensei!
Are ya okay?!
Hey! Stop sayin' useless stuff!
I'm gonna knock ya out!
Great having a friend, right?
You better appreciate it.
Hey, me next!
Ow! Ouch! You're stepping on my foot!
--Yeah... Thanks.
--Sensei! Are you doing okay?!
He thanked me...?
You're hurting my ears! Take turns talking!
--Sensei? Yer coming back, right?
--Sensei!
Huh?
When ya gonna come back?
We thought of the perfect penalty for you leaving without tellin' us!
You kids...
It's me, Aki.
Hey, Akki.
I heard you were stressed over not being able to come up with a good piece.
You're that worried for me?
You sure are attentive, even more than most adults.
I think I'll be fine if I can remember things from the island to arouse my inspiration...
Yeah... Yeah...
He's seriously going to a kid with his problems?
Well, it's not a slump per se, but when I try to write, I can't...
Hina doesn't get it...
Hey! Tell me when someone else gets on the line!
He sure is being played with...
He looks happy.
--Sensei?
--Is that you, Naru?
Yup.
It's boring 'round here without you, Sensei.
I still got a lot I wanna do with you.
So...
...hurry and come home.
We're waitin' for ya!
Can you write now?
Yeah.
That's right!
Sensei, are you looking for something?
Well, I'm not sure if I brought it with me...
It was the last work I did back there.
Maybe...
Got it.
Hm? A name list?
--Ink.
--What?
Make me plenty of ink!
Kanzaki, go and buy me some paper to practice on!
Why me?!
So, he's finally on the move.
I hope he isn't going to do anything strange.
I was against him leaving in the first place.
I don't ever want him to go back to the island again!
Then go and convince him.
What a horrible person!
You know he's going to want to go back!
Are you sending me to get hurt?
You're so horrible! Horrible! Horrible!...
We're partly to blame for
Sei's overly serious nature.
We're not the ones to determine our son's potential.
If going off on his own will make him mature, all we can do is watch...
Dear...
So that's the way of manhood...
Yay! It's Handa Seimei!
He's so refined and cool!
Stop it!
Hey, Kawafuji. Get up.
What time is it now?
I'm finished.
It's my greatest masterpiece.
How is it? Pretty amazing, right?
This is the first time I've written calligraphy like this.
And the title?
Stone Wall...
The summer assignments are going to be posted in the hallway.
Let's go and take a look!
It's time...
Yes, it's time...
I can't wait.
We may get the gold award, you know?
If we're awarded, Sensei will be so happy!
Let's surprise Sensei with a double gold award!
Sensei should thank the gods fer givin' him super students like us!
Yeah!
"Visiting Old, Learning New
Arai Tamako, second year, class one
Gold award"
Yamamura Miwa, second year, class one
Silver"
"Silver"
Well, Miwa-chan...
I gotta go to the restroom.
Why... only... Tama...?
Oh, come on, Miwa-chan. Cheer up already.
It's over... I won't be able to face Sensei...
It's okay. You got the silver award.
That's second place!
There's a freakin' huge difference between first and second place!
She's pissed?!