3... 3... 3...
I've been studying real hard...
No one understands...
The exam is coming, so do a little better.
Put in a few more runs!
Sing a little louder!
I'm doing it!
Brighten up, Hiroshi.
What are you doing here?!
It's okay getting all 3's.
Dad used to get all 3's too.
Yes, you're on the right track to mediocrity!
Being mediocre is a personality too!
If you have nothing better to say, get out!
We're here because we have something we want you to do.
Here.
Take the champon to Sensei.
You know, maybe now's a good time to think.
There's no need to make food for some outsider.
Y'know, I can tell him to cook his own food.
You don't know anything, do you?!
Taking care of Sensei has become a fulfilling part of my life.
I have a son who no longer needs my care,
and a washed-up husband who only speaks well of the food I make.
Within my bland life, Sensei is the only one
that brings out the motherly love and womanliness inside of me...
"Yakamashika"
"Translation: Noisy"
It's been a week since I came to this island.
I still can't write anything that agrees with me.
That was just something
I drew out of inspiration.
"Ease, Comfort, Relief"
That's not my calligraphy.
I came here to immerse myself in calligraphy.
To make that geezer eat his words.
Focus...
Sensei...!
You again! Why are you here every day?
Because Naru is Sensei's commuter wife.
Where in the world did you pick that up from?!
Hello!
Miwa-nee and Tama!
Hey, so he's the rumored guy!
It's the first time I've seen someone wear styled summer clothes.
It's been a while since we came to the base.
Hey, who said you could come in?!
The poster's been peeled off!
The CDs are gone too!
Hey! Why did you come here all of a sudden?
You're the one who came here all of a sudden!
This used to be our base!
Before that, where's our stuff?
Don't tell me you threw it away!
If it's the stuff that was here when I came, it's in that box over there.
Thank goodness!
These were precious to us.
You know... this place isn't your base anymore.
Hey, wait! Don't put that up!
We're not planning on leaving here.
Leave! There's a resident here now!
C'mon, cut us some slack.
I bet you're happy you get to tangle with us young gals!
Don't make it sound lewd!
Wait... It must be you girls.
Huh?
How dare you teach this kid street slang?!
That wife there is the "queen" of Kabuki-cho.
The weather's nice, so I'll go and have a "pillow talk"!
This miso soup is some "serious juice"!
Be careful next time!
Yeah, but I can't do nothin'.
Right?
You were listening to us and learned it, right?
Yup. You taught me nothin'.
Sensei, you better watch out too.
Kids her age can remember words like a mynah.
That's why I'm telling you your words...
Eth-Emu?
Wait! Naru!
I drew this for work...
So, an SM club?
No!
Eth-Emu! Eth-Emu! Eth-Emu!
"Ethnic Restaurant
Emupamusa"
This is a sign for a restaurant!
Tama, whatcha doing?
Hey! What are you doing using my tools?!
Done!
Ta-da!
"Loser"
Write nicer words than that!
Tama, you're good!
I should've figured. You did want to be a manga writer.
Don't bring up the subject!
It may be better than Sensei's!
Really? I guess it's easy being a calligrapher.
Don't underestimate me, brats!
Look! This is the real deal!
I don't know why, but it's amazing!
I don't know why, but you're right!
Wasn't calligraphy one of our summer homework subjects?
Let's have Sensei teach us!
Nice idea!
If we learn from Sensei, we'll have a shot at the gold!
So please help us, Sensei!
Sure, leave it to me!
Okay, we'll come again tomorrow!
Bye bye!
Damn it! What did I do there?!
And these emotions...
...become the salve to the woman in me.
Oh, all right! I'll go!
Focus...
Sensei!
Hina's here now!
You kids...
I don't have time to play now!
Go and play outside!
Come on, focus... Focus...
If I ignore them, they'll probably leave soon.
Mosquito?
There!
Hold it right there!
Losty-losty!
Zho... fvun...!
SM...
You've got it wrong!
You girls, just stay away today!
Phooey...
Not good. My head's starting to spin...
Dang...
For her age, I can't believe
Mom's hooked on such a loafer.
Calligraphers are just a pain in the ass.
Gonna give it to him straight that we can't be fixin' his meals.
Hey! You're there, right?! Come out!
Hey! Answer the damn door right...
H-Hey...
What?
I'm here again!
Hiroshi! What'd you do to Sensei?!
I didn't do anything!
What should Naru do?!
--Hold the champon!
--Got it!
Everyone, lend me a bit of your power!
I said "champon"!
Good thing it's wrapped.
Yeah... But it looks terrible now.
In any case, why is he like half-dead?
He's always like this around this time.
Something 'bout writing words to send to a tournament.
So he's doing an all-nighter?
I guess I'm like this before tests too.
Well, between a talent like him and me...
...the meaning of an all-nighter's gonna be different.
Hiroshi, what's "talent"?
It means there's some who can make do with little effort,
and others who can't do anything no matter what.
Is getting all 3's the best for Hiroshi?
Hey! Who'd you get that from?!
Naru wants to do better now!
Who'd you hear it from?!
That's right! I won't lose doing that!
Hey! Listen to me!
I hid it in this room!
Hey, don't go rummaging in there...
What is this room?
It should be in that box.
Wait, Naru!
Sensei says that...
...he can't write anything good even after writing all this.
Sensei doesn't have talent,
so writing all this isn't enough.
"Zenith"
Naru thinks Sensei is super.
This "talent" thing is so weird.
This should be enough studying already.
You dyed your hair?
Yeah, I'm gonna go with this from now on.
Man, you're so half-baked.
Half-baked...
So, that's why I'm like all 3's...
Hiroshi?
Naru... Sensei does have talent after all.
What? You know, Hiroshi?
Well... not that I understand, but...
Hey! You faked that!
I guess his effort is his number-one talent...
Huh? Hiroshi, are you crying?
I'm not crying!
Liar! You're a grown-up, and still crying!
Shut up! Don't look at me!
What's that?!
Ta-da!
Cicada shells!
Huh? What?!
It's Naru's talent!
I can gather more of these than anyone!
This is "talent," right?
Well, if you're giving it all you've got...
...I guess that's talent.
Ah, you're the Village Leader's son.
Sorry to be bothering you all.
Um...
This is the last meal we're going to bring.
Mom doesn't say it, but I think she's burdened by this.
It was a burden...?
And... I'm thinking of seriously studying for my exam.
I want to follow Sensei...
...and try my very best starting today.
I liked your mom's potato stew,
but I guess it can't be helped.
Were you listening to what I said?
All right... I'll make potato stew and bring it for dinner.
Wait, that's not what I...
Well, I'd feel bad if that champon was the last.
See ya.
I guess I have to cook starting tomorrow...
Huh? Sensei, you know how to cook?
I guess I'll make curry...
Yay!
Sensei! I'm here to play...
Sensei?! Am-Am-Ambulance!
"Nanatsudake Hospital"
"Handa Sei
Private Room"
Heatstroke, lack of sleep, loss of appetite...
Let's check you in for tonight.
Okay...
My, Sensei, you should have told us you weren't feeling well.
I'm sorry. I wasn't getting much sleep.
Sensei? You going to be okay?
Yeah, I'm taking drips now, so I'll be fine.
Huh... Does it hurt more than getting poked?
Hm... I'm not sure.
Sensei, we'll go and get the things you'll need for the stay.
Yes, thank you.
If you need anything, feel free to tell Iku-chan.
This nurse here's young, but already married.
You better not lay a finger on her.
Of course I won't.
Sensei...
Did you know that injections hurt more than drips?
Wha--?!
--I've done it this time.
--Vroom... Zoom...
--I must have been stressed out.
--Zoom...
--I need to hurry back and start writing again.
--Vroom-Vroom...
And why are you still here?
Zoom...!
Vroom! Vroom-Vroom!
Put your mini-car on hold, and listen to me!
Hey, here it is. Over here.
Hiya there!
Sensei, you okay?
--We came to see you.
--Hey!
You girls came to see me?
We have school today, and our school is close by.
I see. You just stopped by on your way to school.
Not like that makes a difference, right?
Sensei! The drip is almost empty!
What?!
Isn't someone going to come and replace it when it's empty?!
Whaddya expect from this low-tech place?!
Naru, press the "Nurse Call"!
Nurse...? There's no "Nurse" here?!
--Nurse? "Nurse"? "Nurse"...?!
--We have to hurry and call Iku-nee,
or else air is going to get into Sensei's arm and kill him!
There's no "Nurse" in here!
No way?! It should be near the "pillow"!
Pillow talk? "Pillow talk"...!
Wha--?! Sensei's out cold! He's a mental wimp!
You didn't need to hurry.
The newer ones stop air from being let in.
Really? I didn't know that.
Give me a break!
I'm already sick, you know...
Sensei? Looks like your fever is up.
Do you want a suppository to get the fever down?
--Anal medicine!
Why'd you react too?
No! I sternly refuse such masochistic pleasures!
Masochistic pleasures...
This is a medical practice.
I had one when I was in elementary school.
I was so embarrassed that... I puked.
Too much information...
Well, let's keep an eye on you.
You girls, don't strain him too much, okay?
--Okay.
Huh? Where's Naru?
Whatcha doing over here?
Come out. You're going to get your clothes dirty.
Nope!
I can press it next time.
If something happens to Sensei...
...I'm gonna press the "Nurse"!
C'mon, the drip is full now.
Nothing is going to happen for now.
But... there are ghosts here.
--Ghosts...?
Grandpa told me... that there are ghosts in the hospital.
They're scarier than monsters.
Dunno what they're like.
Naru's scared too, but...
...I wanna see one myself!
That's gotta be made up by Gramps.
Whatcha doing?
I can't hear you!
I don't believe in ghosts!
What are you going to do if I can't sleep after hearing that?!
This hospital is old, so it's really scary!
Why not just do that anal medicine thing?
What's there to freak about?
'Sup? I brought your stuff.
Yes!
Where are the calligraphy tools?
Request denied.
Why?! I was waiting to get my hands on them!
You're here 'cause you're overworked, right? So just rest!
--I'm at peace when I'm working!
--Tch...
--Are you an idiot?! Can't you tell I'm worried?!
--What's the matter?!
--Oh, yeah?!
--You look agitated!
All right, we have to go now.
See you!
Bye bye!
I'd better go back...
Hello there.
Oh, um, hello there.
Did I surprise you?
A little...
I'm from the room next door.
That was quite lively, wasn't it?
I'm sorry. Was it noisy?
Not at all.
What brought you in here?
Nothing really bad. Just a summer cold.
Come now, it isn't "just" a cold.
Everyone came by worried about you, right?
Those are kids who were happy to see you safe.
Do get well soon, okay?
"Pulse"
Handa-san?! What are you doing?!
Please let the Village Leader know that I want my calligraphy tools!
Your fever hasn't gone down yet!
I have to do this now!
I just came up with an idea! I can write now!
Please! Please let me write! Now, hurry!
--No...
--I need to write now!
--Stop, Sensei!
--Every moment counts in calligraphy!
No! Don't, Sensei! I have a husband...!
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I just wanted to let you know...
His fever went up with excitement...
...so I'll give him a suppository and let him sleep.
Sensei! You okay now?
Yeah, better than ever.
Whoa! That's super!
You really got your complexion back.
Must be because of the butt medicine.
Make sure you take your prescription.
What's with the distance?
Don't test my love of my husband!
What happened?
Now, time to hurry back and start writing!
Oh, you look ready!
Grandpa from next door cheered me up yesterday.
Oh?
He's in this room over here...
Um... Where's the elderly man in this room?
Elderly...?
Sensei, you were the only one hospitalized here yesterday.
Most of the patients stay in the newer facility.
Really?
Sensei? Did you see a ghost or something?
Sensei...!
Hey there!
I brought you potato stew.
What happened to your fingers?!
No! Nothing! These are nothing!
Sensei!
Whatcha want me to do with...
...the bloody onions Sensei chopped?
That's not blood! It's spice! Hot sauce!
The red comes from stuff like that!
Mom...
I kind of get what you mean now.
We'll be bringing food again starting tomorrow.
Huh? Really?!
Isn't that great, Sensei?