I love you, Tada-kun.
She's the one who stole my bike!
What?
Why don't you come down to the station with me?
Masquerade
Hand in hand let's go party night!
I can't stop my heart from dancing
Crying and laughing, we never forget our memories together
Finding your true self
And becoming an adult is difficult work
Maybe I can forget for now
The night is waiting
As our hearts beat excitedly in rhythm
And we frolic about
I nearly realize
The feelings I want to tell you
Even if we are afraid of the past and future
You cannot move if you remain empty
It's all right if we have fun, so let's begin
If I forget all my troubles
and dance the night away with you
I feel like I'll become someone more wonderful
This endless Golden Time,
The distance between us as you approach
Neither closes nor widens
I'll treasure this even it it's the long way around
Traffic
Division
Kaga-san!
Wait here until your parents arrive.
How'd it go?
Looks like I'll be off the hook with just some paperwork.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I've inconvenienced you again.
It's okay. Actually...
Kaga-san, I thought you still hadn't forgotten about Yana-san.
You were so shocked when he confessed to Oka-chan.
I wasn't shocked that Mitsuo confessed to Miss Ultrasonic.
I was sad for myself.
Huh?
Miss Ultrasonic easily acquires what I don't have.
Mitsuo...
A fun life...
New friends...
Even you.
I thought she was going to get you, too.
It made me sad to think about it...
Accepting that I was more and more attracted to you was really difficult for me.
I thought I was just attracted to your kindness because of the pain of being rejected.
I was suspicious of my own motives.
That's why, according to my plan, the correct answer was no.
Your plan?
To mature on my own and be the one to confess.
I thought it was the right thing to do, and I believed it would change the world.
But...
Things don't go according to plan.
You can reject me.
It'd make us even.
It would not!
Kaga Kouko-san.
Your father is here.
I'm Kouko's father.
Ow!
I'm so sorry.
I intend to go apologize to the owner of the bicycle now.
I'll go with you.
I couldn't inconvenience you any further.
My daughter is stupid,
but I hope this won't stop you from being her friend.
Sure.
He's not my friend.
What?
My boyfriend...
What a crazy day.
Incoming Message
Linda-senpai
No subject
I want to talk to you.
Call me back.
Ro-me-o-sama.
Your Juliet has arrived.
Good morning, my boyfriend Tada-kun.
Kaga-san...
You waited for 30 minutes?
Yes, so I could say "good morning" to you.
You could've texted me.
I wanted to express my love.
You know, like...
A dog?
That's right.
A poor dog who died waiting for her owner.
Like Hachiko, the Faithful Dog?
Exactly!
Wow, Tada-kun!
We really do understand each other!
Aw... but I messed up.
How so?
If I had waited for you in front of your place,
I could have been with you longer.
You don't need to wait for me...
We can just meet somewhere.
That won't do at all!
After all...
I love you, Tada-kun.
I don't want to waste a single second or meter.
From your first step and second of the day,
I want to be with you.
What?
Did I say something weird?
No.
I'm just glad we're dating!
Oh, Tada-kun...!
I'll meet you at your place every day.
Oh... um...
It's not easy for me to say this, but you can't come to my place.
Why not?
Are your parents opposed to us dating?
They can't be! I'm harmless!
It's the opposite.
They think I'm harmful.
Harmful?
My father said I should stay away from you.
He said that if a weird girl like me clings to you, it'll ruin your life.
He asked if you were my new target.
Was Yana-san your old target?
Yeah...
In any case...
Our future looks grim.
Like Romeo and Juliet, we might poison each other eventually.
Um... they didn't poison each other...
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
Just what it looks like.
Seriously?!
Why?! When?!
You're kidding, right?!
I...
I love...
I love you.
Man, you're too much!
I... I can't breathe!
I give up!
Pro wrestling!
Oh, my.
Morning.
Huh?
Yana-san, you look so cool.
Oh... I do?
Well, I was kind of hating myself...
so I went to get my head shaved.
The person at the store asked to practice on my head if I was going to cut it off anyway,
and this happened.
Ah...
So, what's up with Banri and Kouko?
They're dating!
Aren't you shocked?
I was surprised for a second, but I'm not shocked.
I mean...
I kind of figured they'd end up together.
What? You did?
Yeah.
As far as I could tell,
you're an unusually tolerant guy who could handle dating Kouko.
For me, it's a load off.
I feel like I've finally been freed from the evil spirit that's been clinging to me.
How surprising.
You sound like you must have recovered completely.
After Miss Ultrasonic rejected you so pitifully, too.
Saying in her cute little ultrasonic voice,
"What? Are you stupid?"
was too much.
I would've been like...
O...
OM...
OMG!
But it's all right.
You're a strong boy.
K-Kaga-san, we should get going.
Oh, right.
I don't want to leave you, though.
I wish we were taking the same classes.
I'll see you later.
Let's stay together during breaks.
Let's eat lunch together, too.
Let's stay together after school, too-
Just go! You're an eyesore for singles!
What's "OMG"?
Oh, My Guts are failing me?
Osha-Mambe Government?
So dumb.
I can't believe what I said at the party...
Have you seen Oka-chan since then?
No...
But if I do, I intend to interact with her normally.
Ah! Good morning, everyone.
I CAN'T DO IT!
I was just going to say that I'm free first period today.
He didn't need to run away.
If he keeps acting like that, I don't know what I'll do.
Yeah...
Well, yeah...
I don't count what happened the other day as a confession.
It happened at a party.
But if he runs away from me like that...
Banri.
Banri!
Several days passed.
Kaga-san and I went to and from classes together
and remained together at college.
Sometimes we even went on dates.
Linda-senpai texted me nearly every day...
...but I never replied.
Coming, coming!
Did you finish cleaning up?
Yeah, sorry to make you wait.
Excuse the intrusion.
Have a seat.
I'll make some coffee.
Maybe I'll make myself at home, then.
Go ahead.
There.
It's so heavy.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Huh? Oh, sure.
It's not a problem!
What's inside?
Just vegetables my parents sent over.
I see.
Why don't we sit over there?
I'm fine here.
I see...
Maybe I should have brought some snacks.
I found a store by the station with nice-looking sweets.
Are you talking about the Bamboo Palace?
Wow, that's amazing!
Tada-kun, how do you know what I'm thinking?
Well...
I need to understand you better, too.
I bet you have potatoes in here!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, right.
There's something else I want to ask you.
Wh-what?
Did something happen between you and Linda-senpai?
Tada-kun, are you okay?
Yeah.
Why are you asking about Linda-senpai?
You said so yourself the other day.
When I asked if something happened with Linda-senpai,
you said the answer was "yes."
Oh...
If it's difficult for you to tell me,
I wasn't planning on asking,
but I'm curious...
Well...
Things were awkward between you and me that day, remember?
Linda-senpai was worried about us.
Oh...
But I guess I lashed out at her.
Things are awkward between us now.
I'll make up with her eventually.
Does that explain things?
Yeah.
Got it.
So, are these potatoes?
I-it's not what you think!
Y-you're right.
It's normal to be interested in these things.
W-well, I am a guy...
But we've only just started dating.
We should let it happen naturally.
Naturally?
Naturally.
Yes...
...in Paris!
Paris?
Paris!
It's my dream.
The first time we're in that situation together,
it's going to be in Paris.
I see...
We'll spend that fateful night in Paris, the city of lovers...
Let's go buy a cake.
Okay.
How are we getting to Paris?
We can buy plane tickets.
Let's buy them! I want to buy them now!
The Eiffel Tower awaits us.
Eiffel, my Eiffel Tower...
Eiffel!
Oh, right.
When are we practicing with the festival club next?
Um... next Friday, I think.
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm getting on!
Damn it.
What's up with you?
You dating?
You're ignoring me?
Who was that?
She seemed kind of scary.
New Message
Linda-senpai
No
smoking
Yeah, magical girls are in right now!
A text?
New Message
Linda-senpai
Shouldn't you read it?
Nah, it's nothing.
What's wrong?
Nana-senpai...
Tada-kun, isn't your phone ringing?
Yeah.
I don't recognize the number.
This is Tada.
The realtor?
Yes.
The room next to yours has a leak.
Could you make sure your room hasn't flooded?
Seriously?
Okay, I'll head right there.
There's a leak at my apartment.
I need to go home.
I'll go with you.
You've got class.
I'll text you later.
Bye!
Nana-san?
You ignored me the other day.
Huh?
We met in the elevator.
You were with your girlfriend.
So that was...
Did you not notice we're neighbors?
Neighbors?
Yup.
I went to greet you a few times after I moved in,
but you never answered the door.
I thought that was just how Tokyo people were...
I'm originally from Warabi in Saitama.
Warabi?
So...
...is yours the room that flooded?
That was a lie.
I'm the one who called you.
I-it's not like that!
Nana-senpai forced me to...
I didn't know you lived here.
She...
If there's something you want to say, spit it out and get it over with!
I can't stand it when you're being indecisive!
Wait!
My shoes are still inside!
Would you like to come in?
She used to be in the festival club.
What?
After I joined, she became busy with her band and work, and she quit.
She kept hanging out with me, though.
Does Nana-san go to our school?
Yeah, she's a third year.
Also, her real name isn't Nana.
Right...
When I told her things were awkward between us,
she told me Tada Banri lived next door to her.
That's how...
So this is your apartment.
This is where you live, Banri...
Tada Banri...
I'm so sorry!
I only confused you more, doing things halfhearted like that...
Banri...
Why?
Why are you crying?
Are you all right?
Banri...
I'm glad I got to meet you again.
I'm really happy.
I was willing to give up everything.
I prayed to God to let you live.
You're alive. You're here.
That's all I want.
I won't ask for anything else.
Linda-senpai, I'm sorry!
What?
I didn't know what you were thinking.
I was afraid...
I ran...
I see... So this is how you found out.
Um...
What was our relationship like?
In high school, we were really close.
You were funny and kind.
You were a good guy.
But you were kind of unreliable.
Even though we're the same age,
I was like your older sister.
Things aren't any different now.
Now that you mention it...
Linda-senpai, the other day you said it was your fault.
What did you mean?
We were close friends.
That much is true,
but you said you wanted to be with me forever.
You confessed your feelings to me on the night of our graduation.
The next day, I was supposed to give you my answer on that bridge.
Then I was on that bridge because...
You were waiting for me.
But I was late.
I've been so afraid.
I thought, if I had been on time...
...maybe you wouldn't have fallen from the bridge.
I've caused you a lot of trouble,
but I just want to support you as your senior,
and as someone who knows about your accident.
If you don't mind, anyway.
Why would you do that for me?
Because you're Tada Banri!
Even if you don't remember,
you're important to me.
I enjoy spending time with you, Tada Banri.
Incoming Call
Kaga Kouko
Hello?
Tada-kun, how's the leak?
Oh, uh... It's fine.
The truth is, I'm having my own problem.
Huh?
In Call
Kaga Kouko
Mitsuo might be in trouble!
In one hand in the sweetened cafe latte I love
The moment I smiled I could smell love
I want to wear my cherry-colored dress perfectly
My heart beats quietly as I rush to see you
(Oh Sweets & Sweets Cherry)
Watch out for that sweet trap
Yes, I'll whisper to you
(Hey, I'm a little anxious)
Ah, I long for this
How should I smile when I see you?
Pretty love, pretty love
I love you so much
Under the sky, under sunshine
Let's hold hands
I can't be honest about my feelings
But pull me along by my hand
Reset
Um... I'm Sato Takaya, a.k.a. 2D-kun.
Tada-kun...
Kaga-san...
I've given up on the third dimension.
Tada-kun...
Inside my head, I have an original wife character.
Kaga-san...!
Tada-kun...!
These days, my favorite anime is...
Kaga-san!
Tada-kun!
You're so annoying!
Kaga-san!
You two are so annoying!
Tada-kun.
Kaga-san.
People happy in real life are so annoying!
Tada-kun.
Kaga-san.