I'm going to Tokyo!
I'm going to Tokyo.
I'll become a different Banri and start over.
Thank you.
Huh?
Thanks to you, I feel like I've suddenly become free.
Oh, okay.
That's great.
Let me do something to thank you.
I know!
If I see your friend at the hospital,
I'll give him a message.
A message?
I promise I'll tell him.
So, you shouldn't come here alone anymore.
It's dangerous.
Your signal will reach him eventually.
I'll make sure it does.
My signal...
It's too late for my signal to reach him.
I didn't make it in time...
Huh?
There's nothing...
...I can do anymore.
All I can think is that,
if I had made it in time, that wouldn't have happened to him.
What's wrong?
If I had made it in time...
I would have held his hand tight...
...and never let go!
Never!
Sorry...
I'm going now.
Hey, what's your message?
Tell him, "You can do it."
Oh...
I'm not supposed to say that kind of thing.
Again? Why do I keep having that dream?
What...
...did Linda say to me then?
Summer Has Come
Ah, if we could meet in a dream, could I say it?
Say, if sadness alone floats down from the sky
If that kind of voice pains you even now
Even if, off to the side, our hands are placed on each other's
This memory wouldn't fade, but...
Even if, when our eyes meet, I can't say the truth...
Your words illuminate the world more than anyone else's
Next to me, "Goodbye means I love you," you say
I can't be forthright
Though I alone sing of loneliness
I can't smile
"Thank you means I'm in love with you," you say
The world's end of love
The time came for our first event of summer vacation.
It's the Awa dance festival the festival club is participating in.
Other universities and Awa dance preservation societies are here, as well.
There they are.
It's so hot.
Wow, they look like girls!
You're right!
There are girls in our club!
Oh, shut up.
It's so hot... Fan...
It's so hot.
I'm amazed you guys can hang around here.
The building's air conditioned, and it feels great inside.
We let you use that space so you could change.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
Huh?
We're matching.
Yeah, that's right.
Today I'm a beautiful woman dressed as a man.
That's great!
You're so handsome!
Thanks.
I'm so handsome today.
Linda-senpai, you really do look better than me.
You can tell I'm not used to these clothes.
Don't worry. It's a battle of charm.
Anyway, your girlfriend's having a problem...
A problem?
Kouko...?
What a hunk of junk.
She's a modern day Yaoya Oshichi.
Note: Yaoya Oshichi was a woman who lived in the Edo period of Japan. In
an ill-advised attempt to get the attention of the man she was in love
with, she tried to set a building on fire, but was caught by police.
Note: (Cont'd) The joke here casts Kouko's decidedly humorous situation in
that of a classic tragic heroine.
Isn't this a job for her boyfriend?
Right.
What's wrong?
Get it together.
Banri...
What's wrong?
Is it heat stroke?
No, that's not it.
She had lots of energy until a minute ago.
Th-they're right.
I'm just n-nervous...
Wh-what?
I can't do it!
I'm going to the bathroom again!
Sh-she's walking funny...
Kouko!
Linda-senpai.
You're fine.
You've already been to the bathroom about thirty times.
N-now that you mention it, that's true...
Your bladder's empty.
There's nothing in there.
Listen to me. Calm down and think carefully.
Your urge to pee...
My urge to pee...
...is a phantom urge!
A phantom urge...
Linda-senpai!
There, there.
Oh, my...
Come on, over here.
We still have time.
Try to calm down, okay?
She's even more of a hunk of junk than I imagined.
Looks like she's out of oil.
Let's put on your lipstick, okay?
Come on, Roboko!
You can do it!
Fight!
It can't be helped.
Let's go.
Goodbye, Roboko.
I won't forget how funny you were.
Wait...
Adieu, Roboko-chan.
Hey...
We'll meet again.
No, no, no!
Don't give up!
You'd leave one of our own behind?
Guess we have no choice.
Kosshi-senpai, hasn't the time come to teach the first years about "that"?
"That," huh?
You're right.
We're going to do "that"?
Looks like we have no choice.
She's right.
It's our only hope.
Huh?
Wh-what do you mean?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Huh? What?
What's going on?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Ahoy, ahoy, ahoy, ahoy.
Together, now!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Banri!
N-no!
Someone help me!
Hey!
Come on!
Kouko!
Hey!
Roboko!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Stop!
I can't do it!
There's no way I can do that!
I can't!
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
All right!
Let's go to our first festival!
Yeah!
Good work, guys.
Good work, everyone!
You're dismissed for today.
There's a fireworks show later at the riverbank near here.
Feel free to attend.
All right!
Changing's too much trouble.
Let's go like this.
Let's at least change into sneakers.
Kouko, Tada Banri.
The next time we meet will be at camp.
Yeah.
Good work today.
Thank you for everything.
Linda-senpai was wonderful.
You danced well, too.
Yeah.
I'm a ghost again.
My feelings for Linda still remain in Banri's heart,
but...
STUPID LINDA
Baka Banri
Until now, I've thought of him as my younger twin.
Even if he didn't notice me,
I thought he respected the feelings
I had always nurtured.
But he abandoned me.
Kouko, have you been to a fireworks show before?
Yeah, I have.
Even though he still has feelings for Linda, he's forced himself to pretend there's nothing.
Really?
The booming explosions are amazing.
He rejected the feelings I had to leave behind in this world.
I'll curse you.
I'll become an evil spirit and make you unhappy.
Prepare yourself.
What is this?
It suddenly started raining!
We've gotta hurry up and find shelter!
Banri, I'm scared!
Canceled?
Yeah.
The seminar house we got for our camp is closed for repairs.
I see.
See you in September.
Later.
You've gotta be kidding.
It's been like this since summer vacation started.
The fireworks display was canceled,
I missed the film showing,
and Yana-san suddenly canceled our plans to hang out.
On top of that, it's so hot every day.
Guess who?
It's me!
Hey, my lover.
Were you surprised?
You were, weren't you?
Yes, I'm a surprising woman.
You took the stairs?
Yes, I sprinted up them.
Why?
So I could surprise you as you came to meet me.
You were surprised, weren't you?
And that's...
And that's the spice...
And that's the spice of love!
Because of that, I ended up like this.
It's okay.
I'll make you a curried yakisoba that's so delicious, it'll blow your pain away.
Huh?
Yakisoba?
I bought ingredients,
and I'm ready to go.
Look forward to it.
Ta-da!
Great! That's great!
Seriously great!
It looks fantastic on you!
Come on, you're exaggerating.
I bet you wear that whenever you cook at home!
Huh?
Well... yeah, I do...
Are you serious?
You're so girly!
You really are a surprising girl!
I love it! Love it!
Well, then.
What should I do?
I'll help you with whatever!
You can't do that!
Wh-why not?
You don't have to help me!
I want to make it for you.
It's a girl thing, okay?
So please, just sit.
Oh...
Okay.
I thought I might need this.
I'm glad I brought it.
Huh?
Why do I have to wear this?
No reason. No reason at all.
Okay, put your hands here.
If you take them out, it's game over.
I'm kind of scared...
By the way, Banri, do you know about that man?
What man?
In a snowy village,
there's a middle-aged man living an ecological, healthy, and sustainable life with his mother.
And you see...
That man...
...is having sexual relations with a bird.
Sexual...
But that's not the important part.
What's important is the sad truth that the man is a peeping Tom.
What are you talking about?
The bird is chirping suspiciously... chirp, chirp, chirp...
and acting strangely behind the door.
The man can't contain his curiosity, and in the end, he commits the crime.
Because of that,
his strange but happy life with the bird comes to an end.
Are you talking about the Crane Wife?
Put simply, yes.
In other words... um... it means...
Don't watch you while you cook?
Right!
What a terrible storyteller...
In any case, you'll make me really nervous if you watch.
So stay right there.
Please! Please! Please!
Well, if you insist...
Good! Face the other way and don't move.
I'll do my very best.
My curried yakisoba will be delicious.
By the way, Banri, did you hear our trip was canceled?
Yeah, just now.
It's too bad, isn't it?
I thought we could reminisce about the time we got lost in those mountains.
I don't think that was such a fun memory.
Huh?
Well, camp or no camp, we'll always be together!
Time to wash some vegetables.
Time to cut some vegetables and meat.
Time to sauté some vegetables and meat.
Time to add the noodles.
Now I'll season them and quickly finish them off like I always do.
It's almost ready.
Look forward to-
K-Kouko?
It'll burn.
Were you watching?
This isn't what you think it is, Banri.
What is it, then?
A joke!
A joke?!
It's my best joke!
Air yakisoba!
Air yakisoba?!
Aren't you surprised?
Laugh, Banri!
Try laughing!
This is...
This is the spice...
This is the spice of love, too!
I really meant to make it myself, at first.
But while practicing at home,
I started getting nervous,
and I couldn't even hold a knife properly.
You're so weak under pressure.
So then our maid saw me and started making it herself.
Saying, "You're useless! Give me that!"
I'm amazed she called her employer's daughter "useless."
She has a foul mouth, but she's really nice.
She even lent me this apron.
Hey, can we talk a little more?
Maybe I'll attend a proper cooking school.
You don't need to do that.
Normal's fine.
Normal's not good enough.
I want to make you think, "She's awesome!
Her feminine charm is through the roof!"
This summer vacation,
maybe I'll throw myself into the culinary tiger's den and train.
Culinary tiger's den?
Maybe I'll do that...
and cancel my family vacation.
Barcelona, right?
A long vacation sounds nice.
But... Banri, you'll...
Don't worry about me.
Even if you spent the summer with me, you'd just be bored killing time.
I wish we could be together the whole time too, but...
Really?
Really.
Of course I do.
I see.
L-let's go.
Y-yeah.
Hey, Banri, you're forgetting something.
Sorry! Thanks.
"Don't go to Barcelona. Stay with me."
I can't tell her to do that.
You can't complain if she abandons you eventually.
Someday a better man will appear, and...
Goodbye, Banri.
Find someone who can make you some delicious curried yakisoba.
Kouko!
I'm not done yet.
I'll make you even unhappier.
What was that voice?
You're wrong, I'm telling you you're wrong
Ah, you still don't notice, huh?
Though I've wanted to touch that arm for the past two or three hours
I do not need forever love
I cannot believe forever love
The urge to scream is so great that, look, I can't stand it
So why, why won't you notice even a little?
Are you really, really in love with me?
I don't need words of flattery
Love me semi-eternally
After 5,000 years or so, I won't be interested
I'm not endless
I will die someday
Being told "I'll love you forever" won't make me happy
First, think only that
You'll love me till I die
Ladies Talk
Amazing!
That's amazing, Kouko!
I love your air yakisoba!
No! Stop! Forget about that!
Huh?
I want it to be our secret. It's a girl thing!
This is...! The spice...! Of love!
I see...