Well, of course, you only look up.
Wait a wee bit and pick up the ones on the ground.
Just looking up isn't enough...
Slowly, at my own pace...
If I put my heart into the work I do, and earnestly approach calligraphy...
...I should be able to find my style soon.
But...
"Demon Geezer 2: The Movie"
What is this movie about?
Was it popular enough to get a sequel?
All right, then.
Huh?
It broke...!
Now what?! Doesn't seem like there's a place to get computers repaired on this island.
Oh, that's right! Kawafuji!
Damn it...
It's been acting up since it fell into the ocean, but it must've finally broken!
No computer... No mobile... No home phone...
How am I supposed to contact anyone?!
"Shiman Ontsuandon"
"Translation: Men of the island"
It's been about a month since I came to the island.
Despite the slower lifestyle, the days here are surprisingly busy.
And there's a place that soothes my heart.
Here she comes!
Yes, this place is heaven for cat lovers!
So cute...
I want to pet them...
But this is someone's residence...
Come here... Come closer...
Shoo! Scram! You dirty cats!
How dare ya stick your paws in the fridge?!
Come now, no need to be so angry.
Anyone would be angry if they ate his sashimi for dinner!
Oh, Sensei, something the matter?
Ah, Sensei, you like cats too?
If you want ta see 'em, come down anytime.
What? Really?!
Before we knew it, them stray cats made this place their home.
W-Well then, if I could...
Come here, kitties!
I told ya, they're strays.
They don't get along with people.
Tell me that first next time...
What am I supposed to do with my spread arms...?
Why not have 'em eat this?
Stewed veggies left over from lunch.
Come here, Whites!
Wow! Look at all of them!
With my sashimi gone,
those lunch leftovers were supposed to be my dinner.
Wow... Look at all of them...
You named them all White?
Just callin' them how they look.
They are strays, y'know?
Most people would call them pets by now...
What about that striped cat there?
Come here, Black!
Not "Stripes"?
Black here's the friendliest of 'em all.
The other strays are bad, but this here's a good kitty.
"※Jikomon = Good/Well-Behaved"
Sensei? Do you want ta hold her?
What?! Really?!
I'll hold her! Please let me hold her!
Then...
Wha--?!
Hurry and take her!
I can't hold 'er much longer!
But how am I supposed to hold her?!
Just grab her hard with both of yer hands!
Okay!
I got her!
It's not bad at all. She's a cute kitty even if she is a stray.
See, I told ya to hold her good.
Oh, my, are you all right?
Sensei? You've got bumps around your neck.
Wha--?! What's this? Itchy!
My eyes! So itchy!
Sensei? You got cat allergies or somethin'?
Allergic to cats...?
Look, a cat!
No, Sei. Don't go near animals.
You don't want to get itchy, do you?
If you get itchy, I won't be able to bear it for you.
I guess I can't own cats...
Sure can't tell until you touch them...
Hello.
Grandma, can I use the phone...?
Hey, it's Sensei!
Why'd you come? To buy something?
You girls are all over the place...
Hey, Sensei, you've got bumps all over your neck.
Let's not talk about this...
Where's Grandma?
She's at an elders' meeting.
If you want something, feel free to look around.
Well, I just wanted to borrow the phone.
Sensei? You know Akki?
Akki?
Yup! Akki!
I'm Akki.
Akki's super! He's good at games, just like Takahashi Meijin!
Who's Takahashi?
Whaaat?!
"Only 1 hour a day for games"
You don't know Takahashi Meijin?
What?! Is that person famous?!
Is that person some Kyogen performer?
He's an expert gamer.
You said you wanted the phone?
Y-Yeah.
Akki...
I think I've seen him before...
You're Tama's younger brother!
Well, yes...
Wow, you two are alike!
Are you a clone or something?
Please stop. We don't look alike.
No, you do look like her. The power of genetics!
Never mind, just hurry and make your call.
Come on, no need to be--
Here.
Whoa, so black!
Well, it is a black rotary phone.
What is this? I've only seen these on TV before...
In an age of mobiles with camera and touch panel controls, these are still around...?
You got freaked!
I'll be playing games here, so please use it freely.
Um, okay...
I'm going to make an important call, so be quiet.
Let's see...
Zero...
What the heck? Pressing it isn't doing anything...
Is this broken?
Um... You're not supposed to press it...
You need to dial it.
I knew that! This phone's dial is just tight!
He blamed the phone...
Like this, right?
See? It spun!
Of course it spun.
You can take your finger off.
I knew that!
Before that, you need to pick up the receiver to make a call.
Please tell me the number, and I'll dial it for you.
If you're going to pity me, give me some money!
--Yeah, hello?
--Be quiet, I'm making a call.
Hey, Kawafuji.
Seems pretty lively down there.
What's up?
My computer broke, so I was hoping you could get me a new set.
I can't do my work without it.
Speaking of, Handa...
I'm thinking of having you take a break.
Huh? What do you mean?
There's a deadline for the
Narukain Exhibit this fall.
It's no time to be working, right?
I was trying to be attentive to you as a friend.
When's the date?
September 10.
"Naruka
Due September 10
Handa and Kanzaki
41st Narukain Exhibit"
Well, if you don't feel like it, you can let it slide.
Take your time thinking about--
Send me the calligraphy tools I'm about to list.
I can expect you to take first this time, right?
Who knows?
I'm still in darkness...
...but one day, I'll find the light. I promise.
So, how much does it cost per minute to use the phone?
I'm still in darkness.
One day, I'll find the light.
Was what I said that bad?
In middle school, you must have said you had something sealed in your left arm.
That doesn't matter!
I spoke for about five minutes, so is fifty yen okay?
Using the phone is a flat ten yen.
Huh? Is that it?
Grandma says it's free, but everyone leaves ten yen behind.
Then, here, ten yen.
And this should be forty yen.
--Naru.
--Yay!
You too, Hina.
Sorry about that.
And here, Akki.
Thank you very much.
Lookie!
I made one huge bubble!
Hey, don't hold it with your hand! That's dirty!
Hina! What are you doing?!
They said you were a calligrapher, so I thought you would be more formal.
Sure can't tell until you meet them...
Like everyone said, you are a strange person.
A strange person?
Can I come over to your place next time?
Does that mean you and your sister are going to ransack the house?
--Go ahead!
--Why are you answering?!
Damn it... This isn't working!
I don't feel like writing...
Maybe it's because I stopped work to concentrate on the exhibit...
For one piece of calligraphy, the burden is heavier than usual...
I need a change of pace to write one up, or else the deadline...
The hell ya doin' there?!
Ya went and spilled my pickin's!
I'm sorry! I was just thinking...
Thinking...?!
Ya think that's a good reason for me ta let ya go?!
Well?!
It's a yakuza!
I haven't seen ya 'round these parts before...
I recently moved here...
You're the calligraphy sensei!
Y-Yes...
So you're the strange one
I've been hearin' 'bout!
Strange person...
So, I got a request I wanted ta make to ya, Sensei.
Ah, where are we going?!
Don't worry! Don't worry!
Forgot my bike.
Agh, I got caught by one
A-ranked annoying old man!
So, Sensei, go ahead and do yer stuff!
Go and write yer heart out!
I guess you ran out of luck being caught by my dad!
After I spoke about you, he was enthused to have you write the ship's name.
So that's your dad...
I give up already...
I can't wait...
Doesn't feel like I have a chance to make a mistake...
Dad's pretty scary when he gets mad...
What's the name of the ship?
By custom, is it "Miwamaru"?
A guy running a saké store bought the ship as a pastime...
...so I'm not letting him use my name.
"Small Vessel Registration Examination Form
Vessel Name: Yuigadokusonmaru
Vessel Owner: Yamamura Iwao"
He's got weird taste.
I'm so glad Mom named me...
What's "Yuigadokuson"?
Hah! It means that I'm a god!
--I'm so embarrassed...
--Like father, like daughter...
Five kanji characters...
That's quite a lot.
The ship's body is curved, so it's hard to scale.
The tools are different from the ones I use too...
Even without the pressure from Pops, I can't fail here...
Look, paint!
Ta-da!
Bam!
The paint's gonna melt your hands.
Wash 'em...!
I need a draft, so I'll go back home and write one.
What?!
"Yuigadokusonmaru"
First, I'll cut out the words I wrote.
Then I'll paint over them, and...
Hold it there, Sensei!
That ain't different from a ship's sheet metal tracin'!
I want my own original ship!
Even if you want that, the tools aren't what I usually use.
Plus I'm writing on something other than paper.
If you want a proper ship, you should ask a specialist...
What?! So what yer tellin' me...
...is you can't do it, and want me ta drive an ugly mass-produced ship?!
That's not it! If I make a mistake, that'll make it look worse!
You gonna make a mistake, Sensei?
Well, no, but there's always a slight chance.
If it's just a slight chance, then no worries!
Just hurry up and write!
Like I said...!
Are pros supposed ta refuse work?
I'll decide what's ugly or not!
I'd rather have Naru do the writin' than sail this ship with a slapped-on printout!
Why, you...!
Okay! Hold it right there!
I'm here with a lifeboat to save this sinking ship! Get it?
Dad, it's time for the saké deliveries.
Sensei, go ahead and write what you want.
The heck are you sayin'?!
What I want?!
--Whaddya mean, "what he wants"?!
--Just like usual!
C'mon, you're a saké store owner, so do that job.
What does she mean, "usual"?!
That yakuza of a father got me completely cornered!
But I'm not the type to go cowering after being told all that!
I'm going to make him weep with gratitude!
But first, I've got to get used to using this brush.
Sensei! I can't get all the paint off!
My hand is gonna melt!
Don't worry. Your hands aren't going to melt.
Anyways, is there anything
I can use to draft on?
Sensei! There's a lot of boards here!
This should be enough to do some drafts!
Thanks, um...
Yay!
What were their names?
Hey! It goes on pretty smoothly!
Naru wants to write too!
I'm working here.
Jackal Cyclone!
I'm finally getting used to using this brush.
"Stomach Wrap Frankenstein"
But I guess I can't hold in what's on my mind...
"Yakuza Father Demon"
I feel like I'm writing well now.
"Yuigadokusonmaru (lol) Yakuza"
"Demon Geezer Phantom Yakuza"
Here I go!
Wait! I didn't take the curve of the ship into consideration!
No! If I do it now... I'll fail!
That was close!
But my neck...! That was close, but my neck hurts!
I forgot to check the ship's body!
I almost failed there! Damn it!
All right... This spot should do it...
--Don't push me!
--Not gonna do anything.
Damn it! Why can't I do this?!
After all those drafts...
Brush or not, just writing on the white surface is scary...
Am I going to mess this up...?
Agh! This isn't going to do!
You okay, Sensei?
You better hurry, or Miwa-nee's gonna come.
Shut up! You're distracting me! Go away!
Damn it, I don't want to...! So scary...!
--He said, "don't want to"?
--Yup.
Calm down... Calm down...
I've faced pressure like this before.
I prefer to take my time, but no matter the circumstances, I've always delivered the best.
This is just like that...
Wha--?!
I got first dibs!
Okay! I'm gonna do it too!
--Me too!
What the hell are you doing?!
You brats! Brats! Brats!!
Look at what you've done! It's all dirty!
Well, Sensei said "don't want to"...
That's not what I meant!
Anyways, I have to cover the handprints...
Eew! It splattered all over!
Just hold on! It's the same for me too!
If I don't do it this hard,
I can't cover up the handprints!
Naru! Fill the bowl with paint.
Okay!
Hina, your clothes are going to get dirty, so step back.
Aww...
Kenta, put paper on any spots where it looks like ink will drip.
Got it!
This is so weird...
After all that fear...
...I can't feel the pressure, and even the brush runs smooth.
And all it took... was a small handprint.
Hurry and hold it! I need more paint!
Okay!
He's sure enjoyin' it.
He's always like that.
The Village Leader was sayin' he works with a smile.
I guess he was tellin' the truth.
Here, seaweed. It's for your work.
Um... This much...?
Isn't this what you just picked earlier?
How do you eat this?
Now that's some mighty good work you did there!
I'll call ya when I launch this baby, so you better come.
I can't believe he's that happy.
It's a good thing I asked ya, Sensei.
"Yuigadokusonmaru"
It's way more than what I wanted for my ship!
Isn't this great?
Naru's handprint is over there...
It's not often I can write on a ship, so this was a great experience for me.
I also found out that I can ease myself thinking I'm dirtying white paper.
Thank you so much for letting me handle this!
Same here. Thank ya!
Well, that aside...
Seems like ya had a lot ya wanted ta say 'bout me...
Huh?! Why, all of a sudden...
"Demon Geezer Phantom Yakuza"
"Yuigadokusonmaru (lol) Yakuza"
"Yakuza Father Demon"
"Stomach Wrap Frankenstein"
Well, that's...!
Whoops, Sensei!
Plus, I use them planks for gettin' from the ship ta the port.
Whatcha gonna do 'bout this?!
I●●● I●●●
I'm so sorry...!
Hey! He's running!
What a grown-up!
He's even dropping the seaweed!
Sensei! Seaweed!
--Seaweed!
Sensei!
Look at the trash...
Yeah, some of 'em who come to fish dumped it here.
Keep warnin' 'em, but they don't listen.
Why not put up a sign with a spin on it?
"The trash you dumped spells doom for the Earth."
Too large-scale. Doesn't seem realistic.
"Don't throw trash, you trash."
That'll only make the reader angry.
"You'll die if you dump here."
Low quality.
Then you think of one!
"If you dump here, a part of you that you can't show others will ooze pus."
Dirty!
"Throwing trash here will make
all the crayfish go away."