"August"
"September"
"Narukain deadline"
Just two more weeks...
The more I hurry, the harder it is to write something good...
You know...
Since coming to this island, I sometimes get this urge to write calligraphy...
Something rises from inside me, and my hands start to shake.
If I can get that shake back in my hands...
Maybe I'll feel better if I take a bath.
Huh?
It doesn't click...
It's not turning on?
This can't be...!
What?! Why?! No!
"Okega Makucchishita"
"Translation: Was almost seriously injured"
Looks like it broke.
How long will it take for someone to come and fix it?
Let's see... Maybe about a week...
Figured as much...
That's right... While we're at it, you wanna try it out?
Huh?
Ta-da! A bath boiler.
You can heat the bath by burning firewood in here.
Does it work?
No problem! We use the boiler at our house too, and it's awesome!
Yeah, but... But what about the firewood? I don't have any.
There's a mountain right there, so it'll be okay.
The branches have to be dry, or else they won't burn.
It's no use... He's already in the groove.
I can't tell him this is a pain...
There's more over here!
I have to do this for a week?
Gross!
You...
I'm sorry, Village Leader!
This should be enough branches.
Sure hope you find a wife who'll keep the fire for you, Sensei.
More than a wife, I want a bath with a gas-powered water heater.
You're twenty-three years old already, Sensei.
Don't you have a girlfriend you're thinking of marrying?
I don't have anyone like that.
C'mon, now.
I've been writing calligraphy all this time, so... How can I word this?
I'm the type who would die alone.
Hmm...
He isn't denying what I said...
Well, you should be good to go.
What?!
Say, Miwa-chan?
Hm?
Isn't the smoke there coming from around Sensei's place?
Looks like it.
A bonfire?
You think Sensei would do that kind of thing?
This is...
...fire!!
It's just a bath.
Is that it? Sensei, you're such a troublemaker.
But if it's a bath, then it's okay.
Even Naru can do it.
You know how to use this?
Yup.
I'm always keepin' watch of the fire when Grandpa is takin' a bath.
"How's the water, sir?"
"Good, but put the fire out
if it gets outta hand"
Are you sure you're okay doing this?
Leave it to me. I'm used to this!
The prep is a pain, but it is exciting, like taking a dip in a hot spring.
Hot!
Sensei, was it too hot?!
No, I'm fine.
What a relief...
It's so relaxing...
I can feel the stress melting away. I can see why the Village Leader is so into this.
It was heated with all that effort, after all...
Sensei! We've got trouble!
What's the matter?!
Hold it.
Naru! Why are they here?!
They came here thinkin' it was a fire.
So, having a kid watch the fire while you take a leisurely bath?
As punishment, we'll take a look at you nude.
That makes no sense!
I bet ya want young gals to look at ya.
Don't treat me like a flasher!
There's no fire here, so get lost!
As usual, he doesn't go with the flow.
What's the camera for?
I was going to take some shots for reference material.
Reference...? Even in manga, nude's no good.
No problem. Just need to censor the tip...
--Only a little.
--I can't relax...
--Say, how 'bout we try this?
--Taking a bath in the afternoon isn't good.
--Huh? What?
--For now, I just need to wait for them to get bored, and leave...
You idiots! It's hot!
Run!
Was it hot, Sensei?
What do you think?! Look at how red I am!
--Run!
--Wait, you come back here!
In any case, I feel fresh and new again.
Now then, time to write...
Hey.
Hiro! Wh-What are you doing here?!
My mom's not home today, so I'll make lunch for you.
But why here...?
First, cut the cucumber.
"Sugar"
Add miso and sugar to your liking...
Then add the cut cucumbers, and mix them together lightly.
Cucumbers with miso are ready with these easy steps.
If it's that easy, I feel like I can make it too.
First, cut the cucumber!
Add miso and sugar, then mix!
--Ready!
--Sensei, did you see what I did?
What? It's the same, isn't it?
What's the same?!
It'll be the same eating it.
Looking bad yet tasting good is what a man's cooking is about.
No way. That's gotta taste bad...
Thanks for the meal.
Whoa! This is good!
Sensei... Yours tastes horrible...
How come I can only taste the cucumber?
Wait, this tastes bad after all.
Hey, wait! You said it tasted good just now!
I didn't say it tasted good.
It only tastes like miso.
Why are you acting so stubborn? So immature...
What do you mean, "immature"?!
Speaking to an elder like that!
Don't point your finger!
If you're supposed to be an elder, act like one!
Sensei!
What's the matter, Hina?! Is there a problem?
Get a grip! Moaning isn't going to help.
Don't rush her, Sensei.
Hina, take a drink and calm down.
She came running over here, so it's got to be an emergency. Spill it already!
Don't be so impatient over a kid's emergency.
Well, it's bothersome, you know?
And that's immature, too.
All right! Just calm down, Hina!
Please, we'll listen!
Naru...
Naru's being bullied by the big kids from the other village!
Over here!
Naru! Are you all right?!
Stop it...!
Oh, hey, that looks fun...
Naru--!
Hina--! Heeelp!
You brought back some adults?!
No fair!
Where'd you brats come from?
This is their playground!
Shut up, bozo fox!
This is our place now!
Bozo fox...?
Must be the brats from Rokunosaki Village.
It's a neighbor village we've been feuding with since my day.
Sensei! Get them outta here!
We were playin' here first!
O-Okay...
Hey! You visiting brats!
Why'd you call someone you've never met before "bozo fox"?!
How am I a fox? Sure, people say my eyes are unpleasant sometimes, but only sometimes.
Sensei's really taking this personal...
Shut up, ya wimpy bean sprout! Go away!
The pain... Why is my heart in pain...?
That brat's impressive.
He saw through Sensei as a loser and a wimp, even when they just met for the first time!
It's no use using strong words against brats like them.
--Hey, brats!
--A blondie?!
He's blond...
What?! Ya gonna try to scare us?!
You kids are older, so can ya let these young ones have the place?
C'mon, please?
Well, if ya really mean it...
...kneel.
Stop! Calm down, Hiro!
Lemme go! I'm gonna show 'em a thing or two!
"*innowasso = spiteful brat"
Ya freakin' stupid brats!
Run!
--You'll get into trouble if you seriously hit them...
--The adults are bein' violent!
--Sensei... Naru and everyone
--Yankee, go home!
--wanna play dodgeball here.
--Get outta here, outsiders!
Ah, well, we can't draw back now.
The kids are relying on me...
Now is the time to dignify myself...
Hey, kids.
Whaddya want, ya limp noodle?!
Limp... noodle...
We're adults, so we won't resort to violence.
But if you kids loiter any longer,
I'll need to make a call.
Whazzat? Who're ya plannin' to call?!
The police!
Why are ya pullin' the cops into this?!
I'm going to make an anonymous call that you kids are bullying other kids.
It'll be embarrassing being taken away, and your parents will be ashamed.
Your lives will be over.
Behold! Adult tactics!
Whoa... So immature...
Dang it! You an' yer dirty tricks...!
Take this!
How dare you deal the finishing blow to my mobile?!
Whaddya mean, "finishin' blow"?
You only got poop on it.
Screw you, brat! Look what you've done to my partner
that I've been using as a watch, even when I couldn't use it as a phone!
"Couldn't use it as a phone"?
Ya tricked us kids?!
What?! Being angry at me when you're the one who humiliated my mobile?!
Hiro. Were you laughing?
Nah, of course I wouldn't laugh...
What's that all 'bout?
Let's leave 'em be, and play ball.
Hey, Sensei! They're ignoring us!
Don't make me repeat myself! You kids go back to your village's playground...
Shut up!
Our playground's been taken over by middle schoolers!
By one super strong fightin' girl, and another with glasses.
It's got to be those two...
That's got nothin' to do with this!
Get outta...
Naru!
Hey! That's going too far!
What? Yer not gonna beat us, right?
If'n ya do, we're gonna tell our parents the adults here hit us.
If ya adults hit kids, then yer really gonna get it from the cops.
You guys're gonna be caught fer child abuse!
We can't have people saying that.
Yeah, adults should never hit children.
Naru? Those kids are saying that they're going to play baseball here.
Just let them play.
Been telling ya to get outta here!
Leave them to themselves.
We'll play some dodgeball...
Sounds good...
--Huh?
--Ya let us have this place!
You guys have fun playing baseball.
We'll just play among ourselves.
Me and Sensei are going to be outfield.
You guys run around.
W-Wait! This is our...
Ow!
Now that's our Sensei.
Going all-out even against kids.
It don't mean nothin' if it doesn't hit!
Klutz...
So, who's next?!
He hit it back...
Get a hold of yourself, Sensei!
If they get the ball, it's all over!
Dang it! You're supposed to be adults!
You're being too serious!
Supposed to be adults...?
You got it wrong...
It's because we are adults...
Eat this!
Sensei! Over here!
In this hot weather?
--It's Akki!
--Akki!
Whatcha doin' over here?
I can't clear the game I played the last time.
Hey, kids! This isn't over yet!
Well, we're good already.
We're gonna play with Akki.
What?!
Wait a minute! Is that it?!
I'm sorry to have interrupted your game there.
No, that wasn't what it was about...
See ya!
We'll come again!
Akki is...
...really mature.
Yeah...
Stop following me.
I'm going home already.
Aww... Let's play a little longer.
Stop pulling!
Got it! Tarzan! Let's play Tarzan!
--Tarzan?
--There's a place right down there!
It's super fun!
Oh, what the heck? But only for a little while.
Yay! C'mon, this way!
Um... I haven't seen a real Tarzan experience like this before...
--It's easy!
--It's not easy! That's just an ivy!
Naru's gonna show ya how it's done!
Stop it! It's dangerous!
Hey!
Like... this...
What should I do...? It doesn't look fun at all.
Here. It's your turn next, Sensei!
--Heck, no!
--How come? It's fun.
Lame! You're supposed to be an adult!
Let's see you say the same once you grow to the size of an adult.
There's no way this can hold the weight of an adult.
But if it can support all of you, then things are different.
Ah, dang it! I'm sorry!
Then yer gonna do it, Sensei?
Sure, whatever. Just don't do anything dangerous in front of me.
Yay! This is gonna be super fun!
You're probably trying to convey the fun to me, but I'm not feeling it at all...
They're gonna get hurt one of these days with this here.
Too bad for the kids, but I need to get rid of dangerous playthings...
You're gonna do it!
I'll fake my jump, and break this off!
--Stop it!
--Stop it, Sensei! You're pullin' it too much!
--It's gonna break!
--Stop it! Don't do it!
Everyone... stop!
Are you kids all right?
Yup! I'm okay!
That was super scary...
thought I was gonna die,
Thought I was gonna die,
thought I was gonna die!
Sensei! You're bleeding!
Are you okay?!
I'm fine... It's just a graze.
Now's the time to use mugwort!
--Look for them mugworts!
--Don't worry. It's not that bad...
Naru! Mugwort!
This herb's gonna stop the bleeding!
It's only a scratch...
That's just going to infect me with germs...
This way's the shortcut home!
Today was another day wasted in vain...
I'm not gaining much from playing with the kids every day.
Is it okay for me to just wait for the moment when I get the urge to write?
Time is closing in on me fast... Real fast...
It's here... It's really here!
The god of calligraphy is upon me!
I can't believe it was so easy to find something I want to write about!
I've got to hurry back and write!
Now I can write...
What's the matter, Naru?
Sensei's not behind us.
Maybe he went back another way by himself.
You think?
Yup! Sensei's always like that!
--Really?
--Yup!
Huh?! Sensei's not home?!
No one was here when we came.
Sensei disappeared when we were comin' back from the mountains.
Disappeared?
Ya know what?
Maybe he got trapped by the monster in the mountains, and is being munched on right now.
Not that there are any monsters, but I am worried that he's not home yet.
Even if he's lost in the mountains, it's not like it's a dense forest.
Good!
A rabbit? Stop freaking me out...
And just when I felt like I could write a great piece of calligraphy...
The time I spent playing with the kids just a while back
already feels like a thing of the past.
This isn't good! Panic is making my brain fabricate memories.
Stay calm... Stay calm...
I just need to go up a little more, and I'll be back on track.
Do your best, Seishu! Do your best, Seishu!
All right!
Ouch... This can't be...
Stop already!
Damn it... Help should be here by now.
Where is everyone?!
"Typical earthquake survival pose"
Being stranded in the mountains is the pinnacle of solitude.
I'm going to die...
I'm really, literally going to "die alone"...
Someone help me... Anyone...!
What's that?
It's just a key...
It's the key to the house.
A spare key... I lost it... Maybe it was when I was playing in the mountains...
Why, that...
This is so stupid! Why am I losing my cool in the mountains in my backyard?
No one gets stranded near their home.
What's this?
Wow... Is this outer space?
Hey, a shooting star!
Please let my bath be fixed... Please let my bath be fixed... Please let my bath be fixed...!
Wait... That's not right.
Please let me go back home so that I can write calligraphy...
See? I knew he fell.
No wonder we couldn't find him on the path.
Sensei... I'm so glad you're safe...!
Dang it... That took too long.
Is Sensei crying?
Sure is...
Great, it's here!
Sensei? Here's the first-aid kit...
It's really here!
Looks like you're busy...
"Seishu Handa"
"Stars"
Inspiration is important after all.
Yeah... I see...
Yeah, I got it.
I'll return.