These are exams we each take separately,
and yet we still feel like we're entering the same arena as many others:
those we fight beside,
those we fight against,
and the onlookers who cheer and jeer.
This is almost like...
We are assassins.
But right now we're also gladiators.
Today, the bell signals the start of a battle.
Tests are a good thing.
The knowledge gained from a night of cramming
will be all but forgotten once you hit adulthood.
And that's fine.
The experience you gain through competition,
having sharpened your skills and broadened your minds
all under the same set of rules...
That is the real treasure.
So fast!
It's so much tougher than midterms!
At a combined junior-senior high prep school,
it's not unusual for junior-high students to start
learning at a high-school level during third year.
The fastest-paced subjects at our school are English, math, and science.
But the same conditions apply to us all.
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
potential takai
We've got a lot of potential
hodo mendokusai
It's just that we're not trying
dropout mentality
We had that dropouts' mentality
hinichijou wo ryougashi
No matter the unusual situation we were in
bokura wa utatatanegao shite
We pretended to doze off
knife kakushimotta
While holding on to a hidden knife
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
doko ka taningoto datta
We didn't really feel invested in the job
dakedo
But now
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Our chances soar each time we challenge you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
revolution
A revolution!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
Episode
School's
Out
Time
1st
Term
So this is the last problem?
Those scrubs!
I spent a year in Los Angeles
when my folks worked there.
There's no way any junior-high level stuff
will trip me up now!
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
If you want to know the truth,
I felt like slapping the cook's face
a hundred times.
It's not going down? What the...
That was a textbook answer!
A little stiff, don't you think?
Don't try so hard, Honor Roll!
Honestly, I wanted to give
that cook a hundred slaps in the face.
A perfect score? From the E Class?!
I'm guessing you never read
Salinger's "The Catcher in the Rye."
Leave it to a fine school to
come up with some fine questions.
The questions cite famous literature.
They'll want the scoring standard to include how much a student reads and how adaptable she can be.
They'll probably lose points if they don't answer in the same rough and concise colloquial style as the source text.
Honestly, I wanted to give
that cook a hundred slaps in the face.
I did it!
Damn! Our English teacher only mentioned that novel in passing in the middle of class!
I guess you didn't have many
friends overseas, eh, Seo-kun?
Like an octopus who practically
pushed books onto you?
I've always admired this kind of subtle rebellion.
You simply must read it in both languages.
It ought to strike a real chord with you at your age.
Dammit!
Ha! Science is all about memorization!
Huh? I can't get its armor off!
But I know I memorized this!
Well, you see...
Got it!
Real science isn't any fun if it's just memorization.
Science absolutely loves when you tell it—
in words, mind you—
that you know what it is.
Even in science, you need language skills
to reach other people.
I understand that now, Korosensei!
Now I've done it!
How am I supposed to know
how many times the Tokyo International Conference on African Development has met?!
That was close.
Good thing I studied that.
Isogai, you little...
Just a fluke.
See, my family's pretty poor,
and when I looked it up out of sympathy for Africa's poverty issues...
No time like the present!
Whaaat?!
Being taken to the actual location
only made me that much more interested.
"Spring has passed and summer come, it would seem—
from those white hemp robes laid to dry in the sunlight
on Kagu's Heavenly Hill."
Your words are as lovely as your face.
But a mere sliver of a satisfactory answer does not an aced exam make.
First Term Final: Math
Math, eh?
Akabane's in the E Class?
He came in second on the midterms, after me.
Quite the showing for an E-Class student.
However...
I have no blind spots—not in math nor any other subject.
Aw...
Everyone's in such a tizzy.
That's not what winning is all about.
Total victory is scoring an easy win by doing what you always do.
He'll be my sacrifice to the proper way of winning.
That'll show 'em.
Two days of exams.
Assassination, our wager—
everything was riding on how many circles for correct answers we got.
Well, class,
your scores in all subjects have arrived.
Here goes.
Starting with English:
First in the E Class,
and first in the whole year level:
Nakamura Rio!
E
Nakamura Rio
100 in English
1st in Year 3
Nakamura Rio
100 in English
1st in Year 3
How's that?
What?!
A
Seo Tomoya
95 in English
3rd in Year 3
Seo Tomoya
95 in English
3rd in Year 3
Perfect.
Though your motivation did have a touch of whimsy that worried me.
Well, there's ten billion yen on the line, you know?
Don't forget about that tentacle now, Korosensei.
I won't.
Nagisa-kun, you put up a good fight,
but you haven't kicked your habit of making spelling mistakes when it really counts.
E
Shiota Nagisa
91 in English
6th in Year 3
Shiota Nagisa
91 in English
6th in Year 3
Still, top marks in a subject means that's one tentacle down.
Let's wait until I've read all the scores before we celebrate, though.
Next up is Japanese:
First in the E Class...
Kanzaki Yukiko!
However!
First in the year level goes to Asano Gakushuu of the A Class!
A
Asano Gakushuu
100 in Japanese
1st in Year 3
Asano Gakushuu
100 in Japanese
1st in Year 3
E
Kanzaki Yukiko
96 in Japanese
2nd in Year 3
Kanzaki Yukiko
96 in Japanese
2nd in Year 3
Kanzaki-san, you improved tremendously.
And that's all that matters.
Asano can really nab those points.
He's crazy tough.
Nakamura only beat him in English by a single point.
He isn't top of the nation for nothing.
No weaknesses—not in any subject.
They're collectively known as the Big Five...
A
Sakakibara Ren
94 in Japanese
3rd in Year 3
Sakakibara Ren
94 in Japanese
3rd in Year 3
...but it really comes down to Asano.
You've got to take him down,
or you'll never get to the top.
Let's move on.
In social studies, first in the E Class goes to Isogai Yuuma-kun.
And as for first in the year level...
Congratulations!
You beat out Asano-kun to take the top spot!
Yes!
E
Isogai Yuuma
97 in Social Studies
1st in Year 3
Isogai Yuuma
97 in Social Studies
1st in Year 3
A
Asano Gakushuu
95 in Social Studies
2nd in Year 3
Asano Gakushuu
95 in Social Studies
2nd in Year 3
An excellent job, especially considering all the fiendish questions you had to deal with!
A
Araki Teppei
93 in Social Studies
3rd in Year 3
Araki Teppei
93 in Social Studies
3rd in Year 3
We're 2 to 1!
Next up is science...
Is it Okuda?
First in the E Class for science is Okuda Manami!
And...
Marvelous!
First in the year level is also Okuda Manami!
E
Okuda Manami
98 in Science
1st in Year 3
Okuda Manami
98 in Science
1st in Year 3
That's 3 to 1!
We don't even have to hear how math turned out!
A
Koyama Natsuhiko
95 in Science
2nd in Year 3
Koyama Natsuhiko
95 in Science
2nd in Year 3
We've already won!
Hooray!
Great work, Okuda!
That tentacle is yours!
And so is what we're asking for in this little deal!
I can't wait!
So that just leaves math.
A
Asano Gakushuu
100 in Math
1st in Year 3
Asano Gakushuu
100 in Math
1st in Year 3
We're 3 to 2 over all five subjects.
We lost to the E Class.
What could be more humiliating?
But it still worked out, Koyama.
I mean, we beat them on total scores.
Hmph.
I got my own back against the guy who stole fourth place from me.
But that guy...
He dug his own grave!
E
Akabane Karma
85 in Math
10th in Year 3
Akabane Karma
85 in Math
10th in Year 3
E
Total Score: 469
13th in Year 3
Didn't even bother to compete, the scrub.
The A Class is mighty indeed.
They monopolize the top six ranks in overall scores for five subjects.
The best overall scores in the E Class
E
Takebayashi Koutarou
7th in Year 3
E
Kataoka Megu
7th in Year 3
were Kataoka-san's and Takebayashi-kun's, both tied for 7th place.
That's to be expected.
Everyone in the A Class studied like mad, too.
The tests' difficulty levels had been greatly increased.
No lazy student could be expected to keep up.
What are you trying to say?
You thought, "I'm so cool I'll ace these exams, no sweat"?
How mortifying!
A
Total Score: 491
1st in Year 3
Congratulations on retaining your top rank in total score.
Or so I'd say...
if it weren't for a certain wager you made with the E Class.
A wager that you lost.
The entire school knows all about your little bet.
You'll have a tough time refusing the E Class's request now.
So what will you do?
Would you like the school to save you?
No, thank you.
I believe you said you'd put a collar on me and keep me as a pet,
or attempt to expose my nonexistent secrets.
You certainly talk big for a whelp
who can't even win a bet with his peers.
Three students have the right
to destroy one of my tentacles:
Nakamura-san, Isogai-kun, and Okuda-san.
You contributed nothing—not to this assassination and not to this wager.
Is that understood?
Those who can't do what they have to
when the time comes for action
will find their presence fading in our classroom.
An assassin who neglects to sharpen his blade is no assassin at all.
He's just a boastful brat swinging around a rusty sword.
Wasn't that a little much?
Don't worry.
I only cut him down because he'll spring back up.
He has been gifted with much talent.
But those so talented often lack experience.
There's the danger of training him up without knowing real competition,
since he can keep on winning without ever really trying.
If great talent knows the frustration of defeat early on,
it can become even greater.
Exams are an opportunity to correctly teach the meaning of winning and losing, and of strength and weakness.
Soak up stacked servings of successes and setbacks, my students!
Take in now what it means to win and what it means to lose!
It's just so important... and I didn't realize it until the very end.
All right, class,
you had a fine showing in the finals,
taking the top spot in three out of five subjects.
Shall we get started with the assassination?
The top three can choose any tentacle they like.
I can lose three, no problem.
Six, now that would have been rough.
Whoa there, octopus!
We got more than three in the top spot!
No, there are three, Terasaka-kun.
Out of Japanese, English,
social studies, science, and math—
Huh? Quit playin' dumb!
Five subjects: that's Japanese, English, social studies, science,
and home ec!
H-Home ec?!
Nobody said what subjects we had to ace!
E
Terasaka Ryouma, Yoshida Taisei,
Muramatsu Takuya, Hazama Kirara
100 in Home Ec
1st in Year 3
Terasaka Ryouma, Yoshida Taisei,
Muramatsu Takuya, Hazama Kirara
100 in Home Ec
1st in Year 3
Good thing we all had a hand in this scheme.
W-Wait a second! Home ec is just—
Just what?
Isn't that a little rude, Korosensei?
Why, home ec is the toughest subject of them all.
Yeah! Don't break your promise!
Four of us scored highest in the most important subject: home ec!
That's seven tentacles in all!
Seven?! Eeek!
Sev-en! Sev-en! Sev-en!
Oh, and Korosensei, we've been talking...
We'll use our prize from the A Class wager to help with this assassination.
What?
The end-of-term ceremony came
hot on the heels of our final exams.
But there was one thing left for us to do.
Aw, yeah, here he comes.
Our oh-so-great student council president.
What do you want?
I'm too busy with the ceremony
to deal with the likes of the E Class.
Not so fast! Aren't you forgettin' something?
We had a bet, Asano, where the winner could make any one demand.
We sent our demand via email.
I trust you have no complaints?
Don't even try pretendin' it was all just a joke!
We could always throw home ec into those five subjects.
'Course, we'd still win!
You sure got the wool pulled over your eyes.
By those punks, no less.
Yes, though their argument was rather tenuous.
But I'm glad.
Since home ec isn't on any of the entrance exams,
Main Campus Home Ec Teacher
Yasui Naomichi
(Prefers olive oil)
Main Campus Home Ec Teacher
Yasui Naomichi
(Prefers olive oil)
Main Campus Home Ec Teacher
Yasui Naomichi
(Prefers olive oil)
And now, for the crowning touch: olive oil!
it's not considered important,
so there's a tendency for home ec teachers
to put whatever questions they like on the exam.
Don't skimp on the sesame oil!
E-Class Home Ec Teacher
Korosensei
(Prefers sesame oil)
E-Class Home Ec Teacher
Korosensei
(Prefers sesame oil)
E-Class Home Ec Teacher
Korosensei
(Prefers sesame oil)
That puts the E Class at an overwhelming disadvantage,
Really pour it on!
since I'm their only teacher.
They must have done some serious research into past testing trends—
all to get the better of me.
With their creative thinking in finding a loophole and the power to focus on attacking it,
I'd say they fit perfectly in my classroom.
By the way...
Why did we have to stay behind?
Karasuma-sensei told us not to come to the closing ceremony.
Because you're an octopus!
Because you're a bitch!
Karma!
Since when do you attend all-school assemblies?
If I skip now, it'll look like I'm running away.
No thanks.
Storehouse Beach!
Storehouse—huh?
Karasuma-sensei!
The fake Ritsu is too distracting! I can't concentrate!
Suck it up. This is to keep Ritsu
from being exposed as a machine.
She's my immediate supervisor's daughter—
tight-lipped and knows better than to pry.
And my supervisor's glad that
Ritsu's tutoring got her grades up.
She's been next to me ever since exams.
My concentration took such a hit I wound up last in class!
E
Sugaya Sousuke
Total Score: 338
95th of 186 in Year 3
Sugaya Sousuke
Total Score: 338
95th of 186 in Year 3
Last in class? That's still around the middle of the year level.
He's come a long way from the very, very bottom.
Now, it may be summer vacation, but don't slack off.
Er, uh...
You don't want to wind up like the E Class, you know...
Even his usual E Class insults are bombing.
All because the End Class vied for the top spot.
Korosensei may not have been with us today,
but we stood with our heads held high.
The final exams made all the students more aware of their performance.
Feeling humiliated and threatened by the E Class,
they'll be driven to strive even harder.
Even at this unusual time,
when Earth's existence hangs in the balance,
my educational principles are functioning flawlessly.
But that will only be possible as long as we have a true End Class.
Measures must be taken while school is out for the summer.
Summer Vacation Guidebook
One for each of you.
Again with the ridiculous guidebooks!
It's like an accordion!
And even this isn't enough.
The temptations of summer
are simply too many to mention.
Now, then...
We're about to head into summer vacation,
but you have a certain main event coming up.
Yeah, the hard-won fruits of our wager!
It's a privilege normally reserved for the class with the best grades—that is, the A Class.
But this time, both the A and E Classes dominated the top fifty.
You more than qualify.
Summer vacation!
The Kunugigaoka Junior High Special Summer Course:
three days and two nights at an Okinawa resort!
Yahoo!
Let 'em have that lousy old domestic trip.
Some Big Five you are, choking when it matters most!
What a joke!
The only winner you've got is Asano-kun!
Will you shut up?
A beaten dog has no business barking.
Sit and stay until I tug your leash.
You'll all pay for this.
My father will, of course, but before that...
I'm coming for you, E Class.
Is that what you'd like to do, then?
Yes. We'll cash in our tentacle-destroying rights
during summer camp.
Seven tentacles is a big handicap. But don't stop there!
Come after me with raw hunger on this island,
surrounded on all sides by water—my weakness!
Let me be honest: you've become formidable students indeed.
I've already given you report cards
to show your parents.
These are my report cards for you.
A classroom of double circles:
we've earned high marks from our target over these past three months.
As you make full use of the basics you learned in the first term,
this summer vacation will be time for plenty of fun, plenty of studying—
and, of course, plenty of killing.
Class 3-E, Kunugigaoka Junior High: the assassination classroom!
Our first term, the fundamentals, is hereby over!
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte