Our assassination plan went so well
that Korosensei wound up in his Absolute Defense Form.
Then all this happened.
We can't rely on Korosensei for help.
We have to steal the remedy from the bad guys... alone.
Not counting the ten patients and the two left behind to care for them,
all capable students must sneak in from here,
get the jump on the guys at the top,
and steal that remedy!
It's too dangerous.
The ease with which he threatened us shows we're up against a real pro.
Yes. Perhaps it would be wisest simply to hand me over.
What do you think?
It's up to all of you.
But... This is...
It's too hard.
They'll plummet to their deaths before they get anywhere near the hotel.
I knew it. It's no use.
We have to send him with those two.
Nagisa-kun, Kayano-san.
I'm sorry, but—
Well, if you're worried about the rock climbing,
that much is a piece of cake.
It's nothing compared to our usual training.
Right?
But we haven't practiced fighting an unknown foe in an unknown hotel,
so, Karasuma-sensei...
It won't be easy, but could you lead our mission?
We'll make that jerk pay for messin' with us!
As you can see, they're no ordinary students.
You have a fifteen-member special forces unit at your command.
Fifteen?
Don't forget about me!
Now, there's not much time.
Attention!
Our objective is the top floor of the hotel at the summit!
Our mission will shift from a stealth infiltration to a surprise attack!
We'll use the same hand signals and link-ups from training!
The only difference is our target!
You have three minutes to memorize the map.
We begin at 2150!
Right!
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
We've got a lot of potential
potential takai
It's just that we're not trying
hodo mendokusai
We had that dropouts' mentality
dropout mentality
No matter the unusual situation we were in
hinichijou wo ryougashi
We pretended to doze off
bokura wa utatanegao shite
While holding on to a hidden knife
knife kakushimotta
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
We didn't really feel invested in the job
doko ka taningoto datta
But now
dakedo
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
As long as we challenge you, it's fifty-fifty
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu kagiri kanousei wa half and half
kiritsu rei lock on
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
A revolution!
revolution
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
Episode
Pandemonium
Time
Fifty... minutes left...
Don't get left behind!
Okano sure can move.
Yeah. She's got the rest of us beat when it comes to gymnastics.
On the other hand, with our teachers...
One guy has to carry the rest. Literally.
Too shaky! Climb more carefully! Ugh!
Karasuma!
The students all have exceptional balance.
I have them climb the mountain behind the school.
I see. No wonder they had those flyboards down pat.
Shut up and climb already!
My hands are getting tired!
Why did Bitch-sensei come again?
She didn't want to be left out.
I wouldn't mind... if she wasn't such a dead weight.
Karma-kun, wait!
I'd like to, but we're kind of on a schedule here.
You're right.
Let's do this!
Mind the sharp rock.
Huh?
Oh, that was close.
Make it snappy!
What, are those biceps just for show?
Still...
If this guy knows about Korosensei, who could he be?
Ritsu, run a final check of our invasion route.
Yes, sir. Displaying interior map.
Final check:
We can't use the elevators, as they require a passcard for every floor.
We'll have to take the stairs,
but they're scattered throughout the hotel,
so we'll have to cover some distance on foot.
It's like a TV station.
What do you mean?
Apparently they have complex layouts to prevent a terrorist takeover.
You sure know a lot about it.
No wonder the bad guys love staying here.
Unlocking side entrance.
Let's go. We're running out of time.
Yes, sir!
There are more guards than I expected.
It'd be too difficult for us all to get past.
Should only a few of us go on from here?
No, the chance of facing multiple enemies makes it too risky.
What should we do?
What's the holdup? Just go on through.
Do you have any idea of the situation here, Bitch-sensei?
How are we supposed to make it past all those guards?
Just go through!
Grin.
I'm sorry.
I seem to have had too much of the liquor in my room.
Oh, er, think nothing of it, miss.
I'm the pianist scheduled to perform here next week.
I came early to see the sights.
A pianist, eh?
We get 'em all the time.
I'd like to see if the piano's in tune. It'll help me sober up.
Could I play a teensy little bit, hmm?
Well, uh... Let me check with the front—
Aw, come on.
I want you to hear me play.
And then critique me.
C-Critique you?
Yes, critique me carefully...
and if I do anything wrong, will you scold me?
She's...
She's freakin' amazing!
Ah, the Fantaisie-Impromptu.
An assassin who not only has obvious skill,
but also knows all too well
how to charm, how to use her wiles...
Using her whole body in such a bewitching way as she plays:
it's aural seduction!
All eyes are on her.
C'mon, don't watch from so far away.
Come closer and make sure I do well.
I'll buy you twenty minutes. Go.
Even we were spellbound,
thinking what a beautiful teacher we had.
We all made it through!
Isn't Bitch-sensei something?
Playing like that with those nails?
She never said anything about being able to play.
There's more to her than what you see every day.
The better the assassin, the broader her skill set.
The woman who's been teaching you conversation skills
is amongst the top one or two masters of seduction in the world.
So my current immobility won't be a problem.
Let's go!
Uh-huh!
Don't let them get the better of you.
Fukuma Denjo Hotel
Current Location
Display Route
All right.
Now that we're past the heavy security at the entrance,
CURRENT LOCATION
3rd Floor Corridor
we should be able to pose as regular guests.
Guests? Do they put up groups of junior-high kids here?
Plenty, from what I've heard.
The coddled kids of millionaires and celebrities.
Brought up like decadent royalty,
they keep innocent faces while dabbling in darker pursuits.
Right! So walk around acting like those kids,
looking down your noses at the whole world!
Yes, that's the way!
Is it, now?
And don't you join in!
However, we have no idea what our opponent looks like.
He might attack while posing as a regular guest like us.
Proceed with plenty of caution.
Natch!
Sorry, Okuda... Takebayashi.
I-It's okay.
Their fevers are so high.
At the very least, we need to cool their heads down to avoid brain damage.
G-Got it.
Um... Could a virus this powerful spread throughout the island?
Probably not. I mean, we're okay, right?
It's likely to be transmitted orally.
It'd have to be mixed into food or drink or something.
I doubt there's any risk of it spreading to a random bystander.
I told the other team that, too.
A virus given to us and us alone...
But when? And where?
Fukuma Denjo: Corridor to 3rd Floor Central Hall
CURRENT LOCATION
It really is like we're all just regular guests.
If anything, they avoid eye contact.
No one wants to cause any trouble, after all.
I originally thought we'd have to take on everyone in the hotel,
but it looks like we can just stroll up to the top floor.
And if something does happen...
3rd Floor Central Hall
CURRENT LOCATION
our point man, Karasuma-sensei, is looking out for all of us.
It'll be a cinch now that we're inside!
Stay alert.
We don't have time to play around. Let's do this!
Hey!
Terasaka-kun! Watch out!
Gas?!
Karasuma-sensei!
How could you tell?
I kill in passing without the slightest hint of bloodlust.
That happens to be my specialty, Helmet Hair.
Aren't you the man who gave us our welcome drinks?
Please enjoy this tropical juice with our compliments.
Fuwa-san!
It's downright fishy for someone like that to be walking around in here!
She's right!
You've got a good eye.
Then was it you who gave everyone that virus?
That's a pretty flimsy accusation.
There would have been plenty of other opportunities to slip you that stuff.
The only time we all ate or drank the same thing
was with those drinks and our shipboard dinner.
But Mimura-kun and Okajima-kun worked on the video right through dinner, and they're both sick,
which narrows it down to those daytime drinks.
And that means...
the culprit is you, mister!
That's amazing, Fuwa-san!
You were just like a detective!
When you read a lot of shounen manga,
you learn to adjust quickly to unusual situations.
Magazine and Sunday are
chock-full of detective manga hits!
What about Jump?
Huh? Jump's detective stuff?
I don't really know, but they're putting out a compilation.
The solution to this mystery is already on the tip of my tongue.
Better pick one up!
Neuro Nougami, the mystery-solving demon. Matsui Yuusei's debut title! 12 compilation volumes now available!
I get tortured nonstop!
That's the kind of manga this is.
That's nasty!
Be more subtle with the product placement, Fuwa-san!
Pay more attention to ethics in marketing!
I guess even if you've found me out, it's already too late.
A poisoner, eh?
And quite skilled in practical application.
My very own paralysis gas for indoor use.
One whiff can bring down an elephant.
Fresh air neutralizes it, leaving no evidence behind.
Now, it's plain to see you have no intention of honoring our arrangement.
Negotiations have broken down.
Guess I'll have to tell my boss.
They're fast!
When did they block the exits?!
When encountering an enemy...
...immediately block their retreat path...
...and cut off communications!
Isn't that right, Karasuma-sensei?
The minute you saw us,
you should've held off attacking
and gone back to tell your boss.
I'm surprised you can still talk.
But all you have left is a bunch of kids.
Once you're dead,
they'll stop following orders and just run away!
S-So strong... And such inhuman speed...
But y'know, Terrifying Teach...
your command...
ends... right... here!
Ka—
Karasuma-sensei!
You can't keep going like this, Karasuma-sensei.
I'll be fine in half an hour.
Don't do anything crazy.
He's the crazy one. That gas was supposed to stop an elephant in its tracks!
Karasuma-sensei's kind of a monster himself.
A pro with both experience and know-how is really something.
And that's the kind of pro waiting for us up ahead.
Can we beat him with our power alone?
Man, it sure is starting to feel like summer vacation, am I right?
Well, aren't you happy-go-lucky!
Says the only one who's absolutely safe!
Nagisa, twirl him around till he's sick!
Okay, Terasaka, I'm jamming him in. Drop trou and spread those cheeks!
That'd kill me!
Korosensei, why does this feel like summer?
The teacher-student relationship isn't a cozy one.
Summer vacation fosters student independence in places beyond a teacher's protection.
If you apply the lessons you've learned in your usual gym classes,
there will be few enemies for you to fear.
This is your assassination vacation... and you can beat it.
Start with a rich seafood stock.
Add plenty of green onions and a spoon of minced garlic...
and a gun!
Gotta love a souped-up gun!
And when the soup trickles through the rifling... That's good eatin'!
Well, it makes my blood run cold.
That gun's loaded, right?
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
And it'll be just fine when it comes to shootin', too.
I tend to it every night like it's my very own baby boy.
The most delicious gun on any given day is the one that suits me best.
It's kinda like my rule of thumb.
You're a weird one, all right.
Are your two buddies the same way?
Yeah, well...
When you've pulled off as many jobs as we have,
you tend to develop your own little obsessions.
For example, Smog makes all his own poisons.
He's so insistent on fine-tuning them for practical use
that he even made his own lab.
Huh. And the third?
What about Grip?
Well...
5th Floor Scenic Walkway
CURRENT LOCATION
Even as assassins go, that one's an odd duck.
Hey, why's he just standing out in the open like that?
That vibe he's giving off...
Oh, yeah. I can totally call it now.
When it comes down to it, he's a killer.
A scenic walkway with an unobstructed view!
Forget a surprise attack or strength in numbers.
Damn it. I wish I had a gun with real bullets.
I never thought I'd need one here on this island.
What a drag-eth.
I can tell-eth from your footsteps that you're not tough enough for me.
And they said some special-forces teacher was tak-eth-ing the lead, too.
I guess Smog's gas must've gotten-eth the better of him.
Probably killed-eth each other at the same time.
Come on out, hm.
He cracked the window with his bare hand!
B-But more than that...
We're all too afraid to say it, but... well...
You sure like adding "eth" to things, buddy!
There it is! Thank goodness for Karma!
I heard it had a cool old-fashioned sound to it, like-eth a samurai.
It's got a cool ring to it, so I'm try-eth-ing it out.
Oh, so he's a foreigner.
I might-eth be doing it wrong, but that's okay.
After I kill you all here,
I can drop-eth the "eth" and no one will ever know.
Bare hands... Are those your killing tools, then?
My skills are actually in quite high demand, you know-eth.
Passing through pat-downs is quite the advantage, after all-eth.
When my prey draws close, I snap-eth their necks.
Or if the fancy strikes me, I crush-eth their skulls.
It's funny, you know-eth.
The more you train-eth your strength for the purpose of killing people,
the more you feel-eth like using it for something other than assassination.
To be-eth precise, a fight,
to the death, against-eth a mighty foe.
But this is quite-eth the letdown.
After seeing who I'm up against,
I've all but lost-eth my will to fight.
Not to mention, it's a pain to mop-eth up a bunch of small fry by myself.
I'll call in my boss and my colleague to help-eth out.
Hey, buddy. Chill-eth.
You seem pretty average for a pro, huh?
Breaking glass, busting skulls?
I can do that much.
But if your opening move is to call in reinforcements,
I guess that means you're too scared to take on a junior-high kid alone.
No! Don't be reckless!
Stop right there, Karasuma-sensei.
His chin is down.
So far he's been showing off his swagger with his chin in the air,
looking down on his opponents.
But this is different.
His words may be as rough as ever,
but his eyes are looking straight ahead, alertly observing his foe head-on.
He'd been lying low ever since finals,
but it seems he's learned well from his failures.
Very well-eth.
Let's see what you can do-eth.
Give this everything you've got.
You're facing one high wall: an adult!
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte