Damn it! This can't be happening!
It has to be some kind of mistake!
Huh?
What are you talking about—
What's this?
There's no way you're getting married!
It gotta be some sort of conspiracy!
G-Getting married?
Issei, I want my first grandchild to be a girl!
I'm so proud of you now!
I thought you were just a useless skirt chaser, but...
Whoa, time out!
Don't let your eyes wander, Issei.
P-President!
Rias-sama, you look beautiful!
Oh, Rias-oneesama, why're you marrying a dork like him?
She's the one I'm getting married to!?
Placeholder
From this day forward,
When did our relationship get this far?
for better, for worse,
Well, it's not a problem if I get hitched with my idol!
for richer, for poorer,
Placeholder
in sickness or in health,
But marriage means baby-making,
and baby-making means the wedding night!
to love and to cherish...
Come, Issei.
You may now seal your vows with a kiss.
A k-kiss?
You look pretty hot and bothered there, brat.
That voice sounds familiar.
Yes, I am inside you.
Wh-Who are you?
I am me.
I've always been talking to you,
but you never heard me.
Perhaps because you were too weak.
I don't get it! What're you on about!?
I just wanted to greet you since
we're fighting together as partners.
Partners? Who are you?
I'm sure you should already know.
Don't you, partner?
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 8 "I'm Picking a Fight!"
You look pretty sleepy.
Yeah, I had a weird dream, so I couldn't get any real sleep.
If it was a sexy one, we want details!
It wasn't.
I'm sorry, Issei-san.
I should've woken you up earlier.
Don't worry, Asia. It's my own fault for oversleeping.
Issei, damn you!
Do you have Asia-chan wake you up!?
Oh, yes, of course.
We're living in the same house, after all!
Issei-san is such a sleepyhead.
C-Could she be serving you rice too?
My mom was praising Asia for being such a good girl!
Oh my, you're embarrassing me!
Why do all these cuties flock to you!?
This unfairness makes me go mental!
So, my friend, I was wondering
if you could maybe get me a date with one of them.
I mean, just hook me up with someone!
Please! I beg you!
I can't really do much even if you ask me to...
They're all demons, after all.
I'm willing to make it worth your while if you hook me up.
Wh-What do you mean by that?
I suppose you could call it...
a gentleman's VIP seat.
H-Hold on a second!
One of them is fine with it.
Really!?
Today is even possible.
She said she'll bring a friend along.
S-So what's she like?
W-Well, a true virgin.
No doubt about it.
A virgin!
Spectacular!
By the way, what's her name?
Mil-tan.
This is...
Hey, look at her breasts!
Her clothes totally hid those big boobs!
This is the super VIP seat I found!
What do you say, Hyoudou-shi?
Th-This is wonderful!
Koneko-chan!?
Wh-What a view!
What a lovely moment!
Save to neural memory.
Backup at HD quality complete!
Th-This small fist!
Don't tell me...
Matsuda! Motohama!
H-Hi, Koneko-chan.
Fancy meeting you here.
You're terrible.
Girls' Changing Room
It hurts!
Are you all right, Issei-san?
He deserved it.
Seriously, why are you always so...
I just went with the flow when my friends invited me.
Issei-san, if you want to see naked bodies that badly,
I-I will...
No, Asia! That's not what this is about!
Yeah, Issei.
I can show you mine any time, so just ask.
P-President?
You've already seen them many times, anyway.
Right?
W-Well, I have, but...
Jeez, Issei-san!
That hurts!
I don't like that lewd smile of yours!
You got it wrong.
Listen to me, Asia.
But really, it's a mystery.
What?
The surveys taken by those who summoned Issei-kun
have all been positive.
They say things like they had fun or that they had a good time,
even though he didn't form any contracts
except when you were with him.
I've never seen this happen before.
He may have failed as a demon,
but all the clients loved it.
How should we interpret this?
It's a problem.
But Issei-kun has his—
That's not what I'm talking about.
Huh?
Just like when we went to get them familiars.
I'm afraid Issei might lose confidence in himself if this continues.
I need to... support him more.
Oh my, you seem uncharacteristically proactive.
What are you trying to say?
I thought you preferred to leave things alone.
Though, you should avoid spoiling him too much.
Rias, you are—
I'm glad to have a close friend like you worrying about me,
but this is my problem.
And I am this club's president.
Right?
Yes, President.
Then, please excuse me.
All right. Thank you for your work.
Koneko-chan hates me now.
I suck so much.
But I can't just keep moping like this!
I'll be the Harem King!
For starters, I'm gonna take a bath to cheer myself up!
Wait, why am I screaming!?
Sorry! I'm leaving!
S-Sorry.
U-Um...
It's my first time seeing a man's,
so I freaked out for a second.
N-No, I was the one who was lost in thought
a-and didn't notice you were already in here.
Sorry.
But, it's okay now!
What's okay?
I heard about the rule of naked
relationships in Japanese bath culture.
Rule?
Yes.
Interacting in the bath
allows people to learn about one another on an even deeper level.
Asia, you may be right, but that's not really what it's about!
I-I want to get closer to you, Issei-san!
Also, you like looking at naked bodies, right?
Hold! Hold together, my sanity!
Asia, naked relationships are like...
Actually, forget it.
You're a girl, so when a boy
barges in, you need to be uptight...
Asia-chan, I'll leave the bath towel here!
I'm not lustful.
I'm not a pervert.
I must protect Asia.
I do live with Asia, but I must not think about perverted things!
Namu namu—
A demon shouldn't recite Buddhist chants!
Why am I trying to kill myself?
A magic circle?
President!?
Wh-What's the matter?
Um...
Issei,
sleep with me!
Sorry?
Take my virginity.
This is urgent!
Th-This is...
What is this?
She chose me to have her first time with?
I'm honored.
But before that, I'm not mentally prepared!
You don't want me?
I-It's nothing like that!
I considered many options,
but this is the only way.
W-Way?
He won't be able to complain once we've sealed the deal.
You still have some shortcomings,
but you have potential.
Um, I'm not sure I follow.
And you look like you can climax
in a few minutes if I ask you to.
President?
Wh-What is this?
Issei, is this your first time?
Y-Yes!
I doubt either of us will be perfect,
but we'll manage somehow.
It's all right. I'll just put yours right in here.
Listen.
I'm feeling nervous too.
Y-Yes. I can feel your heart throbbing.
You ran out of time the other day,
but there will be no countdown this time.
I-I'm not really feeling confident, though.
Are you going to let me down?
I-I'm just... President!
Looks like we were a tad too late.
With such a commoner...
Master and Sirzechs-sama will be crestfallen.
Sirzechs?
My elder brother.
Your big brother?
My chastity is mine.
What's wrong with giving it to someone I have high hopes for?
Also...
I won't let anyone call my cute servant a commoner.
Not even you, my elder brother's queen.
Regardless,
you are the heiress apparent of the Gremory family.
Please take care of yourself.
How do you do?
I am Grayfia, a servant of the Gremory family.
Nice to meet you.
S-Same here!
She's so pretty!
I'm sorry, Issei.
I wasn't thinking clearly.
Let's forget about this.
O-Okay.
Issei?
Then he is that person?
Yes, he's my pawn.
This kid's the one to wield Boosted Gear
and the one the Emperor of Red Dragon's attached to?
Wh-What's the big deal?
Let's talk at my place.
Do you mind if Akeno comes with us?
The Priestess of Thunder?
I don't mind.
It is expected of upper-class demons to have
their queens be at their side at all times.
Sorry for bothering you, Issei.
D-Don't worry.
Let's call it quits with that for tonight.
Last night with the president...
What was that all about?
It looked like something serious was going on.
Issei!
Just unbelievable!
Wh-What?
You're being very intense for this time of day!
Don't give me that crap!
What was that Mil-tan about?
He's like a rival character from a battle manga, no matter what!
And why was he wearing a gothic lolita outfit!?
Is he the ultimate weapon!?
It was just a cute boy who's crazy about magical girls, right?
As if I would hook up with a guy!
Manly
You set us up with men who are more like bears.
They were crossdressing! It was hell!
Manly
I was so scared!
I thought I'd die, you bastard!
We went to the magical world. And he kept talking!
The hell's that "Magical World Serapinia"!?
President's worrying, huh?
I suppose it's some internal affair of the Gremory family.
Would Akeno-san know something about it?
She is her right-hand woman, so she probably does.
What's wrong?
I can't believe I noticed it only now.
What's up?
Hey all!
Grayfia-san!?
Looks like you're all here.
Milady, should I talk to them?
The truth is...
Phenex!
I haven't been to the human realm in a while.
I've come for you,
Rias, my love.
Who's this guy?
This is Raiser Phenex-sama.
A pure-blooded, upper-class demon
and the third son of the Phenex family.
Phenex family?
He's also the fiancé of the Gremory family's heiress apparent.
The Gremory family's heiress apparent!?
Don't tell me...
That is to say, he's engaged to Lady Rias.
E-Engaged!?
My, Rias's queen prepares quite delicious tea!
Thank you for the compliment.
This disgusting guy is her fiancé!?
Cut it out already.
Raiser, I told you last time.
I don't intend to marry you.
But, Rias, I thought your family was with its back to
the wall, so you're in no position to be this selfish.
I'm not going to bring my family down.
I'm going to take a husband.
But I will marry someone I want to be with.
The entire demon world struggles to preserve the lineages of pure-blooded demons
after the last war made them a rarity.
Our fathers arranged this marriage for the common good.
My father, elder brother, and other family
members are all rushing too much.
I won't say it twice, Raiser.
I'm not going to marry you.
You know, Rias, I am the face of the Phenex family.
I cannot have you sully my honor.
President!
I'll take you back to the underworld.
Even if it means burning all your servants to death.
Please calm down.
Milady, Raiser-sama,
as I am here on Sirzechs-sama's orders,
I do not intend to stand idly by.
When it's you, the mightiest queen, saying that,
even I am scared.
He predicted this might happen.
As such, I have been charged to carry out last resort measures if no agreement is reached.
Last resort?
What do you mean, Grayfia?
If you insist on your position, you're welcome to settle the issue
with Raiser-sama through a Rating Game.
Rating Game?
Where did I...
Right, the student council president was saying something like that!
It's a game that resembles chess
where upper-class demons fight using their servants.
Chess?
That is why our powers are likened to chess
pieces. Why we're called Evil Pieces.
I see.
I've played the game many times and won many times as well.
You're not even an officially qualified player,
let alone have any experience.
Originally, only seasoned demons were
allowed to participate in a Rating Game.
Then she's at a real disadvantage!
It's getting worse.
Rias, just to make sure,
are these all your servants?
What if they are?
I have fifteen!
In other words, a full set of pieces.
Beauties?
Fifteen beautiful girls!?
Unbelievable!
What a true man!
H-Hey, Rias, that servant is crying out loud while looking at me.
Forming a harem is his dream.
That's creepy.
Oh, I see.
Yubelluna!
Yes, Raiser-sama.
You'll never be able to do things like this,
you lowly imp.
Shut up!
I can tell you'll flirt with other girls
even after marrying our president!
You promiscuous chicken shit!
Don't you know your place?
I don't care!
All I'm aware of is my position...
Stop, Issei!
as President's servant!
Nothing more, nothing less!
Issei!
We don't need a stupid game!
I'll bring all of you down right here!
Boost!
Issei-san!
Mira!
This small girl?
I can't really attack her.
Issei-san!
Issei!
Hang in there!
President!
I'm sorry.
Who knew the holder of the allegedly evilest
and strongest weapon, Boosted Gear,
would be such a worthless guy?
All right.
Let's settle this with a Rating Game.
Understood.
Raiser.
I swear I'll blast you away!
I'm looking forward to it, Rias, my love.
We'll meet again for the game, then.
Issei!
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
Lesson four!
You're a demon, after all.
It's expected of a demon.
A demon.
It damages demons a lot!
Episode 9 "I Began Training!"
I might become invincible!
You're a pervert.