Sup?
C-Could this be... a bra!?
Why is this here?
Th-Then this is Asia's...
That's a crime, Issei-senpai.
Koneko-chan.
Oh, Issei-san!
Stealing underwear is a real crime.
Crime?
N-No, it just happened to get in my face...
I'm so sorry. I wanted to take them down beforehand.
It's okay!
After all, you have to stay here.
The President said she'll find a place for me to live before I start school.
Intensive early morning drills?
The fight with the fallen angel showed
you need to increase your base physical strength.
I-I see.
I'll pick you up by five.
Five in the morning? Okay.
Then, I'll be off to hand out our flyers.
See you.
Asia?
Yes!
Um, regarding the boarding...
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Cough, cough.
Episode 6 "I'm a Demon, Hard at Work!"
I-It's morning! Wake up!
Cough, cough, cough.
Please wake up! Wake up! Cough, cou—
Come on! It's only four thirty.
P-President!
I'll be right there!
Hey! Pull yourself together!
Y-Yes!
I will become the Harem King!
I didn't expect demons to train like athletes!
Don't grumble!
I don't want to see my servants being weak.
I-I will do my best!
Listen. Physical strength essentially determines your standing in the demon world.
Especially for you, Issei.
G-Got it!
Her breasts! Her breasts!
Do you understand?
Given your ability, your power will increase with greater physical strength.
Yes, ma'am!
Eleven! Twelve!
The President's ass feels so nice!
You're having naughty thoughts.
Your hip movements gave you away!
I can't help it!
This is cranking my animal lust up to the maximum!
She should be here about now.
Huh? Is someone coming?
Sorry!
Issei-san, President, I'm sorry I'm late—
Why did I have to trip?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Asia, why are you here?
She told me to come.
President, why'd you call Asia here?
President?
Oh, yes.
What's wrong?
Now that Asia's here, let's go.
Go where?
Your home, Issei.
Wh-What are all these...?
Those are my belongings.
Turns out I had a lot more than I thought.
These are yours? President!?
That's right! Asia will be living at your place from now on.
Sorry!?
I am fortunate to be in your care.
I asked her where she'd like to board, and she picked your home!
Y-You can't just do that so suddenly—
A-Asia-san, was it?
Yes, Mr. Hyoudou.
W-Wouldn't a different family be better as a homestay?
Issei-san did me a real favor.
A favor?
Yes, he helped me so much when I first came here; when I was all alone.
I think it would be really nice to stay in this house.
Asia!
But if it is a bother, I won't insist.
We're not saying no!
We do have an empty room.
But...
Our son is basically the incarnation of lust!
Yeah!
Don't say it like that! I'm your son!
Then how about teaching her to be a housewife while staying here?
W-Wife!?
H-Honey! I never thought I'd get to see my grandson in this life!
Dear, me too! I can't believe this failure of a son managed to...
Hey, wait a second!
Mr. and Mrs. Hyoudou, Issei-san is not a failure at all.
Sh-She's such a kind girl!
Rias-san, we'll take care of Asia-san!
Please, let us take care of her!
Thank you very much, Mr. and Mrs. Hyoudou!
That settles it.
Um, being a housewife and being my wife are two completely different things, you know?
Wife, huh?
President?
My name is Asia Argento!
I may still be new to this place,
but I'm glad to meet you!
A blonde beauty!
Bust 82, waist 55, hip 81. Good!
Oh, right.
She's in my class.
This is also the President's...
I'm currently staying at Hyoudou Issei-san's place!
What!?
Explain! Why are you living with a blonde beauty!?
Why are you the only one getting all these chances!?
I didn't have a choice!
Who made the decision then!?
That's a relief. Looks like she'll get along with everybody.
Say, does your room have a lock, Asia-san?
It does!
Check the bath and toilet carefully.
Check it?
Yes, you never know if there's a camera installed.
Camera?
Hey, you guys!
You must be exhausted.
Not at all! Everyone in the class was nice to me.
Your friends Matsuda-san and Motohama-san were also...
D-Did they do something to you?
He said I'm invited to the next gentlemen's gathering.
Hm? Just ignore that.
Oh.
S-Sorry.
Don't mind it. I'm all right.
Issei-san?
N-Nothing! Let's keep going.
Okay!
President, we just got back.
Um, President?
I'm sorry. I was spacing out a bit.
Thanks for your work, you two.
Asia?
Yes?
I'm thinking about having you debut tonight.
Debut?
You teleport to a client through a magic circle
and form a contract!
Wait, isn't this too early?
Asia has been a demon only for a few days.
It's no problem.
As far as I've figured out, Asia-chan's demonic power ranks just below mine in this household!
S-Seriously?
You'll be a very capable bishop.
You're amazing, Asia-san!
N-Not at...
It's certainly a great thing, but I feel a little demoralized.
No, I still have more experience!
I have to protect Asia!
What's the matter, Asia?
It's nothing.
Since that's your order...
President!
What?
Let me go this time!
I-Issei-san?
You're still not familiar with this country.
I think you should wait until after you are a little more used to living here.
To be honest, I was worried as well.
It could always be some sort of deviant summoning her.
If I form a contract, you'll do everything I say, right?
Oh, no!
Well, that's probably just my imagination going wild, but still...
It's open! Come inyo!
"Inyo"?
What was that?
Welcome.
I'm Mil-tan.
Nyo!
Sir, did you summon a demon from the Gremory household by any chance?
I sure did.
I summoned you to do me a favor.
Wh-What?
Please... Please make me a magical girl!
You should travel to a parallel universe or something.
I tried that already.
You did!?
Demon-san!
Sorry!
Please grant me fantasy powers.
You already look fantastical.
I want magical powers!
Calm down!
We don't want to wake the neighbors,
so let's go inside, okay?
You're going to make me a magical girl!?
We can talk about it.
Th-Then let's...
Magical Girl Milky Spiral
watch Magical Girl Milky Spiral 7 Alternative together!
Alternative
Magical Girl Milky Spiral
You'll see its magical powers!
This again? So, it was an altogether different kind of deviant...
Why do I only get weirdos?
The President!?
Good work. Looks like you've finished the job.
How was it?
Actually...
All right? The bloomers will look like
panties if you concentrate enough!
I see it, Motohama!
I can see it too!
The blue bloomers were white before I knew it!
You couldn't form a contract this time, either?
The anime he showed me was fun, so I ended up watching it with him till the end.
I'm sorry.
Well, if you couldn't form it, forget about it.
She definitely sounded disappointed.
I'm such an idiot!
The sun's also too bright.
I'll just skip class and take a nap.
P-President!
M-My hand is moving on its own!
Stop! Don't do it, right hand!
Just a little farther!
Oh, Issei.
Um, how'd this happen?
I was feeling a little languid, so I thought I'd take a little nap.
Then I found you sleeping here.
Oh, oops.
Did I disturb your sleep?
Not at all, but isn't it a little too extreme to nap naked...
I can't fall asleep unless I'm nude.
Issei, could it be you like breasts?
Yes, I love them!
Do you want to touch my breasts?
Wh-Who knew such a wonderful phrase exists!?
I'll let you if you do me a favor.
Yes, anything!
Well, then, form a contract with someone.
Um, are we really going together?
As I said, I'll be accompanying you as a supervisor this time.
Well, if I'm with her, there's no way I'll fail.
Then...
Do your best, Issei-san!
Oh, I'll do my best, Asia!
Off you go!
It looks like an apartment.
But what's all this Warring States Period stuff?
Oh, are you the demons?
Um, excuse me, but are you a woman?
Yes.
My name is Susan.
I came here to study because I love Japanese culture.
B-But that getup is...
Oh, I'm sorry!
I clad myself in armor to be protected
from the dangers of the night.
I think you're doing it wrong.
But, I'm glad nice demons like you came.
If scary demons had come, I would've had to... had to draw this Kijinmaru Kunishige!
You just drew it!
So, Susan-san, what do you want us to do?
Please accompany me to the university, so I can retrieve the notes I left there.
That's it?
The university is scary at night!
You're the scariest here.
Damn it. Why am I getting summoned by all these freaks?
What's wrong?
S-Sorry, streets at night are scary.
You are the one who's scary!
Th-Thank you so much.
See you, then.
I fulfilled my promise to the President!
With this, I can grope her breasts without holding back!
I'll start with the right, moving my hands in a circle.
As for the left one, I'll jerk that soft flesh like crazy!
U-Um...
What is it!?
Actually, I have another favor to ask.
Um, we can't really do that.
It's one wish per summon.
Oh, we don't mind.
P-President!
A boy you fell in love with?
Yes.
I'm shy and thus couldn't express my feelings.
He's a very wonderful man.
I bet he looks like a hairy warrior from the Warring States Period.
So, you want us to make him fall in love with you?
If possible, I don't want any demonic powers involved.
I want to earn his love on my own.
That means you don't need us!
Then, why don't you confess to him right away?
That's... I can't just do that!
Maybe a letter?
A letter?
Oh, yeah, a love letter might be a good idea.
Love letter!
It's wonderful to convey one's feelings in writing.
O-Okay! I'll give it a try!
I am writing you about no specific order of business,
thus you may set your mind to ease.
Sounds like an official address.
It's all right.
It's the feelings that matter, not the form.
I'm not sure if that'll get the feelings across.
Yes, it's not the form.
It isn't... about the form.
President?
I'm done!
Sending letters via arrow!? Are you kidding me!?
Mom, what is that?
Don't look.
What is this?
Seems like he's here.
Wh-What!?
The arrow!
Susan!
The arrow is stuck in his head!
Yes, I thought about different ways to do it,
but sending a message via arrow was
the only thing I could manage.
B-But that's...
I have read your letter.
It was a wonderful message!
I'm amazed you caught me off guard and shot me with an arrow.
What a letter!
Oh no, all I was thinking was how to get it to you,
Horii-kun!
I feel like I'm going mad.
I-I want to go out with you if you don't mind.
What!?
Ho-Horii-kun!
I'm so happy!
Susan!
Your armor is wonderful.
Wow, your armor is also so hard and sturdy!
They are the perfect couple.
Y-You're right...
in a way.
Say, Issei...
Y-Yes?
How do you feel about having a romantic relationship with someone you love?
What I feel about it? Wouldn't it be bliss?
Right, bliss.
I mean...
You should never go out with someone you don't even love.
That's just wrong.
So...
Huh?
What am I saying? Sorry.
Oh no, I appreciate the answer.
Didn't you say you want to talk about something, Issei?
Oh, right!
I almost forgot!
All right! No one's around!
Now's the time for her part of the deal!
It's about the promise we made last time!
Promise?
Did we ever make a promise?
U-Um... about the b-breasts!
I know.
You don't need to be so serious about it.
All right, until I've counted to five...
my breasts are all yours.
One!
That's too sudden!
Two!
This is bad! I didn't have a chance to prepare myself!
Three!
Calm down! I need to calm down!
Right? Or left?
Four!
I-I'll just grope both of them!
Issei-san, you're here already?
Sorry, we're late.
Hello.
Five.
All right, that's it!
Too bad, Issei.
Oh my, what happened, Issei-kun?
No way!
Issei, you're so funny.
You wanted to touch my breasts that badly?
Then I'll do this for just a little bit.
U-Um, everyone's watching.
Keep working hard, my cute Issei.
I-I will.
Rias.
Could she be...?
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
Please excuse us.
Sh-She is...
With those visuals, it's definitely god tier!
This is embarrassing!
Oh no!
Episode 7 "I'm Gonna Get a Servant Demon!"
This is wonderful!