Teach
us,
Kunundo
Teach
us,
Kunundo
Teach
n
do
us,
Teach
Ku
nu
Teach
Ku
nu
Teach
Ku
nu
Surprise!
n
do
Teach us, Kunudon!
By upholding our principles of high-growth education,
we provide the ideal environment for drawing out burgeoning potential.
Hi, everybody! It's me, Kunudon!
By upholding our principles of high-growth education,
we provide the ideal environment for drawing out burgeoning potential.
Kunudon-sama!
The students with the best grades at Kunugigaoka Academy are entitled to a fantastic privilege:
Vested interest!
Three days and two nights at a luxury summer school in always-summery Okinawa!
Official passports!
Boost Your Concentration in the Open Air!
The school pays for the hotel and everything that goes with it.
Students can study to their hearts' content!
Sheer debauchery! Yay!
What? What do you mean, the E Class is going?!
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
potential takai
We've got a lot of potential
hodo mendokusai
It's just that we're not trying
dropout mentality
We had that dropouts' mentality
hinichijou wo ryougashi
No matter the unusual situation we were in
bokura wa utatatanegao shite
We pretended to doze off
knife kakushimotta
While holding on to a hidden knife
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
doko ka taningoto datta
We didn't really feel invested in the job
dakedo
But now
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Our chances soar each time we challenge you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
revolution
A revolution!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
Episode
Island
Time
Whoa, just look at 'em all!
Summer vacation had begun...
and with it came our freedom!
Or so you'd think.
Why are we here at school?
Well... I don't want people to see me out catching bugs at my age.
But I've always wanted to do this, and I never got a chance in the city.
Plus, Karma happened to point me to a tree with some good bugs on it.
Though I didn't expect you to come, Maehara.
Never pegged you as an insect fan.
Our next assassination's at that island resort, right?
Wouldn't you say we're missing a little something?
Like what?
Money!
You need buying power if you're gonna snag yourself a swimsuited babe!
That runt won't do the trick,
but a giant stag beetle?
Those babies'll net you tens of thousands of yen!
Auction 'em off online for major cashola,
and we'll make at least enough to cover a fancy dinner and a place to chill out!
I think he's forgotten what this trip's all about.
Yeah. That wasn't your average
fifteen-year-old's vacation plans.
That won't work!
Giant stag beetles're old and busted.
Kurahashi!
Morning! You're here to scrape up some spending money too, huh?
Hey, what do you mean, stag beetles are old and busted?
Well...
I guess they were super valuable right around when we were born,
but today's artificial breeding methods have saturated the market,
bringing their prices way down.
You mean the beetle bubble burst?!
I figured one beetle would make around enough to cover one babe...
No way. These days, babes are way more expensive.
You sure know a lot about this, Kurahashi. Are you into bugs?
Yep! Along with every other living thing!
Hey, since we're all here...
Let's all go bug-hunting!
We're bound to find tons if we all try!
The innocent and genuine Kurahashi-san
knows an insane amount about living creatures.
Just the right helping hand for a bunch of crass-ish guys to have around.
Mmm. Pretty nice haul.
Whoa! Did you set this?
It's a home-made trap of mine.
I put it out last night.
Let ferment for 1-2 days
There are about twenty more of them out there,
so that's about a thousand yen for each of us if we're lucky!
Not too shabby for a side job!
I hope we caught the one I was looking for!
What an inefficient trap.
And you call yourselves the E Class?
Okajima!
Pulling in a measly thousand yen at a time? Yeah, right.
My trap'll bring in a cool ten billion!
Ten billion... You don't mean—
Oh, but I do.
If we're planning an assassination on this tropical isle,
that octopus is bound to let his guard down in the meantime.
And that's what I'm after!
Stag
All right! Here we go!
He went right for my porno trap!
Wow. When do you see the speedy Korosensei too absorbed in reading to make the slightest movement?
That one must be right up his alley.
And what's with the stag beetle getup?
Is he trying to blend in? That's just sad.
Every mountain has one: the smut stash.
The kids who find their dreams there grow old enough to buy their own porn mags
and then leave behind dreams for someone else to find.
Please dispose of recyclables responsibly as per your local council's arrangements.
It's a place filled with neverending dreams.
I'm glad you're here! Lend me a hand!
We'll use our porn power to give him a dream he'll never wake up from!
We seem to have reached maximum crassitude.
I did some major research into his top turn-ons, y'know.
Can't buy the stuff myself, but I found a few.
Wouldn't he like anything with big boobs?
In real life, sure.
A hit
But dirty magazines are dreams.
Everyone looks for their ideal in those pages.
A miss.
For photos and manga alike, the tiniest
difference gets a whole 'nother response.
Photos a hit,
setup doesn't sit well
That's amazing, Okajima-kun. So for the last month,
you've been placing different kinds of porn and carefully observing his reactions?
What kind of grown-up would spend a whole month picking up abandoned porn mags?
That's just sad.
It's just like your traps, Kurahashi.
You need to work out ways to attract your prey for long periods of time, right?
Yeah.
I've got a dirty mind.
If you wanna hate me for it, go on ahead.
But it's only because I'm a super-lech that I know:
Pornography can save the world.
How did he make that sound so cool?!
I'll get him, all right!
Under all that porn is a net strung with anti-teacher BB pellets!
He's buried in that mag right now. We can nab him for sure!
Someone cut this rope and trigger the trap.
I'll jump in there and finish him off!
Anything can be a sword if you polish it enough.
Okajima-kun's porn-sword might just run Korosensei through.
Bwoop!
Wh-What the...
His eyes just went all "bwoop"!
I don't have any data on that face!
What kind of porn does that signify?!
Stag
There you are!
A Miyama stag beetle.
And look at that eye color!
Are they white, Korosensei?
Ah, Kurahashi-san!
Indeed they are!
Wow! Just what I've been looking for!
Yes, right here on this mountain!
Oh, man! And we were so close!
Miyama stag! Miyama stag! Yay!
I don't know what they're so happy about,
but a giant stag beetle and a junior-high girl jumping around on all that porn?
That's one hell of a sight.
Mortifying! How super-duper mortifying!
I'm so ashamed. Such behavior is unbecoming of an educator.
I knew there was a trap under all this porn,
but with each magazine more to my taste than the last,
I couldn't resist!
He saw right through it...
So what's the big deal, Kurahashi?
That's a Miyama stag beetle, right?
In games and stuff, they sell for way less than a giant stag.
Miyamas've been selling for more lately.
They're still hard to breed.
One this size could fetch twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand?!
Plus, take a good look at his eyes.
They're usually black, but these are white.
I taught you about albinism in biology class, right?
Oh, yeah... Like the super-rare creatures born pure white?
Yes, and albino stag beetles are only white in the eyes.
A natural-born Miyama white-eye, as they're known, is extremely rare.
Why, this even has academic value.
You could sell this for hundreds of thousands of yen, easy.
Hundreds?!
I told Korosensei I was hoping I could see one someday,
and he said he'd use his zoom eyes to find one for me!
Okay, you lowlifes: whoever wants this baby, raise your hand!
Me!
What to do, what to do?
I was the one who caught it!
In killing, in porn, in living things:
summer vacation is full of learning and discoveries.
One more week until our assassination vacation to that tropical island.
Old Campus
We'd gotten together to train for it and put our plans in order.
Well, well! I see you little brats are working up a good sweat,
summer vacation notwithstanding.
You should train too, Bitch-sensei.
Your gun and knife skills aren't that much better than ours.
Grownups are sneaky.
I'll just hitch a ride on your strategy and take the best parts for myself.
You think you're a big shot, huh, Irina?
L-Lovro-sensei!
He's here as a special instructor for the summer.
He'll give us tips on our strategy from a pro's perspective.
Spend one day resting, and your fingers and arms forget about killing.
If you don't want to flunk out, hurry and get changed!
Yes, sir!
Even Bitch-sensei can't say no to him.
Yeah, well, he's one scary dude.
Thank you for your assistance.
To make matters worse,
I lost contact with the assassins who'd shown the most promise.
Were they scared off, knowing that even the pros had failed?
Perhaps.
Now all we can do is leave it up to them.
In any case, am I correct in understanding that he is absent today?
Yes. He'd had a trip to Everest planned,
so he's there now, beating the heat.
Good. A confidential strategy is essential for an assassination.
Karuizawa? If you're serious, you'll go to Mt. Everest! To the peak!
I see.
First, we destroy the seven promised tentacles,
then the entire class immediately jumps in to finish him off.
So far, so good...
But what's this very first step: "psychological warfare"?
First we throw him off, blunting his moves.
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Psychological Warfare
Strategy Planning Document 1
Secret
Korosensei was scavenging for dirty magazines earlier.
Stag
Just don't tell your classmates, all right?
So he paid each of us off with an ice pop.
Stag
As if that'd be enough to keep our mouths shut in this day and age!
The entire class will be ganging up and picking on him!
First we'll corner him with that
blackmail material... and more.
A brutal assassination method indeed.
But the key is that final, killing blow.
Pinpoint timing and accurate aim will be crucial.
Are you worried about this class' firepower?
Quite the opposite. Those two in particular are outstanding.
Chiba Ryuunosuke.
He excels at spatial calculations.
As a long-distance sniper, he's second to none.
Hayami Rinka has a nice balance of dexterous fingers and kinetic visual acuity.
She's a soldier who's well equipped to take down a moving target.
Neither is very assertive.
They're the professional type, so their results do the talking.
I would even take them for my own students.
The others are at a respectable level as well.
Good job identifying and nurturing their talents in such a short time.
I see plenty of potential here.
See how your aim has stabilized?
Some shoot better cross-legged than with one knee up.
Yes, sir!
Now that's a pro!
You seem to be having trouble keeping pace with others.
Don't force yourself. Instead, go for a firing style that suits you.
I wanted to ask him something,
this man who knew everything about being an assassin...
Lovro-san?
This boy...
Yes?
What's the very best assassin like?
On closer inspection, he has what it takes.
And what's more...
So you're interested in the world of assassins, eh?
Oh, uh, th-that's not why I...
Well, there's only one person on this planet
who can be called the very best assassin.
As is often the case in this line of work, no one knows his real name.
They know him by a single alias.
Namely:
"The Reaper."
Elusive, incomparably cold-blooded, and with piles of bodies in his wake,
he is known as Death himself.
If you keep having trouble killing your target...
the Reaper will show up sooner or later.
If someone like that might be coming,
we can't let this island chance pass us by!
Very well, young man.
I shall teach you a deadly technique.
Deadly?
Yes: a move guaranteed to kill, from this pro assassin to you.
After that, our tropical-island assassination tour began in earnest.
Not a boat... Anything but a boat!
Everything in my head is going to spill right out!
Korosensei's Weak Point #8:
Prone to motion sickness
Oh! Get up, Korosensei, get up! You can see it now!
Six hours from Tokyo!
The place where we'll kill Korosensei!
The island!
Welcome to the Fukuma Resort Hotel!
Please enjoy this tropical juice with our compliments.
Man, this is the life!
Everything's just so bright and vibrant!
We can go directly to the beach from the hotel.
Looks like they have plenty of leisure activities available, too.
We'll save the you-know-what till after dinner.
First, let's have some fun, Korosensei!
In groups, like we did on our school trip!
I'm all for it. Play hard, kill hard!
That's what makes this an assassination vacation!
Hey, why's that one glider going so fast?
There's no way he should be able to pull off a turn that sharp followed by a barrel roll!
No fair, Korosensei!
The power difference here is just way too great!
Maximum instantaneous velocity measured at 150 kilometers per hour.
With a fighter jet, it all comes down to the engine.
Who's that supposed to be?
Horikoshi Jirou.
No, that's the guy who voiced him!
Too hard!
Besides, he didn't fly 'em, he just built 'em!
It's just all wrong!
Group 1 is doing a good job of throwing him off.
They sure are—and with a little assassination in the mix.
They're trying not to draw his attention to the other groups.
Yeah.
We're up next! Let's do what we have to do and get changed ASAP!
Got it!
We make it look like we're having fun, but we're dead serious.
We give the place a good once-over
to see if we can kill him according to plan.
What kind of pattern is that, Korosensei?
A sunburn. Only the frontmost point of the glider was shading me.
Now, Group 4 is going dolphin-watching, yes?
Yep! In a boat, though. Is that okay?
Sea-rtainly!
While one group hangs out with Korosensei,
the rest work on their preparations.
Where's Korosensei?
Touring deep-sea caves with Group 3.
No way he can see us here.
Then we're free to pick out our sniper spots.
Let's make it quick.
Those two sure are cool customers.
They already feel like total pros.
Wh-What the hell?
The beach is utterly deserted!
The last guest just left.
The E Class has rented out the hotel and its environs.
You know that's overkill!
Why does this happen every time I step out in a swimsuit?!
This is one large-scale assassination plan—the biggest one yet.
So far, it's gone off without a hitch.
C'mon, Karasuma. I want to bewitch someone!
C'mooon!
The only thing left to worry about...
H-Hey, wait—
Look at you, taking charge!
We might be alone with each other, but I wasn't expect—
What was that for?!
There's something I need to ask you, Irina.
You, the pro assassin, said it yourself:
it's not often that your work goes as expected.
Yes, that's right. I saw the documents.
Chances are a complex plan like this will go off the rails once or twice.
Do I look like I'm just having fun here?
I'm gunning for my share of the spoils, of course.
I'll get my opportunity when the brats' plan goes awry—
and I won't let it get away.
I just hope the assassination goes smoothly.
Phew! What fun that was!
No wonder I'm so tanned!
That's beyond tanned!
Even your teeth are tanned.
So much for picking up on your expressions.
All right, Korosensei, after dinner comes the assassination.
Yes, yes. First, the shipboard restaurant!
Hasn't that octopus had enough fun for one day?
Meanwhile, we got to pretend to have fun while we got everythin' ready!
Well, if we kill him today, we can just enjoy ourselves tomorrow.
I guess. Let's put in some effort and finish the job!
Here we are,
at the shipboard restaurant we've rented out.
Let's slowly savor our meal as we take in the night sea.
I get it.
First you'll get me good and seasick to weaken my capabilities, eh?
Of course. That's Assassination 101.
You're so right.
But will it really work that well?
Seasickness is no match for a teacher who's all pumped up anticipating an assassination—
You're too dark!
Am I really that dark?
Forget your expression, we can't even tell front from back!
It's too confusing. Do something about it, would you?
Have you forgotten, students?
I can molt—and in so doing, shed this dark skin!
There! Back to normal.
That's your once-a-month molt!
Just another of its uses.
I tend to save it for particularly sticky situations, but...
What an idiot, hobbling himself before an assassination!
That's right: just once a month.
How have we not been able to kill this screw-up yet?
I guess at least you can see my expressions now.
We'd spent all summer doing special training in preparation for this day.
Everything was in place.
This time... This time, our blades would reach him.
All right, Korosensei. Dinner's over.
Here's where we're meeting.
A floating chapel, away from the hotel.
Take a seat, Korosensei.
There's nowhere for you to run here.
It'll be a fun assassination.
We'll start with a movie.
Your intelligence, your inventiveness, and your earnest efforts...
Those are what I most look forward to.
I expect a no-holds-barred assassination!
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte