TRANSLATION---
Issei, wake up! You're going to be late for school!
Issei!
I'm getting up!
I'll be right down, so wait!
Hurry up! Let's not do this every morning!
As I said, you don't have to come!
Issei, you've gotta get up now!
Senpai, for now, here!
Good morning.
Good morning. P-Please get ready soon.
Dear!
H-Honey, what's the matter!?
Was he masturbating to porn mags again!?
A foreign woman!
Calm down! What about the intercourse!?
Intercourse!?
It's a foreigner!
It's international!
How am I going to explain this?
Before that, why was I in bed with Rias-senpai?
I don't remember it! I don't remember anything!
Why? I gotta remember it!
It must've been my first time!
Remember! I gotta remember that valuable moment!
You have quite an energetic family.
Um, I can see them.
See what?
L-Like, your breasts.
You may look at them if you want.
I "may look at them"? I thought I'd never hear those words!
Then I'll gratefully—
Oh.
Is your stomach all right?
Where you were stabbed.
Stab—
H-How does she know about my dream?
That was not a dream.
You must have an unexpectedly sturdy body.
A fatal wound like that healed overnight, after all.
Healed?
I shared some of my demonic powers with your weakened body.
Say...
Mind hooking my bra?
M-My pleasure!
B-By the way, Senpai, why am I naked?
I told you! I shared my demonic powers with you so you can heal up,
thus I had to hug you naked.
Hug naked!?
It's all right. I'm still a virgin.
Vir—
Oh, I see.
Wait, why am I feeling relieved?
Don't make such a face.
This world is full of mysteries.
Mysteries?
U-Um, Rias-senpai.
What is it?
You were talking about demons or something.
Yes, I am a demon.
And your master.
May I call you Issei?
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 2 "I Quit Being Human!"
Wh-Why!?
No way! Not that guy!
That lowlife, of all people?
R-Rias-oneesama!
Well, no wonder they're surprised.
I'm arriving with Rias Gremory-senpai, the school's most popular idol, after all.
I'll send an errand boy later.
An errand boy?
See you after school.
Wait, Rias-senpai!
Please, hold on!
Issei, you bastard!
You betrayed your comrades in the losers alliance!
Calm down, Matsuda.
Motohama!
First, we want to hear what's going on, Issei.
What happened yesterday after we left you!?
Matsuda, Motohama.
What, Issei?
Have you guys ever seen real breasts?
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
I don't
know!!!
I've never seen them!!!
So, he's the one?
Good day, Rias.
Good day, Sona.
It's not like you to impulsively decide to bring someone into your household.
It's not?
Well, I got myself a silly little brother.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I see.
She said she'd be sending someone, but in the end, no one came.
Hey.
Kiba-kun!
That handsome prince? Fuck off.
Excuse me for a bit.
Oh, please come in.
It's a humble place, but make yourself at home.
Oh, hello.
What do you want?
I'm here on behalf of Rias Gremory-senpai.
Then you are...
Would you follow me?
No way! Kiba-kun and Hyoudou the Pervert?
He'll corrupt you, Kiba-kun!
I'll never accept them as a pair!
They're just spouting nonsense.
Wh-What is this room?
Th-This girl is...
She's Toujou Koneko-san, a first-year student.
This is Hyoudou Issei-kun.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Her petite physique and irresistible loli looks!
She's not only a popular mascot for guys with that kind of preference but also for other girls!
That's Toujou Koneko-chan!
It's such a happy surprise to find out she's an Occult Research Club member!
A shower? In the clubroom?
This is...
Art! Those beautiful lines are a work of art in and of themselves!
President, I've brought your clothes.
Thanks, Akeno.
Rias-senpai!? I knew it!
What a fantastic clubroom this is!
What a creepy face.
Oh my.
Look who's here.
You're the new club member, right?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm the club's vice president, Himejima Akeno.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
I-I'm Hyoudou Issei. Nice to meet you too.
Sh-She has black hair and a ponytail, a rare sight nowadays!
The ultimate, ideal, Japanese female figure filled with tenderness.
She's one of the two great idols of this academy, together with Rias-senpai.
She's Himejima Akeno-senpai!
What a great club!
Thanks for waiting.
Sorry, I spent the night at your place, so I had to...
O-Oh no, I don't mind at all.
Well, everyone's here now!
We welcome you to the Occult Research Club.
But, the Occult Research Club is a mere façade. Nothing more than a hobby.
What do you mean?
I'll be frank.
We are demons.
Th-That was indeed very frank.
The black-winged man you saw yesterday
was a fallen angel.
Once angels serving God, they have been cast down to the underworld due to their wicked nature.
They're trying to manipulate humans and destroy us demons.
Since primeval times, there's been a constant struggle for dominance in the underworld, or Hell, as humans call it.
There are also normal angels, coming here on God's orders to hunt demons.
In other words, we have a three-way standoff.
Do you follow me so far?
Um, this is getting kinda too complicated for a stupid high school student like me.
Amano Yuuma.
I'm sure you remember her.
You even had a date, after all.
I-I have no idea where you've heard that name,
but don't treat it as some occult phenomenon.
Frankly speaking, I find it unpleasant.
Sorry, but...
Yuuma-chan?
She was there. No doubt about it.
This girl is Amano Yuuma-chan, isn't she?
Y-Yes, but how did you get this?
This girl... No, this fallen angel.
It's the same faction that assaulted you last night.
B-But Matsuda and Motohama didn't remember anything about her
and her cellphone address also...
She used her powers...
just like I used mine on your parents.
An upperclassman friend?
I-I heard you were naked together in bed!
That's how kids hang out nowadays, Sir, Madam.
Th-That's just ridiculous!
Is that so?
I see. All right, then.
"When did my parents become so understanding?"
That's what I thought then, but...
Once that fallen angel completed her mission,
she erased memories and records of it from you and the people around you.
Mission?
Killing you.
She came to check whether you have a certain dangerous object in your body.
You were killed once that was confirmed.
Impaled by a light-lance, to be precise.
Blame God for planting a Sacred Gear inside your body.
Now I remember. Yuuma-chan talked about Sa-something.
Sacred Gear.
An unusual power that resides in certain humans.
It is said most of the great men in history possessed it.
Sometimes they have power formidable enough to threaten demons and fallen angels.
Issei, raise your left hand.
L-Like this?
Close your eyes and imagine the strongest being that comes to mind.
Th-This is all too sudden...
Focus, Issei.
O-Okay!
Focus, focus!
Yes, Issei, focus.
Focus...
Foc...
I can't do it!
It's all right. We'll take it slow.
My focus keeps shifting because I can see your panties!
Still, maybe there's been some kind of mistake.
It's a fact the fallen angels fear it and had you killed.
B-But if it's a fact, how come I'm actually alive?
Because of this.
Th-That is...
We grant
your wish.
You summoned me from this flyer moments before you died.
Oh yeah, that time I remembered Rias-senpai's red hair and...
Issei, you've been reborn into the household of Rias Gremory,
daughter of Duke Gremory, an upper-class demon.
As my servant demon, that is!
I can definitely see better at night now.
I thought stuff like demons and servants was just an analogy.
Who knew it was meant literally!?
Indeed, we're the same.
So, welcome, Issei.
Seriously?
I'm a demon?
I'm no longer human?
Demons collect power by forming contracts with humans and receiving compensation for it.
Nowadays, no one manually draws magic circles to summon demons,
so we just hand the circles out to potential contractors.
I-I see.
We usually have familiars do it, but as a servant demon you need to learn the basics.
Work hard and you might get a servant for yourself someday!
M-My servant!?
It all depends on the effort you put in.
I-If they're servants, they will obey me, right?
Yes.
I can do whatever I want with them, right?
Of course!
L-Like even p-perverted things!?
If they're your servants, why not?
If I can't become human again,
I will become the Harem King instead!
All right!
The delivery's done!
Issei, I have one more task for you today.
Koneko received two summoning requests...
so I'll let you handle one of them.
Thanks for doing this.
Oh, I'm the one who should say "thanks".
Does that mean I'm finally getting a contract?
This is a magic circle used for teleportation.
Give me your left hand, Issei.
Oh, sure.
This is a carved seal.
It serves as proof you belong to the Gremory household.
Do as I've told you when you're with the client.
You think you can do it?
Y-Yes!
Glad to hear that.
Off you go then!
Yes!
All right! I'm getting one step closer to my dream!
Huh?
Oh my.
Issei.
Yes?
Looks like you can't jump.
Damn it! What kind of demon has to go on a bike when summoned!?
Higure-sou
This must be Higure-sou.
Good evening, Morisawa-san!
I'm here on behalf of Gremory.
Hello.
I want a different one.
Wait a second! You're the one who summoned a demon!
What kind of a demon knocks on doors?
Like me right here!
Stop messing around.
Koneko-chan always appears from this flyer's magic circle.
Not to mention Koneko-chan's the one I summoned.
Just leave now.
I-I wanted to do that too, but I couldn't!
I rushed here in the middle of the night on my bike and what for?
You're hopeless.
Oh, thank you.
You're a demon, so you must have a talent.
Show me.
Talent, huh? What does Koneko-chan usually do?
There's cosplay and being held in arms, just like a princess!
Y-You don't need a demon for that!
A small girl like her won't be able to lift me if she's not a demon!
I guess you have a point.
Wait.
She lifts you?
So, what's your talent?
Well...
Dragon Wave!
Sorry, I can't do anything yet.
Drago M-ball, huh?
Seeing how young you are, you must've watched re-airings.
I'm from the first generation.
Behold, these are all first issues!
Hoku
to Ken
Drago M-ball - Torida Moe
Y-You're from the first generation; so what!?
What?
I have the special edition of all volumes!
You don't know how every Wednesday, the day after broadcast,
I traveled across the Earth with my comrades to gather energy for the ultimate spirit ball!
I've played hide-and-seek in the park with my friends and we found each other by our life energy!
I still believe the protagonist,
Gon Soku, is the world's strongest!
I think Dell is the strongest!
You could make a case for that too.
Right?
But nothing beats Gon Soku's Dragon Wave!
Let's talk.
Shall we?
All I did was argue about Drago M-ball. I couldn't even form a contract.
What the hell was I doing?
This feeling! It's just like last time!
How strange.
I don't seem to have the wrong person.
I, Calawana, have been ordered to erase all traces.
How utterly strange.
No way!
Why are you alive?
A fallen angel!
She killed you!
The Gremory household seal?
Damn it!
Am I gonna get killed again!?
I see now. You're the one Donnasiege mistook for a stray.
Who knew you'd join the Gremory household?
All the more reason to make sure you won't leave alive!
That bitch's going to kill me!
No! I need power!
I need power to defeat her!
Imagine the strongest being that comes to mind.
Gon Soku!
I believe he's the world's strongest man!
Imagine it.
Dragon Wave!
Power...
Grant me power!
S-Sacred Gear!?
I should notify her first, then kill you!
Sacred Gear?
Yes, that is your Sacred Gear.
Once unleashed, you can activate and deactivate it as you please.
I was so worried it might just stay there!
That's amazing, Issei-kun!
I-Is it?
This has become quite a headache.
The fallen angels now know you're still alive, reborn as a demon.
I'm sorry.
Your encounter with the fallen angel was a fluke,
but understand this:
Don't get cocky and try to take them on by yourself.
Yes, I understand, President.
I'm off, then.
Perhaps you've been too harsh.
He's still a novice.
That's why I'm being harsh.
He needs to be alert.
Yes, I won't let fallen angels take away my adorable servant.
Onii-chan, wake up now!
It's morning!
I'll tickle you if you don't wake up!
I messed up so bad last night.
She might still be angry with me.
Ah, damn it...
Why did I trip?
Wh-Who's that?
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
I got lost and need help.
Anyway, for tonight, observe closely how demons fight.
My name is Freed Zelzan.
Episode 3 "I Got a Friend!"
Bang!
Don't let me down.