Who are you?
Right now, you're not using your power up to its full extent.
Your voice sounds familiar.
You'll never get stronger if you keep that up.
Right, I saw you in a dream once.
You are a special being whose body hosts a dragon.
Stop being so lame or the White Guy will laugh at you.
The White Guy? Who's that?
He'll appear before you one day.
You two are destined to fight each other, after all.
You need to become strong.
I can always share my power with you.
Rest assured, it will be worth the sacrifice.
Show them the dragon within you.
Dragon? You are...
I am the Emperor of Red Dragon, Ddraig—the Welsh Dragon.
Ddraig?
I reside in your left arm.
Why am I...?
Episode 12 "I'm Here to Keep My Promise!"
You seem to have awakened.
Grayfia-san!
Who won?
What happened to the president?
Raiser-sama won the game.
We lost?
Rias-sama resigned.
She... surrendered?
Yes.
You're kidding.
She's the last person who'd admit defeat and resign!
It's because Raiser-sama was trying to kill you.
I don't really remember what happened back then.
You kept going for Raiser-sama, refusing to give up.
Issei, you've done well.
It's all right now.
You've done really well.
Good work, Issei!
So that's what happened.
It was my fault.
I was showing off as though I could do anything.
But I got knocked out like
a loser right before her eyes.
What... What about everyone else?
Asia-san is nursing you here on Rias-sama's orders,
but everyone else is in the demon
realm as Rias-sama's attendants.
Attendants?
For Raiser-sama and Rias-sama's engagement party.
President.
I want someone who loves me as Rias.
I still hold on to this small dream.
I'm sorry, President!
Aim to be the strongest pawn.
I'm sure you can be.
You're my adorable servant, after all.
Become strong, Issei.
I failed to become strong.
I'm weak.
Why am I so weak?
You still seem to be in denial.
Lady Rias is following her family's decision.
Besides, she herself wanted to settle the matter through a match.
I know. I understand.
But the president is accepting something she hates.
She's being forced to accept what her parents decided.
I can't stand it...
With that bastard!
You're a genuinely interesting man.
Huh?
I have seen many kinds of demons over the years,
but you're the first to show what's
on your mind and follow it so honestly.
Sirzechs-sama found you interesting as well.
A magic circle?
You can teleport to the party
using this magic circle.
Are you telling me to be her attendant too?
"If you want to take my sister back, raid the place."
Sirzechs-sama had those words for you when he gave me this.
That side should help you
once you've taken her back.
No need to think this over.
Issei-san?
Asia!
What's the matter?
Thank goodness!
Really, thank goodness!
Although you were completely healed, you stayed unconscious for two days.
I was worried you might not wake up again.
Sorry for making you worry again.
I'm all right as long as you're fine, Issei-san.
That's all I need.
Listen, Asia.
Yes?
I'm going to see the president right now.
Not to congratulate her, is it?
No, I'm going there to get her back.
I'll go with you!
Asia!
No, you stay here.
I don't want to!
I can fight with you!
I can even use magic now!
I want to do more than just be protected.
It's all right.
I'll just drop by to beat up Raiser,
bring him down, and—
It's not all right!
You'll get worn out, covered in blood, and be messed up again!
You'll get hurt badly.
I don't want to see you like that again.
I won't die, no matter what.
Remember? I made it out alive when I saved you.
Then promise me one thing.
Promise?
Come back with the president, no matter what!
Of course!
Also, I want your help with one thing.
You're the only one I can ask to do this.
So please.
I understand.
If you say so.
Thank you.
Hey, you can hear me, right?
I want to talk.
Come out, Emperor of Red Dragon Ddraig!
What is it, boy?
What do you want to talk to me about?
Let's make a deal.
It's supposed to be an engagement party,
but this looks more like a wedding dress.
You're exactly right.
Raiser-sama, you can't.
This area is off-limits to men.
Don't be so rigid.
I'm the star of the party tonight.
Oh, right, the bride is the star. My bad.
I'm not the bride just yet.
What's up with this dress?
It's perfect.
It'll show the demon world the bonding
between the Gremory and Phenex households.
Wearing this makes it easy for you to give up, doesn't it?
Don't worry.
Your dress for the actual wedding ceremony will be on a whole different level.
Following the Phenex family tradition,
it'll be the realm's most gorgeous dress,
decorated with wings of flame!
What horrible taste.
As expected of someone from
such a pretentious household.
Issei!
President, I won't lose.
I swear I'll make you win, President!
You haven't even mastered your magical powers yet,
and your battle experience is virtually zero.
You worked so hard for me
even when injured so severely.
You're an idiot.
No, I'm the idiot.
I was about to lose you.
My adorable, precious...
Yes, my very precious...
Issei.
Rias-sama, it's time.
My brother won a bride through a Rating Game!
It was obvious from the start
who was going to win,
but it was a good show nonetheless!
Look at her bragging.
She must have forgotten that it was broadcast.
President Sona.
The result aside, the match was quite impressive,
or rather, clearly above anyone's expectations.
Thank you for the compliment, but no need to be so considerate.
We don't believe it's over quite yet.
It's not over yet.
Famed nobles of the demon world!
The Phenex family is honored by your attendance tonight.
We invited you all to share the historic moment in which I, Raiser Phenex,
and the heiress apparent of the Gremory family, Rias Gremory,
formally announce our intent to marry each other.
Without further ado, let me introduce...
my empress, Rias Gremory!
Issei!
President!
How dare you break in—
I'm Hyoudou Issei, a member of the
Kuou Academy Occult Research Club!
President Rias Gremory's virginity is mine!
What—How dare you?!
What is that man thinking?
Seize him!
Then why don't we join in?
Sure.
Roger.
Issei-kun, let us handle these guys.
You're late.
Kiba! Koneko-chan!
Oh my, you're finally here.
Akeno-san!
Go, Issei-kun.
Yes!
What's going on?
Rias-dono, what's happening?
A little entertainment I prepared.
Who is that?
Brother!
Does that mean...?
Sirzechs Lucifer-sama!
He's the demon lord?!
Sirzechs-sama, what do you mean by entertain—
Raiser-kun, the Rating Game
was very interesting to watch.
However, against my sister who was unexperienced and had half the pieces, it was a bit...
You have complaints about the fight?
Not at all.
The Rating Game itself would become meaningless if I did.
Not to mention, considering the circumstances involved this time,
my old family would be dishonored.
I wanted something flashy for my little sister's engagement party.
You, boy over there.
I wanted to see for myself the
power of the dragon you possess,
so I had Grayfia make arrangements.
I see. So basically...
Dragon versus phoenix.
Wielders of two legendary powers squaring off would make the party exciting, wouldn't it?
B-Brother!
As expected of the demon lord, that was a very interesting idea.
Dragon-user boy.
Y-Yes!
Would you like to show me and
the high-class nobles your power again?
Sure.
Issei, don't!
You'll be my last flame before I settle down as a married man.
All right, dragon-user boy.
What do you want as a reward for winning?
Sirzechs-sama, no need to reward a mere low-class demon!
He is a demon nonetheless.
We're asking him for a favor, so we
must reward him with fair compensation.
What do you desire?
Nobility?
Maybe a beautiful woman?
You may choose anything.
President...
No, Rias Gremory-sama...
give her back!
Then, begin.
President, I'll settle this in ten seconds!
Defeat my brother in ten seconds?
Is he insane?
Then I'll shut your impudent mouth in five,
in a way that it will never open again!
President, please give me permission to use promotion!
Issei, what are you planning to do?
Promotion! Queen!
It's no use!
President!
I don't have a talent for swordfighting like Kiba does.
I'm not a magic prodigy like Akeno-san, either.
I don't have super strength like Koneko-chan,
nor do I have a wonderful healing ability like Asia!
Still, I'll become the strongest pawn!
If it's for you, President,
I'll overthrow even God himself!
Glow, Over-boost!
Welsh Dragon Over-booster!
This is the power of the Emperor of Dragon:
Balance Breaker, Boosted Gear Scale Mail!
Balance Breaker?
A forbidden move?!
The forbidden...
diabolical magic.
Let's make a deal.
Interesting. Are you determined, boy?
Shut up! Are you doing it or not?
As I said, I'll make it worth the sacrifice.
However, remember one thing.
There will be a count to ten.
Your body won't stand it longer than that.
That's more than enough time to...
knock that fucker out!
Ten!
I'm right here!
Nine!
What's with this power and speed?
Damned, annoying brat!
You're just a monster right now, brat!
This is our clan's gallant hellfire of the phoenix, the firebird, the immortal bird!
Take it and incinerate!
Eight!
There's no way in hell your lame fire can burn me!
If it wasn't for this armor...
So this is his real power?
Seven!
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid of me?
You're just useless scum without your Boosted Gear!
Six!
Is that all you've—
Y-You bastard, what did you do?
A cross!
Five!
You have a cross?!
Our bishop used to be a nun, remember?
I borrowed one she had tucked away.
Looks like holy power boosted with
a Sacred Gear works even on you!
Four!
Impossible!
The cross severely damages a demon!
Even with that dragon armor, he shouldn't be able to hold—
Don't tell me you gave your entire arm to the dragon within it.
Three!
A dragon's arm doesn't suffer from a demon's weaknesses!
This arm is no longer mine.
Eh?
So... see?
I can even hold a cross.
Are you out of your mind?
You'll never get it back!
Two!
So what?!
He even sacrificed his own arm.
There's no way he'll lose!
He'll definitely win and bring President back!
One!
My arm is a small price to pay
if I can have the president back!
Count off!
Too bad. You ran out of time, boy.
Don't give me that crap! I was so close!
What do I need to sacrifice this time?!
My eye? My leg?
I'll give you anything!
Your basic physical strength is the limiting factor.
So it's because I'm weak?
Damn it! Why do I fail at such a critical moment?!
The moment the armor was disengaged,
I transferred some power to the jewel.
It won't last for long, so it's unable to counter Phenex's regenerative abilities.
But...
even so, I will...
never give up!
Well then, time to put you to sleep.
The ceremony will be over by the time you wake up.
Not yet.
How do you put out fire? With water!
Holy water?!
But holy water alone won't be enough to defeat Raiser.
Boosted Gear Gift!
Transfer!
Raiser's flame is...
The boosted holy water is diminishing his spirit and stamina rapidly.
Even the phoenix that rises again from the ashes can't recover instantly from mental damage.
Mental.
Mental. That is to say, his mind is not immortal.
Asia told me demons are weak
against crosses and holy water!
If I boosted and used both of them simultaneously,
it would inflict considerable damage to a demon!
Kiba told me to expand my vision and watch the opponent!
Transfer!
Akeno-san told me
to direct my body's aura to
one area to concentrate magic!
To focus my mind and feel the flow of magic!
Koneko-chan told me to aim for the
line of symmetry of the opponent's body
and try to deliver a deep, precise blow!
W-Wait!
Don't you understand that this marriage is
important to the future of the demon race?!
A kid like you who doesn't know anything shouldn't interfere!
I don't know or care about the complicated stuff!
But I fuzzily remember one thing from the time you defeated me and I lost consciousness!
President was crying!
That's enough of a reason for me to beat you up!
This can't...
be happening...
Brother!
If you have complaints, come at me!
I'm always willing to take you on!
Issei, you are...
You are so...
The match is over.
Thanks, Koneko-chan!
Good job.
You did it, Issei-kun.
Well...
Here goes.
There.
President!
Issei!
Thank you, Issei,
my Issei!
Wh-What is that?
A griffin.
Oh my.
Then why don't you escort the president back, Issei-kun?
M-Me?
Good idea.
Can you?
A-As you wish!
We'll be waiting in the club room!
That griffin was meant to help him
escape in the worst-case scenario, though.
That would have been a big problem.
My father and Sir Phenex seemed regretful.
Unfortunately, this engagement is as good as broken.
Is it really unfortunate?
Your facial expression tells me otherwise.
I did not imagine the Welsh Dragon
would come over to this world.
Perhaps the encounter with the white Vanishing Dragon is not too far into the future.
President!
You're an idiot.
You lost your arm for someone like me.
It was a good deal.
I was able take you back like this!
This time it may have been cancelled,
but another engagement proposal
can come in at any time.
Next time, it'll be my right arm.
Then my eye, I guess.
Issei!
I'll come save you, no matter how many times.
I'm Rias Gremory's pawn, after all!
saenai desho konnanja
The status quo is boring,
watashi kimi no haato wo shidou shichau yo
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
Transform!
Kaben Rider Pinky!
Morning stand up!
otenami haiken doryoku no seika wa
Let's see how much you have improved.
Naked soul, kakusei.
Naked soul, awaken!
That was my first kiss.
Japanese girls give it a lot of meaning, don't they?
heijoushin no pinchi ikinari de aseru
The sudden trouble makes me hurry.
Y-Yes, they do...
Wait, first kiss?!
gyakuten shiisoogeemu osarecha shaku da yo
Don't wanna lose! Turn around the seesaw game.
Was it really okay for me to have your first?
What you've done is just as valuable,
Don't you know? Baby
datte ima kyun to shite
I mean, I get angry at you sometimes,
so consider it a reward!
nandakanda yurushite shimau
but I always end up just letting it slide a little later.
This reward alone makes my hard work so worth it!
mitsumetara gyutto atsuku naru
My heart races when I'm watching you.
Also...
Yes!
I've decided to live at your house too.
kawatteiku no wakaru
I can feel myself changing.
Sorry?
I want to live closer to my servants.
konna toki wa nante ieba ii no
What am I supposed to say in this
situation?
shi shi shi thinking time
Quiet, it's thinking time!
matte matte yo
Give me a minute.
suki de seikai?
Is "I love you!" the right answer?
HURRY UP! ren'airyoku kyoukachuu
Gotta hurry up! I'm trying to become an expert at love,
resson wan kara susumenai
but I'm stuck at lesson one.
konomama ja kimi no koto
At this rate, I feel like
No, holy...
dareka ni torarechaisou
someone's gonna take you before I do.
Oh my.
taimingu wa kocchi de tsukuritai
I want to take initiative and get the timing right.
kono tsugi nante konai no
There won't be a second chance.
Run!
tsuishi kibou aitai ne
I want a supplementary exam. I want you!
Get those perverts!
STUDY X STUDY
Perverts!
motto shinakucha
Gotta study more!
Perverts!
BOY MEETS GIRL
zutto hitsuzen
We're bound by fate.
STUDY X STUDY
kyoukasho wa nai
There's no textbook.
BOY MEETS GIRL
oteage nante arienai
Give up? Never!
You idiot!
I wanted to protect her.
It wasn't for a contract or a covenant.
She needs to be there lofty and dignified
with her crimson hair waving in the air.
There's only one
that I admire.
It's her.