One hour until the game begins.
We're up against Phenex, so what?
Let's show them how strong Rias Gremory's household is.
I trained really hard!
I won't lose!
Issei-san, can I come in?
Go ahead.
Asia?
Those clothes...
I thought I'd wear a nun's attire
since the president told us to dress in
what we feel most comfortable.
Yeah, that definitely fits you the best.
Um, can I stay by your side?
Oh, feel free to.
Asia?
A scary fight is about to begin, right?
Yeah.
But I'll be fine as long as you're with me!
Can I always be by your side from now on?
Yeah, we'll be always together.
It's time! Are you ready?
W-Wake up or—
Let's go, Asia.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 10 "The Decisive Battle Is Starting!"
It's not surprising
that you ladies are so composed.
Excuse us.
Good evening, Sona.
Welcome!
The student council president and vice-president.
Why?
Rating Games are broadcast to members of both families.
They are responsible for it.
I see.
I volunteered for the task.
It's your first game, after all.
I'll show you a fight that won't insult our rivalry.
Everyone, are you prepared?
Yes, anytime.
When it's about to start, you will be teleported to the battlefield.
Battlefield?
An alternate space created just for this game.
It's disposed of after each game,
so you can run wild all you want.
W-Wild, huh?
I will be going back to the student
council room to manage the broadcast.
I wish you the best of luck, Rias.
Thank you, but make the broadcast fair, okay?
Of course.
I do not expect an even match against him, however.
By the way, the demon lord Lucifer
will be watching this fight as well.
I see.
My brother is also...
Did you just say "brother"?
Did I hear it wrong?
No, her brother is the demon lord.
The demon lord?!
Your brother is the demon lord?!
Yes.
Sirzechs Lucifer, known as the Crimson Satan.
That's her brother.
Sirzechs-sama succeeded the previous demon lord Lucifer-sama that passed away in the war.
So that's why the President became the heiress of the Gremory family!
So that's what it was.
I'm the daughter of the Gremory house.
The name Gremory follows me everywhere.
It's about time.
Let's go!
Huh?
Nothing changed.
Did the teleportation fail?
Did I screw up again?
Everyone...
I am Grayfia, servant of the Gremory family,
appointed judge between the Gremory and Phenex families.
Taking Rias-sama and Raiser-sama's opinions into consideration,
we prepared a replica of Kuou Academy,
the school Rias-sama attends in the human world, as the battlefield.
A replica?
Take a look outside.
The sky is...
We're in an alternate universe.
With a replica of the entire school in it.
J-Just how amazing are the demons' powers?
Both parties have been teleported to their main base.
Rias-sama's main base is the Occult Research Club room in the old schoolhouse.
Tsubaki.
Yes.
Raiser-sama's main base is
the principal's office in the new schoolhouse.
Thus, pawns can be promoted when they manage to invade the enemy's schoolhouse.
So I just need to enter the new schoolhouse,
and the promotion will make me as powerful as a queen, the strongest piece!
Oh my. It won't be that easy.
Huh?
It also means their pawns can be
promoted if they enter this building.
You should expect the main base
to have the strongest defense.
You have a point.
What is this?
This is how we'll communicate on the battlefield.
So it's like a transceiver.
The game begins now!
They might be too weak for you,
but do not hold back!
Crush them completely.
The only reason we're playing this silly game is to break down that crimson-haired girl's pride.
The enemy's main base is the new schoolhouse.
It'd be quickest to cross the schoolyard, but...
...we'd be in plain sight.
Indeed, it's too risky.
Then maybe approach the new schoolhouse from the back, across the track field?
They are probably expecting that.
I expect a few of their nimble rooks and knights to be placed around this club house.
It's a classic but foolproof tactic.
President!
Why don't we take the gym first, which is near both the old and the new schoolhouse?
It's pretty close to our base and
would help keep the enemies in check.
The gym is like the center of a chessboard.
Taking it first would give us a tactical advantage.
It's decided then.
It's indoors, so a rook's power would be better suited than a knight's mobility.
Fighting is difficult, isn't it?
Well, we just need to believe in
the president and follow her orders.
You're right.
First, we need to secure the defensive line.
Yuuto, Koneko, go set up traps in the forest.
Yes, ma'am!
Roger.
Come, Shiro.
We'll be going, then.
Akeno, once the traps are set, use illusionary magic on the forest and the sky above it.
As you wish.
Um, President, what should we do?
You're recovery and support, Asia,
so be on standby with me here.
It'd be pointless for you to go and get knocked out.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
As for Issei...
Yes!
Lie down here.
C-Could that be the legendary...
s-so-called lap pillow?
Hurry up.
P-Please take good care of me!
What an amazing sensation!
It's so rich and so tender, yet it envelopes me in a...
But we're in the middle of an important game!
This is unbelievable!
Come on, why are you crying?
I can't believe I'm resting my head on your lap!
I'm moved to tears and they won't stop flowing!
I'm glad I was born!
You're exaggerating.
I can always be your lap pillow again.
Really?!
As I said, calm down and stop sniveling.
Issei, I'll release the spell cast upon you, just a little.
All right, let's go there next.
Now, go.
I feel new power flowing within my body!
Remember I told you I spent eight pawns to resurrect you?
Y-Yes.
Right after resurrection your body couldn't handle all that power.
So I locked it up in multiple layers of spells.
I just released a small part of it.
Then the power I'm feeling right now is...
It's your inherent power.
To fully acquire it, you need Boosted Gear and a tough body to withstand it.
You're still not there, though.
So that's what that intense training was about.
Sorry for thinking of you as a monster!
I'm so terrible!
I didn't know that's what you were doing!
Lord, forgive me for being jealous a minute ago!
Listen, Issei.
Defeat your opponent, even if it's a girl.
Don't hold back.
They won't be holding back either.
I got it.
I promise to bring you victory!
Yes, I'm expecting much from you, my adorable Issei.
President, can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
The preparations are complete.
Ouch!
Then here's the game plan.
Rias-sama has begun to move.
Since she lacks manpower, it's impossible for her to defend the base perfectly.
Knowing that, a quick attack is probably the only choice.
Listen. You won't be able to avoid
a battle once you enter the gym.
Make sure you follow my orders.
Roger.
Yuuto, are you ready?
Everything's looking good.
Akeno, please be ready and await the right moment.
Yes, President.
Commence operation!
My lovely servants,
our opponent is Raiser Phenex, a man considered a promising talent even among the immortal Phenex!
Now, let's kick his ass!
Issei-san, everyone, good luck!
Wow, even the interior looks identical.
Enemies.
I know you're there, Gremory servants.
Sneaking in is useless, huh?
The rook and the unusually spirited pawn, huh?
Though, Mira defeated you instantly.
It's that girl!
I'm Mira, a pawn.
I'm Xuelan, a rook.
I'm Il, a pawn!
I'm Nel, also a pawn!
That rook's level is quite high.
High?
Her combat ability alone may be at the level of a queen.
Seriously?
Well, it's not like we didn't know we'd be at a disadvantage.
We can't back out now!
Boost!
I will handle the rook.
Issei-senpai, please take the pawns.
At least run and keep them busy.
Don't worry about me.
We have a good chance of winning!
All right, let's go!
I knew they'd attack the center first.
Tell me how the other team's doing.
Yes.
Three pawns, Schlia, Marion, and
Bulent, are attempting infiltration.
It's getting really foggy.
A trap?
Nothing I can't handle.
This is child's play.
It's a cute trap you'd expect from a beginner.
Koneko-chan!
Not bad—
Who the hell are you?!
Rias-sama's servant.
Rip it, rip it apart!
Running won't save you!
We're gonna disassemble you!
Don't say stuff like that with such a cheerful voice!
Rip it, rip it apart!
Also, I don't want to get disassembled!
What?!
I dodged it this time!
Rip it, rip it apart!
But I'm managing!
This is pissing me off!
Why can't we get him?!
I trained pretty damn hard, you know?
I'll disappoint the president and
the team if I get knocked out so quickly!
Boost!
Let's go, Boosted Gear!
Explosion!
Huh?
You guys are first!
One!
Two!
Got you!
My stick?
That hurt.
But now I'm set!
If we lose to a man like this...
...Raiser-sama will be angry at us!
Unforgivable!
We're seriously gonna rip you apart!
Now's my chance!
Take this!
My special technique!
Dress
Break.
No!
How was that?
I kept imagining myself blasting away the girls' clothes.
Yes, I kept imagining it for a long time
and used all of my magical talent to make girls naked!
This is my special technique, Dress Break!
How vulgar.
He must have planted his imagination with magic on the girls when he came in contact with them.
I give him points for originality, though.
You're terrible!
You beast!
You enemy of women!
Asia!
I did it!
Issei-san?
Th-This is...
Sorry, Asia, one more time!
Okay, let me go change then!
Y-You did it!
No, it's no good if it only rips the clothes!
Sorry for making you go through this.
I don't mind!
I have plenty of hand-me-down clothes!
Issei-san, please do your best!
It's all thanks to you, Asia!
I'm disappointed in you.
Koneko-chan!
You brought down their rook?!
You're good!
Koneko, Issei, how's the situation?
President!
We're both fine.
Actually, it's pretty nice here.
I'm glad to hear that.
Akeno is ready to make her move now.
Please continue with the plan.
Are you running away?!
The match hasn't been decided yet!
You're abandoning this strategic location?!
Take.
Raiser-sama's three pawns and a rook, knocked out.
A-Amazing!
Akeno-senpai is well known as the Priestess of Thunder.
I heard that those who know her are aware of her alias and immense powers.
The Priestess of Thunder, huh?
I'd die for sure if she punished me with something like that.
She destroyed the strategic
location, using an offensive move.
A very bold tactic for a first timer, as one would expect of Rias.
But wouldn't this force Raiser-sama to go all out for the game?
I'm afraid so.
The real challenge begins now.
We're still outnumbered.
It'll take some time for Akeno to be ready to fire another shot.
We'll join you on the battlefield as soon as she recovers.
Until then, both of you should start getting ready for the plan's next phase.
The next phase is...
We're to meet up with Yuuto-senpai around the track field, and annihilate the enemies in the area.
I wonder if Kiba is all right?
Do they seriously think traps like this can protect them?
That must be their main base!
What just happened?
Too bad.
You can't get out of here anymore.
You're inside a barrier that our queen created.
Shoot, we were distracted by the traps and didn't notice!
We need clever tricks to overcome our lack of manpower.
I don't want to say this since you're actually my type,
but do you really think you'll
defeat the three of us on your own?
Want to give it a try?
Well, knowing him, he's probably doing just fine with a handsome smile.
Koneko-chan, we should go too.
Don't touch me.
Don't worry. I'm not going to use it on a teammate!
Still, that is a terrible technique.
Looks like she's seriously hating me for that.
Wait, Koneko-chan!
Koneko-chan!
Koneko! What happened to Koneko?!
Respond, Issei!
Rias, don't underestimate me...
Raiser Phenex.
Take.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
Ruin Princess, Twilight Healing,
Princess of Thunder,
Sword Birth,
and Boosted Gear.
Those are quite fancy names, but we are Phenex, the immortal!
Episode 11 "We're Right in the Middle of the Big Match!"