It's red...
just like the color of her hair.
It's red.
Her hair is more crimson than strawberry blonde;
the same color is coating my hands.
The beautiful red of that long hair means it's indeed her.
Devote your life to me.
Episode 1 "I Got a Girlfriend!"
I wanna squeeze some boobs.
I agree with Hyoudou Issei-kun!
Stop saying that. You're making me feel empty.
Matsuda, Motohama,
why did we enroll in this school?
This private school, Kuou Academy, just turned coed after being an all-girls school.
Thus, the school has an overwhelming girls to boys ratio,
and many beautiful girls from overseas are attending it!
Which makes us boys valuable.
That means, we'll be popular without having to lift a finger!
You basically can't mess up!
In short, we'll get a harem!
Yes, a successful life full of real boobs awaits us!
Fight on! Fight on!
Or so we thought.
It's spring, we're in the second year,
and we still haven't had a single girlfriend.
Stop saying that. You're making me feel empty.
You lose the moment you give up!
We still have a chance!
Kiba-kun!
What are you doing next?
Hey, how about going to karaoke with us?
Sorry, but I have club activities now.
That's too bad!
Thanks for inviting me, though. I'm really sorry.
Kiba Yuuto of Class 2-C.
He's an idol to all the girls in the school...
...and the enemy of all boys, us included!
Damn it!
It's ridiculous how he's getting all the girls just because he's a little handsome, pretty smart, and good-natured!
Stop saying that. You're making me feel empty.
It's such an unfair world.
Oh, it's almost time!
Where are you going?
Murayama's boobs are so big!
She's 82-70-81.
Katase has great legs!
She's 78.5-65-79.
I miraculously found this spot during PE!
Hey!
Let me see too!
Don't keep it all to yourselves!
Damn you!
Is someone outside?
You...!
What the hell?
Hey, Matsuda, Motoha...ma...
You again?
This is bad.
W-Wait.
Hyoudou, you pervert!
They seriously hit me with their bamboo swords.
Unlucky for you, Issei.
You left me behind!
I wouldn't complain if I had at least seen some boobs,
but I wasn't even looking and they still—
So, there are actually people in the old schoolhouse, huh?
That red hair is so nice.
Rias Gremory.
She's 99-58-90
and has been the president of the Occult Research Club for three years running.
Rumor says her family comes from Northern Europe.
That kid just now...
Sorry?
I mean the kid in the middle.
He's in class 2-B.
If I recall correctly, his name is Hyoudou.
What about him?
Never mind. I was probably just seeing things.
Checkmate.
Oh my.
It was an easy problem.
I did raise the difficulty quite a bit, though.
You did?
I hope the next one will be harder.
My school life's so bleak.
Will my time at the academy be wasted without a single chance to get some boobs in my hands?
U-Um...
You're Hyoudou Issei-kun from Kuou Academy,
aren't you?
Yes?
I've never seen that uniform before.
I wonder what school she's from.
She's so cute!
Um...
C-Can I help you?
Well...
Hyoudou-kun, are you seeing anyone at the moment?
N-Not really.
I'm glad to hear that!
Huh?
U-Um, would you mind going out with me?
What did you say just now?
I've always seen you pass by here and... well...
I knew you were my...
H-Hey, is this...?
P-Please...
Please go out with me!
A-Are you serious!?
Wake up. Wake up!
I-If you don't wake up, I-I'll kiss you!
Wake—
Wh-What!?
Why!?
This is Amano Yuuma-chan.
These are my friends, Matsuda and Motohama.
Nice to meet you.
And she's my...
girlfriend.
Well, you guys should get one soon too!
Let's go, Yuuma-chan.
Okay!
Th-That traitor!
A date?
Yeah, this coming Sunday. Or is that a bad time?
N-Not at all! Of course it's fine!
That's great!
See you.
All right! See you later.
I'm looking forward to our date!
Yeah, me too.
A date, a date!
It has such a nice ring to it!
Awesome!
I see.
As expected, your intuition...
...was right on the money, hm?
I made the correct choice by having you watch him.
President, what would you like to do?
I'll make some preliminary preparations,
but in the end, it all depends on him.
She's a bit late.
Please check us out!
I didn't mean to take one.
We grant
your wish.
"We grant your wish"?
That sounds like a scam.
Issei-kun!
Good morning, Yuuma-chan!
Sorry. Did I keep you waiting?
Oh no, I just got here.
I always wanted to say that!
If I hear the
Way in the
morning I am
content even
to die in
that evening.
If I hear the
Way in the
morning I am
content even
to die in
that evening.
What's the matter?
Are you all right?
We had a lot of fun today!
Yeah, it was a great day!
Th-This is my big chance.
I did it!
Say, Issei-kun.
Do you mind doing me a favor to commemorate our first date?
C-Could she be asking for a ki...
Wh-What kind of favor?
Could you die, please?
What?
Wait, you...
Huh?
Sorry, Yuuma-chan. Can you repeat that?
I think there's something wrong with my ears.
Could you die, please?
I see them!
I definitely saw them!
It was only for an instant, but I saw real boobs!
I've seen my first real-life boobs!
And such a cute girl's, too!
Isn't this what people call an exhibition?
No, not that.
This isn't the time for that.
Wings?
Although short-lived, playing
innocent lovey-dovey with you was fun.
I'll take good care of this gift from you.
So...
Yuuma-chan?
...please die.
Sorry, your existence poses a threat to us.
So we took the initiative and moved in for the kill.
Blame God for planting a Sacred Gear inside your body.
Sa... What?
Thanks for the wonderful memories.
Seriously?
I'm going to die in this tiny, little park because
of the bizarre thing that just happened?
If you were going to kill me, you could've
at least let me squeeze your boobs.
I could only catch a glance, but Yuuma-chan has great boobs.
It's red.
Red, just like the color of her hair.
Her hair is more crimson than strawberry blonde;
the same color is coating my hands.
What am I saying?
I'm about to die.
It's hopeless. Damn it.
I can't move my body at all.
I don't even know why I have to die.
But really, I lived such a crappy life.
If I could be born again, I... I...
Rias-senpai... Her alluring red hair...
If I'm to die anyway, I want to die in the bosom of a beautiful girl like her.
You called me, didn't you?
Wh-Who's that?
If you're dying anyway, I'll take you.
Wings again.
You will...
devote your life to me.
Wake up or I'll kill you.
Wake up if you don't want to be killed.
Wake—
I feel so heavy.
This thing gave me such a weird dream.
A dream?
You really don't remember Yuuma-chan?
I told you I don't know a girl with that name.
Like we said, you never introduced a girl like that to us, and there's just no way you got a girlfriend!
It's just not possible!
I have her mail address right he—
I don't!
Yuuma-chan's phone number and address...
are both gone.
Rias-senpai!
Really?
It's Rias-senpai!
She's as wonderful as always.
She's so beautiful!
Yeah, that air of refinement, which makes her seem unapproachable, is just amazing!
I bet you got a little crazy because of all your perverted fantasies.
I'm not like you! I swear I—
Whatever. Stop by my place today.
We'll enjoy my special collection together!
Porn DV—
Those guys are despicable.
They only think about dirty things.
I hate them.
Perverts.
What I mean is, I got some
freshly released "gentleman's discs".
Oh, that sounds awesome!
Issei, this time you can set aside fantasies for true erotica.
That is...
Transform!
It's Momo-chan's new work, Kaben Rider Pinky!
Quite an ordeal to procure.
Something's definitely off.
Is it even possible for a few days worth of memories to be a dream?
If so, what happened to my real memories from those days?
Hey!
What's wrong, Issei?
You're a Momozono Momo fan, aren't you?
Yeah.
Ah, right, let's turn off the lights for a more intense feel.
Typhoon Lick!
Oh, that looks better!
Doesn't it?
Amazing riding action as expected from the Rider!
Hey, they're not off.
Huh? What did you say?
The lights aren't off.
What?
What the hell are you talking about?
No, that's not it.
The lights are off.
I don't sense light.
But I can see it.
I'm seeing it.
Sorry.
I'm going home.
What, you feeling ill or something?
I can see more clearly than I could during daytime.
And, for some reason, I feel like there's
a kind of power flowing through my body.
No, buy me one!
I'll leave you here if you keep whining!
No!
How can I hear things from that far away!?
What happened to me?
My body is acting strangely.
This park...
Yeah, it was right here.
I was here with Yuuma-chan on a date.
Yuuma-chan...
I don't want to believe it was merely a dream.
What was that?
How unfortunate.
What's going on? I can't stop trembling.
It might just be my lucky day to meet your kind in such a place.
I was going to step back just a little!
Running away?
I have no idea what's happening!
Feathers?
Yuuma-chan?
This is why low-level creatures are so troublesome.
A-Am I dreaming again?
I cannot sense the presence of either a master or mate.
You aren't trying to escape nor are you expanding a magic circle.
Analysis of the situation suggests you must be a stray.
Then I can just kill you.
If I had to dream again, I would've liked a beautiful girl a billion times better than a guy like that!
It hurts.
It seriously hurts.
It wasn't this bad when Yuuma-chan...
It hurts, doesn't it?
Light is a deadly poison to your species, after all.
I thought that would finish you off, but you're quite resilient.
Worry not. I will put you to rest soon.
It's hopeless now.
Someone... help me!
Did you do that?
Guess not.
Don't lay a finger on that kid.
Red hair...
R-Rias-senpai...
Who the hell are you?
Damn you!
Red hair... I see.
You must be from the Gremory family.
I'm Rias Gremory. How are you today, my dear fallen angel?
Oh, wow.
Who knew this was the jurisdiction of the Gremory family's heiress apparent?
Is he of your household?
I will not show mercy if you mess with him.
Well, I apologize for today,
but you'd better not let your menservants run free.
Someone like me might just hunt
them down during his walk, you know?
Thank you for the most helpful advice.
Then let me give you a warning too:
I will not let you off scot-free should you do something like this again.
Same to you, heiress apparent of the Gremory family.
My name is Donnasiege.
Hope we never face each other again.
I was careless. Who knew he'd come into contact with a fallen angel?
He'll die at this rate.
I won't let him die.
After all, he's my...
Master, please wake up!
Master—
I feel so heavy.
I had a weird dream again.
Why is this happening night after—
Huh? Why am I naked?
Where's my underwear?
Rias-senpai!?
It's morning?
B-Boobs!
Good morning.
U-Um, Rias-senpai, wh-why are you...?
Wait, is this a dream?
Right, I'm still dreaming!
Everything you experienced was real.
I am Rias Gremory,
a demon.
A-A demon?
And your master.
Nice to have you, Hyoudou Issei-kun.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Next Episode
Imagine the strongest being that comes to mind.
I will become the Harem King instead!
Grant me power!
Well, I got myself a silly little brother.
I Quit Being a Human!