Damn it!
Was that Raiser's queen?!
I'm sorry.
Koneko-chan!
I wish I could 've been of more help to the president.
Don't worry.
Asia will heal your injuries in no time—
Koneko-chan!
Koneko—
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 11 "We're Right in the
Middle of the Big Match!"
Rias-sama's rook, retired.
Damn it!
How dare you do that to Koneko-chan?!
Come down here!
I'll fight you!
Calm down, Issei.
Those who are rendered unable to fight are teleported outside and treated.
Koneko didn't die.
You need to stay calm!
But...!
Give it up, boy.
No matter how hard you fight,
you can't win against us.
Oh my.
Akeno-san!
Issei-kun,
I'll deal with her, so hurry along.
You need not worry.
I will avenge Koneko-chan with all my might.
Okay, Akeno-san!
I wanted to fight you someday, Priestess of Thunder.
Oh my, I am quite honored,
Bomb Queen.
Raiser-sama's three pawns, retired.
Three?!
Hey.
Oh, it's you.
Those three just now...
Thanks to Akeno-san's barrier,
it was pretty easy to beat them.
With this, the number of remaining pieces is nine for Raiser-sama
and five for Rias-sama.
We can't predict the winner yet.
Kiba, sorry. Koneko-chan was...
I heard.
She's usually not that outgoing,
but she seemed pretty excited today.
It's a pity.
Let's win this, no matter what!
Of course.
Yuuto, Issei, can you hear me?
Asia and I will launch a surprise attack on their main base,
so distract as many enemies as possible to buy us some time.
A surprise attack?
I don't have any other choice.
The plan was to wait for Akeno to recover and destroy each building individually,
but that won't work since he's already brought out his queen.
But, President, it's way too risky for the king to leave the base!
The enemy must be thinking the same.
That's what I'm going for.
Phenex's body might be immortal, but his mind is not.
If I deliver an attack strong enough
to make him lose his fighting spirit,
I can win.
I'll break down Raiser's spirit myself!
If that's the plan
why doesn't the Occult Research Club's male duo...
...show them what they're made of?
You're all hiding, aren't you?!
Fight us fair and square!
I'm Raiser-sama's knight, Carlamain.
You must be out of your mind
to come at me directly.
However, I like idiots like you!
I'm Rias-sama's knight, Kiba Yuuto.
I was looking forward to cross swords with a fellow knight!
Well said, Rias Gremory's knight!
Amazing!
Does this mean I don't have anything to do here?
Not necessarily.
All Carlamain thinks of all day is
swords, swords, and more swords.
She seemed upset about
sacrificing some pieces too.
What an unbelievably unrefined girl.
And when I thought I finally found a cutie,
it turns out he's another sword freak.
My goodness, how unfortunate.
He's using all his remaining pieces to deal with us!
President's prediction was spot on.
But really, Rias-sama seems to have
a strange taste in men.
A cute character with a sharp tongue?!
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
Oh, excuse me, but I'm not fighting.
What?!
Isabella.
I am Isabella, Raiser-sama's rook.
Here I come,
Rias Gremory's pawn!
Hey, who the hell is she?!
What does she mean she isn't fighting?!
She's in the game as a bishop,
but she is more or less just a spectator!
The hell is that?
She—I mean that Miss, is Ravel Phenex.
Phenex?!
Although considered a subordinate serving under Raiser-sama, she's actually his little sister.
His little sister?!
Ever heard of little sister moe?
Many guys dream of it and envy it.
Though, I'm not one of them.
So she's just my subordinate as a formality.
So he said!
So that bird bastard really is a pervert and an idiot?!
But I can understand why he'd
want a little sister in his harem.
You're not as bad as I thought.
Well, I didn't train with Koneko-chan and Kiba for nothing!
But until I build up enough power, all I can do is run away—
Boost!
That was the fifth power-up.
It might've been enough to win against a pawn,
but not against a rook!
Oh, you're completely different
from the time Mira defeated you.
It looks like Rias Gremory trained you well.
You bet!
I, the president's subordinate,
was trained intensively by her!
That's why I can't lose!
I'll defeat you for her sake!
I was waiting.
Rias, my love!
My Holy Eraser!
Unfortunately, that attack doesn't work on me.
Then how about this?
Freeze!
Damn you!
You have two Sacred Gears?!
No matter!
We, proud members of the Phenex family,
control flame, wind, and life!
You lose!
How many Sacred Gears do you have?!
I don't have multiple Sacred Gears.
I'm just making them.
I create magic swords with Sword Birth.
In other words...
I can create any magic sword I want!
This is...!
Amazing.
I didn't know he had such power.
Hey you!
We're fighting! Pay attention!
Damn it! It's almost ready, though.
Boost!
Finally!
Explosion!
Not exactly Dragon Wave, but take a Dragon Shot!
Just kidding...
I saved quite a bit of energy for that one.
That Sacred Gear is dangerous!
I need to defeat you here and now!
Gotcha!
That was so weak!
Burst it open, Dress Break!
What is this?!
Name and save it to the gentleman's
folder on my neural hard disk!
Saved!
All right, here it goes!
Isabella was...!
Raiser-sama's rook, retired.
I won!
Still, that's a terrible technique.
Or rather, a terrifying one for a woman.
That was my first time seeing it,
but how should I put it?
I apologize for the fact he is such a pervert.
Hey! Don't apologize bluntly like that, Kiba—
But...
Hey, you warrior over there!
Can you tell what that is?
President!
It's too early to go for a direct attack!
Did he see through our plan?
You knew I'd come, didn't you?
A virgin like you shouldn't
underestimate my experience, Rias.
You're as vulgar as usual.
Ruin Princess, Twilight Healing,
Princess of Thunder,
Sword Birth,
and Boosted Gear.
Those are quite fancy names,
but we are Phenex, the immortal.
We're immortal!
Do you see now that there's no hope for your team?
Ni!
Ri!
I bet these pawns are stronger than you expect.
Boosted Gear!
Boost!
That was a horrible technique!
You're stupid for letting
your sexual desires drive you!
Get him, Siris!
I can't handle this!
Issei-kun!
President!
Let me have some more fun.
I want to enjoy this premarital foreplay, you know?
Don't be ridiculous!
President!
I'm all right.
You should worry about your own opponent!
But...!
I believe in you, Issei!
Show them what one of Rias Gremory's...
subordinates can do!
That's right!
I'm her subordinate!
He stopped Siris's sword!
With his arm?!
I don't need to think!
I am here for the president's sake alone...
to kick your asses!
What?!
Emperor of Red Dragon,
if you can hear me, respond!
Lend me your power!
Dragon Booster!
I need more! Feel the intense emotion in me!
Boosted Gear!
Dragon Booster Second Liberation!
What's this?!
I-It transformed?
P-Priestess of Thunder, you're indeed formidable.
But your magic is already depleted.
Worry not.
I'll recover after a short rest.
I'm not sure if you'll have time to rest.
That is...
You fell for it.
I see.
This is my new power!
Kiba, liberate your Sacred Gear!
Liberate?
Hurry up!
Sword Birth!
Transfer!
I lose.
Raiser-sama's three pawns,
two knights, and a bishop, retired.
He boosted the knight's ability
with his Boosted Gear?
Emperor of Red Dragon
granted him a new ability:
Boosted Gear Gift!
Rias-sama's queen, retired.
Akeno-san?
Akeno.
Akeno-san was...
Looks like you lost your much-boasted right-hand woman.
I still have Yuuto and Issei!
You wish.
I can't believe Akeno-san was defeated!
Kiba!
Take.
You again!
Rias-sama's knight, retired.
Yuuto!
Resign already, Rias!
As if I would!
You still can't tell?
You'll just end up injuring that bishop and your cute little pawn.
Issei-san!
That took you a while, Yubelluna.
That queen was strong, just as rumored.
I had to resort to this, as expected.
It's still a victory.
I knew I could count on you.
Then...
What is that bottle?
Phenex's tears.
A treasure of my family that can instantly cure any wound completely.
That's cheating!
Oh, we are allowed to use it up to two times in the game.
You have a bishop with Twilight Healing, too.
It's an expensive item that
only my family can make.
Immortality and these tears have brought the Phenex family only fortune since the Rating Game began!
H-Hey, don't ignore me!
I demand promotion.
Give me a queen's power!
Wait for me.
I swear you'll attain victory, President!
President, Hyoudou Issei has arrived!
Issei!
Issei-san!
I'll handle the pawn boy and the bishop girl.
No, I'll deal with all of them.
They'll get a clue this way.
Don't be silly.
You need to defeat me first!
Resign already, Rias!
It's over now.
I read through all your moves.
Checkmate.
Shut up, Raiser!
Checkmate? Read my moves?
Don't make me laugh.
I, the king, am still standing!
I have no choice, then. Do that.
Yes, sir.
Asia!
That was such an intense fight,
yet you survived and made it this far.
I promised, remember?
Yes.
Thank you. You're our lifeline.
Please step back.
Asia! Issei!
Are you all right?
Asia is...
She isn't injured.
She just lost consciousness due to the shock.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect that boy
to shield her with his body.
It doesn't matter.
She can't use Twilight Healing now.
You fucker!
Even after taking my shot directly...
He has a queen's defensive ability now.
Promotion saved him.
President, we're still fighting, right?
Yes.
I'm an idiot, so I don't know what
checkmate or reading moves means,
but I can still fight!
As long as I can form my fist, I can fight!
Well said, Issei.
Let's defeat Raiser together!
Yes, President!
Just wait, Asia.
We'll win and go back together.
Boost.
Boost!
All right!
One more boost!
Boost!
Burst!
Issei!
Boosted Gear places immense physical burden on the host,
incomparable to other kinds of Sacred Gear.
Perhaps I should say it is a miracle he managed to withstand so many rounds of power boosts.
His magic was already depleted when he took Yubelluna's attack directly.
Issei!
His body is already over its limit.
It's over.
Raiser!
Rias!
Even you don't have that much magic left.
Be honest and admit your loss.
How about you resign now?
As if I would!
I'm all right, President!
I'll do everything I can to win!
I'll become the strongest pawn!
I promised you!
You trained me, too!
You're almost dead!
I can still fight!
I'll keep my promise!
Issei!
I'll fight.
I'm your pawn.
I can still fight.
I'll win!
Issei, step back!
Step back!
If...
Issei! Obey my order!
it's for your smile...
I'd love you regardless of rank and name.
Rias-senpai, you're my number one.
Issei, you're so...
You annoy me!
You're a mere subordinate,
yet you so firmly oppose me, Raiser Phenix!
Raiser, what are you trying to do?
You know what! I'll respect his feelings and burn him down...
so that he'll be beyond treatment.
Deaths that occur during a Rating Game are considered accidents, after all!
You bastard!
You!
Issei!
Please! Stop, Raiser!
I lost.
I'm resigning.
Checkmate.
President...
Why...?
Rias-sama's resignation confirmed.
Raiser Phenex-sama wins this game.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
It's supposed to be an engagement party,
but this looks more like a wedding dress.
I'm weak.
Why am I so weak?
...my empress, Rias Gremory!
Episode 12 "I'm Here to Keep My Promise!"
It's not over yet.