A blonde girl's sparkling whites!
This is a rare, no, a super rare sight!
Wait, this isn't the time for that.
A-Are you all right?
Thank you.
She's cute.
U-Um...
S-Sorry!
One sec.
She's just my type!
Version: Blonde Beauty!
Thank you very much!
Oh, you're very welcome.
I've got to keep this conversation going.
Let's see... something to say...
Well, the weather's really nice today and...
I sound like an old woman!
Um, I...
I got lost and need help.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 3 "I Got a Friend!"
Are you on a trip?
Oh, no.
I was appointed to this town's church.
You're a nun, huh?
That explains the look.
I'm so glad I met such a nice person like you.
It must've been divine guidance.
Well...
What's the matter?
Well, nothing.
What was that feeling?
U-Um...
Don't cry; it's just a scrape. You're a boy, after all.
H-His wound...
Huh? I felt a sharp pain just now.
Look! Your wound's gone!
It's all right now.
Sorry, force of habit.
I felt it in my left hand.
That must mean—
I must've surprised you.
Oh...
Well, you have a pretty amazing power!
It's a wonderful power granted by God.
Yes, a wonderful power...
Oh, that must be the place!
Oh, yeah, it's the only church we have in town.
Great!
Thank you so much!
B-But I haven't seen anyone over there.
I'd like to return the favor, so would you like to accompany me?
Oh no, I've got something to do.
I see.
My name is Asia Argento.
Please call me Asia!
I'm Hyoudou Issei.
You can call me Issei.
Issei-san!
I'm so happy to have met someone as kind as you this quickly after arriving in Japan!
Ah, well...
Please visit the church when you find the time.
Promise me!
Yeah, okay.
See you around.
Yes, I hope so.
She's a really good girl.
Don't go near the church ever again.
Churches are hostile territory to us demons.
You'll incite fights between God and us demons just by stepping in there.
And you don't know when those guys will throw a light-lance at you.
S-Seriously?
Then the chill I got near the church was...
Your demonic instincts must've detected danger.
Staying around someone from the Church is inviting death.
Especially since some of the Church's exorcists even wield Sacred Gear.
Issei.
Y-Yes!
To exorcise a demon means to annihilate him completely.
Into nothingness. You turn into nothing.
You feel nothing.
You can do nothing.
Do you know how that's like?
N-No.
Sorry if I sounded too upset.
Anyhow, be careful from now on.
I will.
It feels like all I've accomplished is getting yelled at by the president.
Sorry, Asia.
I don't think I can fulfill our promise.
The president is looking out for you, Issei-kun.
Akeno-san!
Akeno, I thought you already went back.
The archduke just sent us a message.
The archduke?
Apparently, a stray demon is on the loose in this town.
It used to be a servant to another demon.
Like us?
Sometimes, demons betray or kill their masters, so they can live doing whatever they please.
That's what we call a stray demon.
We're headed to a deserted house. A stray demon is said to lure people into it to eat them.
E-Eat them!?
Tonight's mission is to bring it down.
You shall see the utter monstrosity stemming from abuse of demonic power and being without a master.
Issei.
Oh, yes, President!
Do you know chess?
Chess? You mean the board game?
I, the master, am the king.
There's the queen,
the knights,
the rooks,
the bishops,
and the pawns.
Demons from the aristocracy assign the traits of these pieces to their subordinates.
"Traits of the pieces"?
We call them Evil Pieces.
Why would you need to do that?
Anyway, for tonight, observe closely how demons fight.
Y-Yes.
She's here.
I smell something bad.
At the same time, I also smell something delicious!
Will it be sweet?
Or will it be bitter?
Boobs!
Stray demon type: Visor.
Nefarious beings that run away from their masters to fulfill their own desires.
They more than deserve death for their sins.
In the name of Duke Gremory,
I'll kick your ass!
What an insolent girl.
I will cover you in blood as red as your hair!
A line as witty as I'd expect from small fry.
Th-This is a stray demon?
She seems to be just an exhibitionist!
I told you.
They become ugly monsters in both body and heart.
She has such nice boobs, though. It's such a wast—
Huh?
Isn't that a magic circle!?
No joke! She is a monster!
Don't let your guard down.
Yuuto!
He disappeared!
He's so fast you can't see him.
Yuuto represents a knight,
so his trait is speed
and the sword his strongest weapon.
It's dangerous, Koneko-chan!
Die!
Don't worry.
Koneko is a rook.
Her traits are simple:
tremendous strength and defensive ability.
That kind of attack won't even scratch her.
Begone.
I should never fight with Koneko-chan.
Akeno!
Yes, President.
Oh my, what should I do?
President!
Sacred Gear!
Th-Thanks.
Oh, no problem. I instinctively...
Huh?
Akeno, finish her off.
A bad girl who tries to harm our president
needs to be punished!
She's the queen.
The almighty vice commander combining the powers of all other pieces.
Oh my, you still seem to have some energy left.
Then how about this?
She specializes in attacks using demonic powers.
On top of that, she is...
Oh my, you're still energetic!
...a complete sadist.
I wonder how long you can bear it.
She's laughing.
Akeno, that's enough.
We're already done?
That's a little disappointing.
Any last words?
Kill me.
Really?
Then you shall vanish.
Checkmate.
We're done.
Now, let's go back.
Yes, President!
U-Um, President!
What is it?
So what about me?
My piece... I mean, what's my role as a servant?
A pawn.
By "pawn," you don't mean...
Yes, Issei, you're a foot soldier.
A foot soldier?
The lowest rank?
No way!
To have servants, I need to be an upper-class demon.
Unlike the president, who was born as an upper-class demon,
those reborn as demons, like me, need to perform and get promoted.
But I'm a pawn, the weakest piece.
I'm just cannon fodder!
I've a long road ahead to become the Harem King.
The door was left open. That's dangerous.
Good evening!
I'm Gremory-sama's servant demon.
Is the client—
I just got a bad feeling.
Is anyone home?
Koneko was summoned by two people again.
Can you take care of one?
Sure, President.
Make sure to form a contract this time.
Don't let me down.
I won't.
If I just go back now, facing her will be really embarrassing.
I'm coming in!
Setting a nice mood, huh?
Excuse me!
Something's spilled...
This is...
What is this?
Punishment of the wicked.
I'm quoting the Holy Scripture here.
Well, well, if it isn't a demon.
My name is Freed Zelzan.
A young priest who's part of a certain exorcist organization!
A-A priest?
Well, I'm definitely not some worthless shit like a demon.
Is that your doing?
You're no longer human once you start depending on demons.
End of the road! The end!
That's why I killed him!
Getting rid of shitty demons and even more worthless shits bedeviled by them
is my job!
A light-sword?
I'll now stick this sword into your heart
and score a lovely headshot with this fabulous gun!
Bang!
An exorcist's golden bullet...
You like it?
Damn you!
Oh, demonic indeed!
Now that's more exciting to exorcise!
Three o'clock.
Is that look just for show?
I hate that the most!
Oh, Asia-chan, my assistant.
Are you done setting up the magical barrier?
Th-This is...
Oh, right, you're a beginner.
This is our job.
We kill off worthless people enchanted by demons, you see.
N-No way!
Issei-san?
Asia?
What? You know each other?
Why are you...?
Sorry. I'm... a demon.
A demon?
Issei-san is...?
I wasn't trying to fool you!
That's why I thought it'd be best if we never met again.
No way!
Unfortunately, Asia-chan,
demons and humans
are incompatible.
Not to mention we can't live without the protection of fallen angels.
Fallen angels?
Well, let's get this done now.
Are you ready?
Even if you aren't, here it comes!
Asia?
Come on! Are you serious?
Father Freed, I beg you!
Please forgive this one!
Let him go, please!
Do you know what you're saying?
He may be a demon, but Issei-san is a good person!
And God won't forgive you for such a deed!
Don't give me that crap!
Asia!
You fucking bitch!
Have you lost your mind?
Asia!
The fallen angel woman told me not to hurt you,
but I think you do need a little punishment!
Asia!
A chaste nun getting seriously fucked up by a priest.
Doesn't that sound fun?
Don't!
Stop it!
Wait, you've got to pay before you can watch, mister!
Let Asia go!
Seriously?
You want to fight me?
You'll suffer and die!
Issei-san, don't do it!
I have no chance in hell.
I might die here,
but I don't want to run after this girl tried to protect me,
you know!?
That hurts!
Interesting.
I'm gonna set the record for making the finest human mincemeat ever.
A magic circle?
Kiba!?
Hyoudou-kun, I'm here to help.
Oh my, look at that.
Exorcist.
You guys!
I see all the demons are here!
Sorry, but he's with us.
I like that!
So what?
You're a top and he's the bottom?
How vulgar. I can't believe you're a priest.
Don't pretend like you're refined, damned demon.
It's my purpose in life to hunt down maggots like you!
Just shut up and let me kill you!
Even us demons don't jump on just anyone.
I like your intense stare!
Could this be love?
Or intent to kill?
It's so exciting, no matter which side is doing the killing!
You should just disappear.
It seems you've been messing around with my adorable servant.
President!
Oh, are you the real deal?
Yes, yes, I've been messing around with him.
Got a problem with that?
Are you all right, Issei?
I'm sorry.
You just scolded me, but I did it again.
You're so beaten up.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know a stray exorcist was around.
I never noticed because there was a barrier set up until a little ago.
What are you doing, you bitch?
It's your job to take care of the barrier!
Asia!
It's my policy to show no mercy to anyone who hurts my servant.
In particular, I can't stand when a vulgar fiend like you damages my property.
You look pretty damn powerful.
I mean, this is pretty bad.
Multiple fallen angels.
I'm making a comeback!
You'll all vanish in light!
President?
Retrieving Issei is our priority for now.
Akeno, prepare a jump.
Affirmative.
Koneko, I'll leave Issei to you.
Sure.
Damn you demons, I won't let you go—
Hey! That hurts!
President!
We should take her too!
That is not possible.
Only members of my household can use this magic circle to jump.
N-No way!
Asia!
Let me go!
I need to save Asia!
Asia!
Issei-san, see you.
We'll see each other again.
Asia!
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
You'll just vanish.
Thanks for coming all the way out here!
Yes, we can enjoy this precious meeting only today.
Episode 4 "I'm Gonna Save My Friend!"
As a man, I gotta be able to protect my friends!