I'll kill you...
for what you did to them!
That's the spirit!
Come and kill me,
Nagisa-kun!
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
We've got a lot of potential
potential takai
It's just that we're not trying
hodo mendokusai
We had that dropouts' mentality
dropout mentality
No matter the unusual situation we were in
hinichijou wo ryougashi
We pretended to doze off
bokura wa utatanegao shite
While holding on to a hidden knife
knife kakushimotta
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
We didn't really feel invested in the job
doko ka taningoto datta
But now
dakedo
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
As long as we challenge you, it's fifty-fifty
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu kagiri kanousei wa half and half
kiritsu rei lock on
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
A revolution!
revolution
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
Episode
Nagisa
Time
Nagisa...
snapped!
Sure, we'd all like to kill that rotten son of a bitch.
but Nagisa might just go through with it!
No! You have to stop—
Don't be gettin' cocky, Nagisa!
I saw the pitiful way you looked at me when that medicine got blown up!
Quit worryin' about other people, ya damn wimp!
This virus'll go away by itself with a good night's sleep!
Terasaka... You mean—
Murder is murder, even if it's a piece of trash like that.
You gonna give in to the crazy and throw your chance at ten billion out the window?
Terasaka-kun's right, Nagisa-kun.
Killing him isn't worth it,
and being in a blind rage will only work against you.
Besides, he doesn't know anything about the remedy.
We'll ask the poisoner downstairs.
Just knock him out. That's enough.
Hey now, quit being a wet blanket!
If he doesn't come at me with true killing intent, what's the point?
I'll use this squirt's bloodlust for revenge in a most humiliating way,
and finally my own shame will disappear!
Nagisa-kun, take Terasaka-kun's stun gun.
His life, or my life. His words, or Terasaka-kun's words.
Think carefully, now: which are more worthy?
Terasaka!
You... You've got one hell of a fever!
How'd you even make it here like this?
Shaddup. You wanna look at somethin', look there.
Do it, Nagisa.
Kill him to within an inch of his life.
Ooh, don't you look cool!
Korosensei, Nagisa's put the stun gun away!
I see you're determined to use the knife. That's a relief.
Oh, and just so you know,
I do have some spare vials of that remedy.
If you don't come at me like you mean it,
or if your pals get in our way,
you can kiss these babies goodbye.
Hear that, Karasuma? Stay out of this!
This stuff takes a good month to make.
There's not enough for everyone, but it is your last hope.
Karasuma-sensei.
If you determine that Nagisa-kun's life is in danger,
please don't hesitate to shoot Takaoka-sensei.
For him to say that when he can usually see what's coming...
This must be our most dangerous predicament yet.
Even I can tell that much.
We may have managed to defeat those three assassins on our own terms...
but now the tables are completely turned!
Even if Shiota Nagisa did try to turn this into an assassination...
What's wrong? Aren't you going to kill me?
Takaoka's a whole different man.
He's in battle mode!
Even with a mind gone mad, he's still an elite soldier.
His impregnable defense will shut down any surprise attack!
The build!
The skills!
The experience!
Defeating him is far harder than scoring in first place in the national mock exams.
It's not even a contest.
There's no way he can beat that monster!
Hey, don't go getting tired on me.
We're only just getting started!
Looks like it's time for me to pull out one of these too.
A traumatic image accompanies his knife in my dreams.
When he caught me off-guard with that smile of his—
that's when everything went off the rails.
I will not make the same mistake again.
I'll cut off your hands and feet and have them stuffed and mounted.
I'll keep them with me and cherish them forever.
Karasuma-sensei! You've got to shoot him!
Nagisa's gonna die!
Wait.
Stay out of it!
Are we still leaving them to it, Terasaka?
I'm just about ready to join the fray myself.
You been skippin' practice, Karma, so you don't know, but Nagisa...
He's still got somethin' up his sleeve.
Was that the deadly technique?
Yes. But then again,
it didn't look like one, did it?
When I was in a tight spot as an assassin,
I used this to squeeze my way out.
But it has conditions that must be met—three of them.
First: you must have two weapons.
Second: you must be up against an expert.
And third: your foe must know the terror of being killed.
Good.
That's all of them.
What...
Takaoka-sensei...
Will you be my guinea pig?
Wh-What are you doing?!
A deadly technique doesn't necessarily kill instantly.
Given the ideal conditions, of course, any assassin can do the deed.
But reality is rarely that agreeable,
especially when your target is a pro with an airtight defense.
This technique can reliably create an ideal killing situation in such a bind.
It sets the stage for an instant kill.
Sets the stage, huh?
Move from a standstill, as fast as you can,
as far as you can, and make it as loud as possible.
You... lousy... brat!
This works best when they're almost within range.
The closer you get, the more the target will focus on your knife.
Gently let go of that knife in midair while their attention is on it, then...
What... just... happ—
An assassin...
will not overlook those few moments.
In one fluid motion, swiftly draw your second blade, and...
It... can't be...
This brat... got me... again?!
Finish him off, Nagisa.
A good jolt to the neck'll knock him out cold.
He taught me bloodlust.
That some kinds of bloodlust are wrong to hold on to,
and how important it is to have friends to pull you away from that.
The pain of being hit, the fear of a real fight...
I've learned so much from this man.
He'd done terrible things, but setting that aside,
I thought I ought to thank him for his lessons.
And I figured...
No...
...I couldn't thank him without putting on a smile.
Just, please... don't end this with that smile of yours!
That face will haunt my nightmares until the day I die!
Takaoka-sensei...
Thank you.
Yes!
We beat the boss!
Hooray!
Not bad.
You okay, Nagisa?
Yeah.
Well done, Nagisa-kun.
I was so worried about how things would turn out. I'm relieved.
Right. I'm fine, but... now what?
The remedy we took from Takaoka-sensei won't be enough.
Let's start by getting out of here.
I've called a chopper, so you wait here.
I'll bring up the poisoner.
Ha. You're not gonna need no stinkin' remedy.
You brats thought you could get out of here alive, eh?
We've defeated the man who hired you.
You have no further reason to fight us, right?
I've mostly recovered, and these students are plenty strong.
How about we stop now before anyone else gets hurt?
Yeah, okay.
You just don't know when to give up—
Wait, "okay"?
Our contracts don't cover avenging the boss.
Besides, it's like I said: you don't need any remedy.
This here's what I gave you:
a souped-up version of the common stomach bug.
It'll keep going strong for another three hours or so,
but then it'll rapidly lose its efficacy and become harmless.
Now, this is what our boss told us to use.
If we had, you'd really be in dire straits.
Right before using that virus, we three talked-eth it over.
Our boss only gave-eth you one hour.
We figured we could do the handover without having to resort-eth to a deadly virus.
It was enough to make you feel like your lives were in danger, anyway.
So you went against orders?
Can you do that when he's paying you?
What are you, stupid?
If you think pros will do anything for money, you got another think comin'.
We'll do our best to abide by our client's wishes, of course...
I'll blow this remedy up right before their eyes.
Oh, I can't wait to see their faces crushed with despair!
...but he never had any intention of giving you the remedy.
So either we become the killers of a bunch of respectable junior-high kids,
or we take a hit to our professional standing.
We just calmly weighed up which option posed a greater risk to our future.
And that's why, sorry to say, none of you will be dying.
Give the patients that supplement and put 'em to bed.
Just like it says on the tin, they'll feel even better than before they were sick.
I'll believe it once I see those students home safe and sound.
We'll need to detain you for a while for questioning.
Ah, well. You've got a week to wind it up before our next job starts.
What's this?
Not going-eth for a rematch, buddy?
Aren't you just thirsting for revenge?
I don't kill-eth people out of spite.
I'll wait for the day someone puts-eth a hit out on you.
You'd better become-eth someone worth targeting.
And there you have it, kids!
If you really want us to come kill you, you've gotta make it big first!
Then we'll give you the pro assassin's grand tour!
The assassins were gone,
having left us with their own words of encouragement of sorts.
One buzz from Karasuma.
That's the signal that they've escaped.
Hey, I wanna go down the mountain and see the ocean.
Won't someone drive me down there?
Me! Me me me! Pick me!
And so our big infiltration mission was completed with no one at the hotel the wiser.
Terasaka-kun?
Thanks for calling me out back then.
I was about to make the wrong move.
Pfft.
One less student'd make it that much harder to kill that octopus.
Yeah. Sorry.
We went back to our hotel, where everyone was waiting
and told them it was going to be okay.
We slept like logs, each of us tired out in different ways,
and when we woke, it was evening on the next day.
That was one crazy day.
I'm just glad we got through it in one piece.
You were the one in the most danger, you know!
Sorry.
You do get into sticky spots now and then.
We worry, you know!
Good morning!
Or should I say "evening"?
Feeling better?
Yes, thank you.
I see everyone's in their P.E. gear.
We're the only guests, and these are nice and comfy.
And it'd be cruel to have to think up a whole new day's worth of outfits.
Say what?
So Korosensei's in there?
Yeah. It's not like it's going to work,
but he's in there nice and tight so we can kill him when he reverts.
Karasuma-sensei has been leading the charge without rest.
He shows no signs of fatigue at all. Pretty amazing!
He really is. I wonder if we'll be as awesome as him in ten years.
Who knows?
Bitch-sensei might not look like it, but she's great too.
So were the assassins we met at the hotel.
Those moves mastered through long years of experience
Go, me.
and their work ethic really inspired me.
Gimme a max potion.
Then there are people like Takaoka who I really don't want to turn into.
We follow people we admire and leave behind the ones we reject.
Growing up is probably just doing that over and over again.
What was that explosion?!
Did we get him?!
Even as we asked that,
we already knew the answer.
You suffered so much on account of my cowardice.
But you battled enemies and a virus—and did a fine job of it too.
Good morning, Korosensei.
You're just not the same without your tentacles.
Morning!
Good morning, students.
Now, let's enjoy the rest of our trip, shall we?
You bet!
But we're going back tomorrow morning.
Say what?!
With all the time I spent in my Absolute Defense Form, I've barely gotten to enjoy myself at all!
Well, you're sure full of energy.
This is a one-time thing: summer camp with my students!
We Love Summer!
We can't waste a single second!
What are you doing?!
You just said not to waste a single second, right?
Ah yes, Karma-kun.
Wait until your target lets down his—
Hey, hey, hey!
I thought this might be our chance to do him in.
Want to take a shot, Nagisa-kun?
We've got to make the most of the time we have!
I'm all for that!
Here goes!
Wait up!
Over here!
Since I'm feeling better and all...
You put on a swimsuit underneath?
Well, I didn't!
Ha!
Now you've done it!
Lemme at 'em!
Hooray!
Me too, me too!
Sure!
Wait, I'm just going to swell right up, aren't I?!
Tch!
He realized.
That's right. This is it!
This is what summer's all about!
Hey, me too!
Let me—
Die!
Bit on the small side, huh?
Now, students, there'll be fireworks after this!
Don't forget to play with me too!
That octopus...
Karasuma-san, should we start heading out?
Yes, please do.
Hang on!
I thought you were busy burying him in concrete!
You should've invited me if you were heading to the beach!
What a swimsuit!
What desperation.
Shut it, you brats!
Hey, Karasuma, what do you say?
Let's leave these kids behind and check out that—
Whatever.
You really are a bitch.
What was that?!
You squirts have been giving some real cheek lately!
Don't you mess with me, brats!
You did well.
Our E Class—the End Class—is the assassination classroom.
We are killers,
and our target is our teacher.
Good morning, students.
Time for a second term full of hard work in studying and assassination alike!
And in this assassination classroom we share with Korosensei...
the bell signals the start of another school day.
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte