Phew! Helter swelter!
That's what they say in Osaka when a heat wave hits.
Jeez, it's hot.
Why's he got us out here on the mountain at the back?
If he's looking for a pool, there's one at the main campus.
But that's not in this direction, is it?
No.
Hey, Nagisa-kun,
I hear you really knocked 'em dead the other day.
I sure wish I could've seen that assassination of yours.
It might have worked against a human,
but in our classroom, that doesn't mean a thing.
Day in and day out, we try everything we can think of,
but we still haven't found a surefire way
to assassinate our teacher.
All right, we're here!
Behold!
A pool I made specially for the E Class!
Woohoo!
Then our teacher does stuff like this,
which makes him pretty hard to kill!
It's fun, but a little depressing.
I'm a terrible swimmer,
and this suit leaves nothing to the imagination.
Don't worry, Kayano.
I'm sure there's someone out there
who appreciates you for what you are.
You know, Okajima-kun, the nice-guy routine
and pervy camera don't really go hand-in-hand.
Nagisa...
You...
You're a boy!
You just noticed?!
Can you blame us?
Kimura-kun! No running at the poolside!
You could trip and hurt yourself!
Oh, s-sorry.
Hara-san, Nakamura-san!
Watch the breath-holding!
If you stay under too long,
how will we know you haven't drowned?
Okajima-kun, I'm confiscating that camera!
Hazama-san, don't just read all day! Swim!
Wh-What a fusspot.
I've heard of these.
You know, people who act like royalty in their own domain.
Yeah... It sorta puts a damper on all our gratitude.
My elaborate plan makes the most of the natural surroundings, from the scenery to the design.
It must be enjoyed in an orderly fashion!
Korosensei's Weak Point #22:
Super-strict about pool rules
Aw, don't be such a stick-in-the-mud, Korosensei!
Have a splash!
What was that scream?
Karma-kun! Stop that!
I'll fall in!
I'm going to fall! Do you hear me?!
I'll fall in! Please!
Korosensei...
Don't tell me...
Oh, I just don't feel like swimming. That's all.
It's not like my tentacles get too swollen for me to move or anything.
He...
Korosensei's Weak Point #23:
Can't swim
He can't swim!
This might be his most promising weak point yet!
But what's with that kickboard of yours?
I was sure you were gonna swim.
This is not a kickboard!
It is a wafer!
That's a snack?!
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
potential takai
We've got a lot of potential
hodo mendokusai
It's just that we're not trying
dropout mentality
We had that dropouts' mentality
hinichijou wo ryougashi
No matter the unusual situation we were in
bokura wa utatatanegao shite
We pretended to doze off
knife kakushimotta
While holding on to a hidden knife
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
doko ka taningoto datta
We didn't really feel invested in the job
dakedo
But now
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Our chances soar each time we challenge you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
revolution
A revolution!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
Episode
Vision
Time
Whaddaya mean, you're glad your grades went up?!
You wanna say that one more time, Muramatsu?
I-I mean, this is the highest I've ever gotten.
Study Cram
Pre-Exam Slithery
It's all thanks to that octopus's
Pre-Exam Slithery Study Cram sessions—
Study Cram
Pre-Exam Slithery
You mean you actually did that Slithery Study shit?!
Well, uh...
Even after we three swore we
wouldn't give him the time of day?
But there's a big difference
between slithery and non-slithery—
Enough with the "slithery"!
You just played both sides till you got the grades you wanted. Damn traitor!
I don't like how everyone's fallin'
for that octopus hook, line, and sinker.
It just don't sit well with me.
Are you serious, Korosensei?!
It's just like the real thing!
The hell are you doing, Yoshida?
Hey, Terasaka!
The two of us were talkin' motorcycles the other day,
since no one else in school is into 'em.
Not only am I a grown-up, I am also a man among men.
I've been known to dabble in this kind of hobby.
Plus, this baby can hit three hundred kilometers an hour.
What I wouldn't give to ride the real thing one day!
You kiddin'? It'd be faster just to pick it up and fly!
The hell, Terasaka? What was that for?!
You apologize right now!
Korosensei's not just a grown-up, he's a man among men! And you made him cry!
Yeah, what she said!
You guys are just buzzin' like a bunch of bugs...
Time for an extermination!
What is this?!
A bug bomb?
Terasaka-kun! Pranks are pranks, but this is going too—
Don't touch me, monster.
You're beyond creepy—and so are all of you,
getting' pulled into bein' all
buddy-buddy with a monster!
What's got you so bothered, hmm?
If you don't like it, just kill him.
You're allowed to do that here, after all.
You tryin' to start somethin'?
Fine by me! From day one, you've been—
Now, now, Terasaka.
If you want to fight, actions speak louder than words.
Lemme go!
Buncha losers.
What's with him?
Does he have to stir things up?
A world in crisis, self-improvement in the name of assassination,
recovering from being left in the dust...
Honestly, I don't give a damn about any of it.
I just wanna take it easy and live each day as it comes.
And that's why...
Well done.
Here's your 100,000-yen reward.
We got a lot of prep work done, thanks to you.
Now, these guys I don't mind.
That octopus has a good nose on him.
That's why we needed someone on the inside, like you,
to help us set the stage for Itona to really show his stuff.
Terasaka Ryouma, I understand all too well how you feel.
Just relax. Follow my plan to the letter,
and he'll be dead before you know it.
We'll put the E Class back to
the way it was before he came.
You...
You're weaker than that red-headed fellow,
even though you've got more raw energy
and a better physique.
Do you know why I can tell?
There's no vision in your eyes.
No will or way or want to win.
The slow-witted cow who
dimly chews the grass before it
is no match for the wolf with a cow-killing vision.
Why, you little...
Now, now.
Tomorrow we act.
We're counting on you.
What's with all the crying over nothing?
No, no...
These are my nostrils.
Nostrils
I'm not crying. My nose is running.
These are my eyes.
Eyes
What's the difference?!
I've been feeling a little off since yesterday.
Oh, Terasaka-kun!
I was worried you wouldn't come in today!
The spray can you let loose in the classroom yesterday
was like a cedar-pollen allergen that works only on him.
It dulls the senses of tentacled lifeforms.
Now that you've done that, reel him in.
Hey, octopus.
It's time we killed you for real.
Come to the pool after class.
After all, I hear water's your weakness.
You all come help!
I'll knock him smack into the water for you!
You haven't helped with anyone else's assassination, Terasaka.
And now you're ordering us around
when it suits you?
You really think anyone's gonna jump at the chance to help you?
Like I give a damn either way.
Hell, I'd be happy to have the
ten-billion-yen prize all to myself.
What's his deal?
I can't keep up!
Well, I'm not going.
Same.
Oh, let's all go!
Whoa, his snot's all hardened! We can't escape!
Terasaka-kun's all ready to assassinate me now!
This is the perfect chance for everyone to kill and make up!
First of all: you are gross!
Terasaka-kun!
Are you really going to kill him?
Well, geez, Nagisa.
'Course I am.
Then maybe you should tell everyone your plan of action.
Aw, shut it!
You weaklings, always cowerin' together!
It ain't like you got a vision for really killing him!
But I'm not like the rest of you.
I got a vision for killing him, all right... Easy as pie!
Terasaka-kun seemed confident enough in his plan,
but not in himself.
Even his words sounded like someone else's.
The disjointedness of it all was unsettling.
Yeah, there we go!
Everyone spread out in the pool, just like that!
Who does he think he is?
I have my doubts about this.
Do you even have what it takes to make another person swim?
Hey, Takebayashi, shut up and get in!
Terasaka's turned downright tyrannical.
Just like he was back in first and second year.
Ah, I see.
You'll knock me into the water
and have everyone stab me, yes?
Then tell me: how do you plan to do so?
That pistol won't make me move a single step.
This is not a gun but a transmitter that will send us a signal.
Once everyone is standing by in the pool,
pull the trigger to alert us.
You ready for this, monster?
Of course I am. My nose has even stopped running.
I've always hated you.
Wanted more than anything for you to disappear.
Yes, I know.
After this assassination, we'll have a nice, long talk.
You think you can get cocky with me?
C'mon, Itona!
My students!
We're being swept away!
You'll have to jump in and save them, Korosensei.
No way...
You never told me about this!
It's steep and rocky up ahead.
if they fall, they're done for!
In the time it takes him to be nice and save them,
his tentacles are absorbing more and more water.
Mucus can protect them from a little water.
That's right, Itona.
He can use mucus to solidify the water around him
and tweak the permeation pressure.
But he's all out of mucus.
What the hell?
I-I didn't do anything!
It ain't like what he said.
I was supposed to get Itona over here and push him in!
Oh, I get it.
It wasn't your plan.
You were just being strung along.
Look, I'm tellin' ya, it's not my fault!
Blame the guy who put me up to it!
He's the reason everyone got taken for a ride!
You're the one who got taken for a ride.
If you've got time to go pointing fingers,
try using it to figure out what you want to do here.
Last one!
Long time no see, Korosensei.
What you've sucked up there is no ordinary water.
It contains a substance that dulls tentacle movement.
With Terasaka-kun's help, everything went swimmingly.
Itona-kun...
Come, brother.
A rematch to see who's stronger.
I thought I was strong.
I set my sights on the weak-looking ones and put them under my thumb.
That way I was sure to win.
But at this school, that didn't fly.
Hey, let's skip this next class
and hit the convenience store!
No... I've got to prep for English next.
So skip once. What's the difference?
Whoa, a monkey threatening a human!
Huh?!
But at this school, that didn't fly.
Look, Terasaka-kun... No one does that here.
Old Campus
Even the big, bad leader of the pack
is a miserable weakling once he hits the E Class.
Your grades put you dead last, right?
I can't wait for the day when I get
to hurl a few stones at you in E Class!
That's when I realized the cheap weapon
I'd been using had absolutely no effect here.
In fact, it might never work again.
These guys working hard
toward their vision of the future
would undoubtedly grow up
to boss around directionless mooks like me.
I landed in the outcast E Class and figured I could skate by alongside my fellow goal-free students,
but I was wrong once again.
That monster showed up out of nowhere
and gave the class one huge-ass goal.
Left behind again, I wound up manipulated
and used by some calculating schmuck with a plan.
Dammit!
He's fast, and he hits hard!
Much harder than before!
We reduced the number of tentacles,
focusing power and speed in those remaining.
They're easy enough for a child to control.
Is this for real?
Did it really take that little water to neutralize him?
It ain't just the water.
Terasaka!
He can't go all-out 'cause he just got finished savin' you all.
See? Look above him there.
Whoa!
Token chubster Hara-san could fall at any second!
And to protect her and the others, Korosensei...
She's pretty heavy and fat, so this doesn't look good.
We've got to help her!
But how?!
Wait a second... Don't tell me
they roped you into doing all this!
That's right.
Shortsighted guys like me
with no vision and no goals
are doomed to be played
by smart guys like them.
But you know... At least lemme
pick who gets to pull my strings.
I've had it up to here with those jokers,
and I sure don't like the idea of 'em
walkin' off with the prize.
So, Karma... Why don't you try controllin' me?
Gimme a strategy, fresh outta that shrewd noggin of yours!
I'll pull it off perfectly and save all of them!
Fine by me, but can you even handle one of my plans?
It might be the death of you.
Oh, I'll do it, all right.
I'm the perpetrator who gets results.
All right. Time for the kiling blow, Itona.
Hey!
Terasaka-kun?
You tricked me good!
Don't get so upset.
All you did was get your classmates in trouble.
Perfect for a fellow who didn't fit into the E Class like you.
Shut up! I ain't gonna forgive you for what you did!
Itona! You and me, one on one!
Stop that, Terasaka-kun!
He's not someone you can win against!
Stay outta this, octopuff!
What a hero.
Shut him up, Itona.
Karma-kun!
It's all right.
Shiro's not out to kill us students.
And it's precisely because we're alive
that Korosensei's attention is divided.
Even Hara-san might look like she's in trouble,
but Itona's attacks won't be aimed at her.
It's like I told Terasaka:
he'll hit you with a tentacle
hard enough to knock you out,
but that's as fast and as powerful as it'll get,
so hold on for dear life.
You held up well!
All right, Itona, give him another.
Terasaka's still wearing his shirt from yesterday.
Which means it got a direct hit at point-blank range
from whatever was in that weird spray.
That's sure to have an effect on Itona.
So, with that opening in his defenses...
our octopus has a chance to rescue Hara-san.
Yoshida! Muramatsu!
Gimme a real big one!
Seriously?
Sheesh.
His weak points are the same as Korosensei's, right?
So all we have to do is give him a taste of his own medicine.
You've absorbed a lot, I see.
Your advantage is dwindling.
So what now?
We don't want you to claim the prize money, for one.
Plus, your plans almost got us all killed,
and Terasaka got all beat up in the process.
If you want to keep going,
we're gonna have a hardcore splash party.
Well, you got us.
We withdraw.
If we were to slaughter all these children,
who knows how his antimatter organs would run amok.
Let's go, Itona.
Well? Didn't you have fun with everyone?
Why not join us for real this time?
Itona.
We managed to drive 'em off.
Good thing we saved your life, eh, Korosensei?
Oh, I certainly appreciate it.
I still had some tricks up my sleeve, though.
That reminds me, Terasaka-kun...
You said some harsh things
about me back there, as I recall.
So I'm heavy, am I? Fat?
I-I was just objectively analyzin' the situation at hand!
Keep your excuses!
I'll show you what an assassin-trained "fatty" can do!
You really are tactless, Terasaka.
No wonder you let people take advantage of you.
Shut it, Karma!
You don't get to sit up there talkin' down at me!
What?
Is this how you treat your boss?
My boss? Ha!
What kind of boss would make someone take a tentacle on the chin?
For a world-class slacker,
you sure scored a sweet part in all this!
I was just thinking the same thing.
Why not take this chance to sling a little mud?
Hey! Stop it!
Terasaka-kun's not cut out for
putting together plans from on high.
His strengths come through where he's out in the field.
He makes himself and others shine with his
physical might and the ability to get things done.
I look forward to seeing him grow into an action-squad assassin.
Terasaka-kun's pretty violent,
but he's adjusted well to our class.
We didn't show it, but Karma and I—
all of us, really—were pretty happy about that.
So happy that we all overlooked it.
Bigger than water: Korosensei's greatest weak point of all.
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte