We've infiltrated the Fukuma Denjo Hotel to steal a viral remedy from an unidentified bad guy.
We have one hour.
If we don't make it in time, they'll all die!
You seem pretty average for a pro, huh?
Breaking glass, busting skulls?
I can do that much.
But if your opening move is to call in reinforcements,
I guess that means you're too scared to take on a junior-high kid alone.
Very well-eth.
Let's see what you can do-eth.
If you insist...
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
We've got a lot of potential
potential takai
It's just that we're not trying
hodo mendokusai
We had that dropouts' mentality
dropout mentality
No matter the unusual situation we were in
hinichijou wo ryougashi
We pretended to doze off
bokura wa utatanegao shite
While holding on to a hidden knife
knife kakushimotta
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
We didn't really feel invested in the job
doko ka taningoto datta
But now
dakedo
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
As long as we challenge you, it's fifty-fifty
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu kagiri kanousei wa half and half
kiritsu rei lock on
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
A revolution!
revolution
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
Episode
Karma
Time
2nd
Period
Too soft-eth. You'll have to find-eth a better weapon.
Don't need one.
Grip strength capable of crushing skulls...
Once he gets his hands on me, it's game over.
On first glance, this seems like an unwinnable game,
but just switch our positions around,
and it's no different from the unwinnable game we always play.
Wow...
He's dodging or blocking every blow!
That's your defense technique, right, Karasuma-sensei?
Self-defense is low priority for assassins,
so while I don't remember teaching it in class,
he must have picked it up by
watching me dodge their knives.
Akabane Karma... Even in this E Class,
his talent for fighting is head and shoulders above the rest.
I can dodge him... but if I move in to attack, he'll grab me.
What's wrong-eth?
You'll never get past me if you don't attack-eth!
You think?
I mean, I could be doing my best to distract you
while the rest of us slip past, a few at a time.
But relax.
No underhanded shenanigans here.
Now... it's my turn.
Barehanded, like you.
We'll settle this fair and square, man to man.
I like-eth that face of yours, young warrior.
With you, I've got a chance—
a chance to have-eth the kind of fair fight
I can't experience in the world of assassins.
Now's my chance!
It's over-eth.
That gas!
I'm not fond-eth of drawn-out fights.
So I thought I'd give-eth Smog's paralyzing gas a try.
That's dirty!
Ain't nothin' fair about sneakin' that into the fight!
I never said that I only fight-eth bare-handed.
One mustn't get-eth too particular about one's hangups.
That's another key to sticking around-eth in this business.
A spray of gas at point-blank range-eth...
You'll never defend-eth against it if you don't see it com—
Wh-What have you... hm...
Wow, what a coincidence!
Great minds think alike, huh?
How.... did you... get-eth... that...
And how... did you avoid-eth... breathing my gas...
Eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth!
C'mon, Terasaka, make it snappy!
We'll need duct tape and sheer numbers to beat this monster!
Yeah, I'm on it.
That promise of a barehanded one-on-one fight?
It was bullshit from the word go!
Careful taping him up.
With his superhuman strength,
you've got to be cautious even when he's paralyzed.
Yes, sir.
Eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth...
I nicked an unused cartridge from that poisoner guy.
Pretty handy. Shame they're one use only.
How-eth... did you see-eth my gas attack coming?
Is that why you didn't breathe-eth any in?
All I showed-eth you were my bare hands... So how-eth?
Do I really need to say?
I was on guard against everything but bare hands.
Hm...
I'm sure you really did want a barehanded bout...
but you would have had to stop us by any means necessary,
and if I were you, I would've done the same.
I had faith you'd fight like a true pro...
and that's why I was on guard.
Oh, I get it!
Karma-kun's changed... for the better.
He had never known true defeat,
but those final exams taught him all too well:
Losers are people just like you who have their own lives, their own thoughts, and their own worries.
Once you realize that, you inevitably find
that you can no longer make light of your opponent on the battlefield.
You see that your foe has their own motivations. That they're trying just as hard as you.
And you come to see their abilities. Their circumstances.
Someone who can be respectfully wary of their opponent...
leaves no openings on the battlefield.
You grew so much from that one defeat.
You'll make a name for yourself someday.
Seems you're a force to be
reckoned-eth with, young warrior.
I may have lost,
but I enjoyed our time toget—
What are you talking about?
The fun's just beginning!
Eth?
What the hell-eth is that?
Wasabi and mustard. I'm gonna put them up your nostrils.
What-eth?!
I'd been on guard around you all this time,
but now that you're tied up, what's the point?
Eth?
Once these are in, I'll plug your nose with a special clip,
stuff your mouth with ghost peppers—a thousand times hotter than average chilis—
Be Prepared
and then I'll gag you. Done and done!
Now, my friend-eth...
It's time to show-eth me your willpower as a pro.
Korosensei...
Karma-kun hasn't really changed all that much, has he?
No, he hasn't. I'm a little worried about his future.
What the hell did you bring with you, anyway?
Hey, let's get goin'. If we keep draggin' our feet, they'll find us.
They'll find you, you big hulk.
Aw, shut it!
Okay, everyone, the terrace is upstairs.
The bar floor. Could be tricky.
Yes.
Fukuma Denjo Hotel
Current Location
Display Route
You Are Here
There's a stairway to the VIP floor inside a lounge here.
The back entrance is locked,
so we'll have to come in through the lounge to unlock it.
Now we're flying by the seat of our pants.
We really stand out, though.
Let's have the guys hide here.
We'll sneak into the lounge and unlock the back entrance.
We girls won't look suspicious alone in a place like this.
No. You girls would be in too much danger on your own.
Oh! In that case...
Huh?
What beautiful stars!
Right?
All thanks to the CEO.
You bet!
My folks' connections got me a room here.
Got my share of playmates—all with an eye on the family riches.
Lame. What a lame-ass summer vacation.
C'mon, be a man! Now get in front and protect us, Nagisa-kun!
I can't! I can't be out in front!
Give it up!
Go on!
Why me?
We'd like a guy around, but in places like this,
they check guys real carefully.
Yeah, but even so—
It's all part of the plan!
Really?
Yes, really!
Not you too!
You're acting too normal. It's not fresh enough.
But that's not what I'm looking for!
Where did you find these clothes, anyway?
Someone left them next to the outdoor pool.
There's a nice one. I totally dig her awkwardness.
Ugh! Let's get out of this filthy place ASAP!
At least you seem to be enjoying yourself, Fuwa-san.
Hey!
Where'd you come from?
How about a drink? Anything you like—
it's on me!
Go ahead, Nagisa! Keep him company!
Huh? But, Kataoka-san...
We have to act normal, remember?
We'll come get you if anything happens.
How did it come to this?
Oh, so you're Nagisa-chan! I'm Yuuji.
Okay! Now's our chance!
Let's see, the staircase to go up...
It's got to be this way, right?
Hey, ladies.
On your own?
How's about hangin' with us tonight?
Oh, hell. Will it never end?
Look, let me tell you something...
Yada-san?
We'd love to hang out with cool guys like you,
but we're here with our daddies today.
And my daddy's kinda scary.
So let's not.
A-A yakuza emblem!
And it's the infamous tiny-but-terrifyin' Shuuei Syndicate!
I asked real nice and he gave this to me.
Maybe I'll pin it on my schoolbag!
Sorry about that!
Wimps. It obviously wasn't mine.
That was amazing, Yada-san!
C'mon, drink up! I'm paying!
We're gonna kick it tonight!
O-Oh, I'm more of a soda gu—er, girl.
I've got to try to act natural until the girls reach their goal.
Um, Yuuji-kun? Are you here with your parents?
My parents?
Like they have the time!
This is just between us, but my old man,
he's a famous TV personality.
You've heard of him, believe me!
He's such a big deal he can get away with anything.
He was bragging about having squeezed this
woman announcer's ass for 24 hours straight.
Does your dad have some kind of grudge against asses or something?
Dammit! You idiot, Yuuji!
Can't you hit on someone without leaning on the old man for once?
Uber-lame...
That's... not a regular cigarette, is it?
It's more dangerous than that.
Yeah. I just got into it.
At my age, if you know about these, you're cool.
Our teacher said he doesn't know if smoking those will make you cool,
but it definitely makes your life harder.
Life's already hard for us men!
We gotta force ourselves to try to look cool!
And it's even worse for me 'cos I'm always getting compared to my old man!
You girls got it made.
All you have to do is pick a cool guy.
Um... yyyeah.
I think the girls in my class have a little more on their minds.
Wow, you borrowed that from Bitch-sensei?
She's something else. Yakuza, lawyer, racehorse owner...
She's got every kind of pin you could think of,
since she can use them for her work.
You're always so interested in
Bitch-sensei's work, Yada-san.
Yeah... It's not like I want to seduce people, though.
It's like what Korosensei said:
you gotta wield a second blade.
I'm betting her intimacy and negotiating skills
are probably your best bet out in the world.
Whoa, Yada-san. You're going to be one kickass grownup!
Even with those big boobs, I can't help but admire you!
The big-boob-hating Kayanocchi opens her heart!
Look, ladies!
We made it... but there's a lookout.
We might need a man around after all.
Yeah...
Kayano-san, go get Nagisa.
Okay.
Think we can lure out that lookout and sneak past?
I'd rather not force our way through.
If we get the better of him, we'll be found out.
Nagisa!
Kayano!
Oh, um... I gotta go.
What? Already?
Bye now!
Dammit! I can't let her get away without acting my coolest!
Did you have to leave me alone like that?
Sorry! We hammered out a strategy.
Great. I can't wait to get out of these clothes.
Hey, wait up, ladies!
As a special treat, check out my signature dance moves!
Go away.
I've been doing this ever since I was a kid.
These moves always get me the girl!
Huh?
Hey, brat! Tough guy, eh?
N-No... I—
Get over here!
I didn't mean to—
This is a million-yen jacket. I demand compensation!
Your address, now!
Hinata-chan!
Add on pain and suffering, and that's three million total.
Pay up and we'll only leave you half dead!
What?! M-My father will pay! Please don't beat me up!
Excuse me, Mr. Yakuza, sir?
Yeah?
Excuse me, sir?
One of the patrons just suddenly collapsed.
You'd better get him out of harm's way and have him looked at.
Y-Yes, ma'am. Sorry for the bother.
What'd he do, overdose? Sheesh.
Now!
Back to the dance floor with you!
And don't tell anyone about this, okay?
Even when girls pull off something cool so effortlessly,
you still have to chin up and act cool yourself.
It is hard, being a guy.
Nagisa-chan...
If we meet again, keep acting cool, okay?
Though cut out the drugs and dancing if you can help it.
Here we are!
We really sent you into some dicey territory.
You weren't in any danger, were you?
Nuh-uh!
Not remotely!
Wow, you sure changed fast, Nagisa.
Yeah.
Hmm? What's wrong?
It's just...
You girls did everything this time around.
What was even the point of me being in this getup?
Comic relief, duh!
Don't you dare, Karma-kun!
No, I don't think that's it.
I'm sure it wound up helping someone.
If only you could have stayed like that.
History's full of assassins who disguised themselves as women, after all.
Don't you start too, Isogai-kun!
If you're gonna cut it off, Nagisa-kun, sooner is better.
I am not! I happen to like it!
Can we talk about this later?
Or never.
We're in our final stage of infiltration here.
Ritsu?
Yes, sir.
Up ahead is the VIP floor.
These guests don't rely solely on hotel security
but provide their own hired lookouts.
So of course there's some blocking the staircase.
They look way tough, too.
Are they more of the guys who've been threatening us?
Or are they hired muscle that has nothing to do with us?
Either way, we're gonna have to beat 'em to get by.
That's exactly right, Terasaka-kun.
And that weapon you have will do the job perfectly.
Pff! What, you got X-ray vision now, too?
You'll have to take them both down at the same time, or they'll call for help.
I got this, okay?
Hey, Kimura, see if you can lure 'em out this way some.
Who, me?
But how?
How should I know?
Here, Kimura, try this...
What gives, kid?
Huh? Any brains around here?
These guys are total muscleheads!
You slabs of pigmeat oughta quit pretending to be human.
Hey!
Get back here!
Yep, that pissed 'em off!
What's with this brat?
He's crazy fast!
Okay! Now!
Got it!
S-Stun-guns?
I bought 'em to see how electricity worked on that octopus.
Never thought I'd be usin' 'em like this!
You bought those? Weren't they expensive?
Huh? Uh, well...
I came into a little money lately, so...
These two... They look...
Nice weapon, Terasaka-kun.
But check their chests.
Huh?
Judging from the bulges there,
you ought to be able to find something even better.
R-Real guns!
And...
Chiba-kun? Hayami-san?
Those guns are for you.
Karasuma-sensei hasn't recovered enough to fire with any accuracy.
Right now, you two are the best gun-users we have.
B-But this is all so sudden.
However!
No Killing
I will not permit you to kill anyone.
With your skill, you should have plenty of ways to use those to defeat someone without a scratch.
Giving us real guns?
When we couldn't even pull off our mission with airguns?
Let's be on our way, then.
From the looks of things at this hotel,
there's no sign the enemy has set up camp in any great numbers.
They're probably down to one or two hired killers—at most.
Yeah! So let's go murdalize the rest!
Okay, team: we'll have to use the VIP-only
emergency stairs to reach the next floor up.
And to do that, we'll have to go through the concert hall on the 8th floor.
This is starting to leave a bad taste in my mouth.
I was charged with killing some super-creature,
so how'd I get stuck going to meet a bunch of kids?
Revolting.
Sure enough, the only thing tasty around here...
is my gun.
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte