I'm ready!
Then we're off to distribute flyers.
Let's go, Asia!
Wait.
Sorry?
This'll be the last week you have to distribute flyers.
As I've said before, you were doing it as part of your training.
Distributing flyers is actually a familiar's job.
Then we're done distributing flyers?
First, you need to get a familiar.
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 7 "I'm Gonna Get a Familiar!"
This is my familiar.
You've met her previously, Issei.
Huh?
What?!
Then that girl was...
This is mine.
A-An imp?
This is Shiro.
Mine is—
I don't want to see yours.
Oh, come on.
It's a basic thing for demons.
They can assist you, deliver messages, and even find things.
Um, how do you get a familiar?
That is...
Come in!
Please excuse us.
Sh-She is...
Um, who is she?
She's the student council president, Shitori Souna-senpai.
Next to her is the vice-president, Shinra Tsubaki-senpai.
Actually, these are all student council members!
What brings all of you here?
Just a greeting, since both of us have some new servants.
Servants? Don't tell me...
Her real name is Sona Sitri.
She's the heiress apparent of
the upper-class Sitri family.
Th-There are other demons in this school?!
Rias-senpai, you didn't tell him about us?
It's strange he wouldn't notice fellow demons, though.
Saji, the two families do not meddle in each other's affairs.
It's no surprise that Hyoudou-kun is unaware.
You're the guy who recently joined
the student council as the secretary.
Uh, Class 2-C's...
Saji Genshirou, my pawn.
This is my pawn, Hyoudou Issei,
and my bishop, Asia Argento.
Oh, you're a pawn too?
And we're also in the same grade!
I must say that being the same piece as one of the perverted trio seriously hurts my pride.
What did you say, bastard?!
Oh, you wanna fight?
I just became a demon,
but I'm a pawn that was worth four pieces!
Saji, don't.
Also, he was worth eight pieces.
Eight? Isn't that all of them?!
I can't believe it. A lame guy like this—
Shut up!
Apologies for that, Hyoudou-kun, Argento-san.
Try to get along with him, if you can,
he's also a new to being a demon.
Saji.
Yes, ma'am.
Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you too!
To be with a cutie like you, the pleasure is all mine!
Saji-kun, nice to meet you!
I mean, I'll really kill you if you lay your hands on Asia, Saji-kun!
Trying to keep a blonde beauty all to yourself?
As one would expect from a perverted critter!
You must be having a rough time.
Same goes for you.
I was allowed a familiar as soon as I debuted.
I hear you're still handing out flyers.
Don't make fun of me!
The president told me to get a familiar just now!
So you are going to go to him as well?
Yeah, I had sometime next week in mind, though.
But he's only available once a month.
Then how about deciding it with a fair game?
A game?
The winner gains the right to commission him.
Are you talking about a Rating Game?
Oh, no. We'd never even be granted permission for that.
Right.
You can't afford to harm yourself right now, after all.
That's irrelevant.
Oh, I know!
Let's settle it through sports,
like the high school students we are.
Good luck, President, Akeno-san!
President, please win for me!
Akeno, let's win this match.
Sure, President!
Here it goes, Sona.
Yes, go ahead, Rias.
I do want the president to win,
but it'd be nice for this to go on forever...
...so we can enjoy the view.
Yeah!
Wait, you guys!
The school's top beauties are having a match
in shining pure-white underskirts!
The news spread throughout the school at the speed of light!
Not to mention their tennis skills are pro tier!
No, with these visuals, it's definitely god tier!
Agreed!
Wow, there are quite a few spectators.
Souna-sama!
Akeno Onee-sama!
They can't use their demonic powers.
Take this! Shitori-style spin serve!
Naive!
Take this Gremory-style counter!
15-30!
Damn it!
You're doing awesome, President!
They're definitely using their demonic powers.
I think they might be getting too fired up.
It's a magic ball!
It's amazing!
Magic ball?!
They said magic ball!
No way!
The crowd just thinks it's a magic ball.
Thank goodness people are so oblivious.
I expected no less from my rival.
But I'll still win!
I have 108 levels of madoukyuu!
I accept your challenge, Rias.
That's my love for you!
The match just wouldn't end, so...
A team match?!
President and Akeno-san are discussing the matter with the student council right now.
We decided on dodgeball.
The match is tomorrow night at the gym.
Let's do our best for Issei and Asia!
Yes!
Thank you very much!
Everyone!
Asia, are you awake?
Issei-san!
Please come in.
Um, well, it's late...
Asia, do you have a sewing kit by any chance?
Pardon?
They have two more members than us,
so I asked them to referee.
I haven't played dodgeball since elementary school!
The goal is to select a winner,
so we went for a game with simple rules.
Asia-san learned them quickly too.
I'm at my limit!
Just a little more.
O-Okay!
When I watch the two of them, I can't help but...
have perverted delusions!
You're so cute.
Occult
Club
Headbands?
Oh my, they look lovely!
I made them overnight.
You didn't sleep?
President and Akeno-san, you worked so hard for us.
Koneko-chan and Kiba today as well.
So I thought I'd do at least something for everyone.
Occult
Club
Um, so headbands are too lame then?
Not at all. They're well-made.
They're really wonderful, Issei.
Oh no, it's nothing much.
Unexpected of you.
Let's put these on and work hard as a team!
Yes!
Thank you for waiting.
Out!
Occult
Club
Koneko-chan!
Occult
Club
It's no problem.
Occult
Club
Grief of Memories!
Occult
Club
Not bad. You caught Tsubaki's full-power ball.
Who do you think I am?
No!
Occult
Club
Issei-kun!
Occult
Club
Oh my.
Occult
Club
Don't let your guard down!
S-Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Grief of Memories!
Dodgeball is a very scary sport!
Occult
Club
I don't know what sport we're playing anymore!
Occult
Club
President, let's take out Hyoudou first!
Shitori-Style Sinker Bomb Shot!
What?!
Occult
Club
Why?!
Issei, dodge it!
Occult
Club
I-It's all over.
Occult
Club
I'll use Twilight Healing,
so please show me where you're injured.
No, I can't do that.
But I can't really heal unless I see the affected area...
Affected area? It's the genital area! I can't!
I really can't! Please, don't force me!
Okay, then I'll do it over your clothes.
Occult
Club
Are you all right?
Yes...
Hard to comment on this situation.
Can't disagree.
Asia, you stay and take care of Issei.
O-Okay!
Everyone else, this is a battle to avenge Issei!
Occult
Club
Yes, Issei-kun's death...
Occult
Club
...will not be in vain.
Occult
Club
Of course.
Occult
Club
Um, I'm not dead.
Heal, heal well!
Bring it on!
You're the only one left now. Prepare yourself, Sona.
The real match begins now.
Time's up!
We've won! We've won!
We did it!
Then we'll be taking priority on the familiars as agreed.
Of course. I hate losing, but I did have some fun.
But if it were a Rating Game instead of a child's game like this, I wouldn't lose.
Occult
Club
I won't lose to my childhood friend, either.
Well, looks like it'll be a while before we'll have one.
Occult
Club
Indeed.
Well then, see you later.
Occult
Club
Rating Game?
Cheers!
The Occult Research Club has marvelously defeated the student council!
You all made it happen!
I feel bad that I was eliminated.
You made this and raised everyone's spirit,
so Issei-kun, you played a part in it!
Indeed!
Right, Issei-san!
Kiba, you say nice things sometimes,
just sometimes, for a damn handsome boy!
Occult
Club
Now, there's no time to waste.
Let's go get familiars.
Um, right now?
We can only meet him when there's a full moon.
Him?
The familiar master.
Wh-Where are we?
The forest where familiars are created.
We got our familiars here as well.
This place does look creepy, like
something's gonna lash out at me.
Y-Yes.
Gotta catch ‘em all!
Wh-Who's there?!
I'm the familiar master, Zatuji.
Familiar...
...master?
It's a nice full moon today!
The best day to catch some familiar!
I can catch any familiar!
He's a professional when it comes to catching them.
I see.
Now, what are you looking for in a familiar?
Strength? Speed? Or maybe one with poison ability?
Actually, do you have a cute familiar?
One that looks like a girl?
Tsk, you newbies can't do it right.
You want familiars to be useful and strong.
That is to say, you must know their abilities and choose one that complements your own!
Um, I want a cute familiar as well.
Oh, sure thing, baby!
Thank you so much!
You...
The water spirit Undine lives in this lake.
The water spirit!
Judging from the name, it's probably...
someone, as a future Harem King, I'll want to keep around.
Cleaning my ears is an excuse to lie my head on her lap.
I'll gently reach out my hands to touch
her deeply mysterious breasts!
The lake!
Oh, Undine's coming out!
That's Undine.
No, no, no, that's a fighter who came here to bathe no matter how you look at her!
You're in luck, boy.
It's pretty rare to come across one.
A fighting-oriented water spirit isn't bad!
It's bad! It looks more like a hitman than a gentle spirit!
But it is female.
That's one thing I really didn't want to know.
But she had pure eyes.
I'm sure she's a good-natured girl!
Please don't call that a girl.
Wait.
Look!
D-Dragon?
It's cute!
Sprite Dragon.
Child of the dragon that wields cerulean lightning.
It's a quite high-class one.
It's my first time actually seeing one.
Now's the only chance to catch it!
It's impossible to catch in mature form.
Issei-kun has the power of the Emperor of Red Dragon,
so the compatibility should be fine.
I see! All right, Sprite Dragon, I choose you—
Asia!
Oh my.
Slime!
Oh my!
This is embarrassing!
Oh no!
They're dissolving!
So slimy.
Gross!
Damn it!
This is wonderful!
Don't look.
But I've got to do something when you're in trouble!
I can't use my demonic powers like this!
Oh my, this is a problem!
President!
Gotta save this to my neural hard disk!
These are slimes that primarily feed on textile.
Though, they're mostly harmless
aside from eating women's clothes.
Clothes-eating slimes?
President, I'll make this slime my familiar!
Oh my, not there!
This is exactly the talent I was seeking!
You know, Issei,
familiars are very important to demons!
Think carefully!
I've thought carefully!
I'll make this my familiar!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Step aside, Issei.
Creatures like these must be burnt away.
Don't! I have no doubt this slime
was born in this world to meet me!
This is destiny!
You can't separate us!
Issei-san is holding me so tightly!
Slatarou, my partner!
He already named it!
I've never seen a demon who wants
the pests of the forest this badly.
It's a big world.
He's usually a good kid,
but he is too honest with his carnal desires.
President, please stop looking at me with such pity!
With him, I'll become a true hero!
What was that?
Was that Sprite Dragon's lightning?
Slatarou!
Damn you!
Issei-san!
This is...
It only attacks things it recognizes as enemies.
It must've thought the boy and the
slime were attacking the blonde girl.
That means...
It's cute!
Well, looks like you got your familiar, beauty!
I-In the name of Asia Argento,
I order you to form a contract as my familiar!
All right, we're done.
Well done, Asia-chan!
That tickles, Rassei-kun!
Rassei?
Yes, since he shoots lightning.
I took part of it from your name as well.
Well, it's all good.
Nice to meet you, Rassei!
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
but male dragons hate males of other species!
Rassei, you're a mischievous kid.
Why did you die, my friend, Slatarou?!
Grant me that wondrous power!
Death to perverts.
It is said that Sprite Dragons only
open up to ones with a pure heart.
It wouldn't normally follow a demon.
It could be because Asia-chan used to be a nun.
Rassei, you bastard! What are you doing to Asia?
Jeez, Rassei-kun, don't harm others!
See you, Rassei-kun!
I became a demon before her,
but she's more like a real demon than me.
It's depressing.
Damn it! I'll catch a familiar
that'll blow your minds someday!
I'll be looking forward to it.
Good work, everyone!
Good work!
Issei still has a long way to go.
He's just begun.
Yes.
Occult
Club
You're right.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
What a lovely moment!
Issei-san, you like looking at naked bodies, right?
He's also the fiancé of the Gremory family's heiress apparent.
Episode 8 "I'm Picking a Fight!"
Take my virginity.
This is urgent!