Now, then...
What on Earth are you going to do, hmm?
First, you'll get to enjoy a video Mimura put together,
and then the seven top testers will destroy your tentacles.
That'll be the signal for us all to jump in and begin the assassination.
Does that sound all right, Korosensei?
More than all right.
Thanks for setting this up, Mimura.
It was hard work! I was editing all through dinner.
This chapel is surrounded by ocean,
and there's a chance the walls and windows are treated with an anti-teacher substance.
Escape would be too risky.
I suppose I'll just have to dodge everything in here.
Korosensei?
I have to pat you down first.
We may be surrounded by water, but if you smuggled in that swimsuit,
you'd still be able to get away.
You're being so careful!
But I wouldn't pull such a cheap trick.
This teacher can easily dodge my attacks, even at point-blank range.
But...
If we all work together, this might be our chance!
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
potential takai
We've got a lot of potential
hodo mendokusai
It's just that we're not trying
dropout mentality
We had that dropouts' mentality
hinichijou wo ryougashi
No matter the unusual situation we were in
bokura wa utatatanegao shite
We pretended to doze off
knife kakushimotta
While holding on to a hidden knife
kiritsu rei lock on
Stand, bow, lock on
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
doko ka taningoto datta
We didn't really feel invested in the job
dakedo
But now
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on
Our chances soar each time we challenge you
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu tabi ni kanousei ga afureta
kiritsu rei lock on
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
Stand, bow, lock on!
satsui dake ga anata e no message
kiritsu rei lock on
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
revolution
A revolution!
oh yeah
Oh yeah!
sensei target on
The target is our teacher!
Episode
Action
Time
Are you ready?
No need to hold back.
Come right at me!
Here we go, Korosensei.
AC...
Somewhere in Tokyo: Kunugigaoka Junior High, Class 3-E.
As it happens, their teacher is also their assassination target.
People are going in and out of this chapel in the dark behind me.
Tonight, the E Class recon team will close in
That would conceal the number of people and their positions.
on the ecology of this mystery man.
But you underestimate me.
I can tell two students' scents are missing.
From that direction, I can smell the E Class's top snipers, Hayami-san and Chiba-kun.
This video really is well done.
You edited and narrated this, Mimura-kun?
Nice camera blocking, good music... Really sharp.
It pulls me right—
Joining us today are those who shared top-secret intel with the recon team.
Today's Target: Korosensei
We'll hear what they have to say... after this.
His bribery... failed.
Tokyo resident
Korosensei
(age unknown)
Tokyo resident
Korosensei
(age unknown)
It failed?!
His current preference is mature office women.
Here are all the dirty magazines this octopus has gathered.
No! Come on, Okajima-kun!
I told you guys not to tell anyone!
A giant shadow looms over the line for the women-only cake buffet.
Who could it be?
It's him.
I'm Koroko!
Excuse me, but this is for women only...
His disguise can't last long.
What do you think you're doing?!
It's a miracle they found out he wasn't a woman without discovering he wasn't even human.
Porn, cross-dressing, and not a hint of shame?
What a dirty pervert.
Take one!
When he's short before payday,
Thanks!
this man lines up his images to get free tissues.
And what does he do with them?
Thanks!
Fries them up and eats them.
Here we have fried pocket tissues!
I recently noticed they have quite a sweet taste to them,
Has he no dignity as an educator—nay, as a living being?
and a pleasant spongy texture.
And that's not all.
We have a full hour of embarrassing footage of this instructor.
Another hour of this?!
One Hour Later
I'm dead. I'm already dead.
With all that out in the open... I can't go on living.
The End
Now, did you happen to notice anything while you sat through our top-secret video,
Korosensei?
The End
Water!
But I didn't sense anyone pouring it in!
It couldn't be...
High tide!
Someone musta shortened the support pilings on this here chapel.
Seasick, shamed, and now waterlogged...
You've slowed down quite a bit.
Now for the main event...
A promise is a promise. No dodgin', now.
A valiant effort. But I know where the snipers are.
If I just keep an eye out in that direction...
Commence operation!
Begin!
Five seconds elapsed.
Did it come apart?!
Yes!
Thirty-five seconds elapsed.
Flyboards?
A hydraulic cage?!
Korosensei doesn't do well with sudden changes to his environment.
From the chapel to a cage of water!
It'll confuse his weakened tentacles
and lower his reaction speed even further!
Fifty-three seconds elapsed.
Commencing volley.
Taking aim.
Target area: one square meter around Korosensei.
Korosensei is highly sensitive to attacks that make contact.
But we're actually not going to aim at him!
We'll block his escape path with a hail of bullets!
And that's not all!
The final blow...
goes to those two!
The ones onshore are two dummies infused with their scents!
By alerting him to the shore while in the chapel
and changing the setting to a water cage,
we've created a whole new sniping target!
Game over!
You've done well... to come this far!
Nagisa!
This is clearly unlike any of our previous attempts—
it feels like it worked!
Stay alert!
He can regenerate!
Isogai-kun, Kataoka-san, you're in charge of watching the water!
Yes, sir!
But he had nowhere to run!
Look!
Hey...
Uh-huh...
What the hell is that?
My trump card of all trump cards: my absolute defense form!
Absolute defense form?!
Absolute Defense Form?!
The exterior is crystallized,
high-density condensed energy.
The energy remaining after shrinking my body down hardens in a shell around it.
In this form, I'm absolutely invincible!
No way...
So if you always stay in that form, we can never kill you!
If only that were the case.
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
This energy crystal will break down in about a day.
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Absolute Defense Form
High-Density Energy Crystal
Core
Breakdown Begins
After 24 Hours
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
Breakdown Begins
After 24 Hours
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
And the moment it does, my body will re-inflate,
Physical Regeneration
During Reconstruction
Complete
Recovery
absorbing energy and returning to its usual form.
Complete
Recovery
On the other hand, for the one day or so until this crystal decays,
I can't move an inch.
This brings with it certain risks.
What happened to the thing I left here?!
I put it out with the trash.
Burnables
Oh, nooo!
What I'm most afraid of is being placed into a high-speed rocket during that time
and left to float through the far reaches of outer space.
But I've thoroughly studied that eventuality.
Nowhere in the world is there a rocket capable of making that flight within 24 hours.
He got us.
Another trick up his sleeve—after all that.
And he even took its weak points into account!
That was an utter failure.
Invincible, my ass.
Somethin' like this has gotta be breakable somehow!
It's no use. Even a nuclear bomb wouldn't leave a scratch.
Oh, I get it.
No weaknesses means we're out of options.
No! Stop! I can't cover my face without any hands!
Sorry, sorry! Then I'll just...
stick this sea slug on you!
Someone go find me a filthy old guy so I can jam this thing down his underpants!
No! Help!
When you think about it, we can do whatever we want with him.
Yep. And this kind of thing is Karma-kun's specialty.
We'll disperse for now, students.
The top brass and I will discuss how to deal with this one.
Going to throw me in a pool full of anti-teacher material?
It won't work.
I can simply make a portion of my energy explode,
creating a blast like before that'd send things flying.
But you should be proud.
Even the world's combined military couldn't get this far with me.
It all comes down to the magnificence of your plan.
Korosensei praised our assassination like he always does,
but it was our biggest disappointment yet.
Still in shock from our all-in, full-throttle attack missing the mark,
coupled with an unusual sense of fatigue,
we made our way back to the hotel.
Ritsu?
Yes?
You recorded that, right?
Yes! I captured as much of the assassination as possible with my high-speed camera.
I knew the second I fired that I'd missed.
That my bullet couldn't kill him.
I can't say for sure.
The exact time it took him to change into that form is unclear.
However, if your shot had been 0.5 seconds faster,
or if Hayami-san's had been thirty centimeters closer,
you would have had a fifty percent chance of killing him before he noticed.
I was so confident. I mean, we rehearsed
and even practiced firing from a less stable spot—and I didn't miss.
But when the time came, my fingers stiffened and my vision narrowed.
Same here.
The pressure of absolutely not being allowed to miss...
That crucial now-or-never moment...
To think it'd be this different from practice.
I'm just so exhausted!
Let's head back to our room and rest.
I don't feel like doing anything.
What, one lousy miss and you lose all your energy?
We did what we were supposed to do,
so tomorrow we can just enjoy ourselves!
Ooh, yeah! Tomorrow I get to take in some swimsuited beauties for sure!
No matter how tired I may be, I'll always have the energy for a hearty nosebleed!
Man, I'm just not feeling it.
Something isn't right. Everyone's too exhausted!
Can I lean on you for a second, Nagisa-kun?
Nakamura-san!
I want to go back to the room and change,
but I can't seem to move my body at all.
You're burning up!
Just imagining those babes is giving me a nosebleed!
Okajima-kun!
Wh-What the...
Hey! Where's the hospital on this island?
Well... I'm afraid the island is too small to have one.
Incoming Call
Private Number
Hey there, Sensei.
Your precious students seem to be in a real bad way.
Who is this?!
Hey, Ritsu!
Who I am doesn't matter.
Those brats aren't the only ones going after that marked man.
You mean you did this?
How observant.
It's an artificial virus.
Playing Audio
Once you're infected, it's all over.
The incubation period and initial symptoms vary,
but the cells in their bodies will break down within a week,
leading to death.
There's only one remedy, also an original concoction,
but unfortunately, I'm the only one who has it.
I can't be bothered bringing it to you, so you'd better come get it directly.
There's a hotel atop this island's mountain.
Bring me the one with the price on his head.
Come up to the top floor within one hour.
However, Sensei, you seem pretty tough yourself. Dangerous, even.
So send your two shortest students still standing—one boy, one girl.
I've told the front desk to expect you.
Follow the rules, and we'll swap the target for the remedy and that'll be that.
But contact any outsider, or be even a little late, and the remedy...
will be history.
I've got to thank you for immobilizing him like that.
Looks like the gods are on our side.
Private Number
Call Ended
End
A third party joining the fray at a time like this? Unbelievable!
Uh, Karasuma-sensei, aren't you being a little rough? Er...
Karasuma-san?
As we expected, it's no use.
Even when we play the government card,
the hotel just responds with claims of privacy protection.
It figures.
Does it?
That mountaintop hotel is a noted site for illegal negotiation.
A remote island in the southern sea?
Couldn't ask for a better location.
They have connections with some government higher-ups.
Even the police have their hands tied.
Clearly they're not going to cooperate with us.
What are we gonna do? At this rate, it'll be a massacre!
We didn't come here to be killed!
Calm down, Yoshida-kun. We won't die that easily.
Just come up with a way to deal with this.
Yeah... Sorry, Hara.
It's too dicey to do what he says.
Send your two runtiest students?
These two squirts?!
We'd just be handin' him hostages!
First off, I'm pissed at anyone who would even do this kinda thing.
No one lays a finger on my flunkies!
That simple-minded guy...
Heh heh...
I say we ignore his demands!
Let's get everyone to a hospital in the city!
I'm against that.
If it really is an unknown artificial virus,
even the biggest hospitals won't have the antivirals to stop it.
The time wasted in bringing in the sick could hurt them more.
Say what?!
We'll work on treating the symptoms for now.
You'd better hurry to the trade-off spot.
Takebayashi...
There's nothing else we can do.
If Korosensei could move, we might've had a chance.
If only our assassination attempt hadn't gone quite so well for nothing.
So he's the one they're after.
I'm not sure that guy will just let the students go after they deliver him.
What should we do? We only have one hour.
There's still a way.
Korosensei?
All set!
It looks like Ritsu-san's completed the prep work I asked her to do.
I need the healthy students to come here.
Wear something you don't mind getting dirty.
It's so high...
I infiltrated the hotel's computers
and got schematics of the interior, complete with guard locations.
A large number of guards are stationed at and around the main entrance.
It's not possible to enter the hotel without going past the front desk.
With one exception: there is an entryway on this side, atop the ledge.
The terrain is impassable,
and there are no guards posted there.
If you don't want the enemy to get his way...
there's only one thing to do!
Not counting the ten patients and the two left behind to care for them,
all capable students must sneak in from here,
get the jump on the guys at the top,
and steal that remedy!
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
I was waiting for...
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
Is always here
koko ni iru no
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
Shine again
mata hikatte
Irina Jelavich's...
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can control her circulation
Normal.
to change her face color at will.
Red makes her look shy or drunk,
Red.
and blue makes her look uneasy or unwell:
Blue.
an extremely effective tactic when going undercover.
When she tried to show this off to her students,
they accused her of being a cheap Korosensei ripoff.
Look at this!
I can change the color of my face!
She got angry, and her face went all red by itself.
I didn't rip off anyone!
Assassination Classroom!
Irina Jelavich's...
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can pop out the parts of a cereal-box prize and assemble it within one minute.
Fast Forward
While this speaks volumes about her kissing techniques,
we still wouldn't want to touch the finished product.
Also: this is dangerous, kids, so don't try it at home.
Rewind
Assassination Classroom.
Irina Jelavich's...
Irina Jelavich's
Super-Secret Skills Series!
Super-Secret Skills Series
Irina-sensei can use her wig know-how to disguise herself as any number of people.
Believe it!
The culprit is... you!