So, this is what she did when I almost died last time?
It's okay now.
A-All right.
It seems like it will take a little while to heal completely.
That stray exorcist was able to wield quite strong powers of light.
Then, it's not just demons who become strays?
There are many who get expelled from the Church
and end up serving under a fallen angel.
Does that mean Asia is one of those stray exorcists?
Either way, you are a demon, and she is a servant of a fallen angel.
Those are facts.
President!
I'm weak.
I'm too weak.
I'm just a pawn.
I can't even save a girl.
Issei-san!
No way in hell!
If I'm weak...
I just need to train and get stronger!
Ouch!
Maybe... I am hopeless.
No! She's with that insane priest!
I have no time. Asia is being...
Issei-san?
Asia?
High School DxD
The lines come together with a distant voice calling in the skies,
The voice of terror dancing under the cross.
I don't want to show you my weaknesses,
so I push forward, shaking off the wind coming my way.
As I unleash my impulses,
determination starts flowing and building up.
I won't forget those eyes.
Lines being drawn and deleted shake my memories,
DrawX
De
lete
replacing this moment with tomorrow.
In the light tracing the circle of death and rebirth,
yet again the crimson gently trickles down my cheek.
Episode 4 "I'm Gonna Save My Friend!"
Um, Asia-chan?
Uh, yes?
This is how you eat them, Princess.
I-I never would've guessed they can be eaten like that! Amazing!
It's delicious!
By the way, why were you at that park?
Well...
I was on break, so I thought I'd take a stroll around town.
Um, then I saw you, so...
Asia!
Yes!
Let's play to our hearts' content today !
Sure!
Asia
Issei
What's the matter?
N-No! It's nothing.
You like Racchu-kun?
N-No, well...
Yes.
I used to frequent nearby arcades with Matsuda and Motohama whenever we had time after school!
Thank you very much!
This Racchu-kun is a treasure I could get because I met you!
Now, where shall we go next?
Yes, but we can enjoy this precious meeting only today.
I've never had so much fun in my life!
Asia, you're exaggerating.
Asia!
Your wounds from that time?
Y-Yeah.
But really, she's so cute.
Your leg as well, right?
Y-Yeah.
How does it feel?
Uhm, let's see...
I feel really good!
My leg's healed too!
Amazing! You're amazing, Asia!
My parents abandoned me right after I was born.
Huh?
I was told I had been found crying in front of a small European town's church.
I grew up there.
When I was eight, a wounded dog, close to death, wandered into the church.
By myself, I prayed as hard as I could.
That's when a miracle occurred.
Soon afterward, I was taken to a big church
where I was ordered to heal illnesses and wounds of Christians coming from all over the world.
I was so happy that my power could help people!
Then, one day, I encountered a man collapsed on the floor, heavily injured.
But the man I came across was...
She can heal demons? She's a witch!
A witch that heals demons!
I was branded a heretic because I had the power to even heal demons.
So, that's why you had nowhere to go and got picked up by a fallen angel.
But I never stopped praying to God, expressing my gratitude.
Not to mention I never knew what terrible things they were doing.
The Lord must be testing me.
If I can overcome this ordeal, He will make my dream come true someday.
That's what I believe.
Your dream?
I'll make a lot of friends. Together we'll buy flowers and books, and chat...
That's my dream.
I don't have any friends, you see.
Issei-san?
I'll be your friend, Asia.
I mean, aren't we already friends?
We chatted and had fun together, after all.
Well, we didn't get to the flowers or books, but still...
Or is that still not enough?
No.
No, not at all.
But, I'm causing you trouble, Issei-san.
I'm a demon and you're a nun, so what?
We can still be friends!
I...
I'm happy!
Not going to happen.
Yuuma-chan!
Reynalle-sama!
As I thought,
you are a fallen angel!
It was true you're living a lowly life as a demon after all.
Asia, you can't run away.
No! I won't return to a place where I have to kill people!
Sorry, the truth is I ran away from the church...
Figured so.
Huh?
There's just no way you'd hang out with those scumbags on your own accord.
Why are you here, fallen angel!?
A squalid, low-class demon like you
shouldn't address me so frivolously.
If you're going to stand in my way...
A light-lance!
I'll annihilate you completely this time!
Sacred Gear!
I did it!
So, it's just a Twice Critical.
We were completely off the mark.
T-Twice?
Also known as Dragon's Hand,
it's an ordinary item that doubles your power temporarily.
Double my power?
"He has a dangerous Sacred Gear."
That's what my superiors told me,
so I went through that entire farçe.
"I love you! Please go out with me!" Remember?
I remember your ungainly smile.
Shut up!
You won't stand a chance against me with that!
Just hand over Asia and leave.
I refuse!
Issei-san!
As a man, I gotta be able to protect my friends!
Activate! You're gonna double my power, right?
Boost!
Energy is flowing through my body!
Issei-san, Issei-san!
Get it now?
Twice nothing is still nothing.
D-Damn it!
Asia!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
It's amazing.
The pain is disappearing.
Asia, I want you to return with me.
Your Twilight Healing is an extremely rare Sacred Gear, unlike what he has.
I knew it!
You just want me for my power!
If you agree to come back, I'll spare that demon's life.
Cut the crap!
Who'd follow someone like...
Asia, watch out!
Issei-san!
Damn it!
That lance was so much stronger than the one before!
I missed on purpose.
If I hit him, his body will be in pieces.
I doubt you could heal him fast enough.
I understand.
Good girl.
After tonight's ritual, you'll be free
from all hesitation and suffering.
See you later, Issei-kun!
No, Asia!
Farewell,
Issei-san.
Why... am I so weak?
How often must I tell you?
It's not possible.
Forget about her.
You are a member of the Gremory household.
Then please kick me out of your household.
I'll go alone to...
You're asking the impossible.
I'm just a pawn on the chessboard, right?
Losing a single pawn shouldn't...
Enough!
Issei, do you really think the pawn is the weakest piece?
As I said, Evil Pieces possess the same traits as their chess counterparts.
What is the special trait of a pawn?
Promotion.
If a pawn reaches the last of the enemy's lines,
it can be promoted into any piece other than a king.
I could have everyone else's power if I reach there?
As long as I, your master, recognize it as enemy lines, yes.
For example, the church.
And as for your Sacred Gear...
It doubles my power, right? Yuum—
The fallen angel told me.
Use your brain.
Sacred Gear is activated by its owner's will.
The greater your willpower, the more powerful it will become.
My willpower?
An urgent matter came up.
Akeno and I will be out for a bit.
President, we aren't done talking—
Listen. Even with the help of a promotion, a single piece won't stand a chance against a fallen angel.
Yes, I know that.
Are you going?
Yeah. You can't stop me.
You'll get killed.
Even if that's so, I'll free Asia.
I'd like to praise your determination, but it's just too reckless.
Shut up, pretty-boy!
I'll go with you.
You...
Our president said, "Even with the help of a promotion," right?
Yeah.
She also recognized the church as enemy lines.
Then...
At the same time, she implied we should back you up.
Koneko-chan too?
You two going alone would worry me.
This is so boring!
Why do I have to stand guard?
Look who's here.
People call me the fallen angel Mitelt!
Oh my, how courteous of you.
My servant sensed you.
You must be scared about us being on the move.
Not at all.
It's just that we don't want demons interrupting our important ritual.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Our cheerful kids just went there.
Wait, really? Are you serious?
Yes! Boldly through the front gate.
Damn it! I figured you'd be sneaking in from the back!
Well, how many lackeys you bring doesn't really matter anyway.
It won't be a problem.
After all, you two are the only ones who
actually stand a chance of interrupting us.
Thanks for coming all the way out here!
It doesn't matter.
I'm not going to join them.
Oh, you're abandoning them?
What a strong murderous intent!
There must be lots of priests gathered.
Seriously? I'm so relieved you came with me!
We're a team, after all!
And personally, I'm not overly fond of fallen angels and priests.
I despise them.
Kiba?
Huh? Koneko-chan?
They must've noticed we're here anyway.
This is terrible.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
We meet again.
I'm getting sentimental.
Freed!
I never thought I'd meet the same demon twice.
You know, I'm super strong, so once I meet one of your kind
he gets this treatment.
That's why I'm pissed.
About you demon trash hurting my pride!
Where's Asia?
Oh, the junk sister who fell for a demon?
She's at the underground ritual site you can reach through that altar.
Underground, huh?
Well, if you can get past me, that is.
Sacred Gear!
Get crushed.
You're one insolent midget!
"Midget"?
Insolent!
You piss me off!
You're annoying!
You're good!
You're not too shabby either.
It seriously makes me want to kill you.
So he isn't all looks!
I guess I'll get a little serious then.
What is this?!
Holy Eraser, the sword of darkness that consumes all light.
You got a Sacred Gear as well!?
Kiba also has a Sacred Gear?
Hyoudou-kun!
Activate!
Boost!
As I said, you're insolent!
Well, anyway, you know,
if I defeat you, their master, the servants will be nothing.
Come forth, Calawana and Donnasiege!
You're acting cocky.
Unfortunately, we meet again, Lady Gremory.
We need to pay back your servants.
Oh, you're both here.
Promotion!
A rook is a chariot.
It possesses ridiculous defensive ability...
For real?
...and monstrous attack power!
It hurts!
You've done terrible things to Asia!
Now I feel a little better!
Stop... Stop fucking with me, twat!
It hurts!
I don't want to be killed by a demon!
So, farewell!
He ran off!
Anyway, let's go.
There.
It's obvious you intend to interfere with our plan.
Repent with your life!
Akeno.
Got it, President.
What? Are you trying to pull me into a cosplay show?
A barrier?
Isn't this pretty bad?
You can't get out of this cage, I'm afraid.
So, this was your plan all along!
Yes. We came here to get rid of all of you.
My sincerest apologies.
You think we're birds?
You'll just vanish.
Enjoy posing.
Once the ritual is over, even you won't be able to stand in her way.
Welcome, demons.
You are quite late.
Asia!
Issei-san?
Asia, I'm coming now!
Hyoudou-kun, wait!
Sorry to ruin the dramatic reunion,
but the ritual's almost over.
What are you doing to Asia?
I see! That fallen angel's objective was to...
I see, so the fallen angel intends to take the nun's Sacred Gear.
Take her Sacred Gear?
What'll happen to Asia!?
That's...
Then the owner's life will be...
Asia is going to die?
Your Twilight Healing
is finally in my grasp.
The status quo is boring,
so I'm gonna lead your heart!
How amazing is the real you?
soul,
wake
up.
Na
ked
soul,
wake
up.
You might not look all that appealing,
but you won't fool me!
ge
n
za
i
shin
shin
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
Don't
you
know?
Ba
by
I mean, my heart started throbbing
da
tte
i
ma
kyun
kyun
to
shi
te
and I can't tell what it's gonna do in three seconds!
san
byou
byou
I unexpectedly picked up your signal.
cchi
You still don't know anything.
Though my heart's beating fast for you,
shin
cret
and keep it to myself.
nai
sho
de
su
No way I can tell you that!
Let's delve into the curriculum of romance.
STU
DY
NOW!
Don't get stuck on beginner's level!
nyuu
It's not something erasers can erase.
It's written directly on my heart!
chau
no
The pace will depend on my mood, so be prepared!
I don't believe in love horoscopes.
ai
shou
nan
te
shin
ji
na
i
It's the real seconds that count!
shun
DY X
DY
I want more of it!
MEETS
GIRL
This must be destiny.
DY X
DY
Love's unpredictable.
MEETS
GIRL
Let's get together
saa
go
i
ssho
ni
and begin!
ha
ji
me
yo!
Next Episode
This is your reward for getting this far.
You're not going anywhere, bitch!
Don't underestimate Issei.
He is my strongest pawn, after all.
Episode 5 "I'm Gonna Defeat My Ex-Girlfriend!"
Dragon Boost!