You are to light the lanterns hidden in the forest around us.
They're within 500 meter radius around the camp.
Those who can bring back a lit lantern without the fire going out during the next three days
will receive the permission to take part in missions.
However, there are only three lanterns.
Which means that there are only three permissions.
We're in a dark forest. You'll be found out right away.
Huh?
I'm telling you not to use your flames.
This training is designed to turn us against each other.
But if we do that...
It'd be suicide.
Ready...
Huh, what? There's so many of them!
Are they blood-suckers? Demon bugs?
I humbly call upon the Gods of Harvest!
Follow my wishes, leave none unfulfilled!
Ni, give me something for bug repellent!
Ni!
Shiemi?
Shiemi! What's wrong?
Shiemi! Shiemi!
Get lost!
Huh?
Me too.
It's Konekomaru.
He says he found a lantern.
He says it's impossible alone, we've gotta work together.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
You were right, this is impossible alone.
When I saw it, I thought maybe we had misinterpreted the mission...
Yeah. This training requires cooperation.
Rin, you're amazing!
Which planet are you from, Okumura?
I've got an idea.
Hold on tight.
Get going!
It saw you!
This way!
Don't go calling it!
Seal!
Bow to the floor to the Holy Unmovable, the Raging Destroyer King...
He did it!
Now this is one less thing to worry about.
Okumura!
Damn, I can't move.
Rin!
I'm fine! I'll deal with this and catch up with you!
Go on ahead!
You're doing this again?
Sorry.
Idiot! Of course we'll help you!
Shima, your staff!
Don't you break it!
Get ready to run!
Oh great and mighty Unmovable Wise, crush all hesitation.
Swipe aside all obstacles. Hear our prayer. Have mercy.
Return!
Whoa, amazing!
Come on!
This is all I can do!
Run!
Didn't you defeat iiit?
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Episode 15
szia An Act of Kindness
It's not chasing us anymore.
We're saved.
Thanks, Suguro.
I was just returning the favor.
Favor?
You saved me.
You said you wanted to defeat Satan just like me,
without being embarrassed.
Well I'm stupid so I don't really think about that kinda stuff.
I don't think so.
But stop trying to solve everything by yourself!
Don't forget that you're not alone!
Bon's totally right.
You can't defeat Satan alone.
I'll help you, even though I can't do much.
As long as it doesn't involve more bugs.
Guys...
Rin, we're here for you.
Thanks.
But Shima was totally useless this time.
That's not fair, Bon! I did what I could!
What if they knew that I'm the son of Satan?
Hurray, we're all back alive!
Nice. You're still in one piece.
What the hell? You're here already?
I made my familiars do it. Takara was even quicker though.
You took so long with so many people? Lame losers.
Just what is he made of?
What's wrong?
It hurts.
Huh? You're all here? No one gave up?
Then who shot up the fireworks earlier?
It hurts...
Shiemi?
Him? From back then?
Don't just stand there with your jaws on the floor!
Shura!
Go, Behemoth!
I was waiting for ya.
A snake?
I thought I'd have a nice cup of tea while I watch the show,
but this is even better than I expected.
This won't be so easy, Amaimon.
I wanna kill her.
That you won't.
If you try to kill any of them, I'll kill you.
Yes. I apologize. I'll control myself.
A total barrier?
Yeah. It protects everyone inside the circle and attacks everything outside.
For the time being we're safe inside it.
But who was that guy?
Professor, is this training as well?
Ain't this a bit too tough for that!
The training's over.
Now we're gonna prepare for Amaimon's attacks.
Amaimon?
Amaimon... One of the Eight Princes of Hell, the Earth King?
Yeah.
He's a big fish, so big you Esquires won't be able to land even a scratch on him.
Holy Water
I'll soak you in triple-C holy water for extra protection. Come here.
Why is-
such a big fish...
Is this some kind of-
a joke?
Holy Water
Whoopsie, that was close. It wouldn't be a pretty sight if I soaked you.
In the beginning God created the heaven and the earth.
Okay, this will protect you somewhat until you dry.
You're not doing it to Okumura?
Umm... He's, lessee... allergic to holy water.
Allergic to holy water? Is that even possible?!
By the way, where's Yukio?
He was in the way so I sent him away.
What's going on here?
The demon bugs of this forest are supposed to be bound to Tamers.
What's happening?
Why is there an emergency number if no one picks up?
I can't contact the other teachers either.
Why's a big one like Amaimon attacking us?
I wonder...
Hey!
I dunno know why, but he's probably after me.
I know.
Don't worry, this barrier should hold against even Amaimon.
But it looks like he's got some kinda plan this time.
The next time he attacks you'll leave here with the Demon-Slaying Blade.
With the Demon-Slaying Blade?
I bow down to beg your permission.
Take it.
Huh, what? What's wrong?
True Cross Knight Order
Weren't you going on about how you wanted it back?
And weren't you supposed to suppress my power?
You told me not to use my flames!
Shut up already. I warned you,
but you went and used them anyway, didn't you?
I saw it, nyahahaha~
The point is, how are you gonna fight without your flames?
That's...
Amaimon is the King of Earth, he ain't a little imp like the ones you've fought so far.
Think about it.
Moriyama, where are you going?
Shiemi?
Hey, hey, hey! Someone stop her!
Is that a parasite?
Shiemi!
What did you do to her?
I just made a demon bug lay her egg in her.
It took a while for it to hatch and connect to the nerves though.
But now she'll do whatever I command.
Wait, you broccoli!
You wait!
Go! I'll follow you!
Okumura!
You're staying in there no matter what happens! Got it?
That's...
He's doing it again...
Wait!
What the hell do you want from me?
What do you need Shiemi for?
Let's see...
Yeah! I'll make her my wife!
Huh?
Do you promise to be faithful to me in good times and in bad,
in sickness and in health?
Will you love me and honor me
all the days of your life?
Then seal this covenant with a kiss.
Don't screw with me!
That's my line.
Hold back a little, dammit.
Why won't you draw your sword?
Don't be so pretentious.
That shithead!
Bon, don't!
Wait, she told us to stay here!
Bon, calm down...
Man, it's been a while since the last time I was pissed off this badly.
Wipe your ass with that "calm down"!
Not this again...
Shima!
You're kidding me! Stop! You'll get yourselves killed!
I can't believe this...
Why am I surrounded by nothing but idiots? I can't go along!
Hellooo?
Wasn't this girl important to you?
Why aren't you taking this seriously?
Drop dead!
Then I don't need her anymore.
I could take one of her eyes as a souvenir.
One of our cousins has this hobby of collecting human eyeballs, he asked me to bring him some.
Why are you leaving us out of the fun? We're joing in!
Stop! Don't!
Okumura! Get out of there if you have a chance!
I'm here to save Moriyama.
Listen, go back!
Damn!
Koneko, what are you trying to do to Moriyama?
Broccoli...
Shima!
Neko?
Konekomaru!
Were you laughing at me?
I've got no business with you.
Okumura's the one who's pissing me off!
You act all random, then you save a person...
You have no talent, then you save the day...
I can't figure you out!
What the hell are you?
What are you talking about?
I don't like to be ignored.
Stop!
Guys...
You can't defeat Satan alone.
I'll help you, even though I can't do much.
Rin, we're here for you.
Don't forget that you're not alone!
Guys... you were all so kind to me...
Rin!
It's a trap! Don't listen to him!
Yukio, I'm sorry...
I'm not good at lying and tricking people.
So I'll...
I'll use my power for a gentler purpose!
Come! I'll play with you!
Whee!
What's that?
What's happening to Okumura?
That's a demon sword... the Kurikara.
So beautiful!
Burn to ashes!
Tail is one of the weakest points a demon has.
An educated demon would know better and keep it hidden.
You still have loads to learn.
First, your own desires.
Okay.
Are you guys all right?
Where have you been?
I dealt with Amaimon's pet. I wasn't slacking off!
Let's get out of here, it's too dangerous.
You wanted me to take care of this beast, Shiro?
I'm looking forward to it.
Compared to demons who always seek the pleasure in denial,
the moderate ways of humans are easy to corrupt.
So, which way are you taking?
Rin...
This power... It's just like Father's!
Wonderful. I didn't think he could overwhelm Amaimon like this.
You fought enough. Enjoy your rest.
Eins! Zwei! Drei!
Cuckoo Clock!
And now...
He's totally lost control of his flames.
My, my...
What a handful you are, my little brother.
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
It's blue, no matter how I look at it.
Next Episode Preview
Just like that night.
That demon there is the son of Satan?
Precisely.
I'll execute the offspring of Satan!
Gamble