You...
Rin Okumura, the son of Satan!
Yukio...
He is...
an enemy.
Mephisto?
Well done, Pages! Thank you for your good work!
Principal?
What's going on...?
Did you think I'd allow demons over mid-class to enter the Academy?
Doctors, please tend to the wounded.
You can't...
Surprise! I can!
Surprise
This training camp was your Esquire exam at the same time!
During the camp, teachers were observing and testing you.
I'll decide your final grades after reading their reports.
Wait for the announcement, 'kay?
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Damn it!
I can't believe it was a surprise exam...
They had us completely fooled...
Episode 9
szia Memories
We should've considered it...
Will I be all right?
It's pointless to worry about that now.
Compared to you and Shima,
I did hardly anything worth mentioning!
You guys will be fine.
Mr. Okumura told us right before the exam.
An Exorcist cannot fight alone!
...get on well and cool your heads.
They tested our qualities for Esquire in a real battle situation...
But in that case, I was the worst of all.
You'll be fine, I guess.
Those two just sat back and did absolutely nothing.
Don't you have anything to say?
I did it! I got the Claw of the Scaly Dragon.
Shut up, stupid brat! There's nothing I'd want to talk about with you!
He talked! He was so mysterious all the time.
He's so good at ventriloquism!
Damn... Sorry. I woke you up.
It's okay, I'm more or less fine by now.
What were you talking about?
About the exam.
You'll get the best grade, that's for sure.
I don't even want to imagine what would have happened without you there.
Thanks a lot.
Huh? That... no! I should thank you!
You'll pass, that's for sure.
Or we all are failing.
By the way, Okumura, how did you defeat that Ghoul?
Well I just... slashed it with this...
Amazing! You're really fit for a Knight!
Slashed it with that? Would it hurt to be more specific?
You're the greatest mystery.
Yeah, just look at me, I'm a great mistake!
Hey, a mistake?
Mistletoe... Mistilteinn...
You mean mysterious?
He's just a Page but he defeated a mid-class demon without support.
And with a sword? Impossible.
He really is a mystery.
Professor Neuhaus.
May we talk?
What do you want?
Your actions yesterday clearly deviated from the arrangements of the exam.
What are your intentions?
True, there were other teachers on the watch,
but independently putting a student in danger like that
risked the exam itself.
Also...
You tried to make Rin Okumura use his powers in front of other students.
Only a selected few teachers know about him.
Sir Pheles should have briefed you on that.
I acted as I was ordered by Sir Pheles.
Try to kill him, he told me.
What?
Just as you're acting as the brake to his powers,
I was chosen as the accelerator.
It was to understand Rin Okumura's powers as much as possible.
What do you mean?
I mean what I said.
The demon was examined to find out if he's fit for use as a weapon of the Order.
You little genius of an Exorcist are always so busy.
At least share the burden of watching over a demon.
My brother is in relatively good control of his powers and emotions.
At least for now.
You should have seen that yesterday.
Don't underestimate his abilities.
Come on, it's not like I'd actually kill him.
You can relax.
Yesterday was tough, wasn't it, Ni?
Thank you.
But thanks anyway.
Thanks a lot.
Welcome!
Good evening, Shiemi.
Yuki!
Sorry to disturb you this late. Is the Manager here?
She went to stock up so I'm taking care of the shop.
Can I help you with anything?
Aah! It's just the two of us! Aah!
I wanted to talk about your future.
Do you have some time?
I didn't enter the cram school determined to become an Exorcist like the others,
so I didn't really know what to choose...
It's embarrassing to be so half-hearted about it.
Shiemi, do you remember our first meeting?
I had just become an Exorcist,
and I was so nervous.
Don't freak out. Where will you end up if you're already so anxious?
It's just a supply store.
Yes!
Hey, Manager!
I told you about Yukio earlier and today I brought him with me. He's an Exorcist from today!
He's not even 14 yet, so take good care of him for me.
Nice to meet you!
Oh my! Nice to meet you, too!
So young and yet so splendid!
Ah, right, Shiemi!
Shiemi, come out for a second!
That's my Shiemi.
She could be mistaken for a household spirit, couldn't she?
She's my daughter, but she's way too shy.
Shiemi, he's the same age as you but he's an Exorcist teacher already!
Hello... I'm Yukio Okumura.
Hello...
She's as shy as ever.
Sorry... I hoped she'd be interested.
Don't mind her.
Mister!
Huh, me?
It's a charm.
Good luck with your work!
Thanks.
Mister.
That sounds so strange, just call me casually.
For example...
Yuki?
Can I call you Yuki?
Well... it sounds cute... really.
Yeah, that's fine.
Sorry, I was so terrible back then!
I totally admired you! I thought you were amazing!
I'm not that impressive a person.
When I was little I was a crybaby, and my brother had to help me all the time.
You?
He was always doing stuff I couldn't.
So back then I admired him a lot.
Rin is so kind, isn't he?
Yeah.
But people can't stay children forever.
I know that you've worked hard to change.
But you need determination to continue further with your training.
Even more now that you know you have talent as a Tamer.
Talk it through with the Manager and decide before tomorrow's announcements.
With Mom?
Yes. If you become an Esquire, you have to be prepared to risk your life.
You need the consent of your guardian.
I see...
During that test I thought it was useless...
Sorry that it ended up a bit tougher than it should've been.
But a test is a test.
It was controlled not to go beyond a certain level... supposedly.
The teachers were there to ensure your safety.
...it's not like I'd actually kill him.
Sorry, excuse me.
Yuki?
This doesn't feel right.
Mameshiba
Babyshiba tuwned into fwuits.
oppai ni
drinking milk
mero mero
melon-melon
meronshiba
melonshiba
oppai
milk
sui sui
water-water
suikashiba
watermelonshiba
oppai
milk
yada mon
don't want
remonshiba
lemonshiba
oppai
milk
rin rin
app-app
ringoshiba
appleshiba
oppai ni
drinking milk
sukedachi
little fighter
sudachishiba
limeshiba
oppai
milk
ran ran
ram-ram
ranbuutan
rambutan
／人◕ ‿‿ ◕人＼
Didn't you say you wouldn't kill him, Mr. Neuhaus?
Splendid, Yukio Okumura.
Rin!
Shi-Shiemi?! What are you doing here?
Were you trying to seduce me in my sleep?
You wouldn't wake up, so Yuki carried you to another room.
He told me to just stay he-
Come forth!
Why is killing my brother necessary to you?
You're slow.
Look, it is here. For wherever the carcass is, there will the eagles be gathered together.
This is the strongest Naberius I have.
If I could just erase the circle...
You were an enemy after all!
Filthy demon!
Holy water works, even though you wear a human skin.
You can't hide your true nature.
Holy water? As if...
What?
You erased it?
You'll damage your body if you try to summon another.
Do you want to die of blood loss?
Who are you?
I'm a survivor of the Blue Night.
The Blue Night...
The Blue Night took place 16 years ago,
when Satan simultaneously slaughtered many of the world's prominent clergymen.
That?
For a moment Satan possessed my body.
I lost my eye,
and my family who tried to help me.
Satan used my own hands to kill them!
I will never forgive Satan...
Nor any of his demons!
And definitely not the son of Satan!
I will kill you,
even if it costs my life!
Are you satisfied now?
Rin!
If this still isn't enough for you,
I'll fight you as many times as you want.
I'm used to this shit...
Just please...
Don't drag innocent people into this!
As if you'd get away with this!
There are others like me.
Be prepared.
Yuki?! Rin?
Mr. Neuhaus!
You're wounded...
Leave me.
It's closing already.
My wounds have always healed fast.
I'm really a beast.
Yuki! Rin!
Shiemi?
Rin! What happened?!
I'm fine!
A Ghoul wound! That must be treated right away!
It's okay, I'm fine!
No!
Lie down here, right now! Don't overdo it!
Lie down already!
Ni, can you give me some sancho?
Thanks... I'm fine already.
Rin, I've decided.
Huh?
I've made my decision.
What?
He is always doing stuff I can't.
I'm no match to him after all.
Eins, zwei, drei!
You all passed! Congratulations, Esquires!
Hurray!
Congratulations,
Esquires!
Yes!
To celebrate...
we'll have pancakes!
Huh? Pancakes?
Can't we at least have barbeque?!
Pancakes
Ice
You as an Exorcist...
Yeah! I'll help everyone!
Can you fight at all?
I'll do my best!
I'm sorry about professor Neuhaus' actions.
I didn't think a teacher would get so carried away by emotions.
I'll prevent further events like this.
Please.
Mr. Okumura, are you okay with lemonade?
Yeah, lemonade's fine.
Amaimon
It's me.
Yes.
Neuhaus did just as I instructed him, but apparently it was too much for him.
Come to True Cross Academy right away.
I can't enter the campus because of your barriers, Brother.
Neuhaus will lead you through.
We'll talk about the details later. Get it?
Understood.
This should be ready!
Whoa, looks so yummy! I'll help myself!
Oi! Wait a second, hey!
Father and Brother are so obsessed with this Rin Okumura. I wonder how strong he is.
Hope he'll be good to kill my boredom.
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Now, let's have some...
Hey, don't touch that!
Cheese, pork and mochi pancake is one of my top three favorites!
You might be the Principal, but this is first come, first serve.
Hot! Too hot!
You demon!
You will kill it?
Next Episode Preview
There's no Exorcist at the Academy able to tame a demon of that level.
Shiro is dead. He's dead.
You're liars!
Cat Sith