This is the wood of the cross on which hung the Saviour of the world...
Come let us worship.
A living sacrifice?
After years of research I found out that
the best place to connect Gehenna and Assiah is here,
at the top of the True Cross Academy that Mephisto founded.
The stage was ready,
but the quality of the blood we had collected was too low.
We couldn't summon the Gehenna Gate with impure blood.
However, if we were to add Rin's blood, it would change everything.
Huh?!
A mere 5 litres would greatly increase the purity
and allow us to summon a giant Gehenna Gate.
It's impossible! Even if you drained all of his blood, it wouldn't be enough!
That would be true for a human.
Extreme blood loss is no problem with his demonic regeneration.
Rin will be remembered as a hero by the generations to come,
a martyr who died protecting Assiah!
Let my brother go right now!
It's pointless to shoot me.
The plane carrying the Messiah warhead has already departed from the Dragoon Laboratory.
Soon it will pass over the True Cross Academy.
The plane takes orders only from me.
If we don't open the Gehenna Gate, the Messiah will hit the Academy.
What?!
We've already passed the point of no return.
Then... Use me instead!
What?
I will open the Gehenna Gate,
so let Rin go!
Very well.
Is even this according to your plans, Brother?
Those brothers are like two sides of a mirror.
Had he not drawn the Demon-Slaying Blade that day,
their fates would have been different.
What will be left after the chaos passes? Hope... or despair?
Even I am excited to see the outcome!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Episode 23
Truth
This is the wood of the cross on which hung the Saviour of the world.
Come let us worship.
Ye people: what have I made you?
Rin...
or in what have I offended you? Answer me.
O Sacred God,
O Strong saint,
O immortal saint, have mercy...
Are you all right?!
Great, the power really grows exponentially if the twin's blood gets mixed in!
This...
What the hell is this? What's going on here?!
That's the young prof, ain't it?
No way...
Yuki told me he had no demonic powers...
Then what are those blue flames?
Yuki!
Stay back!
What?
What?!
Come, Messiah!
Let us burn Gehenna with the flames of science!
Then the fifth angel blew his trumpet
and I saw
a star that had fallen to earth from the sky
Damn! Run!
and he was given the key to the shaft of the bottomless pit.
When he opened it, smoke poured out as though from a huge furnace,
and the sunlight and air turned dark from the smoke.
What's that light?
Behold, this is the light of man's wisdom!
It is the proof of our victory, the shine of Jacob's Ladder!
What?
What is this?
Then locusts came from the smoke and descended on the earth,
and they were given power to sting like scorpions.
Their king is the angel from the bottomless pit
his name in Hebrew is Abaddon, and in Greek, Apollyon - the Destroyer.
Bugs!
Dammit! We've gotta get away!
What's going on here? Didn't the Messiah activate?
Looks like it was a failure.
This voice...
As if you could even scratch Gehenna with a tiny spark like that.
No way... Father?
Exactly. I'm Satan, your daddy.
You filthy demon!
Don't imitate Father's voice to try and lead me astray!
I'm not imitating.
He was the last person I possessed, so even my voice is like his now.
Shut up!
If you had never troubled Assiah, Father wouldn't have died,
and Mother wouldn't have been killed either!
You got that wrong, kiddo.
I didn't kill Yuri. He did.
Help me, Yukio!
Don't look like you don't get it.
Let me show you, through my own fucking eyes.
I was looking for you, Yuri!
Why are you living in this forest all alone?
You're causing so damn much trouble!
Pack up your stuff. We're going back to the Vatican.
This hobgoblin smells like sunshine again.
Listen to me, dammit!
I'm not going back to the Vatican.
This is my home.
Do you know what people are calling you?
"The Witch of the Forest."
The woman bedeviled by demons.
You're supposed to be an Exorcist.
You shouldn't get any more buddy-buddy with demons.
You're turning it into a mess because you think of humans and demons separately!
They're my important friends, you know!
Wait, Yuri!
We can't allow someone from the famed Egin family of the Vatican to be associated with demons.
Use any means necessary.
Get it?
Understood.
What are you doing?!
Stop!
They are my friends!
Don't make me laugh!
These demons are just tricking you!
We'll wipe out all of them!
That's the purpose of Exorcists!
Please, stop!
I told you to stop!
Blue flames... Are you...
the Demon King, Satan?!
Have you come to?
I'm sorry.
Since when? Since when is that monster in Assiah?
One year ago...
I was dispatched to this area to investigate spontaneous human combustion cases.
Fragile... Too fragile!
It seems I could tolerate those flames.
The Order of the True Cross ordered me to return,
but I stayed in the forest.
I wanted to talk to those flames again.
Do you know who I am?
Get lost already. Or I will kill you too!
If that's what you want...
Don't make me laugh!
I could hear your voice back then.
Everything I touch in Assiah burns to ashes.
That's so lonely...
No matter how much you love something, it just turns into ashes in your hands.
That's so sad...
Shut up, bitch!
If you really feel like that, just use my body.
You let him in?! Satan?!
Yeah. He seemed happy.
Poor little one, it fell from the nest. It's dead already.
Dead?
It means its life is gone.
What's life?
Everything living in this world,
every bug and flower and bird, and even humans,
everything has just one of it.
Every single life is different and unique.
It's very precious.
I want to live too.
You can't just buy or give life.
But you can grow it.
You didn't...
Yes I did.
His children are growing within me.
What?!
What a shame, Fujimoto.
You have your desires like everyone else, but she's the daughter of the Cardinal...
I didn't do anything!
Yuri is possessed by a demon!
And it's not just any normal demon! It's the Demon King Satan!
You were the only one to visit her there.
We will listen to your excuses in court.
Wait! There is no time! Yuri must...
Children of a demon?
Impossible! Operate her right away!
That is banned by the Vatican itself.
Are you telling me to let her bear them?
I will.
Yuri!
They are our children.
I will give birth to them and raise them.
Damn witch...
Accused Yuri Egin,
is it true that you carry the children of a demon?
It is.
Demons often pull pranks and scare humans,
but that just shows how curious they are.
We should learn to love each other.
Demons and love?!
Witch!
Burn her!
Right, right!
I will now deliver the sentence.
Accused Yuri Egin is determined guilty, and sentenced to death!
To save Yuri, I looked for a vessel for myself,
but my power was too great.
No one had a body strong enough to endure my presence.
Withdraw!
Don't be foolish! Who will protect Assiah if we fall?!
Damn demons...
This body won't last long.
Satan... Is that you?!
Run, Yuri...
Long time no see, Fujimoto.
Mephisto, what happened?
Satan attacked.
He came to take back his wife and children.
The Exorcists who could become his vessel have been turned into sacrifices.
You are the only Exorcist capable of action in the Vatican.
Cardinal...
Yuri Egin escaped with help from Satan.
Kill her. And her offspring as well!
What's this?
The Kurikara, a demon sword with the power of the Holy Unmovable.
It may come handy to kill the children of Satan.
Shiro...
You... Those kids...
They are my sons... Aren't they cute?
The one with the blue flames is Rin.
The pale-skinned one is Yukio.
They will... live strong...
They will prove that demons and humans can understand each other.
Wake up, Yuri! Yuri!
What will you do?
The Vatican ordered you to kill the children together with their mother.
The woman died by herself though.
With demonic powers, life would be suffering for them.
What is it? I thought you were going to slay them.
He laughed...
Though I came here to kill them...
You're turning it into a mess because you think of humans and demons separately!
Mephisto.
Yes?
I will raise them.
I will raise them well as human kids!
You, feared for your cold-heartedness, raising the children of a demon?
No way in hell!
Just wait and see!
Then how about making a gamble with me?
If you can raise them as humans, you win.
If they awaken to their demonic powers, I win,
and their lives are mine.
Okay with me.
Then let me help you a little.
What have you done?
I've sealed the demonic power in this sword.
There's no reason for the gamble if he's always covered in blue flames.
Thanks.
No need to thank me.
Now I shall report back to the Vatican that we finished the demon's children.
I bid you farewell.
Truth my ass!
What should I believe?
What I've showed you is merely the truth.
If you think I lied, ask your precious Pope who's sinking over there.
Help me, Yukio...
Tell me the truth!
Did you order Mother... Yuri Egin to be burnt?!
This isn't the time...
Answer!
Now!
Yes, it was my order.
That thing said she'd give birth to a demon's offspring!
Human children are one thing, but a demon's?
Didn't you love her?!
Yuri was already dead to me.
She died the day she gave birth to you demonic filth!
Your existence itself is a stain on the Egin name! I will never accept that!
That...
No...
Finally, I've got the perfect vessel.
You have my blood as well.
I can feel every inch of you as my own!
Let's throw a feast to celebrate the descent of your lord Satan!
Rin!
Are you all right?
Yukio... Is that Yukio?
What are you doing, Yukio?!
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
No Gehenna and no Assiah, a single world where demons and humans can live together.
Next Episode Preview
Close your eyes and try to imagine it.
It should be easy.
Satan's Offspring