Eh? Lelouch went to a resort when you were both young, and that's where you met each other?
That's why we really haven't spent that much time together.
Hey, can you stop speaking in such a formal manner?
We are in the same grade after all.
Ah...
Okay, sorry.
Yup. Yup.
But I see.
You're the first person I met who knows a bit about Lelouch's childhood.
That guy never says anything about it.
Can you pass me that 12 millimeter wrench?
Don't you need an 11 millimeter one for that?
Ah, that's right...
You are sure familiar with this.
The RR1200 from BMC.
It sure is a nice bike.
Oh, you can tell?
Before I joined the army, the person who took care of me rode this model.
My job was to service and wash it.
I was told, "Gosh, I'll kill you if you ride it without permission!"
I was never allowed to ride it.
Wait!
"Gosh"? That sounds feminine... was it a woman?
Yes.
A girlfriend?
No way.
Then... your elder sister?
Don't tell me... your mother?
You are terribly wrong.
I don't have any family.
Besides, the person who took care of me has already...
Ah... this is bad...
I asked something inappropriate.
Don't worry. It's just the truth.
Then... what about your house?
I don't have any.
The unit I'm assigned to is currently stationed at the university across the street.
I'm living at the lodging house there.
Then why don't you stay at the one in the school?
I don't have a roommate in my room.
If it's fine with you...
But I have my work.
I made the choice myself to join the army.
I see.
Yes. But thanks, Rivalz.
Lloyd-san!
Hurry and tidy up your documents!
The luggage that was sent over hasn't been sorted either.
I'll leave all the stuff here to you.
You should know my work style by now, right?
I was thinking about how many years it's been since we met each other at the university's laboratory.
That is... Well... now that I think about it, it's been way too long.
You really like it, don't you?
Eh? W-What are you saying?
I... erm... don't really...
I'm referring to research.
Ah, I understand! I understand!
It's all thanks to His Highness Schneizel that we're able to do anything we want here, right?
Oh? What's wrong?
You look like you're trying to solve the equation for the Surge Cannon.
It's nothing.
Well then, is it okay for all the general affairs of this Technological Department of Special Dispatch Envoys to come under my command?
I'll leave it to you.
Warrant Officer Suzaku, reporting back, awaiting orders.
Suzaku-kun, you can't do that.
You must say, "I'm back" at a time like this.
But if I say that...
It's fine.
It's decided then.
In here, put military and social ranking aside.
It's fine, right?
As you wish.
Then Suzaku-kun, why don't you try and say it?
That's right.
Treat it as if you have just returned to your own home.
My own home?
Yes. After all, this place is like our home, isn't that so?
I-I'm back.
Say it louder and with more energy!
I'm back!
Well...
Welcome back!
Well then.