The first semester's finally over...
Okumura!
Konekomaru!
It looks like most of the normal students are going home.
You're all from Kyoto, right?
That's so nice and elegant...
What's so elegant about that? It's totally normal.
I'm not sure we're going home eith-
Izumo, you should go home too if you have the time.
Yeah, if I feel like it.
You're going home too, Paku? We'll be so lonely...
We'll meet again next semester.
Take care.
If you start missing my voice, just give me a call.
Renzo Shima
You idiot!
Thanks.
"Finally the fun summer is here."
That's what I'd like to say, but you Esquires will now take part
in a three-day long combat training camp.
I and professor Kirigakure here will be watching over you.
Yoohoo.
This training camp is also a test to see if you are fit to take part in missions.
So put your spirit into it!
Yessir!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Episode 14
szia A Fun Camp
Whoa, this feels like a picnic! I'm so excited!
In the evening we can have a campfire and dance and...
Umm, what's Shima doing...?
He can't stand bugs. He's always been like that.
It's so hot...
This is so heavy...
This forest is really peaceful during the day, but in the night it'll be swarming with minor demons.
We must set up our camp before that.
Let's hurry.
What the hell? Doesn't this heat get to him at all?
Come on, keep walking.
Huh? Professor, where's your backpack?
Over there.
This is so nice and cold! I'll have a gulp.
Okumura has some demonic strength.
This'll be our campsite. Now, you boys will help me set up the tents,
and the girls will set up the magic circle and prepare dinner with professor Kirigakure.
Let's begin!
He took it off after all.
I was starting to think he's not even human.
This is turning more and more into a picnic!
It's a camp, for God's sake.
If you beat it like that, it'll...
Just what I was saying!
This is so much fun...
What is? It's just sweltering hot...
The guys are so strange...
You're the only strange one here.
I hate you.
Please teach me how to put on the uniform!
Usually you don't go talking to someone who told you she hates you.
What?
Nothing! Hurry and finish your part!
Sure!
They're all so weird.
Are you done yet?
Her too...
Just a little more!
Ouch!
Curry Mix
I can't watch this any longer! Give it to me!
Let's eat!
This is great! What the hell?
His wife will have no chance...
Okumura, you're so good at cooking!
So tasty!
Well...
This is his only productive ability.
Shut up, moley four-eyes.
I could eat so many helpings of this.
True Cross Knight Order
You eat a lot, don't you, Moriyama?
I haven't felt like this before...
Use your strength for someone else... For some gentler purpose.
Rin, where are you going? Rin!
Culture Festival
I see...
I was always skipping school, so I never took part in events like this.
Hey Okumura, what do you wanna drink?
Is this what it's like to have friends?
I'll come and choose myself.
Shiemi?
I was worried because Rin was acting so weird lately.
But he seems to be having fun. It makes me glad.
You're really paying attention to him.
No, nevermind.
Now let me explain you the details of the training.
Woohoo, a test of courage!
Shura, you're on duty.
Wait a sec, that chick said she's 18! She's still a minor!
18? What are you saying?
This year she's turning twenty-si-
Whoops. My hand slipped.
Do your goddamn work.
Look, he's mad now! Woohoo!
Now let me explain. You are to light the lanterns hidden in the forest around us.
They're within 500 meter radius around the camp.
Those who can bring back a lit lantern without the fire going out during the next three days
will receive the permission to take part in missions.
However, there are only three lanterns.
Which means that there are only three permissions.
That's...
Next, the contents of your shoulder bags.
Three days' worth of water, food and other necessities.
There's also a compass, matches, demon-repelling fireworks and a flashlight.
The best way to succeed is to use your own abilities to the fullest.
So we just have to find the lanterns, light them and come back, right?
Isn't that too simple?
Don't you get it?
This ain't gonna be as easy as the Esquire exam.
We're in a dark forest. You'll be found out right away.
Huh?
I'm telling you not to use your flames.
Don't forget that I'm still a High Inspector.
If someone finds out that you possess Satan's power, I will have to report it to the higher-ups.
Then Arch Knights and the Paladin and who knows what other things worse than demons will come to hunt you down.
See? Use your head in this fight.
Where'd your enthusiasm go?
Are you scared or something?
Huh?
Bon... This training is designed to turn us against each other.
But if we do that...
It'd be suicide.
"Every man for himself" is the correct answer here.
No helping each other.
There are only three lanterns after all. Of course I'll do my best.
Just don't take it as an offense.
Without relying on my power...
Then, get to your positions. Ready...
Huh, what? There's so many of them!
I told you on the way earlier, but the forest is now a nest of minor demons.
I think you should be able to make it through at your current level.
Are they blood-suckers? Demon bugs?
If you get in trouble, use the demon-repelling fireworks.
Professor Kirigakure or I will come to your aid right away.
Why is there only one match?
If you light the fireworks, you can't light the lantern. Think carefully before using it.
I humbly call upon the Gods of Harvest!
Follow my wishes, leave none unfulfilled!
After he had served his own generation by the will of God
fell on sleep, and was laid unto his fathers,
and saw corruption!
Thou shalt not suffer thine Holy One to see corruption.
Ni, give me something for bug repellent!
Ni...
Shiemi? Shiemi! What's wrong?
Shiemi!
Get away from her!
Shiemi! Shiemi!
Get lost!
Damn!
Calm down, calm down, calm down...
God's flames... God's flames...
I'm such an idiot... I did it again.
Using my flames is turning into a habit...
Shiemi! Shiemi!
You... What was that just now?
What was that just now?
Did he see it?
Is Moriyama okay?
Yeah, I think so. But she's unconscious.
Turn off your flashlight already.
The light is attracting the bugs.
Oh, okay.
He didn't see me?
Anyway, what was that blue light earlier?
It flared up so suddenly, I couldn't see what it was...
Dunno... I couldn't see it either.
It could've been that... Umm, what, I wonder...
That's good. Looks like he didn't see me.
And what are you here for?
What do you mean? To help her, of course.
You said no helping each other...
Shut up! I can't just go on when I hear a girl screaming like that!
Shiemi is alright, so just leave her to me and go on ahead.
Leave her to you? What do you mean?
I'll take her back to the camp.
Then I'll head out again.
You...
Rin?
Shiemi!
Ni!
N-Ni...
Don't worry, if you draw a magic circle on a paper you can summon your familiar again.
Really?
Huh? Something's missing...
Did it fall out when I was attacked?
It looked like some huge moth.
Hit the dirt!
Shima?
Bon?
What happened to the "not helping each other" part?
And what about you? Anyway, off with the light!
Okay.
Well... Lots of moths attacked me, they were all around me and then I sorta blacked out...
You never change.
Huh?
Me too.
It's Konekomaru.
He says he found a lantern.
He says it's impossible alone, we've gotta work together.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
I found the lantern.
Now I'm sure it's impossible to clear
this training alone. Let's cooperate.
See, it didn't take ten minutes and he used his powers already!
Though in this darkness it'd blind anyone so I guess it's alright.
I'm afraid I can't hide his powers anymore.
You sound like some old fart!
What are you planning to do, Shura?
You haven't reported to the Vatican and you're not doing anything here...
I'm assessing the situation. I've decided to teach him about swords.
Really? Why?
He told me he wants to become a Paladin!
I have a thing for boys who aim high.
I didn't know what to make of it when Shiro asked me though.
Father did?
I'm not exactly happy to admit it, but I think he was right about how to temper that kid.
That woman knows we're here. So cheeky.
Amaimon, have you greeted the king of this forest yet?
Yes. I killed lots of its kin, so it's cooperative.
Let me watch the show this time.
That woman is hiding the Demon-Slaying Blade.
How should I make the boy mad?
I'm glad you're so enthusiastic, but this time you will do as I say.
He's not listening...
You were right, this is impossible alone.
This is the lantern? It's so huge!
Looks like a stone garden lantern.
It's a peg lantern.
It waits in the night for someone to light it,
and as soon as it's been lit it starts moving,
hunts down living things and uses them as fuel.
Usually women are its favorite.
It's a demon that stops moving with dawn or when its fuel runs out.
When I saw it, I thought maybe we had misinterpreted the mission...
Yeah. This training requires cooperation.
Oh, Bon? I recall you saying something about "no helping each other"?
Because he said that there are only three permissions!
Yeah, he never said only for three people, did he?
Let's all get to it. Does anyone know Kamiki's or Takara's number?
I asked Izumo a bunch of times, but she never gave me her number.
Anyway, I thought up a formation how the five of us can carry this.
Konekomaru Formation
I'll seal it so that it can't move when we light it.
The secret sutra of praising the Holy Unmovable.
Bon memorized the whole of the sutra we need, so he'll do the chanting.
Bow to the floor to the Holy Unmovable,
We should gather some demon bugs to feed the peg lantern with.
the Raging Destroyer King. And beg for his kindness...
It needs feeding so that the fire won't go out. That will be your job, Moriyama.
Here they come!
Shima and I will protect us from the demon bugs attacking in masses.
And finally...
The strongest one of us will be pulling the cart.
Rin, you're amazing!
Which planet are you from, Okumura?
Here we gooo!
Someone's giving up already?
You go pick the kid up!
Okay, but then you have to stay awake!
Who was that?
Either Kamiki or Takara.
Manifest the flames of Garuda, burn the sea of curses.
What happened?
What do we do about this?
Protect those seeking enlightenment, give them peace and determination.
Lo-Look down!
There's a ton of them!
I think I might've just wet myself.
Wouldn't it help if you just got over it?
Okumura, don't say such silly things!
And if you wet yourself, you'll lose all respect!
Heading to the Lotus Treasury World, waiting for the Great King
Bon!
unyielding for ages.
Meditate and learn the wisdom of the gods.
What are you doing?!
Those are the Seeds of Khan! It looks like something's already sealed here.
Live peacefully in the world and give equally to everyone,
Be careful, guys!
I've got an idea.
I only wish to be spared in the destruction
and be solid like vajra beside the Great King.
Make the peg
lantern cross by itself.
But how?
I see! I think I get it!
Let me learn the three great mysteries.
I'll draw it.
Use the power of wisdom to serve as you can.
Okumura is
crazy strong
Bug swarm
Konekomaru
Me
Moriyama
Shima
First Konekomaru and I bring the cart across.
The swarm isn't deep so you can walk through it?
Neko
Oku
Bug swarm
Seal
Use the power of wisdom to bring justice to the world.
I'll prepare the seal on the other side.
Mori
Shi
Me
On this side, Moriyama piggy-backs Shima and waits.
Remove seal
Bon removes the seal from the lantern and frees it.
Bug swarm
Then I run as fast as I can to the other side with Moriyama on my back.
And the peg lantern will come chasing the girl.
Then I'll seal it again.
SEAL!
Right...
You're good.
You're so good at drawing!
Are you telling me to dive into the bug swarm?
With Moriyama's thighs around my head?
I'm gonna be so dead.
You should tame your worldly desires, Shima.
You're so mean, Koneko!
Then I'll carry her too, dammit.
Hold on tight.
Be careful.
Sorry.
Splashing like that...
I'm ready!
We're ready too!
Get going!
It saw you!
This way!
Don't go calling it!
Seal!
Bow to the floor to the Holy Unmovable, the Raging Destroyer King...
He did it!
Rin, we did it!
Okumura, come on out.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Now this is one less thing to worry about.
Rin, behind you!
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
Next Episode Preview
Rin, it's a trap! Don't fall for it!
I'm no good at lying and tricking people...
So I...
An Act of Kindness