The Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon.
There have been some bad rumors about Her Highness, Princess Euphemia but...
You're referring to the incident at Kaminejima, right?
It has been said that she came into contact with Zero during it.
Don't tell me it's connected to the top level?
That can't be possible.
The Governor-General isn't the only one questioning her actions.
Even so, if they are connected to that side...
Yes, we need to break off any ties with them.
Too late.
We have gathered all the evidence, Undersecretary.
You have been receiving benefits from the NAC.
General Darlton, thank you.
With this...
With this, I can finally eliminate those insolent fools who exploited His Highness Clovis.
Due to Her Highness Princess Euphemia's idea for a Specially Administrated Zone,
the number of rats that were thrown into confusion was a lot larger than I thought.
The number of applicants for the Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon has exceeded 200,000.
Looks like this figure will continue to rise.
It's all thanks to you.
Huh?
It's all because someone like you, a representative of the Japanese people, is here.
That's why everyone believes in this place, right?
No. It's because it was an announcement from a Princess herself, isn't that so?
I really am... thankful.
I should be the one thanking you.
You will help me with various things in the future, right?
Yes, Your...
Geez.
Okay.
This is the first time that Britannia has tried to make something like the Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon,
and it is something Princess Euphemia herself decided.
Considering that Her Highness was still a student just a few days back before she announced this radical plan,
we can't deny the possibility of that fact influencing her decision.
Even though it's something Princess Euphemia said...
As you can see, the plan is being carried out smoothly.
I'm still...
Tomorrow's ceremony will be broadcasted to the whole world.
Euphie sure is amazing.
With this, the terrorist cells within Area 11 will lose the support of the people and collapse.
Public order will be restored too.
Personally, I'm against this plan.
But you understand. That's why you sent Darlton to assist her, right?
I must put an officially announced political measure into action.
That is the obvious step for me to take as the Governor-General.
Hmm...
Are you going to accept what is going to happen to Euphie from an official standpoint?
The Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon. That isn't something bad.
Can we find any value in the Japan they give us?
The current situation is the result of our resistance.
There's no need to feel ashamed.
Lord Kirihara, I heard that, due to your close ties with the extraction of Sakuradite,
you have been promised a considerable position within the Specially Administrated Zone.
There's no such thing. I am just invited to attend the ceremony.
What a good excuse.
You all...
What about Zero?
What will the Order of the Black Knights do?
The situation is serious.
Not only our supporters, but also members of the Order are showing interest in joining the Specially Administrated Zone.
The Specially Administrated Zone is different from the Order of the Black Knights since there aren't any risks.
Also, it's a princess from an established lineage compared to a masked man whose identity is unknown.
Just based on looks alone, it's obvious which side is more dependable.
Kyoto said that they are going to support them too.
Why the heck is that?
Because they said that we'll be treated equally.
Equally? Words alone can't be trusted.
I agree.
But if we don't decide upon a countermeasure soon...
You say that you want to join the Specially Administrated Zone?
Over there, it doesn't matter if you're a Britannian or an Eleven...
Hey.
Why don't we follow Euphemia's proposal and have the Order of the Black Knights join them?
As I was saying, a promise from Britannia is...
What Zero said doesn't contradict with joining the Specially Administrated Zone, right?
But that is...
They will use the pretense of peace to force us to disarm.
That will be troublesome.
We will be controlled by the system and lose our independence.
However, we will be branded as the enemy of freedom and equality if we don't join them.
That is why we should join them first!
Even though there's no guarantee?
But we can't ignore this!
I'm sorry for making you take a side trip.
Well, you accompanied me to buy stuff after all.
I heard that you're going to meet up with Shirley.
Well, she wants to buy something too.
Lately there have been too many disturbances due to the creation of the Specially Administrated Zone.
Yeah, yeah.
More importantly, isn't it better for you to hurry and patch things up with Shirley?
What's this about the Specially Administrated Zone?
What's this about providing support?
Who would sign for such a thing?!
Oh, my, my.
Looks like he's an aristocrat.
Isn't equality already in place?
Those below should be obedient and listen to those on top!
Indeed, that is the true reason behind the benevolence of the Vice Governor-General.
Who are you?
You feel great looking down at people, don't you?
Student, that's enough. Step back.
You should hurry up and go home.
Yes, I should. I shall take my leave here then.
Huh? H-Hey...
What are you saying?
Come back, damn it!
What's wrong, Mr. Aristocrat?
Don't confuse borrowed strength with your own strength.
A bastard like you should just die without people knowing...
Well, well, let's stop here.
Old guy, why don't you say something apologetic?
I-Insolent! I am...!
Get lost!
Ah... Thank you very much.
I-It's nothing.
He saved an Eleven, even though he is Zero...
No, because he IS Zero?
If that's so, why was he together with Princess Euphemia?
No, it might become dangerous if I delve too deeply into this.
NAC. No, it seems that you're called "Kyoto" among the terrorists.
You will dissolve during the ceremony tomorrow and leave Fuji.
We are willing to discuss carrying on our business dealings with you if you dissolve unconditionally.
Of course you must cease your support of the Order of the Black Knights.
Whether Zero comes tomorrow or not, that man's defeat has already been ascertained.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Brother.
Where's Shirley-san?
Well, in the end she didn't come.
I couldn't contact her either.
I guess she's teaching you a lesson.
It seems that you have been acting coldly towards her lately.
Is that so?
I'll reflect upon my actions.
Ah, Sayoko-san, can you get me a cup of tea?
Okay, I understand.
Is there something that you're worried about?
Eh?
About Sister Euphie?
I won't say something willful like "I want to see her again."
Since it will cause trouble for Brother, as well as Sister Euphie.
Do you like Euphie?
Yes. Brother, you like her as well, right?
Yes. I did like her.
This is the site where the memorial ceremony for the establishment of the Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon is being held.
The site is filled with Elevens, no, Japanese people.
A large number of Japanese people who couldn't get in have gathered outside of the venue.
Lesley-san, has Zero appeared yet?
No, it seems that, even now, he hasn't contacted anyone.
Note: Yao Long Zhi Fang literally means "House of Biting Dragons" in Chinese.
Why couldn't Zero come? He wouldn't appear.
The data we have on him should be the truth.
Princess Euphemia, it's time.
Okay.
Zero...
It's Zero.
Zero appeared!
You've arrived!
Did you accept your defeat?
What are you planning?
I intended to bring your identity with me to my grave.
Everything will come to an end if the fact that Zero is a prince of Britannia is revealed.
It will be mistakenly thought that this is all a plot going on between Britannians.
It'll be the end of this Specially Administrated Zone.
The target is Zero.
Shoot him if anything abnormal happens.
Yes, my Lord.
Welcome, Zero!
Welcome to the Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon!
Euphemia Li Britannia.
I have something to discuss with you after I land.
With me?
Yes, with you alone.
Something major has happened!
Zero has appeared in a majestic manner.
He's now heading towards the G1 base according to Princess Euphemia's instructions.
Looks like we should have gone as well.
It can't be helped, right?
"Zero won't appear if Lancelot is standing there ready and waiting." Everyone was saying that, right?
There shouldn't be any problem.
Then, this way please.
Princess Euphemia.
It's indeed too dangerous to be left alone with this man.
At least let me...
It'll be fine. Please believe in me.
Hey, how long are we going to stay here and wait?
Zero told us to wait here. Don't you trust him?
But...
Everything was done to confirm Britannia's real intentions.
Vice Commander.
Y-Yes?
It's because we know their intentions that our entire force is lying in ambush in every direction, right?"
Assumption is dangerous!
Even Diethard and Rakshata are on standby.
Zero is most likely intending to make Euphemia...
You sure are cautious.
The camera has already been switched off.
It because I've always been hiding.
Thanks to a certain Imperial Empire.
This is a ceramic needlegun.
Detectors can't find this.
Lelouch, you won't fire at me, right?
Yes, I won't fire at you.
Euphie, the one firing it will be you.
Eh?
I wonder if she's all right. She's alone with Zero after all...
But this is an order.
I've handed her a call switch to notify us during an emergency.
What's wrong?
W-Why are you with Zero?
Looks like he can see me.
Is it due to the influence of the close contact and the incident at Kaminejima?
Or is this guy also...?
If that's the case...
This ceremony is being broadcasted around the world.
During it, if a princess of Britannia, like you, fires a shot at Zero...
What do you think will happen?
A revolt will break out, right?
Yes. Zero will become a martyr if he was tricked into being shot.
Your popularity will drop to rock bottom as well.
What nonsense are you saying?
Together with me, we'll make Nippon...
Aren't you just unilaterally forcing your opinions down upon others?
Isn't that the same as what Clovis did?
Eh?
All the conditions have already been cleared.
Zero will hover between life and death before reviving miraculously.
People react easier to miracles than reasoning.
Here, take it.
Huh?
There can only be one messiah.
Once the people realize that you're a fake, the people will...
I-Indeed...
I only want to ask you a question.
You're...
Don't tell me it's already...
Hey, what's wrong?
Major Kururugi!
Bitch, what did you just do?!
Lelouch!
Stop it!
Stop feeling pity for me!
I won't accept sympathy from you!
I'll try and achieve it with my own power!
I'm willing to taint myself to do that!
Euphemia Li Britannia!
I have already relinquished that name!
I think it won't be long before the main country announces it.
I have relinquished my rights to succeed to the throne as well.
Why?
Don't tell me it's because you accepted Zero.
Since they listened to my selfish request,
in return I have to pay an appropriate price, right?
You sure abandoned it easily.
Are you going to say it was for my sake?
As usual, you sure are conceited.
It's for Nunnally's sake.
That girl said that she doesn't need anything else as long as she can stay with her brother.
Just because of that?
I made up my mind just because of that.
It made me think about what is most important to me.
Lelouch, that is why, I won't abandon anything that is really, really important to me.
Don't worry, I didn't say anything about the two of you.
What about Cornelia?
It's not as if I won't get to see her again...
You sure are an idiot.
A big idiot.
Lelouch, even though I have never beaten you in a game or academically...
However, because of your recklessness, you managed to attain everything in the end.
Come to think of it, before you're a Vice Govenor-General or a princess,
you're just Euphie.
Since I'm just Euphie, are you willing to work together with me?
To me...
you're the worst kind of enemy I face.
You win.
Eh?
Lets plan how we can make this Specially Administrated Zone survive.
Ah, but I don't intend to become your subordinate.
Okay!
But you sure don't have any confidence in me.
Hmm?
Lelouch, you thought that I would shoot you if you threatened me?
A-Ah, you're mistaken.
No one is able to go against any order I give, if I'm serious about it.
"Shoot me." "Relieve Suzaku from duty."
It's the same no matter what order.
Geez, you keep cracking weird jokes.
It's the truth.
For example, if I say "Kill the Japanese."
It doesn't matter what you think.
No... I... No...
I don't want to kill them!
No...
Don't tell me...!
That's right, I must kill the Japanese.
What?
I've become like Mao. I can't turn off my Geass!
Forget the order I just gave you!
Euphie!
Euphie, please wait!
Yes. Since I've finished my discussion with the Chinese Federation,
I'll go back to the main country today.
But the experimental specimen is still here.
Hmm, what about his mental abilities?
There's a limit to what we can do in Area 11.
I see.
I'll talk to the laboratory in Rosenberg.
Can you send him over together with the experimental machine as a set once I've contacted them?
I understand.
Also, about the miracle that happened at Kaminejima...
Let's wait for public order to be restored in Area 11 first.
I'm thankful that the Specially Administrated Zone was created to accomplish that.
It's all thanks to Euphemia that everything has proceeded along smoothly.
Vice Govenor-General, where's Zero?
Everyone who calls themselves Japanese:
I have a request.
Can you all die?
Eh?
What did she just say?
She's lying, right?
Stop joking.
Huh? Suzaku?!
Did he just lose consciousness?
But why?
Erm...
I hoped that you would all commit suicide, but is that impossible?
Then, can all the soldiers please annihilate them?
It's a massacre!
Huh? Is she serious?
Cut off the microphones and cameras!
Euphie, stop it!
Stop!
Move aside!
You terrorist...
Move away!!!
Now, will all the soldiers please hurry?
Princess Euphemia!
What is going on?
Please stop. Doing such things is...
General!
I'm sorry... But I must annihilate the Japanese.
Do it, everyone from Britannia!
Kill the Elevens. Eliminate all the Elevens with all your effort.
Don't let even one escape.
Stop! What are you doing?
I'm an Honorary Knight from Britannia, Kururugi Suzaku!
Stop the battle right now!
Our orders are to obliterate the Japanese.
It was issued by Princess Euphemia herself.
What? By Princess Euphemia?
Stop saying something so foolish!
You're Japanese, aren't you?
What?
What is going on inside?!
Gun salute?
That can't be possible. What about the television?
The broadcast has been terminated.
Euphie, stop it!
This was... caused by my Geass...
Z-Zero...
Our... Japan's... Savior...
Stop it...
I'm neither a savior nor a messiah...
You're... our hope...
Stop it...
Don't... don't force it on me...
Does this mean I have to bear this sin and try to atone for it?
I...
Zero...
Bastard, what did you do to Princess Euphemia...?
Andreas Darlton...
The most trusted among those trusted by Cornelia...
What? What is going on in the venue?
I'm confirming it right now!
Erm... venue... confirm... well...
Why are we unable to turn it off?
Seems that someone is hacking in from somewhere.
Stop it. This is being broadcasted around the world!
They will terminate the broadcast soon.
Upload the data to the Internet.
Do it.
Okay.
Staff officer, Sir!
Seems that C.C. has met up with the Commander.
Okay. There shouldn't be any problems left.
I don't know how you crafted this situation,
but this battle is proceeding better than what we planned, Zero.
It was shocking. You actually went so far.
It wasn't me.
What? Huh?!
I didn't use my Geass...
No, I didn't intend to use my Geass.
I see. Indeed, what happened earlier was...
I made the contract knowing it. I knew how dangerous this power could be.
Yet!
That fellow finally did it!
What is this...?
Princess Cornelia, please wait!
It's fine if only those who can keep up with me follow me into combat!
Euphie!
Have you found her? Where is she?
I don't know.
I can't contact General Darlton either.
Something is strange.
It's too different from how Princess Euphemia usually acts.
It's all right if they are still open for negotiations, but I'm unable to contact Kirihara.
For now, even if it's just us...
That's right. What about the gift?
How unsightly.
Huh?
In the end, you just value your own lives?
Lady Sumeragi, please mind your words.
We must carry on living for the sake of Japan.
What can we do if we are the only ones left?
Enough already, Kaguya!
You're just a girl that is dependant on the status of her family!
What is Kyoto for if we don't act now?!
There's no way that Euphie would issue a massacre order.
No matter what, I must find her.... Find Euphie!
Hey, the Britannian army has come out of the venue.
Yes... Since things have turned out like this, I have no choice but to make full use of Euphie.
That... is the only thing I can do...
To the terrorist: return that machine to us.
That belongs to our army...
Inform all the members of the Order of the Black Knights!
Euphemia has become our enemy!
The Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon is nothing but a despicable trap used to lure us in!
The various Mobile Humanoid Combat Armored Knight units will break into the ceremonial venue!
We will exterminate the Britannians and rescue the Japanese!
Hurry!
Euphie... she'll... she'll definitely...!
Be found and killed!
Who caused it... this situation...
Whose sin is it... this tragedy...
Who desired it... this battle...
Who does it belong to... this world...
Ah, I understand.
But, even so, at least I'll...!