Wait for me. Today I will...
There you are, filthy demon!
I will...
defeat you!
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Summer! Sea!
Swimsuits!
Yeah!
Girls!
Let's swim, Okumura!
Izumo, get changed, come on! Put on your bikini!
I love the sea!
Why...
Come on, come on, hurry...
Fried Squid
Why do I have to help with this crappy squid fry thing when there's all these hotties out there...?
Come come, have some! This fried squid is so good you'd sell your soul for a single bite!
You seem to be enjoying yourself, Okumura.
Huh? Well... I don't mind doing this.
But...
There's not a single customer!
It's weird. This squid really tastes great.
It smells nyammy too. Just a little... Rin?
You can't, it's for sale.
Ah, is that your new familiar cat sith?
Delicious
Fried Squid
They called this a mission so I brought him along...
But how's this a mission?
Though this is still better than looking for seaweed for anti-demon drugs.
This shop and the inn we're staying at are both run by the family of the whiskers guy's wife.
I'm starting to feel like Bon and Koneko were lucky to get away with looking for ghost stones at the Tama river.
Which way?
How about around there by the rocks?
Yeah, it seems quiet over there.
Guess we'd need a cute sales girl to attract customers?
Maybe if Izumo helped out a bit more...
She really sucks at teamwork.
Sorry about that.
You look cute in your bikini today, too.
What are you saying? I helped with the squid fry already, didn't I?
Or do you think that being a salesgirl suits me better?
That's right...
I swam enough already, so just have your fun!
Of course I will. We decided to take turns, didn't we?
Same as ever... Even this heat doesn't melt her.
Ah, thanks for your hard work!
How's the business? I'm so happy to have kind students like you.
Episode 11
szia Demon of the Depths
Teamwork my ass.
But this feels good...
It's been a while.
Too many things have happened.
Eek, my leg cramped!
Hey, are you all right?
Ow, ow! Don't fight!
I was trying to give you mouth-to-mouth!
You touched my breast and assaulted me, how dare you?!
I helped you! Show some gratitude!
You're mean, you boulderhead.
You're the one to talk! Look at my forehead!
My chin is even...
What?
You're... cute.
What are you saying, kiddo?!
I'm not "kiddo"! I'm Yohei!
Hey, are you okay?
You were really lucky.
But where's your heroic savior?
It's me!
Huh?
Ah, you're so short that I didn't notice you at all.
Shut up! My dad said a guy can be small if he's big down there!
Huh? Cut that out!
What? What's wrong with having a big heart?
What?
What's that ruckus about?
This...
What's going on?
A demon.
When the sea turns black,
a demon the size of a hill will appear
and destroy the village.
What...?
It's been known in these parts for a long time.
Gods help us.
What's that?
The priest of this temple drew this about 400 years ago.
A squid monster?
The black stain in the sea is probably the ink of the squid.
But this is just a legend...
Actually, about six months ago the sea turned black,
and a man went out to the sea to face the demon.
He never returned.
Just our luck to run into demons even here.
Wouldn't it be great if defeating that thing was our first mission?
What?
It hurts!
Pay attention!
Oh, it's just you.
Where'd you go earlier? We were worried about you.
Nowhere...
Nowhere? Anyway, you're really a boulderhead.
For real.
Does it still hurt?
Of course!
Sorry.
You saw us coming, didn't you?
Would it hurt to stand aside?
I didn't want to. My dad said a man should always walk straight.
That's just a figure of speech.
Wouldn't you get lost all the time if you always walked straight?
Nah, you wouldn't.
Do you guys know where the pet shop is?
Huh?
The pet shop! The directions are written down on this...
But I'm lost!
Pet Shop
Why do we have to show the way to a local?
Don't you always shop there?
Yeah, but my dog can't take this heat.
Your dog?
Don't tell me it's usually your dog leading the way.
Got a problem with that?
You really have no sense of direction.
I don't wanna brag, but my dad was even worse!
He totally had no sense of direction at all.
How's that bragging? You're always going on about your dad.
He was a great dad.
Was?
He sailed out about six months ago, and he hasn't come back yet.
He's still chasing it.
It? You mean...
Hey, are you talking about...?
The demon of the sea! It caught my dad.
So I'm gonna defeat it for sure!
Thanks for your hard work today!
Raw squid, squid ramen, squid soup...
Fermented squid and pasta with squid ink? It's all just squid.
Come on, dig in!
Umm, but... it's all squid stuff.
It might sound fishy, but lately the fishers have only caught squid.
So much that we're thinking of invading other markets with it, too.
So that's why the fried squid isn't selling at all...
A kraken?
Well, it's a demon of the sea that spits out ink.
Kraken: A demon of the seas first spotted in the middle ages. It looks cephaloid
like a giant squid or octopus. It destroys or capsizes ships with its powerful arms.
According to historical records from Norway, there have been cases where the whole sea turned black from the kraken's ink.
So there's only squid left in the sea because of this thing?
And if it's a kraken, how can we defeat it?
Usually the fatal verse of the demons of the sea is Ephesians 1:18.
But we have limited resources here,
and it's definitely not something a child could handle alone.
What is it, Honey?
Again? But of course, my little kitty.
Something came up, so I have to leave you for a while.
Tomorrow we'll have real part-timers in the shop, so you can rest then.
Real part-timers? Then were we just fill-ins?
He said that "kitty" thing again, didn't he?
But hey, Okumura!
We can go swimming tomorrow!
Yeah!
That was fast!
I forgot to say that tomorrow you'll have to look after Yohei so that he won't go after the demon.
You're... cute.
Oh, come on.
You?
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
Here.
What's this?
An ointment. My dad always has this with him to the sea.
It works right away, just put it on the bruise.
You came here just for this?
Hey!
Sorry, which way is it to my house?
Wake up! Rin!
It's the sea again!
Huh?
Again... That kid must've seen it, too.
I don't mind as long as he's not doing anything stupid...
I'll go check him out!
Izumo?
What? After all, he saved me once...
Besides, I hate people who don't know their limits.
She says that we don't need to take over for her.
It's unusual for Izumo to care about someone so much.
Are you going to sit there on the lookout all night, too?
I'll wait forever if I have to!
Until it comes.
If it's really a demon, you won't be able do anything against it on your own!
Shut up! It's my dad's enemy!
So I'm gonna defeat it for sure!
You sure are a handful.
You know that there are things that you can't do alone?
Just looking at you makes me feel embarrassed.
You're a fool who doesn't know his place and who'll only get hurt.
So you'd just run away if you were about to get hurt?
My dad told me that if someone's being all negative it's because the person has no self-confidence.
They try to make others lose their way too because they're lost.
What are you saying? You're annoying!
I'm... I'm angry, you know!
Then it's okay.
It doesn't matter if you lose your way, just don't lose sight of what you've decided.
My dad told me that.
I think he decided to meet that demon, and he went through with it.
So I won't hesitate either.
Just like my dad, I will...
It came!
That's...
Yohei!
So that's...
It's the demon! And it's spitting ink!
Whatever, just say your mantra!
It's not a mantra, it's a hymn!
Wait, you want to fight it?
If we let it, it might leave the sea and attack the town.
And we have to do something before that kid does!
That's right...
What the riches of the glory of his inheritance in the saints,
and what is the exceeding greatness of his power to us-ward who believe...
According to the working of his mighty power...
It doesn't work at all! Can a squid hear at all?
It's fine, it has those huge ears!
You're kidding, right?
Every kid knows those are fins.
Fins? Seriously?
Blackie!
Amazing! It's just like a monster movie!
Go, Blackie!
Just like that, Blackie!
Don't!
What's wrong?
Don't you know?
Cats get...
Blackie!
Blackie! What's wrong? Blackie!
I'm dizzy...
Cats get sick if they eat raw squid!
Seriously?
Where is he? Did he come this way?
Nope, he didn't.
Really? Did he get lost again?
I've no choice, I have to...
Hey!
I humbly call upon the Gods of Harvest-
Watch out, Izumo!
I can't summon them!
I'll defeat it!
It's him!
Okumura!
Idiot!
You're crazy! Get out of here!
You!
This isn't something a kid can handle!
Shut up! Don't get in the way!
I'll defeat him and avenge my dad!
Hey!
I did it!
Damn!
The hell, at this rate I'll have to...
Hey! Hey!
Yohei! Yohei!
What the?
This voice...
Yohei!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
You all worked hard.
Whiske- Mr. Tsubaki! Where did you go?
I was looking up stuff because we'd have to take special measures
if it really was a kraken, but I figured we were in no danger.
After that I didn't know the way home,
so for six months I lived on uninhabited islands or drifted on my raft.
I was looking for Japan with him.
His sense of direction is even worse than mine.
Dad, wasn't that the enemy?
Yohei, you have to open your heart!
I understood it when I was fighting him.
His heart is just as soft as his body!
He's changed a lot for the better.
But if a man once decided to defeat...
Enough! Yohei, keep your heart as clear as raw squid!
What the hell?
It takes a man's courage to change your decision.
Men are like that.
Really?
Dad, I think I've learned a lot!
You're kidding...
Come, Yohei!
Dad!
What a great ending.
Oh really?
Demons can have a change of heart.
I wanted to teach you that. It was worth calling you here for.
You just made that up.
This sucks!
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Public Transport
Beach
It's that kid...
You came to see us off?
Yeah.
Your dog got better?
Yeah. His name's Snowy.
He's cute, right? With those eyebrows.
Eyebrows?
Yeah. Eyebrows!
What?
Just you laughed so suddenly...
What else could I have done? This was all so stupid.
You got that right...
So stupid...
but it was fun.
An amusement park?
Next Episode Preview
Are you finally feeling like playing with him?
Nice, nice, you're cute, Moriyama!
Isn't that skirt a bit too short?
A Game of Tag