Yueisha
This is the Shonen Jack editorial department.
Will this be your first time turning in a manuscript?
Huh?
JACK
Okay. Then may I have your name and number?
Mr. Moritaka Mashiro...
Oh, you’re a pair?
...and Mr. Akito Takagi.
Do you have time tomorrow?
You’re in middle school?
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can’t be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Every worry floats up to and fills the spring sky
Shinpaigoto Bakari ga Tsumoru Haru no Sora o
I look up, look down,
Miagete Utsumuite
and find myself looking back up at the sky
Mata Kao o Ageteru
I swore I’d find myself in this town
Kono Machi de Mitsukerutte Kimeta Jibun
I tuck away all my important things into my heart for safekeeping
Nakushichaikenai Mono o Mune ni
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can’t be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Carrot and Stick
Yes, I understand.
Thank you in advance.
We have an appointment tomorrow at 3 o’clock with Mr. Hattori who edits for Shonen Jack.
Super
Hero Legends
Anime
Tomorrow? That’s crazy.
But I guess that’s a publisher for you.
So what do you want to do?
I think we’ll be fine if we meet an hour early...
How about 1 o’clock, North Yakusa station?
Give or take...
Sounds good.
I’m— gonna go over the manuscript again.
Yeah, let me check the dialogue again too.
Where’s Moritaka?
He didn’t come home yet?
He locked himself in his room as soon as he got home.
I sure hope he hasn’t been pushing himself too much.
Thanks for the food.
Being a manga artist must be awesome!
Seeing your own drawings all lined up.
I’m still just a gambler.
Gambler?
Manga artists are the ones who can make a living off of only writing manga.
You either have to hit a jackpot right away
or write several fairly successful manga series.
The rest of the folks are all just gambling.
The drawings are good but I don’t know about my story.
The story’s good but I’m not sure about my drawings.
Our...
first ever manga...
You’re early!
What about you? Why’re you...
Well, despite being sleep deprived, I woke up early.
Same here.
I just couldn’t lay there doing nothing.
My brother said to ask for next week’s Jack.
There’s no way they’d give it to us.
Your brother’s at a good university, isn’t he?
Yeah, but he kind of gave up since he’s not at his first choice school.
Now he just parties and does other extracurricular stuff,
making the most of college life, I guess.
Not much of a future.
So that’s why you wanted to be a manga artist.
No, I guess ‘cause of my parents, I didn’t want a desk job.
My dad used to be a banker.
Dad’s late today too?
Yes.
And Brother?
He’ll be late because of prep school.
You had better study hard so you don’t lose to your brother.
Yes ma’am.
Oh, how did this semester’s exams go?
Math
My mom taught at a high school, so she made us study every day.
Great job, Akito!
I’m sure your father would be proud too.
It seems like something got lost in the process of studying.
Do this well on the next ones, okay?
But that’s only in hindsight.
But then...
Why?! How is that any different from being fired for your boss’s mistakes?
What else could I do?
What else—
Then, what about us?
What will become of us?!
Of course, I didn’t really understand what was going at the time.
I’m back.
Welcome back.
You got the groceries, Dad?
Your mother asked me to.
I wanna come with you next time!
Sure you can, next time.
That’s a promise!
Then in fifth grade...
Avenge...
Huh?
Science
You must...
avenge your father, Akito!
What did she mean by “avenge”?
Did she want me to become the manger of some bank?
Was that why she made me study?
Math
Thinking that, I suddenly couldn’t stand studying anymore.
Akito...?
I’m...
I’m not your tool!
I’ll decide my future myself!
After that she became a better parent. She never says anything about my choices now.
Sorry. That was a pretty depressing story.
Then she knows about us becoming manga artists?
Yeah, she knows, and she’s okay with it.
What?
Nothing, just glad to hear that.
You’re smart, but I thought you just randomly decided to be a manga artist.
Well, that’s kind of true.
Well, we should probably get going now.
Yeah.
Yueisha
Finally...
I can’t believe we’re bringing in a manuscript while we’re still in middle school.
Yueisha
Anyone can bring a manuscript in.
What matters is how much they like it.
Yeah.
And what might be the purpose of your visit today?
Um— We wanted to submit a manuscript—
Then please register at the reception desk over there.
Th-Thank you.
Hi. How may I help you today?
We’re here to submit a manuscript—
Do you have an appointment?
Y-Yes, at 3 o’clock with Mr. Hattori from Shonen Jack.
Then could you please fill out this form for me?
Th-There are two of us, so do we each fill one out?
No, one form is enough for both of you.
U-Um, I’m still a student so for ‘Company Name’...
In that case, just write the name of your school.
I’m really sorry— I made a mistake.
You can just fill out a new form.
I-I’m done.
Thank you...
Wait just a second, please.
Yes! However long it—
She said it’d be ‘just a second’.
This is the reception desk.
Mr. Takagi and Mr. Mashiro are here to see you.
Yes.
Thanks for your patience!
If you don’t mind waiting in the third cubicle, Mr. Hattori will be with you shortly.
Thank you for your trouble.
Thank you.
Meeting Corner Hours
So they don’t just let anyone with a manuscript into the editing department.
Looks like it.
I like your enthusiasm.
But you need to make it clearer to the readers.
Yes sir.
So I’ll pretend that I never saw this manuscript.
Huh?
Put a little more thought into it and try again.
Bring in something interesting next time.
Th-Thank you.
D-Did you hear that just now?
They’re here for the same reason we are, right?
Probably.
I was pretty confident up till now,
but I suddenly think he’ll say it’s terrible.
It’d be scarier if they liked the first manuscript we brought in.
My uncle said it’s a good sign if they at least offer us tea.
Takagi and Mashiro?
Y-Yes.
I’m Hattori, an editor for Shonen Jack.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
Let’s not waste time, so can I see the manuscript?
Y-Yes.
Thank you.
You guys don’t have to be so nervous.
Y-Yes sir.
F-Finally...
He’s such a fast reader!
Let me read it again.
Huh?
“The Two Earths.”
The Earth we live on is not the Real Earth.
All of it is no more than a model for experimentation.
...created by them.
Hayato set foot on his home soil for the first time in a while, after being sent back to recover from a war injury.
But only a cruel reality awaited him: the death of his lover, Amy.
Amy!
Get a grip, Hayato! She’s dead!
I saw her! She was right over there!
Amy!
My eyes!
When the light enveloping his body disappeared, he was in a place he didn’t recognize.
Where am— What hap—
Amy!
Please wait, Amy!
Why are you running away?
Welcome, the Other Hayato.
I’m the other...?
What do you mean? Where am I?
You’re on Earth. Well, the Real Earth...
The Earth where you Clones live is a test model for the Real Earth.
It’s where we, the Real Earthlings, simulate various scenarios.
No...
In getting closer to the truth, Hayato became captive.
A resistance group known as “Missing” saved him.
You too?
Yeah, we’re from the Other Earth.
They capture us Clones when they want to send Investigators in.
Then when the Investigators are done, they wipe our memories and send us back.
But if the Investigators are killed, we have no way back, so we have to live here.
Here in this shitty utopia.
Here’s your way back!
Hayato returned to Earth and told his people the situation.
We have to make them see: we’re not just dolls for them to play with!
Thus, the Other Earth began its counterattack.
Hey now. You really think you can shoot me?
I’m your Original, after all.
We’re not just your guinea pigs!
Die!
You guys really are... just animals.
The Real Earthlings surrendered.
But after years of observation, they had come to a conclusion:
That the Other Earthlings were merely foolish barbarians.
Amy, it’s over...
It’s all over...
But you’re no longer here...
I won’t forgive you!
I’m your Amy!
The dead Amy was an Investigator!
If an Investigator dies, the Clone can’t come back.
But you showed yourself to me.
Your Original let me.
He was a kind man.
But the one I loved was always you!
I’ve missed you so much, Hayato!
As he felt his love close to him, Hayato rethought his hate.
Real and Fake.
Real Earth and the Other Earth.
Which one was the actual reality?
This is very well-done.
I’m gonna have some coffee. Would you two like anything?
W-We’ll have coffee too, please. Right?
Yeah!
Um, did you two come up with the story together?
N-No. I did the story and Mashiro did the illustrations, completely separate.
I see.
Are you two hoping to go pro immediately?
Yes! As quickly as possible.
Just “Yes” would’ve been enough.
Okay then, I’ll start with feedback on the story.
Okay!
In general, you have a pretty good sci-fi story.
I think there are definitely people who’d enjoy it.
Okay.
But I think it’s more suited to be a novel than a manga.
There’s excess narration, and a lot of explanation in the dialogue.
If you don’t use the characters and illustrations to tell the story, making it a manga is pointless.
We agreed that I wouldn’t say a word about the story,
but I kind of thought that as well.
Of course, an editor would say as much though.
The story really is well-done though.
But it really seems more suited to be a light novel.
There are all kinds of editors.
No, I really want to write manga.
Is Mr. Hattori someone we can trust?
Is that so?
And you’re Mashiro, right?
Yes.
I think your art is incredible.
Thank you.
But while they’re incredible works of art, they’re not manga illustrations.
Your lines are too thick.
There’s not enough differentiation between characters and background.
You need to practice more and form your own style.
Huh?
Yes sir.
Mashiro’s only been using the pen two months.
Only two months? Really?
Y-Yes.
If that’s true, I can’t wait to see what he produces in the future.
Do you two like this kind of story?
Jack never has this kind of story.
So I thought it’d stand out.
Takagi, you’re the type who figures out what’s popular and what’ll sell before writing, aren’t you?
This is just the conclusion I’ve come to,
but in general, there’s two main types of successful manga artists.
There are those who just write whatever they want and it becomes a hit.
Some people call them geniuses. Others just call them naïve.
Then there are those like you, who calculate how best to create a hit.
But overwhelmingly, it’s not the calculating ones who make it big.
W-Well, maybe that was a little harsh.
It’s more appropriate to say the calculating ones have more hurdles to overcome.
Conversely, the calculating ones who make it, are tough.
They don’t fizzle after one series, which is great for us editors.
Of course I can’t force you, but I hope you’ll bring your next manuscript to us, not another publisher.
If I could, I’d like to keep seeing your future works.
Tetsu Hattori
Let’s work hard, here at Jack.
If anything comes up, just send me an email at that address.
I don’t have much time, but I’ll get back to you as soon as possible.
You shouldn’t be so thrilled about an email address.
I’d give out my cell phone number when I find a golden egg.
You guys are still just copper.
Not only did he give us his opinion, he’s joking around with us too.
Maybe we can trust him.
I’m gonna submit this for our monthly prize if that’s alright with you.
Huh?
By monthly prize, you mean the prize that’s awarded each month to a chosen submission?
Is this going to win?
It’s not that easy.
But people have different tastes,
so maybe some will still consider this as a finalist.
To be honest, we don’t always know what will or won’t be a hit.
If we did, there wouldn’t be so many new series that end quickly.
Predicting what’ll be a hit is pretty much a gamble.
The rest of the folks are all just gambling.
Please give me a call when your next manuscript’s ready.
Until then...
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
That was a success, right?
Even though it was our first manuscript, we got an email address...
What’d you think, Shujin?
About what?
I think Mr. Hattori’s a good editor.
Yeah, I think so too.
Well, how’d it go?
With that middle school pair...
Not good enough. At least right now.
Everyone can’t be a Eiji Nizuma, huh?
But he’s only been using a pen for two months.
The script’s still not quite palatable, but the idea itself is original...
So they sparked your interest?
Yes! Especially because they’re still just 14.
Not to mention...
Working as a pair isn’t easy.
They’re still kids so they could get in a fight and break up.
But since you like them, make sure to raise them well.
I think they’ll have surpassed Eiji Nizuma in three years.
You better pray you have a hit in three years or you’ll be fired.
Good luck!
Any noise annoys an oyster but a noisy noise annoys an oyster most.
Narration Acting Studio
Prince
Crazy Prince
Prince Enterprise
Prince Eight
Unique New York. You know you need unique New York.
Sally sells sea shells by the sea shore.
Man, summer break ends today.
And Saiko didn’t hang out with us once!
Yeah, and I really wanted to see that x-rated one.
He was hanging out with Takagi the entire break.
Maybe they were going to prep school together.
Maybe...
I wanna finish another story before the end of the year.
And this time he won’t say it should be a light novel.
Yeah, I’m gonna work on the things he mentioned and make some amazing illustrations.
Now that I think about it, the theme of “The Two Earths” was too deep.
A question like ‘What is truth?’ really suits a novel better.
Maybe I should’ve kept it something more straightforward.
So you do get it.
I thought so too.
You did? Then you should’ve told me sooner!
We agreed I wouldn’t say a word about the names.
Then next time, say whatever you’re thinking.
So let’s put in a lot of time on it and produce something we can both be proud of.
If you’re okay with it, then I am.
What?!
Silence.
This is how it was when I was in middle school.
These are your seats for this trimester.
What happens if my stomach growls in the middle of class?
The boring everyday gets to me sometimes,
Betaa na Genjitsu ni Tsubusaretemo
but I always get back on my feet, standing strong
Uchinomesareta Jibun Hiroiatsumete
No matter how many times the end approaches me,
Nando Owari ga Otozuretemo
I'll push my own back forward, keeping me on my feet
Sonotabi ni Jibun de Jibun no Senaka Oshita
If I get lost in the meaning of continuing what I do,
Tsuzuiteku Imi ni Nayami
I'll rid myself of those worries and keep myself going forward
Sono Mayoi Sae Tachikitte Yuku
Always
Itsumo
The straight edge that draws the outline of my future
Mirai no Rinkakusen Kaku Massugu na Jougi wa
is made of all the courage I've mustered up until today
Ikutsumo no Kinou no Yuuki de Dekiteru
I'll climb over the tall wall that I never thought I'd face,
Omoiegaita no to Chigau Takai Kabe Koe
and continue my journey, going past the vanishing point
Shoushisuten no Mukou e Susunde
This winding road seems to never end,
Harukanaru Winding Road
but it is the road I personally chose
Hoka no Dare Demo Nai Watashi ga Jibun de Eranda
I set my tiny dreams on fire,
Kasuka na Yume o Zenbu Moyashita
and broke through the dark with its light
Sono Hikari de Yami o Saite
Now that I've broken down the wall,
Kudaita Kabe no Mukou ni
I can see my sky once more
Jibun no Sora ga Mieru
An editor gave us his contact information, and now I sit next to Azuki.
Next
Episode
Everything’s going smoothly.
And our rival’s made his move.
What?!
Next time, Tears and More Tears.
Tears
and More Tears
Tears are the droplets of dreams.