It's delicious! As expected from Brother.
It's filet mignon de porc à l’Avesnoise, because there was pork left in the fridge.
The sauce is surprisingly appetizing. What did you use to make it?
It's made of Madeira wine. The meat was marinated in wine vinegar and beer.
Unfortunately, I'll get drunk.
It's fine, Nunnally.
This is our home after all.
Take your time to eat it, and then have a good sleep.
Okay, Brother.
Does it remind you... of the past?
No way. It doesn't remind me at all.
But good things happened as well. For example, Suzaku-san.
Ah, that was the only time that was fun.
The rest was just full of sorrow, and horrible things but.
Only that time...
Come to think of it, that person hasn't come here lately.
Seems that he's busy with work at the army. Eventually, Suzaku will...
No. I'm referring to C.C..
W-Why?
I guess it's true that you can't date with me around... That's why outside...
Nunnally, you're mistaken. That person isn't anything like a girlfriend... That...
That?
That... erm...
Lelouch, think! I can't say that she's my accomplice... Friend?
Just plain friends with a woman who comes visiting in the dead of night?
That's not persuasive enough!
A teacher from school?
Promising to share my future with a teacher is... Impossible!
That's right! Nunnally doesn't know what C.C. looks like.
Can I just say that she's a boy whose voice hasn't broken yet?
Even so... Even so... Even so... Even so... Even so... Even so... Even so... Even so...
I've returned.
Welcome back, Sayoko-san!
That was quick, wasn't it?
I'm sorry. I had to take leave for my own reasons.
Sayoko-san, you were hired by the Ashford family.
It can't be helped that you have to attend to the tasks of the Ashford family.
How was Milly-san's matchmaking session?
If I remember correctly, this is the thirty-first time...
It's as usual. Milly-sama wrecked it herself...
So, that's why it ended early?
The president is the same as ever.
Maybe it's because she already has someone in mind?
How can that be?
She just wants to enjoy freedom a bit more, right?
I wonder... I'm not sure about that.
Despite how she looks, Milly-sama is surprisingly shy.
That's very persuasive since Sayoko-san, the housekeeper, is the one saying it.
Ah, Nunnally-sama. This is for you.
Hmm? What's that?
It's the second issue of the thousand cranes series.
I heard that there are other good luck charms in Japan that help to grant one's wishes, is that true?
Yes, Nunnally-sama.
Th-That is...!
Since you wanted something powerful.
It feels unusual for a doll... Is it made of a plant...?
Yes. It's a doll made of straw. It comes as a set with these five-inch nails. Please use them together.