He moved!
Is he waking up?
Impossible! Sir Pheles, do something!
Right now I am but a worthless defendant.
How could I possibly engage in this matter while the investigation is still ongoing?
It isn't that complicated!
Just order me to release Satan's son and turn him into a weapon for the Vatican!
I can feel...
The smell of Rin Okumura.
That way, huh?
Ladies should stay back.
Shut up, you idiot! Baldy!
Caliburn, give me strength.
~
Ooh Mister Arthur, you're so violent~
Kirigakure Demon Sword Technique: Slither!
Snakefang!
My... My Behemoth!
There you are!
The time for voting is almost over!
Please decide whether you're for or against!
You... heeded the summons because you knew this would happen?
You knew that the son of Satan would lure an army of demons here!
Oh? What are you talking about?
By the way, instead of thinking up schemes shouldn't you be ensuring the Grigori's safety?
I'm here to settle things with you, Rin Okumura!
You're pissing me off!
Could you all just shut the hell up?
Don't worry, you'll get your turn when I start killing you one by one!
Sir Pheles, I don't care how, just get rid of that demon!
As you command!
Okumura!
How long are you going to sleep there?
Wake up already!
That's...
The Kurikara?
They managed to fix it?
I can hear it...
I can hear Rin Okumura's heartbeat.
Give that to me!
Shima!
No way!
Pass!
Huh? Why me?
Kamiki, over here!
Yessir!
Yukio!
Professor!
Wake up...
Rin, wake up!
Blue flames...
The same glow as that night.
Where am I?
I can't see a thing. I can't feel a thing.
Am I dead?
No, I can hear it...
My...
I'll crush you!
I ain't dead yet!
No way...
I'm... the Earth King...
I can't lose!
Brother!
Rin!
What are you doing?
I am slaying the spawn of Satan.
Stop, Angel.
We will take Sir Pheles' gamble.
Will he become the savior of Assiah,
or a demon king that will bring upon the destruction of everything,
we have no choice but to see for ourselves.
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Episode 17
Temptation
I summoned you all here for a reason.
Emergency Staff Meeting
We have received a notice from the Vatican Headquarters.
So from today on we are officially raising Rin Okumura,
Emergency Staff Meeting
the son of Satan here in the True Cross Academy.
Question!
Yes, Inokawa?
I heard that the fire in the forest the other day
was the result of Okumura going berserk.
Is there really no danger?
I cannot say there is no danger.
However, if he was ever to run berserk again,
we have been ordered to kill him.
The risk is too great!
Is there a reason why we are in charge of him?
Not the tiniest!
However, I would like to gamble...
On the potential of Rin Okumura.
Sir Pheles!
Yes?
Do you really believe that my brother can become the savior of Assiah?
I must believe so...
To make the Vatican approve of his existence.
Your gamble is too reckless.
We must abide by the two conditions the Grigori has set.
First, make him pass the Exorcist authorization exam.
Impossible!
Second, just to be cautious, someone must keep an eye on him around the clock.
I entrust the latter to you, his little brother, and to Miss Kirigakure.
That's impossible as well!
Yet, you must do it.
The game has already started.
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Shura Kirigakure
To Scaredy Four-Eyes
I'll be a bit late. Let's do this!
Every single one of them...
I fix'd it fer now, but I ain't promisin' nuthin' 'bout the next time.
's reckless to store a demon's heart in the Kurikara.
Whate'r happens, 's outta my terms o' guarantee!
's the Demon-Slaying Blade, that was forged to slay the apparitions hauntin' ye olde capital.
Handle it wit' care.
Rin, shouldn't you be going?
Darn... Blackie, watch the house while I'm gone!
Take care!
Why do we have to do this crap on the last day of the summer break?
Stop whining, and get to work.
Konekomaru, we'll manage here, so go and help Moriyama.
Sure.
We're fine.
I bet it still hurts. Why don't you just rest?
Ah well...
Me too!
You get back to work!
I broke my ribs too, you know.
Sup!
Morning, Rin.
Morning...
I almost panicked when there was no one in our usual classroom.
We have to clean up the coal tar?
Why do they make students to do the most tedious jobs?
I don't get a mop?
Dunno, look if there's any left over there.
I'll go throw out the trash.
I'll help.
I can manage this.
Huh? Hey, wait!
He's scared of you, because you're the child of a demon.
You're the son of Satan who butchered many Exorcists all around the world in just one night.
Who knows when your true nature will make you lose control again?
Moriyama!
Shiemi!
They were piling up in the ceiling!
Hold your breath!
If you breathe them in your lungs will rot!
Get away from her!
Moriyama!
Huh? It's not hot...?
Stop! What are you doing?
Do you want to burn her to death?
Huh?
Those blue flames can kill!
My dad, Shima's oldest brother, and Konekomaru's parents were all killed by Satan...
Your old man!
...16 years ago, when Satan simultaneously slaughtered many of the world's prominent clergymen...
So their families were slaughtered too?
I don't give a damn about what the Vatican thinks of you,
but there's no way in hell we'd ever get along with you!
If you hurt anyone close to me, I'm gonna kill you without hesitation!
I'm not Satan! Trust me!
That's enough.
Yukio!
Okumura will be having special training from today, so he's coming with me.
The rest of you continue your work.
We're not done talking yet!
Rin...
Let go of me, you moley four-eyes!
Damn...
Why do I have to take separate classes?
You don't have any time to spare.
Get ready, because your training will start right away
and I expect you to put all your energy into it until the exams.
The hell is this? A batting center?
Set to beginner mode.
Are you listening at all?
Your authorization exam is six months away and if you don't pass it...
I know, they'll kill me.
Begin training.
Don't worry. I could do it without special training too.
And I've gotten rid of plenty of demons so far!
That was all thanks to your good luck.
What?
You told Suguro to trust you.
So what?
You can earn his trust only by showing what you can do.
You have nothing to show, have you?
What?
It's just as the Scaredy Four-Eyes said!
Shura?
The hell are you wearing?
I feel closer to nature like this!
She just didn't change from her pajamas... Yeah, that's definitely it.
You've got the blood of Satan in your veins, and I gotta say it's damn hot blood.
You managed so far because you've got a lot of potential in you,
but if you can't freely use the power you were born with,
you ain't gonna become Exorcist, not to mention Paladin.
What do you want me to do?
Special training. Here.
Huh? A candle?
Let's see... first line up three of those and light the ones to the sides at the same time.
Okay.
I told you to light them, not to torch them.
Once more!
Are you even trying?
Nope, don't light the middle one.
I said, at the same time.
Don't you think you should start training seriously?
It's difficult!
Anyway, do this three times every day, for one hour at a time.
Continue until you can do it while picking your nose.
Huh? Is this the special training? I'm not gonna use the sword?
Do you know why you lost yourself in the fight against Amaimon?
Nope.
Because you're afraid.
That's why the flames take over.
Get used to the flames and build your confidence.
You'll train with the Demon-Slaying Blade after that.
It pisses me off, but she's right...
Okay, I get it!
Do you really?
You look so constipated again.
You'll get an ulcer if you're always so stressed.
And whose fault do you think that is?
Now, come along with me, Yukio of the Scaredy Four-Eyes.
Don't wanna.
That was too quick!
You're such a bore!
Long ago we bet our lunches here.
Nyahoo~ 16 wins in a row! Nyahaha~
Shura, you shouldn't go all out on a grade schooler!
I'm teaching him that fights are never easy!
Hey Scaredy-Eddy, tomorrow's lunch is your treat!
Don't give me foreign-sounding names like that!
You're too easy prey for her, Yukio.
Dammit.
Did you just say "dammit"? That's unusual.
I hate her.
She's so strong and yet she's always fooling around.
I look stupid for taking it seriously!
Don't be so strict...
She could be thinking about a lot of things, even if it doesn't look like it.
All right.
But if I win, you have to stop calling me Scaredy Four-Eyes.
The rules are the same. The one who loses focus first on Infinity Mode loses.
Are you cool with that?
Perfect.
Special Infinity Mode selected.
Begin training.
Amazing! They can take down all the balls at that speed?
Just what are they made of?
You just concentrate on showing us what you can do!
You'd better concentrate too, Shura.
Don't get cocky, Scaredy-Eddy! Just listen!
In the shadow of the pillar in the south end of the room.
He's hiding himself, but you can see him, right?
A spy from the Vatican?
Yeah.
But he's not watching just Rin, but also you.
That can't be.
The Grigori directly ordered me to watch over Rin-
You have the blood of Satan just like Rin.
From the Vatican's point of view you're just as dangerous.
Rin and I are different. First,
I don't have the power.
If you really think so, then why the daily check-ups?
Aren't you just scared that one day Satan's power will appear in you just like in Rin?
What are you talking about?
Or the opposite, you want to have the power?
You're wasting your time trying to upset me like this.
Fine, then...
But be careful, guys like you are the first to fall to demons.
Huh?
Is that what pros are like?
It took me all I had to hit just once or twice on beginner mode.
Dammit!
This!
Blue flames?
What are you doing, Rin?
Ah... sorry.
But wait, only your clothes burnt, not your underwear and body!
Doesn't this mean I have some control?
Not at all!
Right...
I'll bring some holy water.
Thanks.
For the sake of the teachings of the Buddha
and for the sake of all creation...
Memorizing?
Sorry, did I wake you up?
I just had to take a leak.
Try not to wear yourself out...
I want to win.
You mean over Kamiki?
Don't be stupid. Over Okumura.
You're winning already, aren't you?
When it comes to pharmacology or chanting the sutras, you're the best in class.
What's the point in having knowledge if I can't use it in action?
I realized that last time.
Bon...
I have to become an Exorcist before him.
Otherwise it'd be an offense to your parents.
Yeah...
He's so strong... He saw all that and he still wants to compete with Rin...
I can't do that...
Are you scared?
You'll lose someone again... Someone important... Someone you love.
Accept it...
Who's that?
That fear...
Dammit... Why can't I do it?
Do I really have no talent?
Who's there?
Why are you talking to yourself?
No reason... But what are you doing here so early?
I just forgot my pen case here earlier so I came to get it.
I see...
What kind of training is that?
I have to light two out of the three candles.
But I totally can't do it.
Do you remember when the ghoul attacked Paku?
Yeah. During our training in the dorm?
Back then my familiars turned on me because my heart faltered.
Aren't your flames like that too?
If you're not afraid of them, they'll obey you.
I see.
But why are you telling me this? Aren't you scared of me?
Not really. I guess you don't know about it, but demon-human half-breeds aren't that unusual.
Especially among Exorcists.
Really?
Everyone knows that. So you really shouldn't worry about your ancestry.
Just let them talk if they want... to talk...
Eyebrows! You really are a nice person!
Huh? Eyebrows? Don't give me weird nicknames!
My name is Izumo Kamiki!
Thanks, Izumo. You've given me motivation!
I-It's not like I was encouraging you or anything!
What?
Be careful! Something is out there.
Who's that?
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
I don't get it, Okumura suddenly...
Next Episode Preview
I told you I would kill you without hesitation if you hurt anyone close to me!
Have you forgotten? If you lose control...
Konekomaru!
Gale