Stop!
Burn to hell!
Thank you so much for saving me!
I just did what was natural in the situation.
You're amazing, Okumura!
You're a real Exorcist!
I'm not that good.
As a sign of our gratitude...
Please, have some!
Congratulations!
Okumura!
Sukiyaki!
You can just leave if you don't want to listen.
I'm sorry.
Among the Hebrew scriptures, the oldest are the Book of Genesis, the Book of Exodus and Leviticus...
History
What the hell is that guy doing here?
Get lost!
He looks like he was crazy from the day he was born...
Streaked hair...
Piercings...
So rebellious...
He's so cool!
Before this I would've stared back and started a fight after class...
But I'm not going to cause that kind of trouble anymore.
I decided that I'll become an Exorcist.
Okumura!
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Demonology
Episode 5
sziaChild of the Cursed Temple
The lowest of the minions of the Rotten King, Astaroth...
Okumura!
I've never seen any...
It's the Coal Tar!
One's floating right there!
Grimoire Studies
Magic is usually performed by contracting demons.
The Grimoire is the collection of knowledge on the methods and laws governing those contracts.
It has an ancient history.
In the thirteenth century, Reverend William of Auvergne studied demons...
The Key of Solomon you all have is also...
I will now give you the results from the test earlier.
Shima!
Yes!
Anti-Demon
Pharmacology
Review the parts you made mistakes at.
Yes...
Kamiki!
Yes.
Why are you beaming like that?
I have confidence!
Ah, your shop is a pharmacy...
Yeah, for Exorcists only!
So this is kind of my specialty.
Moriyama!
Yes!
What is "sancho"?
Umm, you peel it and put it on burn wounds...
Aloe, then. And "homairi"?
It's a yellow medicine against suppuration.
Ah, turmeric.
I don't mind if you give the plants new names,
but please use the official nomenclature for tests.
Yes...
And this is your specialty?
Okumura!
This was gut-wrenching.
I'm sorry.
Suguro!
Yes.
Two points?
I couldn't do that badly even if I wanted to.
It's because you're always showing off to that chick.
Makes me sick.
What's with this punk?
He's the one showing off!
You did well, Suguro.
What?!
That's impossible!
How could a guy like you get 98 points?!
What?!
I go to school to do my best and to take the Exorcist exam!
Everyone here is serious about becoming an Exorcist!
An eyesore who comes here only to slack off should just get lost already!
Who put you on that high horse so you could tell me off like that, punk?!
I want to become an Exorcist, too!
What?! All you ever do is sleep in class!
Bon, calm down!
We're in class, Bon!
I haven't seen you pay attention even once!
I'm more the practical type!
I'm not good at sitting at a desk and cramming!
It's just as Suguro says. You should listen.
Yukio, just whose side are you on?
I wonder...
Ah, class is over. This is it for today!
What's with that guy? Is he smart?
Ryuji Suguro? He's a genius.
He's here on the same scholarship as I was.
He's the heir of a famous temple in Kyoto.
So a spoiled kid with a good background?
He has great grades, he's athletic
and he's always serious about his classes.
To say the least, he's working harder than you.
You could take lessons from him.
Lessons? Is he that good?
By the way, Shiemi, are you used to cram school yet?
Well... not yet.
You seem so active now that you're like a different person.
Don't worry, just do your best!
Thanks, Yuki.
I have to go to my next class, so...
Be careful not to be late for your P.E. class.
See you later!
Damn, it's just the two of us! What should I say?
Umm... Which class were you in?
I don't mean in the cram school, but in high school.
I only entered the cram school.
Then what about high school?
I'm very shy in front of strangers, so I haven't really gone to middle school either.
Well, me neither.
I couldn't get used to it somehow...
Rin?
Is it strange that I'm in the cram school?
What do you mean?
I'm not that determined to become an Exorcist...
Nor am I smart like Suguro...
It's certainly good to be smart,
but I think it's better that there are all kinds of people in the world.
Rin! Do you have friends?
Huh?
Umm... Rin... will you...
Ah, flirting in broad daylight...
Who're you talking about?!
Is that your chick?
You're taking it easy, bringing your woman to the leading school of Exorcists.
I told you it's not like that!
Then what? Is she your friend?
She's... not... my friend.
Oh I see...
What about you?! You have your followers with you all the time!
Your little circlejerk is disgusting!
Why are you laughing, Shima?!
He does have a point.
What, are you agreeing with him?!
I can't stand this guy!
Aren't they similar in a way?
So similar they can't take it...
Physical training
This isn't just a foot race!
The point is to adjust your body to the movements of the demon!
Watch the movements of the Leaper!
I can't lose him.
He's really fast!
Bon's not slow either... That guy's good.
You're slow, punk! Even if you're Mr. Smart in class,
you're no good at the real thing!
What?!
In real combat the last one standing wins!
Now you're not that-
Oi!
What are you two doing? Do you want to die?
I won't lose to you even if it costs me my life.
Then would you like to die now?
Give it a try, you moron!
Hey, hey! You are in class!
What do you think you're doing?!
Sorry...
Idiots...
Suguro, come here for a little talk.
What's wrong with him?!
Forgive him...
You know, he's always too serious, he's not flexible at all.
He has his goal, that's why he's here.
Goal?
Get it?
Suguro, you're smart and the teachers all have great expectations for you.
It would be wiser for you to stay out of trouble.
May I ask why you're only lecturing me?
Huh?
In a quarrel both sides are to blame, so why isn't Rin Okumura here?
He got in the Academy with special permission from the Principal.
He's got circumstances.
It'd be better if you didn't get involved with him.
Special?
He wants to become an Exorcist to defeat Satan.
I'll kick Satan's ass!
He's the same as me!
It's silly, isn't it?
Is it?
Yeah, he's working hard to rebuild our temple
that was destroyed in the Blue Night.
The Blue Night? What's that?
You don't know?
That's rare.
The Blue Night took place 16 years ago,
when Satan simultaneously slaughtered many of the world's prominent clergymen.
Slaughtered them?
Our high priest told us
that 16 years ago, that night...
Every stronger Exorcist suddenly started bleeding all over their body,
and died in blue flames.
Those blue flames are the sign of Satan.
Our high priest was still just an apprentice back then,
and he prayed all night, quivering in a corner.
After that he became the high priest,
but because so many priests suddenly died mysteriously
the number of both our supporters and visitors to the temple declined
and people started calling it the Cursed Temple.
Shima and I are also apprentices at Bon's temple.
We decided to help rebuild it by becoming Exorcists...
Bon just can't slack off, he's so serious.
So just let this pass...
The child of the Cursed Temple?
Mameshiba
Babyshiba tuwned into fwuits.
oppai ni
mero mero
meronshiba
oppai ni
sui sui
suikashiba
oppai ni
yada mon
remonshiba
oppai ni
rin rin
ringoshiba
oppai ni
sukedachi
sudachishiba
oppai ni
ran ran
ranbuutan
yumistinx.bmp
Just how many times do you plan to fall?
I'm sorry...
And why aren't you wearing jersey like everyone else?
These are the only clothes fit for sports that I have.
Which age do you think you live in?
Next, Shima and Yamada!
Will you let me climb first?
Sure...
Nice job.
It wasn't that hard.
You're good, Izumo.
Who's that? We're in the middle of class!
Yes, it's me.
What is it, honey? What?!
Right now? You're such a reckless kitty.
Listen! Practice by yourselves for now!
The Leapers are generally docile demons,
but they have the ability to attack you by reading your minds!
You will not go down to the race court until I get back,
and under no circumstances should you go within their reach!
Get it? Understood?
I'm coming, my kitty!
He was saying "my kitty", right?
Practice by ourselves in P.E.? Seriously?
Can he do this?
Come on, and they call that a teacher?
I thought the True Cross Academy would be a
sacred place of studying for determined people!
The students are no better either!
What? You're starting to get on my nerves!
What do you know about my determination?
It's clear from how you act in class!
Here we go again...
He got in the Academy with special permission from the Principal.
He's got circumstances.
I bet he's just some spoiled brat who paid his way in...
Bon, be more mature!
Stop, please!
Stop your nagging! Shut up!
Since you claim to have the determination, prove it!
Prove it? How?
That.
If you can go down there and touch the demon without it attacking you, you win.
Huh?
The Leapers look their opponents in the eye and read their minds.
Fear, anger, grief, suspicion...
Point is, if you waver while you look it in the eye,
it'll be your last mistake.
If you aim to become a real Exorcist,
dealing with such a small fry should be no trouble.
If you can get back without getting hurt, I'll acknowledge your determination.
Hey, Bon...
Of course I'll do it, too. And win!
So? Are you in?
Interesting! Okay, I'm in!
Is what you thought I'd say, you blockhead?
I'm not doing it.
What if you make a mistake and die?
Even if something happens, I can't draw my sword in front of people...
And I have my goal just like you.
I can't risk my life with something stupid like this.
Did you tell him?
No...
A goal my ass! You're just scared!
Say whatever you want.
Damn, they're all looking down on me!
All of them!
It's the kid from the Cursed Temple!
You'll get cursed if you go close to him...
Sorry, but would you be so kind as to leave?
I see. Of course. Excuse me.
Dad!
Who was it?
The priest from the Cursed Temple.
He came for donations.
Damn, scary...
That temple should just collapse.
They say mean things, don't they.
Why? Why is he smiling?
Ryuji, you don't have to worry about the temple. Just live the way you want to.
Why have they all turned their backs on us?
It's Satan's fault that our temple is ruined!
I hate it!
Ryuji?
I'll study hard to become an Exorcist and defeat Satan!
Then I'll rebuild the temple!
Defeat Satan? That was funny.
I'm serious! I really am!
Every single one of them...
Why don't you fight?
Doesn't it bother you?
I'll do it! You just stand there and watch!
Stop!
Bon!
Wha- Is he serious?
He'll turn back anyway.
So stupid.
I...
I'm not spineless like you!
I'll become a real Exorcist
and defeat Satan!
Defeat Satan? What are you saying? You're not a kid anymore.
Don't laugh at my goal!
Damn!
Bon!
Hey!
Let go!
I said, let go!
What are you doing? Are you that stupid?
Are you listening? The one who'll defeat Satan is me!
You get lost!
Huh? What's with him?
You're the stupid here!
Who cares about dying?!
And how dare you steal my goal like that?
I didn't steal it! It's original!
Original my ass! I decided to do it first! Get lost!
When did you decide?
What year, what month, what day, what hour, what minute, what second? How many times did the Earth turn then?
Are you a kid?!
Look who's talking!
Yes, it settled down. All students are safe.
He didn't draw the Kurikara.
Well then.
Satan's power might be much less in your control than you think, Sir Mephisto Pheles.
Sorry I'm late.
Long time no see, Earth King Amaimon.
It's been a while, Brother.
How is Gehenna?
Everyone's absolutely livid.
If we didn't get the news of Satan's offspring being in Assiah...
I see...
Then tell our siblings who are going mad with envy
that our youngest brother is being raised under my wing.
Everything's going well.
Understood.
What is it? Do you have something else to say?
No, I was just wondering when you'll return to Gehenna.
Go, don't make our impatient siblings wait.
Yes.
I don't plan to return...
For a hell-raiser like me
there's no better playground than this.
The fun and games start here.
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Breaktime
What's wrong, Rin?
I'm studying.
Is this a sign?
Is it a problem, four-eyes?
My hair's in the way...
What? Did you come to make fun of me, too?
I forgot to say yesterday...
Thanks.
Huh?
I use this to hold up my hair when I'm studying late.
I'll lend it to you.
This is creepy! Is this a sign?
Huh?! You stupid monkey! I'm being sincere here!
Ukobach? I've heard of it before.
Next Episode Preview
It's a spirit of the fireplace...
I'll make the perfect lunch!
What the hell?!
The Phantom Cook