It was not by chance that I met you.
This is called fate.
Please watch over me
so that those eyes could keep on shining.
(Please be) So if this heart
(With me) one day loses its way,
please open the door to the future.
Towards an unknown world.
Dance!
So don't let go of that hand. (Buddy)
Towards a place of dreams.
Hold on to these bonds we have.
Don't panic!
The hymn!
Don't stop singing!
Withdraw!
Don't be foolish! If we fall, who will protect Assiah?!
Demons!
Is he a demon or what?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Let's go!
Demon? Who are you talking about? You're more demonic than I am.
Ah, I did it again.
What am I doing...?
The Blue Exorcist
Episode one
sziaDemons Live In The Human Heart
You lost little lamb, confess your sins and say your prayers.
I didn't do anything bad!
Then what's with those wounds?
I fell on the stairs.
Your back is dirty too.
It was quite a fall.
What about that nosebleed?
I fell onto an insanely hot babe-
What?! After her, Rin! Lead the way!
Liar!
You had a fight again, right?! Why do you always do that?!
Let go, stupid old fart!
They called from your part-time job earlier.
They said that they don't need someone who doesn't come back after completing a delivery.
You're saying that as if someone like me could do a decent job to begin with.
Don't act like a spoiled brat!
One day you'll have to leave this abbey and make your own living!
It's my duty as your guardian to make you ready for that!
Or will you become a priest and lead the abbey?
Who'd want this rotting old church?
Father!
I'm finished with the preparations for moving.
Now I only have to actually move the stuff.
Good job.
Welcome back, brother.
Did you have a fight again?
Shut up!
Even though they're twins, they're totally different!
The younger one, Yukio, is an athletic genius with amazing grades.
Also, this Spring he easily got into the True Cross Academy High School division.
While the older one only causes troubles.
Hey, Rin, if only you had just a fraction of your little brother's virtues.
Shut the fuck up!
I really need to buy a new heater...
Reverend Fujimoto,
you have a guest.
Clean this up before the service!
Yukio, treat your brother's wounds.
Sure. Come, brother.
It smarts!
Try to bear with it just a little longer.
Yukio Okumura, clothes (1)
Yukio Okumura, books (1)
Yukio Okumura, books (2)
Ah, so you're moving to a dorm?
Yeah, school starts next week.
After fifteen years, it's time to leave this abbey.
So is this the last time you'll treat my wounds?
If I become a doctor, I'll help you anytime.
If you pay the fees, that is.
Your dream is to become a doc, right?
Keep up the good work! I'm sure you can do it!
Don't forget about the fees, brother.
But will you be all right without me around?
What? Are you going to scold me, too?
I'm just worried. And not just me.
Father and the others from the abbey, too.
You have fights every day and you drop out from your jobs after a short while.
I'm worried about it, too.
I know I should be growing up already.
But...
Hit!
You're great, Shiratori!
There are too many of them.
They get in the way all the time.
Oi! What the hell are you doing?!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm just shooting down these shitty birds! Shut up and watch!
It might be a test for you.
From who?
God.
You're more and more like the old man.
Ah, here he is!
They're looking for part-timers in the Southern Cross Mall.
A part-time job?
We called them, and they were like "come right away for the interview".
Why did you call them without asking me?!
Go on, I'll lend you my suit.
Why should I wear a suit for a part-time job interview?
Here, my shoes. Don't dirty them!
And here's a map and your CV. Just add your photo there.
Brother...
I've no choice...
What's with this?! How are you supposed to tie this thing?!
Enough. It's easier this way.
Thank you for your help.
Never you mind. Really don't worry about it.
You should be happy. You have your parents watching over you.
If you have problems, ask your mommy and daddy first.
If they can't help, then come asking us, the Exorcists.
It must be hard, to be an Exorcist.
You have to get rid of things that don't even exist.
Demons do exist, in our hearts.
Lie.
They just asked to consult you.
By the way, what's with that get-up?
Everyone insisted on me going to the interview, so I borrowed it.
And the necktie?
It's faster without it!
Heh, you just don't know how to tie it, do you?
Give it to me. I'll teach you.
Raise your collar and close the button.
Man, you're only growing up physically...
You were so cute when you were little, going "daddy, daddy" all the time.
That was like ages ago!
I'm grown-up now, you're embarrassing me!
Grown-up? I can't see any grown-ups around!
Hey!
If it's that embarrassing, show me how much you've grown!
Don't look down on me!
I'll prove it to you that I can do it by myself!
Open your eyes wide and look!
That's not how the saying goes.
Shut up, shitty old man!
Rin Okumura, 15 years old.
You want to start working right after finishing middle school?
I don't exactly like school...
You're very wrong if you think you can keep doing as you please in this world!
That's true.
Line these up at the front of the store.
All of it?
Can't you do it?
I can.
The boss is picking on the new guy again.
No way he could finish that in a day.
Boss, this is the last one!
What are you doing?! Can't you do anything decently?! Get a hold of yourself! Got it?!
I'm not fit for work after all...
What's wrong, new boy?
Cheer up!
Here, have some.
What's this?! It's horrible!
I guessed... The boss bought a lot of it because it's cheap,
but it's not selling at all.
Could I try cooking it?
It's our new product, fried soba!
Would you like some?
It's delicious!
It also smells great!
The secret of the flavor is this sauce!
And as a final touch, some dried fish for topping!
This way the taste will be as if done by a pro chef!
I want some!
Me too! Me too!
Boss?
The staff meeting is at 8 every morning.
Don't be late.
Do your best from tomorrow too!
You got the job! That's great, new boy!
You got the job?!
Yeah, she was like "do your best from tomorrow"!
That's great, brother!
Thanks!
I'm so happy I got some good news before leaving!
What are you all in tears about?
No tears around!
Come home already! Today we're having Yukio's farewell party so we're making sukiyaki!
Gotcha!
Stop! Give it back, please!
This is yours, right?
Huh?
She was at our place earlier...
Hey, wait!
Excuse me!
What's that?!
A monkey?
Damn!
Watch out!
Yui!
Are you okay, Yui?! Yui?!
Rin is late.
I'll go take a look.
Yeah, me too.
You were here after all.
All the sukiyaki will be gone.
Come on, let's go home.
Even if I went home, how could I look everyone in the eye?
What's wrong?
I got fired.
"We don't need a berserk like that in the store."
What happened?
I don't know either!
Don't say stuff like that!
Everyone was happy that you finally got a job!
Why are you so careless?!
Explain it so that we'll understand!
How could I explain something that I don't get myself?!
Brother?
Sorry...
Anyway, let's go home!
Father's waiting too.
Ah, you're back?
Rin Okumura?
Who are you?
I'm Yui's father.
Thank you for saving her.
Her wounds?
Thanks to you, just a few scratches.
That's good.
She was always a careless child,
so she had lots of accidents, falling from stairs and stuff.
That's not it!
She's not careless!
She's being bullied!
Gets her hair pulled and her stuff taken...
Did you see it?
What was he like?
I've never seen anything like that before...
Small, with a face like a monkey...
What?!
Where are you going?
I'm going to call the school and get them punish the ones who bully Yui!
Or else...
That's not it!
It's not humans who bully me!
It's evil ghosts!
Ghosts?
In the night they come to my room and torture me!
Lately even outside of my room...
Yui's always had a lively imagination.
I've heard these tales many times,
but recently her imagination and reality gets mixed up too often...
It's not imagination!
Rin!
Why can't you believe her?
If not even her parents believe her, who could she depend on?
Do it better-
What are you doing?!
It's a four-leaf clover charm. It should protect you.
Thank you!
Don't blame her, please.
She depends on you, her parents, the most.
Let's go home, Yui.
What's with that? Did he actually accept that?
You're a thousand years too early to scold others!
Also, Rin, you're forbidden to go out for a while!
Huh? Why?
The boss from that shop came by earlier with this.
It's a demand for the shop equipment and goods you destroyed!
What's with this?!
Rin! You won't get any sukiyaki!
Why that?!
I thought so...
My stuff I sent yesterday will be arriving in the morning, so I have to leave early.
Take care.
PS: Don't make Father worry any more.
Yukio.
Heartless.
At least say goodbye.
What the-?!
What are these? Bugs?
Why doesn't anyone care about them?
Hey Okumura!
Are you free for now?
You're forbidden to go out for a while!
Are you scared, Okumura?
Do you want to hide under your mommy's skirt?
Sorry about yesterday.
We were just playing with the pigeons, but my hand acted on its own...
What's wrong with him?
How much should we pay?
You know, my parents are kinda famous
and I'll probably get into the True Cross Academy.
It would be a bother if rumors started spreading.
You're going to the same school as Yukio?
That must be a bother.
Yep. So hold your mouth. We'll pay up.
So we'll just both keep silent, okay?
Huh? And I was wondering what you wanted.
I don't need your money. And I won't say a word.
Now, sorry but I've got stuff to do.
Are you playing the cool guy?
Seriously, get honest with yourself!
You're so poor you couldn't even get into a proper school!
Take it. Your brother Yukio worked his ass off and got in the school with a scholarship, right?
So he borrows! So pitiful!
He can't even pay his fee-
You can badmouth me as much as you want,
but don't you dare say another word about my brother!
This hurt...
You went to far!
Huh? He's not human?
Why doesn't anybody see...?
Eye for an eye, tooth for a tooth, huh?
I'll let you enjoy my pain a few times more!
It's enough, Shiratori. If you go further...
Shut up!
Where should I burn you?
Your nose? Your mouth? Or your eyes?
He's really...
Human barbecue!
Stop!
I'm burning?
Blue flames?
Shit! Run!
Heh, those blue flames are the proof of Satan's offspring.
I wasn't mistaken after all.
My name is Astaroth. Shall we go, Young Master?
Lord Satan waits for you.
Satan?
Mischief is in their hearts.
Give them according to their deeds, and according to the wickedness of their endeavors,
give them after the work of their hands, render to them their desert.
Smite them and let them not rise again.
You... you're an Exorcist?!
Blessed be the Lord.
Father...
I shall seal that mouth of yours, so that you cannot spout your curses!
You have heard my curse.
The Lord is my strength
and my shield.
Thou shall perish!
Are you okay?
Or rather, is he okay?
The demon has left him. He should wake up later.
Demon?
You can see them now too, right?
This is...
The Coal Tar that hangs on to dust,
and gathers around dark places and evil humans.
This world consists of two dimensions that face each other like mirrors.
One is our material world, Assiah.
The other is the nothingness of demons, Gehenna.
These two worlds are separate and they're not supposed to interact at all.
But they possess the material of this world and interact with it.
Stand. This incident has revealed them the truth about you.
There will be those who'll come to hunt you down.
You must hide before that.
Wait a sec, I don't get it!
Demons? What are they?
What am I?
You are not a human.
You are the child of a demon born of a human.
And not just any old demon, either.
The demon among demons, the evil god, Satan's child.
It was not by chance that I met you.
This is called fate.
Please watch over me
so that those eyes could keep on shining.
(Please be) So if this heart
(With me) one day loses its way,
please open the door to the future.
Hold on to these bonds we have.
Dance!
So don't let go of that hand. (Buddy)
Towards a place of dreams.
Hold on to these bonds we have.
Next Episode Preview
Don't ever say again that you're my father!
Rin!
Finally I could meet you, my son.
I'll become an Exorcist!
Gehenna Gate