a.t.b. stands for Ascension Throne Britannia. Koureki (Holy Calender) is used to represent a.t.b.
a.t.b. 2009, Japan.
Shinto shrine?
It's the Japanese version of a church.
Is the Pope the Emperor of Japan?
No, Japan doesn't have an Emperor.
The person who gets selected during an election becomes the Prime Minister.
It's only by coincidence that Prime Minister
Kururugi's personal residence is a Shinto shrine.
Brother, are you all right?
These stairs seem to be fairly long.
This is nothing. I can handle it.
To tell you the truth, those stairs were torture to my nine-year-old self.
However, back then, I absolutely would not let any Japanese person touch Nunnally.
The place we were given to live in was just a small storeroom within the Kururugi Shinto shrine.
I was momentarily speechless when I first saw it.
Brother, are we there yet?
Y-Y-Yes...
What kind of room is it?
How's the new home for Brother and I?
It's a wonderful place.
The walls are white like snow, and there are windows with flower decorations.
Sounds like Elder Sister Euphie's room.
Yes. But it's a bit small.
But, since it's just Nunnally and I...
Who is it?!
You over there, come out.
Don't speak so arrogantly.
This was originally my room after all.
Yours?
Britannians are so shameless.
Do you intend to colonize Japan too?
Japan is trying to enforce dominance as well.
You enforce sanctions on countries you deal with.
Erm...
Japan and Britannia aren't that different from each other.
Lies!
They aren't lies!
Try asking your father.
You're a liar!
What's this about white walls?!
Where are the decorated windows in this storeroom?!
Stop it!
I charged towards that boy without thinking.
But...
I was no match for him.
I was defeated just like that, collapsing at his feet.
How's that, you Britannian bastard!
Don't look down on the Japanese!
S-Stop it!
You barbarian!
Please stop!
I don't know who you are, but I'll do anything you tell me!
You... Don't tell me you can't see?
Yes, so please don't be alarmed.
I can't do anything,
be it fighting or running away.
That's why...
Then...
He started to tremble and look around frantically.
And then...
I-I'm sorry!
He dashed out of the storeroom as if he were escaping from something.
Brother, are you all right?
Brother?
Nunnally, I'm okay.
It was nothing serious.
Who was that?
He sounded like a child.
Most likely... Kururugi Suzaku.
Prime Minister Kururugi's child.
That was my first encounter with Suzaku.
To me, who was always surrouned by rivals and vassals, he was my first friend.
And eventually...
he would become the man who was my worst enemy.