Let's get wasted celebrating the descent of your Lord Satan!
Rin!
Are you all right?
Yukio? Is that Yukio?
What are you doing, Yukio?!
Episode 24
sziaSatan's Offspring
The little brother who offered his body to save his twin,
and his older brother who does not know that.
Seems we'll get to witness a tragedy of the highest grade!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Damn it! There's no end to them!
Where do you think you're going?
To the top where Rin and the others are, where else?!
I won't let anyone pass here.
Those are my orders.
This ain't the time for that!
Look! Does that look like okay to you?
Wait, Your Eminence!
Is it true? Do you intend to destroy Gehenna itself?
The Messiah has already been prepared as well.
Now we only have to open the Gehenna Gate.
But genocide using a weapon of mass destruction contradicts the Order's principles!
Understood.
I will make Yukio Okumura command this operation.
You will be my bodyguard.
Your Eminence! Your Eminence!
It may be that the Vatican has made a mistake,
but I'm a knight of the Vatican.
Even if the world was to fall apart, my soul is with the Order of the True Cross.
Come, Shura!
I, Arthur Auguste Angel, will fight you with all my strength!
You're such a goddamn pain in the ass.
Are you running away, Shura?
Who'll run away, I wonder?
Slay me if you want! I'm sick and tired of your stupidity!
What are you doing, Yukio?
Why do you have the blue flames?
Wasn't I the only one with Satan's powers?
Shut up!
You're... Satan?
Yeah, fucker! You just wouldn't realize it, Daddy was starting to feel so damn lonely!
Is that Satan?
Why? Why is Satan possessing Yukio?
Because he was ready first...
Ready to become my vessel, that is.
What?!
You two are of my own blood and your bodies are fucking perfect vessels for me.
I've been watching and waiting for you damn brats to grow up.
Get out of Yukio's body!
Rin!
Rin, are you all right?
Let me finish talking, you shithead.
I've been dreaming for the past 15 years.
A dream to make a new world by uniting Assiah and Gehenna.
A new world?
I got the perfect vessel to move around freely now.
Those morons opened such a fucking huge Gehenna Gate for me, too.
A bloody great chance to fulfill my dream!
But I ain't gonna enjoy it if you go and destroy this Gate too,
so do me a fucking favor and drop dead.
Wait! Fight me before shooting him!
Hey, Bon!
That's Satan himself! There's no way you can do it!
You don't know that without trying first!
Shut the fuck up!
Watch out!
Professor Tsubaki!
Take the raw rice, cleanse it!
Take the clean rice, purify it!
Brewer God, take eight handfuls,
make eight bowls, wide and clean!
Gods, hear my word and pour the wine of Heavens!
Are you all right, Professor?
Just run away! He's too strong for you!
Koneko!
Yes!
The Eternal Buddha have mercy on you!
We'll cover you!
Just get away quick!
Hail to the conqueror of Death! Let the world tremble before thee!
Bon!
It was my dream to defeat Satan!
I can't run away now!
Go! Yamantaka!
Don't look down on me, you fuckers!
Guys!
You're such pests. I'll burn you little shits to ashes together.
Stop!
Didn't I tell you?
Shura!
Show some respect, brat!
Moriyama!
Yes!
Leave this to me and take the wounded to somewhere safe!
Yes! Ni!
So, what do you want, Boobie Babe?
You changed way too much with that demon look, Scaredy Four-Eyes!
That's not Yukio! He's possessed by Satan!
What?!
I don't bloody like it how you fuckers pop up one after another!
Turn to ash, bitch!
What? He wants to merge Gehenna and Assiah?
Yeah.
It's too dangerous here. We should move.
Don't worry. Satan probably won't move from the Gate.
Why do you say that?
He needs it for his plan.
And you, Rin. You destroyed a Gehenna Gate once already when you tried to save Shiro.
He's being careful because of that.
It's like that kick the can game.
Kick the can?
You've never played it?
The one who's "it" is trying to catch everyone, but if someone kicks the can,
he loses, so he can't get away from it.
Just as Shima says, in that way we have the advantage.
Even Satan can't watch out for everything if we attack on all fronts at the same time.
Wait, and what about Yukio?
Satan isn't an opponent we could take out even if we used our full strength.
First we must destroy the Gehenna Gate and stop the demons' invasion.
Are you saying that I should abandon him?
I want to save him just as much as you do,
but there's no way to free anyone possessed by Satan.
You're wrong! Back then the geezer returned to himself in the last moment!
Yukio's soul must still be inside him!
If I call out, he'll come to!
Rin...
I trust him.
Hey, wait! Wait, Rin!
Damn him, he's going alone again!
You shouldn't move yet!
This isn't a big deal.
I'll defeat Satan. Let me go.
What do you think could you do?
What? I dare you to say that again, Kamiki!
No, it's not only you, all of us. If we went there, we'd just get in the way.
I'm not going, and I'm worried about Paku.
Kamiki is right.
Professor?
There are many people in this city who need your help now.
Wait! I said wait, dammit!
Let me go! Yukio is...
There for you to save, yeah sure. I'll help you.
Really?
The talker will take Yukio's attention, calling to him from the west gate.
The attacker will scale the wall and attack from the east.
If the talker can lure Yukio out from the open, we attack at once.
Whoever gets there, attacks.
It's decided then.
I should do the talking after all...
Yukio told you, didn't he? No Exorcist can fight alone.
Cooperating with your teammates and trusting in them is the most important thing.
So whatever happens, you do your part. Got it?
NOTICE - Kids! Bringing about Armageddon can be dangerous. Do not attempt it in your home.
A new world?
Yeah. No Gehenna and no Assiah, a world
where demons and humans could live together.
It doesn't exist yet, but I'm sure we could turn it real one day.
Everyone could understand each other like we do.
Close your eyes and imagine it. It shouldn't be hard.
Yuri, it's close. The world we dreamed of.
It's almost ready.
What? The Boobie Babe from earlier? And alone?
Shut up, Scaredy Four-Eyes!
You're there, aren't you?
How long are you gonna let Satan suppress you? Come on, wake up!
He's just a vessel now! You can scream as much as you want.
Don't worry, I'll wake him up!
With my fiery morning call!
Are you all right? Don't cry anymore.
What's going on here?
Why are all those monsters swarming here?
This is the end! They will eat us all!
That won't happen! I'm sure someone will come to help us!
All praise the one steady as adamant! Hail!
Come!
Hurry, this way!
Paku!
Izumo!
You held out well!
I knew you were coming for us!
Where are we?
Order of the True Cross, Japanese Branch.
The Vatican ordered us to open this place for shelter.
We can hold off the demons' attacks here.
What's wrong, Bon?
Have you seen Moriyama anywhere?
Now that you mention it... When did she disappear?
Did she get lost?
Her cell?
She doesn't have one.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Shura...
That chick is doing well against Father.
But she's still just a human.
She has her limits as well.
What's wrong? Is that all you've got, bitch?
As if!
Just like a fucking mouse.
Dream on.
So you ain't such a fool, huh?
But you've gotta follow me!
Kirigakure Style Secret Sword Technique!
One Snake's Skin Turns Into Hundred!
Shura!
Stop!
Oh? Look, a new guest.
Shiemi...
Please, stop!
Yuki wouldn't do something so mean!
What? Are you a friend of this fucker?
Yuki... Yuki is very important to me!
Give him back!
Don't make me laugh!
It can hold off Father's flames?
That is a seven rowan.
It is called thus because it will not burn even if you lit it seven times.
Indeed a wise choice, however...
You may hold off my flames, but you can't stop a direct attack.
Yuki...
Shiemi!
Stoooooop!
That idiot... Why...?
So you were hiding there after all.
Now that no one will butt in, let's have some bloody fun!
I won't fight my brother.
What?
Yukio, you're there, aren't you? Wake up!
You want to save your little brother?
Dream on!
Yukio, it's me! Wake up!
Pointless! He's mine!
Call all you want, he's not going to respond!
You can hear me, right, Yukio?
Yukio!
Yukio...
You're fucking persistent.
Open... your eyes! Yukio!
Rin?
Rin!
We won't let you.
Do you think you can leave us behind?
You hate your brother.
Your brother who grew up knowing nothing.
I could see demons all my life.
No! I...
He can do everything I can't.
He can get everything I can't.
I... I hate my brother!
He shouldn't even be alive.
No... No!
I... I...
Rin...
Help me, Rin...
Yukio!
Rin! Rin!
Rin!
I didn't expect you to wake up,
but I won't let you go, brat. You're mine!
Finish it! Kill him and let's complete the world we dreamed of!
Come on!
No!
What did you say?
We're the only ones who will die here!
You!
Yukio!
Fucking brat! You want to kill yourself to delay me again?!
You're fucking hilarious!
I swore... to protect Rin!
I have no other choice but this to protect him and this world!
Stop! Yukio, don't be so hasty!
If you die, our dream will be...
What the hell's up with that cool act all by yourself?
Would you be all right with defeating Satan by killing yourself?
Like hell I'd let you!
Don't you understand how the people left behind feel?!
I don't want to feel like that again!
Rin...
I'm so sorry, Rin, sorry...
What?
That voice...
Satan!
I wouldn't have thought you could beat me. What a surprise!
But you know, my dream is not finished yet!
What?!
The Gehenna Gate!
The all-out war between demons and humans is nearing its climax!
I wonder how our little brothers will fend off our raging mad father?
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
Is it right for us to have been born into this world?
Next Episode Preview
What's that light?
The contract is made.
And now, I wish you a pleasant journey.
Stop, time!