Co-op store
Supermarket Nico-Nico-Hall | Open 24/7 | True Cross Shop
Episode 6
szia The Phantom Cook
I overslept!
Thanks for the meal.
Good morning, Rin.
Why didn't you wake me up?!
I tried three times but you didn't wake up,
so I thought you must be tired and let you sleep.
Don't put on that kind brother act, just try four times from tomorrow on!
I'm digging in.
You're gobbling.
We're running a marathon in the third period.
I need to eat or I'll die.
I'll be going then. Clean up after you're done eating.
You're not my mother!
Thanks for the meal!
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Was I late?
It's mine!
Eh, Suguro?!
Look, isn't that Okumura? Rare to see you around here.
Hey!
How long are you going to hold on to it?
Let go already!
This is my sandwich!
I grabbed it first!
Come on, Bon...
You're not kids anymore...
Listen, Konekomaru.
Grudges about food can go on for seven generations!
To prevent that we must settle it here and now!
So you're called Konekomaru? That's one strange name.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Was I late?
Okumura!
And who are you?
We're freshmen in the Special Advancement department, just like you!
I'm Hashino!
I'm Nishiwaki!
I'm Oomoto!
And how may I help you?
I thought the shop may sell out quick...
So I made you lunch...
Please have some if you'd like.
Hey, I was here first!
What are you saying?! It was me!
Umm...
What's going on there?
Our young teacher is popular with girls.
They're so different even though they're brothers...
What do you mean, Konekomaru?
Why are you getting so familiar?!
Rin...
Sorry, I promised my brother to have lunch with him.
Excuse me!
Come!
Okumura! Please wait!
What the hell...?
You saved me, Rin.
Didn't they make lunch for you?
Why didn't you take it? Such a waste.
I couldn't eat all three and choosing just one could get really ugly.
Wow, this looks so delicious!
This is a school cafeteria and yet there's lobster and stuff!
Are you listening?
Amazing! French, Chinese, Italian... There's everything!
It's because the True Cross Academy is mostly for rich kids.
So I'm finally one of the celebs?!
First we need to buy food tickets from that vending machine.
What should I get?
Luxury lunch xxx00 yen, Special lunch 8000 yen, Standard lunch 6000 yen, Hamburger, Pork cutlet curry
Miso...  5800 yen,  ...meal (with dessert) xx800 yen, Tea snack meal 12000 yen,
Great fatty tuna 105xxx yen, ...curry, Lordly meal, Shark fin so...
Food tickets
What the hell?! That's one zero too much there!
I told you, this is a school for rich kids.
Damn it! Screw the celebs!
Calm down, Rin!
I'll treat you to the cheapest, 1800 yen A lunch meal!
Lower the prices of the cafeteria?
That's not possible.
To provide first class meals, we buy first class ingredients and hire first class chefs.
Why does the cafeteria have to be first class?!
Food is culture.
Experiencing first class makes your lives fuller.
Oh.
Says he and then eats instant ramen...
Then at least give me money for living expenses!
How could I totally forget about that?
Even Satan's son has needs.
Wow, a 2000 yen bill!
The mysterious bill, thought to exist only in urban legends!
With this I could buy ten sandwiches!
Is it fine if I pay that every month on the 10th?
Every month? You mean this is for one month?!
Indeed.
And I'm supposed to live off that, you dolt?!
Oh? You are dissatisfied? Then how about a 100 yen bill?
By the way, recently I've been somewhat obsessed with Taisuke Itagaki.
I don't give a damn about your obsession!
Calm down, Rin!
The house-
Father said it often... "Man does not live by bread alone".
Sermons won't fill my stomach.
Are you fine with it? Can you be satisfied with 2000 yen a month?
I work as a teacher and I get my Exorcist salary as well.
You traitor!
Wait... There's a way to keep you from starving to death.
Cook for myself?
I'll pay for the ingredients.
You can make lunch for the both of us.
That way I'll save some money and you won't have trouble with lunch, either.
After all, cooking is one of the few things you're good at.
Not to mention guys who can cook are popular.
Are you serious? Finally my time has come!
If Rin cooks for us he'll wake up in time, and if girls offer me lunch like today,
I can escape by saying that I brought my own lunch without sounding strange.
This plan is like taking down two birds with one stone! Or rather, four birds!
But where can I cook? Was there a kitchen in the room?
You could use the dorm kitchen. It's just the two of us in the old dorm anyway.
You really don't have to do it so late in the night.
I make the side dishes the previous night and put them in the fridge.
Then you take the cold lunch with you in the morning,
and it'll be just the right temperature to eat by lunchtime.
This is like common sense for homemakers.
I see...
I wish you were this good at studying, too...
Shut up!
Just do your damn business and go to sleep!
Yeah, yeah. See you later.
Okay, they're ready.
Huh? A mouse?
Darn, it's this late.
You spotty four-eyes!
What the hell did you call me?!
No matter how hungry you are, there are things you're not supposed to do!
Huh?
Don't play stupid!
You ate all the side dishes that I made for today's lunch!
As if I'd do such a thing!
Then who did it? It's just the two of us in this dorm, isn't it?
Just the two of us...
No...
Everyday at mealtimes our food was prepared...
I didn't even think about it, but who cooked it?
Someone's there!
Someone... but who?
Good morning, boys!
Mephisto?!
So you were making our meals every day?
As if I would do that!
I'm just a temporary replacement.
Temporary replacement?
Ukobach was the one making your meals.
Ukobach?
I've heard about it. It's the spirit of the fireplace, if I recall correctly.
It sneaks in the kitchen while people sleep and makes meals more delicious...
And that's the correct answer, Mr Okumura.
He was working here as my familiar.
But yesterday you used the kitchen and trespassed his territory without permission,
so he became sulky and started boycotting it.
I understand the reasons, but what the hell is this?
Special Imp Oatmeal à la Mephisto!
Go on, dig in.
Don't hold back.
I'll eat it!
Rin, are you all right?
Granny is calling me...
What?! We never even met her!
Wait, don't you dare follow her!
Reasons aside, the misbehavior of the familiar is the misbehavior of its master.
Therefore I'll be taking care of your meals until Ukobach recovers his mood.
And if he doesn't?
Then I will be your cook forever.
Rin!
Ukobach-smukobach... I don't care. I'll exterminate it!
Beating it up wouldn't help much...
How about this? Everything's cleaned up just as it used to be.
Just cheer up already!
Are you still mad?
Just what's your problem?
If you don't want to work, get lost already!
You're not the only one around who can cook!
You finally showed up.
Sir Pheles was with him so I wasn't worried when I left...
But now I have a bad feeling.
Rin!
What the hell?!
Sir Pheles! What on earth is going on here?
They had a frantic duel.
Using all their skills and strength!
A cooking fight?
They matched the best of their abilities against each other, thus giving birth to a new friendship.
That fried rice was damn good!
What? My pork and rice wasn't bad either, you say?
Let's make the ultimate lunch!
I'm sure we can do it together!
Amazing... He's unbelieveable in so many ways.
Okumura, is that homemade?
Well...
Looks so delicious!
Amazing, Okumura! You're not just good at studying but you're also a great cook!
No, my brother made it.
Your brother?
Yeah, my brother's really good at cooking.
Great, Yukio! Impress them with my cooking skills just like that!
Okumura's brother...
You can make such a lunch by yourself, so cool!
And thus I'll be popular with the girls, for the first time in my life?
That's your brother?
There's no way such a brute could cook at all.
Will you teach me how to cook?
Ah, me too!
Damn it, why?!
Okumura's eating his lunch crying.
He must've been very hungry.
Don't even look, idiocy is contagious.
True Cross Academy Boys' Dormitory
Guys who can cook are popular, my ass.
I just let Yukio take credit for this, too.
Shiemi?
What are you doing here?
Yuki!
Can I help you?
The malachites arrived, so I brought you your order.
Sorry for the trouble.
Since you came all this way, how about some tea?
But...
It's okay, come on.
Who's that chick?!
Barging into Okumura's dorm like that.
Is she his girlfriend?
That can't be! No way!
I'm sure she's just a maid or something like that!
Since when do you offer tea to a maid?
Anyway, if we give up here the lunches we made will go to waste!
Let's wait until that chick leaves.
A familiar?
He's the cook of our dorm.
He made this tea as well.
Delicious! Thanks, Ukobach!
Oh, it's so late! I should get going.
Don't worry, I have the magic key connecting to the shop.
Ah, that's right. I walked all the way here.
I'll see you off.
Thanks, Yuki.
"Thanks, Yuki" she says...
How long are you going to wave?
You're happy if someone says it's delicious?
Are you serious?
How long are we waiting?
It's almost midnight.
What else can we do? That chick isn't coming out.
Could she be staying in Okumura's room?
What?!
We have no choice.
We're going in!
Which room is his?
Number 602.
Wait, this smell...
Yeah, someone's been cooking here.
The side dishes for tomorrow's lunch?
Could it be that chick made these?
I made octopus wieners.
Please make some fried shrimp too!
No!
It only deserves this!
He wouldn't even touch the lunches we made...
But he eats what that chick cooked?
I can't let that happen! Never!
What was that?
Ukobach? Is that you, Ukobach?
What's wrong, Ukobach?
Hey, that's...
My classmates.
I don't even want to think about it, but I think I know what happened here.
He started stewing them.
It's strange.
Obviously!
When you're making a stew, you add ginger and a bay leaf to suppress the smell of meat.
That's your biggest problem?
It's elementary! To think that he forgot it...
Hey! What are you trying to make?!
Rin!
Ukobach, didn't you say that...
If someone eats your cooking and says it's delicious...
That's enough for you...
What's this omelet?
Salty!
It has egg shell pieces in it! Who made this?
Rin!
You did?
If you don't like it, you don't have to eat it!
Hey, don't waste food!
Give it back, old fart!
Ah, Rin made this omelet?
Not bad for first try.
Thanks for the meal.
We cook because we want to make someone happy when they eat it.
We're happy if someone says that it's good.
That's why I like to cook, why I want to cook!
Who would call that thing you're making good?!
Why...
Why won't you eat it?
Ukobach spoke?
No... Could it be this is...
Even though I made it for you...
I wanted you to eat it, Yukio...
I see... Their chagrin drove Ukobach wild!
So... It's all your fault!
Huh?
Eat it! Eat the lunches they put their hearts into making!
I bet it's nice and salty, and totally delicious!
Why me?!
So he ate that huge amount of food alone, without leaving a bite?
Amazing, Mr Okumura. That's a great countermeasure.
Don't worry about the girls, they are attending classes today as usual.
Thanks to you, Ukobach cheered up, too.
You worked hard, just rest for a few more days!
Bye.
Hey!
What's this?
To make you recover fast, Ukobach and I made you this special stamina meal!
Don't hold back, dig in!
I'm getting scared of food...
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
From next week, we'll be going to a week-long training camp for the exams.
Next Episode Preview
Shiemi? What are you doing here?
I... Um... Please be friends with me!
Flock of Plovers