Creator   Taro Kawaguchi
Translator   Vincent
Heroes are just legends
Hero Sore wa Densetsu
Hero Legends
Heroes are cool
Hero Sore wa Kakkoii
SUPER
Series Composition   |2eiko Yoshida
Editor   Ayanami-
Heroes are the burning energy that resides in you
Hero Kimi no Naka ni Aru
Atsui Energy
Character Design   Tomoyuki Kamiya
Timer   Lythka          Typesetter   getfresh
Through some turn of events, you've been driven up against a wall
Douiu Wakedaka Dai Pinch
But do not fret or worry, and put on a big, bright smile
Sonna Toki Koso
Waratte Miro yo
Take on the foes who stand before you, no matter how big they are
Kyodai na Aite ni Tachimukae
Art Director   Ticaco Sibata
Color Design   Mayumi Tanahasi
Director of Photography   Kazuya Ivvai
Now, muster your strength, and charge!
Sou sa Ima, Hashiridasun da
Music   Audio Lows
Sound Director   Junwatana Be
OP Karaoke   Shinjipierre
ED Karaoke   pichu
Everyone's smile...
Minna no Egao o
Especially her smile...
Ano Ko no Egao o
Gives me the endless power I need
Omoeba Minagiru Mugen no Power
Heroes are the legends
Hero Sore ga Densetsu
Opening Theme
"Super Hero Legend"
Lyrics/Composition   Keniche Kaswi
Arrangement   Masaki Suzuki
Performed by Hironobu Kageyama
Heroes are super cool
Hero Totemo Kakkoii
Heroes are the burning energy that resides in you
Hero Kimi no Naka ni Aru
Animation Producer   Yuji Mathreekura
Logo   Miho's Wolf          Quality Control   kenners
Executive
Producers
Kenjy Syto
Masa Nojima
Tomoya Negisi
Atsui Energy
The burning energy
Moeru Energy
Director  Keniche Kaswi
Raw Provision  Starks          Encoder   Kristen
Hey, Taka. You got another art award?
Oh, Uncle, you're here.
Yeah, have to at least show up around New Year's.
Mashiro
New Year's Gift
Here!
Thanks!
But you're amazing. This one even has the signature of some cabinet minister!
You could be an artist or designer when you grow up.
But my uncle never once said "manga artist."
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can't be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Every worry floats up to and fills the spring sky
Shinpaigoto Bakari ga Tsumoru Haru no Sora o
I look up, look down,
Miagete Utsumuite
and find myself looking back up at the sky
Mata Kao o Ageteru
I swore I'd find myself in this town
Kono Machi de Mitsukerutte Kimeta Jibun
I tuck away all my important things into my heart for safekeeping
Nakushichaikenai Mono o Mune ni
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can't be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Dreams and Reality
Moritaka! Get out of bed! You're going to be late for school!
Moritaka!
After nine years of compulsory
education, the adults ask incessantly,
"What high school do you want to go to?" and, "What dreams do you have for the future?"
But I, Moritaka Mashiro, just answer with,
"I have no clue." or "I haven't decided yet."
It's "normal" to aim for a better high school, university, or company.
That's how you live a "normal" life.
That's why I always go to school, even though I'd rather game or stare at the computer all day.
Because I don't want to trouble my parents,
because I don't want to be called a shut-in,
and because I don't wanna flip burgers when I grow up.
That's why I'm just gonna get a desk job and call it a day.
If I wanted to try climbing the corporate ladder, I'm already behind all the people with good grades.
That ranking system is only gonna be a continuation of school.
It's a bleak future. Just living is a pain in the butt.
This is my outlook on life after being a good kid for 14 years.
Recently, there was this book I read that said,
that the greatest event in life, our most important raison d'être was to love.
Cut the crap. Something like that could only have been written by a woman.
For someone like me who can't even speak to the girl I like,
love is nothing but agonizing.
This one-sided crush is going nowhere. It's gonna drag me straight to hell.
Midterms start tomorrow. Make sure you all try your best.
Thank you very much!
Saiko, let's go home.
O-Ok.
Saiko, Suzuki, let's go.
Here ya go.
Oh, thank you.
Damn, tests start tomorrow.
Isn't it better this way? We get to go home earlier today.
Then let's make the most of our time!
Yep yep!
Miho, let's go home together.
Sure.
Being in separate classes makes me so lonely!
Hey, Kaya!
Let's go hang out somewhere.
Saiko!
Now, whatever shall we do?
Wanna watch a movie?
Wait, that erotic one?
Yep, that one.
Let's watch that one then.
What about you, Saiko?
I don't want my grades to drop below the class average. I'm gonna study. See ya.
Saiko! So boring.
Huh? My math notebook...
I don't need my notes to study, but I don't wanna leave that at school.
Akito Takagi.
What're you doing? Shouldn't you be studying,
in order to keep your number one place in school?
My notebook? Did he find out that I like Azuki?!
Why so serious?
It's not like it's a Death Note, right?
Why the hell do you have my notebook?
Because I sit way back here.
I know what you drew in your notebook during class,
and I know you forgot it here.
Sorry, but I took a peek inside,
and I thought you'd definitely come back for it.
And so, I waited here for you.
What the hell is this guy scheming?
Even so, Miho Azuki is quite the cutie.
Even though she's quiet and doesn't
stand out, she's the best looking by far.
He likes Azuki too?
Azuki probably likes you too, you know?
Huh? Th-There's no way that's true!
We haven't even talked to each other! How the hell would you know?
I told you already. It's because I sit all the way in the back.
You're saying that you know everything that goes on in class because you sit in the back?
Yeah, pretty much.
But if you don't think she likes you,
then maybe I was wrong.
What the hell. He got my hopes up for a second.
Don't worry. I'll give this notebook back, and I won't tell anyone its secrets.
Alright, thanks.
However, on one condition:
Here it comes.
What?
Probably something like "hands off Azuki."
Team up with me and create manga.
Ever since I was a kid, I've loved manga.
It's my dream to write manga.
I've thought about it a lot, and I really need your drawings.
A national, top class student like you? Becoming a manga artist?
I was born a man. That's why I wanna make it big!
I wanna get rich!
I can't get into showbiz, 'cause I
don't have the looks or the voice.
I'm not especially good at any sports.
But I've got the literary talent and you have the drawing skills.
There's no other choice but manga artists!
Manga is the national pride of Japan!
We're going to leave our mark on history with manga!
So, a student with award-winning essays conceives the story,
and I cover the illustrations.
Interesting.
Isn't it?
But I'll pass.
You'll pass, huh. You must love manga, too. Don't you?
You can't just be a manga artist.
Only those born with the talent can become manga artists. And of those, only the geniuses can.
The rest is all just gambling.
Gambling?
By manga artists, I mean the ones who can make a living only off of writing manga.
Even if you get serialized in a weekly magazine,
every week, the readers rank the
popularity of the manga in a questionnaire.
If you're unpopular, you're cut by the 10th week.
You either have to hit a jackpot right away
or write a successful manga after numerous tries.
If you can't do at least that, it's all just a gamble.
Only 0.001% of them can live off just writing manga. That's about 1 in 100,000 people.
What are these statistics from? Someone give them to you?
Well, I guess it's alright.
My uncle was a manga artist... no, he was one of those gamblers.
Yeah... he "was."
You uncle was a manga artist? You're joking.
It's true.
Who? Who was he?
It was pretty long ago. Even if I tell you, you woul-
Who?
Taro Kawaguchi, a mang-
WHAT?! The one who wrote Super Hero Legends?!
I watched that anime when I was a kid! I even bought the comics!
I really like that manga!
Alright! It's settled!
You've got the DNA of a manga artist. And you're really knowledgeable about manga.
When there's something we don't
know, you can just ask your uncle.
DNA... it's my uncle, you know? My dad's brother.
Even so, my uncle is-
Hold up.
Taro Kawaguchi's drawings were really crappy.
But yours are good.
Maybe DNA doesn't have anything to do with it.
Anyways, I'm not gonna do it.
So you can just keep the notebook.
See ya, thief.
Wait!
Even though it seems like a gamble,
in lotteries, you don't win if you don't buy a ticket.
Same for manga, you won't win if you don't even draw it!
What's more likely, winning 300,000,000 yen or making it big with manga?
Uncle said something like that, too.
Come on, let's try!
You know, writing essays is completely different than manga.
I know.
When I write essays, they're targeted directly at the judges.
I write in a style they'll like.
For manga, it'd be alright if I just cater to the publishers and readers.
Then why don't you just try for the Naoki Award?
Nah, right now you can profit more with manga.
And I like manga better anyways.
I can taste the dream already.
Then just draw it yourself.
There's lots of publishing companies out there just for original stories.
And then you can find someone to illustrate for you.
What? Are you aiming for a steady government job or something?
No, I'm still-
Then why are you so reluctant?
Why...
If you put it that way, I don't really know myself either.
Maybe because it's too much effort.
Anyways, I'm going back to study.
Thanks for the notebook.
At this rate, you're gonna watch
your life pass by at a snail's pace!
You're fine with that being all your life amounts to?
It's weirder to have and strive for a dream in ninth grade.
It's better to start early!
Everyone is just going aimlessly about their lives, avoiding any decisions!
If we team up, we would definitely make it!
You don't know when to give up.
Fine, I'll think about it when I get home.
Really?
The answer's probably gonna be a "no" still.
That's fine. Anyways, please give it a little more thought.
If it's still "no", then I'll give up.
When I was still in elementary school, I wanted to become a manga artist.
Hey Uncle, why'd you become a manga artist?
I'm still just a gambler.
Oh, then why'd you become a gambler?
Because I wanted to be popular with the girls.
So you get popular if you're a manga artist.
Well, I figured that if I got famous and made lots of money,
then I'd get popular.
Don't tell anyone I said that.
Scary...
When I was in middle school, there was a girl that I liked.
We almost never talked up until graduation.
That's a short story!
But at graduation, I got a letter from that girl.
A love letter! Awesome!
Nah, that letter just said something like "Let's do our best" and that was it.
And I replied with "Yes, let's give it our best."
We went to different high schools, so we never got to see each other.
We just exchanged letters back and forth.
Huh, that's kinda nice.
But after high school, she went on to work for an elite corporation
and I ended up at a crappy university.
I had thought of marrying her,
then I realized, "Oh crap! I need to do something so she'll accept me!"
That's what I had thought.
So you became a manga artist!
But then she got promoted to the secretary of the CEO,
and over here serialization was about to
discontinue for a novice manga artist like me.
It felt like the gap between us was getting wider.
And then when Super Hero
Legends finally became an anime...
You confessed, right?
She'd already married someone else by then.
Oh no...
I might have lost the gamble for love,
but if it wasn't for her, I wouldn't have given it my best shot.
But two years later...
Then, we'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you for everything you've done for us.
But really, it all seems so sudden...
What was the cause?
Seems like he overworked himself...
But, he wasn't that busy lately, right?
Didn't he have a lot of debts? On top of tha-
Thank you very much for coming today.
I think Nobuhiro would also have appreciated it.
Oh... y-you're welcome.
In the seven years after Super Hero
Legends, he created two new works.
But they were quickly discontinued.
They said that my uncle died from overwork,
but I thought he committed suicide.
Having dreams, doesn't guarantee success.
If they're not gonna come true anyways, you might as well live a normal life...
Moritaka.
Huh? What?
Is something wrong? I thought you had come
back already, but then you left again right away.
Hey! What are you doing?! Aren't there exams tomorrow?
If you carry on like this, you won't get into South High!
What the hell?!
Everyone is just deciding my future as they please.
Just leave me alone!
It's Takagi.
Takagi? How'd you get my number?
I asked Suzuki.
That's-
More importantly, I'm going to
Azuki's house to confess to her.
You should come too.
Huh?!
Why?! You know I like Azuki!
That's why there's no point if you're not here. Hurry and come!
Wh-What? I have no idea what you're talking about.
Can't you confess by yourself?
I'm not going to screw you over.
I fell for your illustrations, and I like you too.
Are you alright? You're confessing to the wrong person here.
After school I did some detective work on
Azuki, and I found out something amazing.
Then why do I have to come?
Just freaking come already! I'm at the convenience store on Nishi-cho!
Hey! I was waiting for you, Saiko!
That's Moritaka to you.
Alright, let's go. It's just over there!
This is a really nice house. Quite fitting for our Madonna.
Yeah...
I-I'm going to push it.
You've never rang a girl's doorbell before?
Like you have? Then you do it!
No and no. It's your confession.
Then don't mouth off. I'm ringing it.
He rang it!
I'm leaving!
You're just gonna leave me here?! You bastard!
Yes?
U-Uh, I'm in Miho's class. My name is Takagi.
I have something to ask Miho about the th-- test thomorrow.
He stuttered.
Takagi, the top student?
Well, not real- yes.
Wow. Her mother even knows his name.
Wait a second please.
Oh, yes.
Do you think she's suspicious of us?
Yes?
Azuki's voice. Crap!
Um...
Azuki, it's Takagi.
Could you come out here for a second?
I have something very important to tell you.
Wait a second.
Whoa, she's coming out? I wonder how she looks like out of uniform.
Hey, I'm here, too! Don't hog the spotlight!
My bad! I'm like panicking right now.
I knew it.
Azuki.
Yes.
I'm going to be a manga artist.
I came here to tell you this.
His confession... was this?
I heard from your friend Miyoshi
that you're aiming to become a voice actress, right?
Voice actress?
Yeah.
Yeah... really?
I heard that you've been sending your tapes to production companies.
What am I dreaming about?
There's no way she can be a voice actr-
And you've even garnered some praise, right?
Is Azuki really gonna become a voice actress?
Next up, a word from our Mashiro.
What... What should I say?
What am I going to say?
I-I'm going to do the illustrations. This guy is doing the story.
I knew it! Awesome! You two can definitely make it!
Her eyes are shining! Her eyes sparkle! She's so cute!
Th-Then if our manga becomes an anime,
we'll reserve the heroine's voice for you.
This makes me really happy.
I'm going to try my best.
I'll definitely become a voice actress,
then I'll voice your anime. Wonderful!
Wow! Her smile is so pretty!
She's looking at me. And so close too!
Azuki's so freaking cute!
When I was in middle school, there was a girl that I liked.
I thought about marrying her...
Then after our dreams come true, will you marry me?
Huh? Huh?!
What the hell did you just say?
Yeah. What the hell did I just say?
I said my uncle's words out loud. Crap, I'm so embarrassed!
Mashiro.
Y-Yes! I'm sorry!
Uh, how should I say this, just now...
Yes, I promise.
Huh? To what? W-Wait, about the marriage thing--
Yes.
But we can't meet again until our dreams come true.
Huh?
You mean until our manga becomes an
anime and you become a voice actress,
we won't meet and then suddenly we'll just get married?
Yeah, until our dreams come true, we should
both try our best without meeting each other.
Until then, we can encourage each other through texts.
No good?
No, that's fine! Please!
My mom's coming! See ya!
So this is what you meant. I get it. I understand now.
Seems like uncle also had this type of wonderful relationship.
But Azuki promised to marry me if our dreams come true.
Seems like my gamble has better odds than yours.
I will become a manga artist.
Oh, that went way better than I'd expected.
Let's be the best manga artists in Japan!
No.1 in Japan is impossible.
Not with the low birth rates right now.
Plus, there's no way we're going to top Dragonball or One Piece.
Quite the logical analysis you've got there.
And you're not the only person who I'll team up with.
Books
I'm gonna make it. I'll become a manga artist no matter what.
And then I'm gonna marry Azuki!
The King of Manga
Practice
with Mako
and Rabbi
The boring everyday gets to me sometimes,
Betaa na Genjitsu ni Tsubusaretemo
but I always get back on my feet, standing strong
Uchinomesareta Jibun Hiroiatsumete
No matter how many times the end approaches me,
Nando Owari ga Otozuretemo
I'll push my own back forward, keeping me on my feet
Sonotabi ni Jibun de Jibun no Senaka Oshita
If I get lost in the meaning of continuing what I do,
Tsuzuiteku Imi ni Nayami
I'll rid myself of those worries and keep myself going forward
Sono Mayoi Sae Tachikitte Yuku
Always
Itsumo
The straight edge that draws the outline of my future
Mirai no Rinkakusen Kaku Massugu na Jougi wa
is made of all the courage I've mustered up until today
Ikutsumo no Kinou no Yuuki de Dekiteru
I'll climb over the tall wall that I never thought I'd face,
Omoiegaita no to Chigau Takai Kabe Koe
and continue my journey, going past the vanishing point
Shoushisuten no Mukou e Susunde
This winding road seems to never end,
Harukanaru Winding Road
but it is the road I personally chose
Hoka no Dare Demo Nai Watashi ga Jibun de Eranda
I set my tiny dreams on fire,
Kasuka na Yume o Zenbu Moyashita
and broke through the dark with its light
Sono Hikari de Yami o Saite
Now that I've broken down the wall,
Kudaita Kabe no Mukou ni
I can see my sky once more
Jibun no Sora ga Mieru
Next Episode
I'm going to be a manga artist.
You mean "we are."
But, my dad and my grandpa are gonna object.
Huh, really? Our dream's over?
Next time: Idiot and Genius
Idiot and Genius
Just how are we going to realize our dream?