Euphie...
Do I really have to wear this...?
Yes. It's wonderful, right?
I think it really suits you!
But... Erm... Don't you feel that... it's a bit... revealing...?
It's fine!
Anyway, this is the safest one among the swimsuits designed by Brother Clovis.
So, hurry up and change!
I-I get it!
I can change alone...!
It's worn like this!
N-No... Hey, don't do that!
Euphie, enough of your jokes!
T-The princess's swimsuit...
I can't wait to see it.
My son would probably feel envious if he heard about it.
He's a Graston Knight, right?
I respect the fact that you picked up an orphaned boy and trained him to be a knight, but...
Isn't it a bit imprudent of you to say that?
Guil, you are still as old-fashioned as ever.
Note: Katai(固い) can mean old-fashioned or hard.
Er... since we're talking about "hard"... Erm...
Lord Darlton...
Hmm?
It's true that our mission is to be the bodyguards of the princesses, but...
I think you're overdoing it by trying to hide a gun in your swimming trunks...
Is it that obvious? Really?
Yes... To tell you the truth... it looks bizarre...
It can't be helped... Guess I'll give up.
Cecile-san, we came here to be guards, right?
Yes.
But is it really all right for us to be so relaxed?
It's fine.
No one would expect Princess Cornelia to be here as a surprise guest, right?
There won't be a need for a KnightMare to make an appearance.
That's why Lloyd-san's not around.
It's unfortunate that he can't come with us.
I-I'm not really...
That swimsuit is wonderful.
G-Gosh! Suzaku-kun, don't make fun of adults!
That's not quite my intention.
Oh? Suzaku-kun?
Eh?
Yahoo!
What are you doing here?
The same goes for you...!
My family were all once local celebrities after all, so I received some invitations here.
That's why I brought everyone along.
Everyone?
Ah, Lelouch! Nunnally!
Suzaku-san!
Yo!
I'm surprised that you guys came too.
I asked to come along, since I heard that Brother Clovis... His Highness designed the pool,
so I wanted to swim in it.
Swim...? But...
Because I can't move my legs, I feel more free when I'm in water.
A-Ah, that's right... Suzaku-san...
If it's all right with you, would you please swim together with me?
"I'd love to"... I want to say that, but the truth is that I'm here due to work.
Hmm? Work?
Yup...
Ah... That's right...
It's fine since you'll be a distance away, but the two of you better be careful.
Actually...
Today, one of the public facilities left by my brother, Clovis...
This "Clovis Land" shall be opened to the public by me.
The facility was built here on this colony as part of the effort to rouse the idea of Britannian prestige amongst the people...
Cornelia...!
President, take a look. Lulu is staring pretty hard at her.
He looks as if he's going to spring on her at anytime!
That is... Well... She's that great after all...
It's normal for any healthy high school male to want to cling on to her...
Right, Suzaku?
Eh? Erm... Well...
She's great? Is Princess Cornelia really that great?
I wonder how I can be like her...
That is... Hmm...
That's right! You'll probably need to receive various trainings from men.
P-President, what are you saying all of a sudden?!
I understand!
Brother!
W-What is it, Nunnally?
Please teach me various things!
So that I can be as great as Princess Cornelia!
W-Wait! Nana-chan?!
That's right. There might be a need for that someday.
All right, Nunnally.
I'll teach you everything I know.
E-Even Lulu?!
However! I won't be gentle on you.
Okay! I'll do my best!
Until Brother is satisfied with me!
O-Oh! This is pretty amazing!
Is this what they call a beautiful yet dangerous sibling love?
N-No way! There has to be a mistake somewhere!
Lulu!