Begin the attack!
Gloucester?!
They're not supposed to be in Serbia!
Their bulky Knightmares are no match!
They should have surrendered when they had the chance!
What?
Cornelia...
Don't tell me, with only one machine...
So this means that the creatures of Area 18 have fallen, right?
Princess, about the mobilization effort...
Sorry, I'll have you accompany me in finishing it.
No need. Your section has been secured.
Area 11 will be difficult to handle.
I understand.
I will find you, Zero...
to avenge Clovis!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Lelouch.
Welcome home, brother.
From the looks of it, you've already ate dinner.
I was worried.
I thought that you might have been caught up in the chaos that person named Zero caused.
I called you, but I couldn't reach you.
Brother?
C.C.-san came all the way here to see you...
C.C.?
Your friend is quite interesting, having only initials for a name.
Yeah...
Could it be... that she's your girlfriend?
Huh?
Our futures are intertwined with one another, right?
By future, do you mean marriage?
No! No, it's not like that.
So, um... she's kidding...
I hate jokes.
I see. I'm surprised at how quickly you decided, brother.
But they say, "To each his own", so it may not be that strange, I suppose.
Ah, what are you doing C.C.?
You're all wet.
Here, you need to go to the bathroom.
I'll get you a change of clothes too.
Nanali, I'll clean it up right away, so stay right there.
Also, we were lying before...
A lie, a joke.
Who are you?
I told you.
I'm C.C.
That's not what I mean.
You're...
Supposed to be dead?
Do you like it?
The power I gave you.
As I thought, you're...
Are you unsatisfied?
No, I'm grateful.
You pushed my schedule forward a great deal.
Schedule?
The plan to destroy Britannia.
I thought that it would be a little while longer before I could make my move.
Do you think you can destroy it with just that power?
I was planning to do this even without it.
As expected, you're an interesting person.
What are you going to do from now on? You're being pursued by the military, aren't you?
Even if you say the military, it's only a small portion of it.
It's enough if I just keep a low profile.
I'll put up with it here.
Hey, you're planning on staying here?
Men sleep on the floor.
That's not the point...
If I get caught, you'll have problems too, won't you?
Being together is even more dangerous.
If I sleep out there, I will be caught.
Not at your convenience, but at mi-
I hate persistent people.
You're being very careless about this.
More importantly, how did you survive?
How is your backbone?
And that contract you were talking about...
Good night, Lelouch.
Fukushima, Kouchi, Hiroshima.
This makes it seven incidences since Zero appeared.
After Zero appeared, other groups apparently became more hard-working.
Because of that "orange" incident, substitute supervisor Jeremiah has lost his leadership.
He doesn't have the ability to do it.
Thanks to that, the cooperation with the police and unions are in shambles.
It's quite an inconvenience for us as well.
Lend us your strength, Toudou!
Thanks to Zero, Britannia is in a state of confusion!
Now is the time that we, the Japan Liberation Front, should make a stand!
Don't rush it!
The information that Kyoto is giving the Crimson Brocade to Zero is not definitive.
If you concentrate on Zero too much, they will pull the rug out from under you!
Hey, in the end, what did "orange" mean?
What?
You won't answer anyone's questions at all, but you'll ask me questions, huh?
If you don't want to answer me, then you don't have to.
Just like me.
"Orange" was just a casual remark.
But...
There are those who will want it to mean something and will start to analyze it.
The entire world is searching for you.
The entire world is moving because of you.
Lelouch, is this what you wanted to see?
No, this disturbance is merely part of the calculation.
The world will plunge into an even greater chaos.
Private Kururugi Suzaku of the district 11 military, case 1075, concerning the suspicion of Prince Clovis' murder.
We declare you acquitted due to lack of evidence.
Why... all of a sudden?
Please get out of the way!
Look out!
Um... are you injured, or something?
I'm sorry!
I didn't think there would be anyone below.
Oh... no...
I didn't think that a girl would be falling from above either.
Oh?
Is... something wrong?
Yes! Something is wrong!
Eh?
To tell you the truth, I'm being chased by bad people.
So, can you please help me?
We cannot allow that "orange" to affect Princess Cornelia's arrival.
At this rate, the loyalty of us, the Purists, will be questioned.
Is that true?
That Sir Jeremiah is wild...
Then what is "orange"?
At any rate, it's a fact that Sir Jeremiah is guilty.
Saying that he does not remember anything... it's the same excuse as Patre!
Sir Jeremiah's memories are jumbled.
It's the same with those who had their Sutherlands stolen in Shinjuku.
And...
I haven't introduced myself yet, have I?
I am...
Yuffie.
Yuffie?
Yes.
I am...
You shouldn't do that.
You're famous.
The son of former Captain Kururugi, Private Kururugi Suzaku.
It was a lie, right?
The story about being chased by bad people.
Meow.
Meow meow?
Are you hurt, meow?
Meow meow meow~
Meow?
Meow~
Meow meow?
Meow?
Oh my.
We're late, I hope he's waiting for us.
But was he really acquitted?
Apparently on lack of evidence.
Well, it looks like he was thoroughly investigated, thanks to that incident with Zero...
Oh, why...?
Huh?
Do you dislike cats?
Well, I like them, but...
It appears to be a one-sided love.
Kind people are the ones who have one-sided loves.
It ran off.
Yuffie?
Why did you lie just now?
Are you concerned about me?
Eh?
Uh, yes.
Well then, please come with me for a little bit!
When we're like this, it doesn't seem too different from being in Britannia.
You're from the motherland, Yuffie?
Yes!
I was a student up until last week.
Until last week? Then, what are you now?
By student, do you mean a high-schooler?
You can go sightseeing whenever you want, right?
You ask a lot questions, don't you?
Oh, sorry.
Ah, no, that's not what I meant...
Um... today is my last day off, so I wanted to see what sort of place Area 11 is.
Then it didn't have to be me...
No, I'm glad it was you.
Oh, I see...
Suzaku-san, could you take me to one more place?
You may request anything of me, princess.
Then to Shinjuku...
Please show me Shinjuku, Kururugi Suzaku-san.
Lelouch-kun.
Are you busy right now?
Hm? What is it?
It's about that phone call from before.
Phone call?
Um... you know, that time in the bathroom...
Ahh.
Do you know if there are call logs?
I want to contact that person.
It's the school's phone, so I don't think...
I see...
I thought so too...
That woman...
What?
What's wrong- whoa!
No way...
Hey...
Hm?
What are you doing?
Ah, what indeed...
To return to the motherland like this...
I shouldn't have gotten involved with that woman...
Are you an idiot?
Don't just go wandering around!
I'm okay as long as I'm within the school grounds.
Don't be so strict.
No, you're an outsider here.
I'm an outsider no matter where I go.
What's with that person?
Oh.
So she's at it again today.
Again today?
I placed a Geass on her which makes her carve a symbol on this wall every day.
Geass?
This power.
During the contract, that's what I heard.
A test to find out the length of duration, huh?
It's best to understand the specs of your weapon, isn't it?
If you're too uncontrollable, then...
I wonder if it would work on me?
Don't worry.
You and I are accomplices.
I won't do anything that would put us in a disadvantegous situation.
The Shinjuku ghetto is finished.
People had finally begun to return, but...
Aw... As I thought, they won't use the RG's against Elevens.
Hey, over here.
It's the aftermath. Hurry up and take the picture!
I know!
Take a picture of me next!
Me too!
Is that true?
The information about Zero.
Yes, it is information from Sir Curel.
All right.
Put a cordon on the 4th Zone of the Shinjuku Ghetto.
Understood, Sir.
Sir Curel... we will leave the rest up to you.
I wanted you to contact Sir Jeremiah, but it seems you probably won't, isn't that right?
Get out of here, you Britannian pigs!
Stay here!
Wh-What? You're just an Eleven!
We're Japanese! Don't call us Elevens!
What are you saying?
You guys lost to us, you dogs of a defeated country!
Why you Britannian...
Please stop!
Don't resort to violence!
Don't get in the way!
This guy...
You... are you Kururugi Suzaku?
Kururugi, the guy who killed Clovis?
You idiot!
The one who did it was Zero!
This guy is just a slave.
So what if he's an honored Britannian?
Acting so happy...
Selling your pride, comrades and soul...
Are you even Japanese?!
That's not it! I...
That IS it!
You dog of Britannia!
Please stop!
I'm an individual who has received training.
Don't fight with your comrades anymore...
What do you mean by comrade?!
Hey! Let it go.
That traitor...
Suzaku!
Are you all right?
Yes.
It's not okay!
My Prime G and MX 4 are...
You were too late!
Jeez, for being honored...
Why did you let them go?!
You should have finished them off!
You've killed many Elevens before anyway, haven't you?
Who do you think is feeding you?
I will not allow you to insult this man any further!
In order to use the Geass, one must look directly into the opponents' eyes.
There is no problem penetrating through glasses.
Maximum distance is about 270 meters.
After having the Geass cast on them, or when it's in effect, there is a noticeable gap in memory.
This is thought to be damage caused by the Geass invading the cerebrum.
If it has the property of light, then reflection is also possible.
You sure have studied it a lot in such a short amount of time.
The opponent is an empire which has subdued over a third of the world.
There is no such thing as exercising too much discretion.
Understandable for Elevens, but you're Britannian, aren't you?
Britannia is much too large and powerful of an opponent to fight with just one Geass.
So everything would be okay if I were strong?
I wonder if it's bad to be weak.
At that time... for us 10 year olds, the world appeared to be a very sad place.
Fear.
Sickness.
Corruption.
Decay.
Discrimination.
War and terrorism.
The repeated chain of hatred.
A foolish vicious cycle.
Someone must break this chain asunder.
Quite an idealist.
Of course, I don't think that it is possible to get rid of all of that.
I'm not that arrogant.
That's why...
I would at least like a world without war. A place where we won't lose dear ones.
Such a convenient world...
What can you do to...
It's easy.
If someone wins, the fighting will end.
Someone?
I don't know yet.
But if I stop aiming for something, my father will have died in vain.
Captain Kururugi's...?
In that war, my father HAD to die!
Jeremiah!
Today, we will make you pay for the sin of allowing the murderer of Prince Clovis to escape!
Cowardly Curel!
So the information that you found Zero was a lie!
Before Princess Cornelia arrives, we must cleanse the shame of our fellow men!
Jeremiah, this is a purge!
Suzaku-kun!
Cecil-san!
It's dangerous here!
Get on!
The Purists are having an internal conflict.
Let's hurry up and get out of here.
Oh, and sorry about interrupting your little get together. You'll have to do it another time.
Please wait!
Wouldn't this be a good chance to get battle data on the Lancelot?
Eh?
Suzaku...
Sorry, Yuffie... we must bid farewell to each other here.
I have to go.
If I have Lancelot, I should be able to stop them.
So!
Dammit... four on one...
Cowards!
Don't worry, Jeremiah. We'll treat you like a warrior.
There will be no shame to your family name!
Are you serious?
Are you seriously going to kill me, Curel?!
Be silent, "orange"!
Why do you think we exist?!
It's for the Imperial House, is it not?!
All hail Britannia!!!
Please stop!
Don't fight amongst yourselves as Britannians!
That's... the honored Britannian...
The Collaborative Weapon, Lancelot!
What does a special envoy want?
If you are going to interfere, we'll kill you regardless of who you are!
No!
I can't allow a meaningless fight to go on!
MVS stands for Maser Vibration Swords.
MVS?!
So they were already implemented...
But, I'm not backing down!
Among your own allies...
He's going to save me?
Kururugi Suzaku is...?
Even if I can just take out "orange"...
Sir Jeremiah!
Is that Viletta? Thanks!
Do you still plan on fighting?
Everyone back off.
Curel...
So we've come to an understanding?
I'll use the Chaos Bomb.
Eh?
Stop!
What?
That honored Britannian...
Using his own body as a shield...
Both sides, lower your weapons!
I will command you in my name!
I-It cannot be...
I am the 3rd Imperial Princess of Britannia, Euphemia le Britannia!
Eh...
Yuffie...?
I will take control of this area.
Stand down!
As I thought... the Imperial Princess...
Did you know that, Lloyd-san?
Yeah.
She rarely appeared to the public because she was a student.
I-I am truly...
I am truly sorry!
Imperial Princess!
Eh?
On top of me not even being aware, I have been acting extremely rude to you.
Suzaku...
Just as you lost your father, I have lost my older brother, Clovis.
Will you lend me your strength so that others can get by without losing their loved ones?
Yes! Your kind words are more than I am worthy of!
I heard about it, Euphemia.
Don't do such reckless things.
I'm sorry, sister.
However...
While we are here, call me Governor-General, Vice-Governor Euphemia.
A distinction is needed precisely because we are true siblings.
Yes, I understand.
Also, concerning the measures being taken...
Yes, the preparations for the welcoming of the Imperial Princess are being readied in the government office...
You are lacking.
You are weak.
You are being sluggish.
What of Zero?
Capture the enemy of the empire's people!
Zero!
Eh?
From today on, I will be a student at Ashford Academy.
I'm Kururugi Suzaku.
Pleased to meet you.
Yeah, I know.
I'm lying.
To Shirley and Rival...
Even to Suzaku and Nanali.
But... I can't go back... I can't return.
If C.C. is my accomplice, then I have to use that.
Because I don't want to lie to myself any longer.