Hey, Rin!
Rin! Come on!
Yukio still hasn't come back.
That damn Four-Eyes.
He hasn't come home and doesn't even bother to call...
Damn, I'm late!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
The school is temporarily closed today.
What?
Ah, Okumura!
Morning, dude!
Morning!
What's going on here?
There was that hostage incident two days ago, right?
They've called in the principal to take responsibility for it.
That's why the Academy is closed for now.
We can't even enter the school buildings.
There's more.
Good morning, Izumo!
The leaders of the Vatican have been replaced and a new pope was elected.
Why now?
Does it have anything to do with the dismissal of the principal?
Anyway, things here are gonna change a lot.
Not just with the Exorcist cram school but the whole Order as well.
The Exorcist cram school and the Japanese Branch as a whole
Episode 22
sziDemon Hunt
have been placed under direct control of the Vatican.
Please welcome the new Head of the Branch.
I am the newly assigned Head of the Japanese Branch, Yukio Okumura.
Why is Professor Okumura...
He's still a student...
He's the same Middle First Class as I.
In addition to accepting the position of the Branch leader,
Yukio         Okumura
Paladin
I have also received the title of Paladin as of today.
I request your cooperation.
What? Yukio is the new Paladin?
And also Head of the Japanese Branch.
I wonder what this new pope is thinking.
Dammit, he got ahead of me!
I wanted to be the first to become Paladin!
Is that your problem?
Have you ever gotten even close to my level?
Yukio!
Are you really the new Paladin?
I have the title of the strongest Exorcist, just like Father had.
You're my little brother and I know that you work your ass off when no one's looking,
but why didn't you tell me something this important?!
It was an urgent summon.
Then at least send me an e-mail!
Sorry. I will do that next time.
Then it's okay.
The only reason I've been appointed Paladin
is so I could carry out the plan of the Vatican.
What plan?
My people! Our whole history we have lived in fear of the demons.
But that shall end today!
Just as the light of civilization drove away the darkness,
we shall drive away all the demons from this world
and return Assiah to the hands of humankind once again!
I, Pope Ernst, hereby order all Exorcists around the world.
Begin Operation Jacob's Ladder!
"Jacob's Ladder"?
I am responsible for carrying out that plan.
You'll help us too, won't you Rin?
Sure!
I'm off to a meeting now.
Sure, do your best!
Umm, what's this?
Demon slayer weapons developed by the Vatican.
It takes the power of the defeated demon and boosts your Exorcism.
When I hold this in my hand I feel like fighting too.
Shima, it's not a toy...
We're supposed to be Tamers...
Then use that grimoire.
We'll rather stick with these.
Although you're permitted to carry arms, you still lack experience.
Be careful not to get in the way of other Exorcists.
Yes.
"O Sylphs born of the dark mist. gather in the lands of honey and milk.
Spread your crystalline wings and dance in the sky!"
Shima!
Dammit!
Now, shoot!
You did well! We won!
This... is so one-sided.
Hey, Rin! Is this what Exorcists do?
To me it feels we're...
Report.
We have already completed cleansing 443 556 regions,
but we're facing resistance in a number of other regions...
Tell every single Exorcist that this is a Crusade.
Without sacrifices our dreams will never come true.
What is it? Is there something you'd like to say?
No.
Will you turn Rin back to human?
Is that even possible?
The Kurikara has sealed Rin's blue flames into Gehenna.
The human world of Assiah and the demon world of Gehenna
are like the two sides of a mirror.
If we destroy Gehenna as a whole, all demonic power will be gone,
and Rin will return to an ordinary human.
That's impossible...
It's impossible to destroy Gehenna.
No, it is possible.
We have spent 15 years to develop the ultimate weapon, the Messiah.
The Messiah can be launched anytime on my command,
but the Gehenna Gate needs to be opened first.
The Gehenna Gate?
It literally is a gate in space-time between Assiah and Gehenna.
It is believed that only Satan can open it, but we managed to create an artificial one.
To maintain the Gate for a longer time, we need immense amounts of demon blood.
Can Rin really become human again if we destroy Gehenna?
Not only Rin, but you as well.
Did you think I'm not aware of your secret, my grandson?
Hey guys, what are you eating?
Good work today!
These are our rations.
We got yours too while there were some left.
Ah, thanks.
Rin, me too!
Don't worry, you'll get some too.
How can you even think about eating?
Huh?
Shiemi...
A boar!
Retreat! Retreat!
Yukio...
You will pay for this, humans.
You hurt my kin... We have protected this forest for over 2000 years!
He's the Lord of this forest?
Hey, wait! He's...
What are you doing, Yukio?!
What do you mean? I'm hunting demons.
He was the Lord of this forest! He was just angry because we killed his kin!
I am ordered to eliminate every demon from this world.
Every?
What about Blackie and Ukobach and Izumo's Gods of Harvest?
Are you saying you're gonna kill them too?!
Exactly. Just as you say.
We must get rid of every single demon.
Stop!
Are you serious?
Let go, Rin.
Do you really want to kill every demon there is?
Exorcists are not butchers!
I said let go!
Rin!
What did you do to him?
Blackie!
Okumura speaking.
Yes. Understood.
Bourguignon. Take Rin Okumura to the Vatican Headquarters immediately.
Understood.
Since when?
You said the checkups all returned negative!
Was that all a lie?
It's none of your business.
Yukio!
If this plan succeeds we all will be saved.
Stay out of my way!
I have the authority to lock you up too!
We'll be saved?
What are you talking about?
Hey!
Damn Scaredy Four-Eyes.
Bloodsucker weapons? What's that?
's a type o' demon swords that be suckin' human blood.
I check'd the photo ye sent me 'n' it seems t' have been possess'd by a certain count in Transylvania.
Why are they making us use this kinda stuff?
What makes ye think I'd know?
Anyway, jus' try t' use 'em as lil' as possible.
Thanks. Sorry I called so early.
This shit just doesn't feel right.
Bon, where are you going?
To the young professor's place.
He's in charge of this so if I ask he should tell me something.
As if he'd tell you anything.
You'd better look for a more talkative professor.
Talkative?
Like Professor Tsubaki?
That's it!
Are you awake?
Mephisto?
Where are we?
This is the lowest level of the Vatican Headquarters,
and this prison is often called the Cocytus.
A prison?
It surprises me greatly to meet you here.
Pray tell me the details of how you ended up here?
Professor Okumura as Paladin?
And he engaged in a demon hunt...
This is most fascinating.
So why are you locked up?
Eins, zwei, drei!
The Adventures of
Mephisto
It happened 500 years ago.
Picture cards?
I, Johann Faust, was immersed in the most advanced branch of science of the time, artificial life research.
I totally can't see the resemblance...
Keep your comments to yourself.
When the Vatican forbid every aspect of creating life,
I left my laboratory to my students,
but apparently they continued my line of research.
And that's...
Indeed.
The laboratory is located in Poland.
Neuhaus is the student of my student's student, and so on and so forth.
Wait a sec. Professor Neuhaus said that someone revived his wife.
Most likely that someone set a trap for him.
Someone? Who?
Someone who dislikes me, of course.
Thank you for the important information.
It is about time I take my leave.
Wait a second!
Take me with you!
I refuse. Can you not hear the bells signaling the start of the play?
I have no intention to miss a moment of this wonderful show.
Then, if I may beg your pardon.
Hey, wait! You damn clown! I said wait!
Your Eminence, Mephisto has...
Sir Auguste.
You and Bourguignon are to bolster the defence.
No one may interrupt the ceremony we will be performing.
As you command.
I see. Now that I meet you in person I see the resemblance to Yuri is even greater.
Who are you?
I am Ernst Frederik Egin. Nice to meet you, my grandson.
Okumura got sentenced to death?
Why would they do that?
He was supposed to be kept safe until the Exorcist Authorization Exam...
Ah well, the Headquarters are in chaos as well.
We are waiting for Branch Head Okumura's commands as well.
And where is Rin now?
I don't know that, but I heard the execution will be carried out at the top of the True Cross Academy.
At the top?
None shall pass here alive.
What the hell are you planning?
This is the wood of the cross on which hung the Saviour of the world... Come let us worship.
Ye people: what have I made you
or in what have I offended you? Answer me.
O Sacred God,
O Strong saint,
O Immortal saint, have mercy on us.
This is the wood of the cross on which hung the Saviour of the world...
O blood of pitiful demon! Show us the Gates of Hell!
Professor!
Return to your stations right away.
The plan is being carried out right now.
Why are they executing Okumura? He hasn't done anything!
For the kin of Satan just being alive is a sin!
What?
Is that what the Order of the True Cross calls justice?
The orders of the Vatican are absolute.
If you intend to oppose me, I shall strike you down.
Professor Shura!
Too bad you side with the demons.
That's not it. I just can't stand the shine of your bald head.
Leave this to me. Hurry.
Don't disappoint me!
Shut up you baldy!
What's the meaning of this?
What are you doing to Rin?
Can't you see it?
I'm sacrificing him to open the Gehenna Gate.
You lied!
You promised that you'd turn him human again, so...
Rin is a human sacrifice.
He will be remembered forever as the hero who destroyed Gehenna!
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
This...
What the hell happened here?
Look, the Gehenna Gate opened the way for Armageddon!!
Satan! The King of Demons shall burn Hell itself with those flames!
These brothers are like the two sides of a mirror.
Next Episode Preview
Had he not drawn the Demon-Slaying Blade that day,
their fate would have been different.
Even I am excited to see what is coming!
Truth