We hereby declare the restoration of Japan as a legitimate, independently controlled country!
The leader of the group that occupied Fukuoka Base, Sawasaki Atushi,
was the Chief Cabinet Secretary of the former Japan during the second term of the Kururugi Administration.
He sought asylum in the Chinese Federation after the war.
However, we think that he's making use of the internal unrest caused by Zero to carry out this operation.
We are now in the midst of investigating whether the Order of the Black Knights has anything to do with this operation.
The incident at Kaminejima was...
They're not related!
What did Kyoto say?
Uh... It seems that they didn't know anything.
Everything, including the acquisition of Sakuradite, was done arbitrarily.
Zero, what should we do?
Sawasaki's group is cooperating with the terrorist cells within the Kyushu Block.
Honshu is the largest of the four main islands that make up Japan, while Shikoku is the smallest.
After destroying the land traffic network that linked the Honshu block and Shikoku block,
Note: Liaodong is a peninsula in northeastern China. In reality, it was one of the areas that China ceded to Japan after the first Sino-Japanese war.
together with support from the Chinese Federation's Liaodong military district,
Note: Fukuoka, Nagasaki, and Oita are all provinces on Kyushu.
they are using Fukuoka, Nagasaki and Oita as a center of operation to increase the area they have captured.
According to General Tsao from the Chinese Federation, they are only providing humanitarian aid
and are not going against the Manila Convention...
How is Suzaku-kun doing?
He said he'll definitely obey if we engage in battle.
I see.
Erm... Where is His Highness Schneiser?
At the Tokyo settlement.
The next thing that follows after the problem with Suzaku is this, right?
Although the master is not around, we have to clear this obstacle or we won't be able to counter the Gefjun Disturber...
I... am not qualified to be your knight.
If it's about that insubordination incident,
Brother Schneiser said that there's no need to take responsibility for it since it took place during an irregular moment.
I can't forgive myself. That's why...
Was it a burden? Making you my knight...
No, I'm thankful for that.
If that's so...
I recalled it.
Eh?
I... killed my father.
But... I wasn't punished at all. I was living freely.
Once again, I'm being protected like this.
I, alone... without caring about the martyrs to duty and the Elevens...
I'm not qualified as I am now.
"Qualified"...
I am also...
Your Highness Cornelia, we are taking too much damage.
With this weather, we are unable to make use of the sky.
As for land-based combat, it's better if we wait for the weather to stabilize.
It's sure fortunate to have such an intense storm blowing.
Let's make use of this chance to seize Kyushu.
General Tsao, Heaven is acting as our ally.
We will win this war.
There's no need to declare martial law.
That would just increase the uneasiness among the people.
Send a letter to the EU's Foreign Minister Gandolfi.
Ah, also contact the Toromo Institution in Cambodia.
Your Highness Schneiser, using Toromo is...
Prime Minister, Sir!
Ah, Euphie.
What is it?
Is there anything I can help out with?
I hope to do something as the Vice Governor-General of Area 11...
Thank you. That feeling alone is enough.
But...
"Don't let the Vice Governor-General do anything." That was the order from the Governor-General.
From Sister?
Although I willfully selected my knight...
N-No, you are mistaken.
I too feel that Kururugi is...
Euphie, try to be understanding.
Due to the current situation, not even Cornelia has the time for such things, wouldn't you agree?
That...
Darlton, about what I said earlier, an acquaintance of mine knows a route. I'll try and ask him for help.
Understood.
We've already put so much effort into preparing this...
Looks like the school festival is going to be canceled.
That isn't the problem. It's war, right?
War?
Even though a government in exile is stuck in between,
this is war against the Chinese Federation.
Why...
Nina, what about the outdoor booths that we're supposed to borrow from the museum?
Ah, I'm going to do the paperwork today.
If possible, I want to go to the science department after that...
Is it... about that present?
Huh? What present?
There's something I want.
Professor Lloyd said he'd give it to me if I asked...
Lloyd?!
That womanizer...!
Enough already. Continue your work.
Even though you say that, I'm doing the work of three people.
Suzaku is with the army. Kallen is in the hospital.
The remaining idiot has gone missing.
A-Ah... Lelouch, that fellow, seems to have changed...
It was shocking...
I am still in confusion.
Lulu is actually Zero.
I haven't told anyone about it because I want to meet Lulu and confirm it for myself...
Did I... write that?
Why did I forget about them?
About Nana-chan's brother... and about Zero...?
Z-01, Float Attachment contacted.
Confirming the linkage. The avionics are...
You're really amazing.
You got top class in the float simulation as well.
Thank you very much.
Hey, why did you quit being a knight?
That's because...
Even as I am now... Her Highness, Princess Euphemia will still accept me.
If further problems were to arise, I feel that... she would start to hate herself.
A decorative Vice Governor-General...
I knew that from the start...
But I still want to put effort into whatever I can do.
I'm sorry, Brother Clovis.
I was unable to avenge you even though I met Zero.
However, I still can't think of a way to save Lelouch and Nunnally.
I'm not as powerful as Sister or Brother Schneiser.
I'm just a burden no matter where I go.
Before I even realize it, I find myself acting willfully.
Although I went against Sister's decision and selected a knight...
I was rejected by him.
Ah, I heard about it.
You just need to do the paperwork today, right?
A royal is inside viewing at the moment.
Eh? Who is it?
Eh... In other words...?
We won't join up with Sawasaki.
That isn't independence. It's just a puppet government.
One controlled by the Chinese Federation.
But they are calling themselves "Japan".
It's just a change of name and master. There's no future in it.
Disregard that "Japan".
Hmm, then you mean...?
Are we going to disregard Britannia's action?
Zero, I think it's better if you clearly explain the objective of the organization...
That's right.
Even if we leave the Sawasaki's incident out of this, what is our immediate objective?
To form an independent country in Tokyo.
Independent?
Country?
Are you serious?!
Us? A country...?
I see... You are indeed...
Please wait.
No matter how much the Order of the Black Knights grows...
The enemy is a large country that reigns over a third of the world.
Doing that with just us is...!
Then I ask you:
Who are you waiting for to defeat Britannia?
Someone will take your place and do that for you?
A chance will come someday if you keep on waiting?
How naïve!
If you yourself don't act, that "someday" definitely won't come!
Princess Euphemia!
Confirmed the situation.
Case Delta has occurred. Case Delta has occurred.
I beg you, I just want to thank Princess Euphemia, that's all!
Taking her in! Seal the roads!
Seal up all the roads!
Just one look!
I repeat: Seal up all the roads leading to the building!
Ah!
From the hotel...!
I beg you... I beg you...
The interrogation room has been prepared. Bring her over.
Stop it!
She's my friend!
All right. The sky has cleared up.
We can now resume land-based combat.
His Highness Schneiser's proposal can be executed as well.
Do you think the Special Envoy can break through?
Possible if Kururugi is doing it.
He really is someone who's difficult to deal with.
But due to the absence of a commanding officer, they are depending entirely on technology.
Missiles incoming. They are launching from Fukuoka Base.
One minute five seconds before impact!
As expected from them. The aerial defense is well thought-out too.
Shall I clear up the volley of missiles?
We should be able to handle it from our position.
Impact confirmed! We have struck the enemy's floating battleship.
Hmph, even if it's a new model, a single ship is just...!
Hmm? This is...?
We have already confirmed it using the Lancelot.
Major Kururugi, I'm going through the mission instruction one last time with you.
Special Envoy is going to use this ship to penetrate the enemy's frontline from a high altitude.
We are now heading towards the point where you will take off.
Guided Weapon Z-01 Lancelot will use the Float Unit to launch an assault against the headquarters of the enemy, Fukuoka Base.
The energy consumption while floating is high, so please keep track of your operational time.
Yes, my Lord.
ME booster...
Lancelot, take off!
Taking off!
Seems that a bomber has taken off from the enemy battleship, but its speed is faster than that of a fighter plane.
Getting visuals.
A KnightMare...
It's not transported by air, but actually in flight...
Don't tell me it's the one in the reports...
That miraculous weapon?
That means inside it is...?
The presence of Sawasaki Atushi is the pretext those people are giving for taking over the Kyushu Block.
In other words, the new Japanese government will collapse if he dies.
The Chinese Federation will lose their reason to intervene as well, and will have no choice but to retreat.
That... is the enemy headquarters.
Open channel?
I am Sawasaki.
The one who is heading here, are you Kururugi's son?
I see. He actually has a child like this.
Back then... Back then when Princess Euphemia saved me...
I saw a goddess.
It was as if you were shining brightly.
Ah! Sorry!
I should have thanked you for lending me your clothes first.
Don't worry about that.
Also, I'm not that great of a person.
I'm completely useless compared to my elder sisters.
You are not useless!
Huh?
Princess Euphemia being useless...
I'm a good-for-nothing... Completely useless...
My parents are just commoners...  I'm not pretty at all...
That's not true. You are really cute.
A-Ah... That is...
I'm really useless... Completely.
You hate yourself, don't you?
But the same goes for me...
I know it clearly in my head... about Suzaku too...
Ah, I see! Suzaku too!
That's why I can't let Princess Euphemia say that she's useless!
Because...!
Because...
Because I need you.
To me...
Nina, thank you.
It was great meeting you.
Ah!
It seems I understand it now!
This has nothing to do with my father.
I came because I myself wanted to put an end to the fighting.
As long as you surrender...
Do you intend to take away the dream of Japan's independence?
In that case, realize that through the correct methods.
Do you intend to live on willfully like that?
Continuing with that idealistic view of justice?
No, that's...!
The VARIS is...!
That is a Ganruu from the Chinese Federation.
He was distracted by just a conversation. He's still a novice.
Euphie?
Brother Schneiser !
Please allow me to send a private transmission!
The Energy Filler is...!
Huh?! The Float System was destroyed as well?!
Let's use the Avalon to charge straight into the base!
Impossible, impossible!
It's not an all-round shield! We'd be shot down!
Suzaku-kun, for the moment, use the remaining energy only for combat and communication.
Okay.
Surrender, Suzaku-kun.
I promise you that I will treat you well as the orphaned child of Prime Minister Kururugi.
No thanks.
I couldn't forgive myself if I made use of my father's name here.
I see, aren't you similar to him.
That stubbornness of yours is pretty similar to your father's.
Kururugi Suzaku!
Princess Euphemia?
Suzaku, I... erm... you...
Erm... Right now, I'm...
Erm...
Love me!
Yes.
Eh?
Huh?
What? What's the problem this time?!
E-Erm... It's nothing. Just something private.
In return, I'll fall deeply in love with you!
Princess Euphemia...?
Suzaku... Your stubbornness... Your gentleness...
Your sad eyes... Your silliness...
You getting bitten by cats... I like it all!
So don't hate yourself!
I see... I've made you worried instead...
As a person, you are...!
Always so sudden.
When I first met you... When you said you were a princess...
Deciding that I should go to school... Choosing me as a knight...
You are always...
That's right, I'm always sudden!
Because... I suddenly realized...
But due to that suddenness, I felt as if the door to my heart has become unlocked.
Thank you.
What are you doing? Stop that guy!
Can I make one last request of you?
"Last"?
Please don't hate yourself no matter what happens to me.
Also, eliminate everything about me when it happens.
I don't want to cause my friends any trouble, so tell them that I've transferred schools.
Suzaku, don't tell me...
My... energy has been used up.
Ah, this is bad...
Please send my regards to Cecile-san, Lloyd-san, and His Highness Schneiser.
In the end, I still overestimated myself...
Suzaku, don't die!
Live on!
W-What's going on...?
Fire!
What was that just now?
There's a reaction on the radar. Something suddenly appeared!
Reinforcements?
Visuals captured.
That's...?
That white armor is the one called Lancelot?
Reckless way of fighting as usual.
Yes.
It seems that he has backup this time.
A single machine is used to cause confusion in the main base to bring about an irregularity.
Even if he fails, Cornelia can make her move.
Schneiser... Is he the one behind this strategy?
You are a nuisance.
Wasn't the Hadron Cannon supposed to be incomplete?
It was finished...?
I should have been the one to complete it!
We sort of managed to finish it by putting the theory behind the Gefjun Disturber to use.
But the development of the Float System was my loss.
Looks like my opponent is that pudding Earl.
This was unintentional cooperation.
Ah... This makes me sick.
Kururugi, is the Lancelot still able to move?
Zero, it is indeed you.
Zero?!
They are speaking on the open channel?
Yes.
Turn up the volume! We need to confirm his objective!
An Energy Filler?
I'm going to attack the enemy's headquarters now.
What do you intend to do?
What?!
How unfortunate, Zero.
Your wish won't be fulfilled.
I shall engage in this battle before you.
Launch all units! Stop them!
Stop Zero and Kururugi!
Zero, aren't your people comrades of those fighting for the sake of Japan?
We, the Order of the Black Knights, are the enemy of all those who use violence unreasonably.
"Unreasonably"?!
I'm doing it for Japan's sake!
Sawasaki-san, why did you escape to the Chinese Federation if you are doing it for Japan's sake?
You should have stayed for the sake of everyone...
You brat!
A cooperative operation? Gawain and...
Lancelot.
Suzaku and Lelouch are...
What? Zero is...?
Yes, he's with Kururugi.
What is that man thinking?
In order to escape detection by Britannia,
using the Gawain for a sole mission is the right choice.
But it would have been easier if the Guren had been used to provide cover...
I can't head back home or to school anyway.
Right now, even if we don't cooperate with the Lancelot...
What we need is not victory.
What is crucial is the fact that the Order of the Black Knights participated in this fight.
Of course, this won't be officially reported, but rumors will spread.
As Zero said, this is going to aid us in announcing our stance to the world.
What's wrong with asking help from foreign countries while waiting for a chance?
That is what it means to strategize.
Note: Kagoshima is located on the southwestern end of Kyushu.
There is still a defensive line left in Kagoshima.
Ah... Sorry for troubling you.
Sawasaki-san.
This is the end.
Impossible!
Taking down the largest fortress in Kyushu... so easily!
About the terrorist incident that broke out in the Kyushu block due to an anti-government organization,
under the lightning-quick operation carried out by Governor-General Cornelia,
Sawasaki Atushi and four other old Japanese government members were detained.
More than half of the soldiers from the Chinese Federation Army that took part in this incident were detained.
Currently, the governing body of the Chinese Federation has announced that this incident
is a unilateral action taken by General Tsao from the Liaodong military district.
They hoped that we would follow the Spain Convention and exchange captives.
I, Kururugi Suzaku, have returned.
Welcome back, Suzaku.
Er...
Erm...!
Suzaku, I finally understand.
It's not about ideal countries, justice, or other such complicated things.
I just want to see smiles.
The smile of the person I love deeply now, and the smile of the person I loved deeply in the past.
Can you... help me?
Yes, Your Highness!
Although I've eliminated Sawasaki,
I need to hurry and get my next operation going.
I need to first create a place for Nunnally to live.
In order to do that, I need to create a country that can control the world.
The plans for destruction are proceeding well.
When the time comes...
Schneiser and Cornelia... both of them together!
NNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN
Announcement of the School Festival!