Sorry about what happened earlier.
We put so much effort into the welcome party, yet we couldn't make it more exciting.
You call that...
"Couldn't"...
To suddenly see the news about the culprit behind Prince Clovis's murder...
It was unbearable even for me, the great Milly-san.
I don't really mind about that but...
Why are we in the bathroom?
Actually, why did I have to come along?
I already had a shower just now...
Well, well. This is another round of getting to know each other better.
The close contact between na-ke-d fri-ends.
Also, if you wear Lelouch's clothes back just like that, someone will get really pissed off.
Isn't that so, Shirley?
P-President, what are you saying all of a sudden?!
But, wasn't Lulu acting strangely after he saw the news?
It seemed that his heart had wandered off.
Well, Nana-chan was around.
Ah, that was unexpected.
The way he treats me and the way he treats his sister are completely different.
Well, he's in love with his sister after all!
That's going to be tough.
Why are you looking at me?!
You have a wonderful body as usual.
Doesn't that athletic build gives off a seductive and alluring feeling?
P-Please stop looking at me.
It's fine right? Not as if you'll lose anything.
I'll lose something!
Besides, President, isn't your body the most curvaceous?
Oh? Is that so?
Geez, Milly-chan, everyone will catch a cold.
That's right...Y-You are Nina-san?
You look completly different without your glasses on.
Isn't that so?
All this time, I've been telling her to change to contacts.
This girl is really...!
N-No, Milly-chan.
"All this time"?
We grew up together.
My grandfather worked in Milly-chan's grandfather's company.
They were developing KnightMares.
Ashford...
Did they develop the Ganymede and Ion series?
Ah, you know about it. That's surprising.
They were machines that didn't proceed past the testing phrase.
Ah, erm... I read about them from somewhere... That's all I know.
Well, in the end they weren't put into actual production.
The development costs started to pile up and the company eventually closed down.
Milly-chan, I'm sorry...
It's all my grandfather's fault...
Well, I've already told you it's not due to that.
The main reason is because of Grandfather's extravagance.
Extravagance?
Yes. He loved to organize those old fashion parties.
They would go on nosily for days and nights without any good reason.
Well, it's thanks to the contacts he established back then that we were able to create
a presence in this country and even set up an academy here.
But President, you sure inherited the party-loving part from him.
Guess so.
We can only do such silly things while we're still students.
Oh yeah, Kallen-san, are you free after school the day after tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
I think... No, no!
I have something to do the day after tomorrow.
Going out?
1-1600hrs... s-sort of need to go to the Tokyo Tower...
Well, we can do it now too.
Kallen-san, I want to know your three sizes.
Huh?!
We often need to make costumes for parties or events. I need it for that.
In order words... a cosplay show?
Bingo!
No thanks.
No need to be shy. We are all women.
So... Shirley!
I'm sorry, Kallen...
Hold her back!
This is... My, my.
P-Please... stop!
Kallen, you are pretty strong...
Quite a nice body.
Even though you say that you're weak...
P-Please... stop...
That is charming in its own way!
Then...
Pardon me!
NO!!!