When we lived at the monastery,
it was easy to tell whether Rin was home or not.
So if he happened to be late for dinner, we ate in silence...
I'm back!
You're late, Rin!
Welcome back, Rin!
I bet you got into a fight again...
Shut up! It's okay for me to have something to do too!
You're not chasing girls for sure.
As if you'd know!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Episode 20
szMask
What the hell is this?
Kyodo... Nagatomo...
Maruta... Izumi...
Please stand back. They're still breathing.
We'll explain later.
What exactly happened here?
That's....
It appears to be Polish. It says, "Satan's kin must die."
Satan's kin?
Does that mean me?
Who would do this?
When we arrived, one of the victims was still able to squeeze out a few words.
He said "the masked man."
The masked man?
This web is of magical origin.
It covered their bodies completely and hardened into stone.
Will they be fine?
There is a thin protective layer around their bodies.
They must have chanted protective charms when they were attacked.
But its efficiency is decreasing little by little.
They have about eight hours left.
Tomorrow at 2 AM.
We are looking for a compound that could dissolve it,
but we've never seen anything similar, so we don't really know where to start.
Rin!
Don't stop me, Yukio!
You're the one they want!
So they should come after me!
And that's what they want!
I swore to Father that I'd protect you!
Why can't you listen to me?!
Oh shut up!
I can look after myself, I don't need your protection!
We don't have time for all this bullshit!
Rin!
Where are you? Where have you gone?
Who the hell are you?!
You were after me from the beginning, right?!
You should know how it feels...
To lose the ones close to you.
Screw you!
What?
I won't just kill you.
You will enjoy the suffering I was put through.
Rin!
The brother of Satan's son?
Yukio!
Wait!
Shura!
Gimme a break.
I gotta go after you when you pull stunts like this!
Hey!
Freeze!
Professor Neuhaus?
Demons... and those related to demons must die.
Especially the spawn of Satan!
Professor... are you still...
You attacked the monastery, right?
What are you talking about?
Don't play stupid with me. That thread on your shoulder.
That magical thread. The monastery was full of it!
Yukio Okumura, zero points.
Your logic isn't even worth analyzing.
This is just a common spiderweb that can be found anywhere. Even here.
Spare me your excuses.
The message written on the wall was in your mother tongue.
Also, there are only a few who know that my brother and I have demon blood.
No matter how you look, as long as your judgment is clouded you won't find the truth.
You will come with me to the Academy. Let's hear your truth there.
And what if I refuse?
He got away?
Damn, I can't draw it!
What the hell's going on?
Neuhaus?
Yeah. And he holds a grudge against Rin.
I don't think he was there by chance.
I heard he quit and returned to his homeland.
But who knows how much of what Mephisto says is true...
Wait, on the other side of that portal opened earlier with a key...
You said there was a laboratory for the research of artificial life, right?
Connected corpses of humans and animals are often used in
artificial life research, or as Naberius.
There's a connection to professor Neuhaus.
But artificial life research is strictly prohibited by the Vatican.
Where do you think you're going?
I've gotta stop him.
You can't use the Demon-Slaying Blade. How do you intend to fight?
I will go after him. I will ask the other teachers for support too.
I don't want anyone to get hurt because of me anymore!
You're not going anywhere today, that's for sure.
If you think you can always have it your way, you're wrong.
What are you doing, Yukio? Stop screwing around!
I'm serious, Rin.
Or will you knock me down again? With that demonic power of yours?
Yukio... the hell...
Hey, Yukio, what's with all the fuss?
Yukio!
It's an instant tranquilizer.
You're overdoing it...
I have the duty to protect Rin.
I'll leave the rest to your.
Yukio!
Yu... Yukio...
Professor Neuhaus is here?
The tracer's signal is coming from below.
Let's split up.
Use the charms I gave you earlier as your last resort.
If you're attacked with that web, secure your breathing using chants.
Can you hear it?
Don't move!
You're so persistent.
Professor! Raise your hands, now!
Wait!
Professor! Professor Hinokawa!
Yukio, you bastard...
Nyaha~ I see you're still groggy!
You still have some tranqs in your blood. Stay still.
Damn Yukio... What the hell is wrong with him?
I guess it's called "worry".
I've gotta...
Give up! You ain't worth shit if you go there
without knowing how to use a single flame the way you want to.
What?!
Don't you get that you having trouble with your flames means trouble for everyone?
If you learned to control them properly, no one would be
afraid, worried or suffering because of you.
I know that! But...
If you get it, use these.
This isn't the time for training!
This ain't training, this is the real thing.
Huh?
These candles are the people important to you.
If you can't control your flames, they will all die.
You only have one chance.
It doesn't matter if it's training or not.
As long as you can't prove that you can control your flames,
no one's gonna trust you.
Control your flames with your will!
With my will?
So he wasn't alone?
I was careless.
Yes, it's me.
What?!
Understood. I'll head there right away.
Professor?
They've tracked him down.
Where?
In the boys' dormitory of the True Cross Academy.
Koneko!
What are you? Demon or human?
Bon!
Who's the intruder?
According to student witnesses, it's a masked man.
Most of the students managed to escape,
but a few are still in the cafeteria.
Including the students of the Exorcist cram school.
The cram school students?
What are their demands?
He said no one is to enter if we want the hostages alive.
Except...
What?
No one except the son of Satan.
It is a brave act to assault my Academy.
Principal!
Let us make him regret it.
Is... Is the Principal serious?!
Eins, zwei...
Huh, what?
Don't play with fire in the middle of the night.
Oh, it's you? Would you care to explain the meaning of this?
The Vatican has placed a warrant for you.
There is a suspicion that you might be engaged in forbidden artificial life research.
What are you talking about, I wonder?
If you have something to say, you can say it in the Vatican's prison.
Take him.
I will not run away or hide.
However, it makes me wonder your timing for this.
I expect a quick resolution. Stay out of our way.
What on earth is going on? Artificial life?
Wait, professor Okumura!
I'm going to at least find out if there's more than one intruder in there.
I can't fail again.
Wait until support arrives!
And call your brother too!
No!
Don't let anyone call my brother!
Professor Okumura!
There's no one in the other classrooms.
Why? Why are you binding only us?
He's alone.
I'll kill everyone connected to the son of Satan.
What?
That's my cell...
Shima? What's up?
Okumura...
Can you hear me, son of Satan?
You're that masked freak! What have you done to my friends?!
I'm not killing them. At least not until you arrive.
What?!
He wants to call Rin here? Why would he...
Do you want another taste of the pain of losing someone? Or...
Damn you!
It hit!
The tranquilizer won't work?
His brother?
Professor!
I told you that I would kill them if anyone but the son of Satan entered.
What?!
Bon!
This is your punishment for not listening.
Stop! Or take me instead!
I need hostages.
It's more interesting with the brother here too.
Die.
Stop!
You've come, son of Satan?
You can't do anything without your sword!
You're lookin' at the wrong guy.
Resistance is futile.
Do you think you've won?
What?
Rin! Run!
If you can't use your sword...
Shut up!
The flames burn the web?
Great! Do it, Rin!
No! You mustn't use your flames again, Rin!
I have to learn this... and it's now or never!
Blue flames...
He's losing control... Rin!
Help... me.
They are my flames.
And I've gotta control them!
I was supposed to protect you.
You're way too early for that.
I was supposed to be able to protect you...
A woman?
Stop!
Neuhaus!
Snakefang!
Let me go! Don't get in the way!
You're the one in the way!
You were trying to use that demon to attack Rin!
She's... She's my wife!
What?
Start explaining what the hell's going on!
Hot-hot-hot!
What are you fussing about?
It's hot! You did that on purpose!
They have minor injuries, but none requiring hospitalization.
Please rest for a while.
Man, you saved us.
Thanks.
I wanted Father Fujimoto to see how much you've grown...
By the way, where's Yukio?
Huh? What?
Mr. Yukio Okumura?
And you are?
There is someone who would like to meet you.
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
Come in.
Who are you?
I am Ernest Frederick Aegin.
I'm glad to see you, Grandson.
She's my wife.
Next Episode Preview
Just to protect you...
No! I haven't asked for that!
Is this the best you can do, son of Satan?
Get out of my way!
Secret Garden