I'm sorry.
I always thought he'd committed suicide.
He wasn't such a coward.
He was a guy who'd just grit his teeth and do the best he could when faced with adversity.
You'd never hear him complaining.
Yeah.
Even when everyone was asleep, he'd be up drawing something.
Moritaka, have you read "Star of the Giants"?
Huh? Yeah.
Then you know that one line of Ryoma Sakamoto's?
Yeah.
You always did love "Ashita no Joe".
Dad, I think I get it.
Thank you.
Sure.
Azuki?!
It's her mom! This has to be Azuki's mom!
I'll cheer you on from the sidelines while you work on becoming excellent manga artists.
Yes! Thank you very much!
Yes, ma'am!
I'm pretty lucky.
It isn't just you, it's us!
I'll definitely make this dream a reality!
If I can't do this...
I won't be a real man!
I'm not a man yet!
Starting tomorrow...
No— Today, I'm gonna work on my own manga drawing style.
Alright! I'm gonna work hard on names!
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can't be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Every worry floats up to and fills the spring sky
Shinpaigoto Bakari ga Tsumoru Haru no Sora o
I look up, look down,
Miagete Utsumuite
and find myself looking back up at the sky
Mata Kao o Ageteru
I swore I'd find myself in this town
Kono Machi de Mitsukerutte Kimeta Jibun
I tuck away all my important things into my heart for safekeeping
Nakushichaikenai Mono o Mune ni
Can you see the blue birds,
Aozora Tobikau Blue Bird
fluttering through the blue sky?
Ano Tori ga Miemasu ka?
Happiness can't be described by a visible color, but I can feel
Shiawase wa Itsumo Mienai Color Kanjiteiru
Time and Keys
Most pros use the G-pen.
The control G-pens give over the intensity of the line really increases quality.
I never got used to it, so I use a Kabura pen.
This type of pen just makes the cut for the purposes of gag manga,
But real pros should use G-pens.
I try to use one sometimes, but it's really difficult.
Mashiro.
Mashiro, wake up!
Huh?
Oh crap!
It's great that you're studying hard, but your effort's wasted if you fall asleep in the middle of the test.
I-I'm sorry.
Finally done for the day.
You alright?
I've never seen someone pass out in the middle of a test before.
Saiko!
Did you really pass out from studying too hard?
Not really.
Whatever, it's over and done with. Wanna hit the movies?
Yeah! Let's see something x-rated!
X-rated?
Sorry, I've got stuff to do.
What's up with them?
Those two have been inseparable lately.
Were you up all night practicing drawing?
Yeah, I was at the studio past midnight.
Then I went home and practiced till it was time for school.
If I didn't lose my drawing streak on the way to school, I might've taken the test with this pen.
Wow... you even brought it with you and everything.
If I can't get used to using this, it's over.
There aren't any boundaries in manga.
Boundaries?
Unlike tests, there isn't one way to do manga.
Stories and pictures don't have right or wrong answers.
I'm gonna head over to the studio now, you wanna come along?
Yeah!
You seem pumped.
Here you go. Your own key to the studio.
Y-You sure?
It's better if you can get in whenever you need to, right?
W-Wow, thanks.
Since exams are finally over, we can really get down to it.
Wow!
You're seriously talented, Saiko.
You can produce this caliber of drawing in just one day!
Those are no good at all.
What's wrong with them?
The lines are too stiff; the thickness and stress points are a mess.
They couldn't pass as manga works.
Really?
It's really is hard to get used to the G-pen.
I just can't get the lines to form the way I picture them.
I even tried using the Kabura pen once instead.
A Kabura pen?
This one.
Oh. I thought fountain pens
referred to that one in general.
Supposedly my uncle didn't know about G-pens either. So he drew with a Kabura pen instead.
I see.
Then his editor told him to use a G-pen.
But he was used to the Kabura pen and couldn't get a hang of the G-pen.
So he ended up only using the Kabura pen.
You don't have much control over the thickness of lines,
But with a Kabura pen, it's much
easier to produce a consistent line.
With a G-pen, on the other hand, you have
much more control over the intensity of lines.
But its inflexibility makes it
prone to get stuck on the paper.
I see.
So the Kabura pen is no good, even
though your uncle used one as a pro?
Of course it's no good!
My pictures would have no dimension if I used it.
My uncle always insisted that his drawings were terrible.
He said they just barely made the cut because it was gag manga.
I guess he had a point...
It's completely different from making sketches in pencil, to fill in with paint afterward.
The only way is to practice till it hurts.
Here's some more of the stuff I worked on last night.
This is amazing!
Or I guess I shouldn't say that.
He's not satisfied with this at all.
You can draw better backgrounds with a Kabura pen.
And a Maru pen can be used for the extremely thin lines.
Did you use those for a model?
Yeah. I took out all of stuff that was packed in those boxes.
I didn't know they sold this sort of material...
You can make a great manuscript using this, right?
Not without adding impact.
Impact?
These.
Supposedly my uncle assigned these to his assistant using the numbers,
But we have to do it ourselves first.
You're gonna draw all of these by hand?
Using these tools, yeah.
It's not like we have an assistant,
So we even have to apply the screen tones ourselves too.
You cut these out with an art knife then apply them.
Basically, to make just one page of a manuscript, we'd need to...
First, we make a rough sketch on draft paper based on the name.
Then add in the characters and the background using a pen?
Right. Then we'd paint in the black, impact areas using a screen tone.
All that to finish just one page?
That's so much...
Yeah.
That workflow process depends on the person, but that's basically it.
I've finally realized just how much we have to master before we can produce something worth submitting.
It's easy to draw a person standing still,
But unless I can capture movement, expressions, and create composition,
I'll never become a pro.
That'll take an incredible amount of time.
Thinking back on it now, it's amazing my uncle began as a complete amateur and debuted in just three years.
He didn't know about whiteout.
So if he made even the slightest
mistake, he'd redraw the entire thing.
I-Is that right?
But we don't a choice!
If we want an anime by the time we're eighteen,
We don't have a second to waste!
Saiko, I understand where you're coming from.
But you should spend a little time studying the day before an exam.
I know.
I meant to study a little yesterday...
But it was morning before I knew it.
Before you knew it...
Anyway, we've got to start putting in effort now.
According to my uncle, that's one of the conditions for becoming a manga artist.
Conditions for becoming a manga artist?
In the Taro Kawaguchi school of thought.
The three great conditions for becoming a manga artist, if you're not a genius.
T-Teach me!
Number one.
Number One
Pride
Pride!
Think that you're way better than everyone else.
Alright, I've got that one down already.
And on top of that, it's not just pride. It's the truth.
That would be called pride.
Number two.
Number Two
Effort!
Effort
Oh, this time it's something
upstanding, Mr. Taro Kawaguchi.
And lastly.
Number Three
Luck
Yes, luck.
What?
You serious? Luck?
Of course.
We're gamblers, not geniuses after all.
Just sitting around talking about our
dreams won't make them come true.
I'm gonna spend the entire weekend drawing.
Alright!
Then I'm gonna read all of the manga in this studio!
This "Father's Soul" story really gets to you...
"My friends stood behind us in a row, as if to watch till we were out of sight."
Thank you, that's good.
Modern
Japanese
Right, then next... Suzuki!
Y-Yes sir!
Ah, wait, never mind.
W-Why?
No reason in particular.
That's mean!
Ah... Kawasaki, you read please.
You're going to the studio after this, right?
Yeah.
I'll get this week's Jack.
Thanks.
Who's on the cover for this week...?
Do I need anything else?
Saiko!
Come here, come here!
Look at this!
Oh, the winner of the Tezuka Award's been announced.
Winner Announced!!
Prize
1mil yen
Winner
Eiji Nizuma (15) Aomori
The winner is...!
What is it?
His age! Look at how old he is!
Eiji Nizuma (15) Aomori
He's only fifteen...
It says here he's still in high school.
Amazing scores from all the judges.
Eiji Nizuma, huh.
He kind of pisses me off.
Huh?
Look at the 'A Word from the Author' section.
"When everyone was off playing video games, I stayed in and worked hard.
I'll continue to work hard in order to
become a bestseller in Jack one day."
Feels like he's insulting me for being one of those gamers.
We can surpass guys like this easily, don't worry!
If you look closely, the only thing he's
getting praised for is his planning ability.
That's some confidence you've got there.
The rules are confidence, effort, and luck, aren't they?
That's pride, effort, and luck.
Confidence sounds better, don't you think?
Ohh, Kochikame...
Winner of the Tezuka prize at fifteen...
Moritaka!
Huh?
I know you're excited about getting the studio,
But hanging out there every day is a little too much.
You have exams coming up, you know!
I know.
Do you really?
If so, then focus on your—
Could I have seconds please?
Yes.
Thank you, Kayoko.
I'm going up to the roof.
Wait up! I'm coming too!
Wow, that's great! So moe.
It's like you're a pro already!
Yeah, I guess so. If I got serious, I'd take the whole manga industry by storm.
Hey, next I'll think up a story, so will you draw the pictures?
I guess I could. But my rates are pretty expensive.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why is everyone looking in the same direction?
And you didn't draw past their shoulders.
Those guys were laughing, weren't they?
That was Takagi from class 2, right?
Who was the other guy?
Who was he again...?
Who was that?
Kaya Miyoshi, Azuki's best friend.
You know her?
Wait, I was asking about the guy who was drawing.
Ishizawa. Same grade as us.
Does he wanna be a manga artist?
I wonder. It could just be a cry for attention.
But if even Miyoshi could tell, his inability is sure to be exposed.
Don't start slacking off just because midterms are over!
Because you still have your high school entrance exams.
Use these exams to think seriously about your futures.
Yes sir.
Right, time for class to start then.
Johoku Prep School
Alright, I've got the story just about planned out.
Once we get to the studio, I'll start firing off these names like crazy!
Summer Course   Now Open
This summer is your chance!
Build up your foundation and put
yourself in the lead!   Johoku Prep School
Saiko?
Hey.
There are probably a decent number of people
trying to become manga artists like us, right?
Probably, yeah.
Nizuma's only fifteen, remember?
There's Ishizawa too. But I don't know how serious he is.
I've decided: I'm fine just going to North Yakusa High.
North Yakusa?
It might be a safety school for someone like you.
But for me, it's the lowest level that my parents still find acceptable.
I want as much time as I can get to draw manga.
You're planning everything around becoming a manga artist, huh.
I've never realized time was such a precious resource.
I've never been this serious about anything before either!
You sure it's okay if you don't go to the same high school as Azuki?
I don't know where she's gonna go.
She might end up at an all girl's school.
You could just ask her.
No. It's fine if we go to different schools.
It's more...
romantic that way.
I knew it!
The DNA of an idealist...
Graduation
Ceremony
The next time we meet after middle school,
I'll be a manga artist,
And she'll be a voice actress.
Good luck!
Miho Azuki
Until then, you'll just support each other through texts!
Right?
Yeah.
Do you really want to copy your uncle that much?
It's what I wanna do.
I think Azuki would like it this way too.
Saiko.
You haven't even considered the possibility that Azuki will find another guy at her school?
Nope.
I believe in Azuki.
You're really going to North Yakusa, even if it means being separated from Azuki.
Just to get more time to draw manga.
Yeah.
Then I guess I'll go there too.
What?!
You should go to a good college prep school!
If we're aiming to be manga artists together,
Then going to the same school is more convenient.
I don't want to waste time either.
And also... I'm really grateful for this.
I originally thought I'd go to a good college, in case becoming a manga artist didn't work out.
But I realized it's stupid to plan for failure.
Shujin...
North Yakusa for me as well.
Don't you dare fail, Saiko!
I won't! I'll concentrate on my
drawing now that I've decided!
I won't stand to be beaten by kids our age anymore!
Yeah.
I guess Eiji Nizuma is our first rival, huh.
I guess Eiji already discussed with his editor: graduating high school and getting serialized simultaneously.
He already has an editor?
I'm positive he does.
Once he gets that prize, it's like automatic.
If there's an editor who takes a liking to you,
you can get paired up even without that prize.
My uncle said so.
An editor...
Eiji's getting farther and farther away from us.
The quality and type of editor varies widely.
So getting one at random is not always a great thing either.
Since the manga artist can't choose the editor
himself, whether the editor is any good or not...
Depends on luck.
There are editors whose reputations are totally off.
There are editors who just come to pick up your work and do nothing else.
There really are all types. You never know.
That's terrible.
Now for a sort of heartwarming editor story:
I'm ready!
There was an editor who told a novice manga
artist who'd been published elsewhere before,
"I have good feelings about your work. Write more and bring them here!"
But after he read about ten of them...
He ran them through the shredder?!
How is this heartwarming at all?
The novice was used to being turned
down after they read the first couple pages.
So he was really happy someone
read his work all the way to the end.
In the pain and frustration of having his work
shredded, he joined a group of famous manga artists.
Sounds like a good story now.
And then, at his serialization meeting,
I'm sorry about doing that back then.
But I thought that you might grow, and
improve even more if I didn't praise you.
Th-Thank you.
That doesn't sound true.
Supposedly that editor became editor-in-chief after that.
Sounds like a manga story.
My uncle said most editors are like
that, really passionate about manga.
He said they're all people who just love manga.
Yeah.
Hm?
Wanna go see an editor?
If we called and said we had something to show them, we could probably meet one.
We probably could, but we
don't have anything to show yet!
Let's finish something over summer break!
Then bring it to Jack!
Jack's the best option since we
want an anime and serialization!
If it doesn't work out, we don't lose anything!
Let's find out what an editor would think of our work.
Let's see if our combined talents can get through to them!
Alright! Let's do it!
Let's finish a work over summer break and bring it to Jack!
Yeah!
Now that's out of the way, let's get to work!
Hey, look...
Azuki...
I knew she had a younger sister but I didn't know she was this cute.
Oh man, what do I do?
This isn't the time to freeze up!
It's your chance to ask for her email!
But her lioness of a mother is here too.
Yeah, she'd be dangerous one-on-one.
Shut it!
Let's just pretend we didn't
notice them and not say anything.
Okay?
It's kind of obvious we did notice...
Just go!
Looks like she's noticed us too.
She's clearly blushing too.
And hiding behind her mom!
No one asked for live commentary!
Miho, aren't those your classmates?
Your face is all red, sis!
Mina!
Both of you are so shy.
It's impressive that you can pretend not to
know each other when you're in the same class.
I said shut up!
The editor-in-chief praised your work as well.
Nizuma
Of course, I also have confidence in your skills.
I think it'd be a great idea for you to come to Tokyo...
Nizuma?
The boring everyday gets to me sometimes,
Betaa na Genjitsu ni Tsubusaretemo
but I always get back on my feet, standing strong
Uchinomesareta Jibun Hiroiatsumete
No matter how many times the end approaches me,
Nando Owari ga Otozuretemo
I'll push my own back forward, keeping me on my feet
Sonotabi ni Jibun de Jibun no Senaka Oshita
If I get lost in the meaning of continuing what I do,
Tsuzuiteku Imi ni Nayami
I'll rid myself of those worries and keep myself going forward
Sono Mayoi Sae Tachikitte Yuku
Always
Itsumo
The straight edge that draws the outline of my future
Mirai no Rinkakusen Kaku Massugu na Jougi wa
is made of all the courage I've mustered up until today
Ikutsumo no Kinou no Yuuki de Dekiteru
I'll climb over the tall wall that I never thought I'd face,
Omoiegaita no to Chigau Takai Kabe Koe
and continue my journey, going past the vanishing point
Shoushisuten no Mukou e Susunde
This winding road seems to never end,
Harukanaru Winding Road
but it is the road I personally chose
Hoka no Dare Demo Nai Watashi ga Jibun de Eranda
I set my tiny dreams on fire,
Kasuka na Yume o Zenbu Moyashita
and broke through the dark with its light
Sono Hikari de Yami o Saite
Now that I've broken down the wall,
Kudaita Kabe no Mukou ni
I can see my sky once more
Jibun no Sora ga Mieru
Miho, don't you think Takagi likes you?
Next
Episode
I mean, he asked me about your secret dream before, right?
That was just...
What, what?
Maybe I'll tell you someday.
Maybe?!
Summer
and Names
Next time, Summer and Names.
Summer is a busy time for those chasing their dreams!