Paku! Paku...
My friend...
I have to protect her!
I... I have to...
I...
I don't like you, Izumo.
We shall not follow you, woman!
A dream?
I'm so stupid...
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Episode 8
szia Now a Certain Man was Sick
Good morning.
Ah, mornin'.
Get it?
Don't tell anyone that I cried yesterday.
Me? Who would I tell?
Just promise me you won't tell anyone!
Oh shut up, I said I'm not telling anyone.
Here...
Thanks.
If you hadn't been there, who knows what would have happened to Paku and I...
I'm grateful for that.
Wow, you washed it!
Huh?
You're a nice person after all! I misjudged you.
Misjudged? I washed it because it was dirty.
Huh? Seriously? Was it that dirty?
Good morning.
Mr. Okumura.
In two or three days the fever will go down and you can get up again.
Get some rest for now.
Thank you very much, Mr. Okumura.
Get well.
Thanks, Okumura.
What was that demon yesterday?
We're investigating how it got in and where it went right now.
It was a higher level Naberius.
Didn't you say that the Academy is protected by barriers and charms?
That's right, I'm really impressed you remembered.
Are you making fun of me again?
That's true, but every now and then such beasts can sneak in.
We have to brace ourselves just in case.
He's so cute...
Isn't Okumura cool?
Huh? How so?
What's this all of a sudden?!
Mr. Okumura is fabulous too...
It's hard to believe that they're really twins.
Paku...
Izumo...
I... I'll quit the cram school.
Sorry.
What's wrong?
If only I had been nicer...
What are you saying?
It's just that this exorcism thing isn't my world.
We'll still be friends.
So don't look like that.
I love you the way you are.
This is the order of a certain person...
A certain person? Who could it be?
At first I thought it was Satan,
but I can't think of any reason why he'd try to get me killed now.
There will be those who'll come to hunt you down.
Damn it. If they're targeting me anyway, why not attack me head on?
Rin.
Don't just pop up like that!
You too, don't just sit up like that, stupid!
It's okay, I can do it alone.
But why are you doing laundry?
Because I want to be of some use, too...
With stuff only I could do.
Too?
You're all working hard to become Exorcists and help people, right?
I see. So you don't want to become an Exorcist?
I don't know...
But first let me just do my specialty, laundry.
Most of ze demonz 'ave a so called le "fatal verse", words or quotes zat will make zem le die instantly.
Aria specializez in le memorization and le recital of zose fatal verses.
Zen let's 'ear you recitez what I gave youze for 'omework.
Kamiki!
Kamiki! What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. Umm...?
Ze "Te Deum". Continuez from where we were le last time.
Yes!
"Every day we thank thee. And we praise... "
We praise...
...praise...
Yez?
I... forgot.
Oh, now zat is unusual for you, Mademoiselle Kamiki.
Zen Suguro, 'elp 'er out.
Yes.
Every day we thank Thee.
And we praise Thy Name forever, yea, forever and ever.
O Lord, deign to keep us from sin this day.
Have mercy on us, O Lord, have mercy on us.
Let Thy mercy, O Lord, be upon us, for we have hoped in Thee.
O Lord, in Thee I have hoped; let me never be put to shame.
Zat was le perfect!
Amazing! I was so surprised.
Be careful not to fall for me now...
You're really smart after all!
After all?!
More than being smart, Bon's just good at memorizing.
Konekomaru, that means I'm smart, right?
Y-Yeah!
Memorizing isn't that great a skill.
Huh? Did you say something?
Bon...
I don't want to hear that from someone who can't even remember four lines!
It's not that I can't, I just chose not to remember!
Aria are totally defenseless while chanting, so they need to be protected by their team.
They're just luggage!
What?! We're aiming for Aria, you know!
Bon...
So scary!
If you want to hit me, go on!
I really can't stand you. Don't laugh at people's dreams!
Ah, that you'll defeat Satan?
Are you telling me not to laugh at such a joke?
Then what about you? Why do you want to become an Exorcist?
Go on, tell us!
Why...
I've never told anyone why I want to become one.
Unlike show-offs like you!
You little bitch!
Ouch! If you want to fight, do it somewhere else!
That's enough.
How about you behave yourselves?
What's with this stone? It's getting heavier!
It's a low level demon, too.
It gets heavier... while you hold it.
You don't even know about Ghost Stones? Pathetic.
Shut up! It's because you had to pick a fight...
It's called collective responsibility.
There's another purpose to this camp besides studying,
and that's strengthening your bonds with each other.
I don't want to have any bonds with these people!
You have to get along with each other!
An Exorcist cannot fight alone!
Support each other's abilities and cover the weaknesses.
Everyone fights in teams of at least two!
In actual battles, a quarrel in the team can lead to death!
Think about that.
Now I'll be gone for three hours on a mission.
Due to the incident with the Ghoul yesterday,
I'll lock every entrance to the dormitory
and put up strong barriers around it.
Lock the entrances? Then how can we get out?
There's no need for you to go out.
In the three hours that I'll be gone,
you will get on well and cool your heads.
Three hours... he's the demon here!
I can't take it anymore. Are you two really related?
He's a really nice guy. Somewhere deep within.
We're in this nice situation because of a certain someone.
Says the one who grabbed me by the collar.
And who started the fight to begin with?
Don't fight with me in the middle!
You really are an annoying woman!
Tell me something new. So what?
You'll just scare everyone away like that!
What?
The stone fell on my foot!
What's going on? Did he turn the lights off, too?
That can't be it!
Then is it a blackout?
No, look. There are lights outside.
Is this building the only one without power?
Let's go out.
Shima, be careful.
Heh, events like this always make me excited.
A real test of courage.
Huh? I guess I haven't slept enough.
I just...
That's...
It's the Ghoul from yesterday!
Didn't he put up barriers?
What's this?!
Ugh, it's its miasma!
I have to do something! I have to protect everyone!
Ni! Can you give me eely-billy?
Whoa...
Amazing!
Thank you, Ni!
You saved us, Shiemi. Thanks to you...
It's coming!
It's lively for a corpse!
The Ghouls get really active when it's dark.
Shiemi, what's wrong?
I feel dizzy...
What? It got so hot suddenly.
What's wrong with you?
It's because of the Ghoul's miasma.
Doesn't it bother you?
Damn, Yukio, where did you go?
If Moriyama's strength runs out, the barricade will be gone.
Then we'll be done for.
He's not picking up his phone.
Then...
What are you doing?
I'll go out and lure it away.
If it follows me, you guys run away.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Don't worry about me, I'm stronger than I look.
You idi- hey! Come back, Okumura!
Okumura!
Stop!
You're after me, aren't you?
Come!
Nice, follow me!
What a guy...
Anyway, let's just get out of here.
Moriyama, you can lower the barricade.
Wait. Didn't you hear that?
Huh?
You're kidding me.
The lights...
If I turn on the lights, the Ghoul will get weaker.
I can't just sit and wait until it gets through.
Let's kill it with chants.
Huh? Bon, that's fine but do you know its fatal verse?
I don't, but Ghoul type demons usually have their fatal verses from the Gospel of John.
I memorized all of it already, so if I just recite it, I'll hit the right one somewhere.
All of it? That's more than 20 chapters!
21, that is.
I memorized one to ten. Let me help.
Sure, let's do this, Konekomaru.
Wait a second!
If you start chanting, it'll go and attack you!
As if I cared! A girl is protecting us all alone!
A guy can't just sit back and wait!
Bon, you're the real man.
I haven't memorized any of it.
Oh, you had that with you?
If it gets through, I'll help you.
You're stupid.
What? You had such a big mouth earlier,
but now that things get real you wet yourself!
Stand back if you're not going to fight!
Konekomaru, you do it from the first chapter, I'll start from the 11th.
Don't let it get through.
Let's do this!
Yes!
Now a certain man was sick...
In the beginning was the Word...
F a c i l i t y   R o o m
The switchboard...
This is it.
It's all off! If I turn it on...
Back off!
That's it, those flames are what I wanted to see.
Those blue flames.
You!
Looks like you can't use your powers in front of others,
so I took the liberty of inviting you here, Okumura Rin.
Son of Satan!
Let not your heart be troubled: ye believe in God, believe also in me.
I have yet many things to say unto you, but ye cannot bear them now.
It's almost gotten through!
...signifying by what death he should glorify God.
Bon has almost reached the end!
Moriyama!
Damned thing...
And when he had spoken this, he saith unto him, 'Follow me.'
Why do you know?
How can you know about that?
Was yesterday's incident your doing, too?
Indeed.
Show me! Show me that power!
You won't get away with this!
I see.
Where is he? Where did he go?
Hey, you!
Kamiki...
Get a hold of yourself!
Today... you weren't your usual self.
Are you all right?
Am I all right? Me?
Why is she worried about me?
Bon, are you done yet?
I wasn't my usual self. She's right.
It's not like me!
I humbly call upon the Gods of Harvest.
Follow my wishes, leave none unfulfilled!
Woman, how dare you summon us again?
Know your pla-
Obey me!
She broke out of it.
Then went this saying abroad among the brethren, that that disciple should not die...
Bon!
One, two, three, four, five...
I'm a bad person, but I'm also a sore loser.
Tremble as a leaf, tremble I say!
But that's who I am!
Fall... and never return to life!
You did it!
No way!
This is the disciple which testifieth of these things, and wrote these things:
and we know that his testimony is true.
The lights!
I suppose that even the world...
I suppose that even the world itself could not contain the books that should be written!
Bon!
I'll di-di-die!
Bon...
What a relief.
Was there another one here?
You... the other one?
I took it out. You defeated yours, too? Amazing...
What the hell's wrong with you?! Do you want to die?!
Wait, do you want to kill me?
Are you all right?
Yeah, thank you.
I hate you.
Huh?
But thanks anyway. That's all.
Paku... I...
Izumo... I love you the way you are!
I'll do my best.
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
You don't know anything!
What am I seeing...?
Ah, Yukio! Where were you?!
You...
Next Episode Preview
What is the meaning of this?
It was all to understand Rin Okumura's powers as much as possible.
This doesn't feel right.
Yuki! Rin!
Memories