This Japan of yours...
They say it's a small country, but the climate in the north is quite different from the south.
Amaimon!
I told you that the Infinity Key is not for sightsee-
Tha-That's the Honey-Honey Sisters yukata that
counts as a rare item even in the holy lands!
I just queued and bought it.
Well done!
This is the true Japanese samurai spirit!
And the wonderful world of moe!
Having such a great little brother fills my heart with joy.
By the way, Brother, where is he?
Over there.
An amusement park?
Oh, so you finally feel like playing a bit with him?
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Episode 12
szia A Game of Tag
I'd rather bring a date to the amusement park after school, not come here like this...
How was your team's last mission, Shima?
I'm not even sure if you could call it a mission...
It was a huge squid.
Squid...?
Squid.
Oh well, that's bullshit.
What?!
I mean, there are people who are not even doing anything!
Well...
Sorry we're late!
Shiemi, what happened? Your kimono...
The kimono's not fit for missions, so the Principal assigned me a uniform.
We're late because Kamiki had to show me how to put it on.
Why me?
It's not too weird I hope...
It's good, it's good, it's hella cute, Moriyama.
Thanks.
Hey, isn't that skirt a bit too short? Huh, Yukio?
Why are you asking me?
Huh? You were checking out her boo-
That hurt, four-eyes!
Now that you're all here, let me assign you in pairs.
Miwa, Takara.
Yamada, Suguro.
Why?
Kamiki, Shima.
Okumura, Moriyama.
I'm with Rin!
Lately we've been getting sightings of a ghost and reports of damage
here in MepphyLand, so today you'll investigate that.
You have to find it today while the park is closed to public,
and as soon as you do, report to either professor Tsubaki's or my cell phone.
Then, can someone please define what is a ghost.
Kamiki?
Yes. Ghosts are demons that possess vapors emitted from the corpses of humans or animals.
They often exhibit residual emotions from the lifetime of the subject.
Very well.
How many ghosts are there?
There is only one, although there have been sightings from all around the park.
It takes the appearance of a small boy.
It usually does nothing more than pulling hands or lifting skirts.
What?! Lifting skirts?!
Those are childish pranks. Then again, it is a child.
But if we leave it be, there's a danger of it becoming more vicious.
It should be easy with this many people.
Any other questions?
Very well.
Head out!
Rin, you watch the right side. I'll watch this side.
Okay.
It really suits her well. Wait, isn't this... like a date?!
Are you okay?
Shiemi? What's wrong? What happened to your face?!
Are you angry?
No... I'm... Not laughing.
Huh?
Hey, wait a second!
You're acting weird!
Shiemi?
I really wanted to go to the amusement park,
but I couldn't stand so many people around me, so it was out of the question...
I guess it's normally crowded and a lot of fun...
But I...
Then let's come here together next time!
Okay!
Really?
Do you really mean that?
Yes, I do!
Okay! Then let's decide where we should look next!
Huh?
Rin?
A voice...
Voice?
Why did it...?
Here it comes.
Amazing, Rin! How did you know?
It's like a gift?
Why are you crying?
Hey, don't talk to demons!
But he's tiny and he doesn't look dangerous at all...
Hey! How long do you want to keep on crying?
You shouldn't yell at him!
I just...
I was very sick... But my parents promised me we'd come here when I get well...
But I died, so no one...
I see, so you were just lonely.
Shut up, you hag!
Stupid! Stupid!
That brat! I wanted to rub-
Hey, wait!
Rin?
Wait!
Where did that pervy brat go?
Rin, I'll check over there.
Sure.
There!
Stupid!
Hey, wait!
Catch me if you can!
Ouch! That kid... What does he want?
Ah right, I should report that we found him...
Who are you? Give it back!
Who? Ah, yes.
I'm Amaimon, a demon king. Kinda like your big brother. Nice to meet you.
Also, I'm not giving this back.
A demon?
So this is the Demon-Slaying Blade?
Hey! Give it back!
Let's see how it works.
Would it hurt to help me look?
Hey!
There you are!
Stupid hag!
I'll catch you now!
Stop!
Don't screw around!
I see. So the sword is connected to Gehenna.
And the scabbard is the gate itself.
If the sword is sheathed the gate closes, and when it's drawn it opens again.
Come on, make up your mind!
Then let's leave it this way.
Your flames are in Gehenna, and your body is in Assiah, right?
Who cares!
What did you do to our brother's head?
What do you want?!
What do I want? I had some free time so I came here to play.
This is an amusement park after all, so let's have a lot of fun!
What?
Okumura! Did you turn the electricity on?
No, I didn't do anything.
Can you see anything from where you are?
Now that was cool.
I studied Japanese games as well.
Come on, catch me if you can!
You little... don't screw with me!
Hey, hag, wake up already!
Wait!
Too bad! Catch me if you can!
Could it be that he's...
I was very sick...
I really wanted to go to the amusement park...
Maybe he's like me?
But then...
Okay! Such a bad boy! Wait!
Wait!
This reminds me, I went to the seaside the other day!
What is he talking about?
You gotta be kidding me...
Surfing's so much fun!
You...
What?
I learned about this game, too.
What's that? What's happening?
That doesn't look like a ghost to me...
It's something else.
I don't get it... Why are Father and Brother so obsessed with him?
I'm up here!
This is such a let down. I hoped you'd be good for killing some time...
Now this is better!
An earthquake?
What happened?
Amazing! It's like in a movie!
Playtime's over!
Help!
Shiemi?
Stupid! Run!
I won't make it...
Amazing!
What are you laughing at? We could've died!
I'm already dead!
But...
I was very sick, so I never played outside.
No one ever scolded me or picked me up.
Today was a lot of fun!
Thanks, sis!
Oh? Is it over already? So boring...
Brother's been holding me back, but I'm thinking I should break your sword...
Stop!
Sever the head of the snake that
devours the eight princesses.
Who are you?
You're Amaimon, the Earth King, aren't you?
How could a big fish like you get inside the Academy?
Mephisto let you in?
You're in the way...
You are the one in the way.
Ah, screw it.
Next time.
Wait!
Take care!
People will be here soon. Hide your tail!
He took my sword so easily...
He was so strong...
I lost it for a second!
This is no different from back then!
Rin, are you okay?
Don't touch me!
Rin?
Sorry. Never mind.
Anyway, are you all right?
What happened to that brat?
He disappeared. He said "thanks, sis."
I see...
Rin! We should totally come here together next time!
Yeah...
Shiemi!
Yuki?
Are you all right?
Yuki, Rin is wounded, he needs help.
Rin, what happened?
You're late, Yukio.
What took you so long? I had to make my move!
Long time no see.
You can't be...
Aren't you Yamada?
I'm fed up with this look anyway.
The Vatican Headquarters dispatched me to investigate risk factors in the Japanese Branch.
I'm Shura Kirigakure, High Inspector, Upper First Class Exorcist.
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Why have you been hiding the existence of Satan's son?
Next Episode Preview
Oh, I haven't been hiding him!
It's all for the sake of the Order of the True Cross.
I wanted to believe in you, Shiro.
Proof