My birthday?
Yeah, your birthday. When is it?
March 6th, but...
And your blood type?
B type.
Jupiter centric, Pisces, B type with a wood aspect.
Kamiki Izumo
Heaven score: 14
Earth score: 17
Human score: 9
Total score: 31
Outer score: 22
Moriyama Shiemi
Heaven score: 10
Earth score: 7
Human score: 4
Total score:
17 Outer score: 13
6th March, Pisces, B type
Wu Xing: Four, Green, Jupiter, Wood
It is all clear to me now!
Moriyama is a hopeless romantic who always walks her own path!
She's a dreamer, but escaping reality in a good way!
And you, Izumo?
October 11th... A type.
It is all clear to me now!
Izumo is an idealist who interacts equally with everyone!
Though she's good at adapting to her environment,
she takes her ideals seriously and often complains about reality.
Amazing!
What exactly are you doing?
Fortune-telling from your star sign, your blood type, and the Four Pillars of Destiny.
I've got it all in my head.
Why don't you use your head for useful studies instead?
Oh come on, I know you're interested.
Goodbye.
Izumo is really hard to get to.
Tell me my fortune too!
Nope, I can't do it for guys.
Why?
I can only tell the fortune of girls!
It's not the same to do it for guys.
Who cares, my birthday is-
I'm telling you that it won't work!
I wonder how Satan's son was born...
Yeah...
What is it?
September 27th
Kamiki's birthday is so close!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
"Kamiki's birthday party"
"Preparation meeting"
We should organize a surprise birthday party for Kamiki!
Kamiki's birthday party
Preparation meeting
September 27th
Episode 18
sziaA Day When Nothing Happens
Why do we have to celebrate her birthday?
Bon, we decided by majority rule, so don't complain!
Then let's decide on everyone's duties!
What do you do at a birthday party?
There should be presents... and a cake.
We should prepare snacks and drinks too.
And decorate the room...
I see!
Presents, huh? I wonder what would make her happy.
It must be some kind of meat.
Barbeque or sukiyaki or roast beef...
That's just what you'd want to eat.
A spit roasted turkey would be nice too... it would fit the party.
I've never seen one in my life though...
Okumura, your menu is starting to sound a bit weird.
A flower bouquet would be nice, wouldn't it?
Thank you, Shima!
You can't eat flowers!
Rin!
There are many edible flowers!
Our garden has them too in the spring.
Even you, Moriyama?
Shut the hell up, all of you!
Shima arranges the present! Research it and have it ready by Sunday!
Roger!
Okumura prepares the cake! Don't buy one, bake one yourself!
Sure! I've never made sweets before though.
Konekomaru, you do the shopping and act as Okumura's advisor.
Moriyama and I will decorate the room.
You ain't half bad at getting stuff done, Bon.
Bon, could I do something else...
It's okay, I know how much you love Japanese sweets!
You'll do fine!
But cakes and Japanese sweets are very different...
You can do it!
Let's do our best, Konekomaru!
Yeah...
Keep this a secret from everyone. Be very careful.
Good luck, everyone!
A birthday, huh?
Ah, Shima! Are you looking for someone?
Umm, just... Is Paku around?
She just came back.
Paku!
What's going on?
Can I have a word with you? Come with me for a second.
No way, those two...!
Sorry to drag you out here so suddenly.
I don't mind.
Great, you're so nice, Paku!
Your looks and your kindness are both top grade!
Okumura, read the recipe for me, please.
Sure, let's see.
Four eggs, 200 grams of sugar, flour...
What are you two doing?
I'll leave the rest to you!
What?
No-Nothing! See you later!
And that's how it's done.
Amazing! Suguro, you're so good at handicrafts!
Well...
Umm...
What are you doing?
Umm, well, we're just...
It's none of your business!
Hey! Wait, Suguro!
Just... what?
Are you going out with him?
Huh?
You were chatting during the lunch break like two little birdies.
Ah, Shima? No way!
Really?
Really! He just asked me about the upcoming bir-
Bir-?
...bird watching tour!
Never mind then... I was worried because he's such a flirt.
What are you making, Rin?
A birthday cake!
Cake? What's a cake?
You'll know once you see it.
After all that happened...
It's so awkward to be alone with Okumura.
What's next?
Umm, you sieve the flour and mix it well with the rest.
I'll do it!
Konekomaru, you're good! You really haven't done this before?
Yeah, I just watched and learned.
But you too are so good at this, it's hard to believe that this is your first time.
You're really good at cooking!
I guess so. There were only guys at our place and everyone sucked at cooking,
so I had no choice but to do it myself.
Done.
But you know,
it's a lot more fun to cook for someone else, not just for yourself!
You're right.
Let's make the best cake ever, Konekomaru!
Don't do that! The fluff is the life of the dough!
Do it lighter! More gently!
Huh? Like this?
Don't stop!
Sure...
You're working hard.
Yuki!
I got the message this morning that the herbs I ordered have arrived.
Right away.
Umm, True Cross Academy, Faculty of Pharma...
Ah, this time it's my personal order.
That's unusual.
I heard about the party.
It was your idea, wasn't it?
I'm sure Kamiki will be happy.
I'm doing it partially for my own sake.
Granny and Mom celebrate my birthday,
but this will be the first time I celebrate with my friends.
I've made friends since I started the cram school,
so I thought we could all celebrate together.
It's selfish, isn't it?
I think it's wonderful.
By the way, when is your and Rin's birthday?
It's on December 27th.
Have you ever had a birthday party?
Well... more or less.
More or less?
It's so close to Christmas, we always celebrated the two together at the monastery.
But it never had this birthday feeling.
I hope the party will be a success.
Yeah! You should come too, Yuki. It'll be fun!
This is...
It's just the first try though.
Well, this is my level!
No way, no way, no way!
Huh? What about Norway?
There's no way this'll do!
Konekomaru! You were supposed to keep an eye him!
I just... looked away for a moment...
Leave Konekomaru alone! It's perfect, isn't it?
It's totally wrong!
What's wrong with it?
Looks like a perfectly fine birthday cake to me.
Huh?!
So birthday cakes and Christmas cakes are different?
You always learn new stuff, even at the age of 15... Right, Rin?
What should we do with this?
Thank you for your patronage.
This is just a small token of our gratitude.
Exorcist cram school students.
Thank you for your patronage.
This is just a small token of our gratitude.
Exorcist cram school students.
Thank you for your patronage.
This is just a small token of our gratitude.
Exorcist cram school students.
Thank you for your patronage.
This is just a small token of our gratitude.
Exorcist cram school students.
Thank you for your patronage. This is just a small token of our gratitude. Exorcist cram school students.
Giving a cake celebrating the birth of God... to a demon?
My goodness! It is fantastic!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Man, you sure don't need the uniform to be gorgeous.
Oh come on! Let's go.
Yeah.
Did I warn you for nothing, Paku?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
You're such a weirdo, Shima!
How about this one?
I think it's pretty nice.
You're standing too close!
I think Izumo was collecting this series.
Those eyes charmed me.
Charmed me... Charmed me... Charmed me...
Charmed him?!
My heart is whispering too.
My heart... My heart.... My heart...
Her heart?!
They fell for each other?
This is going way too fast!
Where did they go?
It's raining.
Damn, I don't have an umbrella with me.
It's okay, I brought mine.
Sharing an umbrella?!
What's wrong?
I've got something in my eye.
Which one? Let me see.
NOOOOOO!
I got it.
Izumo?
What are you two doing?
She found us out.
"She found us out", my ass! You and you!
Didn't you try to k...
K-Kiss Paku here?
Huh?
I didn't! I didn't!
What are you saying, Izumo?
Then what were you doing so close to each other?
We were looking for your birthday pre-
And that's how she found out.
Are you seriously this stupid?
Sorry...
Why are you so mad?
I won't let you just use me like that!
Use you?
Yeah! You're just using me to have your little fun!
Izumo, you should be happy rather than...
Sorry, it was my idea to make a surprise party...
There's nothing to apologize for. Moriyama wanted to make you happy.
Is celebrating your birthday such a nuisance?
That's not it...
Then what is?
I'm just saying that it's unfair.
Unfair?
It's unfair to start celebrating birthdays now!
What about everyone who's had their birthday after we started school?
One of us has to be 16 already!
I remember you guys were talking about scooter licenses!
You're too sharp, Izumo.
See, I was right.
If you want to do this, then do it properly for everyone!
Otherwise I won't take part in it.
That sounds good.
Then Bon and Shima and Kamiki...
And Paku too!
So that means four presents?
Then I'll give back the collected money to Suguro and Shima... Umm...
This is turning into a hassle.
Then let's throw a party for everyone, even for those who have their birthdays later!
Is it okay to write this in hiragana?
Just wait a moment, I'll spell it for you.
H-A-P-P-Y.
Okay, we did it!
Happy Birthday
to Everyone at Cram School!
You have your drinks?
We made it!
We've been waiting for you!
Okumura made that one?
Well, it's the only productive thing I'm good at.
He said it himself...
Konekomaru!
Thanks, Konekomaru.
All together...
Happy birthday!
Then the presents we all have been waiting for!
We'll decide who gets what by lottery!
I'll go first!
What's wrong, Yuki?
I was just thinking about how much fun everyone's having.
You're not having fun?
I am.
You've been so weird lately, Yuki.
We've been told that our birthday is December 27th, but it doesn't really mean anything.
No one knows who gave birth to us when and where.
What kind of a person was our mom?
I picked you kids up under a bridge.
That again?
It's true!
It was midwinter but this huuuge watermelon was floating in the river.
When I opened it, you guys were inside!
Seriously?!
I didn't really know which way I should cut the melon.
I couldn't do it right, so I accidentally cut you into two.
No way!
Father was always using stupid excuses and he never told us the truth.
But just once...
I first met you two on a snowy day like this.
That's the only clue I have.
Now we have no way to figure out our true birthday.
Wow, this is so cool!
Yuki, thanks for being born!
Huh?
No matter when you were born, I'm happy you're here!
Thanks.
Hey, you two have numbers 2 and 7 left, take your picks!
Let's go!
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
It suits you perfectly! It's a miracle!
It's a birthday party!
Okumura speaking.
Yes. Understood. I'm on my way.
What's up, Yukio?
Our monastery was...
attacked.
I can't let anyone get hurt because of me anymore!
Next Episode Preview
You're not going anywhere today.
What's all the fuss about, Yukio?
Professor, you're still trying to...
Mask