Mameshiba
Baby!
Shiba!
baby-baby-baby babyshiba
baby-baby babyshiba
Baby!
Mameshiba
baby-baby babyshiba
LOVE
Eternal life?
Exactly!
You are experiencing the sorrows and delights of this world in the flow of time we call "eternity".
However, the moment you wish to die your soul will be mine.
Can you accept that?
Fascinating.
I shall accept your gamble.
The contract is made.
And now, I wish you a pleasant journey.
Eins, zwei, drei!
The Blue Exorcist
Dark side in my heart is
nuguisarenai kako no kanashimi
the unerasable sadness of the past.
It's alright kokoro ni mo nai
It's alright if I don't really mean it,
Blastar hanachi te wo nobashita
so I fire my blasters and stretch out my hands.
sakete toorenai michi wa itsu kara ka konna datta
Since when has my way been unavoidable like this?
soshite daremo inakunatta...
And now there's no one left...
unmei nante kuso kurae
Fuck this destiny,
yarikirenakute cry for pride
I cry for my pride, I can't bear it.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
hibiku ai no uta
An aria of love resounding through
yuganda sekai magatta negai
this distorted reality of twisted prayers.
kuzuresatte iku risou to ashita
My dreams and tomorrow are collapsing,
haite suteru hodo ni taikutsu datta
because throwing away the lies would be boring.
Good bye precious life.
unmei nante nurikaete
Go and repaint this destiny,
kizu darake ni natte try for pride
try it for your pride, covered in wounds.
Ah, ah, ah, alone in my world.
soredemo ai wo utau
Even so, I sing the song of love and
hizunda sekai todokazu negai
let its wish reach through this distorted world
kizuki ageteku kizuna to ashita
to build our bonds and the tomorrow to come.
haite sutete mo kekkyoku taisetsu nanda
Throwing away the lies was important after all,
because this is my precious life.
Dark cloud in my heart is
harewatari michi ni hikari wa sashita
disappearing and light is shining on the road I'm on.
Let's fight osore wa nai
Let's fight, there's no fear.
moroha no tsurugi furikazashita
I brandished my two-edged sword.
Mameshiba
Babyshiba tuwned into fwuits.
oppai ni
drinking milk
mero mero
melon-melon
meronshiba
melonshiba
oppai
milk
sui sui
water-water
suikashiba
watermelonshiba
oppai
milk
yada mon
don't want
remonshiba
lemonshiba
oppai
milk
rin rin
app-app
ringoshiba
appleshiba
oppai ni
drinking milk
sukedachi
little fighter
sudachishiba
limeshiba
oppai
milk
ran ran
ram-ram
ranbuutan
rambutan
Rin!
I'm fine!
It's just a scratch, it's nothing!
What is that?
It's a dimensional rift.
He wants to open the Gate wide enough to swallow Assiah!
I've been dreaming for the past 15 years.
A dream to make a new world by uniting Assiah and Gehenna.
This is going just the way Satan wants!
Rin! Yuki!
Damn!
Shiemi!
That's...
You wicked creatures who would trample the blooming lilies of the fields,
I, Arthur Auguste Angel, will hand judgment down on you!
You're late, you baldy!
I will handle them. You just sit there quietly.
Don't order me around!
Zodiac Slash!
Damn!
It won't work if we attack on our own!
We must synchronize our attacks!
It's just as Yukio says.
If we don't work together, we can't get through the defenses on that huge wall-thing.
Are you all right?
I haven't fallen so low as to need you to worry about me.
It's a stain on my record to cooperate with the offspring of a demon,
but we have no choice.
Kirigakure Style Demon Sword Technique: Slither!
Snakefang!
Zodiac Slash!
Huh?
We did it?!
What?
No way...
Rin!
Have you found Moriyama?
We can't! There are too many people!
Don't tell me she's gone with Okumura!
What?
The barrier has been damaged.
Every exorcist get ready to drive the demons back!
Everyone else go evacuate further inside!
I didn't think the demons could make it this far.
Will Okumura be all right?
Of course!
He's so stupid he'd forget to die even if he got killed!
Mameshiba
Hey, didjuno?
Ignowance is bwiss.
Happy back to school
Yukio? Are you all right, Yukio?
Rin! What about the Gehenna Gate?
It's over the city...
I'm sorry, Rin.
Yukio?
It's all my fault...
It's because I did all that...
Yeah. You were headstrong and stubborn,
and you probably don't even consider me your brother at all.
You're a mean little brother.
You didn't tell me you could see demons,
or that you were a teacher at the cram school.
Not to mention becoming the paladin.
It's really tough to have such a smart little brother!
Ouch!
Just depend on me once in a while like when we were kids.
Rin...
Rin!
Blackie, where were you?
Sorry! I'm not going to run away anymore!
I was the familiar of the strongest exorcist, Shiro!
Get on, Rin!
All right!
I'll go too!
Yukio, but...
I guess it's because I had demonic power awaken in me,
but I can hear Blackie's voice now.
Can I get on too, Blackie?
Sure, let's go together!
The demon's spawns are leaving.
It's no longer about demons or humans.
They love Assiah, where they lived together with Shiro.
Yuki... Rin... Please, come back safe!
What's that?
Hurry, this way!
Damn, there's no end to them!
I hope the boys are all right...
We should worry about ourselves first! Let's go!
The black mist that appeared around the True Cross Academy in the evening
is still present and in a 20km radius the Order of the True Cross has been...
Even if I went there, I wouldn't be able t' help them at all.
I've t' do what I can do.
North of the True Cross Academy campus...
Gods o' the Forge, please protect Lil' Ryu 'n' his friends!
There's no end to them!
We must do our best!
They will calm down at dawn! We must hold out until then!
Dawn? But the sun just went down...
We can't hold out like this.
Umm, Professor!
What is it, Miwa?
The Japanese Branch is connected to the Vatican Headquarters, isn't it?
So what?
The time difference is seven hours!
What? What? What does that mean?
What's with the time difference?
We could evacuate to the Vatican Headquarters with the magic keys.
Over there it's still daytime...
Yes! The sun!
You're a genius, Miwa!
Now we just have to lure the demons to this plaza!
No, we don't need to do that.
I have an idea.
Damn!
They're coming!
Hold on!
Thanks, Blackie!
We've gotta attack the Gate itself, Rin.
But those small fries are in the way!
And even if we attack it directly, they'll just shield it again!
We're "making a sun"?
We'll guide the sunlight over to the Japanese Branch.
That way we won't have to evacuate here,
and we won't get the people in the Vatican in trouble either.
We're ready!
Then let's begin!
Here they come!
Stand back!
What's that light?
It's so pretty!
The demons are confused!
Rin!
Yeah, this is our only chance!
Yukio!
Rin!
They're flying!
Bravo! Amazing!
They can control the flames surprisingly well!
You are amazing indeed, Okumura Brothers!
Let's do this, Rin!
Yeah, let's smash that Gate to pieces!
Why... Why would the brats born from me and Yuri destroy our dream?
We don't give a damn about your dream!
We are just protecting
our friends!
This world!
No matter what!
This light...
It's so warm.
Rin... Yuki...
Satan.
Yuri... I'm sorry.
I couldn't fulfill your dream.
It was still too early.
The boys will show whether or not the path we chose is correct.
What the hell!
It's all in ruins!
Is it over now?
Okumura!
Sup!
You're alive!
And you're not even hurt!
You moron! Don't make us worry like that!
What happened to Satan?
I guess he went back to Gehenna.
But he might come back one day.
I see.
Rin! Yuki!
Shiemi.
Why are you two always so reckless?
She's mad!
Don't make me worry like that!
Thanks, Shiemi.
Are you our mother or something?
Oh my oh my!
What a troublesome bunch you are!
Takara!
Where have you been all this time?
Brother, your beloved toy town is in ruins.
Brother?
I just remembered this man from hundreds of years ago,
who took on one of my challenges and stood his ground.
A challenge?
Yes. It was a challenge literally with his life on the line.
And who won?
Of course I did, but at the moment of his death the man shouted,
"I now enjoy the highest moment - this!"
I finally understand how you felt back then.
(WIRED...)
mau chou no you ni hirari
I'm lightly fluttering in wondrous light
chuu ni tadayou fukashikina hikari
like a dancing butterfly in midair.
koko wa dokoka betsu no sekai
Is this place in another world?
rakka suru sokudo wa kawaranai
My fall isn't slowing down so
cut the rope.
Cut the rope.
atama wo meguru suuchi wa
The numbers that make my head spin
rasen wo egaki kyuujoushou
are forming a rising spiral
juudaina ayamachi ni mo kizukazu ni
and there I notice a terrible error.
hito kara hito e to tsunagaru
Connecting people to one another
awaku seiran ni kagayaku wire
is a shining pale indigo blue wire.
totemo kirei de maru de kinu no ito
It's beautiful like a thread of silk.
kore ga unmei to iu kusari nano ka
I wonder if it's what they call the chains of fate?
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in this
wired life.
sagashite demo karamatte
You seek for it and yet you're already caught,
tadori tsukenai
so don't try to struggle.
What is wired life?
nogarerarenai nante
You're a beautiful fool in
oroka de utsukushii
the way you get entwined in it.
There is wired life.
Mameshiba
mame mame mame mame
mamerry christmas mame
mamerry christmas
hachoo~
waa~
mame mamerry christmas
A month has passed since then.
Principal Mephisto... I mean, Johann Faust returned to the Academy,
and classes started again as normal.
It's been used as a love potion since ancient times.
The roots are vaguely human-shaped.
You must be careful when pulling it out of the ground, it screams very loudly.
Hearing that sound directly can cause death...
Yukio lost his paladin rank and got demoted back to middle first class.
They said it had something to do with the human resource management of the Vatican, but I don't really get the details.
Where are we going?
That's a good question.
You called me here, and you still don't know?
The Principal gave me this key,
saying I should come here with you.
What's wrong?
I see.
Hey, Yukio!
Right before Satan possessed me, his memories came rushing in.
Mother gave birth to us in this abandoned forest... giving her life in exchange.
What?
Snowmen. They're a type of golem.
Let's go. It'll lead the way.
This is where we were born.
On a snowy night Father found us here.
Mother gave us to him before her last breath.
Is that Mother's?
You must have seen it in those memories...
What kind of a person was she?
She was a wonderful person.
That's not enough!
More like... she looked like someone... or that she had big eyes...
Rin... Is it really all right for us to have been born into this world?
If it wasn't for us, Mother and Father would still be alive,
and so many people around us wouldn't have gotten hurt.
Are you really that stupid?
We were born because the old fart and Mother worked so hard!
You should treasure the precious life we got from them!
Yeah, you're right.
Rin...
They were amazing, weren't they?
Of course! They were our parents after all!
Route 3 inbound lane at the True Cross Junction blocked!
The vicinity of the south gate of the Academy is sealed!
The enemy is Ghost Rider!
It's a dangerous demon that possesses vehicles and causes terrible accidents!
Don't let your guard down!
Here it is!
Sup!
Rin, what are you doing?
Esquires aren't allowed to take part in the operation!
Oh come on, don't be so strict.
Brothers are there to help anytime.
It's dangerous, so get back here right now!
Rin, watch out!
Rin!
You did it!
How do you like that?
Rin!
What's going on?
The enemy is a demon that possesses vehicles.
It switched from the bike to a truck!
Stop, Yukio!
Why are you getting in the way?
Look, there's someone in the truck!
That's just a corpse!
We have to get rid of it along with the truck!
Why are you judging it so easily?
They run wild because you don't listen to them!
We have to take down the demons who hurt people!
No! You should listen to their side of the story! That's what a true exorcist is like!
At least the old fart would've said so.
Rin!
What do you two think you're doing? It's coming!
I'll keep it busy, in the mean time you look for its weak point!
Let's go!
Rin!
Hey!
Episode 25
sziaThe Highest Moment
Mameshiba
Babyshiba tuwned into fwuits.
oppai
milk
dou dou
grape-grape
budoushiba
grapeshiba
oppai ni
drinking milk
buru buru
blue-blue
buruuberii
blueberry
oppai ni
drinking milk
pichi pichi
energetic
piichishiba
peachshiba
oppai ni
drinking milk
kan kan
so noisy
mikanshiba
mandarinshiba
oppai
milk
shinbou
confident
sakuranbo
cherry
oppai
lots of
ippai
milk
painshiba
pineappleshiba