Ever since I was little I knew I wasn't good.
Why do they keep a wild child like him...
We'd be better off without him around...
He's like a demon's child.
No... I'm not a demon!
A Place of Friendship
Southern Cross Mall
The path of the righteous shall not be revealed to the unfaithful.
I lower the Ladder of Jacob with the aid of the Lord's Hand.
Let's go!
You're kidding me...
Are these stray dogs? They stink!
They're Ghouls. Demons that possess dead bodies.
Ghouls?
We're lucky that we're in Japan, otherwise human-form Ghouls would've showed up, too.
Are you calling this "lucky"?!
Wha... A bomb?
Don't worry.
It's just holy water.
Heh, I'm getting a bit too old to protect the kids...
Stop calling me a kid!
Let's go home while we still can.
Do you mean that this isn't over yet?
I told you...
They'll be coming for you.
The sun is setting soon.
That's when the demons get active.
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Episode 2
szia Gehenna Gate
You really don't remember anything?
Yeah...
Not even that you wanted to kill Okumura?
And that his body caught fire?
No... I don't remember anything.
I lent you 500 yen for dinner, Shiratori!
I paid the doctor's fee for you!
I bought you that Magical☆Poemy body pillow that you wanted so much!
I see... you did so much for me...
Or wait, you're just screwing with me!
I really paid the doctor's fee!
Huh? Why?
We told you, you started a fight with Rin Okumura.
Okumura?
You wanted to give him a lesson but he beat you up instead.
So bad that we had to take you to the hospital!
Now that you remind me, my body hurts all over...
Are you okay, Shiratori?
Did he hit you too hard?
Right... Okumura, that bastard...
He screwed me up, Okumura...
Okumura!
Who the hell you think you are, Okumura?!
Screw you!
Shiratori...
I'm not gonna stick around...
This is bad!
Hey, wait for me!
I'm accustomed to this body, after all...
Where are you, our Young Master?
Welcome back!
How are the preparations?
We got rid of all the Coal Tar.
We've drawn threefold barriers around the monastery.
Double it.
We can't hold out until morning.
We're being chased by Astaroth's minions.
Pour triple-C strong holy water into the sewers!
Don't let a single one get in.
Understood!
Follow me.
This is the Demon-Slaying Blade, called Kurikara.
It's a legendary sword passed down since ancient times.
Your demonic powers are in this sword, sealed by its scabbard.
My powers?
This sword is more important than your own life.
Never ever hand it over to anyone else.
Don't let go of it even while sleeping.
Also, you must never draw it.
If you draw it, your demonic powers will awaken and you will never be human again.
Wait... If I'm a demon, what about Yukio?
Is he...?
You are fraternal twins.
In the womb Yukio's body was too weak so the power rejected him.
You are the only one who inherited the demonic powers.
Everyone knew about this?
That I'm not human? That I'm the offspring of a demon?!
So this is the place where our Young Master is held in his temporary form.
Idiot! What do you think you're doing!
Hey...
That hurt, you fucker!
I'm coming for you, Young Master.
Why did you keep such an important thing a secret all this time?!
I could raise you only if you were human.
You were allowed to live on that condition, despite the demonic blood running through your veins.
Condition?
I raised you as human and that's why we told you nothing.
Nothing about the secrets of your birth.
Come!
I have come for you, Young Master.
Let us head back to Gehenna together.
The demons' attacks will weaken when dawn comes.
Get out of here and hide somewhere where the demons can't find you!
Hide? Where?
Take my phone. There's only one number in there.
It belongs to my best friend.
Call him as soon as you leave the monastery.
I'm sure he'll protect you...
Hey, wai-
We're not done talking yet!
The path of the righteous shall not be revealed to the unfaithful.
The mist of uncertainty shall conceal the Gates of Heaven.
Protect Rin!
God dwells in my fist!
Demons dwell in my heart!
Heed my call, Guardian of Fertility, Moorkin!
Damn Exorcists...
Let me out, damn geezer! Let me out!
I'm... a demon...
Damnit...
Why do they keep a wild child like him... He's like a demon's child.
I'm not a demon!
I'm really...
Brother...
What are you aiming at?
Moorkin!
He's fast!
Kyodo!
The Lord gives and the Lord takes away. He shall bestow you life and happiness!
Praised be the name of the Lord!
Rot away, you piece of shit!
A human getting cocky?!
Maruta!
You won't get away!
He's huge...
I'll tear every single one of you apart!
I said we're not done talking yet, you damn geezer!
Young Master... What are you do...
O Lord, bind a millstone around its neck so that it shall never again rise from the depths of the Leviathan!
St-Stop...!
Chain it in darkness eternal, where it will not hear nor see!
Nagatomo, get the car ready!
Yes sir.
Izumi and Kyodo, put the Seal of Tetramorph on this boy.
And don't forget to perform the purification ritual.
Yes, sir.
Wait, we should treat their wounds first!
Our first and foremost priority now is to hide you.
Realize that you're the target of the demons!
I see... so if I leave it'll be all over?
Rin!
Then I'll leave!
That should make you feel better!
Rin!
Let go of me! You'd throw me away anyway!
I've been a problem child all my life...
We're not even really related!
Just strangers...
Rin!
Just be honest! That you got tired of pretending we're family!
Or can't a clergyman talk like that?
Maybe you want to play a good father to the end?
Don't screw with me! You're not my father or anything!
Don't ever call yourself my father again!
It's almost daybreak. Hurry and pack up!
Fine...!
Oh no...
Reverend Fujimoto!
Don't come closer!
Get... away... from me!
What's going on?!
At last I've got this body!
Finally I can meet you, my son!
Or whatever!
What's wrong with you, Old Man?!
He's possessed! Satan has taken over his body!
What?!
Exactly. I'm Satan. The God of Gehenna and your real father.
You can call me Daddy if you want.
Reverend Fujimoto!
Shut the hell up!
Guys!
Don't ruin this touching meeting!
I don't have time for that!
I am too strong for Assiah,
so you can't bear my presence for long.
Not even this man's body. Nor your mother.
What's this?!
This is the Gehenna Gate.
The magic gate connecting Assiah and Gehenna.
Let's go back to Gehenna!
Don't come near me! Stay away!
What's that? Did you wet yourself?
Pathetic... Take back your demon powers already!
I'm not a demon! I'm human!
This... I... I'm a...
You have the blood of the God of Gehenna,
yet your body is of Assiah. You are special.
That was a nice scream!
Today you will be reborn as a demon!
Someone!
Help me!
Happy birthday, my son!
That's... not...
He's my son! And you'll give him back!
You filthy Exorcist...!
Taking your own life, what a worldly priest you are!
But it's too late.
The Gehenna Gate won't let go of anything!
Old Man! Get a hold of yourself!
Damnit!
Hey, Daddy...
What?
Why am I so different from everyone?
Am I really a demon's child?
No, you're not.
You're a human child.
The Demon-Slaying Blade...
Stop, Rin! Did you forget what Reverend Fujimoto told you?!
If you draw that, you will...
Old Man...
If it's that embarrassing, show me how much you've grown!
I haven't shown you anything yet!
Don't die on me, Old Man!
Daddy...
Brother?
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Welcome back, Rin.
Did you find a job?
Man, you're only growing up physically...
There's only one number in there.
It belongs to my best friend.
Call him as soon as you leave the monastery.
I'm sure he'll protect you...
Nice to meet you.
I represent the Japanese branch of True Cross Knight Order.
My name is Mephisto Pheles.
I was Reverend Fujimoto's friend. Please accept my condolences.
Are you Exorcists too?
Indeed. And we know everything about you.
It seems Reverend Fujimoto tried to raise you as a human,
but contrary to his wishes, you awakened.
Son of Satan wandering around Assiah is a threat of extinction to humankind.
In the name of the Vatican, we are to dispose of you.
Weren't you supposed to protect me?
I'd prefer not to mix public and private matters.
You have two choices left.
Be killed by us,
or kill us and run away.
You could also kill yourself, so actually that makes three choices.
Now, which one would suit you best?
Make me one of you!
I don't care what you say or what you think.
I'm not the son of Satan.
My father is Shiro Fujimoto and no one else!
I see. So you want to follow Reverend Fujimoto's dying wish?
But think about it. What would you do if you became an Exorcist?
Kick Satan's ass!
What's so funny?
What? Like Satan's son becoming an Exorcist?
This is great! I haven't had such a great laugh in a while!
I'm serious!
Interesting! Very well.
But... Sir Pheles!
Really?
This is a measure beyond the law.
However, Rin. The path you've chosen is not a simple one.
One day you'll have to face your fate and you'll regret not dying here.
I don't care. I'm not a human or a demon anymore.
I have no choice but to go forward!
I'll become an Exorcist!
Welcome to True Cross Academy.
Next Episode Preview
From today, you will be studying here, too.
What the hell?! No one told me about school!
Just die.
Brothers