Lord Jeremiah, how does it feel?
Sitting in the Deputy Governor-General's seat.
What bad manners. Your background will be exposed.
Well, Lord Jeremiah, my lineage differs from yours anyway.
Don't say that.
Once the revolution undertaken by the Purist Faction is complete,
I'll submit a proposal for you to become a baroness.
Baroness...
Not some imitation like a Knight, which lasts for only one generation.
True nobility that your descendants get to inherit.
Yes, Sir!
Tomorrow is Kururugi Suzaku's execution.
I'll leave the details of the parade to you.
I've already checked and arranged everything from the coordination of the television stations to which route to take to the courthouse.
I've established counter-sniper measures as well.
I'll leave this to you.
I must not be shamed any further than this!
Twice I've allowed members of the royal family to be killed...
Huh?
It has already been eight years.
That was the first mission I had as a soldier.
I was assigned as a guard at the Aries Imperial Villa.
Aries Imperial Villa... Eight years ago...
If I remember correctly, Queen Marianne was...
That's right.
Because of the orders from above, a minimal number of guards was placed on duty.
As a result, we weren't able to prevent rebels from penetrating our defenses...
It was the first setback I faced...
I was a man who'd never known failure since I was a child.
I was then posted to Area 11...
The place where Queen Marianne's orphans, Prince Lelouch and Princess Nunnally, lost their lives...
And now... even Prince Clovis...
Lord Jeremiah...
His Highness Clovis... Queen Marianne...
Please laugh at the useless me...
I am...
Please wipe away your tears.
Sir, it isn't like you to say that.
Is that so? That's true I guess...
The way I am now, even my sister, Lilycia, would laugh at me...
That's right. I'm a man from the noble Earl Gottwald's family.
I shall avenge His Highness Clovis and regain our former honor!
Come with me, Viletta!
Yes, Sir!
I shall take hold and seize the future with my own hands!
I will become a Knight of One, the personal sword of His Excellency!
That's right. I'm able to do it.
Since I'm Jeremiah Gottwald.
Lord Jeremiah, why!?
Listen up. Relay this to the entire army.
Let them go, with as much effort as you can!
Let them go, with all your effort!
This is a direct order from me, Margrave Jeremiah Gottwald!