This place was our home for 15 years.
Kids! Dinnertime!
Sure, Daddy!
Today we're having curry!
About how the geezer died...
About me...
Yukio hasn't asked anything.
What could he be thinking?
It's time to leave, isn't it?
I already feel so lonely!
Feel free to drop by anytime!
This is your home!
Sure.
By the way, where's Yukio?
Did he go back to the dorm already?
No, but I haven't seen him today.
I'm scared!
Yukio.
Yukio, come with Daddy...
The Blue Exorcist
sei wo uke sorezore ga jinsei wo ouka
After birth, people live as they wish
nou no black box wo shiru sore wa kou ka
They then learn the black box in their head; is that bliss?
you wa limit line wo subete ryouga
Just cross over, beyond the line of your limit
saa ikou ka fumidasu sore wa kyou da
Let's go, take a step, and I mean this minute
yappa hibi wa ika sen kou sotsunaku konashitecha no no
Life's a bitch, so if it's easy, you're doing it wrong
stop nagare wo mikiwamena mazu mono to mo sezu ikou ze (here we go)
Stop, which way is the world going? Then ignore it and go wherever (here we go)
todokanu mono ya kagiri aru mono ni
There are things I could never have, things with time
atsuku naru mune wo osaetsukeru no wa
Is there a reason I force my heart upon them?
rikai mo sezu osaetsukeyou to shitekita
I never tried to understand, I just forced it on them
ano otonatachi to onaji jan ka yo
I'm no better than those lifeless adults
doushitatte kanawanai esoragoto darou ga
Even if it's just a pipe dream I could never have
mune wo moyasu hi wa dare ni mo keseya shinai
But no one can put out the fire in my heart
sora kara furu kuroi ame ga kono mi nurashi furitomanakutomo
The black rain may pour hard and leave me drenched
mada ore wa kawareru jibun de kaetemiseru
But I know I can change, I will change myself
kore ga sou "pride" sorezore no basho de
This is my pride, what makes up my core
mada mada kieru na kokoro no hi wo
I won't let my fire be put out; not yet
mada mada ikeru zo ikeru zo
I'll keep going, and I'll never stop
Episode 3
szia Brothers
That one-man clown act is late.
And Yukio's not here, either.
That was close! Where do you think you're driving?!
Oh my, what a sunny day!
A beautiful clear sky to accompany you on your new journey!
What's with that car?
Where the hell are you planning to take me to?
To True Cross Academy, of course.
True Cross Academy?
Exactly.
You know, to the general public I'm the Principal of the Academy.
And thus from today you will be a student of my Academy as well.
Sorry for the wait!
I'm glad I don't have to be separated from my dear brother!
Yukio?
Thank you for going through all this trouble, Mr Faust.
Faust? Weren't you Mephisto?
Johann Faust V. It's the name I use in public.
Now let us head to my True Cross Academy!
What's going on?
I asked him to make me an Exorcist...
The hell...
What's wrong?
Nothing...
By the way, where were you this morning?
I visited Father's grave.
Did you go too?
No...
Too late to do anything about that.
We'll soon arrive at the center of True Cross Academy Town.
Welcome to True Cross Academy!
Amazing!
This is the Academy Town with all of our educational institutions.
Please study to your heart's content!
Okumura, change to your uniform.
Would it have hurt to tell me earlier?
You're good at tying your necktie.
I can't trust him.
Yukio's being himself and asking nothing.
Hey Yukio. Were you surprised that a dropout like me got into your True Cross Academy too?
Huh? Sorry, I'm a bit nervous...
Freshmen representative, Yukio Okumura.
Yes.
Yukio's...!
The freshmen representative got the highest grade on the entrance exam, right?
Amazing!
Yuuka, isn't he cool?
Passing through the gates of the Academy I so admired,
I feel nervous just as much as grateful.
That crybaby who always got bullied...
All the more, I hope we will be able to further our skills through friendly competition.
I'm the freshmen representative, Yukio Okumura.
Freshmen! I'll be leading you around the Academy, so please follow me.
Okumura, what faculty are you in?
The Special Advancement faculty...
Wow! And you're so tall, too!
When I grow up, I want to be a bus driver!
I want to become
a doctor!
Huh, you want to become a doctor?
Well, um, that's...
Amazing!
That's so cool! You'll be the best doc ever!
Well... I don't know...
I'm sure of it!
Thanks!
That's right, he's going to become a doctor.
Yukio doesn't know anything.
I can't involve him in this.
This is my problem.
Entrance Hall
What the...?
Is this really a school?
School Cafeteria
There's even a chandelier...
Like in a five star restaurant!
Classroom
Wow, it's huge!
This classroom is just too big!
This desk is even larger than the one in the monastery!
What's wrong with that guy?
What's he doing here?
Well, this would be it for today.
Everyone return to your rooms and be sure to attend classes starting next week.
I just wanted to work after middle school.
I couldn't care less about high school.
I'm doing this just to become an Exorcist!
Oi, where's the dorm? No one told me that!
A dog? Oi, hey!
What the?
Pardon me. But the Principal can't just meaninglessly wander around the campus.
I didn't know Exorcists could transform!
They can't. I'm special.
With this key you can conveniently go to your cram school classes from any door.
Cram school?
Cram school for Exorcists.
While you will be attending high school classes just like everyone else,
the Exorcist training will take place in the cram school.
As a Page, you will study Exorcism.
While the high school classes begin next week, your cram school starts today.
You're prepared, right?
Of course!
But let me warn you.
It is a secret that you are Satan's offspring.
Even if we can cover up your teeth, ears and tail,
there's no explanation for your flames.
Please control yourself.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Great.
Then, shall we get going?
Wait...
Now try opening this door with your key.
Sure.
Ouch!
Amazing!
The first-year classes are held in classroom 1106. Let's go.
Sure.
This way.
Just for today I'll stick around, too.
Damn, this is making me nervous.
Ein... Zwei... Drei...
Let's go.
You can still talk?!
Didn't you want to become an Exorcist?
Isn't that the reason why you're here?
It's so dirty...
I'm Rin Okumura. Nice to meet you.
Who the hell are these guys?
They are going through Exorcist training just like you.
Some of them are yet to receive a Spirit Wound,
and some already have it.
Spirit Wound?
Wounds or illness inflicted by a demon.
You become able to see demons when you get a Spirit Wound.
It is necessary to go through it to become an Exorcist.
Well, you don't need it since you're a demon yourself.
Your teacher has arrived.
Good afternoon. I'm your teacher, Yukio Okumura.
Huh?! Yukio?!
Mameshiba
Baby!
Shiba!
baby-baby-baby babyshiba
baby-baby babyshiba
Baby!
Mameshiba
baby-baby babyshiba
LOVE
Nice to meet you. I'm Yukio Okumura and I'm a new teacher here.
I will be teaching you Anti-Demon Pharmacology starting today.
Nice to meet you!
...to meet you...
Hello!
Huh?! Yukio?!
What's wrong?
Don't you "what's wrong" me!
What's wrong with you?!
Although I'm the same age as all of you,
I've been studying Exorcism from the age of seven.
I finished my studies two years ago.
So please address me accordingly while in class.
From the age of seven? You're kidding me...
He's a genius in Anti-Demon Pharmacology, the youngest person ever to get the Exorcist certificate.
Is there anyone among you who has yet to received a Spirit Wound?
Three... Then let's start the first class with the ceremony of the Spirit Wound.
Ceremony of the Spirit Wound?
He will summon a demon and make it give a Spirit Wound to those who don't have it yet.
Actually this classroom is usually vacant so it has become the nest of goblins.
Are we going to be all right?
Don't worry. They are low class demons without any power in particular.
What's going on here, Yukio?
You...
Hey Yukio!
You are in class.
Sit down.
Could it be that he knew... about Father... and about me?
As I said earlier, goblins are low-class demons-
demons are still demons.
Hey Yukio, explain it!
If they smell rotten animal blood they get excited and go wild.
Wait a sec, Yukio! Explain this to me! Yukio!
What do you mean?
Are you screwing with me?
Guess this can't be avoided.
I'm sorry but please wait outside the classroom while I have a little chat with Mr Okumura.
Annoying brat!
What's going on?
So? What did you want to ask about?
Don't play dumb with me!
What's going on here?! You never told me about this!
I guess you should just explain.
As I said earlier, I became an Exorcist two years ago.
I was training from the age of seven,
under the guidance of Father, of course.
The geezer?!
Then you knew everything about his work?
Yeah.
You were the only one who didn't know.
Since I received a Spirit Wound from my demon brother when we were born...
I've been able to see demons for as long as I can remember.
That's... but why?
Why didn't you tell me anything until today?
I asked you why?!
Let go of me.
Yukio!
That stinks!
Yukio?
Hobgoblins.
There are many of them so they go even wilder.
I'll get rid of them, so you...
We're not done talking yet!
Anyway, what did you think about me until now?
What did I think about you?
It's obvious.
You are a demon, and as such you pose a great danger.
That hasn't changed.
You're such an idiot.
Why did you say you wanted to become an Exorcist?
Revenge? Or...
Or is this how you want to repent for what you did to Father?
If that's how you really think...
You should quietly hand yourself over to the Order,
or just die.
Are you saying it's my fault that he died?
Isn't it so?
He was protecting you all this time.
And I was watching the whole time.
Since Father's body was the only one able to host Satan, he was constantly targeted!
He kept Satan at bay with pure willpower!
He was the strongest Exorcist!
As long as his willpower didn't falter...
There's no way Satan could have possessed him!
You said something to him, didn't you?!
Never call yourself my father again!
If Father had any weakness it would have been you, Rin.
You killed Father!
You're right to call me an idiot, so I don't care what you tell me.
However...
Don't you go pointing a gun at your brother!
We're brothers, aren't we?!
I didn't kill our Father!
If shooting me would make you feel better,
go on and shoot!
Shoot!
Don't think so lowly of me. I won't fight my brother.
What were Father's last moments like?
He was so cool.
He died protecting me to the very end.
I didn't decide to become an Exorcist out of revenge or some complicated reason like that.
I just want to become stronger!
I don't want anyone to die because of me anymore!
I'm scared.... I don't want to see those scary things anymore!
Yukio.
Yukio, come with Daddy and fight.
Don't you want to become stronger than those things lurking in the dark
so you can protect your brother and the others?
Protect... my brother?
Yeah.
It's the same.
Huh?
I became an Exorcist because of what Father told me... I wanted to get stronger.
It's the same as you.
If you really want to become an Exorcist,
this won't be the last time you hear what I just told you.
Just die.
Every Exorcist is after your life.
You should be prepared.
Yes, sir.
Sorry for making you wait.
Let's continue with the class.
What happened?
What's this?
What the hell did they do?
602... 602... Let's see.
Huh? Why are you here?
Are you surprised?
I insisted and they put us in the same room.
Also, we're the only ones in this dorm.
You're dangerous so I have to keep an eye on you.
Keep an eye on me?!
Is this a prison or what?!
Yes and I'm the warden.
You want to become an Exorcist, right?
Then you should be able to bear with this.
You little...
Excellent!
Keep up that spirit!
Now, let's do today's homework.
Homework?
Weren't you listening?
Sure I'll do it! I should do it, right?
Kimi to deatta no wa
It wasn't by chance
Tada no guuzen ja nai
that I met you.
Kore wo unmei to yobunda
This is what they call fate.
Sono hitomi ni utsuru
Reflected in your eyes is
Bokutachi ga kagayaite
the way we keep on shining together.
Irareru youni zutto
Let's keep our gazes locked
Mitsume tsuzukete
so it won't fade away.
(Please be) Dakara moshi kono mune ga
(Please be) Maybe the day will come
(With me) Michi ni mayou hi ni wa
(With me) that we'll lose our way
Mirai e no tobira wo hiraite hoshii
while looking for the door to the future.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off
Michinaru sekai e to
We'll soar high
Mai agarunda
towards an unknown world.
Dakara sono te hanasanaide (buddy)
So don't let go of my hand. (Buddy)
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Tsukanda kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
Ready, ready, ready for the take off.
Yume ga mezasu basho e
Hold on to the bonds we have
Te ni shita kono kizuna
while aiming for
Nigiri shimete
the place of our dreams.
I should think of a class even you could understand...
Every flower that God ever created grows here!
Next Episode Preview
They sneak in through the weak spots in peoples' hearts.
I hate you, Mom!
Get a hold of yourself, damnit!
Garden of Amahara