Immediately go to the World of the Living
and check for the spirit waves
of the Arrancars
as well as the Espada.
Also, simplify the procedures
to execute a Gentei Kaijo!
So, in order to meet
the Head Captain's demands...
Have one of the staff go to
the World of the Living, Akon.
What will you be doing?
I'm very interested in
investigating the Arrancars,
but there's no guarantee that
I'll come across an Espada
in the World of the Living.
Well, I'll set out in the winter
during the showdown.
These are the research documents.
The captain probably just doesn't
want to be bothered with this.
Hey! Who wants to go to
the World of the Living?
I don't want to.
I have a chronic illness.
- Yes...
- Huh?!
Umm...
Can I go?
Tsubokura, huh?
How unusual... You normally
just eat sweets and slack off.
I guess it's okay.
Huh?! Really?!
Yeah... Someone from Squad 4 will
protect and guide you on this mission.
Understood!
Oh, Tsubokura, one more thing...
Huh?
Give this to Third Seat Madarame.
It's the molars he wanted.
Oh! Okay!
So this is the Senkaimon that
leads to the World of the Living...
All right! The day has finally come!
The World of the Living probably
has a lot of sweets that we don't have.
All right. I'm going to stuff myself!
First...
Western sweets! I believe
they were called "cakes."
I wonder how sweet they are
and what they taste like!
Umm...
Hello...
Are you all right?!
Umm... Are you all right?
Owowowow...
Sorry...
I was ordered to go with you
to the World of the Living.
I'm Hanataro Yamada of Squad 4.
I'm Rin Tsubokura of the Department
of Research and Development.
Hello?!
URAHARA'S SHOP
what is this store?
This is Urahara's Shop!
I come here often when I'm here.
Excuse me!
Huh? Isn't anyone here?
Wow! Amazing!
There are so many sweets!
Oh! This looks delicious!
Don't eat that without paying!
Tsubokura?
What are you doing here?
Oh! Tessai! It's been a while!
Actually, for my current mission,
I've come here to research
battle sites with Tsubokura.
As well as simplifying Gentei Kaijo,
even just a little,
in preparation for battle against
the Arrancars and the Espada.
Yes! I've heard about that
from Captain Hitsugaya!
Indeed, we had a rough time
in the last battle
because the Gentei Kaijo
was taking too long.
I shall show you the place
where the Arrancars appeared!
Thank you very much!
Ayasegawa, show them the way!
I'm still not convinced...
Why me?
Captain Hitsugaya said that you
looked like you had the most free time,
so he was going to
make you go with them.
F-Free time?
We're counting on you!
Why does this always
happen to me?
Say, are you finished yet?
I really am busy.
Could you hurry it up?
How is it?
Yes! I've picked up a pattern!
Please take us to
the next place, Ayasegawa!
It's such a bother to
have to walk to get around!
Sorry...
I'm not very good at Flash Step.
I see...
Huh?
What is it?
Tsubokura's gone...
He's gotten lost now?
Here! Thank you very much!
What are you doing?!
We're on a mission!
Well... They were selling
such delicious-looking cakes,
so I ended up buying one.
Ended up?
Huh? But how could you buy one
when you're not in a gigai?
Oh, as for that...
I used this!
This is a machine that can make
a soul look as if it's a physical body.
If you have it, you can
buy a cake without a gigai!
I don't care.
Can you finish up?
A ghost!
This is...
A bound spirit...
Umm...
Can you see me?
Yes... We're Soul Reapers.
That's great!
No it's not!
You seem attached to this store,
but it's dangerous for you to stay here!
Wha-?!
H-Hey, what are you going to do?!
Hollows will come after
a soul like you if you stay here.
Or you'll become a Hollow
and attack your relatives.
Huh?
In order to prevent that,
we're going to send you to Soul Society.
No way! Wait a second!
There'll be trouble if you do that!
Listen to my story!
It's all right! You'll feel better soon!
Please!
Get ready!
Umm... Won't you listen to his story?
That's right! Let's listen to it!
What an amazingly long chain.
Bound spirits usually
cannot move from their spots.
And?
Yes...
My name is Heita Momoyama...
I'm a cake baker who
used to work at that shop.
But I was hit by a car
in front of the shop.
I worked hard every day
training to make cakes...
But you can't make cakes anymore.
You don't have to say that!
Tsubokura, you're unusually
responsive to talk of cake...
So what's troubling you?
Well...it's my mother...
My mother comes to
pray for me here
every morning when
the streets are still deserted.
But lately, she's been getting thinner...
Unable to bear it,
my older sister and her husband
suggested that she live with them.
Oh... Well, that's a good thing.
But...
Despite the fact that I was training,
I never had my mother
eat any of my cakes.
Huh?
So!
I want you to make a cake!
I'll teach you how.
Huh?
I want my mother to eat
one of my cakes!
It's a bit odd, but if you make it
to my specifications, it's still my cake!
Please!
Jeez. I never expected you to say that...
Let's do it!
Huh?!
You just want to eat cake, don't you?
Anyway, let's do it!
We're talking about cakes!
I knew it...
Thank you very much!
- Wow!
A first appearance!
Urahara's Shop's kitchen!
What a nice kitchen...
Thank you!
I consulted with Tessai
and remodeled it just recently.
Try not to damage anything.
Okay...
I have all of your ingredients.
Feel free to use them!
But it's kind of odd for Ayasegawa
to be interested in this as well...
I'm not interested in it!
Let's make a cake!
Yes! I'm counting on you!
This is odd...
But these clothes aren't so bad.
Beat the fresh cream harder.
Yes!
Huh?
Umm...
For some reason my egg
became mushy...
How did you do that?!
I told you that it needs to be
at body temperature!
That's too hot!
It'll become a hot spring egg!
S-Sorry.
Remake it!
Yes!
Don't taste it too much.
Make it smaller.
Like this?
That's too small!
Then you should do it!
I'm asking you to do it
because I can't!
We finished!
Now we can give it to your mother.
Not yet.
Huh? Why?
Because we have to taste it.
Oh, that's true.
If it tastes good,
we'll make another one to give to her.
But I can't eat it...
This is the first time we've eaten cake.
What?!
We don't have them in Soul Society.
Isn't there anyone
who has had cake before?
Umm...
Roar!
Zabimaru!
You're still too slow!
Well, you are getting a little better.
Once more, please.
Here I go...
So that's the case.
So you want us to see how it tastes?
Well, I've had cake before, but...
I know everything there is to know
about the World of the Living.
I'll give it a taste.
Here you go.
We need to remake it.
I probably won't be able to
eat a delicious cake...
Don't say that. Let's give it our best.
Momoyama.
It seems that his mother
is moving tomorrow.
That means that tomorrow is the last day
that she'll come to leave flowers.
Yes. That's just right.
This is good, too.
Things are looking good.
That's good. Yes. It's very good.
Tomorrow is the last day...
Huh?
Let's make a beautiful,
delicious cake for your mother.
Ayasegawa...
Thank you very much!
Then let's give it our best!
All right!
We did it!
If it tastes good, we'll be set.
It's incredibly soft!
I feel kind of happy!
Yes. It's a beautiful taste.
R-Really?!
It's time for your mother to come.
Let's hurry.
Yes!
Excuse me...
Who are you?
We're friends of Momoyama.
We heard that you
would be moving today.
I see. Thank you for looking
after Heita when he was alive.
This is Momoyama's cake.
Huh?
Actually, we made it...
But it was made according to
the recipe that Momoyama taught us.
So this is Momoyama's flavor.
This is Heita's?
It's a bit late, but this is my cake, mom.
Sorry... I can't accept this.
Huh?
Wh-Why?
I can't stand cakes anymore.
Whenever I see a cake,
I always remember him...
It's so painful.
No way...
So...I'm sorry.
Wait, mom!
Give this to me!
Mom!
No way...
My cake...
I wanted mom to eat it.
Wait, mom.
Don't go, mom!
It can't be!
Momoyama!
Calm down...
This is bad. The Spiritual Pressure
is attracting them...
It's coming!
A-A Menos Grande!
What?!
Getting worried over a Menos?
How unsightly!
Oh no!
Yumichika!
How careless of me...
Take this.
Leave it to me,
thank you very much.
Are you all right?
Shut the hell up!
Worry about yourself before worrying
about others, thank you very much!
O-Okay.
Calm down and try to
maintain consciousness.
What's going on?
Mom...
Don't go, mom!
How could you?!
Momoyama!
Get a hold of yourself!
Crap! It's only a Menos...
- What should we do?
- Why won't you
- He's really going to become a Hollow.
- eat my cake, mom?!
Don't, Heita!
That's it!
In this case...
I have no choice.
Hey, what are you doing?
Here I go!
Fill up!
Hisagomaru!
Now, Ayasegawa!
Bloom, Fujikujaku!
Hanataro, what was that just now?
It was my zanpakuto, Hisagomaru.
This?
Yes.
Hisagomaru gets to Shikai
by absorbing people's wounds.
Then it shows its true power.
Then you healed
Momoyama's wounds?
Yes.
A chest hole is a wound of the heart.
It wasn't fully open yet, so I thought
that I might be able to do something.
Hmm? That's not bad.
Mom!
Mom! Are you all right?
Heita!
I'm glad, mom...
Why are you...?
Mom? You can see me?
When did he...?!
Mom, I finally completed my cake.
Then it was true?
Yes. It got a bit smashed,
but I can guarantee that it tastes good.
Yes. It's delicious...
Really?
Yes. Very...
So this is your cake.
Sorry, Heita...
I won't ever say that it hurts
when I see a cake anymore.
Yeah...
The machine you made that makes
souls take physical form...
So it doesn't just work on you?
Yes. It can work on any soul.
Doesn't that mean that we wouldn't
have had to go through all that trouble
if we had used it on him
from the beginning?
I see. Yumichika, you're really smart!
He's no good...
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
I'm back.
Hey... Good work.
How's the data?
It's okay.
Come to think of it, did you give
Third Seat Madarame his molars?
Oh... I stomped on them
when I was fighting the Menos.
So I did as you told me to do.
I put them in a bag
with a note that says that
"they're molars
that only idiots can't see."
Hey... You really did that?!