Odds or evens...?
I'll go with evens.
Odds...
Oops.
I lost.
Tragic.
The captain of the Harusame's 4th Squad
was once considered a lone
flower in the darkness,
but after losing out
in a grab for power,
she stole money from the
group and disappeared.
I never expected her
to come back like this.
No kidding.
I never expected you to be a
sucker for a vixen like her.
Kids wouldn't understand.
We live in an age where everything
fits in the palm of your hand.
But you want a woman who
isn't so easy to hold on to.
Like a DS?
She's more like a Genesis.
I see.
No wonder it was so hard to find her.
We're talking about your
beloved Genesis here.
But it looks like she couldn't
fit in down there either.
She gambled and lost.
And so did you.
Hey!
Don't jump to conclusions.
I'm not like a certain stupid captain.
I don't let my emotions
get in the way of my work.
Yeah, yeah.
Besides, she changed her face
and name when she escaped to Earth.
How was I supposed to recognize her?
Yeah, yeah.
And I'm a Nintendo fan, not a Sega fan!
You listening?!
Oh well.
I was interested in seeing the
exalted team work of the Shinra,
but they were just a bunch of grunts
who stood no chance
one-on-one against a Yato.
Wouldn't be much of a fight.
Anyway, they stole my glory again.
We should go show our gratitude.
To the samurai.
Odds or Evens
Shinsuke Takasugi?
You haven't heard of him?
He signed a pact with us.
He's the leader of the mercenary
group known as the Kiheitai.
Are they from Earth?
They're samurai, I think.
The remnants of those savages
who resisted until the very end
when we opened up their land.
Admiral Assho--
I mean, Admiral Abo.
He must be very special for
you to remember his name.
He only cooperates with us
when our interests happen to coincide,
but he can be very useful.
You could consider them the
Harusame's enforcers on Earth.
They were responsible for
hunting down that vixen.
Oh, really?
However, there is one
issue that concerns me.
I've heard that they are actually
a terrorist group which seeks to
unseat the government of Edo.
But when we struck a deal
with the central ward which
allowed us to sneak into Edo,
they offered to draw the
government's trained dogs
away from us.
Do you know why?
That's easy.
Each side is using the other,
so they're using the Harusame
to get close to the Bakufu and
take down the central ward.
What?! Really?!
I mean, you're absolutely right!
They're plotting terrible things!
Yes, I knew all along!
S-So that's how it was...
Damn!
We finally obtained the right to
strip Earth of its valuable resources.
If they succeed, we'll lose
all our business there.
Well, I doubt that Takasugi person
stands a chance against
the Tendo or the elders,
but he can probably crush our forces.
I-If that happens, the
elders will have my hide!
That's true.
Well, do the best you can.
Thanks for the food!
W-Wait, Kamui!
Why do you think I summoned you here?!
For a free meal?
No!
The 7th Squad is responsible
for cleaning up our messes!
So what do you want me to do?
Dispose of the tools
that we no longer need.
Good grief.
Strong words, coming from a
tool that never had any use but as a decoration.
This place would be much more
comfortable if we disposed of that pig.
Aren't you both four-legged creatures?
Can't you get along, Captain Koro?
Kamui...
You have the backing of
the captains of the twelve squads.
We're ready to throw our support
behind you at a moment's notice.
Admiral Asshole is just
a puppet for the elders.
All he cares about is his own safety.
I wanna work for someone
who will let me run wild.
Then why don't you take control, Koro?
I can't lead.
I just want to go crazy
and not have to think.
You sound just like our boss.
Besides, I have an eyepatch over one eye
and a hook instead of a hand.
I'm not captain material.
No, you're the spitting
image of a captain.
You're clearly gunning
to be the captain.
Anyway, I'm willing to lend you a hand.
If you're gonna take down that
Takasugi fool, count me in.
Don't interfere.
I finally found myself another samurai.
Abuto, isolate Takasugi
from his minions.
Take the fleet and wipe out his men.
Captain Koro, you're
free to help out there.
Here we go again...
Sorry, but I won't let
anyone ruin my fun.
I can't stand space.
It's so dark everywhere.
Can't tell if we're moving
forward or backward.
Lord Shinsuke, are we
moving forward right now?
Sorry about sounding so whiny.
I've been getting worried.
Doesn't matter which way we're going.
If you get lost,
just follow my lead.
Whether you're deep underground
or far above the clouds,
I promise to take you to our goal.
There's no need to worry
as long as you believe in me.
L-Lord Shinsuke!
I...  I'll follow you to hell and back!
We share the same goal.
Let us march on.
Now sign this petition.
We oppose the
Greater Edo Ordinance Regarding
the Healthy Development of Youths!
Before you try to regulate free speech,
you should learn to
regulate your own heart!
Pedophilia predates manga and anime!
Is it not our goal to foster
a culture of acceptance?!
Incidentally, I'm not a
pedophile.  I'm a feminist.
Bansai-senpai.
Where's Lord Shinsuke?
He stayed behind on the mothership
because the admiral needed
him for something.
We're supposed to return
to Edo without him.
Needed him for what?
Well, I haven't the slightest idea.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Was it a mistake to join
forces with the Harusame?
Why are you saying this now?
We will defeat the Bakufu
and rebuild the world.
Didn't you agree to the plan?
But we're out of our league...
The Kiheitai aren't
on the same level as a
galactic crime syndicate.
Soon enough, we'll become their pawns.
The way things stand,
we've sunken to the level of the
Amanto-ass-kissing Bakufu.
Besides, now that the
Bakufu and Harusame
are working together,
we've become a liability.
What if Lord Shinsuke is...
So in other words, you're
worried about Shinsuke?
Don't worry.
That man won't fall
before the Bakufu does.
Did you forget the promise he made?
I'll simply destroy...
...the Greater Edo Ordinance Regarding
the Healthy Development of Youths!
Don't mess up my memories!
Die!
We'll destroy you first!
Master Bansai!
There's a Harusame fleet ahead of us!
What? Do they truly
intend to eliminate us?!
L-Lord Shinsuke!
Hey.
So we meet again.
Sorry about cutting
straight to the chase,
but either way, you're going to
be surprised when I say this.
Please die.
That's not much of a surprise.
It was obvious from the
moment I first saw you.
You're sharp.
You see, I've been dying
to fight a samurai
from the moment I first saw one.
And you kind of smell the same
as that other samurai.
What a coincidence.
I've been dying to kill
that stupid samurai
with the silver hair.
You must have super powers or something.
Is there a secret behind
that left eye of yours?
Kamui!
I told you not to interfere.
I won't interfere.
Huh?
Kamui, we're here to kill you.
Did I miss a message or something?
Nobody ever mentioned that
we were up against such a big family.
You Yato are too dangerous.
A blade that's too sharp will
attract many foes, Kamui.
You got me good.
Never expected Admiral Asshole
to pull a fast one on me.
I'll kill that idiot for you.
So feel free to rest in peace.
Vice-captain!
There's a Harusame fleet
behind the Kiheitai!
It's Captain Koro's 8th Squad,
along with the admiral's personal fleet!
Looks like we were tricked.
Wh-What's going on?
The Harusame are fighting each other?
There's no need to worry, folks.
Everything is going according to plan.
Takechi-senpai...
That is the Harusame's 7th Squad.
The strongest Harusame force, drawn from
the elite ranks of the
Yato, the warrior tribe.
Their leader, the brilliant Lord Kamui,
is more highly regarded
than the admiral now.
The 12 squad captains are looking
to overthrow the admiral
and name Lord Kamui as their leader.
So by that reasoning,
that fool of an admiral
intends to eliminate the 7th Squad,
which threatens his position?
Exactly.
We were used as bait to isolate
and crush the 7th Squad,
the strongest of them all.
So we're being used
by the Harusame again?
It's easier for us to take advantage
of that useless admiral.
But still...
Destroying your own fangs to
hold onto your position...
There are always more fools
when an organization begins to grow.
Friend Takasugi, that
was an excellent job!
There are no longer any
rogue elements to oppose me!
You also performed admirably, Koro.
No, Admiral Assho...
Admiral Abo.
I was simply performing
my duty as one of
the 12 squad captains.
Now that Kamui has been
made an example of,
the captains who supported
Kamui will come
to their senses and swear fealty to you.
It was kind of a waste.
Hm?
That kid took enough poison to
instantly leave an
elephant incapacitated,
but he was able to fend off my blade
while smiling the entire time.
And he managed to kill off
twenty or so of your men,
despite his injuries.
I have a feeling that his absence
will be far more damaging
than what he did to your men.
It doesn't matter.
Your Kiheitai can fill the
void he's left behind.
Sorry, but I'll pass.
It's better to be the head of
a cat than the tail of a lion.
I'd rather be a bandit chief
than a pirate or bigwig.
Besides, I'm not giving
up the Kiheitai name.
Allow me to compensate you...
I don't need anything.
Let's keep it simple, just like before.
Be careful.
He's harder to read than Kamui was.
I know.
No more fooling around.
Odds or evens, odds or evens...?
Odds.
Too bad...
Evens...
Oops, now it's your turn to die.
That gambler's cursed.
If you lose, you run out of luck.
I lost, so I know what
I'm talking about.
Coming from a monster who
doesn't die when killed...
They patched me up and spared my life
so I could be executed in
front of the others, right?
When's the big day?
In three days.
Three days...
I wonder which one of us will die first.
I'm sure you've figured it out already.
The people here only
care about themselves.
Doesn't matter how hard you work.
They'll just abuse you
as much as they can
before they get rid of you.
True.
I would prefer to be used by someone
who isn't so pathetic.
Those sharp fangs of yours
will only rot in this place.
Why did you come here?
I'm the same as you.
Searching for a place to
use my sharpened fangs.
But this leaky boat
won't take me anywhere.
I'd rather hitch a ride on your ship.
See ya, space fighter.
I don't see how the admiral
took out the 7th Squad...
Did he have help from the elders?
No, I heard that the idea came
from Takasugi of the Kiheitai.
It's a sad story.
Those guys worked their
asses off for the Harusame.
Nobody's doing jack for
the sake of the Harusame.
If someone is in the
way, you eliminate them.
That's how it goes in the Harusame.
Men, take a long, hard look!
This is what happens to
those who defy my authority!
When you cross me, you cross the elders!
When you cross the elders,
you cross the Harusame!
When there is no order,
a battle-hardened army will
be reduced to a headless mob!
How can he say that crap
with a straight face?
Kamui, do you have any last words?
Can I say something real quick?
Yes.
Admiral Asshole!
Kill him! Kill him now!
Hold on, Admiral Assho--
Admiral Abo.
Will you allow me to kill him?
Huh?
Unfortunately, I never had the
chance to fight him one-on-one,
but I can at least serve
as the executioner.
On my signal, jump Takasugi.
Our luck ran out when I
got on this leaky boat.
You're saying that we share
the same fight, Earth fighter?
Who knows?
All I know is that neither of us
will be doing any sightseeing.
Sure we will.
Down in hell.
You bet.
Have a nice nap in hell,
leaky boat crew.
Wh-What?!
I told you so.
That gambler's cursed.
I wanted to see which one
of us would die first,
but you're trying to
get us killed together?
It's more fun to dance
with a batshit crazy idiot
than a plain old idiot.
Samurai are a blast.
Takasugi!
You're nothing more than tools
that are no longer needed!
I'll turn you into spacedust!
You're the one who's no longer needed.
Didn't you hear me?
I'm the executioner here,
the only executioner
needed in this place.
Off with your heads.
Lord Shinsuke!
This is how the Joi do it!
I'll follow you to hell and back!
Are you insane?!
You believe that we stand a
chance against the Harusame?
We should be focusing our resources
on the Greater Edo Ordinance Reg...
You'd have to be insane...
...to pick a fight with
the rest of the world!
Accursed monkeys!
What are you doing?!
Crush them!
What?!
Oh?
I rowed out here because I was worried,
but you're looking better than usual.
Blockhead.
The 7th Squad!
Impossible!
Why are they alive?!
Admiral!
Bad news!
Now that the 7th Squad is back,
the other squads are beginning
to side with them!
Th-The tables have been reversed.
Huh?
Admiral!
C-Curse you, Kamui, Takasugi!
You won't get away with this!
A-Admiral!
Why are you running away by yourself?!
Take me with you, Admiral Asshole!
Ah! You finally said it!
I kept pretending that I didn't hear
you, but you finally said it to my face!
You're a dead man!
Get this ship moving!
What are you doing?!
Shut up!
My men always do the work,
so I have no idea what to do!
Don't you have a hook on your hand?!
You're supposed to be a captain!
You're supposed to be an admiral!
Huh?
H-Hey!
What's that?!
Ka-Kamui!
It's not Kamui, Admiral Asshole.
Starting today,
I'm Admiral Nincompoop.
I owe you big now.
Oh well.
Guess I'll have to put off
our fight for a while.
Besides, I'm looking forward
to touring hell with you.
Now, where do we start?
I'm guessing the planet of samurai?
Odds or evens, odds or evens...?
Evens.
Too bad...
Odds...
Next Episode
I Can't Remember a Damn Thing About the Factory Tour
Next time:
I can't remember a damn thing
about the factory tour.