Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
I wonder how long Kurosaki
and Renji are going to train.
Who knows?
Well, we should let them run amuck
until they're satisfied.
Honestly. That fool is depressed
just because he lost once…
Yeah…you're right…
What's with that?!
Will fighting make him feel better?
Idiots sure are simple!
Come to think of it, what happened
between Ishida and Yoshino?
Ishida was really worried
about Yoshino…
Who knows?
The Bounts are our enemy!
What good would it do to worry
about an enemy?!
Yeah… Anyway, we’ve a lot of
questions to ask that woman
once she recovers a bit more…
I'm exhausted…
We got carried away and
now it's morning…
Everyone, breakfast has been prepared!
I even prepared some
for the freeloader!
That always bothers me…
Where's Urahara?
The store owner is in the back
repairing Lirin and the others’ gigai.
Want some coffee?
Yeah.
Coffee?
Thanks…
Here you go.
That's gross!
What are you doing?!
What is this disgusting drink?!
It's coffee…
Don't you know what it is?
No I don't!
Renji, can't you drink coffee?
What a kid.
What did you say?!
Do you want some sugar in it?
Huh? Sugar?
You put in sugar to drink it?
What a strange tea…
Just a little more…
One more…
That's too much!
How much of a sweet tooth
do you have?!
What's this?
It sure is noisy this morning…
Good morning!
Hey! Morning!
Hm? What is it?
It seems you've gotten over it…
It was quite a pain…
This guy was completely depressed…
Shut up! I wasn't that depressed!
Oh?
What's with that look?!
Well, fine…
Let's start from the beginning.
Yeah!
Wow… That looks delicious!
You have a good eye!
I used french toast as a base and
spread melted bean jam on it
in place of honey.
It's bean jam toast!
You're still making things like that…
Let’s eat!
Rukia, do you know
–how to drink this coffee thing?
–It's delicious!
What are you talking about?!
I've already cleared that drink!
Ooh. That's amazing!
Are you surprised?!
A brief rest between battles…
A happy circle of friends.
What a great thing!
What's wrong, Noba?
Are you worried about something?
The Bount…
Oh, Yoshino's presence?
Well, yes. It seems she left
the premises a bit earlier,
but we're all adults who can take
responsibility for our own actions.
It's not something we should
be making a fuss about each time!
Besides, disturbing this
happy morning circle
with troubling information is stressful…
We can tell them later
when things have calmed down.
Yeah.
Master Kariya, I had everyone besides us
head to that location, as you commanded.
I see…
Fixing a broken clock will once again
start the motion of time…
For Bounts, time was stopped
from the very beginning…
Even if our gears are fixed,
and wound up, it will never move…
Humans live with time.
They reject us Bounts…
We just exist. That's it…
The Bounts have time that doesn't flow,
and are despised by humans…
But… We will try to move
that motionless time.
We will change fate ourselves…
in order to do that.
URAHARA'S SHOP
Where are you going?
Are your wounds okay?
You had pretty serious injuries,
didn't you?
Well, it's none of my concern…
Huh?!
W-Wait a second!
What are you doing?!
Don't touch a lady so familiarly!
Where are we going?!
Can you track Yoshino's
Spiritual Pressure?
Yoshino? Is Yoshino
that old Bount lady?
Come to think of it,
her presence wasn't in the house…
Tell me where Yoshino is!
All right…
To tell you the truth,
one disappeared this morning…
What did?
Well…
Oh? Another one?
No. Two?
What disappeared?!
Hmm…well…
Their presence disappeared…
–Presence?
–Yes!
That's right! A presence.
Pre-sence!
Hm? What's this fuss about?
Come to think of it,
Lirin sure is late…
I wonder if she's still sleeping.
–As I was saying…
–What is it? I want to join in!
You've come…
Are you serious?
What are you talking about?
Do you really plan to do this?
Well…who knows?
I'm going to put an end to this!
Oh?
Which way?!
Hey, I'm getting dizzy!
Don't swing me around like that!
This way?
Or is it this way? Hurry!
Stop it! I'm getting dizzy and
getting even more confused!
You said that it still wasn't time yet…
The situation has changed.
What in the world changed?
Are you curious?
It's up to you…
I need your help…
Stop it!
Are you serious?
But I won't let you!
Zeig dih, Goethe!
What do you want, Yoshino?
You're my alter ego, aren't you?
What is this all about?
Do you have any problems
with dying here?
We're going to die together?
All right…
Back here again?
What was that sound?
It seems that Bounts are fighting!
That's dangerous!
Are you running away?
Goethe, calm down!
Yoshino…
Wait!
If you go, you'll just be in the way!
So that's what's going on.
In other words, Yoshino,
Ishida, and Lirin, have left…
What did you say?!
Tell us that sooner!
I've tried many times!
Stop! Now's not the time
to be quarreling!
Damn!
At any rate, let's go after Ishida
and the others!
Noba, do you know
where they're heading?
Yes, I do.
All right! Let's hurry!
Everyone!
What is it, Urahara?
–Don’t tell me you're trying to stop…
–No… But this is a race against time…
Kurosaki and Abarai,
run ahead of us with Flash Step.
We will catch up with you.
–All right!
–Also…
Our goal is to get Ishida back,
we should avoid a fight if possible!
Yoshino!
I'm all right…
Goethe, fight as you please
without concern for me!
Why are you rushing to your death?
Jin…
Yoshino!
It's amazing that you can use
a doll in your condition…
We control this world's great power
with these crests.
But if our balance is lost,
our power goes out of control
and attacks us.
There's no way that
you can summon a doll
or even freely control one
in your decrepit state…
I don't care what happens to me
if I can stop you!
That's wrong…
You really don't know your own worth.
Huh?
Your doll, Goethe, doesn't have
subservient feelings towards you…
He has feelings of love…
That is because even though
we cannot leave descendants,
you're the only Bount
who has a maternal power…
What? What do you mean?!
Quincy boy, I know you're here…
How about coming out?
Y-You! Why did you come?
He couldn't just let
a pitiful woman die alone…
Am I wrong?
What do you plan to do with me…
a Quincy?
A Quincy without his powers…
is useless!
I no longer have a use for you!
But since you’re here…
I'll show you something interesting…
–What do you plan to do?!
–Yoshino!
Yoshino… I can't move…
Goethe…
Over there!
Ishida!
This is as far as you'll go!
You!
You won't pass here.
An important ritual is about to begin…
Ritual?
We won't let things go
the way you want them to!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Guard, Dalk!
Fine… This is boring,
but I'll play with you.
What is this ritual!
You don't need to know!
What do you plan to do with her?!
Yoshino has a maternal power…
Maternal?
From past experience,
I learned that my targeted power
cannot be achieved
by just sucking the souls
of living humans…
And when I researched
the best way to absorb souls,
I arrived at this woman's power!
Be glad! You're going to become a mother!
That's right.
You'll breathe life into new dolls!
Stop!
Yoshino!
Goethe…
Yoshino…
You still want to fight?
How admirable…
Ishida!
What the--?!
Don't take your eyes off me!
The crest is…
Etched in his body…
Jin has…
Fused his own body with his doll…
Well, that's right…
Yes… You were always strong…
And will continue to be strong…
I was only used…
Just a foolish woman…
But…
Goethe!
Yoshino…
I’m sorry…
What do you plan to do?
Do it!
All right…
Come, Goethe…
Yoshi…no…
We're together until the end…
Mama…
Yoshino…
Oh? So you fused with your doll,
as I thought you would…
Let's go…Goethe!
She lost her crest.
But she's not absorbed by the doll…
So this is Yoshino's
maternal spiritual power…
What?
They're floating in mid-air?!
I won't let you interfere!
Damn! What in the world
is going on?!
I'm your opponent!
This power is what I wanted!
But…it would be bad if
I let it wither away here.
Jin!
Stop!
Yoshino!
Don't die! You can't die!
I wonder if I can die now.
What are you talking about?!
Th-That’s…
This is fine.
This way of dying is fine…
No!
What direct eyes…
Thank you, proud, last Quincy…
I was waiting for this moment…
Zeigt euch, neue leben.
Yoshino…
your life shall be newly reborn!
What?!
Hey! Come back here!
Ichigo!
What's that?!
Wonderful!
It's as we planned!
The birth of a new doll!
That's right! More!
More must be born!
Wh-What was that?!
Hey!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
What were those bird-like things?
One of Lirin's friends?
How insulting!
I'm the blue bird of luck!
That's what you think of yourself as?
Aren't you more like a cursed doll?
What did you say?! How insulting!
I'll put a curse on you!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Captain Kyoraku!
Don't come!
Old Gramps Yama took
his time to summon me…
This can't be anything ordinary…
Old gramps Yama…
This is…
What is it?!
Let's go, Nanao…
Huh?
That old man called me,
but he’s sleeping…
Well, he is old…
Tune in again!