became the final confirmation.
When Kira defeated Kibune,
Genryusai acquired the Bakkouto,
the proof of Kumoi's treason.
Genryusai then ordered
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
to storm
the Kasumiohji Clan mansion.
Kumoi ordered his subordinate assassins
to hold off the attack
as he attempted to escape
into a facility protected by a barrier,
but he was stopped
by Yoruichi's efforts.
Cornered, Kumoi tried to barricade
himself in the tower
by using Rurichiyo as his hostage.
Don't do it!
Amagai…
W-What's going on?
What did you just do?
You did a good job…
Substitute Soul Reaper.
What's that…
supposed to mean?
Ichigo!
Rurichiyo!
See you.
What the hell did he do just now?!
I have never seen such a Kido.
Most likely a special technique
used to relocate
while completely suppressing
one's Spiritual Pressure.
That means…
Yes. I hate to admit it, but there is
no way for us to pursue him.
That's not an option!
He has Rurichiyo!
What is it, Amagai?
What brings you here out of the blue
with the Kasumiohji Clan's princess?
State your business.
Can't you tell?
I suppose you couldn't.
You probably never
even dreamed that
someone in Soul Society
would be coming to kill you.
Kill me? For what reason?
Shinetsu Kisaragi…
Kisaragi?
Surely you haven't forgotten.
I have come from hell on
Shinetsu Kisaragi's behalf to defeat you.
Bloom in glory,
Benishidare!
I thought I had completely
suppressed my Spiritual Pressure.
Just what I would expect
from the princess's guardian.
But your resistance
is meaningless.
Silence! Benishidare, Sange!
Princess! Quickly!
Damn you!
Shake, Daichimaru!
What?!
Princess!
Kenryu!
You're safe now!
Princess!
Enryu!
So that is what
your voice sounds like!
Do not be embarrassed!
It is a fine voice!
Come, Princess!
We must move now!
Right!
Kenryu! Enryu!
Amagai… What do you
intend on doing with that?
This?
This is the core of the Bakkouto.
The battles up until now
were for the purpose of
allowing this core to absorb
the Spiritual Pressure of the strong.
And now,
when I feed this to my Bakkouto…
it will display it's true power.
So that's what you were up to.
You were after the Bakkouto as well.
Of course.
How foolish.
Render all things in
the universe to ashes!
Ryujinjakka!
Prepare yourself,
Shusuke Amagai!
How did you…
What have you done?
The ability to cancel out
the power of Soul Reapers…
That is the power of my Bakkouto.
As long as this Bakkouto is active,
all Zanpakuto are useless.
All except for…
my Raika.
Bankai! Raika Gouenkaku!
Are the two of you all right?
This is nothing.
You're still alive?
What's that look in your eyes?
Do you want me to kill you first?
Stop it.
I thought your beef was with me.
Those people have
nothing to do with it.
Nothing to do with it?
You're wrong.
You are not the only one
I am after!
I will kill the heir to
the Kasumiohji Clan…
along with you!
Rurichiyo!
Ichigo!
I'm sorry I took so long.
How did you…find us here?
Sir Kenryu left behind
a Hell Butterfly.
So it made it in time.
Old man!
Why aren't you fighting back?!
Because he can't,
even if he wants to.
My Bakkouto cancels out
the power of Soul Reapers.
What?!
Genryusai's flames
have no effect on me!
Amagai…
I don't want to believe it, but…
Are you our enemy, after all?
Who are you?!
Byakuya, are you done here?
The lieutenants are mopping up
the remaining enemy forces.
How's your end?
We have taken control of
the Bakkouto workshop.
Captain Soi Fon is preserving
the site as we speak.
More importantly,
where is Shusuke Amagai?
Amagai?
He entered the grounds when
Madarame and others first stormed in,
but I haven't seen him since.
What?!
Something happened to Amagai?
He is the true mastermind
behind this commotion.
What?!
At Urahara's request,
I was looking into the on-going confusion
regarding the logistics of Soul Society.
In the process,
I came across the cleverly hidden
secret of the Kasumiohji Clan's dark side.
Gyokaku Kumoi was the first
to create a Bakkouto.
He developed the weapon
by applying techniques used to create
goods for the royal family.
The Bakkouto is a weapon
that forces its wielder to display abilities beyond
that which the wielder possesses.
The resulting toll,
however, is huge.
I don't know where
Amagai learned of the existence of the Bakkouto,
but he approached Kumoi
in order to get his hands on it.
And he was moving forward
with some sort of grand scheme
using the Bakkouto.
To that end, he needed to become
a Squad Captain in order to
gain a grasp of the movements of
both the Soul Reapers and Soul Society.
Imagine that.
Anyway, Amagai, who became
a captain in order to carry out his plan,
began making his move.
With regard to the fact that the shutdown
request for the Restrictive Current
didn't properly go through
shortly after he made captain…
He discreetly
voided that request,
allowing him to show off his powers
to his squad and win their support.
Then he approached
the other captains to gain their trust,
and advocated cooperation between other
squads and proposed training exercises.
However, his true purpose was to
analyze the fighting ability of each squad.
Then, as he steadily
made preparations,
he even took advantage
of an unexpected opportunity.
You mean Ichigo Kurosaki?
That's correct.
He originally intended to make
his move after much further preparation,
but Ichigo's intervention
caused confusion in Soul Society.
He instigated the ambitious Kumoi
and magnified the commotion,
instantly plunging
Soul Society into chaos
by using the Kasumiohji Clan's
assassin squad
and Kibune, his Third Seat,
whom he chose himself.
There was a report that
Lieutenant Kira defeated Third Seat Kibune.
Kira did?
The fact that he defeated Third Seat Kibune
became the final confirmation.
Amagai apparently didn't
calculate on Kira winning.
He underestimated
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
He was willing to go that far?
To what end?
About that…
Shinetsu Kisaragi…
How is it that you
know that name?
Shinetsu Kisaragi…was…
the name of my father.
That's right. My father's name
was Shinetsu Kisaragi.
The Soul Reaper
you murdered!
The Head Captain…
killed him?
Old man,
is what he's saying true?
It's true.
I killed the Soul Reaper
named Shinetsu Kisaragi.
How did you find out
that I killed your father?
After you cut him down,
my father was still barely alive.
That day,
my father was acting a bit strange.
I went to look for him.
Father!
That place was where my father
always trained with his Zanpakuto.
Father?
Father!
Why?!
Please open your eyes!
Father!
Father was down to his dying breath,
but he said it clearly.
That you cut him down.
That can't be.
Old man…
That's right.
This man killed my father,
his subordinate.
Several years after
the death of my father…
I changed my name and enlisted
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
claiming I was from
the Rukon district.
I did it to investigate the truth
about my father's death.
I gathered information.
And then I realized…
"Bakkouto."
That was the last word
my father said!
What was a Bakkouto?
Why did my father say that word?
It took many years,
but I gradually came to understand.
My father somehow came to stumble
upon the existence of the Bakkouto
and was apparently delving
into its mysteries by himself.
Then, in order to find out the truth about it,
he infiltrated the Kasumiohji Clan.
But…
In those days,
you worked in collusion with the Kasumiohji Clan
and were involved in
the development of the Bakkouto.
My father grasped proof of that!
That is why you…
silenced him!
On top of that,
even if there were suspicious activities in the Kasumiohji Clan,
you refused to intervene until now
using immunity as your reason.
I…
I swore revenge against you.
Defeating you was my only thought
as I spent the years training myself.
Then, I approached the Kasumiohji Clan
and obtained the Bakkouto.
I distinguished myself
with the Expedition Unit.
Finally making it as a captain,
I waited for my time of opportunity.
Now is the time for me to
take my revenge for my father!
You're…
Rurichiyo Kasumiohji's fiancé,
Shu Kannogi.
You are Soul Reaper Squad Captains,
are you not?
Yes, that's right.
Why are you here alone?
Please help Ichigo
and the others!
What?
Ichigo and the others
followed Ruricchi and
Captain Amagai to the Head Captain!
Out of my way, Kurosaki!
Shut up!
I've been listening to you
all this time.
You bastard.
That was nothing but selfish babble!
I just told the truth.
I'm not talking about whether
that was the truth or not!
Because of your selfish actions…
other people were…
Do you have any idea
how much pain Rurichiyo was in?!
Ichigo…
Her life was targeted
over and over,
and she went through
one terrifying experience after another.
She wanted to be free,
but there was no time for that.
If you want revenge,
do it yourself!
Don't involve people who
have nothing to do with it!
You stay out of this!
You don't get it, do you?
Move!
You're the one who doesn't get it.
If you want me to move…
you'll have to force me!
Yoruichi, you should've told us
you were here as well.
Sorry!
But it suits me to secretly work
behind the scenes.
How should I put it?
I like seeing the surprised look
on everyone's faces!
Just for that?
Just for that.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Chojiro Sasakibe,
Squad 1 Lieutenant.
Inspired by English gentlemen he saw
long ago in the World of the Living,
Sasakibe tries to
master his tea hobby
by growing tea leaves in Soul Society
and brewing his own.
Huh?!
Lieutenant,
the Squad Barracks!
That wasn't me!