Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
It went that way!
Don't let it get away!
This game of chase is over!
Give it up!
Roar!
Over here!
C'mon, here I am!
Here! Here!
Whoa!
One down!
Zabimaru!
Oh!
You've already finished it off?!
Just as we would expect of
Lieutenant Abarai's Zanpakuto.
You don't say.
This was a piece of cake.
Right, Monkey?
Right. This was nothing
to get excited over…
– What?!
This isn't good!
Let's save them!
I can't pull free!
– W-W-Wait! Wait!
Scatter!
– Ow!
Senbonzakura!
You both let down your guard.
Today, we owe our lives
to Senbonzakura.
I'll say…
He's just what you'd expect of
Captain Kuchiki's Zanpakuto.
He's calm and collected.
And his skills are
beyond reproach.
So different from you-know-who.
Bastards…we can hear you,
you know!
I'll go and give them some grief.
Never mind.
Hurry and finish up
those letters of apology!
Why do we have to
write these things?!
Yeah! Why?!
Shut up!
Then be quiet and stay
in sword form instead!
When you stick your nose into
things, it gets pretty messy!
Remaining in
sword form is boring
now that we're able to
take manifested form!
But what's the use if you
let the enemy get away?!
It's not our fault…
We get our fighting techniques
from our master.
Why does it always
end up like this?
For crying out loud…
It's really a nuisance,
always getting compared to
the Captain's Senbonzakura.
Sorry about that.
Where're you going?
To return the sword,
that became a sword beast,
to the Department of
Research and Development.
What about
your letters of apology?
I finished them.
Man, those two
aren't very likable…
SCREW THIS, YOU IDIOT
Those damn…!
Hey!
Anybody there?
Maybe they're out?
Looks that way…
What now?
Shall we try again later?
That's too much trouble…
Okay!
We're in!
Damn it!
Snake!
What're you doing,
you big butt broad!
Shut up!
Stop complaining and pull!
Good grief…
What're you doing there?
Can't you see? I can't get free…
Ow ow ow…
Senbonzakura…
You guys have sunk pretty low
to go sneaking into
someone else's barracks.
What?
Stop it, Snake…
So what're you doing here,
Senbonzakura?
My master told me to bring
the sword beast here.
That's exactly what we were told.
Seems no one's here today.
Yes…
It seems they're all out
doing experiments.
They're pretty bold,
not leaving someone behind
to watch the place.
Wait a minute…
How did you get inside,
Senbonzakura?
I came in through the front.
You're an intruder as well!
Coming back would
be a waste of time.
Let's go!
– Hey…
Doesn't he seem like
a little kid to you?
Seems the Soul Reapers
don't know his true nature.
This place is creepy!
You're like a little kid. Pathetic.
Oh, that one's empty.
How do you know how to
operate that, Monkey?
I've been here
many times with Renji.
I watched and learned.
It's in!
Senbonzakura…
What're you doing?
Don't startle me.
You made me drop it.
Messing around could
cause big trouble…
– What's going on?!
Damn it!
What just happened?
The emergency barrier walls
have locked us in!
What're we going to do?!
Easy…
Scatter!
– W-Wait a minute!
It's quite sturdy…
– In that case…
– Don't say "In that case"
Don't do anything anymore!
I was about to become
snake sashimi.
These walls are reinforced
to keep violent sword beasts
from getting away.
Right! Right!
So that's it?
Huh?
You're an annoying fellow.
Then what do you
suggest we do?
All we can do is
wait until the people
from the Department of Research
and Development to return.
Oh, I see…
Then we have no choice.
Not yet?
– Huh?!
They're still making us wait?
Hey, what're you…
I can't wait any longer!
– Wait a minute!
I've already counted
to ten in my mind.
You're not in a bathtub!
Let go of me!
Just calm down!
– You're…
Ashisogijizo!
So you stayed behind
to watch the place?
We're saved!
Let us out of here!
Huh?
Seems our voices aren't
getting through to him.
Over there!
Don't you understand?
He understood!
Good!
What the… hey!
He's back…
I'll kill him!
Stop it!
Let go of me, you two!
I'll kill him right this minute!
What did you expect?
We're dealing with Ashisogijizo.
Stop it!
– Stop!
– Curse him!
Okay, Ashisogijizo…
Push the button!
Hurry up and push it!
What?!
Why're you running away?
Did you break it on purpose?
It's because you gave off
a murderous aura!
What're we going to do now?
The remote control's broken…
We'll have to wait
for the people from
the Department of Research and
Development to return, after all…
I told you—
I can't wait any longer!
Bankai!
Stop it!
Get down!
Child's play.
– Cut it out!
What did you do that for?!
That's what we want to ask you!
Destroying everything
doesn't get us anywhere!
To escape.
It needed to be done.
You went too far!
What's that?
The defense mechanism
has engaged.
That's bad!
We'll be locked in again!
Let's get out of here!
Senbonzakura…
is the exit this way?
I don't know.
Then why're you running lead?!
Do you think I'd run behind
anyone except my master?
Don't run out in front
because of foolish pride!
Never mind. Just follow me!
It'll catch up!
Run in there!
Ouch…
Are you okay?
Yeah…
Huh?
Your…mask…
Again?
Oh well.
Where did that spare
come from?!
I feel alive again.
So, where are we?
Looks like the control room.
Perfect.
I'll shut down
the alarm immediately.
What the hell is this?!
No way…
Is this set up to monitor
every inch of Seireitei?!
Why is there such a thing?!
It's disgusting to be able to
see each individual's private life!
Huh?
Hot!
What?
What're you doing?!
You shouldn't look into
an individual's private life.
Never mind.
Don't play with the controls!
What's going on?
Most of the barracks
were built by
the Department of
Research and Development.
It would seem they can remotely
control things from here.
Then we must be careful.
Darn…
Why won't it turn off?
Stop it, we said!
Let go of me!
Seireitei is…
What are you going to
do about this?!
Can't help what's
already been done.
That's not going to help!
Anyway, since you were with me,
you're guilty, too.
Why us!
Joint liability.
– If that's how you feel, then you
– What?
– should apologize to us first!
– Monkey!
Monkey, Monkey, Monkey!
– This isn't good… What'll we do?
– What is it now, Snake?
I think he's angry for
what we did to him earlier!
Do something, Monkey!
Don't ask the impossible!
– Senbonzakura…
All right…
I accept your challenge!
– How could you interpret
– what just happened that way?
Bankai!
Scatter!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You bastards!
Don't you understand
the meaning of stop?!
Bankai!
Hikotsu Taiho!
What the hell just happened?!
Ow ow…
The world is spinning…
Why did you do that
without any warning?!
That's dangerous.
– Look who's talking!
Hey!
– Renji!
Wait, wait, wait…
Who are you people?!
We know you're
the cause of this!
You've destroyed
this entire area!
– Why does it always
– end up like this?!
– All we did was get caught
– in this guy's rampage!
On what basis do you
make such claims?
This all began when you fiddled
with the remote control
and got us locked up!
It was Ashisogijizo that broke
the remote control and locked us in.
Huh?
But you're the one who messed
around in the control room
and caused terrible damage
to Seireitei!
It was the Department of Research
and Development that committed
the immoral act of secretly spying
on people throughout Seireitei.
Huh?
– What?
– But you were the one who
– indiscriminately did Bankai
– and reduced the laboratory
– to shambles!
You were the ones who
blasted the entire laboratory.
– What?
Wait a minute.
Senbonzakura broke down
the front door first and…
But, but we were the ones
who blasted it away, and…
That's enough!
Come on!
Write those letters of apology!
Why do only we
have to do them?!
It's not fair!
Hey, hey…
You still have all these to do.
And you'll need to go and
repair the buildings you destroyed.
What?!
I'm exhausted…
Never mind.
Just hurry up and do it!
I never knew Senbonzakura
had such a short temper…
And he has zero consideration
for those around him.
He's so different
from his master…
No…
I think that's pretty close to
Captain Kuchiki's true nature.
Like the way he'll do anything
it takes to achieve his objective.
Come to think of it…
Byakuya had a short temper
when he was a kid.
He was so arrogant…
So naughty…
R-Really?
Reporting!
A new sword beast has
appeared within Seireitei!
A team from Squad 6
led by Senbonzakura
has set out to put it down!
That's not good!
If he goes alone,
the damage will be severe!
We'll go, too!
Right, Monkey!
Hey! Stop!
Looks like they've become
Senbonzakura's guardians.
They'll suffer.
Now about the issue of
the Department of Research and
Development's spying on us…
I think we can forget about it.
Seems all the data
has been destroyed.
We'll call it even.
What is all this?!
What in heaven's name
happened while I was away?!
Lieutenant Abarai, I'll need
those repairs done by today.
But…that's asking too much!
Did you think that we didn't have
backups of the spy camera system?
Huh?!
We'll expose your embarrassing
moments to the entire nation.
I'll have the repairs
finished today!
Illustrate Guide to Soul Reapers!
SQUID SWORD BEAST
Damn…
What a powerful sword beast!
Sorry to you keep you waiting,
everyone!
Now that I'm here,
you can all feel safe!
Thank you, Caped One!
You were awesome,
Mr. Gentleman!
Okay! That was a great success!
No. Nobody knew who it was.
THE END