Shusuke Amagai was the one responsible
for the string of disturbances.
He did so in order to
assassinate Genryusai.
He joined the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads
so that he could take revenge on
Genryusai for killing his father.
After long years of preparation,
Amagai waited for the moment when
the Soul Reapers were dispatched
to put down the rebellion
by the Kasumiohji Clan,
leaving few people
around Genryusai.
Amagai’s Bakkouto
possessed the power
to render the Zanpakuto of
the Soul Reapers powerless.
After rendering Genryusai’s
Ryujinjakka powerless,
Amagai used Bankai and attempted to
settle the score once and for all.
However, Ichigo arrived and
stood between the two,
whereupon an evenly
matched battle ensued.
Only Ichigo, who possessed
the ability to Hollowfy,
was able to fight without suffering
the effects of the Bakkouto.
After an epic battle,
Ichigo’s Getsugatensho finally
struck Amagai.
Getsugatensho!
No… It can’t be.
I knew it. It’s not over yet.
There is no end.
Until I accomplish my revenge…
Stop it! You can’t do anything
in your condition!
As I told you…
I will not find my answer
until I kill them.
And beyond that…is death!
Th-That’s…
That’s…
Stop it! If you remain like that, you’ll…
Gouen Ryuga, Homura!
Ichigo!
You underestimated me,
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Could it be? The Bakkouto has
not taken control of him?
I am suppressing this with
my Spiritual Pressure.
It hasn’t grown, has it?
You’re next…
Genryusai!
It appears you haven’t discarded
your pride as a Soul Reaper.
Pride, you say?!
You, who spoke of order
in the Soul Society,
but eliminated those
who did not follow your will?
I don’t want to be lectured
by you, Genryusai!
I will take care of
both you and Rurichiyo!
Princess!
Ichigo!
You’re still alive?
You’re a stubborn fellow.
I’m your opponent!
Ichigo!
Rurichiyo, don’t look so sad.
I’m okay.
You should be dead.
Why do you go to such lengths
to keep coming at me?
There’s no reason why you should
save this old geezer!
Shut up, already!
Bastard!
Do you know how many people you
made unhappy just for your selfish cause?!
You used the Kasumiohji Clan,
tricked the Soul Reapers,
and got involved with the Bakkouto.
You think it’s all right
to do anything
if it’s for the purpose of
taking revenge for your father?!
You think the people who cried
because of you don’t matter?!
In spite of the chaos that
occurred in the Kasumiohji Clan,
Rurichiyo made the firm decision
to shoulder that burden and live on!
Rather than run from her destiny,
she chose to challenge it.
She’s not like you,
who chose to run from yours!
I’m going to squash
your stupid selfish revenge!
Can you do that
with the strength you have?
I sure can!
Even if you can hollowfy,
it’s still a fact that your Soul Reaper
powers are neutralized.
That means you can’t bring out
all of your powers.
So what of it?
You shouldn’t underestimate me!
Don’t get so full of yourself, kid!
His speed has increased.
If that’s the case…
Gouen Ryuga!
Got him!
Now!
Homura!
What?!
Got you.
So that’s how…
That was how you blocked
my first flame.
Though I haven’t perfected it yet.
Once I get the hang of it,
I’ll cut down all your attacks!
Then I’ll end this before that happens!
Damn!
I’ll have to do something about
the Bakkouto on his right arm, after all.
He’s guarding his right side.
As I thought, his right side with
the Bakkouto is weaker.
In that case…
His movements have changed.
He’s moving more broadly
from side to side,
drawing my attacks with him and
reducing my attacks from the middle.
However…
Raiendan!
He attacked the ground to
conceal himself?
Is he going to attack from there?
No, from the right.
Getsuga…tensho!
I saw that coming!
What?!
Ichigo!
Lady Rurichiyo!
How's that?
You can’t use that sword anymore!
Curse you!
With this many injuries…
Even if you defeat me and the old man,
you won’t get away unscathed.
It’s useless to fight any further.
Useless to fight any further, you say?!
I told you at the start, this is a life
that I’ve already discarded!
If I can have Genryusai’s head,
that’s all that matters!
I’ll take every one of
you bastards with me!
Stop it, Amagai!
If you continue to feed it any more
Spiritual Pressure in your condition,even you won’t…
I said I don’t care!
The only way to stop people who
won’t listen no matter what I say
is to blow them away!
Ichigo!
Ichigo…
Kurosaki…
For someone who became a captain,
you’re doing a foolish thing.
What would you know?!
Revenge is my life!
Ichigo!
Ichigo won.
Yes.
Not yet.
Curse you, Genryusai.
I’ll get my father’s revenge!
Stop it, Amagai!
Master Genryusai!
Old Man Yama!
Stay where you are!
Amagai!
The Head Captain is not
your father’s killer!
What?!
Your father was a victim,
swallowed up by the Bakkouto.
As you know,
back then in the Kasumiohji Clan,
Gyokaku Kumoi misused
special techniques passed down
through the Kasumiohji Clan
for casting gift swords
in order to develop the Bakkouto.
Then, using prototypes,
he began experimenting on people.
When Master Genryusai
became aware of this,
he attempted to investigate, but…
Cease your intervention
in the Kasumiohji Clan.
Using their political immunity as a shield,
he was denied permission to
investigate the Kasumiohji Clan.
However…
Master Genryusai… Please allow me
to handle this matter.
Kisaragi…
I shall find it and return
with the secret of the
suspicious sword without fail.
Shinetsu Kisaragi…
At the time, your father was
Master Genryusai's subordinate
and an outstanding student.
Master Genryusai ordered him
to conduct an undercover investigation
in utmost secrecy.
However…
A Soul Reaper, huh?
Well, well, you’ll make
a valuable guinea pig.
Stop it!
Kill the person who sent you here!
Master…
Both parties could not reveal
the truth about Kisaragi’s death.
There was the secret of the Bakkouto,
and the undercover investigation
that violated Central 46’s orders.
As a result, Kisaragi’s death
was kept hidden.
Master Genryusai seemingly repaired
relations with the Kasumiohji Clan.
Those were probably
the records that you saw.
Then…
he killed my father because…
The torment Old Man Yama felt after
having to kill his own student…
Can you imagine what that was like?!
No way…
I was consumed by my hatred and
was unable to see through to the truth.
You, and your destiny itself,
seem to have been consumed
by the Bakkouto.
Be careful of the Bakkouto.
Of the Bakkouto…
I did a terrible thing.
So you’re Kisaragi’s son?
You are a lot like him.
Sir Genryusai…
I was a shallow fool in all of this,
wasn’t I?
You need not be ashamed.
Forgive my failure to save
you and your father.
W-What is he doing?!
Byakuya…
Shusuke Amagai still has
his dignity to uphold.
He is a man who became
a captain.
Let him end his life
the way he wishes.
Kira…
Sorry for dragging you
into such a trifling matter.
Captain Amagai…
I enjoyed the time I spent with
you and the men.
Farewell.
Captain Amagai!
Ichigo… I am truly in your debt for
all you have done this time.
I owe everything to your people.
I am grateful.
Forget it. Don’t worry about it!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Thanks to your efforts,
our clan avoided being abolished.
I thank you from
the bottom of my heart.
Sure…
That was the first time you received
a decent thank you.
Shu…
Will you be remaining
with the Kasumiohji Clan, as well?
Yes.
The wedding was called off,
but I…you know…still like Ruricchi.
W-What are you talking about?
I mean, I’m your fiancé…
But, are you sure about this?
Succeeding the Kasumiohji Clan
at your age…
I do not mind.
It is the clan everyone tried to protect.
And I have also made my decision.
You’re finally free of people
targeting your life,
but you’ll be unable
to play freely once more.
What are you talking about?
Thanks to you and the others, Ichigo,
I was able to fully experience
the outside world, was I not?
I will never, ever forget
the World of the Living
and you and the others, Ichigo!
If I have those memories,
I will be fine!
Don’t worry, Rurichiyo!
If anything should happen,
we’ll be the first to
race to your side!
No thanks.
Huh?
Having to borrow your help
would mean
that the Kasumiohji Clan has committed
another mishap like this one.
There must never be another
unfortunate man like Shusuke Amagai.
That is my mission.
Rurichiyo…
The next time we see each other will
be when I’ve accomplished that.
Is that clear?
Yeah.
You can do it.
Farewell, Ichigo!
Let’s meet again!
I’m glad we managed to
get that out of the way.
I need to get back quickly
and report to everyone.
I have somewhere to go,
so I’ll part with you here.
We’re in the middle of the Precipice World.
Where do you think you’re going?
To prepare for the next episode
and beyond.
I don’t have time to explain.
Huh?!
What are you talking about?
Let’s see now…
Welcome back, Ichigo!
Are you done dealing with
the grown-up issues?
Nel?! You’re…
Hurry, Kurosaki!
You have to use Bankai
and get over here!
Here?
What?!
Now we’re all set!
Wait, Inoue! What’s going on?!
Starting next episode, we’ll be resuming
the Hueco Mundo Arc!
Huh?!
– I’m looking forward to it!
– Huh? Huh? Hey!