KISUKE URAHARA
12/31
YORUICHI SHIHOIN
1/1
For crying out loud.
That Matsumoto...
Ditching her duties...
Where'd she go?
Happy New Year's!
I swear, she is such a...
What the-?!
That voice!
Listen up, everybody!
We'll now begin the Women's Soul Reaper
Association New Year's party!
We'll start with our Chairwoman passing
out monetary gifts for the New Year.
Thank you very much!
Such a cute envelope!
It is cute, but... A giraffe?
A cat.
Lady Yoruichi.
Here you go!
Your envelope has a bear,
Captain Soi Fon!
Oh...
And I will also pass out my Squad's
New Year's cards, as well!
Chairwoman, aren't New Year's
cards ordinarily mailed?
HAPPY NEW YEAR
How silly!
Hey, Matsumoto.
Huh?
What's the matter, Captain?
Everything's the matter.
I realize it's New Year's, but you mustn't
neglect your Soul Reaper duties.
Lieutenant!
Hey!
What's with these New
Year's cards!
They're disgraceful!
Please collect all of these unbeautiful
New Year's cards
and make ones that
are more decent!
Huh?
More decent?
HAPPY NEW YEAR
FROM SQUAD 10
Like this?
No, I don't think so.
Look, Matsumoto...
Just a minute.
I believe New Year's card designs are the
prerogative of the person who sends them.
Hey, I was talking...
She's right.
I mean Squad 7 is using Captain
Komamura's photo.
WISHING YOU A
HAPPY NEW YEAR
And it's not even the
year of the dog.
He has nothing to do with
the Chinese Zodiac!
Then what's this?
HAPPY NEW YEAR
Is it the year of the cat this year?
Definitely not!
This is...Lady Yoruichi's.
What's the matter?
There's a New Year's card
for you as well, Yoruichi.
Ah!
Let's have a look.
Oh...
I forgot to send one to Soi Fon.
My preference would be...
That's no longer a
New Year's card!
I'd preferred it if I were
a bit shorter.
Nobody asked you about
your height complex!
For crying out loud!
Why do women keep changing the
subject, Captain Hitsugaya?!
Don't ask me.
There's way too much mixing
of work and play!
Don't you agree, Captain Hitsugaya?
Will you quit asking me?!
I don't think I like what
you just said.
Huh?
Comments that look
down upon women
are absolutely unacceptable,
Captain Hitsugaya!
I didn't even say anything!
First of all, isn't it petty for men to
be making all sorts of comments
over a small thing like
New Year's cards?!
Look who's talking!
Don't go there, Ikkaku.
You can't win an argument
against women.
What?!
Are you saying we women
are nothing but talk?!
Hey, I'm not a part of this.
That's right!
We won't lose to men,
and not just at arguments!
Then I suppose we'll have to
settle this once and for all!
Hisagi! Kira!
As a man, I have my share
of pride to uphold.
What?
You're on.
I'm game.
Hey...
Now, now.
Calm down, everybody.
Since it's come to this,
it'll be the women versus the men
in a fight to the finish!
The First Annual,
Men vs Women: New Year's
Whacky Karuta Tournament!
Why karuta?
Okay, let's begin!
What? Aren't you going to explain
the rules, Chairwoman?!
You know the rules. It's
a regular karuta game.
Okay, the first card is!
It's early morning;
The Third Seat Madarame.
The year's first sunrise.
It's early morning;
The Third Seat Madarame.
The year's first sunrise.
Found it!
The New Year has come;
The Third Seat Madarame.
Large stacked rice cakes.
The New Year has come;
The Third Seat Madarame.
Large stacked rice cakes.
Found it!
He hit the jackpot;
The Third Seat Madarame.
Pachinko ball face.
He hit the jackpot;
The Third Seat Madarame.
Pachinko ball face.
Hey!
What's with these cards?!
I get the feeling you're
picking on me!
That third card... What's
with the pachinko balls?!
It's got nothing to do
with New Year's!
You are ejected for arguing
with a game judge!
What?!
What kind of rule is that?!
I never heard of that one!
I never mentioned it.
THIRD SEAT MADARAME
EJECTED FROM GAME
Year of the Rabbit
Of course, even doggies, too,
wear rabbit ears.
Year of the Rabbit
Of course, even doggies, too,
wear rabbit ears.
That one!
Hah!
Got it!
Sorry about that.
That's not fair!
She has a further
reach than I do!
Not my problem.
Greeting the New Year
saying prayers of long life
for the Head Captain.
Greeting the New Year
saying prayers of long life
for the Head Captain.
It starts with "Greeting
the New Year," so...
Gre...gre...gre...gre...
Where is it?
Gre...gre...gre...
Hey, gre...?
Whoa?!
LIEUTENANT HISAGI TEMPORARILY
EXITS DUE TO INJURIES
Outrageous... So outrageous.
Damn it!
Using your "weapons"
to make Hisagi bleed.
You would go that far?!
He started bleeding from
the nose on his own!
Festive New Year's broth
with freshly pounded rice cakes
Gegetsuburi.
Festive New Year's broth
with freshly pounded rice cakes
Gegetsuburi.
Since it's come to this...
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Got it!
Hey, no fair!
That's going way too far!
Judge! Wasn't that illegal?!
Well...
Zabimaru...
Was that the year of the monkey,
or the year of the snake?
Zabimaru...
Was that the year of the monkey,
or the year of the snake?
She wasn't even listening to us!
And that wasn't even
in 5-7-5 form!
Za...za...za...
Found it.
Worthy of display
Beautiful and radiant
You and New Year's day
Worthy of display
Beautiful and radiant
You and New Year's day
Bakudo Number 4: Hainawa!
I'm taking it!
Hado Number 31:
Shakkaho!
Okay, back to the game.
Now you've done it.
We're even.
Why...is this happening?
LIEUTENANT HISAGI EXITS ONCE
AGAIN DUE TO INJURIES
Putting up a kite
is so much easier with
a good pair of shades.
No you don't!
Bakudo Number 30:
Shitotsusansen!
Okay, now!
Huh? It's gone.
Got it!
What?!
So that one was a decoy!
Are you an idiot?
Now that it's come to this...
Hado Number 58: Tenran!
Bakudo Number 62:
Hyapporankan!
Bloom! Fujikujaku!
I can't keep up with this anymore.
Poor Yoruichi
Not among the Zodiac
Consolation prize.
That card...is Lady Yoruichi's.
That card...
Hey! Wait! Hold on a minute!
I won't let you have it!
Happy, happy!
Captain.
Come to think of it, was there something
you wanted to see me about?
Yeah...
Happy New Year, Matsumoto.
Happy New Year, Brother.
I will try to do my best this
year in good spirits.
The first-of-the-New-Year shrine visit.
I wonder how everyone's spending
their New Year's?
Hey! Slow down!
It's not like the store is going anywhere,
and nor is your New Year's monetary gift!
So slow down, will you?
Hurry up!
Why are you making
me carry all this?!
Because you're a guy!
Can't you even carry one
or two game consoles?
I have to save my energy to
play them when I get home.
It's obvious you're planning to play
these the moment you get home!
Yup!
You plan to monopolize them!
That's right.
No fair! You always
get to play first.
Quit whining.
Stupid!
So that's how Ishida spends
time with family.
Everyone spends New Year's
with their families, after all.
That's so nice.
I'm sure it must be the same
at Tatsuki's place too.
It wouldn't be right for
me to bother them.
Why am I being so gloomy at
the start of the New Year?!
Happy! Happy New Year!
I've got to be cheery!
Why the huge yawn so
early in the New Year?
I can't help it.
Yesterday, Iba and the others made me
party with them deep into the night.
Ichigo and the others would laugh
if they could see your face.
Forget it already.
Let's hurry and finish our rounds
of New Year's greetings.
I want to hurry home
and go to sleep.
Inoue?
Huh? Kuchiki and...Abarai!
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year.
Yeah, likewise.
What're you doing by yourself?
I was thinking about making the
first-of-the-New-Year shrine visit.
A shrine visit?
Yes. But it looked crowded, so I
figured it didn't have to be today.
Are the two of you on your
way to a shrine too?
No, we came to the World
of the Living as part of our
rounds of New Year's greetings.
I see.
I seem to be meeting with
a lot of people today.
So you've already met
with some people?
Yes. There was Kurosaki, Ishida,
and my school friends.
I really shouldn't say "met,"
since I only saw them.
So Ichigo and the others
are nearby? Perfect.
Let's get our New Year's greetings
over with quickly.
Coming, Inoue?
No, I'll pass.
Everyone is spending today
with their families.
I don't think it'd be right to interrupt
their family time together.
Is that what New Year's is like
in the World of the Living?
There are people like me too,
so I think there are all kinds.
I see.
Okay, then let's go
somewhere else.
You come with us too, Inoue.
Huh?
Just a minute.
URAHARA SHOP
Yoisho!
I should've known
we'd come here.
Hi there, you three.
Happy New Year.
What is all this commotion?
We're pounding rice cakes.
Wanted to do something festive
for New Year's, you know.
Why don't you join us?
Oh my, thank you.
Here I go.
Why am I doing this?
Go, Ururu!
Yoisho!
Almost!
What do you mean "almost"?!
Sounds like you want me to get hit!
Aren't you supposed to
aim for the mortar?!
Uh...
Hey... Wait a minute.
Yoisho!
Yes!
Okay, here it comes!
Silly! Why're you hitting
it back nice and easy?!
Pitiful.
You suck, Renji.
Shut up! I haven't had
enough sleep!
Okay, next.
W-Wait... You're too close!
Inoue, aren't you wearing
too much ink?
You're pretty inked up
yourself, Kuchiki!
But...
We're nothing compared to Renji.
Shut up.
Nuts and Star?
What are you talking about?!
Your clothes are all stained,
so why don't you change into these?
Those are...
Wow! Kimonos!
I feel I've totally experienced
New Year's now.
Now all that's left is the
first-of-the-New-Year shrine visit.
A shrine visit, eh?
Shall we go on the
way home then?
No way, not me.
Stop!
What now?!
Now see here, Renji!
Sea bream holds a special place
in the New Year's feast.
Long ago, they talked of "staring
at the sea bream,"
where no one touched the sea bream for
the first three days of the New Year.
There is literature that
describes how,
even today, the custom of not eating sea
bream on New Year's day still remains.
Okay, okay, I hear you.
Renji!
Damn you, that hurt!
What'd you hit me for?!
Damn it! Kid! Watch
where you hit me!
Man, that really sucked.
If I knew this was
going to happen,
I wouldn't have come to make
my New Year's rounds.
Do you really feel that way?
Huh?
I haven't enjoyed New Year's
this much in years.
I'm glad you had a good time.
But why do I always get stuck
with the short end of the stick?
New Year's is meant to be a
time when you mellow out.
That might be true,
but whether you're feeling mellow or not,
it's not fun if you're all alone.
Inoue...
New Year's broth is ready!
The New Year's broth, he said.
Let's have some, Kuchiki.
Yeah.
Come on! You too, Renji!
What?
We'll see you, Inoue, Kuchiki.
Get home safely.
You can return the
kimono next time.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Thank you, Kuchiki.
I'll be going home now!
Wait, Inoue.
Huh?
Weren't we making a
New Year's shrine visit?
No, it's gotten pretty late.
The people are probably gone,
so I don't think it'll be all that much fun.
No, you never know.
But the vendors are probably gone,
and we can't pull our fortune predictions.
Never mind. Let's go anyway.
Huh? Okay.
Just as I thought, no one's here.
But we came all this way,
so let's say our prayers
before we go back
even though we'll
be by ourselves.
Then include us too.
You're all here!
Happy New Year, Inoue.
Kurosaki.
Don't be such a stranger, Inoue.
You could've at least called us.
Ishida...
Sado...
Happy New Year, Inoue.
Happy New Year.
Looks like you made it in time.
You're starting off the
New Year like a taskmaster.
Thank you.
Come on, let's do it.
Let's get it over with.
I want to go back and sleep.
You just won't admit it, will you?
Huh?!
I pray for another enjoyable year
together with everyone.
Ichigo!
What, Rukia? You're small!
Oh, it's you again, Rukiruki.
Then this must be a dream.
This is not a dream!
And I'm not Rukiruki either!
Ow! Don't poke me.
Now let's go!
Go where?
The castle.
What are we doing this time?
Monster.
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers.
This sure was an eventful year,
wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Well then, shall we put
on the finishing touch?
Happy Birthday, Yoruichi!
Happy Birthday, Kisuke!
No one remembered
again this year.
Kind of sad, isn't it?