Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
The dustiness of Rukon District
hasn't changed at all…
Hey!
You!
You again…
What a coincidence…
Well, that's fine…
Zeig dih, Nieder!
Here I go!
What's this?
You don't even have a zanpakuto?
She's gotten stronger…
significantly stronger than before…
There's one!
Rukia, there's no way you can beat her.
You don't even have a sword…
Humph… Worthless trash…
From what I've heard…
it sounded like Mabashi
took good care of you…
You sure are cute…
It's making me excited…
Silence!
Oh?
You want to fight?
My, my. Another fight?
I was in the middle of
my afternoon teatime…
Didn't I tell you not to call me
when my mustache is at its thickest?
Don't complain and follow my orders!
I'm going to go all out!
You idiot! A Bount talked you into this…
Don't get emotional!
And what in the world
do you plan to do
with a decrepit looking sword?!
Not going to do anything?
Then I'll go first!
I-It's begun!
Here we go!
She got me!
I'm going to get you back!
What?!
Oh, Rukia!
In your current state,
you're no match for her!
Why don't you run away?!
You cannot defeat me!
You might not even be able
to touch me…
You shouldn't underestimate me
too much!
That's a nice expression…
Let's all torment her!
Beautifully!
With perfect techniques!
We'll torment her!
Aw…Jeez!
I can't watch any longer!
Wh-What's this?!
What are you doing, Rukia?!
Stop wasting time and
defeat her already!
Lirin--!
All right!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh, all creation, flap of wings.
The one who carries
the title of human!
In the name of truth
and temperance,
dig your claws into
the wall of sinless dreams
Hado 33! Sotatsui!!
Why didn't you defend yourself?!
You're still naive…
What is she doing?
Did she give up already?
That's…
Could it be that
she's absorbing reishi…
She absorbed reishi…
Stupid Rukia, run away!
Lirin…
S-S-She's become a monster!
This taste…
No matter how many times I taste it,
I can't get enough of it…
Quickly! Run away quickly!
This way! This way!
What's this?!
Was that on purpose?
There's a thin line between sadism
and masochism!
Look out!
Take a look at the result of devotion!
This is the splendor of my life!
Rukia!
It's pointless to escape…
Don't make me say it
over and over!
An illusion?!
So you're responsible for them!
I never thought
you could trick me twice…
Save me!
So what do you want me to do?
Do you want me to let her escape
and fight you in her place?
Huh, runt?
Hado 4!
Byakurai!!
Rukia!
You saved me, Lirin…
You diverted her attention…
Huh? Well…
That's pretty good…
The fun's just beginning…
H-Hold on a second…
She's really a monster!
She's incredibly dangerous--!
Save me, Ichigo!
We were able to learn new information
concerning the Bounts
from old documents owned by
the Kuchiki family.
Therefore, I shall report it here.
Oh?
At one time…
There were many experiments
performed here in Seireitei
which are now forbidden…
It was well before the establishment
of the Department of Research
and Development…
Rantao, a scientist known
as the Evil Researcher,
became the leader of
these experiments.
The experiments involved eternal life.
But an unexpected accident happened…
that affected a portion of souls
in the cycle of rebirth.
A mutated strain of humans with
abnormal abilities were born
in the World of the Living…
Those are the Bounts…
And after the accident,
Rantao took responsibility and
was banished from Seireitei.
The Bounts were purged
so as not to cause harm to
the World of the Living…
Cause harm to
the World of the Living, huh?
Well… It sounds as if some superior
wanted to conceal this
in order to defend his own interests.
Kyoraku!
It doesn't matter…
Whatever the case, this is the result
of what we have created…
It seems the Bounts really came to
Soul Society for revenge…
But…
Whatever their reasons,
we must annihilate the Bounts.
In regards to this event,
at the moment…
Soul Reaper substitute Ichigo Kurosaki
has entered Soul Society
from the World of the Living.
Well now… He sure works hard…
I've come to inform you!
Just now, Bount waves and Squad 13's
Rukia Kuchiki's Spiritual Pressure
have been detected!
Open the gates!
Hurry! We're headed to
East Rukon District Area 43!
Kuchiki, we're going now!
Kurosaki!
What's wrong, Inoue?!
W-W-We found them!
A-A Bount's presence!
This is bad!
What?!
Hado 4! Byakurai!!
What happened?
It seems that your power's
a lot weaker than before.
I'm surprised…
I didn't think you had
that kind of power left…
So what are you going to do?
We're going to corner her splendidly!
And finish her off perfectly!
That's right!
What?!
Bakudo Number 1!
Sai!
All right, I stopped her movement!
Hado 33!
Sotatsui!
Impossible. She's unharmed?!
You sure don't give up…
Well… It's good; the fun lasts longer…
Lirin?!
Rukia, this way, this way!
Wait a second…
Here, take this!
I picked it up for you!
What's up with that?!
What's wrong with your arm?!
You can treat it a little better with
the kido you're so good at, can't you?!
No… Well, I can, but…
Rukia, could it be that
your Spiritual Pressure is completely…
What's wrong?
You didn’t run away in time?!
– Rukia!
– She’s here!
Take these children and run away!
Huh? Huh?! But that means…
Quickly! First, get these children to
a safe place…
Lirin, this way!
Throw away your sword!
Let go of her!
That depends on you.
I have a lot of patience,
but I'm reaching my limit…
Rukia…
I'll crush this girl's head
if you do anything funny!
Stop!
Don't you care
what happens to her?
How naive…
It makes me excited just thinking
of how to finish you off!
Rukia!
It's finally over!
I don't really like to torment.
Do it together.
I'm going to slice her up to the point
where flesh and blood are
indistinguishable from each other!
Roger!
Stop!
Stop! Stop that!
You sure are noisy!
Ichigo…
Ah, I'm beautiful right now!
Just look at the perfection
of this technique!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Rukia!
Byakuya…
Inoue!
Take care of that girl!
I'm going to take care of Lirin!
All right!
Kuchiki!
Why it's Captain Kuchiki!
Quickly, get the Med Crew!
Yes!
How is she doing?
It's all right. She's just unconscious.
Then take care of Lirin!
It seems pretty bad!
Ichigo…
You gave it your best…
Inoue is coming right now…
Big Brother…
– My role ends here!
Wait!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather
trust and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won’t get started if you don’t act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Rukia's older brother sure came
at a good time.
Do you suppose he was waiting
for the best time to appear?
How shrewd.
He really knows how to make
an effective appearance.
It seems that he's not just
a rich boy from a good family.
Don't blame me
if he slices you up later on…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers…
– Golden!
What a nice moon.
Beautiful!
Well, have a cup of sake.
Oh, thanks.
Moon watching should always
be like this!
Wow… That's a good way to drink!
All of you, cut it out!
It's all smooth!
Tune in next week!