You there, Ukitake?
Yeah.
What’s going on
that made you ask me to meet you here?
Something’s been bothering me.
So I thought it’d be better to meet
where there was no one around.
Is it about Ichigo?
Yeah.
Something about this incident
doesn’t sit right with me.
Agreed.
How should I put it?
Everything seems too perfect.
Yeah…it does.
So, what do we do?
Yeah…
We may need to take another look at
this incident from the beginning.
Both Kurotsuchi and Zaraki,
who disappeared in the
Precipice World earlier,
returned safely.
Captain Kurotsuchi,
report on what happened
in the Precipice World!
Just thinking about it
makes my skin crawl!
I will never forget that impudent face!
Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
He interfered with us inside
the Precipice World!
He trapped us there!
Not even capturing and rebuilding him
would be enough for me!
Captain Zaraki,
did you see him as well?
You think I’d make a mistake
about Ichigo’s presence?!
There’s the Combat Pass
Captain Kuchiki obtained.
Circumstantial evidence of Kurosaki’s
crimes continues to increase,
and he shows no intention
of turning himself in
and explaining himself.
Now just a minute!
Isn’t it premature to
draw such conclusions?
I don’t believe Ichigo
would do such things!
Captain Ukitake…
I find it hard to believe that
Kurosaki is responsible as well.
That is precisely why we need to hear
his side of the story!
What naïve nonsense is that?!
That man is, without
a doubt, the culprit!
Even during his battle with Aizen,
he was secretly doing something
in the Precipice World!
We must quickly capture and interrogate him
by whatever means necessary!
Okay, okay, calm down.
The Soul Society owes
Ichigo Kurosaki a debt of gratitude,
but we cannot clear him of
suspicion because of that!
Send a team to the World of the Living
to capture Ichigo Kurosaki immediately!
I don’t think they can afford such a
large-scale effort
just for Ichigo alone.
Kyoraku!
Yeah…
It looks like they’re
about to move out.
Open the gate!
Nozomi!
Everyone else went to bed.
You should also…
What is that?!
Kon! What's wrong?
That stupid Nozomi!
Damn!
She tied me up all of a sudden!
What’s she up to?!
Nozomi!
Miss Kujo!
Kujo!
Found her?
No.
She couldn’t have gone too far.
We can’t follow her
Spiritual Pressure.
Is she really a Soul Reaper?
Ichigo!
Rukia! Did you find her?
No, not yet.
The lieutenants are also
looking for her, but…
Kon says she appeared
to be looking for something
yesterday as well.
Damn!
The captains are preparing
their next course of action.
We can’t afford to be
running around like this!
What just happened?
Looks like a Senkaimon opened.
I sensed the Spiritual Pressure
of several captains.
What bad timing!
Anyway, we need to hurry
and find Miss Kujo!
Yeah!
Kon!
Of all the times for him not to be here!
And I don’t have my Combat Pass.
Rukia, I’m counting on you!
Leave it to me!
Ready?
Okay! Let’s go!
You can run all you want,
but it’s futile.
You idiot.
What are you doing in
a place like this?!
How did you know I was here?
Huh? Beats me!
I just knew!
Don’t underestimate my intuition!
But man, why are you so
intent on being alone?
Do you hate us that much?
Or what?
Do you have some objective?
Well?!
It’s none of your business!
They’re coming!
Damn it! Wait!
Hey!
Come back here, you!
Nozomi Kujo should be with
Kurosaki and his allies.
If we check every strong
Spiritual Pressure in this town,
we should run into them.
I already knew that.
But are you sure about this?
Our perceived duty is to
capture Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ignoring orders from
the start for the sake
of Kageroza’s personal
request is not a good idea.
Not an issue.
Whichever we give priority to,
the distance to our goal is the same.
Neither suits me.
But since we’re already here,
wouldn’t it be fun to
fight with the originals?
Yes, it would.
I’m interested in my original as well.
I’m not interested in you!
You?!
You’re…
The originals!
Let’s get rid of these guys!
We have the advantage in numbers.
What was that, Hisagi?!
We always fight one-on-one!
This is not the time for…
There’s no disadvantage in numbers!
Including me, it’s four against four.
This is the record of recent
traffic through the Precipice World.
Showing it to you is
actually prohibited.
Please make sure
no one sees you and look at it here.
Sorry about this.
Ukitake didn’t keep a copy
of the records of his
subordinates’ passage
through the Precipice World.
I’ve got to put together a report,
but without his squad’s records,
we could get in trouble.
Huh?! Just a minute!
No, never mind. Th-That’s right!
Anyway, if anyone sees us here,
I’m the one who gets reprimanded.
Sorry, sorry.
I’ll treat you to
something next time.
I’ll be waiting, but not hopeful.
Well, if you’ll excuse me.
Bye bye.
Hey, Kyoraku!
Now, let’s get started.
Here they come!
Who are you?!
Who cares?
Now it’s four against four!
Now we can fight face-to-face
without holding back!
Then let’s each fight
our own imposter.
Huh?
But I don’t have an imposter,
so now I have to fight this guy?!
Man! What is that Shihakusho?
And…that weird scarf…
Huh?
What’s the matter?
That scarf…
I’ve seen it before.
Yeah, you probably have.
What?!
I’ll tell you where
you’ve seen it before!
Smash’em, Gegetsuburi!
Gegetsuburi?!
That means you’re…
That’s right!
I am…
Marechiyo Omaeda!
Huh?
You’re…me?!
He’s totally different than you!
What the hell happened?
How would I know?!
More importantly… Hey, you!
What’s with the outfit?!
Are you making fun of me?!
You’re so darned ugly that I
refused taking on your body!
What?!
They allowed that?!
They did!
And now, as the new Omaeda,
I’m going to eliminate
you from this world!
What’s with that?!
That’s priceless!
Why not?
You are ugly, so why not
have him take your place?
He can be the real one and
you can be the imposter!
How dare an imposter
take me for a fool!
Smash 'em, Gegetsuburi!
Hey!
You can't lead the charge without me!
I'm coming too!
Me too!
Hey guys, take this seriously.
Huh?!
Hey!
What the hell?
His Gegetsuburi is way bigger than mine.
Naturally!
Because everything about me…
is superior to you!
That’s cheating!
Beautiful.
I’m able to see my form, which I had
never seen outside of a mirror,
in three-dimensions.
Indeed, seeing myself
like this is not bad.
Extend, Hozukimaru!
Just as I expected of me!
You’re good!
So are you!
Say, Ikkaku.
Would you mind doing me a favor?
What, Yumichika? Can it wait?
No, it can’t.
It’s very important.
Never mind.
Concentrate on the fight!
I can’t do that!
Huh?!
Because I can’t damage
such a beautiful me!
So please, Ikkaku, swap with me!
Not my problem!
What kind of movement is that?!
With your body,
it’d be faster if you rolled!
Shut up!
I didn’t tumble! That
was a martial arts move!
Whatever!
Hisagi!
I want to say you
did well blocking that
last attack, but…
Why won’t you do your Shikai?
You’re not still afraid of
your Zanpakuto, are you?
That’s naïve.
In a fight, power is a necessity.
That is why I have no hesitation
in using this power!
You originals suck!
The outdated old model needs
to step down right now!
Reap…
Kazeshini!
Too easy!
What’s wrong with you, Hisagi?!
Unlike me, your opponent uses
the same exact weapon as you do!
Shut up!
Remember what Captain Kurotsuchi said?
Reigai possess exactly the same
power as us, the originals,
but there is one difference.
The difference is that they
are more belligerent.
As the battle progresses
and becomes more and more bloody,
that characteristic
becomes more pronounced.
Which means they can go beyond
their limits from the start?!
Damn! We’ve got to do something.
Oh…I know just the thing.
Hey Hisagi, do as I say!
What’s the matter?
Did you decide to give up?!
Unfortunately no!
If you guys apologize now,
we’ll spare you!
Man, you never learn.
What?!
How was that?!
Why you…
What the—?!
I see.
Your Gegetsuburi seems to
have gotten not only bigger,
but heavier as well.
When your movements are
that heavy and slow,
capturing you is easy!
You bastard!
I’m your opponent!
You guys underestimated us!
You relied too much on your power!
You call yourself Stealth Force?!
Bastards! That was a dirty trick!
Bakudo 62: Hyapporankan!
Damn it!
I never thought I’d lose to this pig!
What’s up with that stupid
look on your face?!
Shut up!
Hado 63: Raikoho!
I can use a technique like that?!
Run!
That Spiritual Pressure just now…
Someone is fighting nearby!
Why?!
Did you think that, like you,
I wouldn’t be able to attack myself?
You’re mistaken.
When I see you,
I think you’re beautiful,
just the way you do.
But…
Am I the only one who thinks
you’d look even more
beautiful covered in blood?
Just as I thought.
You look more beautiful
covered in blood.
I wanted to try it once,
but I didn’t want
to damage my own body.
I’m glad you were available!
Looks like they’re about
done over there too.
Is this all the power
the original’s have?
Damn…you…
What should we do?
Shall we finish them off?
It’s a bother, but let’s do that.
You’re…
Are you guys…Reigai?
Oh, you know of us, do you?
Don’t move!
Shut up!
Stop it, Ikkaku.
There’s no point in fighting
these weaklings anymore.
We should start looking
for Nozomi Kujo.
You’re right!
Stop!
This is definitely odd.
But who from here would…
Oh, it’s you, Inaba.
What’s with that outfit?
Hey…
What’re you—
It would seem this
shows signs of having been altered.
Then someone from Squad 12 must have…
Huh?
What is it?!
Shunsui Kyoraku!
We’re taking you into
custody on suspicion of
altering Precipice World records!
What?!
Okay, so that’s how they’re
going to play this.
The original Omaeda was nothing!
I, the Reigai, am definitely
more handsome and stronger!
Yeah…
Hey, Hisagi!
Don’t hesitate to
ask for my help, ok?!
Yeah…
Soon, I’ll even become captain!
Actually, I don’t really care.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Now then, about our next operation…
Why are you in charge?
Kageroza is a member of my squad!
I’m the one who plans the operation!
Operation?!
-No using petty tricks!
-Ouch, that hurts.
-You guys will just be…
-Hey, it hurts.
in our way!
Calm down, everyone.
Captain Komamura?!
What’re you howling for?!
That’s not right!
Why can’t you understand this?!
As I was trying to tell you, that won’t work!
You wanna fight right now?!