Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who
keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Ichigo and Toshiro's advance
troops barely defeat
the Arrancar that Aizen had created,
but both sides suffer
a lot of damage.
Concerned that they cannot defeat
the stronger Arrancars as they are,
the Soul Reapers all decide to
prepare themselves after the battle.
Uryu and Sado also begin training
to become stronger.
Meanwhile, Ichigo,
sensing that he cannot
suppress his inner Hollow,
visits the Visored.
I'm surprised you knew
where we were...
...Ichigo.
Your coming here means that
you've decided to join us, right?
Nope!
I'm here to take advantage
of you guys.
I won't join you guys, but...
I want you to show me how to...
...suppress the Hollow inside me!
Is your barrier all right, Hachi?
It is not all right...
Cut it out!
You still don't understand?!
I keep telling you not
to be scared, Ichigo!
I'm not scared.
I'll tell you something useful.
Use your Bankai.
Shut up.
I know...
You think that if you
use your Bankai
against someone as
powerful as I am,
you're suddenly going to lose
control of your inner Hollow.
You're scared, aren't you?!
I said, "Shut up!"
Baldy...
I get annoyed when I look at you!
You keep getting nervous!
I've had enough!
If you hate this so much,
then do whatever you want!
You don't have to use your Bankai
or turn into a Hollow!
I'll just finish you off...
And it'll be over!
Think...
How can she become a Hollow
and still remain conscious?!
How can she put on and
take off that mask?!
I'm fighting her in person!
I can watch her as much
as I want!
If I watch her and think about it,
I should understand!
That's why I came here!
I won't use my Bankai...
I won't turn into a Hollow...
I won't open up
my soul to him.
Ever again.
That's enough.
You don't have any complaints,
do you, Hiyori?
You understand now don't you, Ichigo?
Your Hollow can't be suppressed
just by thinking about it
with your mind and body.
You pass!
We're going to pound knowledge
of how to suppress your Hollow all
the way into the heart of your soul!
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Ichigo's not coming back!
Shut up... It'll be all right.
He'll come wandering back after
two or three days.
How can you be so calm?!
It's got to be a kidnapping!
A crime's been committed!
What's this?!
What's wrong, Yuzu?!
You're crying!
J-Just wait a second, Yuzu!
I'm going to show you
my killer one-shot gag!
Umm... I do this, and...
I'm a mustachioed man!
You were always
a mustachioed man!
Rukia, how was it?
Did you find my brother?
No...
I'm sorry.
I see...
I don't even sense any trace
of his Spiritual Pressure.
Where did you go, Ichigo?
Brother...
Tsk... Don't make this kid cry.
What a hopeless big brother...
Lunch is late...
Hiyori, make something to eat.
Baldy!
Why do I have to
make something?!
Even if I did, I wouldn't let
you eat it, baldy!
Love, did you hear
Prince of Darkness's new song
that just came out?
Anyway, Rose, did you read
this week's Jump?
No...
- You never let me read it anyway.
- This is amazing!
Lisa, make sure you look
after that Soul Reaper.
I'm watching him!
Shut up!
You're not watching him!
You're just looking at
swimsuit models!
Shut up! Go away!
Don't interrupt me!
You're on duty today, right?
I just have to shout out, right?
All right...
One, two!
One, two! One, two!
- One, two!
- Lunch sure is late...
- Baldy!
One, two!
I can't...do this!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'll slap you around if
you act stupid, baldy!
Th-That's my line...
That's what I'd like to say!
You bragged about
how you were going to
pound in the knowledge of
how to suppress the Hollow within me.
So why do I have to row
for more than a day
on this clearly handmade,
beat up, silly machine?!
Are you stupid?!
Or rather, am I stupid for rowing
on it like you told me to?!
That's right! You're stupid!
You're the only stupid one!
- And you're bald!
- We're back...
- Ah, thank you!
- We finished training,
so stop blabbing
and listen to us, baldy!
Shut up with the "baldy," fangs!
How can you consider
this training?!
If you think I'm talking
about your hair, you're wrong!
- I'm saying you're wearing a bald wig!
- I bought you lunch...
- Also, my fangs are
- Do you want to eat it now?
- my most attractive feature, baldy!
- Ah! I will!
You called me baldy again!
How is Berry?
He's fuming.
Hmm...
It seems like he doesn't like
the Super Hiyori Trainer.
What?! Only now?!
I don't think that Hiyori explained
the trainer very well.
Why you...
I feel the same way...
She always says one
or two things too little.
Don't complain.
Row until you collapse!
Why you...!
Wait, Ichigo...
The Silly Hiyori Trainer...
"Super!"
...is the foundation of your future training.
Foundation?
The level of your training
is determined
by how long you can row
on that machine.
What do you mean by "level"?
It's as Hiyori says.
Don't complain.
Keep rowing on the Silly Hiyori Trainer.
Want me to make you
say it, baldy Shinji?!
I'll hurt you, baldy Shinji!
We'll teach you how to control
your Hollow transformation...
When you are able to row
on that machine
for at least three days straight.
N-No way!
I'm bound to row on this thing
for three days or even a week!
I can tell after rowing on it all day!
A person expends an incredible
amount of spirit energy
just by touching it.
That's what it's made to do!
Your plan is to see how many days
it'll take for me to collapse,
so you can measure my maximum
spirit energy capacity, isn't it?!
But with my current spirit energy,
I'll definitely go for at least five days!
There's no point in measuring!
Teach me how to control
my Hollow transformation!
I don't have time!
I don't have time to be playing around
with you Visored!
Shut up!
You don't have time?
That's surprising, coming from
someone who doesn't know
about the Hogyoku's awakening time.
Wait... What did you just say?
I said, stop blabbing when
you don't really know anything
about the Hogyoku or
about Hollow transformations!
What's this? How do you know
about the Hogyoku?
We know about the Hogyoku,
the Arrancars, and Sosuke Aizen...
We've known all about them
for many, many years.
I'll tell you the details another day.
I thought that I should take my time
and get your soul prepared our way...
But when I think about it...
You became a Soul Reaper,
got your Shikai,
and got your Bankai
at incredible speed.
How do you know about that?
I see...
As you say, it might be better for you
if we just teach you how to
transform into a Hollow.
Here I go, Ichigo.
Don't regret it...
Hachi, build a double barrier.
Yes.
Can you hear me, Ichigo?
Right now, you are going to undergo
a complete Hollow transformation.
Don't get eaten! Consume it!
If you get eaten up...
...it's all over.
Hachi, place a barrier here, too.
What?
Don't say that!
It's not cute when
an old man says it!
Also...
Place seals all over Ichigo's body.
Yes.
Wall of iron sand, monk-like tower,
the shimmer of burning iron,
unmoving and silent until the end...
Bakudo 75!
Gochu Tekkan!
Hey...
It's been a while... King...
What's wrong?
You look pretty gloomy...
Where is old man Zangetsu?
You bastard...
I don't understand.
When you talk about Zangetsu,
are you talking about
the one that you're holding?
Or...
...is it the one...
...I'm holding?
A white Zangetsu...
You asked me where
Zangetsu was, didn't you?
I'll answer you.
I'm Zangetsu!
It's here!
Say, shouldn't we hide
his zanpakuto?
There wouldn't be any point.
That would just make him
more frantic!
Hachigen, open this up.
I'm on duty today.
I'll go first.
Yes.
Don't kill him.
Only if I don't die.
I'm Lisa Yadomaru.
Pleased to meet you.
You bastard! What did you do
to old man Zangetsu?!
How persistent!
Don't make me keep saying it!
I'm...Zangetsu!
Ichigo... I'm not sure if you know...
but Zangetsu and I...
ere one to begin with.
Both Zangetsu and I are your power.
I was a part of Zangetsu.
Even though we all share
a single body,
outlooks change depending
on who's in control.
If life is in control, you have flesh.
If death is in control,
you become bones.
It's the same reasoning.
My power has increased,
control has switched over to me,
and Zangetsu has become a part of me.
The more you try to draw
out Zangetsu's power,
the easier it's become to
control your soul!
Is that so?
Then that means that
if I defeat you here,
old man Zangetsu will become
the center of my power once more.
You?
Defeat me?
That's impossible.
You think so?
Tell me it's impossible
after seeing this!
You just don't understand.
I'm telling you...
...it's impossible.
Ban...
- ...kai!
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
You there in front of
the TV lacking exercise!
The Super Hiyori Trainer that
Ichigo was using
can be yours for a low, low price!
Buy it now,
and you can get it signed
by Hiyori Sarugaki, the Bleach heroine!
Isn't that fraud in two different ways?
What did you say?!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Hold my breath! Hold it!
- Kon!
- That voice!
- Give me back my gigai!
- That's...
- That's my perfect body!
- Kon!
- If I trade places with him now,
- Where are you?!
all my woes will be gone!
Hanataro! Toss that over here!
Oh! O-Okay!
EXTRACTION PRINCESS
All right, now!
May misfortune be upon you!
Huh?