I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who
keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil, that fill this world.
Aizen, who has brought chaos
upon the Soul Society,
has begun to set his plan into motion.
Arrancars, created by Aizen
using the Hogyoku,
a material that removes the boundaries
between Soul Reapers and Hollows,
appear in Karakura Town.
Zanpakuto? Are they like us?!
Like Hirako and me?
Ichigo and his friends emerge as
victors in a tough battle
against Ulquiorra and Yammy,
but sustain injuries that are
more serious than anticipated.
Ichigo also becomes fearful
of the existence of the Hollow within him
and loses his will to fight.
It is at that time that Hitsugaya
and several other Soul Reapers
are dispatched from Soul Society.
If you're afraid of losing,
just become stronger.
If you're afraid of the Hollow
within you,
then become stronger until
you're able to destroy it.
That is the kind of man
you are in my heart!
Rukia manages to talk sense
into the depressed Ichigo
and restore his confidence.
However, at that time,
Grimmjow, an Arrancar
who was displeased with how
Ulquiorra handled his fight with Ichigo,
comes to the World of the Living
with several other Arrancars.
You will show them no mercy!
If they show even a glimmer
of Spiritual Pressure...
kill them all!
Let's go!
This Spiritual Pressure...!
It's them!
Rukia!
I know!
1...2...3...
Six of them?!
So many!
Are they headed here?!
No, they're searching for
Spiritual Pressure,
but they're not coming this way.
What's going on?!
They're not interested in the size
of the Spiritual Pressure.
They just want to attack!
They intend to kill every human who
has even a little Spiritual Pressure!
Huh?!
Ishida should have zero Spiritual Pressure
right now!
What about Chad and Inoue?!
As for Inoue,
Captain Hitsugaya and
Lieutenant Matsumoto are nearby.
It should be safer than other places!
Sado's place...
There's...one approaching!
So they're here, huh? This way?!
Let's go, Yumichika!
Yeah.
Run to a place where
you won't get hurt.
Right!
Captain!
Where is Orihime Inoue?
I'm having the gigai watch her,
so that she does not participate
in the battle.
All right.
Get ready, Matsumoto.
Huh?!
Here they come.
So fast!
How do you do?
Captain!
Why you-!
Arrancar Undécimo,
I am called Shawlong.
I'm the captain of Squad 10,
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
Squad 10 Captain...
My, my, how impressive.
Then...I aimed right.
No.
Hmm?
You probably...
missed big time.
Oh?
You mustn't do that, Chad!
Your treatment's not over!
No, I'm fine now.
Go back and make Inoue well.
What?
You're not a Soul Reaper?
Missed!
Whether it's a miss or not...
is decided after you fight!
That's true. Well then...
I'll thrash the whole lot of you,
then I'll say it again.
That each one of you...
missed big time!
I would be dead...
if Ichigo had come a second later.
I would definitely be dead.
Chad...
Stay back.
W-Wait, Ichigo!
- My injury is-
- Chad!
Chad!
Never mind... Leave it to me.
I see...
Oh...all right. I'll leave it to you, Ichigo.
You're okay, Sado!
Ichigo...
You don't need me to watch
your back anymore?
Am I no longer able to fight
side-by-side with you...?
Ichigo?
Well now... How shall I go
about thrashing you?!
Rukia...
Yeah... I saw Sado on the way.
What'd you say to him?
Nothing... Just to stay back
and let me handle this.
Stay back, Ichigo.
Huh?! What're you saying?!
Are you...?
I said, stay back and let me handle it.
You're too eager.
If you're like that before the battle,
you risk losing your life senselessly.
Rukia...you...
Your Soul Reaper powers...
Are you shocked?
My Soul Reaper powers did not return
because of Urahara's gigai.
So by removing the gigai and
living in Soul Society,
which overflows with reishi,
it was only a matter of time before
I regained my spirit power.
Overflows with reishi?
Yes.
Have you forgotten?
The Bounts absorbed the reishi
in Soul Society and gained power.
It wasn't as rapid as those guys,
but Soul Reapers also reap
the same benefits.
Your powers hadn't returned
during the battle with the Bounts.
After Captain Aizen's rebellion,
I was supposed to recuperate and
restore my spirit power slowly.
But those plans went awry
due to the sudden appearance
of the Bounts.
Soul Society was in total confusion.
After all, it was an emergency situation
with no one in Central 46.
And in the midst of all this,
Bounts appeared in Karakura Town
and you all stood on the front lines.
Seireitei had no choice
but to use someone
who was familiar with the area.
Someone familiar with the town
and the people?
And that's you, Hanataro,
Ganju and Renji?
Don't you think there was a problem
with the personnel selection?
You all were pretty useless...
Wh-What are you?!
Be good and stay back! Pyon!
Huh? Pyon?!
The Female Soul Reaper Association's
most popular Soul Candy, "Chappy."
She's the first Soul Candy I tried to buy.
There was a mix-up and instead,
I got Kon.
No kidding!
Then she's the one who
was supposed to enter my body?!
Yes, pyon!
Hate to admit it,
but I'm happy it was Kon!
How rude! Pyon!
Shut up!
- But damn, you're strong!
- Rude! You're rude!
- Actually, I'm shocked too.
- Oww!
- Before you returned here,
- Oww! Oww!
Inoue treated my wound
and after that
my spirit power was restored to
an unbelievable degree.
- And...
- Shut up!
Pyon!
Rukia!
Arrancar Dieciseis, D Roy.
Squad 13-
Hey, no need to tell me.
If I listened to the names of
everyone I'm about to thrash,
there wouldn't be enough time.
I see.
In that case...
At least remember the name
of my zanpakuto.
Dance...
Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai...
Tsukishiro!
Wha-?!
What...is this?!
Dammit!
Too bad, Soul Reaper!
My true battlefield is in the sky!
Your sword,
which freezes the ground,
has no effect in an aerial battle!
Too bad...
Sodenoshirayuki is not a sword
that "freezes the ground."
Everything within this circle...
is the freezing domain of
my Sodenoshirayuki.
Owww! Oww!
Silence! If you're not quiet,
I shall silence you with force! Pyon!
Cut that pyon, pyon crap!
It hurts so bad, I can't keep quiet!
Let go of me, idiot!
Pyon!
You're gonna break my arm!
You're gonna break it!
I'll pummel you!
I can't afford to get pummeled,
so I'll kill you before
you kill me! Pyon!
Wait, wait, wait!
Your job is to just hold me back!
Yay! Yay!
I'll just make your arm go pyon♪
What are you doing, fool?
– Huh?
Rukia!
Are you…okay?!
What about that one?!
Did you beat it?!
Of course.
Otherwise, I wouldn’t have come back.
You…
That zanpakuto…
Sodenoshirayuki.
Rukia’s ice-snow type zanpakuto
has been declared
the most beautiful in Soul Society.
The blade, the guard, the hilt…
It is a zanpakuto like pure snow.
You see, pyon.
Well, it’s all for nothing.
Hmm?!
Owww!
At the present time,
Rukia has the strength of
a seated officer! Pyon.
However, if she is assigned a seat,
the risk level of her missions
will be much greater
than if she were to remain
in the rank-and-file.
Hence, a certain person did not want
to put Rukia in the face of danger,
approached the captains and
requested that she be taken off
the list of candidates
to be assigned seats.
A certain person…?
Yes…
Byakuya Kuchiki…
You see, pyon.
And I said it’s all for nothing.
So just get off of me!
Oww!
I’ll just make your arm go pyon♪
How long are you
going to keep that up?
Enough already,
we must hurry and…
What?!
Was D Roy killed?
Oh well.
I’ll just have to…
kill the two of you together.
How do you do, Soul Reapers.
I’m Arrancar Seis, Grimmjow!
So D Roy has been beaten.
That scum…
He begged to come along.
So I brought him,
and this is what happens.
Hey! Where’re you looking?!
Roar!
Zabimaru!
Even if Lord Aizen took him
under his wings,
scum is scum, after all!
Whoever fought D Roy was lucky.
That D Roy was unbelievably useless
as an Arrancar.
Compared to that…
You guys have no luck at all!
You’re up against me.
You’ll be tossed around…
and you’ll die!
Huh?!
What’s happening?
This is so scary.
I hope it’s not nearby.
Cripes… All this racket
in the middle of the night.
Who are these delinquents anyway?!
That Mizuho…
buy your own juice!
Aw man, I hate this area.
It’s so dark.
I’ve been seeing ghostly figures
a lot lately.
Nope. I don’t believe in them.
I don’t, but…
They still give me the creeps.
Oh?
That’s the guy
who’s always battling beasts.
'Evening, Mr.Af!
Filming again tonight?
By the way,
Mr. Af stands for Mr. Afro.
Idiot! Shut up!
I have no time for you!
If you cherish your life,
don’t hang around here.
All the lives in the world
won’t be enough!
What’s with him?
I was just trying to say hello.
He could’ve at least stopped
for a short while.
Come to think of it…
I've never seen the TV show
that he's in.
Maybe it’s on a cable channel.
Wh-Wh-What’s this?!
What? What? What is this?!
What’s happening?!
Agh! Y-You’re the one I saw
in school this afternoon.
Wh-What are you doing
in the middle of the night
carrying a Japanese sword…
covered in blood?
Huh?
You’re the one from this afternoon…
What’s the matter?
Is that all a Soul Reaper is?! Huh?!
Wh-What?! Soul Reaper?!
Soul Reaper?
As in real Soul Reapers?!
What are these people talking about?!
Hey kid.
Y-Yes?
I have a juicy proposition…
You’re interested, right?
Well…err…
It depends on the proposition,
don’t you think?
Frankly, we don’t have a room
for the night.
On top of that,
you’re now involved in this fight
and about to get killed.
Err…I think you’re the one
who’s about to get killed.
And so!
I will save you from that guy.
So put us up at your house
for a while.
Huh?
Not “huh”!
Is it gonna be “yes” or “no”?!
Y-Yes!
All right! It's decided!
Hey…
Hmm?
You haven’t told me
your name yet, you big oaf.
Huh? Me?
I’m Arrancar Trece…
Humph!
Hmm?
No, never mind.
Introductions aren’t necessary
since I’m about to kill you.
Is that so?
It seems you and I have
different styles of protocol.
Huh?
“Always introduce yourself to
the one you’re about to kill.”
That’s the final etiquette that
I teach to every pupil I train.
If you’re putting your life
on the line,
you’d want to know who
it was that killed you.
Know me as Third Seat of
Zaraki’s Squad, Ikkaku Madarame!
But don’t bother to tell me
your name.
Just make sure
you remember my name!
It’s the name of the man…
Who will kill you!
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
…And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
Captain, the hard skin of
an Arrancar is written as “steel skin”
and is read “Hierro.”
Matsumoto, I wonder which
is thicker…
Theirs or the skin on your face?
Oh please! Don’t compare
my soft womanly complexion to that!
I think yours looks firmer.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
So on and so forth.
That’s about it in
the World of the Living.
Hmm…
Continue, but increase observations.
Yes! And this…
Huh?
Oh, Lady Yoruichi. So gorgeous!
Her daily attire is splendid too!