Licht Regen!
Help me! Kurosaki-kun!
That's impossible...
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Resurreccion Segunda Etapa.
He has witnessed my form, and
yet still has the will to fight?
Fine...
Then I will make you understand...
Such imprudence, Ichigo Kurosaki.
To throw down the gauntlet against
a frighteningly superior opponent
is beyond my comprehension.
If it is because of what
you people call "heart,"
then because you possess
"heart," you humans
suffer injuries...
And because you possess "heart,"
you lose your lives.
I'm not necessarily fighting
because I think I can win.
I'm fighting because...
I must win!
Such nonsense.
So you've come, girl.
Kurosaki-kun...?
You're just in time.
Watch closely...
The moment the life
of the man to whom
you've entrusted your hopes
comes to an end.
Stop!
No!
It's useless.
Even if you could get to him,
your powers are not enough
to keep him alive.
Kurosaki-kun... Kurosaki-kun...
I'll say it again.
It's useless...
Licht Regen!
How unexpected.
Among Ichigo Kurosaki's allies,
I had you pegged as the
most levelheaded person.
I am levelheaded.
That's why I have the
leeway to fight you!
Kurosaki-kun!
As I feared, those wings can
deflect all long-range attacks...
But if I get any closer...
At any rate, I've got to create some
time for Inoue-san to heal Kurosaki.
One more time!
Damn it!
Though I expected it, he's
overwhelmingly strong...
I need to stay calm,
and attack from a distance.
There must be an opening somewhere...
Are you done already?
Earlier, I was observing
how fast you were...
You are, after all, merely human.
That seems to be your limit.
I'm just getting started.
Is this the arm?
What should I do?
Somewhere in my mind...
I thought Kurosaki-kun would be all right...
That he would win...
By believing that, I was able
to turn my eyes away...
But...
What should I do?
Ishida-kun...
There's nothing to worry about.
I've anesthetized it and
stopped the bleeding...
Inoue-san...
I'll leave Kurosaki in your hands.
Ishida-kun!
What should I do?
What should I do, Kurosaki-kun?
I don't know what I should do...
I don't know...
I don't know anything...
Kurosaki-kun...
Kurosaki-kun!
Help me! Kurosaki-kun!
She's calling me...
I can hear her...
Get up...
Help me!
I will...
protect you!
Kurosaki...?
Impossible...
There's no possible way
he could be alive.
What is that form?
Who are you?!
Inoue-san!
Can't you hear me?
I asked you who you are.
It would seem...
you don't understand language.
Impossible...
That was without a doubt a Cero!
And one powerful enough to
blow away my Cero Oscuras.
There's no way.
He may resemble a Hollow,
but there's no way a human
could unleash a Cero!
Don't mock me!
Blowing away Cero Oscuras
for a second time?!
No...
It can't be...
Is that really...Kurosaki-kun?
My greatest ability is not
my capability to attack...
It's regeneration.
In exchange for immense strength,
we Arrancars lose most of our ability
to regenerate at ultra-high speeds.
But I alone am able to regenerate
all of my body parts other than my brain
and internal organs at high speed.
I don't know how you took on that form,
but no matter how much your
capability to attack increases...
If you're going to stop and
see what happens to me
just because you tore off one arm,
defeating me is...impossible.
Lanza del Relampago.
Don't come near.
Stay where you are.
If possible, I don't want to unleash
this at close range.
I missed.
It's difficult to control, after all.
That guy...can fire a technique
like that more than once?!
What?!
He completely slipped past my Pesquisa!
That wasn't a Flash Step he did just now.
It was a Sonido.
How can he be so fast?!
I can't even follow him.
Kurosaki-kun...
You're not getting away!
Did you think you could
rattle me with that...?
Don't mock me!
That's impossible...
With his bare hands...?!
He defeated him...
Damn it...
I never thought I...would be
defeated by a Hollowfied human.
It's...ludicrous.
I see. There is no mercy.
How Hollow-like.
Go ahead.
I lost to you.
I no longer have meaning.
Do it.
Because you possess "heart," you envy.
Because you possess "heart," you devour.
Because you possess "heart," you rob.
Because you possess "heart," you irritate.
Because you possess
"heart," you despise.
Because you possess "heart," you anger.
Because you possess "heart..."
I desire everything about you...
Arrancar Encyclopedia
Today, we're talking about Cero Oscuras.
Espadas in release mode are able
to unleash a special Cero.
Its power is several times
that of an ordinary Cero.
That's enough!
Cero Oscuras.
Hey! What's the big idea?!