Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
A Menos appeared…
and he defeated it.
This news will eventually reach
the Soul Society.
Ichigo…
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Ichigo!
What's the big idea so early
in the morning?
You had a realization or something?
Shut up! It's what your sister did!
A washing was enough,
but she went and…!
Looks good on you.
Yuzu must've felt sorry 'cuz
you were so dirty.
Shut up!
She even put this ornament on my ear!
And she used super glue!
It won't come off!
Let's see…
Cripes! She thinks
I'm just a stuffed toy and…Owwee!
Hey! What're you doing?! Owwee!
I thought it'd come off if
I pulled hard enough.
N-No!
No good. I think your ear'll come off first.
Why you--!
Look at the time! I'd better hurry!
Breakfast! Breakfast!
D-Damn it…
Why am I the only one who's
always treated like this?!
Am I not a comrade?!
Am I not an equal?
Well then, I'll leave on a journey.
And I'll find the one…
who will be kind to me!
The place where I truly belong!
Hey Rukia, time to leave for school!
Huh? Hey Rukia!
Pipe down! I can hear you fine.
Huh? Something happen?
It's nothing.
I'm just tired from
yesterday's incident.
If that's all…
I'm going ahead.
What's with her?
So I stormed out of the house.
But I wonder…
I have no money,
so I can't go that far.
Huh?
What's that?
Pick me up!
You're Ichigo's classmates!
Girls can't resist picking up
a cute stuffed animal.
Yes! Perfect!
Oh what a…cute stuffed animal…
– Dirty stuffed animal.
– Oof!
– Eh?
– Huh?
S-Shucks...
They're staring…at me.
It just spoke, didn’t it?
Yes, it did.
I guess it can't be helped
in a case like this…
It's running away!
Ryo Kunieda,
Karakura High School Track Team.
I run the 100 meters in 12 seconds flat!
You won't outrun me!
No! Why?!
All I wanted was some kindness!
In short…
Huh?
Kuchiki! Good morning!
Good morning, Inoue.
Let's walk together.
Of course, with pleasure.
But you really come early,
don't you?
Of course.
It's almost summer vacation, right?
I kept thinking about it and
can't sleep, like, sparkle!
I see!
Oh yes! Kuchiki, do you have
any plans for the summer?
Not really.
There's a huge Fireworks Festival
in August.
Tatsuki and the others,
we're all planning to go together.
Won't you join us?
A Fireworks Festival?
Yes! We should ask Kurosaki, too.
It'll be like the time we all went
to the Burarei program.
I just know it'll be fun.
That was some event, huh?
Uh-huh…
But he came along just for his family,
he can be very kind.
He has such a fun family,
he should lighten up a bit more.
Kurosaki has a permanent frown
on his face.
I thought you didn't care
too much for Kurosaki.
Not really.
When you take a good look at him,
he has an interesting face.
Please come to the
Fireworks Festival with us.
I'll think about it.
Okay come on, Tatsuki!
I found you, my goddess Orihime…
– Earlier was just a rehearsal.
– Go, Orihime! Hang in there!
– Hime! You look great!
– The real thing starts now.
First, I'll lie there helpless
in front of Orihime.
Like the Holy Mother,
she is sure to hold me gently,
– So cute!
– and cuddle me in the Valley of the Gods!
Yes! My target has always been Orihime!
Her and only her!
Once decided, you must act quickly!
And then, soft, warm cuddles await…
Sure Kill! Dragon Bazooka!
A perfect ball!
This isn't supposed to happen!
I did it! A one-run lead!
Yakka = soccer and baseball
Orihime, I think your game of "Yakka"
isn't fair to the defense.
And a one-run lead isn't cause
for a celebration yet!
Huh? Really?
Let's call it a day.
Free period's over anyway.
– I was just getting warmed up!
– What're they doing anyway?
Ichigo!
What're you looking at?
Hey hey hey!
You were looking at Inoue, weren't you?
Sheesh...talk about well-shaped jugs!
Get offa me!
And quit babbling nonsense!
What?!
We're healthy high school boys!
What's wrong with being
interested in cute girls?!
All right already!
There's nothing wrong with that.
Huh? I get it!
You prefer...the Mizuiro type, huh?!
Both of you! Quit fooling around
and start helping over here!
Oh sorry!
There! That's the last of it.
Yes, thanks.
By the way...
Ishida hasn't come by yet today.
I saw him yesterday.
At Central Park, mumbling to himself.
And sounding so dramatic, too!
– He always acts like he's in a drama.
– This guy was nearby?
– Well, that's true, but...
– Close call!
I'll bet he's in some theater group.
There were some weird men
around him, too.
And there was even an explosion...
it was pretty wild.
God, thank you for making him
such an idiot!
Ishida…!
What happened to those injuries?
I fell...from the stairway.
Yeah. Like, for real.
Hmm...well anyway, take your seat,
and let's continue class.
– Really? Is it okay?
– Sure?
Don't let it bother you.
It's not your fault.
He brought it upon himself.
I-I wouldn't worry about injuries like that.
Really? Who said not to worry?
I said don't let it bother you.
Why you--!
Was it a fight?
Ishida? No way!
I can't believe that Ishida was
that late... Third period!
Keep it quiet.
Ichigo!
Let's have lunch together!
Sure, but can I invite
someone else, too?
What? A new girl? Who?
Ishida…
Let's eat lunch together.
What?!
W-Why Ishida?!
Eating with a guy like that
can't be fun at all!
I get it! It must be the bandages!
Were those bandages that funny, Ichigo?!
Shut up.
– No thanks!
– So blunt!
C'mon. It's Keigo's treat.
Why?!
Then fine.
Stingy bastard!
I've been suspected from
the very beginning.
There's probably not much time left.
Oh, there she is!
Rukia, come and join us for lunch!
Jinta, get serious and sweep properly.
Shut up! This is the age when
men are silent and play soccer!
Goodness...
Huh?!
Tessai... Kisuke...
A kitty.
Oh! If it isn't Yoruichi! Welcome back!
Here you go! Upsy daisy!
What is that cat?
Its name is Yoruichi and
it's the Boss's best friend.
– Huh? A cat as a best friend?
– Once more?
– I feel sorry for the Boss sometimes.
– Here! Up and up!
– I guess you could say that.
– Upsy daisy!
T-This is such a painful lunch!
It's like we're cursed.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's only you, Chad.
Why are you so scared?
Shut up! Just leave me alone!
Hey Keigo, say something
to cheer us up.
Wha--?!
T-That's impossible!
Hurry it up.
If you're gonna get so moody,
you shouldn't have asked Ishida!
Say, I ate saury in Meguro recently.
And the waiter...
– Kurosaki, why'd you invite me?
– I swear...
– Out of sympathy for these wounds?
– He looked like a comedian.
If that's the case, it's misplaced.
And I don't care to be pitied.
Shut up! I just felt like it...that's all.
I didn't ask you because I like you.
So just be grateful I asked at all.
As if I'd be grateful!
Besides, I prefer to eat alone.
I like to be alone when I eat, too.
Well then...
Just look the other way.
– Why should I be  the one to look away?
– These two...
They're so alike.
All together now!
Tadah! Today's lunch is
Castella sandwich!
Castella sponge cake with bean jelly
is the ultimate for sweets lovers.
Not again...
Orihime, how come she can
eat such things and not gain weight?
All the nutrients are going
to her breasts, that's why.
Kuchiki, do you like Kurosaki?
What?
Or, to put it bluntly... Just what is your
relationship with Kurosaki?
Well, we’re frie--
Mahana, that was way too bold!
Why? You're the ones
who want to know, but can't ask.
So I popped the question for you.
Err... Well...
I'm not that interested...
Maybe, not you...
You don't care for Ichigo
anyway, Michiru.
Well, it's not that I don't like him.
His face just looks a bit scary.
Really? I think he has
an interesting face.
Huh? When did you get over
your fear of Kurosaki?
Well?
What's the story?
Kurosaki is...
Kurosaki is just a friend.
– Are you serious?
– Yes.
You don't feel anything for him?
Not at all?
Not at all.
Too bad! If you like Kurosaki,
then I'd have to start liking him...
and Tatsuki can start liking him...
and why don’t we all start liking him?
Then it would have been
a sure win for the girl's team!
This kid is starting her
nonsensical rambling again!
A group competition from
the start sounds interesting.
But I want Orihime's first
happy face to be all mine!
And so... Let's begin with
a one-on-one relationship!
Come on, Orihime!
Stop it!
Ughh... That was a nice parry...
That wasn't a parry, it was a punch!
I know! I'll come up...
with a new concoction
with bean jam...
So let's eat it together, all right?
Err... I'll think about it.
Not the same answer again!
You keep saying,
"I'll think about it."
Oh really?
I don't...
I don't belong here.
URAHARA STORE
Why do I have to be treated like this?!
Damn! This is all Ichigo's fault!
You just wait, Ichigo!
I'll use the deadly weapons that
weird manager has collected here
and get my revenge!
Huh?! Who are you?!
Wanna fight?!
Just because you're also
one of the cat family,
don't put me in
the same class as you!
I'm a lion!
Hah! Scared ya, huh?
Good riddance!
That was easy!
Hmm... Mod Souls can
even enter stuffed toys.
Hello!
W-What the--!
Yoroichi told us.
You're that cat from earlier!
– Now then... What'll we do with you?
– Hey, you two!
– Hey Ururu, grab his feet!
– What's the big idea?!
'Kay.
– One and two and...!
– Hey! Cut it out!
Noooooooooooo!
Ichigo!
Huh?
What is it?
A Hollow?
No, it's not that.
Are you feeling all right?
Huh? Yeah, there's nothing
wrong with me.
I see... Then that's good.
Is there gonna be another
one like yesterday?
What would we do if a Menos Grande
appeared so easily?
You're...acting a bit strange today.
Did something happen?
Well...
– It's...!
– Huh?
Ichigo!
Sorry I ran away!
I understand now! I realize that
my place is with you!
Ichigo!
You ran away? Hey you...
I'm over here!
Ohhh! The world was so cruel to
this one who ran away from home.
I'm...I'm going back to your room!
Going back, huh...?
What's wrong?
Nothing. But he's really become
attached to you.
He's a pain in the neck.
But look at you! Look,
you have stuffing coming out.
– Hey! What're you doing?!
– I'm amazed he didn't die.
– Oh well, we'll take you to him.
– Let go of me!
HANDICRAFT CLUB
Why me?
Why not? I thought this is
your specialty.
I refuse.
Why?
I don't need to answer that.
So selfish!
Oh I got it!
Can't do a thing with those hands!
Yeah, it's impossible. Yeah...
Can't even thread
a needle like that, huh?
How insulting!
These wounds are nothing!
Give it here!
And just watch me!
The work of a master!
Oh no...
– This is a piece of cake for me!
– What's this...?
Is it all right?
– I dunno...
– What's happening to me?
Finished!
This is...!
Unbelievable...!
Huh?!
Who are you?!
He's been powered up.
Such bad taste.
Pretty bad.
What is this?!
I have high-grade fabric so that
I can accept orders at any time.
And the material I used here--
Shut up!
Just cut the crap!
Making fun of me and... Huh?!
Huh?!
I'm going to run away, after all!
What's the matter, Yoruichi?
Is it going to rain?
Stop putting on an act, Kisuke.
You know, don't you?
Those guys are here.
Will you talk about it before
or after your milk?
Hey Rukia!
It's dinnertime... Huh?
Geez, she went off somewhere again.
Thanks for everything.
Rukia
Rear conformity 113!
Neural coefficient 88.5%.
Is this for real?
She's actually in a Gigai...
I didn't think the data from
the Visuals Department was reliable.
Rukia Kuchiki...
Found you!
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I'm Ishida, president of
the Handicrafts Club.
I just want to say one thing...
this episode did not showcase
all of my talent.
If I had more time, I could've come up
with a more fashionable look.
In time, I'll show you my work that
will make your spine tingle.
Just you wait.
Noooo!