Two Brothers
You have 24 hours until
the beam cannon fires.
If your decision comes too late,
tomorrow will be remembered
in the history of space as
the day the star wars began,
a day that will live in infamy.
And the first act of war will be to
reduce Earth, the catalyst, to space dust.
It would be unwise to attempt to search
this large planet for our present.
There is an emergency defense
system built into it.
If you try anything funny,
this planet will be destroyed
before the beam cannon ever fires.
Did that guy come back
to destroy his home?
As a planet, Beam and its population are
basically one big weapons manufacturer.
But as a nation, they're too smart
to butt into interstellar politics.
However, there's a group called the
Firestarters who pulls strings to start wars.
The Galaxy Sword Master
has made his name through
his exploits in those wars.
But if he is, in truth, a fictitious hero
whose purpose is to start those wars...
Hajime-nii!
Whew, you're awake!
Are you okay?
Hajime-nii...
Oh, Shin-bo.
As you can see, I'm doing fine!
Man, it's such a lovely morning!
Edo mornings are so beautiful.
How about it?
Let's go for a jog like we used to.
Sure.
He probably doesn't realize
that he's being used.
How do we stop the mechanical
half of his body?
Spit it out.
It's not something Shinpachi
or Otae can handle.
Okay, we will now chase down the
interstellar wave beam cannon.
Grab every person who looks suspicious.
Hijikata-san, what would
be a suspicious person?
Someone who looks like he
might shoot out beams.
Hey, this guy's shooting
idiot beams from his head.
Throw him in the slammer.
Let me go!
Want me to murder you guys?!
Hey, Kondo-san! Say something!
Hey, stop this!
Someone who looks like he
might shoot out beams...
This is the worst threat
the nation has faced since
the founding of the Tokugawa Bakufu!
The Yagyu must step up to
score points with the Shogun!
Scratch that.
Step up to protect Edo!
More paper money!
Complete our celebrity blockade!
Hey, who included Takagi
Boo with the celebrities?!
Didn't you say to use
a Drifters blockade?
No, I said to use a celebrity
blockade, Father!
Oh, then I should look
for women who are easy.
No, that would be a **** blockade!
Could it be...?
Hey, is this good enough?
I don't know since I've
never done this before.
Temperature's perfect!
Thank you very hamnida!
Care to join me?!
Want me to kill you,
Pervy Sword Master?!
A bath really hits the
spot after some sparring.
Right, Shin-bo?
Are you trying to kill me?!
You need to scorch your delicate
spots to make them squeaky clean!
What kind of gunk did you
pick up out in space?!
Still, where is he hiding
the beam cannon?
All I can see is a little pistol.
Listen to me, Gin-guy.
If you stab him with this blade I've
rigged with a disruption device,
it will delay the activation of
the emergency defense system.
That will be your chance to destroy
the mechanical half of his
body and fully disable him.
What will happen to the
human side of his body?
I already gave you an explanation.
That machine is keeping
him alive right now.
If the machine is disabled, the human half
of his body will go back to being dead.
What are you doing here?
Why are you carrying
that weapon, Gin-san?
You know the answer.
I'm here to cut down your first love.
You're not trying to hide it.
Half-assed lies don't work on women.
Your eyes are puffy.
That's what you get for eavesdropping.
You used to be so weak.
I could barely feel you
scrubbing my back.
You've really grown up.
Though you haven't changed down there.
You're one to talk!
You're still out of my reach.
I'll never be able to catch up to you.
Shin-bo, you're already
stronger than me.
All I got for leaving Earth
was this beat-up body and the
hollow title of Sword Master.
After returning to Edo and seeing
you guys, I realized something.
If you can't find something
close to protect,
you can wander the entire universe
and never achieve true strength.
I should have returned sooner to
the country of the samurai.
Why does it sound like you've given up?
We can work together
to find the answer.
We can work together to become strong.
So don't say that.
Our Hajime-nii would
never look so defeated!
Shin-bo, so you know?
We understand.
So please, we won't ask
you to wait until tomorrow,
but could you give us
a little more time?
Please lower your sword,
Gin-san.
I always wanted to introduce
you and Gin-san to each other.
I always hoped that one day,
the two of you would sit
here next to each other
while I washed your backs.
But now...
Why is it you?
Why did this have to happen?!
I beg you, Gin-san.
Just give us a little more time.
Let him
be Shin-chan's big brother
a little longer.
I won't be able to restrain the
other half of my body much longer.
I was prepared to end my own life,
but I came back to Edo
because I wanted to see you
and Otae-chan one last time.
Soz about getting you
into all this trouble.
But I'm glad I got to see this
city of samurai one last time—
You're in my way.
Move it.
Why do you all have those
looks on your faces?
Did you forget what the
School of Beam Saber
teaches about reacting
in these situations?
Well, Instructor Obi-one?
Hajime-nii!
Stop it!
Gin-san!
Hajime-nii is still...
Still...
I told you, you're in my way!
Shinpachi!
Shin-chan!
Damn, he got away.
Please wait!
Why...
Why are you doing this?!
Why would you be so cruel?!
Hajime-nii knows everything!
He understands what's happening!
He's prepared to end his own life!
He can't do that.
It's not his body anymore.
You were washing a dead body
with some junk attached.
I dare you...
I dare you to repeat that.
Stop it, Shin-chan!
Please stop this, both of you!
Sorry, but I'm not interested
in sitting around with
a bunch of emotional saps,
waiting for my death.
If you can't handle the job, I'll do it.
It's that simple.
Wait...
Wait.
I said to wait!
Are you deaf?!
Shin-chan!
How can two big brothers
be so different?
Look at me.
Is this the face of a big brother?
True, your nose hairs are sticking out.
Oh, you're right.
Shin-chan!
Hang in there, Shin-chan!
Excuse us.
The emergency defense
system hasn't activated.
That man must have done something.
Was he able to sense my
intention to kill that boy?
Hey!
What are you doing up there?!
What the hell?!
He can shoot beams from his eyes!
After him!
Don't let him escape!
We can't find him.
Same here.
You better find him before
I finish smoking this.
Shah that guy up before these curtain
rings can "shah" the curtain shut.
Or else it's seppuku time.
You middle management people are useless!
Get out of the way!
I'll let you go if you
tell us where he is.
That's what we want to know!
Can you cut it out?
Shin-chan...
Everyone's up in arms.
Are you so intent on
destroying Hajime-nii?
In any case, this gives
Kondo-san and Kyubei-san
an excuse to rid themselves of their rival.
That's despicable.
You're all despicable!
Not as despicable as your leader.
Come in, this is Kenofi.
There's been a problem.
I request assistance.
My current coordinates are...
We weren't spurred into action
by my lady or Kondo-dono.
It was your leader.
This was a mistake on my part.
I didn't expect him to have
such a dangerous man as
his new brother figure.
Why are you all so obsessed
with the brother thing?
Neither Shinpachi nor I am
interested in being brothers!
Gin-san did?
Hijikata-san...
Looks like the news has gotten out.
Sorry, but we can't let you pass.
The Shinsengumi are on the job.
Do not worry.
We will search every nook
and cranny of the building.
You should go take a bath and
wash every nook and cranny of your body.
Wh-Who are you people?
We aren't here to capture Obi-one.
We're holding off the
cops who are on his tail
and making sure that you all are safe.
Wh-Why would you do that?
Because your leader got down
on his knees and begged us to.
If you kill me, you will
lose their trust forever.
Given that, why did you come here?
I'm not interested in
battling to the death
with a bunch of crying fools
standing nearby!
This is much better!
Battling to the death?
Don't make me laugh.
You're unconsciously trying to
avoid attacking my left side.
So this is the power of
the Galaxy Sword Master?
Not very impressive.
That title's too flashy for you.
You should stick to
being a big brother.
"I'll figure out a way to
bring Obi-one back alive,
so could you stay put and
not do anything until then?"
He planted his empty head
right against the floor.
Want to see a picture?
Why did he do that?
Why did he ask you for help
when he didn't say a word to us?!
That idiot!
He wanted to keep us away
from Obi-one-niisama.
Don't worry, Obi-one.
Nobody else will be joining us.
I won't let you get any
more blood on your hands!
So
come back, Obi-one!
Come back and be their big
brother one more time!
He was the only one who hadn't given up
on saving Obi-one-niisama.
Do you seriously believe
that he's still capable
of returning?!
Come in. This is Kenofi.
I need to be picked up immediately.
Kenofi?
Are you really Kenofi?
We've already locked on to your
signal and begun the retrieval.
Kenofi, where are you right now?
I-Impossible!
What is the meaning of this?!
Man, it's not easy when we all
work for a bunch of losers.
No way...
Wh-Who are you?!
Identify yourselves!
From the School of Tendo
Mushin Beam Saber!
Yagyu Kyubei.
And Kondo Isami.
We've come here to
reclaim the human half...
...of our instructor, Obi Hajime.
You were able to disrupt my
transmitter with that strike?
You just came here to buy time
while your allies work to
disable the beam cannon?
Like I said, nobody else
will be joining us.
Will you leave that body first,
or will you get rid of me first?
It's a waiting game now.
Foolishness!
Damn those Earth apes!
They tricked us!
We clearly got the short
end of the stick.
Stuck helping our rival in love.
A victory here won't win us anything.
We've still got it better
than that idiot
since he had to beg for help.
Plus he'll be losing his
position as a brother figure.
Besides, now I know
the reason why Otae-chan was able to
smile when times were tough or painful.
Even if her smile isn't
directed our way,
I just want her to truly smile again.
I see. That means...
I should laugh with them.
So people who are truly strong
laugh when they want to cry.
They endure all of the pain and sorrow
while laughing with everybody else.
But one day, you must become
samurai strong enough not to cry.
Captain Okita, are you sure about this?
Image has been deleted.
Sorry, big guy. I couldn't stop them.
We little brothers have our own pride.
Well, let's get going.
To our big brother's side.
It seems that you people are intent
on keeping that man alive.
But you've been wasting your time.
What's that?
Nobody can stop him at this point.
Not us, not him...
The emergency system
will recover shortly.
When that happens, you
Earthlings will be finished.
Kondo...
Bullshit.
That's bullshit.
Then why...
Then why did he have
to play the bad guy?!
Why did he have to get
on his knees and beg?!
Can you give those two big brothers
back to Shinpachi-kun?
It'll be thirty minutes
before my system recovers.
There's only one way to stop the
beam cannon before that happens.
You have to destroy me, Obi-one.
I'll be sending your little
brother and this planet
to see you shortly.
You can wait in hell for them.
Did you call me his little brother?
You people throw the word
brother around too much!
Neither Gin-san nor I am interested
in being brothers, you fool!
To Be Continued
We have a big announcement
about the second movie.
Next week, the censored
areas will be revealed.
Gintama the Movie ----
In theaters on ---- ----th!
Hey, squinting won't help you.
If squinting helped, you'd have a lot of
boys spending 1/3 of their time squinting.
Liquor and Gasoline
Smiles and Tears
Next time:
Liquor and Gasoline, Smiles and Tears.
There's a huge atmosphere swing
between the movie preview and
the next episode preview.
That's just business as usual
in the Gintama anime.