What’s the matter?!
Taking your sweet time to
analyze the situation?!
You want to get this over with, right?
Same here!
Just as I suspected...
He didn’t simply make Kurosaki’s
Fullbring his own...
His attacks are combined with the
power of Kurosaki’s
Spiritual Pressure...!
This is going to be a problem...
So, did you come up
with any great ideas?
What’s that supposed to mean?
Just that.
You’re the one who suggested
we analyze the situation.
Weren’t you trying to come with
an idea to quickly take him down?
Are you stupid or something?
There’s no such thing.
What? There isn’t?
I was observing his Spiritual Pressure.
Listen to me.
His Spiritual Pressure contains your...
Well, I’ll be going, then.
Wait, Kurosaki!
The fact that his attack is combined
with your Spiritual Pressure means...
Ah, you finally decided to come out...
So?
Did you come with a plan
while you were hiding?
I just checked.
He didn’t have any, so I came on out.
A Getsugatensho, huh?
Bring it on.
I almost died because
of that the last time.
If you’re going to beat me, I
suppose that’s the only way.
Don’t do it, Kurosaki!
He’s egging you on!
Getsugatensho!
The fact that he has your Spiritual
Pressure combined with his own
means it’s possible that he can
also use your techniques...!
Are you listening, Kurosaki?!
I heard you.
Quit nagging.
Who’s nagging?!
You have a bad habit of not
hearing people through!
Listening to you won’t change a thing!
It’s not as though that’s
going to diminish his powers!
It does change things...
At least you can be careful.
Watch it, Kurosaki.
His last blow made it very clear.
It wasn’t just your Spiritual
Pressure and Fullbring that he took.
He’s probably acquired every
one of your abilities...!
How cruel of you…
Am I not…your benefactor…?
Doesn’t it pain your
heart to do this…?
You are indeed my benefactor.
And I do appreciate it.
However, you are Ichigo
Kurosaki’s enemy.
I will not hesitate to kill that enemy.
Regardless of who they are.
Damn…
Good, you’re finally out.
Captain! You got out pretty quick.
Shut up. You’re just slow.
Abarai.
What happened to you? You’re a mess.
You look pathetic!
Sorry…
I escaped that dimension quite
a while ago via the explosion,
but I was unable to move
for some time, so…
Oh, so that huge explosion
came from you?
What about your opponent?
Did you kill them?
She’s dead… I think.
What about you?
Uh, well…
He disappeared after I
scolded him a little…
Scolded him?!
That’s why you took so long!
Taking your damn sweet time!
Sorry, sir…
Why’re you guys arguing
the minute you show up…?
Huh?!
This is none of your business!
You’re right. Fine.
Get it out of your system.
Hey! This wasn’t part of the deal!
You said you’d free me
once I shut down my powers!
Once we confirm that
everyone is free, we will.
Kuchiki and Kuchiki aren’t here.
Can you refer to them
by first names, sir?
You’re confusing us.
I’m losing feeling
in my arms and legs!
Rukia!
Look after her.
Yes, sir!
Is she all right?
She’s alive.
Her wounds are slight,
and there isn’t any irregularity
in her Spiritual Pressure.
However…
there were no signs of
the enemy or its corpse
in the area where Rukia collapsed.
You look like you know something.
Of course not.
I hardly know anything about
Riruka’s abilities…
Neither of us wanted to show
the other our abilities.
I don’t know if she’s
dead, or if she got away,
but I’d be grateful if she were dead.
Come on! Isn’t this enough?!
Melt this ice already!
Not yet.
Why not?!
Oh, I can’t undo that one.
It’s the truth!
Did you know?
Fullbringers and Substitute Soul
Reapers can trade their powers.
When we first joined Kugo,
we traded a portion
of our powers with each
other as a sign of loyalty.
We also placed a small
restriction on those powers.
Here’s the restriction
I share between Kugo…
“If Kugo is within the
range of my abilities,
then I cannot undo them
unless he orders me to.”
That’s pretty good.
You put yourself at
quite a risk, though.
I had no such intention.
I suppose not.
You’re just fighting with
everything you’ve got, right?
So, what are you fighting for right now?
What do you mean?
Tsukishima’s dead.
Actually, he’s not dead yet,
but his Spiritual
Pressure is nearly gone.
I’d say he only has about
ten minutes to live…
And…
when a Fullbringer dies, all traces
of his abilities disappear.
Understand what that means?
If Tsukishima dies,
all of the memories of the past that he
inserted will return to
what they used to be.
Your family and friends will
all be just the way they were before.
So I’ll ask you once more:
Right now, what are you fighting for?
No answer?
Then let me tell you one more thing.
It’s about the enemy you
should really be fighting.
They’ve stabilized…
Yes.
Tessai,
I’ll leave the rest to you.
Yes, I will see to them.
Where are you going?
To where everyone is.
To assist? I’m coming with you.
No, most of the fighting
is probably over,
so I’m going to provide healing.
You’ll be of no help,
Isshin, so stay here.
Shouldn’t we try to
wrap this up quickly
by assisting Ichigo with his fight?
If we don’t do that, then…
He’ll find out from Kugo Ginjo?
That’s fine.
He was going to find
out sooner or later.
The enemy I should really be fighting?!
Yeah.
Don’t mess with me!
I’ve had enough of your mind games!
That’s right.
You see yourself in at a disadvantage,
so you present a shocking “fact”
to lay on the psychological pressure
in order to make your point that
“You’d be better off
joining with me.”
Isn’t that right?
At a disadvantage, you say?
What ever makes you say that?
Sorry, but I can fully defeat
the both of you right now.
Why don’t you try shooting
at me from the back?
I’ll parry your shots while
keeping our conversation.
Kurosaki.
Do you know why you were
entrusted with a Combat Pass?
What do you mean?
When you were handed the Combat Pass,
you must’ve been told
something like this:
“If the Soul Reaper is deemed
beneficial to the Soul Society,
it is customary to give
them the Combat Pass.”
Listen closely, Kurosaki.
That’s a lie.
It’s no simple task for an
organization to determine whether
someone will be of benefit
or a detriment…
And the biggest issue is that if they
“hand out Combat Passes
to those of benefit,”
they’ve never told
Kurosaki what happens
to those who are not.
More correctly…
Whether someone is of benefit or
detriment to the Soul Society
has nothing to do with it.
Combat Passes are handed
out equally regardless.
The official name for Combat Pass is
“Substitute Soul Reaper
Combat Pass”…
It certifies that one has permission to
conduct Substitute Soul Reaper
duties in the World of the Living.
I know that.
But have you ever, to this moment,
truly felt its authority?
I am Ichigo Kurosaki! I’m
a Substitute Soul Reaper!
Here’s my Combat Pass!
What the hell is that?
I’ve never seen or
heard of such a thing.
What’s with this thing?
It isn’t any help at all…
Are you saying the Combat
Pass has another function?
Yeah.
The function of the Combat Pass is
to keep watch and control.
Thanks to the Combat Pass,
the Soul Society is able to
keep constant tabs on your whereabouts,
and allowed them to control
your Spiritual Pressure,
at least while you had
the Combat Pass near you.
Didn’t you ever question…
Why your Spiritual Pressure that
rages out of control
when you’re agitated,
even in Soul Reaper form,
never had any effect
on you when you were in human form?
Why, when you used your Combat
Pass to produce your Fullbring,
your Spiritual Pressure gushed
forth from the Combat Pass?
Why, during your Fullbring training,
you heard your friends voices
via the Combat Pass?
Surely you must’ve
questioned them before.
The Combat Pass is a
device that communicates
with the Soul Society,
absorbing your Spiritual Pressure,
then analyzing and controlling it.
You were given that so the Soul Society
could keep watch on you and control you.
It’s not that you never
felt it was strange.
You simply pushed those questions
into the back of your mind.
People who you bonded with in battle
would never do that to you.
You didn’t want to believe
they would do that to you.
Ichigo.
I will tell you.
The man who came up
with this plan is…
Jushiro Ukitake…
The Captain of Squad 13.
The Combat Pass?
What’s that?
The Soul Society also has a law
covering the emergence of
a Substitute Soul Reaper.
It has been decided since
ancient times that if
the Substitute Soul Reaper is
deemed beneficial to the Soul Society…
then we are to give this to them.
That one is yours now.
I see…
Thank you, Ukitake.
Ukitake did…?
We were tricked by the
most peace-loving man
among the 13 Court Guard Squads!
Ichigo!
The man’s aim is to
watch and control us in order to
use us as pawns of the Soul Society,
and to eliminate us if we resist!
This is bad…!
Kurosaki!
There’s no way Kurosaki
can cope with these truths
in his present state!
They all know!
Everyone in the Soul Society
besides you knows this!
They abandoned you and
left you to die, Ichigo!
Don’t listen to him, Kurosaki!
Shut the hell up!
Bankai!
Rukia!
…Renji…
You all right?!
Does it hurt anywhere?!
Yeah…
Right now, my right shoulder hurts…
Is Ichigo still inside…?
With this many captain-class
Soul Reapers present,
destroying that dimension
should be easy…
I get it…
They’re waiting to see his decision.
What?! What’s going on?!
Impossible…!
It’s collapsing…
Bankai.
“Shut the hell up”?
Shut up about what?
Do I annoy you so much
that you’d do Bankai to kill
me at once to shut me up?
What would that do?
Would that hide your eyes
from reality once more?
Shut up.
That one was towards you.
But what I said earlier wasn’t…
It was towards Ishida.
“Don’t listen to him,
Kurosaki!” my ass.
Shut up.
Mind your own business!
Kurosaki…
I also thought what Ukitake
said to me sounded odd…
What?!
But I didn’t want to believe it.
I didn’t want to suspect Ukitake.
That’s why I always shoved those
thoughts to the back of my mind.
But then I realized something…
I asked myself, “Why was
I suspicious of Ukitake”?
Ukitake is a lot smarter than me.
If he really was planning to deceive me,
he would have done so in a way
that I wouldn’t notice.
But Ukitake handed me
the Combat Pass along
with that explanation.
And I soon realized
that the Combat Pass had no function.
I’m guessing that Ukitake purposely
allowed me to realize that.
He purposely let me come to that
realization and make my own choice.
Regarding what?
Coming to that realization
didn’t leave you any
choice in the matter.
I did make a choice…
I chose the path of protecting others.
I wanted power.
I wanted the power to protect all
sorts of people, all the time.
When I lost my powers, I
remembered that feeling.
Rukia gave me the power I
sought to protect people.
Everyone helped me regain
the powers I had lost.
That’s why I will protect
everyone and fight you.
There go the negotiations.
You leave me no choice!
I didn’t want to have to kill you.
Bankai.
Oh yeah, I forgot about that…
You were a Substitute Soul Reaper
yourself, weren’t you?
That’s right.
But there’s something else you forgot.
As I told you…
People like us were
attacked by Hollows before we were born.
Inside me…
is the power of a Hollow.
Is that so?
Bring it on, Ginjo.
Let’s hurry up and settle this.
You talk big for a kid.
Time will try to constantly
try to catch up with you.
And with a roar, it will overcome you.
Do not look ahead.
Hope only lies within the unforeseeable
current that will close in from behind.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Hey.
Long time no see.
It’s me, everyone’s idol, Kon!
Since this is the last “Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers,”
I’ll let you in on an interesting
story about myself!
After Ichigo lost his powers,
these two were deeply troubled…
“What could we do to help
him?” they wondered.
This is what I told them:
You guys need to have faith in Ichigo…
Huh? We’re done?!
Is this the end?!
I was coming to the best part!
Why?!