Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
So the manifested Zanpakuto are
being controlled by Muramasa?
Well, it's apparently
not that simple.
His power is
not really mind control.
He amplifies any dissatisfaction
that a Zanpakuto has
and uses that to lead them on.
Which one of us is
truly the strongest?
If I can find that out, I will
gladly cross blades with you.
In order to get our Zanpakuto back,
we need to fight them and have
them surrender to us once again.
I see.
In any case, we found one way
to solve this issue.
This is good news.
Yeah, but…
It's going to take a lot of time
for all of us to find our Zanpakuto
and make them surrender to us.
Will the enemy stay quiet
while we do that?
I think not.
We've got to do it anyway.
I'm coming in.
Ah, you're here.
What did you want?
I heard you made
your Zanpakuto surrender.
I called you here to find out if
you learned anything from them.
I see…
They don't remember
anything, though.
Yeah.
I'm hungry, Renji!
Shut up!
You really don't
– remember anything?!
– You shut up, Renji!
Not a single thing!
– You guys…
– This is boring!
– You're too stupid.
– I'm hungry, Renji!
– Well, we're your Zanpakuto,
– This is boring!
– after all.
– I'm hungry!
Are you trying to say
– that I'm stupid?
– This is boring!
Stupid Renji!
– You could say that.
– Stupid Renji!
– Shut up!
– Stupid, stupid, Renji!
Hurry up and turn back
into Zanpakuto!
I don't want to!
We can't tease you
if we're Zanpakuto!
You bastard!
Catch me if you want me
to turn back!
Hey! Get back here!
Why should I?!
Stay still, damn it!
Oh, my. You're full of energy.
But this is Squad Four's barracks.
You mustn't romp around
like a child…
Lieutenant Abarai.
I hear Zabimaru lost
to a Soul Reaper.
Yeah. Getting beaten
by a Soul Reaper…
How pathetic!
You think you can say
whatever you want
just because you
won your battle?
You only fought
a third-rate Soul Reaper!
Your former partner
was even worse.
He was the Squad Two
lieutenant, right?
I'm surprised you used to
work for him.
You bastard!
I'm really embarrassed about that!
Stop it, you two!
None of that matters.
We just have to clobber
those guys who piss us off.
I really hate guys who
only know how to fight.
You're one to talk.
You're just as silly as they are.
What do you want, Tobiume?
Stop making jabs at me.
Oh, did I hit a nerve?
You're really not cute.
That's why men always
run away from you.
What?!
Men never go near you because
you always wear that smelly perfume.
What?! You act so innocent,
but men don't go for that nowadays!
Men like stuff like this!
Who'd like a dark-tanned
beast like you!
What did you say?!
What of it?!
Darling!
Save me! Tobiume
is picking on me!
Hey, Haineko!
Stop telling lies!
See how scary she is?!
You're doing it again!
Get away from him!
He doesn't like that!
What's all the fuss?
It's nothing. Right?
Y-Yeah.
Oh! Wait up!
Muramasa…
I heard you let
a Soul Reaper get away.
That's not like you.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
He has a special power.
He's just a Substitute
Soul Reaper!
If he shows up in front of me,
I'll shred him into pieces!
No… If possible,
I want to capture him alive.
Oh yeah?
I don't mind doing something
like this once in a while.
Sounds like fun.
I'm up for that.
Well, I'm sure it'll be
a good way to pass the time.
He's in as well.
You were pretty reckless.
It'll take a while for you to heal.
Take it easy and rest up.
Thank you very much,
Lieutenant Kotetsu.
Ichigo… I'm sorry.
Rukia… Why did you
go back by yourself?
As I said before, there's no way
that Byakuya would die so easily.
I am well aware of that.
But…
I have an indescribable anxiety.
Leave Byakuya to us.
We'll find him.
Okay.
Ah! There you are!
I finally found you.
I hear you got back
your Zanpakuto.
Tell me all about it.
Hey!
Don't let your guard down!
I know that.
What's wrong?!
Jeez, you've got to be kidding me.
Making me go check
the past archive records
to see if a Zanpakuto called
Muramasa ever existed…
Honestly, what a pain.
He shouldn't complain.
He jumped at
Captain Ukitake's request
because he didn't want to do
an investigation of Seireitei.
Did you say something?
– Nothing, sir!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Are you all right, Lieutenant?!
Ow…
Who put this thing here?
Whoa…
Oh, my!
What is this?!
What's going on?
Who's there?!
How pathetic.
They're not even good
for warm-up exercises.
Oh?
– Delicious!
Could it be that you're…
That's right.
I'm the mighty Gegetsuburi!
I see, I see…
So you're Gegetsuburi.
You truly are my Zanpakuto!
You look pretty stylish!
Huh? Have you ever
looked in the mirror?
You're balding!
I'm not balding!
This is a hairstyle!
That's lame.
You're the reason why
my manifestation looks like this!
What?!
For someone who's supposed
to be my Zanpakuto,
your taste is
pretty messed up!
What?!
Want to fight?
Heh! I'm going to make you
surrender to me!
Try if you can!
Stay out of this, Hozukimaru!
I don't like interfering with
other people's battles anyway.
Oh, no. Did I kick the wrong one?
Looks like it.
It's no big deal.
It's just Omaeda.
Anyway, I never expected to
find Zanpakuto here.
This is perfect. I'm going to show
you the results of my training!
Who the hell are you?!
I missed you, partner!
What?
That weapon…
That's right!
I'm Hozukimaru!
Are you really Hozukimaru?
Want to confirm it?
How do I do that?
However you want.
Let's see…
Well, it's been a while,
so why don't we do "that"?
"That"?
If you're really Hozukimaru,
you should be able to
keep up with me.
I see… "That"…
Let's do this!
Okay!
– Luck, luck, luck! L-L-Luck!
– Luck, luck, luck!
– Luck!
– L-L-Luck!
– Luck, luck, luck!
– Luck!
– L-L-Luck!
– Lucky!
What the hell are you two doing?
What?
Did you forget about it, Ichigo?
It's my "Lucky Dance"!
I showed it to you
the first time we fought!
You did?
Whatever.
Anyway, your dance was perfect.
You are, without a doubt,
Hozukimaru!
This is perfect.
If I defeat you,
my Zanpakuto power will return.
Will you be able to?
I'm going to give it a try.
You're open for an attack!
I missed!
What's the big idea?!
It's your fault for not
paying attention in battle!
What a cheater.
Winning is all that matters!
If you're my Zanpakuto,
you know my rules
for fighting, don't you?
Of course.
Battles are always
fought one-on-one.
Whoever dies…
…no regrets!
What's wrong?!
My Zanpakuto can't be this weak!
Don't be hasty!
We've only just begun!
So you can fight!
You're really blood-thirsty,
aren't you?
We both are.
This is where
the real fight begins!
In that case,
I should start getting serious.
Huh? What's that?
Ikkaku!
Are you all right?! Hey!
You again?!
Stop sneaking around
and come on out!
As pitiful as he is,
my Soul Reaper partner
is a member of
the Stealth Force, after all!
I see…
That's how it goes!
That's not going to work!
This…is…nothing…
Ikkaku!
Are you all right?
What's this?
Is this all you've got?
You bastard!
Wait, Ichigo!
Don't interfere.
This is my battle.
Ikkaku…
Stop right there!
We've surrounded the area.
Sorry, but that's the situation.
Ukitake!
Wait, Captain Ukitake!
This is my battle!
This is no fun.
What?
I said, that I'm done for today.
You can't do that.
What are you doing?!
Hold him down!
Yes, ma'am!
Wh-Where is he?
He's gone!
Don't let him get away!
After him!
It's no good.
His Spiritual Pressure
is already gone.
Captain Soi Fon!
What should we do with him?
Shall we hand him over
to Lieutenant Omaeda?
Where is Omaeda!
Over here!
He's unconscious, though.
Lieutenant!
Pull yourself together!
There's no need for that.
Leave him!
My, my… You sure are strict.
For the time being, I think we
should hand that Zanpakuto over
to the Department of
Research and Development.
That's fine.
Come to think of it,
where's Ichigo?
Isn't it obvious?
Don't think you can
get away from me.
Bankai!
That was…!
Byakuya?!
Huh? Where's Gegetsuburi?
I sent him to the Department
of Research and Development.
Oh, thank you very much.
Wait, what?!
Don't worry about Squad Two.
From now on, you can focus
on your family business instead.
What's going to happen
to me and Gegetsuburi?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Food tastes best after
a training session!
Today I'm having…
Whoa!
What is this?!
Hey! Don't let my frog loose!
You still have much to learn…
What happened to
the food inside?
Perhaps the frog ate it.
My lunch…