<right>I'M THE NEW CAPTAIN!<br><br>
Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends have
marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
One by one, Ichigo's friends fall
amid their fierce battles.
After many hardships, Ichigo fights
his final battle with Grimmjow.
Grind… Pantera!
Is that really Kurosaki?
G-Give it your all, Ichigo!
Come on! What are you doing?!
You cheer him on too!
Huh?
Don't “Huh?” Nel!
Ichigo is fighting for you!
So why are you afraid of him?!
That's right…
At first I came here because
I wanted to protect everyone.
I thought I was ready.
But…
I heard that Kurosaki and
the others came to save me,
and I was happy
somewhere in my heart.
When I saw Kurosaki
wearing a mask,
I thought that he may not
have come to save me.
That's not true.
That's actually…
None of that really matters.
Don't die…
Don't die, Kurosaki!
You don't have to win.
You don't have to try.
Just don't get hurt anymore.
Kurosaki!
Sorry, Grimmjow.
It seems that…
I can't lose to you any longer.
It's over.
Don't make me laugh!
D-Do you think…that you've won…
against me?!
Kurosaki!
Gillians have no sense of self.
It is said that Gillians,
the lowest level of Menos,
are born when hundreds of Hollows
combine with each other.
However, that is not correct.
Hollows eat human souls in order to
fill the void of their lost hearts
and rid themselves of
their hunger for souls.
But in rare cases, a Hollow appears
with an extreme hunger.
For some reason, they seek out
the souls of their fellow Hollows.
Hollows that want Hollow souls
naturally come together
and begin eating each other.
As they do,
their souls become entangled,
they lose their individuality,
and they become
giant and foolish Gillains
who have immense
spiritual power.
But sometimes one of
the Hollows that was eaten
has abilities and a sense of self
that surpasses the others.
In such cases, they become a Gillian
that has not lost its sense of self.
That Gillian continues to evolve
by eating other Gillians,
and soon comes to
be called an Adjuchas.
Those who have become Adjuchas
are exposed to a greater fear.
The fear of regression.
If an Adjuchas doesn't
continue to eat Hollows,
it will regress into a Gillian.
Those who regress are guaranteed
to lose their individuality.
They'll never become
an Adjuchas again.
What's this?
You're a pretty small Adjuchas.
Sorry…
I'm going to eat you.
Why you…
What's this?
D Roy was defeated instantly.
This is a first.
Guys like this exist, huh?
You're strong.
What is your name, Adjuchas?
Grimmjow.
I'm Shawlong.
Join us, Grimmjow.
I won't ask you to do it for free.
What are you doing?
We have no intention of
remaining Gillians or Adjuchas.
We will become Vasto Lordes.
In order to do that,
we need power.
We need a strong power
to draw us all together.
You are suited for that.
Let's go together, Grimmjow.
You…will be our king,
Grimmjow.
What's with that look on your face?
You're always like that.
No matter how much I best you…
You think that you can beat me.
You think you're stronger than I am!
I hate that!
What do you hate?
Do you hate that a mere human
is treating you like an equal?!
That has nothing to do with it!
It doesn't matter if you're a human,
a Soul Reaper, or an Arrancar!
I'll crush anyone
who takes me for a fool!
I'll begin…with you, Kurosaki!
Here I go.
Wha—?
What is that?!
Desgarrón.
It's my strongest technique.
What?
I told you that
we give up, Grimmjow.
How long do you think it's been
since we started following you
Who knows?
We realized that we cannot
become Vasto Lordes.
Since eating
our thousandth Hollow,
we can no longer sense
our power getting any stronger.
Today's prey makes
three thousand.
We realized that continuing
to do this is useless.
How stupid.
If you want to quit,
then just go ahead and die.
I'm going.
Yes, that doesn't matter.
But if you're going to go,
then do it after you've eaten us.
Those who have had
parts of them
eaten by other Hollows
stop evolving completely.
D Roy can't become
a Vasto Lorde anymore.
We already know that.
And our evolution
has come to an end.
You cowards.
I told you that we've
realized something.
Those who do or don't
become Vasto Lordes
are probably determined from
when they were Hollows.
No…
Perhaps even before then.
We realize that now.
From the moment
we became Hollows,
it was decided that
we would become Adjuchas,
and you would
go beyond that.
Eat us, Grimmjow.
It's over, Kurosaki!
You make me sick.
You're going to lose to me!
You're all cowards.
Fine… I'll eat you all.
Become my flesh and blood
and watch what happens.
I…
I am the king!
You're…
You're not the only one
who wants to win.
What?
“I’ll begin with you,” you say?
That’s my line!
It's as you say.
I came here to fight with you.
I came here to defeat you,
Grimmjow!
I'm going to defeat you!
I'm going to defeat Ulquiorra!
I'm going to defeat Aizen!
Rukia!
Chad!
Ishida!
Renji!
And Inoue!
I'm going to bring them all back!
I can't lose to you, Grimmjow!
Damn…
K-Kuro—
Wounds…
Are you wounded?
Inoue?
Thank goodness.
It's the usual Kurosaki.
No.
Thank you.
Ichigo!
Y-You idiot! What are you thinking?!
We're up high!
We'll die if we fall! Jeez!
Thank goodness.
I'm glad that you didn't die.
Yeah.
Thanks, Nel.
Kurosaki…
Let's go… Everyone's waiting.
Yeah.
Now that I've saved Inoue,
I'm going to get back the Hogyoku!
What are you doing, Ichigo?
If you don't get ready, we'll be late.
Rukia?!
You're safe?!
Huh? Stop talking nonsense.
We're going to school!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Huh?
How long are you going to
stay dressed like that?!
H-Hey…
What's the meaning of this?!
Where's Hueco Mundo?
Where are the Arrancars?
– Ichigo!
– Nel?!
Due to production
going a different route,
we're going to
appear a little later!
I just came to say farewell until then!
Going a different route?!
Now that you know,
get changed already!
Hey… What are we doing?
A new story starts
in the next episode!
NEW CAPTAIN SHUSUKE AMAGAI ARC
A new captain is coming to
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
Are you serious?!