Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
So running away is
all that's left for you!
You disappear from
my range of vision
to attack with projectile weapons…
You're as rotten as you look!
Rotten? What of it?
Does it have anything
to do with life and death?
It's not compatible with
my way of fighting.
Like I care.
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to take lives.
I have no interest in
how my master fights.
I always thought that
the relationship between
a Zanpakuto and a Soul Reaper was
one of communication and synergy.
I don't know about
other Zanpakuto!
I'm me. I cut down lives!
I thought that was our sole
agreement between you and me.
I see.
Then it's easy.
If you die and my Zanpakuto
disappears, so be it.
I don't like you.
I just realized that.
Fine with me.
Because the feeling is mutual.
You say the Sword Beasts are
attacking Rukon District?
Yeah…
Seems like they've teamed up
and are going on a rampage.
I hope the damage doesn't get
any worse than it already is…
Let's hurry!
What is that?!
Speak of the devil…
Must be a Sword Beast!
No…
That's not what it is…
That's…
Hisagi…
– Isn't that your Zanpakuto?
– Go on ahead.
I'm the one he's after…
Hey!
Let's go on ahead.
Not bad.
A surprise attack again?
You don't give up, do you?
That's right.
I'm sorry, but I'll do
whatever it takes.
Until we settle our fight,
I will pursue you
to the ends of the earth.
Reap, Kazeshini.
What's going on, Kira?
Wasn't that Hisagi's Zanpakuto,
Kazeshini?
Did it join the Sword Beasts?
No, that's not what happened…
Hisagi's Zanpakuto…
Kazeshini, is unlike
the other Zanpakuto.
It seems it continues
to act independently
even after the Muramasa
incident was resolved.
Kazeshini is a Zanpakuto
that reaps lives.
Hisagi said that once
it targets someone,
it will keep pursuing its target,
even if that target
is its own master,
until the fight is settled…
You're saying it stakes
its own life to kill?
Man…Hisagi sure has
a difficult Zanpakuto…
Yeah…
As usual, you keep
running from my blade!
While you fight by hiding,
as usual…
I don't like the way
you always try to
pull a surprise attack on people!
I don't care!
My goal is to reap your life!
It's meaningless to debate
our methods just for that!
Bakudo 62, Hyapporankan!
You bastard…
This is what you were aiming
for right from the start…
Who knows?
At any rate,
until you attack me head-on,
I have no intention of
settling our fight!
For crying out loud…
Always trying to be the hypocrite!
I hate it!
We agree then.
Didn't I say the same thing?
I hate the way you fight…
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, Hisagi…are you done
with your business?
Yeah, sort of…
What's the situation?
We were too late.
By the time we got here,
they had already disappeared…
The only way is to chase them down
before they do more damage…
You attacked
your master again, I hear.
Give us a break, will you?
Because of your selfish actions,
the Soul Reapers are
starting to think that
we're going to cause
more trouble for them.
Why do you insist on
trying to kill you master?
You're free of Muramasa's
mind control, right?
It's none of
your damn business…
None of our business?
What you do is your business,
but stop making trouble
for us in the process.
We are Zanpakuto…
If you want to isolate yourself,
we won't stop you.
But we won't help you, either.
That's great!
Because I don't have any intention
of looking after you guys, either!
He's so gloomy.
Look who's talking!
A Sword Beast!
A Sword Beast is attacking!
Help!
Stop!
Fancy meeting you here!
You're mine!
I don't have time to fight you!
Come back here!
Hey!
Is it that important to protect
people you don't even know?
Lost him…
Someone!
You?
It's not him…
Wait.
Who are you?
Huh?
You're not one of us…
Are you one of
the Soul Reaper's dogs?
A Soul Reaper's dog?
Stop messing around!
You…
You're…not one of them?
Don't lump me in with them.
Please…look after the baby…
I beg you…
Say what?
Sorry…
I'm not one of the Sword Beasts,
but I'm still a Zanpakuto.
I have no interest in anything
but reaping lives…
This kid's hands are going to
make my blade rust…
Let go!
Move!
Stop crying!
I hear crying!
Over there, Iba!
Don't cry! Come on, don't cry!
I guess I have no choice!
Listen…
I came this far
without killing you.
Be grateful and just
go disappear somewhere.
Man, you are such a pain…
Don't follow me!
If you follow me this time,
I'll get rid of you!
Oh, so you like that…
Just wait here for
someone to come get you.
See ya!
What the hell?!
What is that on your back?!
Kazeshini,
he looks so good on you.
Damn it…
I'm going to kill you…
Hey, kid…Laugh…
I said laugh…
Gloomy kid…
I know I already said this,
but look who's talking…
How did this happen?
You should've just
left the kid somewhere.
Shut up!
I don't know how,
but it just turned out this way…
Anyways, somebody take him!
Huh?
What're you talking about?
You said you were grateful that
we wouldn't be helping you.
No, but that was…
Good luck raising a kid!
Bye-bye!
W-Wait a minute…
What the hell is this?
Something's not right…
Why is this happening to me?
This Spiritual Pressure…
The lieutenants are
on the move…
Here I come!
Idiot!
You'll cut yourself
if you touch that!
Do you want to die?
I said no!
Okay, okay. Don't cry!
Man, this brat really
gets under my skin…
Huh? What happened?
What? You must be kidding!
You're kidding me! No way…
Damn it, this really
messes things up…
There they are…
Hey, what was that for?
H-Hey!
Damn! Don't fall asleep here.
Have you heard, Hisagi?
About what?
Among the Zanpakuto,
there's a rumor going
around about yours.
Found you.
Stay right here…
Okay…
Just be quiet and
stay here for a while.
Help!
Stop! Hey!
You're not getting away!
Man, they sure take up
a lot of time…
Stubborn bastards!
Why now?
I won't get a better opportunity!
There, there, you're a good child.
Don't cry!
Please spare us!
No!
What?
Woman…
Y-Yes?
Did you try to take away this kid?
Yes…because
he was crying alone.
Do me a favor…
take this kid and…
You again?
Soul Reaper's dog!
You…
We will kill our enemies!
I've got you now!
Fancy meeting you here!
Umm…
Take that kid and
get away from here.
Huh?
Just get away.
Right!
Hey…
I've been waiting for this…
You said…
You wouldn't settle this until
I attacked head-on…right?
Yeah.
That's why I'm here…
Yeah…
– Reap…
Go to sleep,
go to sleep little darling…
Go to sleep, go to sleep
You're a good child…
Go to sleep…
One question:
What'd you do with the kid?
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Hey, why don't we put an end
to this right about now…
Yeah, good idea…
We get along don't we?
You think so?
Don't…cry…
Hey…Am I going to turn back
to being a normal Zanpakuto?
Yes…
When I'm a Zanpakuto again…
What will you and I fight for?
We'll fight to protect something…
I see…
Can't stand words
from a hypocrite?
I don't!
But…
I guess I don't have a choice…
Don't cry…huh?
Hey Wabisuke, who was that kid
Kazeshini was carrying around?
He wouldn't return home…
and he had a baby…
There's only one conclusion we
can draw from those two things…
Are you saying?!
It was his love child.
I knew it!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Sir Kira!
This isn't much,
but I wanted you to have this.
What?
I caused you
a great deal of trouble
when I was under
Muramasa's mind control…
This is a small token of apology.
No, that isn't necessary…
You're very kind, Sir Kira!
I'm looking forward to working
with you from now on!
Ah!
Sorry. If you'll excuse me…
I caused you so much
trouble in the past…
He's like a totally
different person now…