Me too!
Konso Cop Karakurizer.
They are born on the whim
of Professor Urahara...
No, no, that's wrong!
They are warriors of justice
born from his love for peace!
They fight to protect the people from evil!
Go! Karakurizer!
You are the protectors of
peace in Karakura Town!
Go get'em!
KONSO COP KARAKURIZER
S-Somebody...
Somebody help me!
Stop right there!
Miss, you're safe now.
I will take care of that guy in no time!
Karakurizer!
Job...
Switch?
What the heck?
Whoa!
Hey you! That guy was mine.
Thank you very much for saving me.
Don't mention it.
Were you injured, young lady?
Oh, Michel...
My hero.
Shock! Shock! Shock!
And another shock!
Everything is going as planned.
I'm impressed with you.
Or, in this case...
Perhaps I should be impressed with
myself for creating a being like you.
Just you wait and see.
This time, Karakura Town will be mine!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Hey, scheming owner!
Kisuke's out buying merchandise.
Hey, Karakurizer!
Beast?
Why are you all gathered here?!
-We were called here.
Have some tea.
But I wasn't called.
I think he forgot about you.
Don't forget!
If it helps, Spirits is
abroad doing a shoot.
I mean, he's absent because
he's carrying out a mission.
Now then, I'll read Kisuke's orders.
Good day, everyone!
It appears that the Female Arrancar
you previously defeated
is up to no good again.
Please investigate.
The end.
Is that all?
Yes.
Man, how sketchy can he get?
But never mind that.
There's a guy other than us in this town
who has the power to defeat Hollows!
He wears an odd cape and flies
through the sky like some sort of hero!
Damn it!
Say... Isn't that Michel?
Oh yeah, the Whole chick did say that name.
Michel!
Who the heck is he?
-What?!
Huh? Huh?
Why're you looking at me like that?!
What the hell's going on?!
Wait...
You really don't know?
You're so behind.
He's the handsome Spiritualist
everyone's raving about.
Handsome Spiritualist?
MICHEL, THE GREAT SPIRITUALIST
He's really cool.
He's nice.
And he can fly with his cape!
They're even selling
replicas of Michel's cape.
These days, you hardly see
anyone in town without a cape.
What's with that? It looks lame.
Not at all!
It matches his gallant figure perfectly!
Huh? I thought you weren't
interested in men!
I wasn't?
Here's the love of your life!
It's my prized photo of Inoue!
My, it's Orihime.
What?!
Is that all you feel?!
She's cute,
but what more of a comment
did you expect from me, a girl?
You're kidding, right?
I'll take that.
At any rate, you met Michel.
Met him? Well...um...
How lucky! I wish I could've met him too!
You've got it all wrong!
He got in my way!
Besides, there's no such
thing as a perfect man
who's both handsome and nice!
Well, there is, so give it up.
I'll bet he helped you just as you were
about to screw up.
Not so!
But, why is Michel in Karakura Town?
Maybe Michel's also here
to investigate the Arrancar.
If that's so...
If we go and investigate,
we might run into Michel too.
Okay! Let's go meet Michel!
-Yeah!
-Let's go! Let's go!
-What?!
W-Wait!
I'm telling you, he had
no intention of helping me!
Hey, are you guys listening?!
He was a jerk, looking
down on me with a sneer.
No way. He's a good guy.
How do you know?
Well, the other day,
there was a TV shoot done
without Michel's knowledge,
but he was super nice through it all!
Oh, I saw that too.
He was seriously cool!
Michel!
No shoving, no shoving.
Can I have your autograph?
Thank you.
An autograph?
He's so wonderful!
Can I have one too?
Me too!
That bastard.
Hey, what're you doing?
It's Michel!
It's true. He's here in Karakura Town!
He looked this way!
Bye.
He's coming this way!
Hey there!
You're the young man who was
attacked by the Hollow earlier, right?
Are you okay?
Huh?
I had a shoot to go to so
I couldn't make sure you
were all right, but...
Were you injured?
Come on! Don't you have
something to tell him?
Something to tell him?
A thank you!
He saved you, so say a proper thank you!
But I didn't ask to be saved by him.
I'm sorry. He has no manners.
That's all right. It's no big deal.
So cool!
I'm disappointed in you, Kon!
Sis...
But...I...
Even if you don't want to say it,
he did save you,
so you need to say, "thank you."
Inoue...
What's the benefit of
making yourself look bad?!
No one's going to sympathize with your
"he disgusts you because
he's perfect" excuse.
We'll help you out!
Okay!
I will be a man!
MAN
Th..ank...
Huh?
Hi!
We're your fans.
Can I have your autograph?
If you don't mind, can
I shake hands with you?
Please?
What's that?!
Look out!
What is this wind?!
I'll handle this. Don't interfere!
Job Switch!
Wait!
Huh?
Oh no!
You're okay?
Yeah...
With a single blow?
Monsters like that are dangerous,
so don't get any ideas
about fighting them,
and just leave them to me.
So cool!
Were you injured?
I'm fine.
He seems okay, as well.
Thank you so much, Michel!
That was super cool back
there! I was deeply moved.
U-Um... Can I please shake hands with you?!
-Could you tell me your 3 sizes?
-Oh, come on...
Know what? I hear Michel
is in Karakura Town.
Oh no! What if we meet him in person?!
They're all wearing capes!
Even here?!
Look! That's Michel!
Huh?!
Residents of Karakura Town!
Thank you always for your support!
I'm Michel.
Today, I have some special
news I'd like you to hear.
Those guys!
The young men and women I met today,
the Karakurizers,
have been protecting this
town unbeknownst to you all.
Karakura Town is a marvelous town to have
such wonderful young men and women!
I'm very happy to have been
able to come to this town.
I've presented them with
a specially made cape.
A genuine flying cape!
Michel sure is cool!
What?!
He's generous, and he's nice.
Michel's totally better.
Inoue, forget about this guy.
You're right.
Sis!
Inoue!
They're right.
He's way better, isn't he?
So? How did it feel to fly?
It was a little scary, but it rocked!
We owe it all to you, Michel,
to be able to experience something like this!
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
I was just thinking
that he might have also wanted to fly too.
You mean that fake Kurosaki?
Yeah.
Let it go.
It's his own fault for
just leaving like that.
Well, yeah, but...
Are you that worried about that young man?
Not worried...
But he's still our teammate.
You'd rather be with him than me?
Of course not!
Michel, you're way better, of course!
But...we've always fought together, and...
But he disappeared without even
saying thank you for being saved.
Karakurizer is a bad guy.
-Yes.
-Yes
Why is everyone suddenly saying such things?
Besides, why say that now, Michel?
Wait...
Since when did I become
so into Michel anyway?
I intended to let you play a little longer,
but the effects wore off too quickly.
W-What's going on?!
Karakurizer!
KONSO COP KARAKURIZER
-Karakurizer!
Home is so far away.
What are you?
Beast!
And Michel?
I've come under orders
from a certain individual
to invade Karakura Town.
You people are in the way of that objective.
He was a villain after all!
That is why I've placed everyone,
including you, under hypnosis.
And then, I used those
capes to suck away all of your Spirit Energy.
It's meaningless.
By now, you hardly have any power left.
See?
I'll quickly send you to your
death with the other three.
Now prepare to die!
Bastard!
I...I can't take him.
For now, I need to report this to someone.
It's not...over yet!
He... Karakurizer
is still left!
Oh, you mean him?
For some reason, my powers didn't
seem to work on him, but...
Who cares, anyway?
Karakurizer won't...lose
to the likes of you!
Is that all you have to say?
It doesn't matter what you believe.
This is reality.
Hold it right there!
I leaped out without thinking.
You...
You saved me the trouble of looking for you.
Are you all right?!
I...I'm okay.
Never mind me.
I know.
Leave the rest to me!
I-I heard everything!
I'm taking you on!
Is that so? In that case...
W-What the heck?
I simply borrowed their Spiritual Pressure.
Now, shall we begin?!
Job Switch!
Here I come!
D-Damn it...
You're no match for me.
No matter what you do, it's useless.
I'm more powerful than you are.
And what's more, I'm handsome.
Do you think you can beat me?
Now, it's over, Karakurizer!
Don't give up!
Karakurizer!
Go!
Why you...
No matter what, I...
won't lose to you!
What is this cape?
Why are we wearing these things?
Who is this guy?!
Lame!
Here's another one!
Don't get so cocky!
What's with your face?!
You're missing a tooth!
So lame!
What?!
A tooth...
My tooth!
Damn it! Where's my tooth?!
There's no way I'm going to lose to
such an uncool-looking bastard!
What?!
How dare you!
This is my true form!
I will make short work of crushing you!
Oh, so you're not even close to handsome!
You're just an ordinary Hollow!
My Great Kick!
Don't underestimate my leg strength!
Take that!
What?!
There's no way...
I'm going to lose to...
an ugly Hollow...
like you!
Special Technique!
Ri-z-er!
Beam!
Pose!
You did it, Karakurizer!
There's no such thing as a perfect man!
I'll get you for this!
Karakurizer!
If I hadn't been around,
you'd have been goners!
Be thankful!
That's why we said thank you!
We were wrong.
There had to be something wrong for me
to be turned on by someone
other than Orihime...
and a man at that!
You owe everything to me.
Another juice for me!
Kon remained normal because
he was a Soul Candy.
But I won't tell.
Peace has returned to Karakura Town
thanks to the efforts of Karakurizer!
But the evil Hollows will continue
to target Karakura Town.
Go, Karakurizer!
Your battle will continue on?
The peace of Karakura Town is
saved thanks to the efforts
of the Karakurizers!
Are you kidding?
I'm the one who saved the day today!
Rephrase that to a singular!
Thanks to the efforts of the KarakurizerS!
Hey!
Go get'em!
You're doing it on purpose, aren't you?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I'm home!
I've been waiting for you, Karakurizer!
Ishida! You...that cape better not be...
Relax. This is my own.
RIZER CAPE
Now that I think about it,
Ishida designed that suit.
Thanks for rescuing those capes from evil!
Oh! Well that's what I do!
As a token of appreciation,
I've done an upgrade to your
stuffed animal form!
Go on, jump right in!
Don't go doing unnecessary things!