Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
I won't…give…in…
What the—?!
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
This isn't good!
Garganta is opening up…
And we're in a bad situation…
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Sodeno…shirayuki…
There are others who've
come to help, as well!
Sorry to keep you guys waiting!
Renji…
Looks like Soul Reapers
aren't the only ones here…
Could it be that those people
are everyone's Zanpakuto?
What's going on?
Weren't the Zanpakuto
in rebellion?
Please explain, Sodenoshirayuki.
Yes, ma'am.
Captain Kurotsuchi undid the mind
control over the Zanpakuto.
Anyway, that's what happened.
We apologize for
the turmoil we caused.
In exchange…
We will work hard to make it up.
Snap!
Growl!
– Roar!
Extend!
Tear in Frenzy!
Hey you!
What's the idea of going ahead
of your master?!
What're you talking about?
Right now, master shmaster,
it doesn't matter!
How I hate this.
Do you realize how ugly it is
to rush to get the credit?
You don't seem to get that
being jealous of
getting beaten to the punch
is far more ugly…
They're coming!
Yeah.
Somenomai, Tsukishiro!
It's a Cero!
Good grief…
Can't let those hot-blooded
Zanpakuto do the job alone…
Thanks for helping us.
Helping you?
I had no such intention.
I'm just taking care of
what needs to be done.
Shunko!
Ishida?!
What're you doing, Ishida?!
You!
What will you do if your careless
attacks damage the town?!
And Kurosaki's still inside there…
Not my concern.
My mission is to
get rid of that thing.
I won't let you interfere.
Captain Soi Fon!
Stop it!
This is no time for that.
Our priority is the Hollows
that surround us.
All right, fine.
Captain Hitsugaya…
You people check for Ichigo
Kurosaki's Spiritual Pressure
to find out how he is
doing inside there.
Thank you very much,
Captain Hitsugaya.
But our enemy's
numbers are so great…
Even if we faced them
together with our Zanpakuto,
they're still going to be
difficult to handle…
At this very moment,
Captain Kurotsuchi continues to
release the remaining Zanpakuto
from the mind control,
but there's not enough time to wait
for them to rendezvous with us…
Let me confirm with you.
We will take care of
all of the ones here.
Is that okay with you?
Of course.
I have your back.
Mind your own business…
Roar!
Monkey… Weren't those two…
Yeah…they had us
completely fooled…
Cut it out.
We're in the middle of a battle.
But you know…I get it…
I know how Hozukimaru feels.
He even put on a hokey act
by claiming he wouldn't
accept Soul Reapers…
Whatever the reason,
it doesn't sit right.
This is no time to be
talking about that!
But…
You can sort out your feelings
later, at your leisure.
More importantly, right now,
we have a mission as Zanpakuto.
Yes, I understand.
Let's do our best, everyone!
Did your personality change after
the mind control was undone?
You think so?
At any rate, I don't like it!
Enough!
She can't help it.
It's not just the Zanpakuto
that feel that way.
Rangiku…
Although we are members of the same
Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
we have no intention of
being bound by the mission…
It's none of my business
how you people feel,
but it's also my right
to think what I want.
Are you okay, Captain?
Surely you're not going to say
you've reached your limit
with only injuries like those,
are you?
Karakura Town has been
placed in an Area Freeze.
We're now free to use full power.
What do you mean "full power"?
If you get carried away
and commit a blunder,
we're not cleaning up after you!
You don't want someone
with a big butt
cleaning up after you,
right, Renji?
Why're you such a dummy
like your master!
Can't help it!
Because, in fact, he is a dummy!
Hey! Cut that out, you guys!
But…let me say this, Captain…
I'm sure there are people
who want to give you a
piece of their mind…
But Captain, I…I…
Renji.
Let's go.
That's what you get for
trying to play it cool…
You suck!
Shut up!
Come on, let's go!
Let's do this, Omaeda.
Right! I'll show those guys that
they're no match for me!
Smash'em! Gegetsuburi!
Damn it you!
What'd you do that for?!
Don't tell me you
haven't been released
from Muramasa's mind control!
It's not that!
Then what's the big idea?!
Kicking your beloved master
in the back like that!
Address me as "Mister."
Huh?
Say, "Smash'em,
Mister Gegetsuburi"!
What?
What Soul Reaper addresses
his own Zanpakuto with "Mister"
– when doing a Shikai?!
– Uh, excuse me…
You can do it! Make history!
– Don't talk nonsense!
– This is hopeless.
It's because you were
being so annoying!
That's because you won't
address me with "Mister"!
Raise your head…
Captain Komamura…
Wow…
That grazed me a bit…
Maybe I took too much rest…
My body seems a bit slow.
Keep wasting your time,
and I'll take care of
everything by myself.
That's fine with me,
but the least you can do is to keep
from getting caught in my power.
Yes, Sir… We're sorry.
I think I dribbled…
It's no use…
I can't sense Ichigo's
Spiritual Pressure…
Kurosaki…
There's no sense
just waiting like this.
We need to take measures fast.
Wait, Ishida!
What's with that?!
Muramasa's Spiritual Pressure
is out of control.
Even with a captain's Bankai,
it won't be easy to defeat him.
But unless we do something…
What was that?
That's…
No way!
Are more of them
still coming out?!
Is this for real?
We're not going to have to face
all of them, as well, are we?
Looks like we are.
Man, this makes
so much extra work…
Captain Komamura…
Looks like this is no time
to be arguing, eh?
Guess we have no choice.
Times like this are the only time
you two get along, it seems…
We won't get
anywhere like this…
The Spiritual Pressure
of the sphere
has increased even further…
It's inducing the fissure to
expand and attracting Menos.
At this rate, infinite flow of
Menos will come this way.
There'll be no end!
I'm going!
Where?
To that fissure.
If I can seal it,
that should help, right?
Are you an idiot?!
How're you going to
seal something that big?!
The fissure!
This is bad.
More is about to flow out…
We have to stop it!
How?!
Do something!
You do something!
Captain Kuchiki!
Brother!
They're…
What immense
Spiritual Pressure!
In his depleted condition…
Where is that power
coming from?!
He's using his Spiritual Pressure
to force them back!
It's crazy reckless!
Is that even possible?
It might be possible with
immense Spiritual Pressure…
However…
Incredible!
Now!
Did we do it?
Yeah…
Are you all right?
Who do you think you're asking?
Man, he is one reckless dude…
That's nothing…
In the end,
he needed our power, right?
Oh my…am I beat…
Isn't that because you're
older than you think?
Huh?!
All right!
Let's take care of the rest!
Right!
What the?!
Is it still expanding?!
What's with that thing!
What about Kurosaki?
Can he be saved?!
I don't know…
But since we can't get near it,
we'll have to leave
the rest to Ichigo himself.
But…
Ichigo!
Kurosaki…
I hear a voice…
Who is it that calls for me?
So…it's you?
Fine. Let's settle everything
once and for all!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey! Get up!
Everyone's already left for battle.
Kazeshini?!
I've come to my senses.
I'm sorry about before…
I hurt you really bad.
From now on, use me all you
want as your good Zanpakuto.
Kazeshini…
I'm sorry for saying all
those nasty things to you…
Did you believe
I'd really say that?!
Huh?
I did it! I did it!
– You're an idiot!
– Hey, you!