Dog Food Doesn't Have As
Much Flavor As You'd Think
What's that look for?
Got a problem?
If it's not enough, eat the meatballs
on the bottoms of your feet.
meatball (paw pads)
Sorry, Sadaharu.
You'll have to make do with this today.
Odd Jobs is going through
a food shortage right now.
We're all starving.
That's a good boy.
Gin-chan, Sadaharu understands.
Good.
Then the three of us can split this.
Thanks.
What the hell?!
Don't you have any human dignity?!
You shouldn't steal food from your
pet, no matter how hungry you are!
You should be ashamed!
Can you blame us?
It's been ages since
we last had a client,
so we don't have a single
grain of rice left.
The situation's so grim
that we may go from eating dog
food to eating the dog for food.
Eating the dog for food?!
You're moving from pissing off the
PTA to pissing off PETA now?!
What's that about PETA?
Does the PTA eat PETA?
The PTA only eats up
teachers with an attitude.
That's completely different!
Quit your bitching.
Whose fault do you think this is?
It's because of this large animal
that eats a lot and never works,
and the glasses boy who just
wears glasses and never works.
Hey! You've crossed the line now!
Apologize! Apologize to my glasses!
Seriously, you should
try to understand
how hard it is for me to
take care of you all.
Hey, you're sporting some
yummy-looking wings.
They're not wings!
They're greasy glasses!
And they're not greasy!
You're wearing shellfish to be fashionable?!
Are you supposed to be Takeda Kumiko?!
Wait!
These people are so hungry
that they're hallucinating!
Hand that over!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Those are my glasses!
You can't eat them!
Hey!
Why are you grilling them?!
You should try to understand how hard
it is for me to take care of you all.
Please take me home.
Enough already!
Egg on rice again?!
Why do you waste food like this?!
What food? The fridge was empty.
Your head is empty!
Sadaharu puts up with the meager
servings of cheap food we give him.
Shut up and eat.
Ah, is that so?
Here you go then.
Gin-chan! Sadaharu isn't
your garbage disposal!
And there's no food left
if you refuse to eat that.
Sorry, but unlike the rest
of you, I'm a gourmet.
You animals can have your pet food.
I-It's so cute!
What is this?!
Where did you find it, Captain Okita?!
Hold on, Sogo...
Isn't that the Odd Jobs dog?
I don't know if he was
dumped or if he ran away,
but he was urinating in the streets.
Uh, so why did you bring him here?
Oh, you remember how we screwed up
the last time we tried to boost
our image with a mascot?
We should give it another try.
We can make some money by dumping him
and Hijikata-san at the South Pole
and making the one who
returns alive our mascot.
That wouldn't be a mascot!
It'd be a scum-cot!
Give me a break.
We don't need any symbols
of weakness like mascots.
Besides, we already have a
mascot in Kondo-san, you fool.
He's no mascot! He's a shit-cot!
Who was that?! Who
called me Ridley Scott?!
Thank you!
Nobody had anything
nice to say about you.
And why do we have to take
in their used goods?
He'll interfere with our work.
Get rid of him.
Vice-Chief, are you telling us to
throw out this adorable creature?!
Adorable, my ass.
I'll have you all commit seppuku
for failing as warriors.
Then you throw it out!
Fine, you fools.
Kondo-san...
I just remembered that we
don't have any police dogs.
You commit seppuku!
Shut up!
I'm just saying that
we need police dogs!
There's nothing adorable
about this furball!
First, we'll run some tests to
see if it's qualified enough!
And I won't go easy on dogs, dammit!
Listen up! Police dogs
depend on their noses.
They need to be able to sniff out
suspects, drugs, and all kinds of stuff.
So here's a test.
Half-fat, quarter-fat,
non-cholesterol, non-oil, mustard.
Can you tell the difference?
They're all mayonnaise!
Hey, what are you planning on
using these police dogs for?!
What kind of crime are
you preparing for?!
First, identify my favorite type.
Uh, nobody knows what you
like! And nobody cares!
Ah, the quarter-fat?
An excellent choice.
But right now, I'm in the
mood for some non-oil.
Your preference changes?!
But I like your taste.
Here's your reward.
Enjoy.
You just wanted to feed
the dog mayonnaise!
Don't be shy.
Hurry up and eat.
Hurry up.
Yes, there, there.
Honestly, I don't know what happened,
but you should probably make up soon.
I know.
Gin-san isn't the kind of person
who would kick you out.
You probably left because he
was being nasty as usual.
Unfortunately, I won't be
able to keep you here.
You already have a home, after all.
But if you plan on making up soon,
you can stay here until then.
I can't let Gin-san's precious
pet die on the streets.
Stop, that tickles.
I envy you.
Do you do this with
Gin-san all the time?
I wish I could have been
born as Gin-san's pet.
Just kidding.
I'll go make something to eat.
You must be hungry.
Wait here.
The moment I've been waiting
for has finally come!
This is my chance to
become Gin-san's pet!
His white fur will be my wedding dress!
Hold on, Gin-san.
Your cute pet will be coming
back to you soon.
Ah, I see.
It must have been difficult
to have such a lazy owner.
But Sadaharu, I knew that
you would wake up one day.
The spirit of the Joi burns within you.
I knew that it would guide
you to your true leader.
That you would find me.
And that is why
I've been waiting here since
that game of Kick the Can
two months ago.
You can't have an episode about
Master Shoyo without me.
I managed to adjust my
schedule so I could squeeze in,
but I didn't expect this to take so long.
I'm an expert at hiding,
but it's been so long
that I had to wonder if
the game was already over.
If anyone had even noticed
that I was playing...
I felt like crying for a moment.
Runaway Kotaro tried a
little too hard there.
I caused everyone so much trouble.
Well, everyone's probably been
worried and looking for me.
I should probably head back.
Crap...
After staying in this position for two
months, my body is stiff as a rock!
Zabeth, call for a doctor!
How could this happen?
I don't think I can last long
enough for sensei to arrive.
S-Sadaharu-kun...
I apologize.
I won't be able to keep my promise
to become your owner.
And can you please relay a
message when the doctor comes?
Tell him to charge any taxi or
any other transportation costs
to sensei.
Please take me home.
Did you see him around here?
Yeah, it was a really big dog,
so it must have been him.
He was dragging a little puppy around.
Sadaharu...
Sadaharu, where are you?!
Say something if you're there!
Please come back!
Sadaharu!
What? Work?
Yeah, we finally have a client.
No more eating dog food.
Weren't you supposed to
be looking for Sadaharu
instead of wasting time?
Wasting time? Want me to punch you?
Aren't you worried about him, Gin-san?
Sadaharu hasn't been home in two days.
He was starving when he left,
and we don't know if he's
gotten anything to eat
Sadaharu!
or if something's happened to him.
How can you expect us to work?
Come back, Sadaharu!
That's not good, Shinpachi-kun.
You're thinking like a NEET now.
Nothing's happened to him.
Huh?
He left because he
couldn't get any food.
It's that simple.
An animal doesn't understand
the concept of family.
Besides...
I'm not interested in keeping
anyone around who isn't
willing to share when times are tough.
Even if he's just an animal.
There you go.
If you like dog food, you can eat
it for the rest of your life.
I'll go make some money and
have a chocolate parfait.
W-Wait, Gin-san!
Gin-san!
Edo Animal Hospital
It's a mononoke!
The dog god Moro has come
to hunt down our patients!
Scram, mountain dog!
This is where humans live!
Mononoke should go back
to the mountains!
It released something!
Be careful!
You'll die if you touch that stuff!
Sadaharu!
1 Fourth St.
So the owner of this house is dead?
Yes, he died all alone.
He kept a lot of dogs, and there were
many complaints from the neighbors
about the smell and noise.
There was a relative who liked
dogs and visited occasionally,
but it appears that they grew distant.
And the number of dogs was declining.
There was only one left when he died.
When the neighborhood association
cleaned his place,
she didn't know what to do
with it, so she threw it out.
W-Well, it was a mutt, sick and
frail, so nobody wanted it.
There have been rumors that
he's been wandering around.
We've been receiving complaints
from various pet owners.
They're worried it may
get their pets sick.
So could you catch it and
dispose of it for us?
Is that even necessary? It probably
died already if it was sick.
I hope so, but if we wait for it to
become a problem, it'll be too late.
If it's dying anyway, does it matter
if it happens a little sooner?
Honestly...
That old man left us a
big mess to clean up.
What's this huge dog?!
Hey, hey.
This stray's bigger than I was expecting.
It'll take some effort to dispose of it.
You know the puppy they're
talking about, right?
If you turn it over,
I'll let you come home.
The reward will buy us plenty of
food, so everyone will be happy.
Do you see a problem?
Wait up!
Odd Jobs, catch that monster!
Why are you standing there?
Hurry up already!
If you turn it over,
I'll let you come home.
Then the three of us can split this.
It stinks!
What's going on?!
Who would do such a thing?!
So many fish...
It was our dog.
It looked like he was taking
care of that puppy,
so I tampered with the
food he was bringing it.
Look. See this?
My dog is very bright.
He fed the puppy poisoned
food to do my job for me.
So can you pay up now?
Yo, you awake?
General Animal Hospital
You were suffering from malnutrition.
They told me I shouldn't have
a pet if I can't feed it.
Although you're the one who
ran off and starved yourself.
But you helped deal
with the puppy for me.
You can eat all you want today.
What?
I thought you might understand
how it feels to be an owner
after taking care of that puppy.
Were you hoping for fish tails?
Or is the portion too small,
considering the reward?
Don't blame me.
There were a lot of expenses
associated with this job,
so I used up most of
the money we received.
Besides, the Sakata family always
shares when times are tough.
We share the food
and the pain.
Thanks for sharing.
Thank you so much!
You kept Grandpa's dog safe.
Well, you should thank
the big dog inside.
Hold on!
You haven't paid for all the
medicine you fed the puppy!
Hey!
Sakata-san! Wait!
Hold on a sec!
What's this Final Act business?!
This is news to me!
Well, they're probably just fooling
around again with a fake!
Or they're pretending that it's fake.
Or it is fake.
That's what they want you to think.
But it's really fake.
You're not making any sense at all!
We only lasted half a year this time,
but thank you for all the support.
The movie is coming up in July,
so please continue to support Gintama!!
See you sometime...