Hi there, Captain Hitsugaya!
How’s it going?
Kyoraku… Ukitake…
It’s been a while.
Did something happen today?
No, just here to make a regular report.
I got grilled on the cleansing progress
within the Tenkaiketchu zone.
Oh, that should be done
as early as today.
What?!
I got a report from Nanao.
Damn that Matsumoto.
That was our squad’s
responsibility. That slacker!
Sorry. Would you mind reporting that?
He seems pretty upset.
It’s a good thing.
Being able get angry or
laugh about ordinary things
is a sign that peaceful
times have returned.
True.
Nanao, I’m done here.
That completes our share
of the cleansing.
I’m beat.
Never thought we’d end up
having to erect barriers
over such a wide area.
Can’t do anything about it.
It was to be expected after
something as extraordinary as
swapping part of the Soul
Society with Karakura Town.
But I didn’t expect
to be doing this sort
of tedious work for an entire month.
One month, huh?
Rangiku…
Are you all right?
Of course.
Now then, Nanao.
Since our work here is done,
what do you say the two
of us reward ourselves?
What?
Nothing.
Just thinking you’re
back to your old self.
Really? I’ve been—
Been really depressed!
Matsumoto here.
Matsumoto, you idiot!
Do you have any idea how many
times I tried to call you?!
What’s the big idea with not
making a regular report?!
I’m sorry, Sir!
I was working the entire time.
We’ve finished the assignment,
so Nanao and I were about
to go out for some—
Get back here immediately!
Oh, come on, Sir!
There’s nothing wrong
with having a little fun!
We can’t spare the time!
It’s always like this!
Let’s not fight it.
Why do you do this to
me every single time?!
Everyone is waiting for us.
Jeez… What’s up
with this passageway?
It’s giving me the creeps.
I agree.
But this is the designated path.
Nanao…
What is it?
Did you sense anything
strange just now?
Strange?
You don’t mean a…
What’s going on?!
We’re back.
Sis!
I told you not to leave the room, Kon!
Bug off!
You’re not stopping me from
giving Sis her daily hug!
Hug?!
Damn right!
The feeling of Sis’s kick
squeezing my cotton stuffing…
is a moment of ecstasy!
You could never under…
No, I wouldn’t!
Hollow. Hollow.
Man, they keep popping
up day after day.
Let it go.
Hey!
Sis and I aren’t done—
We’ll be gone a bit.
Behave yourself, Kon.
You too, Chappy.
Aye-aye, Sir!
Just a minute, Ichigo!
What am I to you anyway?
Why bring that up now?
You’re always using me when
it's convenient for you!
I’m not your substitute, you know!
What’re you talking about?!
Ichigo!
We have to hurry!
Right!
Anyway, watch the place
while we’re gone!
Hey!
Tsk!
Hey, don’t you feel like
saying something to…
Pyon!
Jeez…
Ichigo!
A Senkaimon opened nearby.
Does it have something
to do with Hollows?
No.
Then that comes later!
Kurosaki! Kuchiki!
Need help?
We’ll manage!
Looks like Kurosaki hasn’t
experienced any changes
since that one time.
Yeah.
Kuchiki remained here to assist him,
so Ichigo hasn’t had to use more
Spirit Energy than necessary.
Lieutenants Matsumoto and Ise, you say?
Yes.
I haven’t been able to contact
them since their last message
yesterday evening saying
they were returning.
I would like to check and
see if there are any records
of them passing through
the Precipice World.
No problem.
Give me a minute.
Hey, Inaba!
Bring me the record of traffic
through the Precipice World.
Yes, Sir.
But it does seem strange that you
haven’t heard from both of them.
Excuse me.
Well?
Lieutenants Matsumoto and Ise, correct?
At the moment, we have no confirmation
that they returned from
the World of the Living.
Perhaps they haven’t passed
through the Precipice World.
What?
This is becoming very strange.
It was around here…that
I sensed something odd.
There’s nothing here.
Oh well, rather than waste
my free time doing this,
I should find me a beautiful babe.
What the—?!
Huh?
What’s a girl doing
here all…n-n-naked?
No, never mind that. Is she alive?
Hey you!
Huh?
What do you think you’re doing?!
No, I was just…nothing!
Lecher!
Pervert!
Somebody! Police!
You’re making a mistake!
You’ve got it all wrong!
Arrest him, quickly!
Come on, lady!
I understand the situation.
What do you think, Captain Kurotsuchi?
Well, if it isn’t in the record,
they must still be in
the World of the Living.
It’s hard for me to believe
that those two would remain
in the World of the Living
without contacting us.
Then could they have
been involved in some sort of
accident in the Precipice World?
The Department of
Research and Development
monitors the Precipice
World 24 hours a day.
Are you suggesting we missed them?
Yes.
What?!
You’re going to blame your
subordinates’ lack of training on me?
Now, now…
Responsibility aside,
I’d like to confirm that
the two of them are safe.
I have news to report.
Lieutenants Rangiku Matsumoto and
Nanao Ise have just returned.
What?!
Matsumoto, what the hell
were you doing until now?!
Huh? What are you talking about?
My, my… This sure turned
out to be quite a farce.
Where did you two go off
to on your way back?
Umm… We came straight back
after completing our mission.
That’s right!
You gave me an earful just
a short while ago, Captain!
A short while ago?
Yes… About three hours ago.
Which means the time
axis is out of sync?
It does seem something has gone
wrong in the Precipice World.
I’m calling an immediate
Captains’ Meeting.
Captain Kurotsuchi, report.
After a detailed study of the data
from within the Precipice World,
I discovered a time gap
has formed between
the World of the Living
and the Soul Society.
And this gap is continuing to expand.
At this rate, we will no
longer be able to intervene
in the World of the Living
within the next day or so.
Captain Kurotsuchi, is
there any way to stop it?
Of course there is!
An adjustment can be made immediately,
but I’m more worried about the cause.
I’d like to do a detailed survey
of the Precipice World first.
Very well.
With regard to this matter,
I put Squad 12 Captain, Mayuri
Kurotsuchi, in charge of the survey.
Also, I order Squad 11
Captain, Kenpachi Zaraki,
to provide security within
the Precipice World.
What?
Tsk!
Why do I have to do such
a troublesome task?
You should talk!
Can a barbarian like
you provide security?
You might trigger a
catastrophe instead.
What?!
Shall I start with you?!
Enough!
That’s an order!
I also order Squad 6 Captain,
Byakuya Kuchiki, and
Lieutenant Renji Abarai
as well as Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya, to
assist Captain Kurotsuchi.
Dismissed!
So…
Who is this?
I don’t know,
and it’s a problem.
If it’s a problem, then
why is she sleeping here?!
How should I put it?
It just happened that way.
Things never “just happen”!
Not the blanket!
What’ve you done?!
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
I haven’t done anything!
She was lying unconscious
looking just like that!
Ichigo…
What is it?
I don’t sense anything
from this girl.
Huh?
Ordinarily, even if she
lacks Spirit Energy,
I would sense something
if she’s human.
But this girl…
I don’t even sense her existence.
Kon!
Where did you find this girl?!
In the parking lot at third street.
Just as I suspected.
That’s where the Senkaimon
opened earlier.
Then is she a gigai?
I don’t know.
Anyway, I’ll report this
to the Soul Society.
Hmm?
Hey, Akon.
We got an inquiry from
Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13.
Ignore it! No time for that right now.
But take a look at it.
Huh? What is this?
Excuse me.
Oh, Inaba.
Captain Kuchiki and
the others are about
to enter the Precipice
World to conduct a survey.
Would you mind showing them the way?
Understood, Sir.
I have communications
with Captain Kurotsuchi.
What took you so long?!
I apologize. I had
trouble adjusting it.
How does it look?
Did you learn anything?
As I suspected, the cause was man-made.
Kenny! This is fun!
Huh?
More importantly, are Byakuya Kuchiki
and the others not ready yet?
See?
Yes, sir. They’re about to enter now.
Move out the way.
Go! Go!
Stop it!
Even with this area being fixated,
the Restrictive Current would
still reacts to Spirit Bodies.
I don’t care if you fool’s
turn into space-time dust,
but I won’t allow you to
interfere with my survey.
Won’t allow us, eh? Try me!
It appears you're too stupid
to understand words.
Master Mayuri! Something’s coming!
You’re safe!
What’s wrong?
We suddenly lost communications
with the Precipice World,
and a state of emergency was declared!
What about Kurotsuchi and Zaraki?
We…still haven’t…
Where are you going?
To Squad 1.
We found something important
in the Precipice World.
You’re saying you haven’t
met up with Captain
Kurotsuchi and the others?
That’s right.
What is the important item?
We found it near the area where we
were supposed to rendezvous with
Captain Kurotsuchi’s group.
I don’t know what connection
it might have to the incident.
This is!
But I believe it warrants
investigation.
With Kurosaki?
Yes.
I received orders from the Department
of Research and Development
to appear before them with
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
I’ve never received an
order like that before,
so I tried to confirm it.
Then communication failed.
It does seem strange, doesn’t it?
By the way, how’s that girl doing?
She’s still asleep.
I was hoping to ask her
some questions, but…
I don’t know.
At any rate, I’m thinking
of going to the Soul Society.
I wouldn’t recommend it.
You see, Yoruichi went
there a few days ago.
She was supposed to return immediately,
but we haven’t heard from her.
It’s not wise to go there
in your current condition.
Then all the more reason, right?
I have to go.
I suppose I have no choice.
Kurosaki…
At the moment, your Spiritual
Pressure is stable,
but it will gradually decrease.
Yeah.
And the more you overexert yourself,
the sooner the day will come when
you lose your Spirit Energy.
Please keep that firmly in mind.
Yeah, I know.
Be careful, both of you.
What’s the matter?
Something’s not right.
Not right?
You haven’t noticed?
There’s no trace of
Spiritual Pressure.
Trace?
Many Soul Reapers come and
go through here every day.
Yet…
That’s because, you know, that
Cleaner thingie comes and cleans it up.
That’s impossible.
Aizen destroyed it a month ago.
Oh…that’s right.
At any rate, let’s get
out of here quickly.
Right.
Hey, Rukia.
What?
It’s coming.
What’s coming?!
What’s with that?!
I thought you said it was gone?!
I never thought it would
regenerate so quickly.
How quickly does it
regenerate normally?!
That I don’t know.
What?! Why you…
My Combat Pass!
Never mind that!
Hurry!
Bankai!
Ichigo! Are you all right?!
Yeah…this is nothing…
Ichigo! What’s wrong?!
Ichigo!
And the more you overexert yourself,
the sooner the day will come when
you lose your Spirit Energy.
Crap…
Damn it!
Hey!
Toshiro!
Have you seen Rukia?
She should be around—
Don’t move!
Throw down your sword, Kurosaki!
What? Why do I…
I’m arresting you as
a material witness!
Don’t resist!
Material witness?!
What’re you talking about?!
Byakuya!
Nothing personal.
We’re not doing this
because we want to either.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
We’re placing you in confinement.
Thank you for waiting.
Shall we go then?
Hold on!
We start a new story arc,
and the first thing we do is confine
the lead character? What gives?!
No need to worry, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Byakuya!
We will fill the void
while you’re gone.
So rest assured.
This is all wrong!
No problem.
Chad, you too?!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey! Kon here!
Let’s get started here with a
look back at my legendary origins!
I am a Mod Soul originally created
to battle Hollows as part
of “Project Spearhead.”
But the project itself was cancelled,
Some scenes may vary from actual events.
and I was about to be discarded
when Sis rescued me.
Sis…