Gyokaku Kumoi,
having grown impatient
with the failed attempts
to assassinate Rurichiyo,
gives his retainer Hanza Nukui and his men
strange swords known as the Bakkouto,
and dispatches them
to the World of the Living.
Here I come, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Bankai!
Rukia battles one of
the assassins, Douko,
and is hurt by
the ominous Bakkouto, Retsurai.
Kenryu and Enryu
come to her aid
and she manages to release her Kido
and continues to hold her own.
Amazing!
I can feel the power
building inside me!
This is the power
of the Bakkouto?!
Meanwhile,
Ishida battles Kuzuryu
and is locked in a corridor of mist
created by the Bakkouto, Shiragiri.
Shiragiri, Mugen Kairou!
This is…
There!
What?!
Over here.
An illusion?
How long can you
keep running?
And finally, Sado is also
caught up in a fierce battle
against Genga and
his Bakkouto, Kakuyoku.
I’ll show you…
the true power of my Kakuyoku!
There’s no sign…
of his presence.
You’re mine!
He is much faster
than I thought.
I must stop his moves.
What?!
The finishing blow!
Prepare to die!
Don’t think that’s the extent of
the power of this Bakkouto, Retsurai!
What?!
What? Is it over already?
Miss Kuchiki!
Kenryu! You must
help Miss Kuchiki!
Right!
You fool.
Lady Rurichiyo!
Take this!
What?!
Take Lady Rurichiyo!
You’re in my way!
Kenryu!
Enryu!
Damn it!
Not only his speed…
I must immobilize the blades on his back,
or there’s no chance of victory.
That’s it!
Hado Number 33:
Sokatsui!
Damn!
Why you…
You squirming little…
Well then…
Die!
Somenomai…
Tsukishiro!
What?!
Why you…
Now!
Bakudo Number 4: Hainawa!
What?!
Bakudo Number 1: Sai!
You think you’re so clever.
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
I did it.
Take Lady Rurichiyo!
I won’t forgive you.
I won’t forgive you!
What is this?!
What?!
Stop!
What…What happened just now?
What’s going on?!
His Spiritual Pressure is scattered throughout
and I can’t sense his presence.
What is that sword?
Seeleschneider.
The only bladed
Quincy weapon.
I never heard that
Quincies use swords.
Perhaps we use other weapons
you’re not aware of.
Don’t kid around.
Strange…
This mist is created
with reishi.
So why is the convergence
of reishi weakening?
Then…
All right.
What’s going on?
Even if he’s using the Flash Step,
his speed is too fast.
Also, that blade…
I used my Seeleschneider on it,
but there’s not even a knick.
Did he repair it with
the reishi in this mist?
No, because then I could
accumulate reishi easily too.
It can’t be…
Has he actually combined
with the mist?!
So that’s it.
Yes, it seems you figured it out.
This mist is my body.
But with that leg,
you can no longer use the Hirenkyaku.
You cannot escape
my Shiragiri, Mugen Kairou.
I wondered what you would do.
It’s useless.
You seem to be waiting for the moment
that I materialize physically…
but it’s useless.
Now, how long
can you hold out?
I figured that would
be your move!
Wha—?
W-What is this?!
Sprenger.
It is a Quincy Zeichen I drew
with my Seeleschneider.
When did you…
It’s all thanks to you.
What?!
I purposely created openings
in five directions.
And because you attacked each opening,
I was able to set up the barrier.
Not yet.
Not with something like this!
As if I’ll let you get away!
What are you doing?!
It’s over now!
Impossible!
Do you intend to blow yourself up?!
You’ll be caught up in it too!
You’re the one who’s getting hit
by the attack directly!
Damn it.
Lady Rurichiyo, are you hurt?
I am fine. But Enryu…
Enryu!
Please rest assured.
Enryu is quite sturdy.
It must’ve been painful
for you too, Kenryu.
We must tend to your wounds.
The sword used
by that assassin.
He called it a Bakkouto.
Wha—?!
You! Hold it!
Just what are those swords?
He appeared from
within the wall?!
This is the power of
my Bakkouto, Kakuyoku!
Crap!
What’s the matter?
You can’t just keep
running away!
Then… I just have to
break the wall!
Too naïve!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You can’t break the wall unless
you turn your back towards me!
Not necessarily.
Damn it!
What is this brute strength?!
Well, your act of desperation
won’t work a second time!
That’s fine.
I won’t let you go
inside the wall again.
Ridiculous!
What?!
You want to crush me
before I go into the wall?
Interesting.
Let’s see you try!
Just how much tougher
can you get?
You too.
What’s so funny?
Nothing.
I never imagined that a man like you
existed in the World of the Living.
I came to Nukui
wanting this sword.
And not only do I
possess this sword,
but I have found an opponent that
I can test its power on to its limit!
How can I not laugh?!
Forget it! That sword is
sucking the life out of you.
I’m well aware of that!
I only want to know
the extent of my power!
This is the final attack!
Fine.
I will garner all my strength
to counter you.
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo.
So you still had
a hidden power?
Forgive me.
That’s all right.
Try it if you can!
Kakuyoku! Give me strength!
La Muerte!
Sado!
Chad too?!
You!
That Spiritual Pressure
belongs to your friend and mine!
What of it?
You jerk!
On the battlefield,
the one who loses his temper dies.
Shut up!
Oh?
You display fine swordsmanship.
I know your moves!
Wha—?!
I told you before.
I never fall for
the same move twice!
That Zanpakuto derives its attack
from reflected light.
So if I shatter that, it’s all over!
I wonder about that.
What?!
I told you, depending on
the Spiritual Pressure of its wielder,
this sword can
get infinitely stronger.
Miss Kuchiki, are you hurt?
I’m fine.
But the house is in tatters.
That’s why we have
quick and efficient insurance
for whatever happens
to the house.
Where did you
get this insurance?
Urahara’s Shop.
I wonder about that.
Complete Quincy.
Today’s segment is about
the application of the Seeleschneider.
SPRENGER
This is called Sprenger.
Seeleschneider is used to create
a formation in the ground.
Then reishi is activated
to set off an explosion.
It is powerful, but due to
the time it takes to form,
it is wise to have the aid of comrades.
Relying on others again, eh?
My hand slipped.
I swear you’re doing
that on purpose!