As for the laundry, the towels
are in the upper right drawer.
Put the washed towels
in the bottom drawer.
Take out the kitchen garbage on
Tuesday and Thursday by 8:00 AM.
If not, it may not be taken away.
You should wrap leftovers in plastic wrap
and put them in the refrigerator.
Period...
All right.
That about covers it, I guess.
Rangiku and Toshiro will make
a mess of things if they're left alone.
I'm giving you this.
While you're wearing this,
it'll place a special spiritual membrane
around you that will prevent
anyone but us Arrancars
from detecting you.
At the same time, you'll be able
to pass through objects at will.
Wear it and don't take it off.
Yes.
I'll give you a twelve-hour reprieve.
During that time, I'll allow you to
say goodbye to only one person.
But...
If that person realizes what you're doing,
I will consider it a violation of my order.
Your time limit is midnight.
Settle everything by then and
go to the place I told you to go.
Don't forget... You can only
say goodbye to one person.
That hurts!
I told you, that's enough!
Let go of me!
I can't do that!
Shut up!
You're tightening
my bandages too...
Don't choke me.
Good job, Ururu!
Make him pass out!
Stop!
Ikkaku! Crap!
Let go of Ikkaku!
You're injured.
I want you to stay still, Ayasegawa!
Let go, let go, let go!
You shouldn't move, either!
Oh my, oh dear, Lirin,
you mustn't do that.
Yumichika is injured. You must be
more gentle when you restrain him.
What are you saying?!
It's his fault for not listening to me!
Is Yumichika all right?
No problem.
Don't say such irresponsible things!
No!
Yumichika, calm down!
I'll rewrap your bandages.
Shut up!
My, my...
They're noisy wherever they go.
Kisuke Urahara...
He's a mysterious man.
He's been thinking about something ever
since the Arrancars disappeared.
Anyway...
We were lucky that this is
all that we suffered
after all those Espada attacked.
We underestimated them...
They're already prepared!
We've got to hurry
our battle preparations...
But how quickly can we
get completely prepared?
Matsumoto!
Oh. Yes...
Did you get in touch
with Soul Society?!
Well...
Oh, sorry!
What are you doing?!
Huh? Well, I seemed to have
bumped into something.
What would you bump into here?!
How stupid...
That's odd...
I thought it felt kind of squishy.
Only Arrancars will be
able to detect you.
At the same time, you'll be able to
pass through objects at will.
Forgot something...
Hey, Mizuiro, quickly, quickly!
Umm...
If you don't hurry...
Could you stop singing
that song, Keigo?
Also, don't talk to...
Forgot something... Hey Hey!
Hey, please cut that out,
Mr. Asano.
Oh yeah!
They can't see me right now...
I told you...
Stop being formal with me.
We're friends, aren't we?
Yes, yes. I understand, Mr. Asano.
You don't understand...
What's wrong?
Why's this chair on the floor?
Did Ichigo come to school?
Can't be...
Someone probably bumped into it.
Yeah...but...
Anyway, it's strange that
Chad, Inoue, Kuchiki,
and, for some reason,
Ishida all took off from school!
Oh! Could it be that they're
doing something fun together?
We really are being left out!
Don't group me in with you.
What?!
Besides...
We may not be the only ones
who have been left out.
Huh? Umm... What?
Well... For example...
Arisawa...
Besides...
We may not be the only ones
who have been left out.
For example...
Arisawa...
Come on! Don't dawdle!
Yes!
Tatsuki...
Where are you kicking?
Go get it!
Hey, Arisawa!
What are you doing?!
Yes!
Don't forget... You can only
say goodbye to one person.
That's odd...
I can't contact Inoue
in Soul Society.
I wonder if there's
Spiritual Wave interference.
This is the best I can do...
My techniques don't heal.
They're actually a form
of spatial regression.
In order to activate
my techniques,
I need to specify exactly
what I want to regress.
Right now,
Ichigo's wound has
Arrancar Spiritual Pressure mixed in
with his own Spiritual Pressure.
With him in this state,
this is the best I can regress it.
In order to get him out of this condition
as quickly as possible,
we need to get as far away
from him as we can.
Since we have Spiritual Pressure
that is similar to that of Hollows.
Take him home and
let him get some rest.
That is the best treatment
for him right now.
Okay... I understand.
Ichigo... Who are they?
What kind of power...
are you trying to obtain?
Why did the Arrancars stop fighting
halfway through and leave?
There are lots of things
I don't know.
All right! Anyway,
I'll stop by Inoue's house...
I said you can't!
Brother needs rest!
But... But Karin...
He might wake up!
Right?
But...
U-Umm...
Can we eat dinner here?
Yeah... Please do that...
I'm sure Ichigo will be pleased...
Umm...
What's wrong?
Well... actually...
I've made some for you, too!
Wow! What's this?!
Doesn't it look delicious?
Um... But I actually
need to get going...
What?!
I'm still not hungr-
What was that noise just now?
See? Rukia, you are hungry!
No, well... Umm...
Since you made it,
I guess I'll have some.
Wow! Thank you, Rukia!
Come on, Karin!
Bring the tray!
Oh, right!
M-Mr. Kurosaki!
Hey, Rukia!
How is that idiot?
Well, he's been
sleeping all this time.
Don't worry!
Honestly. Getting beaten up
by students from a different school?
How pathetic!
He's still got a long way to go...
Umm... Sorry...
This all happened because
I got tangled up with delinquents.
What are you saying?!
I'm really glad that you're safe!
Whoa! What a waste...
Thank you very much...
Oh...Rukia...
It's cold tonight. If you're going out,
be careful not to catch a cold.
Okay...
All right!
There we go...
I came here...
Well...Kurosaki...
I came to say goodbye.
Actually,
I wanted to say goodbye
to Tatsuki, Sado, Ishida, Kuchiki,
and many other people, but...
I see... Yuzu and Karin
ate dinner here today.
I suppose they'd want to.
They were sad that you
weren't around for so long.
They wanted to eat dinner
with you in your room.
BLUSH
Kurosaki's...room?
Come to think of it, this is the first time
I've come to Kurosaki's room alone.
It smells like him...
It's no good...
I can't do it.
I'm no good... I'm doing this
even though it's the end.
Kurosaki, I had a lot of things
that I wanted to do.
I wanted to become
a schoolteacher.
an astronaut.
I wanted to be
a cake maker.
I wanted to go to a doughnut shop
that had all kinds of doughnuts
and say I wanted everything.
I also wanted to go
to an ice cream shop
and say that I wanted everything.
I wish I had five lives!
I would be born in
a different town each time.
I'd fill my stomach with
different things each time.
I'd have a different job
each time.
And each time...
I'd fall in love with
the same person...
Thank you, Kurosaki.
Good-bye.
Hmm... I'm not getting through.
Your Soul Pager is too old.
Mine is a new one that won't break
even if an elephant were to step on it!
But its design is terrible!
I feel sorry for you for not being
able to realize how great it is!
Then does yours get through?
It's out of range!
Then don't brag!
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey, listen to this!
Yesterday, there were
huge noises in town.
That was Ikkaku and the others
fighting again, wasn't it?
Is that so?
Who are they?
001 IKKAKU
A spy with a license to kill?
Or...
Is he the attendant of
a former shogun who fights evil?
He might be your brother in law.