I'm fighting because...
I must win!
If you don't know it,
I will teach it to you.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
I cannot go back to you now.
mou kaerenai wa
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ulquiorra.
Here I come... Here's what
you wanted to see...
My Hollowfication!
Come back here!
Damn it...! How far does
he intend to go?!
Is this
above Las Noches's ceiling?
That's right.
Two things are forbidden below
the ceilings of Las Noches.
The first is Gran Rey Cero,
a Cero that exists for an Espada.
And the other is
the sword release of an Espada that
is ranked cuatro and above.
Enclose...
Murcielago!
Don't be flustered.
Hold your stance.
Extend your consciousness.
Don't let down your guard
for a moment.
It's not possible...
He's too fast.
This can't be happening.
I went into Hollowfication...
But I couldn't react at all...!
The power of your so-called
Hollowfication has increased.
You've also increased the length of
time you can produce that mask...
But I never thought I could
break it so easily...
How unfortunate.
Watch closely...
I can see it.
A hole...
opened up in the sky.
So that sky really was fake.
Inoue-san...
I'm glad you're all right.
I shouldn't say it yet.
It'll be all right.
Kurosaki...will win.
I will truly be able to say that
when you defeat him,
Kurosaki.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Fire your Getsuga.
Fire it at me.
That is your most powerful form, capable
of even holding up against an Espada.
And Getsuga is your most
powerful technique...
Fire it now and show it to me.
I will demonstrate our
difference in strength.
You want me to unleash Getsuga...?
Don't get smart with me!
You didn't have to ask...
I was going to do
it anyway!
Getsuga...
Tensho!
Just as I thought...
You are, after all, merely human.
He's...unharmed?!
Your black Getsuga is indeed
very similar to our Cero.
Cero? Don't compare it to
something like that!
I see. Then you haven't seen it yet.
Since this is your last chance,
I will show it to you.
This is the black Cero that an
Espada in release mode
unleashes...
Cero Oscuras.
Inoue-san!
What was that?
What happened up there?
Ishida-kun.
Is it possible to lift me above that
ceiling, using your powers?
At the time,
I couldn't refuse Inoue-san's request-one
that I should easily have anticipated.
Please...
I would soon
regret that decision.
Damn...
Do you understand now?
No matter how closely
your form and techniques
resemble those of an Arrancar,
the difference in power is as far
apart as heaven and earth.
Imitating Hollows is a
reasonable path to follow
for humans and Soul Reapers
seeking to gain power.
But you humans will never catch up
to Hollows for all eternity.
Getsuga...
I told you it's useless!
Why won't you let go
of your sword?
You've seen how great the
difference is in our powers,
yet you still think you
can defeat me?
Difference...in power... So what?
You...think I'd give up...
just because you're more
powerful than me...?
I knew you were powerful
from the very start.
At this point, nothing changes...
No matter how many times
I see how powerful you are.
I...
will...defeat you!
U-Ul...qui...orra...
Nonsense.
Ichigo Kurosaki...
Those are the words of someone
who does not know true despair.
If you don't know it,
I will teach it to you.
This is what true despair is like!
This is incredible.
I learned this when I went
through Garganta.
I realized along the way here that I could
use this in Hueco Mundo, as well.
If I had realized it
just a bit sooner,
I could have applied it
in battle, too.
Ishida-kun...
Wh-What is that?! It came from
above the ceiling...
What is this?!
Is it Spiritual Pressure...?!
It's too different...
It's unlike any Spiritual Pressure
I've ever experienced before...
It's not just powerful or huge.
It's a different sort.
Thick and heavy, enough to
make me aware that it's
something different than
Spiritual Pressure...
If feels as though there's an ocean
spread above the sky.
I've never...
This isn't good... Let's hurry!
Resurreccion Segunda Etapa.
Among the Espadas,
I alone have made this
second-stage release possible.
I have not even shown
Lord Aizen this form.
He has witnessed my form, and
yet still has the will to fight?
He is not so confused
that he feels no fear...
But neither are those the eyes of
someone who has given up on life...
Does it mean he believes
he can win...?
Fine...
Then I will make you understand, even
if I have to turn your body into dust...
...to do it.
Such imprudence, Ichigo Kurosaki.
To throw down the gauntlet against
a frighteningly superior opponent
is beyond my comprehension.
If it is because of what you
people call "heart,"
then because you possess
"heart," you humans
suffer injuries...
And because you
possess "heart,"
you lose your lives.
I'm not necessarily fighting
because I think I can win.
I'm fighting because
I must win!
Such nonsense.
I don't sense Kurosaki's
Spiritual Pressure...
Where is he?
So you've come, girl.
Kurosaki-kun...?
You're just in time.
Watch closely.
The moment the life
of the man to whom
you've entrusted your hopes
comes to an end.
Stop!
What'll we do...?
Kurosaki-kun was supposed to be in charge
of this week's preview, but he can't...
Girl... I shall take
over for him.
Okay! Then please dance wearing
the Afro wig and glittery dress,
just like Yoruichi-san did
in the ending credits!
...Huh?
Arrancar Encyclopedia
Today, we'll talk about Ulquiorra.
MURCIELAGO
His sword release
is "Murcielago."
And, amongst the Espadas, he is the only
one who has a second-stage release.
That form is...
Huh?
I haven't even shown it
to Lord Aizen.
There is no way I would
show it to you.
Hold on a second!
Now...show it!
Never!
You're desperate, aren't you?