I’ll have you out in no time!
Come on, come on!
Kon!
Kon! Kon!
Kon!!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
Stop…
Kon…
Hado Number 31, Shakkaho!
Stay away!
How pitiful.
URAHARA’S SHOP
No word from Urahara yet?!
Not yet.
They’re taking too long.
If you’re all so worried,
why not go and check?
Ikkaku!
Are you fully recovered?
This doesn’t even count as an injury.
So, how about it, Renji?
Well…
Please go!
Huh?!
Earlier, we confirmed many
captain-level Spiritual Pressures
inside the Seireitei.
Then Brother and the others are…
Boss gave us permission to
be flexible as needs arise…
I believe now is the
best time to attack…
Renji!
Right!
We’re heading into the Soul Society!!
All that’s left for you
is self-destruction…
I won’t have to do it myself anymore.
Who is this guy…
Nozomi? No…
Is this Kageroza?
Given my druthers, I prefer not
to fight with brute force…
Agreed.
But that’s precisely why it
makes sense to press this
battle with brute force…
Unlike you, who shirked
brute force combat training,
I received considerable training here.
Crap…
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!!
What do you think?
Yeah…I think we have a problem…
They pretend to fight one-on-one,
but strike at the openings
of other opponents.
I know…
That gives them a numerical advantage.
Yeah.
We need to make sure we kill
them to reduce their numbers…
For crying out loud, they’re
such barbarians…
I wish they’d try to leave those
future guinea pigs as
unharmed as possible.
Oh my, and you’re going to just
watch from your lofty perch?
How can a person like you be a
captain of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads?
Amusing…
Spoken by a Mod Soul…how
very amusing…
I’ve made up my mind.
Oh? What about?
To do a live-body experiment
on the Squad 4 captain’s Reigai
who always irritates me…
Claw out…
Ashisogijizo!
Minazuki.
Bakudo Number 63,
Sajosabaku!
That won’t work on me…
What?
Impossible…
Captain Kurotsuchi!
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
It won’t be long now…
Even in that state, you still pursue me?
Bakudo Number 30, Shitotsusansen.
I don’t have time to
waste dealing with you.
Hado Number 58,
Tenran!!
Bakudo Number 99, Restrict!!
I told you, I can’t be wasting
any more time here with you!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
Looks like Kageroza has
achieved full strength.
Finally, a game-changing
turn in this battle…
Yeah, victory is ours.
Bakudo Number 4, Hainawa!!
Whoa!
That was so dangerous of you.
I suppose catching you
off-guard is pointless
if you can still see my attack.
In that case…
I’ll just have to block your view!
Bakudo Number 37, Tsuriboshi.
You’re wasting your time!
Bakudo Number 63, Sajosabaku!
Gochu Tekkan!!
What?!
Had you going there!
Firing salvos of techniques
leaves you wide open.
Hado Number 88, Hiryu
Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!!
Bakudo Number 81, Danku!
Didn’t I tell you
I’d block your view?
There’s no way I wouldn’t
know what you’re thinking.
Hado Number 32, Oukasen!
I pity you…
Unable to return to being a Soul Reaper
nor are you able to
become a full Hollow…
A polar opposite from the
complete being I have become…
Raiku…
Farewell, Substitute Soul Reaper!
What?
Ichigo!
Roar! Zabimaru!!
Huh?
Is this Spiritual Pressure…that
of Kageroza’s?
No… Did he get Kujo?!
Nozomi…
It’s the worst possible situation!
So it’s you people…
You should know by now that
you’re no match for me…
What did you come here for?
We came to save our friends!
Friends?!
Loneliness is not a sin.
No matter what the circumstances,
I don’t need help from others.
Other people only get in the way.
To help…is mere pity…
It is jealousy towards the strong…
An insult to a noble spirit.
To be alone is to be the only one.
The privilege…of a superior soul.
Friends, you say?
If your lives are of so little value
that you’d sacrifice them for
another without hesitation,
then die here and now!!
This ends now!!
Matsumoto!
We’re here to help, Captain.
No one asked for your help.
But…
These small fry are making it
hard to concentrate on my fight.
You guys handle cleanup.
Yes, sir!
With pleasure!
Ishida!
His Zanpakuto takes slices
of space and recreates them.
When we fought last, I thought
he was manipulating time,
but that’s not what he does at all.
He uses his Zanpakuto to recreate
a space that didn’t exist before
and shifts his location
in space in that instant.
Isn’t that right?
Oh…
I apologize for underestimating you…
This time, I will show
you my true power.
No you won’t!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Seethe, Sumitsukigasa!
What was that?
What’re you looking at?
Cry, Benihime!
This ends it!
Abarai!
You’re not getting away!
What?!
Sumitsukigasa!
W-What just happened?
That was the true power of
my Zanpakuto, Sumitsukigasa.
W-What?
Duplicating an adversary’s attack
and reproducing it is the
power of “Raiku”…
Absorbing an adversary’s
Spiritual Pressure and
turning it into one’s own is
Nozomi’s “Arazomeshigure.”
Sumitsukigasa possesses
the power of both.
Raiku consumes a great deal
of my Spiritual Pressure and
entails a risk when reproducing
an adversary’s attack…
But with the power of Arazomeshigure,
I am now able to absorb the attack
and continue to counterattack
indefinitely.
That’s absurd…is that even possible?
I am both Kageroza
Inaba and Nozomi Kujo.
Should it be any wonder that
her capabilities now reside
in my Zanpakuto?
I’ll crush that power
of yours head-on!!
Abarai, don’t!!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!!
Fool…
Sumitsukigasa.
Renji!!
If we attack recklessly,
the force will be absorbed
and directed back at us…
What can we do?
In that case…
All we can do is mount an attack
that he can’t absorb…
Tetsuzaemon!
Don’t be distracted
by multiple opponents!
Concentrate only on your own!
I know that, sir!
Cursed Reigai…
They’ve turned this into a brawl,
attacking at random and
effectively exploiting
our unguarded moments.
The pride of the originals,
who value fighting one-on-one,
is working to our disadvantage.
At this rate…
Damn!
Licht Regen!
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
Hihio Zabimaru!!
Those attacks won’t work!
I will put you down one by one so that
you won’t be able to
coordinate your attacks.
Now, Kuchiki!
Hakuren!!
Don’t mess with me!
What?!
Damn you!
Too slow!
Now that I am one with Nozomi,
my powers far surpass yours.
Your inept trickery will have no effect.
So you were after
Nozomi…for this power…
Yes.
This is the original
power of my Zanpakuto.
But my weak original body was unable
to wield it to its full potential.
My true objective for becoming a Reigai
was to be able to fully
control this Zanpakuto.
Are you…
planning to use your power to
rule the the Soul Society…?
Rule?
You still believe that nonsense?
What?!
My objective is to destroy
the Soul Society.
Iro Oni…
White!
For that reason,
I can’t afford to waste any more time.
Die.
Ichigo!!
Captain!
If you continue to use your Bankai,
our squad’s repair budget
is going to run out!
Don’t let it bother you, Tetsuzaemon.
But your Bankai draws
the most attention!
That’s why the other squads are
going to blame everything on us!
You mean, all of this?!
Yes, sir…
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Today, I will personally explain
how to create my invasion force.
Reigai are what you might call Gigai
that allow to Mod Souls to be active.
That is why they revert to Mod Souls
when their bodies are destroyed.
Conversely, as long as this pill
remains, they can be recreated.
Now then, as for the all-important
process of creating Mod Souls…
Hey! Are you guys even listening?!