Nakasaki, I heard you just had a kid.
Uh, where did you hear that?
Is it male or female?
It's a girl.
Maybe I should take her.
P-Please don't...
Girls become independent
earlier than boys.
It won't be long before she
stops listening to you.
Th-That won't happen with Fuko!
I will raise her to be the
biggest father lover in Japan!
Yeah, that's the spirit.
Th-This is...
I-I can't accept this much money!
It's not for you.
I only spend money on fine women.
Let her drink the finest
milk you can find.
Th-Thank you very much!
The Man's Household Situation
is Hard, His Heart is Soft
How many times have I told you?!
Wash my underwear
separately from Father's!
Forgive me, ma'am.
I'm going to wash them again myself!
Geez!
Oh, sir.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll wash that again at once.
Hm? Are you the new maid?
What's your name?
Ichihara
Ichihara?
What's your first name?
Hayato? Etsuko?
It's not Etsuko, it's Ezurako.
Your face looks familiar...
It's not Zura, it's Ezurako.
Forget it.
Be careful from now on.
Do my laundry separate from Kuriko's.
And make sure we don't
eat at the same time.
It's not Zura, it's Ezurako.
Yeah, just listen to
my daughter. Got it,
Ezurako?
It's not Ezurako, it's Katsura.
What?
Oh, I made a mistake. It's Ezurako.
Whatever. Just go.
Oof.
The police commissioner,
Katakuriko Matsudaira.
The man who is known as the Destroyer
to those who wish to
disrupt the order of Edo.
The greatest foe of the Joi patriots.
In an attempt to uncover a scandal,
I've been working undercover
at his home for a week.
My focus has shifted away from my
inability to learn anything useful
to this peculiar loneliness I see.
Is this what it means to be a father?
If so, what is a father? What is a man?
Who does he fight for? Who
is he trying to protect?
Um...
What are you doing, Ezurako-san?
I'm terribly sorry.
After working as a maid for so long,
I've picked up this
habit of eavesdropping.
You also picked up the door.
Please let me know if
I'm being a bother.
I also have a graffiti version
and a mental AT Field version.
Please get rid of it.
You're making too much noise.
Um...
Sorry about yelling at you earlier.
It's okay. I didn't mind.
I said to get rid of that.
Did you think you could fool me?
Um, to make up for earlier,
some of my friends booked
Greater Edo Hills tomorrow
for my birthday party.
Would you like to come?
Thank you very much.
Oh, will your father also be coming?
I would never invite him!
Besides, he wouldn't come if I did.
His birthday is very soon.
I'm sure he'll celebrate it
at the usual place with all those women.
It's always the same.
He uses his work as an excuse
to avoid facing his family.
I refuse to call that coward my father.
I wonder why...
I am starting to feel concern
for my greatest foe.
Is it because Matsudaira's daughter
was a nicer girl than I expected?
Or because I didn't want
to think that I've been
crossing swords with a man who
can't control his own family.
Sir?
Miss Kuriko's birthday
party is tomorrow.
You shouldn't be sleeping out here.
Man, I'm gonna hurl...
Miss Kuriko wanted you to come.
You're going to Kuriko's
birthday party, right?
Give that to her.
It'll make her happier that way.
Are you trying to teach her how men
are foolish, weak, and underhanded?
Is that your duty as a father?
Ezurako-san, that's enough!
And why are you walking
around with that board?!
It's fine, Nakasaki.
I like a maid who's willing
to speak her mind.
But I'm not much of a father.
Young people think
that men grow wiser as
they get older, but it's not true.
I'm just as stupid as I always was.
Still the same old shy kid who
can't bring myself to look
my precious daughter in the face,
or even talk to her.
I'll leave this with you.
I was becoming more confused.
The man spoke openly
of his own foolishness.
Was he a big shot, or just an idiot?
F-Forgive me, dear!
Crafty or innocent?
And I was most confused
by my own behavior.
Um, excuse me.
You're supposed to be dressed
formally for this affair.
And that is what I did.
Um, only the left side
is dressed formally.
And that's just a drawing.
Ah, you have a problem
with me wearing a tuxedo?
Don't worry. I also brought a dress.
Um...
We're not supposed to let
anyone suspicious in.
What about me would be
considered suspicious?!
Everything.
How dare you insult me?!
Are celebrities so special?!
Your birthday party's probably
nothing more than an **gy!
How can you say such a hateful thing?!
A sinful gathering where you wear masks
and put things on your sticks,
and shove them into...
That's just a cheese fondue!
Don't say that so loudly here.
Have you no shame?!
You're the one who's
having naughty thoughts
about a cheese fondue!
Oh, sorry.
She's with me.
Ah, Nakasaki-san.
I'm here in place of the commissioner.
I see...
So he isn't coming.
Ah! Ezurako-san! Nakasaki-san!
You came to the party!
I'm so happy!
Now come inside!
What is this?!
What's happening?!
Did the system malfunction?!
No...
It's a terrorist attack.
Incoming Call from Kuriko
Hello?
Is this Katakuriko Matsudaira?
Your daughter's life is in our hands.
The Blues Crew has taken
control of Greater Edo Hills.
If you value your daughter's life,
you'll listen to our demands.
Hey, can you hear me?
Is somebody in there?
That's weird. It sure stinks.
Can't you let a man
take a dump in peace?
What?
That's...
Th-The commissioner!
So he did come.
What are you doing up there?!
I appreciate it, Ezurako.
Thanks to you, I won't be late.
Wh-Where are you going, Commissioner?!
That was no longer the frail back
of an old man washing underwear.
That was the stalwart back
of the Destroyer we feared.
The hostages include the children of
various Bakufu officials
along with Kuriko-chan.
The Blues Crew must have learned about
this party and planned the attack.
I remember that some of
their members were arrested
for plotting to assassinate the boss.
They're demanding that
those members be released.
And they also want the boss's head.
If we don't agree to their demands,
they'll start killing a
hostage every thirty minutes.
I'll go negotiate and
try to buy us some time.
You guys need to find a way inside.
Yes, sir!
And Yamazaki,
did you get a hold of the boss?
His phone's been busy the whole time.
Damn that old fart.
What's he doing?
Hello? Ane-chan?
Sorry.
I won't be able to join you tonight.
Right now? I'm in a duct.
No, I didn't change careers.
I'm devoted to you, Ane-chan.
Oh, sorry. I got another call.
My men are so annoying.
Buh-bye.
Ah, he finally answered the phone!
Are you okay, Commissioner?!
How many times did you
call me, you fool?!
Don't call my phone when
I'm in terrorist territory.
You're terrorizing my
conversation with Ane-chan!
You have no right to talk when you're
calling female escorts while
sneaking up on terrorists!
I was just settling matters
so the women left behind
in this cruel world don't grieve.
When a man dies, everyone
should be wearing pure white.
I have fifty more girls
to call, so hold on.
It's too late to clean up your act!
Your soul is completely black!
Anyway, Hijikata-san and the other men
will be entering the building soon.
Don't do anything hasty.
No, we can't wait for them.
Ezurako-san?
They've taken over the security system.
It won't be easy to
approach the building.
Huh? Then we shouldn't be here.
I put something in this
car to jam their radar.
And I did the same thing
to Matsudaira's present.
You're...
I happen to be acquainted
with Edo's top tinkerer.
In three hours, they'll
begin executing hostages.
In other words, I need to end
their lives before they end mine.
Exactly.
Ezurako-san!
But you won't be able to do it
by recklessly wandering around alone.
I'll assist you.
I knew something was fishy.
You're no ordinary maid.
I'm just an ordinary maid
who enjoys eavesdropping.
How are negotiations going?
It'll take a day to secure
the release of our brethren.
They're obviously trying to buy time.
Tell them this.
We aren't giving them any more time.
Yes, sir.
And one more thing.
Tell them that Matsudaira's
life is already ours,
though, technically, we still have to go
through the formality
of taking it from him.
I didn't expect him to sneak in
by himself to save his daughter.
H-He won't come!
He would never try to save me...
Don't make a fuss. You'll
be seeing him real soon.
We'll have him tied
up with a red ribbon.
Listen up. They're holed up in the
main control room on the top floor.
You're on the 9th floor.
Every floor from the 10th
up is packed with guards.
I see. So this marker
on the 9th floor is me.
Wait a moment!
Why did you use this symbol for me?!
Don't get the wrong idea.
That's the tip of an ice cream cone.
And the three markers on
the 10th floor are enemies.
Why do they get cones when I don't?
Otherwise, you wouldn't be
able to tell friend from foe.
Give me a cone!
I love to suck the last bit of ice
cream out of the end of a cone.
Fine, I'll put corn in your poop.
I said cone, not corn!
And you said poop. You just
admitted that it's poop.
Uh, does it really matter?!
In any case, you need to avoid those
ice cream cones as you make
your way to the 50th floor.
Look carefully.
The tip of the ice cream is
tipping left and right, yes?
The tip indicates the
direction they're facing.
When the three tips are tipping
in the same direction,
you should tip past them.
That's too complicated!
Why do you have to use
the word tip so much?!
Ah, hold on...
There's an ice cream cone coming down!
What?! It's tipping like crazy!
Is it in a hurry?
10th floor... He didn't get off!
Has he noticed that the
commissioner's on the 9th floor?
Hide quick!
Oh, no!
Huh?!
W-Wait!
The ice cream cone split in two!
What's going on up there?
A guy ran off somewhere.
But the ice cream's
still in the elevator!
He just pooped his pants!
Apparently, both people and poop
are registered under
the ice cream marker.
Why is poop even registered
on your scanner?!
And why am I not registered as a human?!
He took the elevator
down to find a bathroom,
but he couldn't hold it
in and had to sparking!
Look.
The cone is becoming wet.
Is he wiping his ass?
No, he's probably crying.
Wait, I thought that there were
only enemies above you, but...
It's mostly poop up there!
I can no longer tell which
are human and which are poop.
When I blew up that bathroom,
I probably burst the water main.
They can no longer take
care of their business.
Still, this is too many!
However, we can use this
situation to our advantage.
Look!
Th-This is...
They're all running down in
search of clean restrooms!
They really need to take a shit!
They're using the stairs.
This is your chance to
take the elevator up!
Hold on!
The wet cone is racing to the
elevator at a crazy speed!
Did he notice the commissioner?
No, now that he's calmed down,
he's returning for his underwear
so he can destroy the evidence.
Hurry, Matsudaira!
He made it in time.
Th-That's...!
He's hanging on to the
bottom of the elevator!
He is dedicated to his underwear!
He really doesn't want
anyone to find out!
Commissioner! The cone is below you!
And which one is the commissioner?!
Ah! The cone is using the pointy
edge to try to break through!
Uh, what pointy edge?
That's just a marker!
What?!
He penetrated the poop!
Wait, is that the commissioner?!
Or is it the poop?!
Which is it?!
He's trying to drag Matsudaira off!
Oh! Saved at the last second!
How?!
How can poop save him?!
Is that actually Matsudaira?
Ah! The cone con finally
cornered himself and fell!
Why was he trying so hard to protect
a pair of dirty underwear?!
This is bad.
The Ice Cream Gang has noticed
that something is wrong!
When he makes it to the
top, he'll be gunned down!
They split up! What the hell?!
How the hell are two turds
moving around independently?!
It's going to draw their attention
so Matsudaira can make it to the top!
It's just a pair of
underwear with poop on it!
How did it turn into the
commissioner's partner?!
Look!
The Ice Cream Gang is ignoring the
underwear and gathering
on the 50th floor!
No shit, Sherlock!
He's completely trapped!
What?!
The ice cream cones are disappearing.
This poop was actually the diversion...?
Happy birthday to you.
He really took out all of
the terrorists by himself...
No, there's one cone left.
Sorry about that.
Your precious underwear
and squad are all gone.
No, I should thank you.
No one will know now.
You're placing your duty as a
cop over your duty as a father?!
Well, you can't call yourself a father
if you don't mind your daughter
being used as a shield.
But you can't even call
yourself a man if you let
someone who hurt your daughter
walk away unscathed.
A father's duty isn't much to speak of.
Kids are raised fine by their mothers.
As long as I'm bringing in
money, I have no other use.
All that's left is to praise her
when she does something good,
and scold her when she
does something bad.
That's about it.
This fist represents my duty
as a police commissioner
and a lousy Edo dad.
That's...!
My...
My underwear is still around!
The decoy was my own underwear.
I have one thing to say
to you as a father.
Wash your own
shitty underwear!
What a waste.
This was your chance to
score some points with her.
She won't remember a thing.
I'm fine with playing
the role of a lousy dad
since it's easy.
Open the box.
It's not your present.
I found it when I was cleaning
your daughter's room.
She was probably going to give
it to you if you showed up.
Happy Birthday Father
Don't worry.
I left your present in its place.
How is that supposed
to make me feel better?
A maid who goes into my daughter's
room without permission
gets fired on the spot.
Nakasaki!
Yes, sir!
Dump this rotten maid in a ditch.
Understood.
I'll dump the maid in a ditch
where the police won't notice.
Stop yapping and leave!
Yes, sir!
The next time we meet, you'll
meet more than my fist, Katsura.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
The police commissioner,
Katakuriko Matsudaira.
Matsudaira
The greatest foe of the Joi patriots.
Stop that, sir!
It doesn't matter if he doesn't
feel welcome in his own home.
I can do the laundry!
The world is his home.
Forget it. I'll do this.
And so he goes off to work again.
Oh, Miss Kuriko.
That's a lovely hairpin.
However, I have seen on display
the bond between father and daughter
as they stand back to back.
As well as the dignity of
a so-called lousy father.
Katakuriko Matsudaira.
You make a fitting opponent.
Next Episode: Blue and Red Ecstasy
Next time:
Blue and Red Ecstasy.