Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
It's all right…
You don't have to watch me.
I won't go--!
What's this?!
Who is it?!
Koga?!
I've come for you.
I won't go!
You have no choice.
Kariya is waiting.
I refuse!
Try to take me if you can.
Zeige dih, Goethe!
Zeige dih, Dalk!
This is…
What is it? Do you need my help?
Yeah…
What a hopeless person…
But it's okay. I love to fight…
I feel like chasing you
even more if you run away.
Goethe, do it!
Do it?
Wonderful… I'm getting excited…
Damn…
Goethe!
Are you all right?
There're stairs over there!
Now's our chance!
Oh… I'm hot…
She can still move?
I'm falling in love with you.
Goethe!
Oh my…
Where are you going?
What should I do with these feelings?
Who will accept them?
Look out!
Goethe!
I'm so happy! You came back!
Accept…my feelings!
No!
No… You disappeared…
Dalk!
How rude… I know.
You want me to hurry.
But it's not good to be hasty.
I want to take my time and enjoy this.
Don't harm the Quincy.
Which means that…
I can do what I like to the woman.
Oh no!
That was close.
What are you doing?
Now's not the time to
be protecting me…
I didn't protect you…
Huh?
I just decided I wouldn't run away.
I no longer want to be a burden…
nor will I be made a key person!
Oh, how wonderful! I'm delighted!
What a nice manly thing to say!
You make me want to hug you!
There's no mistake!
It's already disappeared,
but there was a sign of two Bounts!
That's fine,
but try not to be seen by people…
What do you mean by that?!
How rude!
That's not what I mean.
It's strange for four stuffed animals
to be walking around…
Stop calling me strange!
I'm serious!
I didn't choose this look
to begin with.
I'm putting up with this
because I can't get out of it…
Fine, fine! Is that so…
Oh!
It's here!
Oh ho. This is definitely suspicious!
Hm? There are traces of
Ishida's Spiritual Pressure!
Huh?!
You're right!
Ishida!
Ishida…
There's no mistake.
Ishida was brought here…
There's fire.
Which means it's that woman and…
The other one…
is someone we don't know.
It looks like they were fighting
over the Quincy…
I think so, too.
They were fighting for Ishida…
This set up…
is it a “Princess Uryu Ishida Story”?!
No! How disgusting!
No… It kind of matches…
Hot! I'm burning!
That was hot…
Noba… You can suck in flames?
Isn't it hot?
Not a problem.
Ichigo!
Huh?
Ishida's bandages…
Can someone follow
Ishida's Spirit Ribbon?
It's no good…
Ishida's Spiritual Pressure is very weak
and he's suppressing it.
That bastard…
He won't even let us know
if he's been caught by Bounts!
It's all right!
That's right. It's all right.
In this situation, we may be able
to follow the Bounts' reishi residue!
Really?
Yes, but I'm frustrated…
My powers would be better
if I was in a gigai!
We mod-souls' real bodies are small pills…
We can't walk or even speak
unless someone puts us in a gigai…
Say, I've always thought
it was strange, but…
If that's the case,
then why don't you put each other
into your gigai?
Wh-What's up with that?!
He didn't have to tell me.
I knew that! I knew,
but I just acted like I didn't!
Well, how could I have missed that!
This is definitely an example
of people not being aware
of their surroundings,
or a Copernican revolution!
I knew!
I knew, but I was acting dumb on purpose!
Of course, I was!
At any rate,
let's go after the Bounts!
Yes!
What?! What about me?!
I'm the only stuffed animal?!
Wait for me!
Tenth Squad Captain Hitsugaya,
and Lieutenant Rangiku Matsumoto.
Eleventh Squad Captain Zaraki,
and Lieutenant Yachiru Kusajishi.
– Entering.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What were you doing at
a time like this?!
If you were regular squad members
you would be my pet’s food
because you were incompetent!
Captain Ukitake, what did you
want to talk to us about?
I'm the one who wanted to talk!
I summoned everyone here because…
General Captain Yamamoto
is not here today.
Now then. Twelfth Squad Captain
Kurotsuchi will explain the details…
There are no details!
It's my databank!
Someone has been breaking in
and looking at it!
Looking at it? Looking at what?
Would it surprise you if I said…Bounts?
Furthermore, the enemy planted a trap!
It would destroy all the data
if it was removed!
Do you know what this means?!
Do you?!
This is both a challenge and
a great insult towards me,
the head of the Department
of Research and Development.
If someone here is involved
with the culprit,
give me your name immediately!
I'll pickle you in a pool of acid!
Stop picking a fight, Kurotsuchi…
We're high-ranking officials of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
Have you already forgotten
that just recently…
we were betrayed by that
so-called high-ranking official?
This is a dangerous problem
which involves all of Soul Society.
We shouldn't act hastily…
Humph! How unreliable!
Well fine…
But if anyone does anything else
to make me look foolish…
be prepared, because I have a plan!
I have a bad feeling about this…
Huh? What about?
This Kurotsuchi incident and
the fact that we found Ichinose.
What?! Why?
I don't know…
You are worried about Maki, after all.
It’s not that.
It just all seems fishy…
I've figured it out!
There's a mansion that fits the description
a little further down from here.
Huh?
There seems to be an incredibly
rich man who lives there,
but no one has ever seen him…
Kariya won't forgive you anymore.
If you think I'm lying,
then come out of this room
and meet Kariya.
It seems you can't even get up.
You shouldn't try anything stupid like
using your doll in that condition.
You'll be attacked.
So this is it…
What a huge garden…
I can't see the house…
There's no mistake!
This is it!
All right!
Let's split up and search for him!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Would you like to see the Quincy?
Koga caught him, huh?
Yes. He's in the hall right now.
He's our valuable trump card…
I'll greet him.
Shall I advance our plans?
No…
Why are you holding back?
I don't understand.
We’ve lived for a long time…
In that time, all of our memories
have become coated in gray…
For the first time in a while,
I can see the world in color.
Is it wrong if I wish to
enjoy this a little longer?
I understand, however…
Silence!
Udagawa, you don't understand!
That's it…
What's wrong, Rukia?
The Bounts' Spiritual Pressure.
Being this close I can clearly tell;
even without the mod-souls…
There are…five, six, seven…
eight of them…
Really?!
Since we don't know their plan,
we can’t waste time!
Let's go!
What's wrong? Are you afraid?
So you're Ishida?
It's natural to be cautious.
We've given you quite a rough invitation.
Who are you?
Jin Kariya…
I wish to borrow your Quincy powers.
In order to gain the power
of Hueco Mundo?
There's no changing the fact
that we are both rejected beings…
due to our unique abilities.
Unique abilities…
That's right. I have a proposition.
Can we live cooperatively together,
instead of acting like enemies?
Bounts can protect you.
No, we may be able to
revive your lost power.
Don't you think
that's a good proposition?
You know I have no powers, so why?
I told you. We're the same.
Do you think I'll believe you?
It's understandable to be suspicious.
But we have time.
I can wait until you understand.
Forever in fact…
You can make yourself at home.
Do you plan on confining me here?
You're an important guest.
Dalk, that's enough.
Oh, too bad.
I see… This is my prison.
Kariya is a kind, but terrifying person.
I'm warning you.
Thank you for your consideration.
You'll understand soon…
Huh?
We headed straight towards
the mansion, didn't we?
Yes.
Hmm… I wonder which way it is?
I haven't been able to get
a hold of my sense of direction…
Me too.
Hey! Woah!
Ow! Wait for me!
Darn! This is also the wrong way?!
This mansion has too many extensions!
No, that's not the only thing…
Huh?
Something is messing up our senses…
Could it be mineral veins or
the effects of a strong magnetic force?!
We've been discovered!
What's this?!
You bastard!
Red Flame Cannon!
What is this?
Who knows… But this is bad!
Huh?
Look!
At any rate, let's run away!
Hey!
Oh no!
Damn! I don't want to make
a big fuss, but…
Lirin!
Ichigo!
Oh ho?! Could those things
coming behind you be…?!
Noba! Erase them!
You saved us…
Why are you here?
We had no choice!
The house was filled with
those strange eyeball dolls!
Noba erased them,
but they just kept creeping out.
There was no end to it!
That's why we went outside…
But we didn't expect them
to be outside as well…
I'm tired…
It seems they won't let us rest!
Oh…here they come.
Why you!
I can't take this any more!
Let's go!
Where are we?
Oh… That's a pretty
impressive tapestry.
This depicts witch hunting…
Yes…that's right…
Who are you?!
Welcome…
Soul Reaper Substitutes.
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Lirin, where did you hide your gigai?
Under your bed.
What if someone finds it?!
It's all right.
I hid it with a doll set and made it
look as if it was a secret hobby of yours.
What if someone finds it?!
A secret hobby…
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
I must endure!
I can't show my shame!
Where is it?!
Hm?! Tetsuzaemon, what's wrong?
Captain! Nothing…
I just have a bit of a stomach-ache…
The toilet is right there.
Thank you. Excuse me!
Captain…
What's wrong?
Tune in again!