The land of the samurai.
There was a time, long ago, when our country was called by that name.
With the arrival of the Amanto from outer space and the Sword Ban twenty years ago,
the samurai class fell into decline.
In these hard times, there was one man left with the spirit of the samurai. His name is Gintoki Sakata.
Kagura and I, Shinpachi Shimura, work at Odd Jobs Gin, which is coincidentally...
Enough already!
Why would you reuse the introduction now?!
Because this is supposed to be a new show!
We have to explain the context for the newcomers!
It's a waste of time to worry about the context of this anime.
The audience is only kind of paying attention.
Right.
So Gintama is kind of back in 16:9.
The first episode of Gintama in a year.
It'll take a little time to get back in the flow,
but for now, it's back to work.
[Odd Jobs Gin-chan]
[Snack Otose]
It feels like I haven't been here in forever.
Good morning!
I guess he's still asleep.
Seriously, we're finally back on air...
Wake up, Gin-san!
Vacation's over.
The show is back...
This town hasn't changed...
Everybody's walking around with glum faces.
Wait!
Who are you?!
What are you doing in here?!
I'll call the police...
Shinpachi.
You haven't changed either.
Couldn't find anything to do while we ran reruns for a year?
You never learn.
Th-That voice...
Hey, now.
You even forgot my face?
Well, they say it only takes a man three days to grow out of his boots.
It's me.
Gin-san.
[Everyone Looks a Little Grown Up After Spring Break]
What?!
Long time no see, Pachi-boy.
How you been doing?
No, wait!
Long time no see?!
What?!
Sure, it's been a year since the show was last on air...
What the hell happened to you in the past year?!
That's long enough for my hair to grow out.
Forget your hair!  You look like a completely different character!
You're acting like we just ran into each other for the first time in years at the World Martial Arts Tournament!
Why do you have a scar?!
Why do you have that patch on your chest?!
What do you mean?
Did you forget the promise we made?
Huh?
After the show ended, we held a little pow wow.
Don't you remember?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
With the TV show and movie over with,
Gintama was starting to lose its novelty.
So we discussed how it was necessary to
give the show a breath of fresh air to keep the fans interested.
Each of us would use this break to work on a remedy.
And then we would return to New Odd Jobs.
We'll meet up at Jabaody Archipelago in two years!
We never made any promises!
Where the hell is Jabaody Archipelago?!
Doesn't matter where it is.
It comes down to feeling and inspiration.
Inspiration, my ass!
You stole that promise from a different anime!
Nobody was waiting for you fools!
Man, I spent all my time training hard.
What were you doing?
I had a rough time.
Getting blown up by weird aliens...
Impaled by cyborgs...
Losing my woman to some guy with a mad widow's peak...
You keep using flashbacks from other shows!
And you did all of this in one year?!
Huh? One year?
What are you talking about?
Two years have passed in this anime in the past year.
That's not much of a difference.
And you're clearly lying!
I mean, this show follows the Sazae format where nobody ages...
I'm not lying.
Just look at how much I've changed.
I'm back!
'Sup!
Long time no see, guys!
How you been doing?
Huh?
Did you shrink, Shinpachi?
Uh, er...
Excuse me.
Who are you?
What? It's me.
Kagura.
Wait!
What?!
You look exactly the same.
Right?
This guy didn't do anything the past two years.
Wait! This is...
Kagura-cha-
Kagura-san?!
You've gotta be kidding!
She's completely grown up!
They say it only takes a woman three days to grow out of her boots.
No, they don't!
I'm tired after the long trip.
Bring me some clothes.
I'm gonna take a nap.
No, wait.
There's something else we need to address first...
Too slow, Nappa!
She's fast...
She changed into her pajamas and plopped herself on the couch the moment she got home.
She's grown into one hell of a pajama girl.
Am I supposed to be impressed?!
And what was the point in standing on my head?!
Kagura, where were you training?
Nowhere really.
I flew around space with Pappy.
Oh, I brought some souvenirs you can eat...
Huh?
Are you talking about this?
Sorry, I already ate it.
He's fast...
He finished them off before I even mentioned them...
Gin-chan's grown into one hell of a greedy guy.
That wouldn't be considered growth!
And do you feel you have to stand on my head to look impressive?!
It appears that my two years of training wasn't for nothing.
We're going to start a new legend here at New Odd Jobs!
I'm getting excited!
Nothing's changed!
Hell, the two of you have regressed!
Anyway, is it true?!
Two years have passed while I wasn't paying attention?!
Nobody told me about this!
Why was I the only one left behind?!
That's what happens when you treat the break as a vacation.
You're supposed to work hard when people aren't watching.
You're the one who's trying to convince everyone you were training during the break!
[Sugar Content]
Personally, I want to know how you're able to look exactly the same after two years.
Two years is enough for ramen to grow stale.
By the way, Sadaharu tagged along with me and grew a lot, Nappa.
Can you stop calling me Nappa?
Ah, it must be Sadaharu!
Pets weren't allowed on my ship, so I had to put him on a different one.
Oh, he hasn't changed at all.
Why did you say that he grew a lot, Kagura-san?
Actually, he looks smaller now?
Here's the receipt.
[Odd Jobs Gin-chan]
Uh...
Excuse me.
Sadaharu just left.
Uh, our pet just ran off, Mister.
It's been a while.
I, Sadaharu, have finished serving my time.
Him?!
Hold on!
That's impossible!
This is clearly the delivery man!
That dog was obviously Sadaharu!
That was a delivery dog from Planet Komainu.
Sadaharu's shy, so I had him delivered by a dog just like him.
Just like him?!
That was obviously Sadaharu!
And they don't look anything like each other!
Like I said, he grew a lot.
This isn't called growing a lot!
This is called turning into a completely different creature!
Shinpachi, dogs grow faster than humans.
Two years is enough for them to become old men.
This guy is literally just an old man!
Brother Shinpachi,
if I've done anything to offend you, I apologize.
Brother?!
Please don't blame Sister.
I will make amends!
If a doggy or two will satisfy you...
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
What do you mean by doggy?!
Why does this remind me of pinky amputation?!
What's wrong with this Sadaharu?!
Why is he acting like a direct-to-video fan?!
Huh?
Wait a second.
That's...
On closer look, there's something at the end of his tail...
Sadaharu?!
There's a small Sadaharu on his tail?!
What's this?
What's going on?!
Uncle, Brother...
Mind if I tell you an old story?
There was a very happy dog who belonged to very wonderful owners.
However, the dog always wondered if he was worthy of his owners.
In order to join his owners as they marched on, to move forward,
the dog chose to fight alongside them.
Day after day, he would place his tail in scorching sand.
Why would you do that?
Day after day, he would make his tail watch Karate Kid 3.
Eventually, a firm wart appeared on his tail.
It continued to grow bigger.
However, as the wart grew in size,
his body shrunk.
As though the wart was sapping his strength...
Do you understand?
That's right - I am that wart.
How could I possibly understand?!
Long story short, the wart traded places with the original.
That's so short that I have no idea what you mean!
Do not worry.
Sadaharu and I may be different in appearance,
but our minds are connected through this tail, and we share the same destiny.
You can call us the Wartio Brothers.
That's not funny!
Please call me Wartiharu.
It is an honor.
I'm not gonna call you that!
How are we supposed to keep this freak as a pet?!
I won't have it!
I refuse to accept this!
Hey! Wait, Nappa!
Otose-san!
Hello?
Listen to this!
Gin-san and Kagura are...
What's all the fuss about?
Don't just barge into a lady's room.
You should knock first.
Is there a fight going on, Master Shinpachi?
It's probably something stupid again.
Just ignore him.
It's a waste of time to listen to him.
I knew it...
You haven't changed at all...
They were lying about two years passing.
What are you babbling about?
In any case, it's been...
...quite some time since I've seen you.
A long time.
A very long time.
You're all Wartiharu!
Oh, you recognize us?
There's nothing to recognize!
You've all evolved into different creatures!
And an android is capable of growing warts?!
They were all intent on improving themselves,
and after pushing themselves too hard for two years, we were born.
For now, you can call us Wartise, Wartirine, and Warti.
So there's nothing left of Tama-san?!
Like I said,
everybody's been working hard while you weren't watching.
We've all been trying to grow.
Only their warts have grown!
Pachi-boy, it doesn't matter what you think.
The past two years aren't coming back.
You have to face reality and look to the future.
You'll have plenty of chances to redeem yourself!
Right now, you're denying yourself that chance...
The chance to create a wart!
You bet I'm gonna deny that chance!
Just leave me alone.
There was a two year jump during the one year break like in One Piece...
Warts turning into old men...
Everybody leaving me behind...
How am I supposed to accept this?!
Shin-chan, may I come in?
Sorry.
I don't want to see anyone right now.
It feels like everyone's gone to a faraway place.
I've experienced this many times before.
I dream about this all the time, Sis.
We're all running in the darkness.
But everyone else is faster than me.
I try my best to catch up,
but I end up alone in the darkness.
Shin-chan, you're a lucky boy.
Because you have a goal to guide you through the darkness.
The truly unfortunate are those who stand still without any sense of which direction to go.
And it's hardest on the person who's running out in front when he can't tell left from right...
True, they aren't nice enough to slow down for you.
They may take a lot of detours...
But you believe that he's moving forward, right?
You're very fortunate to have someone like that, Shin-chan.
No matter how far away he gets, you'll still be able to see him.
And as long as you keep moving, I know that you'll be able to catch up.
It only makes sense.
Since I'll be there to kick you along.
Sis...
Sis!
It doesn't matter if two years have passed!
I can go anywhere if I'm with you!
That's the little brother I know!
You can hang on tight to the two of us!
I won't go easy on you!
But I promise to take you to Neverland!
Honestly...
Don't get so excited that you forget about us, Isao-san.
Though I'll always be right behind you.
Now that we're all happy, let's have dinner!
Hurry up, or you won't get any!
Please, wait for me, Isao-san!
What's for dinner tonight?
Your favorite.
What? Curry...
Omelets.
Thought so!
Y-Yay!
This will help me forget everything bad that's happened!
Now, Isao-san.
Open wide!
Come on, Otae-san.
I can eat my own food.
Please, why are you acting so shy?
We're married now.
This is a perfectly normal thing to do.
You're such a doll!
Nobody would be able to guess which one of us used to stalk the other one!
Don't say that.
If I'd known how kind you were,
I could have found happiness much sooner.
I never imagined that you would quit the Shinsengumi and help us with our dojo.
The Shinsengumi can do fine without me.
They have plenty of responsible people.
But it's my job to support you, Otae-san.
I'm hopeless without you...
Oh, please!
I can't believe I said that!
I'm finished eating...
Oh, Shin-chan?
You barely touched your food.
You need to eat so you can work, Shinpachi-kun.
Huh?
Today's your first day on the job!
That's right.
Isao-san helped you find this wonderful job,
so you need to work hard.
Here.
It feels good to know that you'll be there to replace me.
I'm trusting you to take care of the Shinsengumi.
We won't see each other much since you'll be living there while training,
but do your best.
The two of us...
No, the three of us will always be here to support you.
Right.
Hmm?
Three of us?
Three of us...?
Shin-chan, you'll be an uncle when you return.
Become a samurai that will make this child proud.
R-Really, Otae-san?!
I'm going to be a father?!
Did you hear that, Shinpachi-kun?!
H-Huh?
Shinpachi-kun?!
He's fired up!
Man, he's a very dependable little brother...
No, a very dependable uncle.
That was when Ikazo...
Are you shitting me?!
God!
What have I done to deserve this?!
I go on vacation for a year and this is what happens?!
It's not right!
The Odd Jobs members have changed!
And what's worse, that gorilla of a stalker somehow managed to land my sister
and become my older brother!
I'm the third wheel now!
They sent me to the Shinsengumi to get me out of the house!
I'm completely out of the loop at Odd Jobs, at my own home!
This short amount of time was all it took to leave me with nowhere to belong?!
This is awful...
It's like I'm the only person left in an unknown world...
Where am I supposed to go?
I understand how you feel.
I was once in your position.
Ky-Kyubei-san?!
Sh-She totally looks like a girl now!
And her hand...
S-Sorry...
Kyubei-san...
You're okay with touching men now?
And your clothes...
S-Sorry...
I couldn't ignore you when I saw you crying...
Otae-chan is gone now,
so I decided that I needed to change.
I see...
Because she lost my sister...
D-Do I look strange?
Ah! Sorry about what I said!
You look really cute!
You're totally my type!
Th-Thank you...
U-Um, Shinpachi-kun,
you aren't alone.
I'm here for you.
So you can come here when you're feeling down.
I come here all the time.
It helps when there's someone else who feels the same way as you do.
And do you mind if I ask a favor in return?
Huh?
Well, um...
Could you experiment by touching me from time to time?
Huh?
What's she talking about?
It seems that I'm fine when you touch me.
I wonder why?
Maybe it's because you resemble Tae-chan.
Or maybe...
M-My heart is about to burst!
I want to forget about Tae-chan...
I have to learn to live with men.
So...
Is it okay?
Was Kyubei-san always this cute?!
It's okay!
Absolutely okay!
I can help you every day if you want!
I'll help you with anything you need!
I can touch you every day!
R-Really?
I'm so happy.
Then touch me more.
Please be gentle when you experiment.
Wait! What?
Hold on!
Kyubei-san!
If I...
If I experiment there...
I'll...
...turn into a mad scientist!
Huh?
There's something here...
Something that feels very familiar...
Well?
How is it compared to yours?
I just finished having the procedure,
but I couldn't tell, is there anything abnormal about it?
What procedure?
For that.
For what?
The procedure to attach a male organ.
What the hell did you do?!
You were asking me to touch your balls?!
Unlike before, I'm a woman on the outside and a man on the inside.
I've been completely reborn!
You've only made it worse!
I'm tired of trying to become a man or a woman.
Now, I search for a new world where gender doesn't matter
with those people.
Kyu-chan!
We're heading back!
Oh, it's the cutie from Odd Jobs.
She's aiming for a incredibly wrong new world?!
Kyu-chan's trying to steal him! Eek!
It's bon voyage to a new world with the blue beard pirates?!
Wait, are you working at a gay bar?!
Heh, I'm their ace.
Why are you so proud?!
This is so crazy that I have no idea what's going on anymore!
Enough, Sir Kyubei.
You actually attached that foul member to your body.
I see that you're intent on making your character overlap with mine.
You are...
We are both considered serious characters.
We only differ in gender.
You intend to eliminate that difference and take over my role.
But I was one step ahead of you!
While you were attaching that foul member...
I...
Became Zurako!
[To Be Continued]
[Next Episode]
[Everyone Looks Pretty Grown Up After Summer Break]
The show is finally back,
but what the hell is going on with everyone?!