Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
KARAKURA STATION
Hello, it's me… I've just arrived…
Yeah… Yeah, is that so?
I ate dinner before I came…
We're too late!
This is Karakura 3790!
We found the target!
We're going to capture it!
Oh no!
Are you all right?!
Damn!
We've failed to capture the target!
One of us is injured!
Send the Med Crew immediately!
It's serious!
What in the world
are they planning…?
Ichigo.
Stop repeating the same thing
to yourself…
I’m getting so irritated!
I saw it on the news this morning…
People from all over
have gone missing…
That means…
Those monsters they let loose
might be attacking people…
Dammit!
As usual, Lirin and the others' sensors
didn’t catch anything either…
Where are those Bounts hiding…?
Renji.
Huh?
Has any information come
from Soul Society?
The Stealth Force seems to be here,
but I haven't received any information…
At any rate, we can't do anything
until we find the Bounts
and those creatures…
Is there a way?
Right now, Urahara is making
a powerful sensor at my request.
Until it's finished, we're just going
to have to take our chances
at coming across them in the streets.
Will Ishida be all right…?
He seemed really shocked
about Yoshino…
He stayed silent even when
I talked to him…
I'm a bit worried…
There's nothing we can do…
He's fallen in love with
that Bount woman, huh? Gosh…
Don't make fun of him…!
That's not very considerate…
Huh?
You're one to talk about
being considerate!
What did you say?!
Stop it!
Really. Why are you two
always like this…?
Now's not the time to be
quarreling among friends!
Gentlemen…
Several hundreds of years ago,
we lost many friends in
this underground capital.
I am especially moved that
we will begin our final plan here.
Though it is an ambitious plan,
the spite of our fallen allies
will give us unlimited power.
It seems that Soul Society
has made their move,
but there's no need to worry.
The mineral here eliminates
all Spiritual Pressure.
Furthermore…
Our newly born dolls also contain
large amounts of that mineral as well.
Let's take the time to
refresh ourselves!
Now then, gentlemen,
there are a few who don't know
the results of my research.
I shall show you.
Bitto.
They suck out the souls of living humans
and bring them here.
This is a doll that was created
from Ugaki and my technology.
Ooh… That's what you were doing?
Well, we ended up trading
the life of one of our friends, though…
But how is that different from us
directly sucking people's souls?
It can't just be that there's no danger…
The souls that Bitto bring
are of high purity.
In other words
they're concentrated…
We shall begin sucking souls,
a practice that was considered taboo
by our tribe.
That energy will be gradually
stored up in our bodies.
With this, our abilities should leap to
more than ten times our current level.
What?
What did you say?!
More than ten times…
Is that true?
Of course. This is the truth.
With this power,
we will fulfill our long-cherished wish.
I'll go first.
Burn this into your mind!
The moment that our tribe's laws
and history change!
I have no feelings of pain
or regret…
All I feel is joy and power!
Wonderful!
I see… The collected souls are
concentrated within the Bitto's body.
I never thought it would produce
this much power…
That's not too bad…
I'll pass… Are you serious?!
Mabashi…!
You’re not planning to do
that as well? Are you?
So you’ve chickened out?
You baby!
That's not it!
I'm asking what you think about
breaking our tribe's laws!
Say, Sawatari…
What is it, Mabashi?
I know. Long ago, you sucked
many living souls…!
That was quite long ago…
The side effects! That's why
you've aged so much!
That's why it was a taboo!
How annoying! It doesn't matter
if it means we gain power!
It's not as if we're going to die!
What did you say…?!
Calm down, everyone.
Let's not say things that'll ruin
Kariya's historical moment.
Please allow me to—
Shut up!
The laws are one thing,
but things like this are…
Stop, Mabashi!
There are always controversies
in the world.
There's nothing wrong
with asserting your opinions.
It doesn't matter…
S-Stop…
Mabashi, the next time
you accuse me of something,
you do it at the risk of your life!
Then you can say whatever
you want!
Didn't I tell you before?
Right now, I am the law
of the Bount tribe!
The Stealth Force…was defeated?
They couldn't have…
Not all of them, but a few have…
It seems that their stomachs were
pierced by those monsters.
Furthermore, the monsters
that the Bounts released
removed living human souls
and escaped…
How cruel… The way they do things
isn't beautiful…
Captain Hitsugaya,
what are they planning to do?
Gathering information is
the job of the Stealth Force.
We're going to the World of the Living?
Yeah…
You four will go.
I have already spoken
to the Captains' committee.
Why us?
A monster has appeared.
That's our specialty.
Even if it isn't a Hollow…
Then our targets are those monsters?
No. We're targeting the Bounts.
Excuse me…
What is it?
That's pretty messy work, isn't it…?
Unlike the other lieutenants,
I don't like ugly things.
Why was I chosen?
When I asked Zaraki,
he said you had the most free time…
N-No way!
What about it?
N-Nothing. Is that so…?
I have the feeling that they're planning
something even worse.
We can't leave it to just
Ichigo Kurosaki and Abarai.
I'm counting on you!
Yes!
URAHARA'S SHOP
It's not bad
for last minute preparations…
It's wonderful, store owner!
Now then…
I'm very sorry for interrupting you.
Not at all.
So what did she say?
This is a message from
Madam Yoruichi.
“I will be investigating in
Soul Society for a while.
Be careful of the Bounts' movements”
I see… So how are things
on the other side?
Various posts are gathering information
on the Bounts.
But they’re still uncertain.
All right.
Thank you for your help.
I will excuse myself now…
I have to return to
Madam Yoruichi immediately…
But…
What is it?
I can't believe that Madam Yoruichi
lived in a rundown shack like this…
What did you say?
Calm down… I'm sorry…
But it's pretty comfortable here…
Keep in mind that if something happens
to Madam Yoruichi,
you won't get away easily!
My, my…
I'd like to avoid being chased
by the Punishment Force…
Hey! Ururu! Jinta!
Sorry it's late, but…
Could you go out for me for a bit?
Okay…!
But to call this place a rundown shack…
Excuse me…
You should go in your room.
It would be bad if you were targeted…
Thank you…
Umm, are you all right?
You look pale…
I'm all right… Urahara is calling you…
Y-Yes…
I’m counting on all of you tonight
as well.
Let's all split up and be
on the look out!
Someone who is fighting a monster
should exhibit
elevated Spiritual Pressure…
All right…
Will they really come out?
Nothing will happen if they don't.
It's pretty tricky now…
Say, why are you two like that?
Protecting Orihime is the duty
of the Hikoboshi,
who would be me, Kurodo!
I wouldn't be of any help in a fight
as a stuffed animal…
It's dangerous for her to go
by herself…
That's not fair!
Then I'll go into a gigai as well…
Lirin, that's enough! We're going!
Ooh… What is this…?
It's amazing…!
How is it, gentlemen?
It's better than I imagined, Kariya!
This isn't bad.
I feel as if I've become younger
by a hundred years, easily…
What a feeling!
Even though this is a doll I created,
this is definitely a great achievement
that marks the coming of
a new age for Bounts!
This is still just the beginning.
If we continue to absorb this,
an even more wonderful world
will open itself for us.
This is addictive!
I think I shall have some more…
Well, this was worth taking
the effort to research…!
Mabashi!
What's wrong?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I don't want to do this!
Master Kariya, will you allow me
to treat his wounds?
There's no need for that.
Huh…?
He'll be cured… in an instant…
S-Stop! Let go! I…
Bitto!
S-Stop…
I told you
there's nothing to be afraid of…
Welcome, Mabashi, to the new world.
Lirin, any sign of them?
Nothing at all…
I wonder what's going on…
Can't Urahara finish that
sensor already…?
I give up…
I've always been curious about it, but…
Huh?
What kinds of things do Sado
and Noba talk about
when they're alone together?
Who knows…?
It's probably,
“What should we have for dinner?”
or “The weather is nice today.”
Oh yeah, maybe something like,
“It's delicious if you top
your ramen with chocolate.”
That would be you…
Really?
I can't imagine them having
a conversation…
Do they even talk?
CONVERSATION FAILED
Ichigo that bastard…
Where in the world did he go…?!
The same with Sister!
How could they leave me behind…?
“Guh?”
You bastard!
What do you think you're doing?!
Why, if it isn't the mysterious critter
from Ichigo's place…
Mysterious critter?
Don't underestimate me!
What are you doing here?
I was just taking a walk!
A walk?
That's right!
I just wanted to get a bit
of the night air!
You were left behind, felt lonely,
and chased after Ichigo, didn't you?!
H-How could you say that?!
I was worried about Sister…
I was so worried…
So I wanted to help her a little…
H-Hey! I'm not finished talk…ing…
Roar! Zabimaru!
Someone’s Spiritual Pressure
just increased!
It's Renji!
It seems he's fighting…!
Renji…
Let's go!
Where are you going?
Revenge…for her?
That's not it…
You need to recover your Quincy powers
in order to do that…
That's a thorny path.
The Bounts said earlier that
they needed a Quincy's power.
And afterwards, they said that
they had no need for a Quincy…
Didn't they?
Which do you think is true?
Which do you think?
Who knows…?
Did you ever think about
what would happen
if you were able to recover
your power?
If I wasn't there,
she might not have died…
Was that the case?
I have to find the truth.
With your pride as a Quincy at stake?
Yes…
That's the kind of tribe we are…
He's young.
But that's not bad at all…
You kid! You're all right now!
Stay still!
Damn!
These guys really are targeting
the souls of living humans…!
I'll slice down every one of you!
Master Kariya…
What is it…?
A Soul Reaper is destroying the Bitto.
How impertinent…
He’ll soon learn what happens
when you damage a Bitto.
Hey, you don't look like
you have any wounds…
You can't even hear me, huh?
Wh-What is this?
What is this?!
Don't leave my side!
Bring it on!
100 or 200…
I'll crush you all!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Kurosaki, Urahara said that
he completed the tool to track Bounts!
All right!
Now we'll know where they are!
He said he designed it
to match you perfectly.
Designed?
Yeah.
He said he can’t wait to
see your surprised face.
I've got a really bad feeling
about this…
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
ASUDORA DRUGSTORE
Thank you very much…!
Oh my. Rangiku,
are you going on a trip?
I'm going on a business trip
to the World of the Living!
The cosmetics there
don't really match me…
Women always have
a lot to pack at times like this.
Don't you hate it?
I actually wanted to cut my hair
a little before the trip,
but my captain is so noisy…
Who's noisy…?
Captain?!
Get going already!
Look at me…