You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Renji…?
Why? Why you…
Renji!
Good morning.
How are you, Rukia?
Gin…Ichimaru…
Now, now…
Such bad manners as usual.
You must always address me
as Captain Ichimaru.
If you don’t change your attitude,
you’ll get a scolding from your brother.
I apologize, Captain Ichimaru.
Oh no. Did you think I was serious?
Don’t worry. I won’t turn you in.
I don’t mind it from you.
Why…?
Why have you come to
a place like this, Captain Ichimaru?
Oh… no particular reason.
I was out taking a walk
and thought I’d visit…
just to tease you a little bit.
I never liked this man.
Shortly before I joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
my brother became
the Captain of Squad 6.
This man became the Captain
of Squad 3 about the same time.
I remember him chatting with my brother
whenever they happened to meet…
It didn’t look like anything other
than two captains
exchanging pleasantries.
There was never anything
of any substance said.
However, it didn’t look
that way to me.
From the first time I laid
eyes on this man,
I broke out in a cold sweat
all over my body.
His fingertips…his lips…
Even the slight movement of his eyes…
reminded me of a snake.
And although he was
speaking to my brother,
I felt as though he had
his hands around my throat
and I was frozen,
unable even to blink.
I’ve always hated this man.
It seemed like he could find
the smallest crack in those around him
and seep deep down into
you like venom.
That’s the kind of fear he arouses…
I didn’t have any reason for it.
Something inside me rejected
everything about him.
Despite the many times
we’ve spoken over the years,
those feelings have never changed…
Even now…
I still feel that way about him.
What’s the matter?
You’re in such a daze.
Nothing…
Oh, by the way,
it seems he isn’t actually dead yet…
Abarai, that is.
It’s true…
I can vaguely sense something
like Renji’s spirit energy…
But it’s so weak…
He will die soon.
Poor thing. All he did was
try to save you, Rukia.
Don’t speak so lightly of him!
Are you afraid?
Wh-What?
You don’t want Abarai and
the others to die, do you?
Thinking about not
wanting them dead…
don’t you suddenly feel
afraid of dying?
Want me to save you?
C-Captain Ichimaru!
What… What are you saying, sir?!
Well? I could save you
this instant if I wanted to.
You and Abarai…and the others.
Is he serious?
What could he gain
from saving me?!
And there’s even less reason
for him to want to save Ichigo and Renji!
But…does he really mean it?
Just kidding.
Bye-bye, Rukia.
I’ll see you at the Sokyoku.
I thought I had abandoned
all hope.
I thought I lost my reasons for living…
I had no regrets.
I had no fear of death…
Yet…he was able to shake my resolve!
By holding out that small sliver
of hope,
he managed to make me
yearn just a bit…
He made me want to live again!
He shattered my resolve!
Quit fretting…
over something like this!
Tosen!
What are you looking
around for, idiot?!
This is ridiculous!
How can you call yourselves captains
with that level of strength!
Come on and stand up.
You don’t look dead to me yet.
At least die after releasing
your Bankai.
Don’t get so full of yourself!
A traitor like you isn’t worthy
of Bankai!
Hold it, Komamura.
I’ll do it.
There are three ways
to become a captain in
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
The first is to pass
the Captain’s Exam,
presided over by three other captains,
including the Head Captain himself.
The second way is to receive
the recommendation of
six or more captains,
and be acknowledged by at least
three of the remaining seven captains.
The third way is
to defeat the previous captain
in a one-on-one battle,
which must be witnessed by
two hundred or more squad members.
So what’s your point?
Kenpachi Zaraki…
Ever since the moment
you killed the former captain
of Squad 11 and replaced him,
I’ve felt a deep unease about you,
unease that has become a certainty…
A certainty that you’re a demon…
that you thrive on violence
and blood…
that you’re different from
the rest of us.
And that you were bound someday
to destroy the peace.
And sure enough.
Now you have saved the Ryoka
and here you fight against us,
threatening to bring even
more chaos to the Seireitei.
And all because of
your insatiable bloodlust
and your love of fighting
for its own sake.
Am I wrong?
Enough babbling.
So you’re claiming to be
the hero of justice?
Get to the point.
If you hate me so much,
just attack!
No hatred. I never actually
said that I hated you.
I just find you unforgivable!
Everything that you say and do…
threatens the very peace
we have established!
I do not hate you.
However, I must erase you
in the name of peace!
Tosen!
Bankai!
Suzumushi Tsuishiki Enmakorogi.
This is my Bankai.
This entire space is my Bankai.
Well Zaraki? Even you
could not have expected this.
But…
you probably can’t see anything.
What is this? I can’t see a thing.
I can’t hear a thing.
What do you think of a world
without light or sound?
Isn’t it frightening?
The Enmakorogi steals
all Spiritual Pressure,
all perceptions and
senses of those within it
and creates a dark, silent hell.
Only one can escape this hell…
the one who wields
this Suzumushi.
It’s useless! You cannot catch me.
No matter how skilled one
may be,
when deprived of light so suddenly,
it is the end.
With the sudden darkness,
a tiny fear is born.
The slightest fear slows
one down by half a step.
But I who have known
no light since birth…
You are a demon, after all.
You have no fear to begin with.
Fine!
Then, I will not give you
any chance to feel fear!
It ain’t over yet!
Ichigo, there’s no time left.
I can’t believe my resolve
was so weak.
How depressing.
That’s Captain Tosen’s Enmakorogi…
Is he having a tough battle? Or…
I’d better get over there fast.
Not so fast!
I haven’t lost yet.
Don’t kid yourself. You’ve lost.
Sorry to disappoint you.
In Squad 11, to lose means to die.
That’s different from Squad 9.
Like heaven and earth.
That’s why we’re fighting.
Fight, huh? But you really
should put down your sword.
There’s no way a fifth seat
can defeat a lieutenant.
Shall I tell you a secret?
The reason why I’m a fifth seat…
is simply because
I don’t like the number “four”.
What?
I think the number “three”
is the prettiest.
But that belongs to Ikkaku.
So I chose the fifth seat,
“five” being the closest in resemblance
to the number “three.”
And one more thing…
In Squad 11, we have
an unspoken agreement…
Our zanpakuto can only
be direct combat type.
We all live to fight.
So Kido type of zanpakuto is
thought to be for cowards.
Anyway, the secret begins from here…
What is the true power of
my zanpakuto?
Now, don’t tell Ikkaku and
the Captain, okay?
I don’t want them to dislike me.
Why you--!
Am I alive…?
H-Hello…
Why are you tending to me?
I brought him here.
Rikichi, you…!
Hanataro was captured trying
to save Rukia…
So I thought he would
help you with your injury.
He waited for a chance
to unlock the cell.
I see. Thanks.
Oh no… Actually…
Someone had tended to
your wound before I came.
The only one who could’ve done this…
Lieutenant Abarai!
Please don’t give up!
Ichigo will save Rukia.
So…
Yeah, please don’t give up!
I couldn’t believe it.
That you had lost to the Ryoka.
Or that you had broken out of jail.
And I couldn’t believe
you would raise your sword
against members of
your own Squad.
But, I…
I joined Squad 6 because
you were my hero!
No matter what happens,
I want you to live!
And I want you to be cool and
fight for what you believe in!
Rikichi…
Why…
Right now, he can’t use his eyes,
ears or nose.
He cannot even sense
Spiritual Pressure!
Then how…is he able to
counter me?!
Again! He dodges a fatal blow
at the last second!
Every time he parries,
his counterattacks
get more accurate too!
Is he really a demon, after all?
I got a hit this time.
Just a graze but still…
This Bankai that destroys senses
is a nuisance.
But at least I still have
my sense of touch.
And as long as I have that…
I can feel the moment
his blade makes contact,
then dodge and counterattack.
At least that way, I won’t die.
My blade is starting to
make little hits…
but this is getting boring.
It’s more fun when you can
cut and slash.
Now then…
I can’t see and I can’t hear.
As for the Spiritual Pressure,
I never felt much of it to begin with.
Dammit! Why do I have to
waste time thinking like this?!
So stupid!
Use your instincts!
That’s what I’m doing right now!
Maybe you should be using
that mind-eye thing
to try to visualize your enemy,
you know?
If I could do that
I wouldn’t be having this problem!
What would I do? Let’s see…
I’d give up in a beautiful way.
Die.
Hold it…
That’s it!
An easy way to see his position.
He’s smiling again.
After all this,
he still enjoys the fight?
You’re dangerous,
Kenpachi Zaraki!
You are too dangerous
to be allowed to live!
He didn’t dodge…
Or…he couldn’t dodge?
Hey! So we meet again!
Impossible!
I can see now. I can hear, too.
Is it because I’m holding you?
Or…is it because
I’m touching your sword?
Either way it doesn’t matter.
Bring on the next attack.
I know your trick now.
Next time, I’ll be able to grab your arm
before you penetrate my body.
Dammit…
I must not lose. I can never lose
to the likes of you!
I wish I could gather all the clouds
so they would never again obscure
the light that shines from the stars.
That’s beautiful…
I’m going to become
a Soul Reaper…
If there is not enough justice…
I will become justice itself.
And I will wipe out all the evil
in this world
like the wind casts away
the clouds in the sky…
with all the justice in my being!
Tosen!
Not yet!
It’s not over yet!
I quit. I’m bored.
I have no interest in fighting
a man with one foot already in the grave.
I’m out of here.
Dying is futile.
If you die,
you can’t fight anymore.
I swear it! If it takes my very life
I will stop you!
What an idiot!
If you wanna die so badly, die!
Komamura!
That’s enough.
This man will never understand you.
Don’t sacrifice yourself.
Komamura, I…
I know.
What a shock…
So that’s what’s under
that basket.
You don’t look shocked.
Outward appearances have
nothing to do with fighting abilities.
The only question is…
if your beastly appearance means you
fight with a beast’s strength.
That’s what matters.
You see only what’s on the surface.
You have no respect for
an opponent’s inner strength.
That is your weakness.
I am not kind like Tosen.
Bankai…
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh.
Here I come, Kenpachi Zaraki!
A fight to the death,
just the kind you love!
A fight to the death, huh?
Great! That means I can come
at you with everything I’ve got!
And then after you’re dead…
go reincarnate yourself
and come at me again!
And now…
Let us begin the execution.
So few people showed up.
Heh…?
The squads with both the captain
and lieutenant in attendance are…
the Head Captain’s Squad 1
and our Squad 2…
plus Kyoraku’s Squad 8.
It’s no surprise that Squads 5,
11 and 12 are missing…
But what about the rest?
Even Unohana of Squad 4 is missing.
B-Brother…
Rukia Kuchiki…
Do you have any final words to say?
Yes… Just one.
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
How does the Sokyoku work?
I think it transforms into something.
What if it becomes a giant robot?!
Sokyoku Transformation!
Come on bad guys, bring it on!
Hey, that's pretty cool!
You look like
you're having fun, Ikkaku.
Squad 10 Lieutenant,
Rangiku Matsumoto!
Such divine cleavage!
Squad 4 Captain,
Retsu Unohana!
Mom!
Squad 5 Lieutenant,
Momo Hinamori!
You're my kid sister from today.
Squad 8 Lieutenant,
Nanao Ise!
Scold me, please!
Squad 2 Captain,
Soi Fon!
Is she a zashiki warashi ghost?!
The former leader of
the Punishment Force, Yoruichi Shihoin!
She can turn into a cat.