But there's one problem.
This monkey doesn't have a name yet.
How about Jugem?
Let's call him Shit-Tosser!
Runny Diarrhea?
How about Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear?
Let's just name him
Shinpachi's Sorry Life.
How about Balmung Fezalion?
Issac Schneider.
Okay, finished.
That's frickin' long!
I have bad news for her.
Though it's good news for me.
The shogun's family has requested
the return of the monkey.
You don't need to feel sad.
It doesn't matter how
far apart we are...
I'll always be by your side.
Take care.
The Name Reveals the Person
T-T-T-T-T...
Terrible news!
Fa- Papa, is something wrong?
That monkey ran away!
How can this be?
Now, the honor of the
Yagyu Family is in peril.
Wait! Kyubei!
The third squad will search
the area near the castle.
The second squad should be
setting traps to capture it.
Everyone else should head into
town and comb the streets.
Understood?
Don't forget your bananas and nets.
Yes, ma'am!
Move out!
Please be safe,
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the
Life of Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Schneider
1/3 True Love 2/3 Hangnail Anxiety
Betrayal Knows My Name Or Does It Really
Ignore Calls Squid Dogfish
Halibut Trout-Cod Dogfish...
This Is a Different Dogfish,
I'm Talking About The Dogfish Shark
Kaluga Angler Ray
Yuuteimiyaoukimukou
Pepepepepepepepepepepepe
Runny Diarrhea.
Otae-chan Love
There you are!
Wait!
Please wait!
Found it!
This is where the last
sighting took place.
I see.
Continue the search.
Yes, ma'am!
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Kagura-chan, what are you doing?
Writing a proposal.
A proposal?
Since this Odd Jobs business
isn't making any money,
I'm going to sell this idea to
Bandai Namco for a huge profit.
Then I can live the rest
of my life in comfort.
All done!
Huh? What is this?
Record of Light and Dark: Fakinaway.
Wait!
Record of Light and Dark: Fakinaway
Trading Card Game Proposal
You're going to continue
the joke from last week?!
This age of chaos begins with what is
later known as the
Ragnarok Shepherd War.
Uh, what does that even mean?
And what's about to begin?!
You have done well to
make it here, my son...
Balmung Fezalion
Also known as the Black Wind.
Balmung Fezalion!
Captain of the Fakinaway dark knights.
He is normally a composed person,
but when his comrades are in trouble,
he loses sight of his surroundings and goes berserk.
No, I should call you
the Black Wind now.
A minus. His dreaded enemy, the Demon
Emperor Runny Diarrhea, is his father.
A third eye appears on his forehead
when his true powers awaken.
Demon Emperor Runny Diarrhea!
Later becomes the Brutal
Emperor Kaiser Fakinaway.
It all ends today!
I will avenge my dark knights!
Right now!
I will put everything I
have into this strike!
Ultimate attack!
The command still shows up?!
Hell Fakinaway!
Uh, Kagura-chan?
You can stop.
How much longer until
this drivel is over?
We're about to get to the good part.
What?
You never realized that
the powers of darkness
I granted you could never
be used to defeat darkness?
Though the outcome may
have been different
if you had powers of light.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Y-You are...
Issac Schneider
Also known as the Prince of Light.
The Prince of Light...
Balmung's younger twin brother.
Issac Schneider!
While his brother was abandoned at
young age, Issac was able to live in comfort.
He realizes his father's
dark intentions,
The timing on his entrance
is a little too perfect!
and achieves peace with Balmung
after the Ragnarok Shepherd War.
Balmung, we will talk later.
Right now, we must
focus on defeating him.
Hmph, don't expect me to thank you.
Brother...
Let's do this!
Hey, hey give me your body,
no, no, that's all I need.
Kiss on my lips to shut it up!
Don't touch me!
Hey, hey I don't anything!
Any more about me,
wow, wow, wow, wow,
wow, wow, wow!
Bad communication!
Then they form a band,
which is now known as B'z.
The End
Hold on a second!
That's how the story ends?!
They're just going to
ignore their father?!
I had to suppress my
instincts and think hard
all night to come up with this ending.
Don't act like you actually put
any thought into this crap!
Yes, who is it?
Tojo-san?
D-D-D-
Damn it all!
That monkey ran away after three days!
It's managed to run around the
city while evading all pursuit!
As a result, the Yagyu
family has been accused
of failing to properly train the monkey,
and every single member has been
forced to search for the monkey!
I knew that would happen.
The beast isn't going to listen
to anyone besides Kyubei.
Serves them right.
That's what happens when you take
someone's pet away from them.
This isn't the time to be gloating!
The lady has been
searching for the monkey
for the past three
days without any rest!
She's so worried that she's
barely eaten anything!
And if we can't find the monkey,
the lady will have to disembowel
herself as punishment!
That sounds extreme for one monkey...
Yes, this is Tojo...
What are you doing?! Haven't
you found the monkey?!
I-I'm very sorry!
Please wait just a little longer!
Do you understand?!
That monkey was a gift from the shogun!
If anything happens, the responsibility
will lie with the Yagyu!
Hey, Gramps.
Did Goku come back yet?
Don't worry, young master.
Goku will be back very soon.
Hey! You hear me, Tojo?!
I'm sure that you know what
will happen if you fail!
Worry not.
I was able to secure
Shit-Tosser's favorite target.
Yes, if we use Shit-Tossed as bait,
Goku will come to throw
shit at him, yes.
Hey, when you say Shit-Tossed,
you're referring to this, right?
You don't mean me, right?
Please!
Think of this as a sacrifice
for the lady's sake!
Bastard! You're going to use
me as a shit receptacle?!
Toilet
That monkey is obsessed
with throwing shit at you!
We can use that obsession
to draw him out!
You're going to just let the lady die?!
You're going to let me
be covered in shit?!
Does it really matter?
It's not like you're losing anything.
I'm losing something deep inside
that I can never have back!
You were always aloof like
the gas from a septic tank.
Normally, you say that a
person is aloof like a cloud!
How does that metaphor even work
with the gas from a septic tank?!
Gin-san!
Gin-san! Look!
The shit's hit the fan!
Emergency Bulletin
A large number of monkeys have escaped from the zoo!!
A bunch of monkeys have
escaped from the zoo!
Emergency Bulletin
Shocking! A monkey that can open a lock!!
We bring you footage from
the security cameras.
Watch as an unidentified animal
opens the door to the monkey cage.
It's him!
That monkey has released
all of those monkeys
into the city to interfere
with our search.
That's impossible.
How can a mere animal be so clever?!
We won't be able to single it
out from that troop of monkeys!
It appears that you are our last hope!
The monkey that runs straight
here to throw shit at you
is the one we want!
Hey! Hold on!
Monkey!
Show yourself!
I've brought your favorite
shit receptacle!
Now get your ass out here!
Unload your shit!
Hey! What's going on?!
All of the monkeys are aiming for me!
What is this?!
What do they think about me?!
How do they see me?!
Was one of your ancestors
a crab, or perhaps Frieza?!
No, that's not it.
Gin-chan is descended from gas
that was expelled from Tripitaka's butt.
That would be a fart!
That would mean I was
descended from a fart!
What do we do, Tojo-san?!
We'll be covered in shit before
we can pick out the correct one!
Let's use Odd Jobs' extensive
network to create a perimeter.
Tell them to set up in locations
around Edo, use bananas as bait,
and call his name!
We're going to fall back on
the oldest trick in the book?
We can make it work if
we have the numbers!
What?
A monkey that has a
bell around its neck?
And its name is...
Uh, it's Jugem Jugem Poop-Tossing...
You got it wrong.
It's Shit-Tossing.
Oh, what she said.
Uh, Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the
Life of Shin-chan's
One-Day-Old Underwear...
Huh, not one-day-old?
Wait, which is it?
When did he get shit on his underwear?
Just say it was today.
I don't have any shit
on my underwear today!
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing
the Life of Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Slicer...
Huh? Schneider?
It's Balmung Schneider?
No?
Oh, you mean Issac?
Huh?
Right, so when did Shin-chan
get shit on his underwear?
Uh, when was it?
Just say it was tomorrow.
How am I getting shit
on my future underwear?!
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the
Life of Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Schneider
2/3 True Love 1/3 Hangnail Anxiety...
What?
1/3 True Love?
What about the other two thirds?
Hold on, um...
When did the underwear get dirty?
It's always dirty, I'd say.
Cut it out!
Give me the damn phone!
Now, you've got it wrong.
It's Squid Dogfish Halibut
Trout-Cod Dogfish.
Yes, but This Is a Different Dogfish!
No! You're missing a pe!
Pepepepepepepe...
This will never work!
Most of the questions are about
the shit on my underwear!
How are we supposed to tell
people this long-ass name?!
That's why I said we
should make it shorter!
What do we do now?!
We can't draw it out!
Yes.
What? Is that true?
Thank you so much!
I don't know how to thank you.
I appreciate the help!
Rejoice!
Katsura-dono just told me that
he's captured the monkey!
Huh?
You have such amazing friends!
He dispatched someone to
bring the monkey here.
Really?!
I don't see how he was
able to remember the name.
Ah, Elizabeth!
Is that it?
Balmung Fezalion
Also known as the Black Wind.
There's a bell on his neck.
Wait a sec! Isn't that
Balmung Fezalion?!
How did they find him?!
And he's real?!
Why would a banana work as
bait for a dark knight?!
It's Balmung!
Later becomes the Brutal
Emperor Kaiser Fakinaway!
Seriously, how did he
mistake that for a monkey?
What do we do?
This is bad.
Balmung's glaring at us.
His third eye is glaring at us, too.
Oh no!
Once his third eye is open,
it will bring another
Catastrophe of Sephiroth!
Hey! Somebody apologize to him!
Go tell him we got the wrong guy
before he starts the
Catastrophe of Sephiroth!
Hell Fakinaway!
Oh, shit!
He's going to use Hell Fakinaway!
That's bad! Hell Fakinaway is bad!
You're also gonna throw shit?!
Balmung is throwing shit at us!
Balmung is throwing a
shitload of shit at us!
That wasn't Hell Fakinaway!
He's no different from those monkeys!
Wait!
Issac Schneider
Also known as the Prince of Light.
Enough of this.
Th-That's...!
Issac Schneider!
Hasegawa-san brought
us the Prince of Light
who was able to turn Balmung
back to the side of light!
Everything's okay.
Whew, they're going to
talk things through.
Now we can relax...
Here's our...
Bad Communication!
What kind of shit are
you trying to pull?!
Issac is just a monkey!
And why is Hasegawa-san throwing shit?!
What kind of Bad Communication is this?!
Gin-chan!
We've been surrounded
by so many monkeys!
Hey! Somebody do something!
Th-This is...?
Tojo, everyone...
Thank you for serving as decoys.
We were able to capture
all of the monkeys.
Kyubei-san!
Monkeys, huh?
There were three idiots mixed in there.
Wow! So many!
So many monkeys!
Hmph, took you long enough.
Is the young master's monkey in there?
Yes, most likely.
But we won't be able to
identify which one is his.
What do we do?
Look for a bell.
He should be the only one that's wearing a bell.
Curses!
Clever little rascal.
Goku, you don't want to be my pet?
You don't like me?
That's not the problem.
It's just that there's
someone who he doesn't want
to be separated from, who
he loves more than you.
Kagura-chan!
Little girl!
How dare you insult Lord Mori Mori?!
Let me educate you!
This is the nephew of the Shogun, Lord Shige Shige...
Shut up, Gramps!
Y-Yes...
Is that true, Yagyu guy?
Huh?
Uh, well...
That means I took Goku away
from someone he cares about.
No wonder he ran away.
Sorry, Goku.
I'm always stuck inside the castle,
so I never had any friends to play with.
So when I saw Soyo-chan's monkey,
I got really jealous.
I just wanted to be your friend.
But I ended up taking you
away from your friend.
I'm sorry.
Lord Mori Mori, please stop crying.
He doesn't hate you,
and he isn't unwilling
to be your friend.
That's not the problem.
But his name...
He has a wonderful name
that carries the hopes and
dreams that were given
to him by his friends.
Will you call his name with me?
Ready and...
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the
Life of Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Schneider
1/3 True Love 2/3 Hangnail Anxiety
Betrayal Knows My Name Or Does It Really
Ignore Calls Squid Dogfish
Halibut Trout-Cod Dogfish...
This Is a Different Dogfish,
I'm Talking About The Dogfish Shark
Kaluga Angler Ray
Yuuteimiyaoukimukou
Pepepepepepepepepepepepe
Runny Diarrhea.
Yeah, he can't say that.
He can't say that.
Lord Mori Mori can't say that.
Diarrhea...
Jugem Genome Barbossa Fanta
Pipipipipipipi Barf Diarrhea!
He made up a name!
Lord Mori Mori couldn't remember
the name so he made one up!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry about what I did!
I'm sorry about getting your name wrong!
Here you go, Yagyu guy.
Lord Mori Mori?!
It's okay.
I don't want to see my friends look sad,
whether it's Barf Diarrhea
or the Yagyu guy.
Besides, I can't remember
such a long name yet.
In return...
Uh, Yagyu guy...  I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Uh, could you let me add to his name?
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the
Life of Shin-chan's
Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Schneider
1/3 True Love 2/3 Hangnail Anxiety
Betrayal Knows My Name Or Does It Really
Ignore Calls Squid Dogfish
Halibut Trout-Cod Dogfish...
This Is a Different Dogfish,
I'm Talking About The Dogfish Shark
Kaluga Angler Ray
Yuuteimiyaoukimukou
Pepepepepepepepepepepepe
All's Well That Ends
Well Runny Diarrhea.
The End
Ask Mr. Ginpachi
Ask Mr. Ginpachi...
...is back!
Okay, we have a little time
leftover so I'll read a postcard.
From someone with the pen name
"Okita-kun Love Pudding."
I have a question.
Couldn't you write out
Odd Jobs with two kanji?
Why do you use three?
Please tell me why.
Okay, here's your answer.
Originally, it was just two kanji,
but people might mistake us for some
kind of general store
that sells everything.
We're supposed to be a bunch of people
who are willing to do everything.
So we added the extra
kanji to differentiate.
Well, the result is that
our various guests keep reading
it wrong in the script.
I should mention that a lot of
people also read Amanto wrong.
Next Episode
The maid was watching
when the man who is feared
as the Destroyer of Edo
revealed his true nature.
A shocking truth about the father...
Next time:
The Man's Household Situation
is Hard, His Heart is Soft
The man's household situation
is hard, his heart is soft.