(Nagauta Matsu no Midori)
A New Year’s Special Issue?
Yes!
“The Soul Reapers overcoming
their Squads’ differences
to welcome the New Year!”
That’s the theme we’ll be going
for in our next Seireitei Bulletin!
Okay...
We’ll hold a non-competitive,
yet unique Soul Reaper event!
And I decided to put you in charge!
Huh? Why me?
If you complete it successfully,
I’ll give you a huge byline
as planner and editor!
What?
It’s set, then.
Do a good job, Kira!
Uh, but...
I never said a word about accepting...
He is so bossy...
Okay!
I’m definitely turning it down!
Turn down what?
H-Hinamori?!
What’s the matter?
Why do you act so surprised?
Oh, it’s nothing.
So, what are you turning down?
Huh?!
Uh, it’s...
What is it?
Is it that serious?
No, actually...
But that sounds great!
Why’re you turning it down?
Huh?
Having the Squads overcome their
differences to get along
is a wonderful thing!
Yes, it is, but...
Hisagi is entrusting you with this important
task because he trusts you, Kira!
No...I don’t think that’s why he...
You can do it, Kira!
Y-You think so?
I do!
Hinamori!
Be right there!
Well, I’ll be looking
forward to your article!
All right…I’ll do my best!
So today, you’ll all be flying kites.
Have fun.
Okay, ready…
This is a lovely New Year’s sight.
Hinamori said she’d be coming later…
I hope I can make this all
exciting before she arrives.
Say, Captain…
The others’ kites are flying high, but…
Our kite isn’t doing as well.
That’s because you made
ours look like this!
That’s why I told you to
do a more ordinary design!
Huh?
Whose kite is that?
What’re you doing, Hisagi?
Can’t you tell?
What, is there a problem?
Uh…we’re the hosts here…
The purpose of this event is to
have all Squads get along, right?
So what’s the issue?
All right…
Please help make sure everyone has a
good time flying their kites, okay?
I heard you!
Whoa!
It’s really getting up there.
Huh?
Hisagi, you bastard!
Oh, sorry.
I’ll untangle it right now.
Our string snapped!
You did that on purpose!
Don’t be silly…
Maybe your string was weak?
What?!
Squad 11’s weak?!
Is that what you’re trying to say?!
Hey, please calm down!
He’s insulted Squad 11’s pride—
I won’t stand for it either.
It was just a kite!
Hey Hisagi!
Let’s see whose kite—yours
or mine—flies higher!
You’re on.
Oh, yeah?!
Okay, let’s do this, Yumichika!
Right!
Now hold on, both of you!
Hisagi!
Why’d you have to start an
argument from your side?!
Huh?
It’s theatrics to kick things
up a notch. Theatrics!
There, you see!
Kotsubaki!
Our Captain will always
be number one, right?!
You bet! Now leave this to me!
What?!
It’s a hassle, but since
Captain Soi Fon might scold me,
I’d better take first place.
What?!
See? I’ve really kicked
things up, haven’t I?
This can’t be happening…
Look out!
Out of my way!
I’ll give it my best, too!
That hurt…
Looks like you’re having a hard time…
Captain Kyoraku…
We’re enjoying ourselves.
The two of you…aren’t competing?
We’re different from those barbarians.
I’m relieved to hear that.
Look, look, look!
Collision coming! Collision coming!
Hey!
What’re doing to our kite?!
For starters, I’ll go after the
easy-to-knock-down women’s kite!
Omaeda!
That’s a cheap shot!
Who cares?
It’s you women’s fault for being weak!
Hado Number 31! Shakkaho!
My kite!
Women are weak, and easy
to knockdown, you say?
I will not tolerate…
such insults!
Way to go! Do it! Do it!
Shakkaho!
Yes! Success!
Don’t underestimate Squad 13!
I figured this might happen,
so I put together a kite using
new materials made in America!
Good job, Kotsubaki!
Wait a second…
What sort of situation would prompt
you to make a kite like that?
What’s that?!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
This is our Squad 11 captain’s kite!
Things are becoming quite heated…
No you don’t, Madarame!
Your kite is no match for mine!
You can’t beat our “True
Lady Yoruichi” kite!
Nooooo!
It’s no use.
This is out of my control…
That voice…Hinamori?!
Help!
What’s going on?!
Get me down!
Hinamori!
What is she doing up there?!
Allow me to explain!
Hinamori, who arrived late to the grounds,
became a victim of the kite battle
between the Punishment Force and Squad 11…
Unfortunately for her,
the rope she grabbed was
pulled skyward by the kite
and that’s how she ended up, up, there!
This is no time to be explaining!
We’ve got to do something
and help Hinamori down…
Bankai!
Huh?!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
If that’s the way they want to play,
we’ll take down Ikkaku’s kite together!
Hado Number 58!
Tenran!
I’ll save you, Hinamori!
Shiro!
Hinamori!
Captain?!
Hinamori?!
What was that wind?
Hey!
Don’t get distracted!
What’s that?!
Go, go, Baldy!
Go, go, Meow-Meow!
Do your best, both of you!
Why…?
Why won’t anyone listen to me…?
Keep your chin up, Izuru!
Hisagi…
Use this, Izuru!
Use this to complete your mission!
T-This is…!
It’s about time we settle
this once and for all…
Yeah!
I’ll send your kite crashing
down with the next hit!
Pull!
Go!
I will stop you both myself!
Raise your head! Wabisuke!
Huh?
Isn’t that…
I hope not…
You fool!
It’s the start of the New Year—what
is the meaning of this?!
Extra, extra!
SEIREITEI BULLETIN
GIANT KITE CRASHES INTO SQUAD 1 BARRACKS
Read all about it!
Extra!
I’m such a loser…
Sorry to make you wait, Renji.
That’s okay. Sit down.
So, what did you want to
see me about today, Rukia?
Have a drink first!
This is sake from the World of the Living!
Come on, just one drink.
Renji!
The reason I asked you here is…
I’ve been asked to perform a dance.
So, you're having trouble
getting the steps right,
and that’s why you wanted to talk to me?
Yes…
I’ve learned the choreography…
But…
The Celebration Dance is
something Hisana once did.
Keep that in mind so as not to
embarrass the Kuchiki Clan.
I’ve been told that my sister
danced it beautifully…
I could never match her.
Oh, yeah?
I see, but I’m not sure
I’m the one to talk to…
Oh yeah!
Hey, show me this dance of yours.
You want to see me dance?!
I can’t tell whether you’re
good or bad without seeing it.
I suppose you’re right, but…
Well?
That was a strange-looking dance…
What?!
How dare you call it “strange-looking”
after coming just to see it!
Getting angry isn’t going to help!
Didn’t you think it was
strange-looking yourself?
Well, yes, but…
Be that as it may, this is one
expensive-looking kimono…
It sure is!
This piece was painstakingly made
over a long period of
time just for this dance!
As long as you can get the dance right,
there’s no need for you to wear…
Huh?
Rukia, what’s this?
Oh, that’s a book on dance for beginners.
What about it?
I’ve got it!
Rukia, come with me!
No, I have to rehearse my dance…
Never mind, let’s go!
H-Hey! Wait, Renji!
Don’t worry! This won’t take long!
We’ve come with a request!
Hey, what’re we doing at Squad 11?
You’ll see—I want to get stronger!
Quit slacking, damn it!
Listen up, you guys!
Fighting has no holidays!
If you slack, I’ll kill you personally
and toss you into the river!
And what do you guys want?
Let’s join them, Rukia!
Why me, too?!
I see…
This’ll be fun!
Hello!
What are you planning to do at Squad 10?!
Never mind. Just indulge me.
My, what brings the two of you here?
The Captain’s not here right now…
If I do say, Rangiku...
You look especially ravishing today!
Huh?
What’re you talking about?
Did you come all this way
to sexually harass me?
Of course not!
Rukia here wants to learn the
secret of your feminine charms!
Right, Rukia?
Huh?!
Oh?
Not…really…
Oh, I see…
So you’ve finally awakened
to your own femininity!
I said…
Come in, come in!
Hey, wait!
After all the trouble I went through…
I don’t have time for your games!
How was that?
Okay, I guess.
Don’t comment when you
weren’t even watching!
What is that you’re doing today, anyway?!
Can’t you tell?
I’m practicing my New
Year’s calligraphy.
Do that at your own place!
Why not give it a try?
Huh?
Doing calligraphy and calming your mind
might help you immerse yourself
even further in your dance!
Is that how it works?
It can’t hurt to try!
Okay, done!
Well?
Doesn’t your mind feel calmer?
It does…
By the way…
What time is it?
About seven, maybe?
Seven?!
Is it that late already?!
Calm down, Rukia!
Don’t get so flustered!
Quiet!
Because of you, I’ve wasted more time!
That’s not fair!
Then what about all I’ve done…
Forget it!
Go home.
But…I was trying to…
I said, go home.
Hey, hear me out!
Ouch…
Are you all right, Rukia?
Yes…
I’m fine…
The kimono…
Oh no…
I’m…so sorry, Rukia!
About the kimono, I’ll...
This piece was painstakingly made
over a long period of
time just for this dance!
Get out…
Rukia?
Get out!
Master Byakuya.
What is it?
It’s about…
Where am I?
Long time no see, Kuchiki.
Sir Kaien!
I came today to check on you.
Sir Kaien, I…
No, don’t say a word.
Listen, right now you’re…
THE BOY AT THE TEMPLE GATE
—A CANDLE IN THE WIND
“The boy at the temple gate—a
candle in the wind”!
Huh?
You know the proverbs:
“A cornered rat cannot repent.”
“Nothing ventured is
worth two in the bush.”
“Out of sight…fall from trees.”
Uh…yeah…
But, Kuchiki!
Fear is greater with or without consent.
In one ear and a nail in the other.
Even a worm has a god who will save it.
Don’t ever forget that!
Please don’t go, Sir Kaien!
What should I do?!
When your toes are tired, put
a chili pepper in your socks!
So long!
Sir Kaien!
A dream?
What a strange dream…
Brother!
Hisana wore that kimono
when she performed at the Celebration Dance.
You should wear it, as well,
when you dance at this year’s ceremony.
Brother!
However, what’s important
is not the kimono,
but your attitude towards
performing the dance.
You know what I’m talking about…
There was someone else who said
the same thing before I did…
Let’s join them, Rukia!
You look especially ravishing today!
Doing calligraphy and calming your mind…
That Renji…
So that’s why he went about
doing all those things.
Rukia, there’s still time before
the Celebration Ceremony.
Use that time to practice your dance
and not embarrass the Kuchiki Clan.
Thank you very much, Brother!
Hello!
Oh, if it isn’t Hanataro…
It’s been a long time.
I came today to see Lieutenant Abarai…
Oh, Renji?
Is something the matter?
No, just that Renji…
has shut himself up in his
room since yesterday.
I understand.
Then…
TO RENJI ABARAI
please see that he gets this.
All right. I’ll be sure he gets it.
Well then, I’ll be going.
How unusual for Renji to get a letter…
I wonder who it’s from?
RUKIA KUCHIKI
Dear Renji,
This coming January 10th,
I will be performing the Celebration Dance.
I’d really like you to come and see me.
Thank you.
Rukia! Your dance has greatly improved!
Really?! My feet were warm,
making it easier to perform.
Thanks to my advice, no less!
I kept a chili pepper in my socks!
Sir Kaien was right all along!
What about my advice?
Thank you so much, Sir Kaien!
Another Illustrated Guide for the year!
Ichigo!
Let’s have a kite-flying contest!
Keigo?
That kite’s humongous!
Ichigo!
Let’s give it our best!
What the hell?!
Ishida?!
Why so glum?
The Quincy Dance recital is coming up…
It’s not going well…
Q-Quincy dance?
Let’s do it!
You’re on!
My recital…
Huh?!
W-What…?!