Rise and shine, Big Brother!
Get up!
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: 17 YEARS OLD
HAIR COLOR: ORANGE
EYE COLOR: BROWN
OCCUPATION:
Still sleepy…
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HE CANNOT SEE GHOSTS
Ta-da!
Oh yeah, today’s your
school entrance ceremony.
Karin, pass the soy sauce.
Here’s your soy sauce!
What’re you so angry about, Yuzu?
I’m not angry!
I saved showing you how I look
in my uniform until the day
of my entrance ceremony,
but you won’t even look at me!
See if I care!
I’m not serving you the tastiest
scorched portion of the rice!
Your skirt’s unzipped.
See? I am looking.
Dummy! You’re so dirty-minded!
My glasses!
What’s the matter, Karin?
Nothing.
Yuzu!
Check this out, Yuzu!
How’s this suit look?
Which matches better, this
necktie or this bowtie?
They both look okay. Doesn’t matter.
Doesn’t matter?!
Yuzu!
Don’t be like that.
Come on, take a good look!
Yeah, that’s fine. Whatever.
Whatever?!
Thanks for breakfast.
It’s been 17 months—a little
over a year—since that battle…
I’m in my last year of high school.
Chad and Inoue apparently told
everyone about my Soul Reaper powers.
They said everyone
believed them right away.
Seeing stuff like that happen
right before your eyes
doesn’t leave much
doubt, though, you know.
Despite that, everyone
accepted me without a word…
that was cool.
‘Morning.
But now,
I no longer possess Soul Reaper powers.
Ever since I lost my Spirit Energy,
Karin’s own Spirit
Energy became stronger…
Have a good day, Big Brother!
I will. You take care, okay!
Nowadays, the high-level
spirit medium abilities
-belong to Karin.
-See you!
She’s not too thrilled about it,
-but she doesn’t come
to me for advice.
-Hey, wait up!
Seems like she’s working
her way through it okay.
Let’s go, Mizuiro!
Okay.
Ichigo!
What’s up.
I’ll see you guys later.
Yeah. See you at lunch!
Ichigo! Ichigo!
I’m tapping! I’m tapping out!
‘Morning.
Oh.
Ichigo, did you bring
the game I lent you?
The new one’s coming out
soon, so I need it back.
Yeah, I have it right here.
What? You forgot it?
Shut up. I brought it with me!
Here!
Since losing my Soul Reaper powers,
the Combat Pass appears to have
ceased functioning, as well.
The visual barrier’s gone, and
the Hollow alarm won’t sound.
It’s become a mere piece of wood—
I even forgot I had put
it in my school bag.
Now, the only thing left to show
that I was once a Soul Reaper
is this thing in my hand.
Ishida! Where do you
think you’re going?!
To the nurse’s office!
Now Ishida is eliminating the
Hollows that I used handle.
You’d think he could
just let Imoyama do it,
but the guy seems even less
capable than we thought.
I hope he doesn’t overdo things
and upset the Soul Society…
Ever since that day,
Rukia hasn’t been back
to Karakura Town even once.
Any plans on what to do for your future?
You mean like after high school?
What do you mean “like”?!
What else is there?
We still have time.
After this semester, we
have career counseling.
It’s time you start thinking about it.
You had good grades at the start,
but your grades fell from the second
half of your first school year…
Quit reminding me.
I had a lot going on back then.
It couldn’t be helped.
Besides, I’m still above average.
I wonder how Rukia is doing these days.
Why’re you bringing up Rukia now?
You know…
because I think she could
at least drop by sometimes.
Since then, she hasn’t
dropped by even once.
Don’t you think that’s cold?
She’s not being cold.
She was relieved of her
Karakura Town duties.
Not coming back is normal.
Don’t you miss her?
Of course not.
It took me 16 years to
earn this normal life.
I hope it stays peaceful
like this until I die.
You have a good point…
I don’t ever want to go through
scary stuff like that again, either.
That’s right.
I never once felt superior
because I could see ghosts.
I never thought of making a living
from it or using it to help others.
All I ever yearned for was a
life without seeing ghosts.
I got the life I yearned for.
Hey! Damn it you!
Wait, you!
Give me back my bag!
Mizuiro.
Come to think of it…
Hold this.
Stop!
There’s one other thing I still have
that proves I was once a Soul Reaper.
The physical training I did and the
reflexes I developed in order to win
come in handy sometimes.
Whoa!
That was pretty awesome, kid!
Thanks!
You hungry?
I’ll buy you ramen. Come on.
No thanks.
I want to avoid getting
scolded afterwards.
Please don’t tell anyone
that I hit somebody.
Oh? Sure…
I see…too bad.
Let’s go, Mizuiro, Keigo.
Well, what do you know?
You’re rather cautious…
Ichigo Kurosaki.
How long do you plan
on sleeping, Ichigo?!
Do I have to slug you?!
Come on, wake up, Ichigo Kurosaki.
You fool! Get up, Ichigo!
Get up!
I-chi-go…
Y-You idiot!
You really are an idiot!
I could’ve fallen!
You could’ve killed me!
Big deal.
If you die, you’ll go to
the Soul Society, right?
Talking big now, eh?
Look, you’re not going to die
falling from the second floor.
Because of you, I had a weird dream.
To apologize, hurry up and fall.
Stop that! I’ll fall!!
You’re going to make
me fall for real!!
A weird dream? What about?
I don’t remember.
Trying to tell you made me forget.
So what’s your offer?
F-Five thousand yen…
Five thousand yen per week?!
Get real!
Next!
Here!
I’m Satoda, vice-captain
of the soccer team!
We’d like to borrow your
skills, Mr. Kurosaki…
Just say how long and how much.
-We soccer team have prepared
a budget of two…
-Ichigo…
-Huh?
-He’s talking business.
-no, 1.5 times that of the basketball
team you helped out last time.
-He’ll be a while.
-Oh, I see.
-Please help us out!
-So he’s done renting himself
out to the basketball team?
This sucks…
I won’t have Ichigo
to hang out with again.
You make it sound like he
hangs with you all the time.
Uh…that’s right, he does!
It’s not like I have nothing better
to do than making a nuisance of myself
by bugging Ichigo at his
part time jobs all the time!
-It’s true, it’s true,
it’s so true, I swear!
-If you say so.
-What’s my position?
We’d like you to be our goalkeeper!
Chad would make a better goalkeeper.
Mr. Sado turned us down saying
he found a better-paying job!
So I’m his follow up?
Was Ichigo always so
obsessed with money?
He’s probably saving
up for after he graduates
so he can live on his own.
What?!
You mean he’s moving out?!
No, that I don’t know.
Whatever the case,
Ichigo’s old man
doesn’t seem like the type
who’d loan Ichigo money for anything,
so I think it’s a good idea
for him to save up now.
Oh…
You might be right about that.
Thank you very much!
We did it!
Okay! Let’s go tell our captain!
You decided on the soccer team?
For how much?
That’s a secret.
When do you start?
Today.
Huh?!
What happened to basketball?
My contract ended last week.
What about you? No after-school sports?
I have my part-time job to go to.
Didn’t I tell you?
Since last month, I’ve been
assistant instructor at my dojo.
You’re the assistant instructor?
I’m glad I quit your dojo.
I refuse to call you Sensei.
Shall I force you to
call me that right now?
It’s Miss Inoue…
She’s gorgeous…
Like an idol…
The first time I saw her, I thought,
“Man, am I glad I came
to this high school!”
I took a picture of her the
other day with my cell phone.
Really? Send it to me!!
Huh?
Kurosaki!
Tatsuki!
Oh, Inoue…
Stupid! That’s dangerous!
You’ll fall!
We can see your panties!
Ouch!
You deserved it!
The next time you do
something that dangerous,
I’ll hit you even harder!
Harder than just now?!
You’ll crack open my head!
You don’t have to
get so angry about it!
She didn’t hurt herself.
Shut up!
You have no business lecturing me
about how to teach Orihime a lesson!
I didn’t lecture you!
I’m saying I feel sorry for Inoue!
That’s what I call lecturing!
Uh…the thing is…
I want to ask the two
of you for your advice.
Advice?
Yes. It's about…
my life’s theme,
“The Hahaha Song,”
where I cheer on comedians who have
the right amount of popularity
by matching them to the tune
of the Do-Re-Mi song…
“Right amount of
popularity”? What the hell?
The problem is, recently, all
I’m able to do is hum it!
Isn’t that a good thing?
Why do you think that’s so?!
You’ve grown up.
Wrong!
How do you do that?!
Your eyes look like the number 3!
Orihime’s gotten a lot
better at making faces…
The correct answer is!
Because I don’t know whether I should
start at “Do” with
Dokurodan or Doburock!
Which do you think would be better?
It doesn’t matter!
Oh! I just remembered!
I don’t have time for this!
What’s the matter, Tatsuki?
My part-time job!
Weren’t you working, too, Orihime?
You’d better get going.
You sure are busy. Hang in there.
You act like none of this concerns you,
but did you let your boss know?
Didn’t your boss chew you
out for not doing that before?
If you don’t give her proper notice,
don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Mr. Kurosaki!
Please join us at practice!
Mr. Kurosaki…
Huh?
You dumb ass!
Do you realize what you’re asking?!
You took off last week,
and came to work only
one day after that,
and now you want to take
off another week again?!
That’s why I’m apologizing…
Do you think an apology
makes it all okay?!
You couldn’t care less, could you?!
Just get over here or you’re fired!
I am? All right, I
guess I had it coming.
Huh?!
N-No, hold on…what’re
you saying, Ichigo my boy…
I’m saying I can’t
blame you for firing a guy
like me who doesn’t
take his job seriously.
I’m very sorry.
Thank you for looking after
me for such a long time.
It hasn’t been long!
It’s been only half a year!
The real fun of the Odd Jobs
Service is still ahead!
Our adventures will go on
for a long time to come…
And so the adventure ends…
There’s a guy named Kurosaki here!
Come on out!
What is that?
What era is he from?
I don’t know any throwbacks
from another time like him…
He broke seven teeth of one of my boys!
Seven! Are you some kind of moron?!
Normally it’s two at most!
Oh…that makes sense.
Kurosaki, I know you’re listening!
You’re probably trembling in fear,
wondering how I found out your name!
You got careless!
He got a good look at your face!
I have ways of finding you!
At any rate, Kurosaki,
Until you come out,
me and my boys from Miyasho High
are sealing off the school gate!
You people…
Enough with the outdated antics.
Can’t you see you’re
making trouble for everyone?
Actually, you guys seem on the smart
side for Kurosaki’s friends.
You understand what I’m saying, right?
Now hurry up and go home.
Huh?! What?!
Are you Kurosaki?
What did you just say?
W-What the hell was that for?!
Are you mocking us, you bastard?!
That’s just what I
was going to ask you…
You got a good look at the guy, right?
What about me says “Kurosaki”?!
Did you find him?
Yeah.
The next Substitute Soul Reaper
seems like an interesting fellow.
Tatsuki!
No! People will see your
panties if you run so fast!
Say, does this look okay for my lunch?
No! You can’t eat anything
that’s sweet for lunch!
There’s this two-hour comedy TV
special today that I want to see.
No! It’s bad for your eyes,
so you can only watch
TV for one hour per day!
What are you, her mom?
Illustrated Guide to Keigo!
Today, I’d like to go back through the
changes in my hairstyle
during the 17-month blank.
DECEMBER OF FIRST SCHOOL YEAR:
AS PENALTY FOR LOSING A CHRISTMAS PARTY GAME
First…
The Mohican.
I made him do it.
THE FOLLOWING DAY, HIS TEACHER
FOUND OUT AND CASTIGATED HIM
So…
I shaved my head.
SUMMER OF SECOND SCHOOL YEAR:
AS SOON AS HIS HAIR FINALLY GREW BACK…
Then…
I had a fashionable perm done.
That was awful.
FALL OF SECOND SCHOOL YEAR:
GAVE UP THE UNPOPULAR PERM AND HAD A STRAIGHT PERM DONE.
And then came…
THE SHOCKING
the shocking
black hair.
Look, you’re turning
off the viewers…
THE END