Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who keep
a close eye on the countless souls,
good and evil, that fill this world.
While visiting the Visoreds,
Ichigo, after intense Visored Training,
finally succeeds in suppressing
his inner Hollow.
Meanwhile, conducting his investigation
at the Daireisho Archives,
Ukitake finds a possible clue
to Aizen's goal.
In order to kill the Soul Society's
Royal Family,
Aizen attempts to create the Ouken,
the key to enter the palace.
And to do so he needs
100,000 souls,
and an Enriched Spirit Zone
in the radius of one spirit mile.
In other words, Karakura Town,
as well as all the nearby
land and people,
will be ripped away from
the world and will disappear.
Wait one moment, Captain Hitsugaya...
There's someone who's been
waiting here to talk to you...
You...
Hitsugaya...
I see... You've awakened, Hinamori...
Is it all right for you to be walking
around already?
Yes...I'm all right now!
I see...
You don't look like
you're all right, you idiot.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Hitsugaya...
...for not believing in you.
There was something wrong with me
for pointing my sword at you.
I really...
You idiot...
That won't bother me forever...
It doesn't bother me,
so don't let it bother you.
Get some sleep already.
Get rid of those bags
under your eyes.
Okay... Thank you, Hitsugaya...
Besides...
You're still like a kid.
If you don't get a lot more
sleep than other people,
you'll stop growing!
Take a look at Matsumoto!
You won't be able to catch up to her
unless you sleep for
at least ten years!
Sh-Shut up! Rangiku is different!
Besides, Hitsugaya, you of all people
shouldn't talk to me about growing!
Hinamori!
Don't make me repeat myself.
It's not "Hitsugaya,"
it's "Captain Hitsugaya."
Yeah... That's right...
Say...
Can I ask you something, Hitsugaya?
What is it?
Are you going to...
fight Captain Aizen?
Are you going to kill him?
Please...
Save Captain Aizen!
What Captain Aizen is doing is bad...
But I'm sure that he has
a good reason for it.
That's right!
I'm sure that Captain Aizen is
being forced by Captain Ichimaru,
or someone else, into doing...
Sorry. I let her talk out of respect
for her wishes...
...but it seems that it's still too early.
No... Thank you very much.
Captain Hitsugaya.
Excuse me.
Aizen!
What's wrong?!
Your power's dropping!
That's not...true!
Huh?! Help Sado out
with his training?!
Why me?!
It doesn't seem like
he'll leave if I turn him down.
You're not answering my question!
Why not?!
It's not such a big deal...
That's right!
You must be big-hearted...
Stay out of this, outsiders!
He asked you, didn't he?
Then you should help him!
You need the power of a Bankai
to train Sado.
Then, even more so,
you should do it!
You have a Bankai, don't you?!
OH COME ON!
Oh, come on! A mere handsome
and perverted shopkeeper like me
OH COME ON!
would never be able to use a Bankai!
Don't you know the details
of what's happening?!
OH COME ON!
I've known for some time now that
you used to be the Squad 12 captain
and that you were the one
who created the Hogyoku!
Eww, gross!
That's why people say that
young people these days
have no manners!
That's right!
Shut up!
Anyway, he asked you! You do it!
Just listen to him, Ururu...
He's just a freeloader.
But, in the end,
he doesn't have any manly spirit.
Yeah...
He really doesn't do anything...
As they say,
"Those who don't work don't eat!"
That's right!
Shut up! I won't fall for that!
You're the same, too!
Anyway... I won't be any good...
My Bankai isn't good for training
people or helping people.
All right! I understand! Let's do this!
Huh?
Abarai, you have something
you want to ask me, right?
Y-Yeah...
Let's make a deal...
If you do routine chores
around here for three months,
I'll answer any of your questions!
H-Helping with training
isn't a routine chore!
It is! You're still putting in effort
and risking your life!
Or will you give up asking me
what you want to know?
He was so resistant...
But Abarai is really getting into it.
Come on! You can't get strong
if you just run away!
Don't underestimate me!
Sado, your power still has
room for growth.
You should be able to move on
to the next step
if you keep fighting against a Bankai.
There's just one concern...
Your power is different from that
of a Soul Reaper or a Quincy.
Yes... It's as if your power is...
I told you not to undo
your Hollow transformation!
What are you, stupid?!
It was dangerous if I hadn't!
Shut up!
Baldy!
Shut up! Going as far
as you can is your training!
What?!
If you want to fool around, then quit!
Those two are getting along
unexpectedly well.
Yeah.
There...
A cat is walking across
that wide area
as if there's a rim around it.
The birds and the other animals
don't approach it.
No... They can't approach it...
That's because...there's a barrier here.
What an incredible barrier...
But why?
This is such a powerful barrier,
but it's kind of like
my Shunshunrikka shield.
I can do this!
Hurry up, Ichigo! One more time!
Shut up! I got it already!
That hurts!
I keep telling you that
the first move you make
after you take out your mask is slow!
If you get hit...it's over!
The time he can maintain that
state isn't getting any longer.
Well, he won't make
immediate progress.
Four seconds.
That's quick!
Say, say, why is Berry doing this?
This is the training to remain in
his Hollow form for long periods of time!
You did it too, remember?
I didn't do that.
What? You liar...
It's true.
Mashiro was able to remain
in her Hollow form
for 15 hours from the beginning.
She's the only one who didn't train
to maintain a Hollow transformation.
Really? I forgot about that.
See?! Stupid Kensei, you grouch!
Why you...
Now, now...
What's wrong, Hachi?
Someone has passed through
my barrier and entered this building.
Is it a Soul Reaper?
No...
The Hachigyo Sogai placed
around here is a technique
I created when I became
a Visored...
It's impossible to disperse it
with Soul Reaper kido.
Then who is it?!
Is it a Visored like us?!
I don't know...
What's most confusing is that
the intruder didn't destroy my barrier,
but passed through it.
I don't think even a Visored
could do that.
Then who in the world
is this intruder?
It's coming...
- A...
- A human?!
Oh... Umm...
S-Sorry...
Where's the bathroom?
Just kidding.
Huh?!
She said that she was kidding.
It's a joke.
Don't get mad, Kensei.
I wouldn't say I was kidding
in this situation.
What are you doing, Ichigo?!
Crap!
Kurosaki?!
Inoue?!
I see...
So that's what's happening now...
What is it?
N-Nothing... I was just thinking
that you aren't very surprised.
I am surprised...
But when I'm suddenly told
about something like
this Ouken, the royal key,
my mind can't keep up.
Don't look so worried, Inoue.
It'll be all right. I'll stop Aizen.
I can still get stronger...
I can sense it.
Thank you for informing me, Inoue.
All right!
Let's begin training again, Hiyori!
It's "Ms. Hiyori", baldy!
- I know...
- I see...
Kurosaki wasn't surprised,
not because his mind
couldn't keep up...
It's because he's getting stronger.
It doesn't matter what
his enemies' goals are...
Kurosaki only focuses
on his own strength
and what needs to be done.
The surprise doesn't shake his heart...
Kurosaki is really getting stronger.
And he isn't dark and scary like before.
But it's not just in a gentle way...
It's a strange feeling.
Tsk! Who was that woman?!
She just talked to Ichigo and then left.
It seemed like she was Ichigo's friend.
That girl...is Orihime.
Huh?! What's this, Shinji?!
You know her?!
Orihime is...
...my first love.
That's a blatant lie!
Shinji, you always say
that to cute girls!
You even said that to me!
Is she implying that she's cute?
He says that to all cute girls?!
That's odd! He's never said that to me!
Cause I didn't say it to you, idiot!
Don't look the other way!
Hachi.
Yes?
Your barrier is perfect.
There's no mistaking that.
Yes.
So how could that girl,
Orihime, find this place?
And furthermore, how could she get in?
I don't know for certain.
But my impression of
her Spiritual Pressure up close...
She has the same type of
barrier-making abilities that I have...
That's what I sensed.
It's probably because of that ability
that she was able to detect
this place while it was in a barrier,
as well as pass through my barrier.
I never expected a human
to have that kind of ability.
It's a little hard to believe.
So here you are, Inoue.
Yoruichi!
Kisuke asked me to find you.
Mr. Urahara?
He wanted me to take you to
his training ground immediately.
Tilt the goblet to the west, Wolke!
You're still hiding Gintô...
You're pretty cautious.
It sounds like you're calling me
a coward.
That's right.
What's wrong?!
You call that running away?!
Your dodging speed is getting slower!
Is this your limit?!
My limit... He's right...
My arms and legs can't move
much anymore...
But his Spiritual Pressure
is definitely getting weaker.
He said that my power
would come back
if I kept dodging arrows,
but there is still no sign of that.
I don't know how much of what
he told me was a lie.
But he'll kill me at this rate.
I'm at my limit...
I've got to stop his movements
and end this training!
And my only chance is...
Now!
My final Gintô!
The silver whip strikes
the five-fingered stone bed!
Gritz!
All right!
Too bad. It's over.
He got me...
Crap!
To wear down both mind
and body to its limits
and take a shot from a
spirit bow 19 mm to the right
of your heart's sinoatrial node...
That's the only way to regain the powers
you lost from Quincy Letz Stile.
Honestly... Why did you use a Gritz there?
If you used a Haizen,
you could have at least injured me.
That's why I say you're stupid.
It makes me sick.
But...I'll let that slide for today.
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
Kurosaki, are you going to
continue training?
Yeah. I'll get stronger if I stay here.
We'll train him on
his sense of humor too!
When he leaves,
he'll be a splendid Kansai Comedian!
Wow... He's being taught genuine comedy!
I'm so jealous!
Why?!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Abarai, clean this room too!
Quickly!
After we let Sado rest for
half an hour,
we're going to start his training again!
I know!
He's getting him to do general chores
in addition to training Sado.
Urahara really is good at that.
He tricked him...
Red Pineapple, really is stupid...
Stupid...