Oh, sorry.
No, I wasn't paying attention either.
Your bag...
I'm so sorry.
Were there any eggs inside?
It's okay.
There wasn't anything important inside.
Really, don't worry about it.
Bye.
Ah, please wait!
You forgot this.
Oh, thank you.
So...
Do you like anpan?
Meals Should Be Balanced
I don't.
Anpan and milk.
This is how I run a stakeout.
I don't eat anything else until it's over.
Basically, it's an offering to the gods.
I personally can't stand it, but the god of stakeouts is a big fan, so that's that.
A truth that has been shown in police dramas around the world.
For the success of this stakeout,
I must suppress my desire to eat curry, katsudon, and yakiniku,
and munch on anpan instead.
You're not supposed to come into contact with the target.
And you're supposed to be an inspector?
Do you realize how weird it is to stake out a stakeout?
You should have volunteered if you have nothing better to do.
Don't get so upset.
I see that you're only eating anpan again.
You can be superstitious if you want,
but you won't last long if you aren't eating right.
Sorry about the wait.
Oh, thanks.
Don't even bother, Vice Chief.
I don't need ramen!
Well, if you insist, I suppose I don't have a choice.
An order from you is absolute.
Huh? What'd you say?
Nothing.
So how would you describe this Sachi Narasaki?
She seems to be a nice person,
going by the five days I've been watching her.
I find it hard to believe that she's the older sister of a brutal Joi terrorist.
Oh?
If you look at Sogo,
one sibling tends to be more responsible when the other is anything but.
Vice Chief, you're a little too close...
And what about Donbei?
He's been running around like crazy.
Apparently, he stole money from his fellow terrorists.
They're trying to chase him down.
His only option is to run to his sister.
I can't say that I like the idea of using his sister as bait.
Do you like the idea of letting her brother run wild?
Besides, what if the Joi who are chasing Donbei decide to use her as bait...
We'll use his sister as bait to wipe them all out.
Leave the dirty work to us.
Yamazaki, I'm giving you a different mission.
Protect the girl.
Sagaru Yamazaki's Observation Report:
Week 1 of Living on Anpan
I've been living on anpan for an entire week now.
What I'd give for a bowl of miso soup.
The girl hasn't made a move yet.
Sachi Narasaki.
Owner of the bar Nonbei.
The story is that she's a dutiful daughter
who's been running her father's business by herself since he died four years ago.
On the other hand, her brother Donbei is notorious for being a nasty villain.
He regularly came to his sister for money after she took over the bar.
A dutiful daughter under duress,
the younger brother who continues to put her in danger,
and the terrorists who are after them.
My mission is to monitor the Joi terrorists,
while protecting the girl.
I, Sagaru Yamazaki, Shinsengumi inspector, vow to protect her!
And with my newfound determination, I once again munch on anpan.
Day 8 of living on anpan.
When I went to the supermarket yesterday,
I could hear people whispering, "Anpanman is here! No kidding!" in the back,
Nonbei
but the girl hasn't made a move yet.
Her customers are all regulars.
Every day is the same.
I can only hope that her peaceful life lasts forever.
As I begin to forget my purpose here,
I once again munch on anpan.
Day 12 of living on anpan.
I've just realized that it's been days since I've talked to anyone.
The last words I spoke were, "No, put it in one bag," three days ago,
but the girl hasn't made a move yet.
For a moment, I almost thought that she was looking at me,
Nonbei
but it must have been my imagination.
As I try to pull myself together,
I once again munch on anpan.
But I could only finish half of it.
Day 15 of living on anpan.
When I went to the convenience store,
people started whispering, "The one-bag guy is here!"
"He's gonna buy anpan and milk!"
"In one bag!" and stuff,
Nonbei
but the girl hasn't made a move yet.
What do I do if nothing happens?
As I attempt to ignore those doubts,
I once again munch on anpan.
And then I throw it all up.
Day 20 of living on anpan.
It's been so long since I last spoke that I was wondering if my voice still worked,
so I screamed at the top of my lungs and the guy next door replied,
"Shut up!"
while banging on the wall, which had me jumping up and down with joy
over the fact that I actually held a conversation,
but the girl still hasn't made a move yet.
She just smiles day after day.
There are more exciting ways to live.
Such as harboring a fugitive younger brother.
And with that thought, I once again...
...smash anpan against the wall.
Day 22 of living on anpan.
Give me a break already.
When is her younger brother going to show up?
When will I be released from this anpan curse?
Shut up!
Hurry, younger brother!
Save me from the endless anpan!
As I make a wish from the bottom of my heart,
I sparking the anpan into the sky!
Day 23 of living on anpan.
I sparking the anpan into the supermarket clerk!
Day 24 of living on anpan.
I sparking the anpan into the convenience store clerk!
Day 25 of living on anpan.
I sparking the anpan into the vice chief!
Day 28 of living on anpan.
I wake up and discover that I have no memory of the past few days.
However, despite all the change I've gone through,
the girl hasn't made a move yet.
Like always, she scatters anpan on the road,
{\a6]Anpan
and puts the anpan above the entrance.
And then at anpan-night,
she anpans the anpan and anpans.
Anpanning the anpan to anpan the anpan and anpanny anpan, anpan, anpan...
Day 30 of Living on Anpan
ANPAN
Day 31 of living on anpan.
When I woke up, I was standing in an unfamiliar place, covered in anko.
Who gives a damn about the mission or girl?!
I refuse to take another bite of anpan!
I couldn't take it anymore.
I no longer cared.
I headed back to the room to pack up and leave.
But there I found...
I didn't realize we were neighbors.
You'll ruin your health if you only eat anpan.
Here are some leftover meat and potatoes if you don't mind.
Thank you for watching over me.
From Nonbei.
The tears wouldn't stop...
I don't know when she realized I was watching her.
I don't know how much she actually knew.
One thing was clear...
I wasn't worthy of her gratitude.
Since I was ready to abandon her because of my stupid superstition...
That day, I turned against the god of stakeouts.
Greater Edo Hospital
Day 3 of meat and potatoes.
I woke up...
...to find myself staring at an unfamiliar ceiling.
And the vice chief with a disgusted look on his face.
Vice Chief, where am I?
The hospital.
Huh?
What happened to me?
What about Sachi-san? Her brother?
What happened to them?
They got away.
What?
They took the money and ran.
Yamazaki...
We were tricked by the girl.
The siblings were working together to steal money from the Joi.
The sister noticed my presence immediately,
so she spent an entire month acting to fool me.
And once I fell apart,
she used the pretense of kindness to poison me.
Women are damn scary.
Hiding under layer after layer of makeup.
Do we ever get a chance to see their real faces?
Well, she still served as the perfect bait.
We rounded up all the ruffians who were trailing her.
That more than makes up for the two who got away.
We were able to freely move around because you were there.
Sorry about the wait.
Yamazaki, you did a good job.
Vice Chief, this isn't like you.
Are you trying to make me feel better?
It's not like I'm depressed or anything.
I'm used to being fooled by women and failing missions.
But I was hoping that...
...I could at least lose on my own terms.
I guess that you aren't in the mood for ramen.
Can I ask for a favor?
It really worked, Sis.
We have enough money to fool around for a while.
What are you going to spend it on?
You're such an idiot.
Money isn't meant for fooling around.
Money is used to earn more money.
Come on...
What's wrong, Sis?
Well, I had a feeling that someone was watching us...
Please...
Are your senses shot after spending all that time with that Shinsengumi failure?
Oh, sorry.
Watch where you're going, fool!
Are you okay, Sis?
I'm so sorry.
I'm in a hurry to get to the festival.
Anpan
Festival?
Where is this festival, eh?
Right here. The Yamazaki Spring Bread Festival.
Day 63 of the Yamazaki Bread Festival.
Y-You really like anpan, huh...
I don't.
And so, I once again munch on anpan.
Sure.
I happen to be a fan of baseball.
I'd be happy to accompany you.
I knew it...
You don't want to come with me.
Um, I said that I'd be happy to accompany you.
Of course...
Happy to accompany me...
Happy?
Huh? What'd you just say?
I said that I'd be happy to watch the baseball game with you.
Ho... Ho...
Home run!
Um, you destroyed the tickets.
We Are All Warriors in the Battle Against Fate
A true man isn't measured by high education, high income, or height.
The three Hs mean nothing.
The only H you need is the H for the hair on your ass.
One ass hair and constant persistence is all it takes to penetrate that giant wall.
Well, you girly men probably wouldn't understand.
He's not really girly, he just eats shit.
Shut your trap, you sick bastard.
This must be a trap.
As a fellow sadist, I can guess what's in her mind.
Shut up!
Don't let jealousy cloud your judgment, Benny, 'kay?
BENNIE K?
I don't listen to them.
The rain dripping from the roof can carve a hole in stone after enough time!
My relentless rain of love has finally spread open her tightly shut legs!
Your metaphors are too obscene.
Did she say anything else?
No.
She'll be waiting in front of the station at one on Sunday.
And she told me to stop following her around after this.
And to never visit her business again.
Well, we'll be in a relationship now.
So that won't be needed anymore.
Isn't she telling you to completely forget about her after indulging you one last time?
Shut up!  'Kay, Hayashiya?
His name is Pa Hayashiya.
If this is the last time, I won't get another chance!
I will make her mine!
I'll hit a walk-off home run and lead Otae-san back to the bench!
We're right in the path of the typhoon.
She's not gonna show.
Guess you're out of luck.
It's a little early,
but a gentleman is supposed to arrive early and wait for the lady.
Kondo-san...
Don't worry.
The weather will improve.
Whether it's raining cats or dogs or spears,
my rain of love will never falter!
There's something lodged in your arm.
Huh?!
It's terrible!
A cargo plane is on fire!
Part of its load is falling towards Edo!
Oh.
Don't worry about it.
It's gonna drop right here.
It really is raining spears!
How bad is my luck?!
I'm like a sponge for bad luck!
The tickets!
Wait!
It's not safe to run out into the street!
S-Sorry...
I'm fine.
Uh, you're bleeding.
I haven't even made it fifty meters,
and I've already experienced fifty years worth of bad luck.
Damn it, I'm going on this date!
First, I need the tickets...
Check it out.
Aren't these tickets for the game today?
Awesome!
We don't have enough to play baseball because of the typhoon.
Let's go watch the game!
Excuse me, kids.
Could you let me see those tickets?
What do you want, old timer?
Huh?
Whoa, you're covered in blood!
Actually, I just dropped my tickets.
They're probably the ones you're holding.
Could you return them?
What?
You got any proof?
Okay.
Then I'll give you something better in return.
Is there anything you want?
Hm, we have nothing to do because of the typhoon.
Play baseball with us in the gym!
S-Sure thing.
I still have time.
And it's just a bunch of kids.
Kagura's pitches are always so thrilling!
Old timer!
The catcher is supposed to catch the ball!
R-Right...
I-I need to get going soon...
What's that?!
Don't you want these tickets?
Okay!
Let me throw the ball next.
Anything but battery mates with the China girl.
Okay.
Here it comes.
See ya, old timer!
Let's do this again sometime!
Beetle King - Throwaway Matches
Kind of serious contest!
There will be kind of serious battles now!
Let us know which match was obviously thrown!
This isn't just bad luck!
I'm bruised all over, and it was just a waste of time?!
Some evil force is actively interfering with my love!
Oh, you found something nice there.
You should go with your brother.
Doesn't he like baseball?
I don't know if he'll come.
He hasn't left his room ever since...
Wait!
Where did you find those tickets, China girl?!
I didn't find them.
Sachiko-chan did.
Sachiko-chan!
Those belong to me!
I'll be in a lot of trouble without them!
Really?
I thought they were a gift from God.
It's too bad.
Make sure you don't drop them again.
Th-Thank you...
Are you sure?
This could be a chance to get your brother to go outside!
Ah, it's okay.
Anything baseball would be like salt on an old wound.
My brother used to love baseball so much.
He would always play catch with our father by the river.
I loved to watch them.
But one day, my brother threw the ball too high,
and our father went after it.
He hasn't...
...come home since.
How far did our father go chasing after it?
My brother's been waiting for him to come back with the ball.
Sachiko-chan!
Are you sure?
Are you really sure about this?
What would you know?!
Brother!
Y-Yes...
That's right...
Stop throwing balls into the past.
Baseballs are meant to be thrown forward!
I could feel your ball touch my heart!
I'm sure your old man felt the same way!
Thank you for helping my brother come outside!
Nice job, gorilla!
I'm going to use my full strength!
Huh?
I want you to feel my true strength!
Wait, wait, wait...
Here I go!
Wait a second!
Thank you very much!
Why is everyone interfering with my love?
It's like the heavens are trying to keep me away from Otae-san!
But I refuse to give up!
I can still hit a walk-off home run!
You found our father?!
Wasn't he dead?
He's lost his memory?!
Is there anything you can do?!
Something to help him remember?
There isn't anything to...
What is this burning passion in my chest?!
Father!
Your memory's back!
Yeah.
I remembered everything by playing catch.
Father!
I don't know who you are, but thank you very much.
Is there any way to thank you?
No, it's okay.
Anyway, you've finally been reunited.
The three of you should go enjoy the game.
Those are...
It's okay.
Have fun in my place.
Thank you very much!
We'll return the favor one day!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm already late.
I guess that Otae-san and I aren't meant to be together in this lifetime.
Fate has chosen to stand in our way, and there's nothing I can do about it.
As I watched the skies clear the moment I relinquished the tickets,
that was the conclusion I reached.
I wonder if Otae-san is waiting for me.
Of course not.
Kondo-san.
Toshi?
Sorry it's not your girl.
Heh, the girl doesn't matter anymore.
I'm devoting myself to the sword.
I see.
Sorry to bother you while you're down,
but we have a problem on our hands.
A meteorite is approaching Edo.
Huh?
It's nothing serious.
The meteorite's the size of a baseball.
It's so small that they couldn't detect it until now,
but at this rate, it's going to hit your date spot in 15 minutes.
What?!
We'll have to issue an evacuation order.
Well, there probably won't be much damage,
but you better stay away from the dome.
Huh?
Kondo-san?
Kondo-san?!
I just know it!
The meteorite is headed right for Otae-san!
Because I was trying to defy fate and make Otae-san mine,
fate is going after Otae-san now!
Hey!
Here it comes!
It's coming this way!
Huh?
Is it coming...
...for me?
No.
Kondo will pinch hit for you.
Kondo-san...
Mister!
We've got you covered!
I'll catch it if you miss!
It's over, fate.
I'm not interested in going to heaven.
I live for love...
To protect my loved ones...
I live as a samurai!
Here's a walk-off home run!
I'm walking off.
Next Episode
Meals Should Be Balanced
Next time:
It's too confusing when talking about the poster girl for a poster store,
so call her a sandwich board