Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Sorry, everybody…
What do you mean,
“Sorry, everybody”?
You won, you idiot…
Thank you!
Thanks to you,
Kenny had fun fighting!
It was a long time since
I saw Kenny having so much fun!
Thank you so much!
Here we go…
Ichigo… If you can, please don’t die.
And if you can, please play
with Kenny again, will you?
Please…
The sounds…have stopped.
Do you think Ichigo is all right?
We’ve come this far.
We have no choice
but to believe in him.
That’s true, but…
This is no time to get distracted.
It’s our turn now.
We’re going to jump across.
Are you ready, Hana?
Yes.
Here we go!
I’m counting on you!
That was dangerous!
Sorry…
The sounds have stopped…
And the Spiritual Pressure is gone.
Both of them…
Which of them died?
I don’t know.
The diffused reflection of
the Sekki-Seki is causing
the traces of Spiritual Pressure
to be wiped away.
Why?
There should be no good reason…
that blood is spilled for my sake.
Please tell me…
Kaien…
There now…
That should do it!
It should be fine now.
Umm…
Huh?
You tied up my arms, too.
Oh, sorry ‘bout that.
Oh, it’s too much trouble!
Hana, you can just fly with it!
Hold it…
Stop it! My arms are going to tear off!
This is impossible!
I'm sorry, Ichigo. I'm a little late…
You’ve been beat up good.
But with Kenpachi Zaraki as your foe,
you could not have expected less.
Taking him out in the process
was quite an achievement.
But, I must say, you fought well.
You endured well. I am impressed.
Do not worry.
I will not allow you to die.
Where’d you come from…kid?
That’s a sword. Aren’t you scared?
It’s a tool for killing people.
Kid… What’s your name?
You don’t have one?
I don’t, either.
Oh!
Yachiru…
Hurray! Hurray! Kenny’s up!
Yahoo!
What about that guy?
Huh?
I called for Unohana.
She’ll be here soon.
What about him?
I don’t know.
I don’t think he’s dead.
That’s good…
This way, I can pay him back.
There’s nothing to pay him back for.
Sure there is! I lost.
You didn’t lose, Kenny!
You idiot! What’s with that look
on your face?
But you didn’t lose!
Ichigo said, “Zangetsu and I –
the two of us – are fighting together.”
It was two against one!
You won, Kenny!
Don’t laugh like that!
Fighting together with
your Zanpaku-to…?
Yachiru…
Hmm?
You remember that time
I gave you your name?
Of course!
I even remember how many clouds
there were in the sky!
Yeah… Me, too.
K-Kenny…?
Be quiet…
I’d forgotten for a long time…
How painful it is, having no name.
Everyone else would be called by name,
but I didn’t have one.
That feeling…
It is read “Yachiru.”
It’s the name…
of the one person I wish to be like.
I’ll give it to you.
Ya…chiru…
I’m Kenpachi.
It’s the name given
to the mightiest Soul Reaper
in every generation.
I will take that name starting today.
I’ve kept you waiting
for such a long time.
You might think,
“What the heck, after all these years,”
but…do you think
you could tell me now…
what your name is?
No good, huh?
I want to get stronger.
I found someone to fight.
I can get stronger. I want to fight!
I want to get stronger!
It’s been a long time…
since I’ve felt like this.
I want to get stronger!
I had no name, and no parents.
Where I was, was North Rukongai,
Area 79, known as Kusajishi.
I have no memory of
seeing anything there,
other than the color of blood.
Everyone around me was closer
to beast than human.
A baby like me could have been
stomped to death at any time.
Then, you came along.
From North Rukongai,
Area 80, Zaraki.
From the very depths of darkness,
you carved up my bloody world
in an instant,
and…you gave me a name.
If you hadn’t appeared,
I would not be here today.
Yes. Since that day,
you have been my entire world.
You can do it, Kenny…
You are the strongest, Kenny!
So, let’s get stronger
and stronger together!
Huh?
Kenny?
Kenny…
Kenny!
The Spiritual Pressure
has finally died down.
Still, it sure was something fierce.
What’s wrong with you?
Your body is trembling.
How pathetic!
W-What?!
You’re the one who’s trembling!
What?! What part of me?
What’s this? Bird droppings?
H-Hey, what’s the matter?!
Huh?!
There you are, damn you…
I won’t let you get away!
Ganju, you overdid it.
That was mean.
Shut up! What about you?!
What was that medicine?
This?
It’s a kind of anesthetic
called “Shinten.”
One drop on the skin of someone
with low Spiritual Pressure
will cause him to get dizzy and pass out.
Y-You’ve got some
scary stuff there, kid.
You think so?
But anyway, let’s hurry.
Oh…?
So the entrance is the shutter type.
Now the question is,
how do we open it?
No problem.
Huh? What do you have this time?
I borrowed a spare key
from the underground water channel
storage room last night.
H-Hey… Is it okay for you to do that?
It’s probably not okay, but…
But I thought about it last night.
Ichigo is getting
all battered up fighting…
while all I do is keep running away.
It looks pretty bad, I thought.
I want to save Rukia, too.
So I decided I’d do all I could
toward that end.
Even if it means
I will be punished later.
Of course, stealing a key
is about all I can do.
That’s why I’m no good.
No. I’d say it’s enough.
Huh?
What you’ve done…
Man, I tell you.
Everybody’s desperate
to save this person.
This Rukia must be quite a cutie…
Well, uh, it’s not that…
You don’t have to get embarrassed.
Let’s see what she really looks like.
Hey, Rukia!
Huh?!
Who are you?
Ichigo’s…comrade?
It’s me, Rukia!
I’m so glad!
You’re all right, aren’t you?
You’re…Hanataro!
Why are you here?
We can talk later.
Ganju, let’s hurry and
get away from here.
Huh? What’s wrong, Ganju?
The pattern on his clothes…
the unraveling eddy from heaven…
Are you…
a member of the Shiba clan?
Huh? Oh, do you know each other?
Yeah.
I know her.
As if I could forget…
that face…
She's…
the Soul Reaper
who killed my brother!
W-What are you saying, Ganju?
Rukia wouldn’t…
My brother’s wounds were from a sword.
His neck was slashed,
and he’d been stabbed in the chest.
If he’d fought with a Hollow,
why did he die of sword wounds?!
And at that time, she told me…
that she had killed him!
Ganju!
That--that can’t be true!
It’s all right, Hanataro.
He is correct.
R-Rukia?
A member of the Shiba clan…
No doubt, it was your elder brother.
Shiba Kaien…was killed by me.
Do as you wish.
If I die by your hand,
I will have no complaints.
What?!
Please stop, Ganju!
We didn’t come here for that,
did we?!
Didn’t we come here to save her?!
Please, Ganju!
Didn’t Ichigo entrust us
with his determination?!
Shut up, will you?!
W-What’s with this Spiritual Pressure?
What?! Aizen’s been killed?!
When? By whom? Why?
This morning, before dawn.
The murderer and motives are, as yet…
unknown!
Why didn’t you awaken me earlier?
Sir! I was concerned about your health,
so I delayed the report.
Please punish me.
That’s not fair, Kotsubaki!
Captain, please punish me, too.
Don’t copy what I say, Kiyone!
I’m not copying you!
That’s enough.
In any case…
I can’t stay here like this.
That’s…Squad Six Captain,
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Byakuya Kuchiki…
H-He’s…
You know him?
Of course.
The Kuchiki clan is one
of the four noble houses
with the highest rank.
That guy’s the current clan leader.
Of the thirteen captains today,
he’s probably the most famous.
This is the worst thing
that could happen…
Someone like him appearing
at a time like this.
It’s no good.
There’s no way we could win.
Maybe we should just beg for our lives.
W-What are you saying, Ganju?!
Let’s run away with Rukia!
You idiot! Do you see any way out?!
This bridge is the only way!
Are you telling me
to risk my life for her?!
She killed my brother, you know!
For someone…
For someone like her?!
I understand.
I guess it can’t be helped.
There was never any reason
for you to save Rukia, to begin with.
It would be asking too much
to force you to stay here.
So, at least when you escape
from here,
please take Rukia with you.
I’ll make a stand here,
and hold him off.
W-What are you talking about?
I think I understand how you feel.
No one would give his life
to save his enemy.
That’s got nothing to do with it!
You felt the Spiritual Pressure,
didn’t you?!
No way can we handle this.
I know that, too.
Still, I came this far because
I wanted to save Rukia.
I can’t just leave
without doing anything!
Thank you for everything you’ve done!
I’ll be on my way.
Don’t do it, Hanataro! You can’t…
What are you doing? Let me through!
That fool!
What does he think he can do
without even a Zanpaku-to?
He’s trembling…
You’re just a weakling.
Don’t go acting so tough!
Dammit!
Hey!
Stay back!
Ganju…
Not…again!
Sorry, Brother.
Avenging you will have to wait.
If you’re gonna blame anyone,
blame Sis for not raising me to be
a coward who would run out on his friends!
Here I come, young ‘un!
I am your opponent!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
The story is finally
reaching a climax.
Maybe it's time for me
to reveal my secret.
Can you guess what my secret is?
You can speak human, but not cat!
You dye your fur black!
You're actually a dog!
Bingo! Listen, you trying to
make a fool of me?!