Ichigo receives serious injuries
in his fight with Ulquiorra.
Then Grimmjow appears,
bringing Orihime with him.
Kurosaki…
Heal him.
Orihime finishes healing Ichigo and,
on equal terms,
the battle between Ichigo
and Grimmjow begins.
Bring it on!
Let's have a fair fight to the death!
That's not good enough.
That's not the side of you
I really want to fight!
Take this!
This is the most powerful Cero,
which only Espada are allowed to use!
Inoue…
Wait, Grimmjow!
Gran Rey Cero!
Sorry…
Are you scared?
It's hard to tell you not to worry
when I look like this.
But I'll tell you anyway.
Don't worry.
I’ll end this soon.
That's good.
I've been waiting for this moment!
Grind…
Pantera!
Inoue…
From here on, place a Santenkesshun
in front of you and Nel.
And make sure never to undo it.
Do it now!
S-Santenkesshun!
I reject!
What's this?
Sound pressure?!
All this power, just from yelling.
Damn it!
What's wrong?
This isn't your best.
Come out!
Getsugatensho!
That's good, Ichigo Kurosaki!
It’s those eyes!
It’s those eyes of yours that I hate!
Look…
The space is still warped.
Gran Rey Cero…
That's not something to be
used within Las Noches.
What, are you scared, Mila Rose?!
Who's scared?!
I can hear your teeth chattering
from here, Apache!
What did you say?!
Well, what of it?!
Stop it, both of you!
When you raise your voice,
you look weak.
– What the hell did you just say, Sun-Sun?!
– Why you stupid…
My, how vulgar.
What?!
Turn this way!
Why you…
Grimmjow is getting carried away.
Don't be bothered by that.
This is a battle with an Espada
in his Resurrección form.
It's no surprise that
you would be scared.
It's a very basic fear.
Embrace it.
Yes.
But…
Is the person he's fighting
really human?
Judging by the quantity, density,
and
darkness of his Spiritual Pressure,
he can't be human.
It's as if…
I'm watching a battle
between two Espada.
I've got you, Ichigo Kurosaki!
It seems you've increased
the amount of time
that you can maintain
that masked state!
Have you trained
since our last battle?
Or have you unconsciously gotten better
during your previous battles?
Either is fine. I'm glad.
It would be boring if
your mask immediately cracked,
just like in our last battle!
It would be boring if my mask broke?
Don't make me laugh!
That's my line, Grimmjow!
You're boring.
So don't undo your sword release!
Is that the best you can do,
Ichigo Kurosaki?!
I-Ichigo…
Kurosaki…
Is that really Kurosaki?
Take this!
Inoue!
I-Ichigo!
Kurosaki…
I'm all right.
This is nothing.
Did you go to save them?
That's quite the effort.
What's wrong?
You're breathing heavily.
If you have time for idle talk,
you should worry about yourself!
Don't act tough.
You already took five hits of that.
It would be strange
if you were still all right.
Your mask is at its limit too.
My limit?
Who's at their limit?
How persistent.
That's how I want it.
You look like you're
getting pretty worn out too.
Sorry.
But you're just imagining it!
I mustn't be afraid.
I mustn't…
…be afraid.
When I remember those eyes,
I feel as if Kurosaki has
become someone else.
I feel as if Kurosaki
can't see me.
Just like my brother.
Kurosaki…
M-Masked Ichigo is being
completely overpowered.
In his fight with Lord Dordoni…
And his fight with Lord Ulquiorra…
When Ichigo put on his mask,
he always won overwhelmingly.
When Ichigo was masked,
he was invincible.
But…
That Ichigo…
is getting so beat up.
G-Give it your all, Ichigo!
Give it your all, Ichigo!
Come on! What are you doing?!
You cheer him on too!
Huh?
Don't “Huh?” Nel!
Ichigo is fighting for you!
So why are you afraid of him?!
You said that Ichigo
was a kind person, right?!
That's right! Nel thinks so too!
Ichigo is kind!
When he heard your name,
he lunged at Lord Ulquiorra!
Ichigo is human!
But he's become a Soul Reaper.
He's put on a mask and
is using such insane power!
There's no way that
he can't be suffering!
He has to be suffering!
But Ichigo is doing this for you!
He's fighting by using that power
and becoming bloodied!
Wh-Why aren't you cheering him on?!
That's right…
At first I came here because
I wanted to protect everyone.
I thought I was ready.
But…
I heard that Kurosaki and
the others came to save me,
and I was happy
somewhere in my heart.
When I saw Kurosaki
wearing a mask,
I saw that his eyes
looked like my brother's
and I became afraid.
I thought that he may not
have come to save me.
That's not true.
That's actually…
None of that really matters.
I…
I'm not afraid of Kurosaki.
What I do fear,
is that Kurosaki…
It looks like you
really are at your limit.
It's over, Kurosaki.
Don't die…
Don't die, Kurosaki!
You don't have to win.
You don't have to try.
Just don't get hurt anymore.
Kurosaki!
Sorry, Grimmjow.
It seems that I…
I can't lose to you any longer.
I don't like it.
The way he takes me for a fool.
Damn… He makes me sick.
I'll destroy you all!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
In the end, we only used up
what little funds we had left.
It'll be all right!
I took pictures of everyone!
What? Really?
Look!
Old man, Hon-Hon, Izurun,
Recchan, Byakki, Bow-Wow,
Shun-Shun, Kenny, and Mayurin!
It's a big success!
BIG SUCCESS
How is this a success?
FINISHED
Huh?! We're finished?!