I found out…
I wasn’t strong…
Nor was I weak…
There was no hatred…
No anger…
Only…
Bankai…eh?
I hope that’s not your way
of saying your Spirit Energy
has fully returned.
Maybe…
Want to find out?
You guys wait here.
Kurosaki…
I’ll finish this in an instant!
Don’t push your luck with
some makeshift Bankai….
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Damn it!
Kon! No!
What’re you saying, Sis?!
We can’t stand here and wait!
Kon…
At times like this, we should
be fighting together!
How much rest do you guys need?!
You’ve rested enough!
You don’t know when
to shut up, do you?
All right! Let’s go!
Wait!
Sis!
If you insist on going…
We’ll all go together!
Guys…
Somenomai, Tsukishiro!
You people never learn!
Stop making trouble!
You’re the one causing trouble!
El Directo!
Damn it…
Hado 73: Soren Sokatsui!
Huh?!
Getsuga…
Tensho!
He’s unable to absorb
Kurosaki’s Getsuga!
As we suspected, Kageroza is
unable to harness Hollow powers!
It’s more powerful…
Wondering why my Getsugatensho
is more powerful now?
Somewhere in my mind,
I was afraid of losing my Spirit Energy.
But I finally realized
it once I lost my powers.
Realized what?
That I can’t stand the thought
of regretting without
giving my best shot.
I will defeat you with
everything I’ve got!
I admit that you are different
compared to when we last fought.
However…
It hardly matters.
Is he manipulating space again?!
At this rate,
capturing Kageroza will be difficult,
much less saving Nozomi.
Is there some way to save Kujo?
Soul Chain and Soul Sleep…
The two vital points of a soul, if
we can shatter his Soul Chain…
I get it…
If we stop the flow of Spirit
Energy within his body,
there’s a chance that he
will split back into two.
But…
The Soul Chain, right?
Kon?!
Kon?
I’ll go tell Ichigo!
Is that the best you
can do with the help
of your so-called friends?
Or has your Spirit Energy
completely run out?
I thought I told you…
As long as I can save Nozomi…
and protect my friends,
then it doesn’t matter!
In that case,
I’ll end it quickly for you!
The strap!
This is what I was waiting for…
What?!
Huh?!
Let go of me!
Damn you!
Let go!
Take this!
Do it!
Getsuga…
Tensho!
Did we win?
Damn you… Damn you…
Don’t.
What’s…
happening to my body?
My head!
Damn it!
Ichigo…
Nozomi?!
Finish us.
This is our only chance!
Please!
Ichigo!
The Soul Chain!
Shatter his Soul Chain!
Go! Ichi...
What?!
Damn you…
Stop fighting a futile battle.
You’ve lost.
You think…I’ve lost?!
I’ll show you if it’s futile or not!
If I’m going to lose this body,
I will destroy everything!
Renzan: Hajokuri!
What?!
Hey!
What the hell is that?!
I don’t know!
What the hell?
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
It’s unbelievable.
He still had this much power left?
No, this Spiritual Pressure is the
Reishi of the Soul Society itself.
He’s absorbing it?!
What is that?
How are we supposed to deal with
that kind of Spiritual Pressure?
This wasn’t part of the plan…
Things are getting interesting!
It would appear you guys weren’t
expecting this either.
This Spiritual Pressure is insane.
So much force with
just a single blast…
What should we do now?
It’s growing bigger and bigger.
I think we’re in trouble.
Damn it. We have to act fast.
Oh, crap!
Danku.
Old Man Yama!
Kageroza Inaba’s, or should I say…
Ouko Yushima’s every scheme is spurred
by vengeance against the Soul Society.
He intends to destroy the
Soul Society along with himself.
Damn it!
Never did I dream the
end would be like this.
But, so be it.
Come with me, Ichigo Kurosaki…
to that place between
chaos and nothingness.
It’s getting bigger!
It’s up to us to stop it.
Wait.
Reigai!
You people…
Going for an all-out attack?
That’s not it.
Do you recall, Master Genryusai?
Certainly, to the real ones,
what we’re doing might seem like
a simple rebellion by imposters.
But we Reigai have our way
of following through
with what we believe.
And what is that?
We cannot tell you just yet.
The time has come for you
to understand the
meaning of those words.
What?
You claim that what you protect
is very clear to you—
and it is for us, as well.
We will protect the Soul
Society in our own way.
It is the duty of us Mod Souls to stop
a fellow Mod Soul who
has gone out of control.
Let’s go!
What?!
They’re…
Oh well!
Damn them!
You’re not stopping me!
Again?!
You’ve done enough…
What’s happening?!
Stop it, Nozomi!
Let’s end this.
Nozomi! What’re you doing?!
Those guys…
Looks like they had pride, as well.
Is everyone okay?
Yeah, just barely…
Ichigo…
Looks like your invasion force
didn’t work out the way you planned.
Now all that’s left
is to rescue Nozomi.
Why?!
Why can’t I defeat you?!
Why?
Why can’t I defeat you?
What drives you this far?
Damn…
you!
You have something to protect, don't you?!
You have friends!
To be there for!
To shield!
To be close to!
Only the weak would seek
the aid of others…
So why…
Why are you so strong?!
We found out.
We weren’t strong,
nor were we weak.
There was no hatred.
No anger.
Only that we were alone.
Nozomi…
Were we…mistaken?
I don’t know.
I see…
Nozomi!
Are you all right?
Kon…
Yes, I’m all right.
Your right arm.
Oh, this?
This is nothing.
Well, all’s good now, right?
You’re right.
C’mon, let’s go back to the
World of the Living, Nozomi!
You’re…
Nozomi…
Forgive me, Ichigo.
This was the only way.
Ichigo, what’s going on?
Kon…
This is as it should be.
What’re you talking about, Nozomi?!
There’s nothing good about it!
At the very end, I told him…
This time, I would be his friend.
Friend?
I learned what it meant
to have friends.
Now it’s my turn to teach him…
Don’t say that!
It’s like you’re going
to disappear forever!
I won’t let you do this!
Thank you for this, Kon.
I…couldn’t protect you, huh?
That’s not true.
You did protect me.
We were alone.
But we’re at peace now.
It’s because all of you…
Because Ichigo, and you were there, Kon.
Yeah, I’m there for you!
I’ll always be there for you! So…
All this time, I couldn’t
hear it…but now I can.
The voice of my soul deep inside me…
Can you hear it, Kon?
I can’t hear deep inside of you…
But…
If you let me put my ear to your
breast, I’d be willing to try.
You really are a pervert,
you know that?!
Well pardon me!
Don’t forget us…
I won’t…
After all, we’ll always be…
Friends…forever…
Hey, there’s something I want to say
before we head back to
the World of the Living.
Oh yeah? Go for it.
Let it all out while you can.
Bankai!
Bankai, Bankai, Bankai,
Bankai, Bankai, Bankai!
What the hell was that about?!
I’m stacking up on
my call outs since I
won’t be able to do them for a while.
Ichigo.
Ukitake!
Let me return this to you.
You dropped it in the Precipice
World, didn’t you?
Oh…
You saved us again.
Thank you.
Don’t mention it.
I have one for you, too.
No thanks!
I have something a lot better!
Okay, let’s all head back
to the World of the Living!
-Right.
-Right!