Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
I sense some faint
spiritual pressure.
Let's split up and find it.
– Okay!
Leave it to me!
Hey! Can you handle
this on your own?
Don't treat me like a kid!
I found one!
You're a sword beast,
aren't you?
Don't move!
NARUNOSUKE
This is weird!
I mean… he's a Zanpakuto.
Well, I'm a Zanpakuto too, but…
No, I like older men.
I don't like wimpy-looking guys
who are clearly younger than me.
I couldn't care less about him.
I prefer slightly chubby older guys
to string beans like him.
But…
This is bad!
Sparks are flying!
Damn it!
Are you all right?
This is weird.
I like gutsy, testosterone-driven,
manly men.
Not weak and
pathetic guys like him.
Sorry, but a sword beast
is a sword beast!
I need to get rid of you!
Don't look at me like that!
He's triggering
my maternal instincts!
I guess I have no choice.
How are things on your side?
I'm finished.
My side is fine.
Well? Did you find him?
Yeah.
You dealt with him, right?
Yeah…
Hey, Rangiku…
What is it?
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing!
There's nothing
out of the ordinary! Yeah!
Hey… Hey…
Matsumoto!
Oh, Captain…
What are you doing?
Never mind that!
You're slacking off again!
That's because I was going to
eat the manju I had been saving,
but it disappeared!
You ate it, didn't you?
Why would I do that?!
Besides…don't hide manju!
Hyorinmaru, get me some tea!
You must think my Zanpakuto
is your housekeeper, or something.
That aside, we still aren't done
eliminating all of
the sword beasts.
Don't let your guard down!
Okay…
By the way, where is Haineko?
Who knows?
Probably loafing
around somewhere.
Is this really okay?
I don't belong to an organization
like the Soul Reapers…
But still…
Hey! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Tadah!
There we go!
Thank you very much.
Umm… Why are you doing this?
Why?
Aren't I an enemy you
should be chasing down?
So why did you treat my wounds?
I'm not petty enough to attack
an injured opponent.
Besides…
unlike the other sword beasts,
you're not aggressive at all.
It's no big deal!
I'm just saying anything.
Well, whatever!
He seems perfectly normal!
You're a sword beast,
aren't you?
That's the name
you all have given me.
I'm just a regular Zanpakuto
who has lost his master.
My master was
a cowardly Soul Reaper.
Unfortunately, I'm just like him.
In order to survive,
I needed to protect myself.
I needed to become stronger.
I tried to become friends
with the other sword beasts…
But in the end,
I ended up being hunted down.
That's why I'm hiding like this.
Your injuries are still pretty bad.
You should rest!
Sorry.
W-What?
Is there something on my face?
You're different from the other
Zanpakuto and the Soul Reapers.
You think so?
All right!
Then I'll do something
about your situation!
Huh?
You don't seem dangerous at all.
I'll ask the others to treat you
like a regular Zanpakuto
instead of a sword beast!
DON'T EAT!
RANGIKU'S
Can you do that?!
Leave it to me!
What's your name?
I'm Narunosuke.
I'm Haineko!
Ms. Haineko, huh?
Stop that!
You make me sound old.
Then Big Sister Haineko.
That makes me
sound even older!
That's impossible.
Huh?
We don't know when Zanpakuto
who've lost their owners
will go out of control.
They're dangerous.
We have to deal with all
of them in the same way.
But there may be sword beasts
who aren't dangerous!
I wish that were true.
But we know from
Squad 12's research
that while each
sword beast is different,
there is a high possibility
that they will eventually
lose their minds and
go out of control.
Our job is to stop them before
something terrible happens.
So why are you asking me this?
Did you find a new sword beast?
No! It's nothing!
I was just curious!
See you later!
A Soul Reaper would dispose
of even a kid like him…
I can't mention him to them!
But she mentioned
that sword beasts
have a high possibility
of losing their minds…
Does that mean there are
sword beasts who haven't?!
That's right! He's different!
He said he was
a regular Zanpakuto
who had lost his master.
If I explain things to Rangiku,
I'm sure she'll understand!
You like younger guys?
No way. Gross.
That might be a problem.
Oh, Haineko!
How do you do?
Anyway, I've got to do
something about it myself!
Is it good?
Yes! Very!
I can't imagine a kid like him
going out of control.
He's definitely not a sword beast!
He's a regular Zanpakuto!
I'm going to eat with you!
By the way, am I still going to
be treated as a sword beast?
Did you talk to
someone about that?
O-Oh! That!
I asked my Soul Reaper
about that!
She said she would talk
to her superiors about it.
It seems they're kind of
busy right now,
so it might take some time!
I see.
A-Anyway,
about my Soul Reaper…
She's an odd woman!
She's not a bad person, but she
did something funny recently…
That's so amusing!
Isn't it?!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah…
You still haven't
healed up completely…
You should rest a little more.
Thank you, Miss Haineko
When I'm with you, I feel relaxed.
R-Really?
I wonder what happened to her.
Who knows?
I'm back!
What? What's wrong?!
Don't you think it's
wonderful to be alive?
Don't you, dear Rangiku?!
D-Dear Rangiku?
What?
They're becoming
more frequent!
Hello!
I brought lunch again!
I brought a little sake too!
You can drink, right?
Your wounds should be better now,
so have a drink with me.
Miss Haineko …
Sorry. I still can't have
fun like you can.
Huh?
How am I going to be dealt with?
You told me that
you would handle it!
Were you lying?
No… Um…
To tell you the truth…
I see…
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
A sword beast is
just a sword beast.
My situation has not changed,
but it cannot be helped.
Where are you going?!
If I stay here, Soul Reapers
will come after me again.
I need to escape
before that happens.
It's impossible!
Not in the state you're in.
My wounds have healed.
Thanks to you. I'm grateful.
Not yet!
Besides…
Are you all right?!
Narunosuke!
This is…
But we know from
Squad 12's research
that while each
sword beast is different,
there is a high possibility
that they will
eventually lose their minds
and go out of control.
I'm all right now.
I get headaches sometimes.
And my hands start to
do things on their own.
Lately, I've been worrying that
they've become more frequent.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That aside,
you need to stay here until you
no longer have those headaches.
You're very kind.
Our supplies?
That's right.
We've been missing
a lot of things lately.
Someone is taking medicine
and food from the barracks.
Do you know who it might be?
No.
But there may be sword beasts
who aren't dangerous!
What's wrong?
You noticed?
Of course I did.
Where were you?
Just hanging around.
So what did you want?
Umm… Well…
By the way, did you know
that someone's been
stealing medicine and food
from our barracks?
What? I had no idea.
Yeah. Honestly, it's disturbing.
Never mind.
It's nothing!
What am I going to do?
At this rate…
What's going to happen?!
Well…
You'll be okay.
You just need some rest!
You're lying!
What's going to happen to me?
Narunosuke!
Are you all right?
Hang in there!
What's happening to me?
You're becoming a sword beast.
Rangiku!
I thought it was strange.
It all makes sense now.
You followed me?
Why didn't you tell me
about this earlier?
Why did you hide this?
Please try to understand
my position here.
I'm a lieutenant.
And you're my Zanpakuto.
Anyway…
Get away from that sword beast!
Wait! He's not a sword beast!
He's suffering!
He'll go beyond suffering.
He'll lose his mind
and go out of control.
That's what happens
to sword beasts!
I'm going to become
a sword beast?!
No! There has to be
a way to save him!
There isn't.
No way!
Miss Haineko…
Please save me…
Get out of the way, Haineko!
I'm getting rid of him
for his own good!
I can't!
I'm going to save him!
Why won't you understand?!
If you want to kill him,
then consider me a sword beast
and get rid of me too!
It seems I can't reason with you.
– Growl…
Haineko!
I have no choice!
I have to restrain
Haineko with bakudo!
Stop! Narunosuke!
Rangiku!
Haineko?
Growl…
Stop, Haineko!
I'm sorry I couldn't
keep my promise.
Miss Haineko…
Narunosuke…
Thank you, Miss Haineko…
Narunosuke!
I was in love with him.
I couldn't tell him.
I know.
Are you all right?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
You're making fun of me,
aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I think you're foolish, though.
I think I still like younger guys.
Why?
Even if I grow old,
it's never too late.
Oh, you…
Hey, Captain, should we
give something to Haineko
to help her soothe
her broken heart?
Oh, yeah. Perhaps…
Right?
Alcohol and shopping is always
good for a broken heart.
But I'm worried about
Haineko going off on her own,
so I'm going with her.
This is all for Haineko!
Matsumoto!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Anyway, Ishida, I want you
to make some cool clothes
that'll make Lieutenant Sasakibe
really stand out!
Why me?!
That cape…
That was popular in England!
Oh, you know about it?
Of course!
I don't think you
should go with that.
– Wow…
– Oh?
Lieutenant Sasakibe!
That really looks good on you!
I incorporated a lot of
19th century English designs
into it!
Is that really okay?
TO BE CONTINUED