Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends have
marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars' hideout.
But Sado is defeated by Nnoitora,
and Rukia reaches a draw with
Aaroniero and runs out of strength.
As the situation gets worse,
Ichigo hurries to Rukia,
but he is blocked by Ulquiorra.
So Inoue really didn't go to
Hueco Mundo of her own free will!
I'm going to go at full strength!
Bankai!
Upon learning that
Ulquiorra was responsible
for taking Orihime
to Hueco Mundo,
Ichigo challenges him to a battle.
But Ulquiorra releases
a powerful Cero.
Ichigo is hit and
receives crushing injuries.
Was that your best?
What?
You're the leader of the Espada,
aren't you?
That means that if I defeat you,
this battle is pretty much won!
I see…
That's unfortunate.
Wha—?!
Four?!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you do defeat me,
there are three Espada above me.
You can try a thousand times.
You will not be victorious.
It’s a lie!
Kuchiki and now Kurosaki?
That can't be!
Ul…
Orihime…
Let's play.
Meanwhile,
Octava Espada Szayelaporro
has sealed away Renji's Bankai.
Renji is thrust about by attacks
from Szayelaporro's Fracciónes.
What's wrong?
You look like you've taken
quite a beating, Renji Abarai!
You're…
Ishida!
I'm sorry.
You looked like
you wanted to go outside,
so I tried to open
the door for you.
It looks like I used too much force.
Oh? Do you want to say something?
If you have something to say,
then say it.
We'll listen to you.
If you have no business here,
then please leave.
Who do you think you are?
Menoly!
Honestly…
Lately her Cero has been acting up.
Says the Cero comes out
without her noticing.
If you don't be careful,
she might hit you by mistake.
Unlike that Bala just now,
it might kill you.
What's wrong? Say something.
I serve Lord Aizen and his desires.
Don't talk about Lord Aizen!
Don't get cocky just because
he talked to you directly!
What's with that look?
Stand up!
Stop!
Why you…
How pathetic!
You can't win against an Arrancar
with human strength!
Why you…
What's with that expression?!
I'll make you unable
to go before Lord Aizen!
Loly!
Just leave it at that!
If we go too far…
Shut up!
If you don't want to do this
then you don't have to!
Hey, Loly!
What?!
G…
Grimmjow!
Hey.
You seem to be having fun sneaking
in here while Ulquiorra's not around.
What of it?!
How did you get in?!
How? Through the wall, of course.
Wh-What kind of joke is that?!
Why not?
I don't know who did it,
but the entrance was broken already!
Why you…
Cut it out!
Out of the way.
Oh? Did I use too much force?
Grimmjow!
Menoly!
How dangerous.
Be careful of how you use your Cero.
L-Lord Aizen won't let you
get away with doing this to us.
Hey… Wh-What is it?!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Don't come near me! No! No!
Boom!
Idiot.
Lord Aizen should kill you!
Kill you! Kill you!
You idiot.
Aizen would never do anything
for the likes of you.
Wh-Why?
This is in return for my left arm.
Huh?
What?
What am I doing?
Did you think I came here
just to save you?
How naïve.
I returned your favor.
Now you can't complain.
Now I want you to help me.
Medazepi!
Medazepi killed!
– Killed, killed!
– Him! Killed by him!
There are quite a number of them.
I'm not sure how strong
they are individually.
Uryu! Hey, Uryu!
H-How are they reacting?
Are they trembling in fear
at your sudden appearance?
Could you stay out of this, please?!
Whenever you appear,
you kill the tension!
Wh-What? How rude!
I always act with
a sense of pee retention!
Oh, I mean “sense of tension.”
Shut up!
Our guest wants to say something.
Let's listen to what he has to say.
Thank you for your consideration.
Sorry this is sudden,
but I want to know.
Are you the Espada?
How very perceptive!
I am indeed Octava Espada,
Szayelaporro Grantz.
Number eight, huh?
I'm relieved.
You're not a very strong number.
Yes, well…
Don't worry.
I'm still stronger than you.
By the way…
Who are you?
Uryu Ishida… I'm a Quincy.
A Quincy…
You're that rare creature
that fought that stupid woman!
A Bankai-user and a Quincy!
I am lucky!
Yammy would probably
yell out “suerte”!
You're right.
I don't know about this Yammy…
But I get to fight someone like you,
who has a lot of openings.
I'd like to yell out “suerte.”
But I get to fight someone like you,
who has a lot of openings.
I'd like to yell out “suerte.”
– Lord Szayelaporro!
What?
You fool! Did you think that
your arrow went through me?!
That it pierced me
and went through me?!
Is that what you thought?
Didn't you think it was strange that
I knew who you had fought?!
I've already analyzed
all of your abilities, Quincy!
I…
How?
It was her.
She did it.
Fix your face.
Fix it right now.
Hey!
Wh-What are you doing?
Shuno! Ayame!
What are you doing?!
Huh?
You're kidding, right?
What's the deal with her?
What is it?
She's…
She's…a monster!
My arrow’s power is weak?
Why you…
That thing earlier…
What?
Crap!
Hmm… I think I need to adjust it a bit.
Now how about this?
Aww man… What is Uryu doing?!
You should be able to defeat them
more easily with your arrows!
Uryu!
Th-That was close.
He worried me.
It's useless.
Why you…
Look… That's going to disappear too.
Damn!
Abarai!
Don't stand around doing nothing!
You can still fight, can't you?!
Finding weaknesses is your forte!
His tricks…
Isn't there anything
you can do about them?!
Don't be silly.
I have something!
All right… I believe you!
Don't shoot poorly!
That's no problem.
As long as you’re
not the one shooting!
What should we do, Abarai?
I'm just going to hit him
with my Spiritual Pressure.
You can't mean…
A double suicide, huh?!
I see. You thought this out!
No! Stop acting stupid!
Oh no… I couldn't help myself.
Let's do our best as a stand-up trio!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Since you don't know Lady Yoruichi,
I shall describe her features!
LADY YORUICHI
SEARCH COMMITTEE
She has long, tanned arms
and legs with lovely muscles.
She has beautiful back hair and
big slanted eyes that shine like the sun.
Her body is covered in black fur.
Her big ears and
long whiskers always
– gallantly point towards the heavens.
– How do we catch
someone like that?!
Also…
If you catch her by her tail there's
a high possibility that she'll freak out.
So be careful, or else.
She'll kill you.
She's a monster!