Kibune had come into possession
of the Kasumiohji Clan's Bakkouto
in order to attain the power to
become the strongest Soul Reaper.
Lieutenant Kira put everything he
had on the line to challenge Kibune,
who only believed in power.
After an intense battle,
Kira was finally able to defeat Kifune,
who had shown his true colors.
Meanwhile, Ichigo and his friends
entered the Kasumiohji mansion
in order to rescue Rurichiyo.
They battled against
Hitsugaya and Squad 10.
Go, Kurosaki!
Leave this place to me!
Thanks!
Let's go, Shu!
Reign over the frosted heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Sever, Raika!
Around the same time, having obtained
Kibune's Bakkouto as proof of treason,
Genryusai finally gave out the order
to put down the Kasumiohji Clan.
Notice!
It has come to light that there were
suspicious acts of high treason
found against
the Kasumiohji Clan.
All squads of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
will enter the Kasumiohji mansion
immediately and secure this evidence!
You ruffian!
Sorry!
Shu… Do you know
where Rurichiyo is?
Maybe…the one in the back.
Kumoi didn't allow us
to go near there!
Okay, which way?!
That way!
Rurichiyo, where are you?
For generations, the Kasumiohji Clan
has forged and delivered
heirloom swords to the royal families
that were used for ceremonial purposes.
The techniques they use
were kept strictly in-house.
For that reason, they have maintained
the right of immunity for a long time.
However, certain factions
within the Kasumiohji Clan
have taken advantage of
the fact that we cannot
easily interfere with them,
and went off to break the
taboo of producing a
dangerous blade such as this.
Now that we know this with certainty,
it is only natural that we make our move.
Head Captain, did you expect this outcome
when the Substitute Soul Reaper…
I'm assigning Captain Kuchiki
of Squad 6 to lead the raid.
Yes, sir!
Reporting, sir!
Head Captain Yamamoto
has changed his orders!
He has ordered all Thirteen Court
Guard Squads to take control of our clan!
What?!
Damn!
That bastard.
What happened to,
"That will never happen"?!
"I guarantee your safety,"
he said.
That was the reason why I
went along with his plan,
even at great risk.
Now I have no choice
but to use these.
What? A change of orders?!
Yes! Our orders are to
seize the Kasumiohji Clan.
What's going on?
That's the complete opposite!
I do not have any details yet.
It would seem we don't
have to fight any further.
Lieutenant Matsumoto!
Who are they?!
They're Kasumiohji Clan
assassins!
What's this?!
These men are using
a blade called the Bakkouto!
Bakkouto?
This is the Kasumiohji Clan's
dark secret.
I see.
So we don't need
to hold back, right?
Growl, Haineko!
What is it with them?!
Don't they feel any pain?
Shuhei!
Head Captain has given
the order to raid this place!
The Kasumiohji Clan is
suspected of treason.
His orders are to assist
the Substitute Soul Reaper!
Which one of you is next?
They seem to be using
quite unusual swords.
They're not beautiful.
Those things won't
make you a match for us.
Don't let the other
squads out do you!
Show them the pride of Squad 7!
Looks like they made it in time.
Captain Hitsugaya…
Evidence of forbidden techniques
connected with treason
have been found within
the Kasumiohji Clan.
Our orders are to
take control immediately.
What?
I'm glad things didn't drag on
any further, Captain Hitsugaya!
Hey, wait!
Rurichiyo!
Damn it!
How far does this continue?!
It is a huge mansion.
We'll just have to keep
going as far as we can!
What the heck?!
Ichigo!
Stand back!
What?!
Are you serious?!
You mean their swords are all Bakkoutos?!
Their souls have been
taken over by their swords.
Ichigo!
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
Rukia!
Ichigo! Renji did it!
The order was given to raid
the Kasumiohji Clan!
Is that true?
Yes!
Which means that bastard Kumoi
decided to bring out his secret weapon.
Yes. Who'd have imagined they'd
produce so many Bakkoutos.
Rukia… Take Shu
and go on ahead!
The intense security means
that there's something
important up ahead, right?
Got it! I'll leave this place to you!
Go, Rukia!
You bastards!
I'll take you on all at once!
Something seems
to have started.
Ichigo Kurosaki and the others
might have done it.
Yes.
We'll use this commotion
to rescue Lady Rurichiyo.
You must've sensed it as well.
Rurichiyo's presence.
Man…
What is up with these guys?!
And the ugly way they fight…
Can't something
be done about it?
The way they fight…
It's like throwing away their lives.
Or more precisely,
they have lost their souls.
So this must be the power of
those swords called the Bakkouto.
But they're wrong to think they can
stop us with something like that!
Captain! What's happening?
Exactly what it looks like.
It seems this was all part of
the Head Captain's plan.
The Head Captain's?!
The Kasumiohji Clan is an aristocracy
with a special status.
No one can interfere with them except
under extraordinary circumstances.
The Head Captain already had
his hands on information
that the Kasumiohji Clan
was up to no good.
By sheer coincidence,
Kurosaki became involved,
so he used him.
That's…
It shows just how much
he trusted in their abilities.
He's a wily old fox.
S-Sir Kumoi?
Why are you dressed like that?
Silence! Don't leave your posts!
Reporting!
Both the main gate and building have
been occupied by the Soul Reapers!
Fighting is still going on
in the garden, but we cannot
hold them much longer.
I know that!
All I need is for them
to buy me some time.
Just until I can get inside
the Bakkouto workshop.
Once I'm there…
Sir Kumoi!
The Soul Reapers are
in the Bakkouto workshop!
What?!
That can't be!
The barrier there was bestowed
on us by a royal family.
It can't be broken by
the likes of the Soul Reapers.
Charge!
I am Jushiro Ukitake, Squad 13 Captain
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
We will now conduct
an inspection of the premises!
I want everyone to remain
where you are.
You can't get away
this way, either.
Thank you.
All right, start talking.
Soi Fon!
Good work. That was a wonderful job
of breaking through the barrier.
Yes, ma'am!
But…the barrier around the workshop
was an extraordinary one.
Where did you learn how to break through
such a powerful barrier, Lady Yoruichi?
From a man who was angry
with the Kasumiohji Clan
for interfering with his business.
Curse those Soul Reapers!
Sir Kumoi,
we have nowhere else to run.
I know that!
The princess!
Bring Rurichiyo to me!
Since it's come to this,
our only choice is to use her as a shield!
They're…
Hey you guys!
You'll die if you keep this up!
Damn!
We've reached a dead end.
How can that be?
I thought this way was
the most suspicious.
That's…
These people are
Ruricchi's attendants.
Lord Shu!
Suspicious men have
taken Lady Rurichiyo!
So Ruricchi was here after all!
Yes. She returned a while ago
and was locked up in here.
We were told to look after her here,
and stayed with her.
And so, where is she now?
The man standing guard
opened that wall.
A hidden passageway!
Looks like it goes up.
Okay, let's hurry!
Sir Kumoi?
Where were you until now, sir?
Well…I had many things
to look into.
This is no time for that!
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
have stormed the mansion!
They have already taken control of
much of the mansion!
Is that so?
We must have you explain to them
by going to the front lines, Sir Kumoi.
No, that would be a problem.
What do you mean, "a problem"?!
Sir Kumoi…
Do you think we are not aware
of what you are doing behind our backs?!
– Lady Rturichiyo!
– Lady Rurichiyo!
What is the meaning of this,
Sir Kumoi?!
What have you done
to Lady Rurichiyo?!
– Sir Kumoi!
What have you done?
Take care of them.
Yes, sir!
Why did you kill the vassals?
Quiet!
I am the princess of this clan!
Do you think you can go unpunished
for killing my vassals?
Shut up!
This clan belongs to me now!
You're nothing more than
a mere hostage!
Don't get cocky with me!
What am I a hostage for?!
Who is it that you are afraid of?
Tell me!
Quiet!
For what purpose
am I being treated like this?
Explain!
Don't you ever stop talking?!
Come!
Ichigo!
Rukia! Shu!
Rurichiyo is close by!
What?!
So she was here after all!
Yes!
She climbed up here
via a shortcut!
Which means…
There!
Rurichiyo!
That hurts!
Put me down more gently!
Shut up!
You should be thankful
that I'm allowing you to live!
I am a mere hostage!
I cannot judge what
I should be thankful for!
Then shall I give you
a little lesson?
That's as far as you go!
Who said that?!
Ichigo!
Sorry to make you wait,
Rurichiyo.
Ichigo…
You are late.
What in heaven's name
took you so long?
I was getting tired of waiting.
Yeah…sorry.
I'll rescue you now.
Kill him!
Not a chance!
Damn…
I'm taking Rurichiyo back!
Curse you.
– Lady Rurichiyo!
– Ruricchi!
Miss Kuchiki! And Sir Shu too!
Don't move!
You bastard!
Ruricchi!
Come near me, and she dies!
No…
Damn!
Gyokaku Kumoi!
What is your objective?
Why did you create a weapon
like the Bakkouto?
That's none of your business!
He is planning to use the Bakkouto
to disrupt Soul Society
and grab power as the leader
of the noble family.
Shut up!
You bastard. You did this
to Rurichiyo just for that?
Eliminate the opposition.
That is one of the conditions for victory!
Unforgivable!
I don't need your forgiveness,
you idiot!
You're the idiot!
Leader of the noble family?
Absurd!
Even if it means a short life,
I want to stand on top of the world!
For that purpose,
I will do anything it takes!
Ruricchi!
Don't do it!
Amagai…
I'm surprised you found this place.
Yeah.
Captain Amagai, this guy seems to
be the mastermind of this incident.
It would seem so.
Captain Amagai?
Ichigo!
Amagai…
Why?
I wonder why.
Now that you've killed the mastermind,
we'll never know the truth!
The truth, you say?
W-What's going on?
What did you just do?
You did a good job…
Substitute Soul Reaper.
What's that…
supposed to mean?
Ichigo!
Rurichiyo!
See you.
What in the world just happened?
Why?
I did everything just as you said.
So why is it only me that's…
Could it be?
Kumoi and Captain Amagai?!
That couldn't be.
Damn!
What the hell is going on?!
Out past the fields laid darkness.
A life fading away.
Feelings left behind.
Many years have
passed since then.
And I have come back
to this place.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Golden!
What's with these guests' faces?
I can't get through this.
I came to eat snackies.
Thank you!
Come again.
What?!