Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
You're mine!
Not deep enough!
That thing's face…
It was Inoue's brother.
But why would Inoue's brother
come after me…?
I don't know.
But judging from the Hollow that
attacked you last time,
it seems a powerful Hollow
who remains in the dark
wants to devour
your spiritual power.
And it probably controls
several Hollows.
Then Inoue's brother's appearance
would make sense.
No way! So, what should I do?!
I can't kill Inoue's brother?!
Think! If you don't kill him,
he will wander around forever!
And there's no doubt that
he will attack you again.
Wait, we may not have time
to worry about him!
What do you mean?
That girl is in danger!
Wasn't that delicious?
Yeah. How about
some dessert now?
I have some leeks and
bean jam jelly.
What?
They go great together.
I'm not too keen for that.
Huh? What was that?
Oh…poor Enraku!
This is terrible.
How come you're all torn up?
What's that?!
The Hollows target their own kin?!
It happens frequently.
What do you mean?
Hollows are fallen souls.
Souls that were not guided into
the Soul Society by a Soul Reaper.
Souls that were not protected
by Hollows.
They lose their hearts and
become Hollows themselves.
Now that this Hollow has
failed to devour you,
he will go after the soul of
the one he loved most in his life.
Remember the bruise
on Inoue's leg today?
That was the mark left by a Hollow.
Then that accident was
Inoue's brother's doing?
Perhaps.
What is this?
O-Orihime!
What is this?!
How come there's blood?!
W-What is that?!
W-What is that?
What's happening?
What is that ghostly thing?
Is that…
me? Why?
What is this chain?
I can't breathe…
Tatsuki!
What am I doing here in a daze?!
Take that!
Tatsuki! Tatsuki!
Stay away!
Tatsuki! What's wrong?
Tatsuki!
It's useless, Orihime.
She can't hear us,
let alone see us.
Tatsuki!
How…How do you
know my name?
How sad, Orihime…
Have you forgotten my voice?
It's me…can't you tell?
Stay away!
How sad…
I'm so sad! So sad!
Aren't I the one you're after?!
Dammit! Tatsuki, you got
caught up in this?
Kurosaki?
It IS you! But why?
Inoue… Say, how come
you can see me?
Huh… Well…
Soul Reapers are spiritual beings.
Only other spiritual beings can see you.
It's impossible for
ordinary people to see you.
Spiritual being…?
That's right.
In other words, she's a spirit.
Orihime is dead!
Dammit!
Don't move!
Ichigo!
Hey, Ichigo!
Hang on, Ichigo! Ichigo!
Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
Let go! Let go!
Kurosaki is hurt! Let go!
Orihime…
Have you forgotten me?
Brother…?
Ichigo! Wake up, Ichigo!
Will you shut up?!
Is that any way to talk?
Where were you hit?
Forget it. I'm okay.
Really? Good.
Don't forget.
He may have been Inoue's
older brother, but he's a monster.
He doesn't have a human heart.
Kill him without fail.
Are you really my brother?
Yes, I am, Orihime.
You're lying. My brother would
never do what you're doing.
I was lonely.
Huh?
You were forgetting
about me…little by little.
After I died,
you prayed for me every day.
I watched you…
It was your prayers
that gave me peace.
But after about a year,
you became friends with that girl.
After that…
you began praying for me
less and less often.
And when you entered high school,
you stopped praying for me altogether.
That's why…I was so lonely…
Brother, you're wrong…!
Listen, Orihime!
If you have even a shred
of feeling left for me,
do not betray me anymore!
Just listen to what I tell you.
It won't take long.
I'll devour that Soul Reaper
and end this quickly!
Wait! Kurosaki has
nothing to do with this!
Please stop, Brother!
Don't hurt him anymore!
Be quiet!
Whose fault do you think it is
that I became this way?!
It's your fault!
You will listen to what I say!
Otherwise…
I'll kill you first!
Stop!
Listen, you…
Do you know why big brothers
are born first?
It's to protect the little brothers
and sisters that follow.
Ichigo!
Yet you're threatening to
kill your own sister?
Don't say that,
even if you are dead!
Shut up! Orihime is mine!
I raised her when our parents
abandoned us!
It was when Orihime was three…
I've protected her ever since!
Orihime!
Come to me! If you listen to me,
I won't lay a hand on the others.
Wait, it's a trap!
He no longer has
the feelings of a brother.
But…
Entrance Ceremony
Brother!
What's happening?!
Orihime is…mine!
As if! Inoue is Inoue!
She doesn't belong…to anyone!
Why are you hesitating!
Finish him!
Inoue…
Ori…hime…
I'm sorry, Brother.
It's my fault. It's all because
I begged you not to leave me alone.
Brother! Please don't die!
Please don't leave me alone!
That's why you couldn't…rest in peace.
Orihime…
I sensed that you were
always beside me.
Even yesterday,
when that car almost hit me…
You protected me, right?
You pulled my leg to
get me out of the way.
So that's why...
But if I keep depending on you,
you'll never be able to rest.
So I wanted to show you…
I'm happy.
You don't have to worry about me.
But that made you lonely…and sad…
That's not it!
What's going on?
He's fighting the Hollow inside him.
He didn't become
a Hollow by choice.
He probably was taken over
by a Hollow.…
Why?
Don't you get it?
His target was supposed
to be you.
A soul that is devoured by
a strong Hollow
is manipulated by that Hollow.
In other words, a Hollow who is
after you took over a soul
whom you would hesitate to fight,
and forced him to attack.
Right now, he is desperately
fighting that Hollow.
For his sister's sake…
Orihime!
Ori…
Inoue!
Stay calm!
The chain attached to her chest,
the Chain of Fate, is still connected.
As long as it is connected,
she will not die.
I need to treat her. Get back.
I can use my Kido to save her.
You gave that to her
as a present, didn't you?
Inoue said so…
That's why she wears
it every day.
Hey!
Even if I stay here like this,
eventually I'll revert to being a monster.
So now…while I still have
a semblance of sanity…
I want to disappear.
Hey! Hey wait…!
Ichigo!
He's making the right decision.
Once you become a Hollow,
you can never go back to what you were.
Let him pass on.
Rukia!
It's all right. Reaping a Hollow
is not really killing it.
You're cleansing its soul and
allowing it to enter the Soul Society.
That is why we
Soul Reapers exist.
Wait, Brother…
This hairpin that you
bought me that day…
We had a fight over it, remember?
Because I said it was too childish.
I let you go to work
without saying anything…
That was the last time
I would see you alive.
So, I want to say it now…
Brother, have a nice day.
Yeah, I'm off now.
It's true!
A sumo champion
really came to my room…
and blasted a hole with a gun!
Huh?
Not again! Can't you make
it sound more realistic?
At least, say a pro wrestler came
and caused a brawl outside.
Well, I like Hime's silly imagination.
I'm saying it's true! Right, Tatsuki?
Uh…yeah.
Huh? Tatsuki, don't tell me you agree.
So is that what you did yesterday?
Yes.
Kurosaki, what is this…?
Inoue?!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Memory Replacement.
I erased her memories of tonight
and replaced them with new ones.
Memory Replacement?
But I can't choose the new memories,
which can be a problem.
In any case,
we'll find out tomorrow.
You used it on my family
the other day, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
What is it?
I don't have the resolve
to do this yet.
I'm not such a fine human being
that I can promise to risk
my life for a stranger.
However…
I'm not a total slime who'd watch
someone get hurt before my eyes.
I'll help you…
do the work of a Soul Reaper.
Thanks, I'm counting on you.
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Brother, thank you for watching
over me all this time.
I'll do my best to find happiness.
So…Brother, take care.
Inoue…This is supposed to be the preview…
Aw no, we're out of time again!