Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Huh…!
Hey...
Hey! What time is it?!
This is bad, Big Brother!
It's nine already!
N-No!
Come on! Bonnie!
Hah! Good girl, Bonnie!
But we don't have time today!
Hurry and let me ride you!
Hold it! You're running away?!
Who's running away?!
Hey Dandelion!
We'll settle this
for sure tomorrow!
So you just wait there until then!
Now don't you go floating
away like cotton!
Let's go, everyone!
Huh?!
Cut the crap! That's my--!
They're gone.
That was a disaster… I'm speechless.
Dammit! Just who the hell is he?!
I wonder if Jidanbo is all right?
The wound has closed up, but…
Big-bodied men have lots of stamina.
I'm sure he'll be okay.
You're right.
He's so big and so strong.
I'm sure he'll be okay.
Still… Who is this Kukaku Shiba
we're going to meet now?
Yoruichi never gives us any details…
It's probably someone he knows
who can get us to Seireitei without
passing through the gates, right?
Probably, someone who is
famous for his skill.
Oh! It must be a cat with
pedigree papers!
Like a Persian cat…
Or an American Short Hair…
or a Dalmatian.
Inoue…
It doesn't mean it'll be a cat just
because Yoruichi knows him.
Also…a Dalmatian…
is a dog!
A dog?
Judging from the name,
he's probably a well-built man,
someone like a samurai.
No, he'll be an old hermit-type master.
I know!
See? Like this and this and…
Done!
A hermit-like macho samurai with cat ears,
and a tail!
No doubt about it!
I can't tell what you drew…
Oh? Then how about a skinny
guitar-wielding samurai?
You don't understand, Inoue.
He has to have a cape.
Oh shucks!
But Kurosaki is late.
Shall I call him?
No, I'll go see.
Now then, I have to think up
the next Kukaku Shiba!
No…you don't have to think.
Huh?
What?!
Not going?!
Not "not going."
Just go on ahead.
I'm going to finish the fight with
that guy from yesterday!
What are you saying?!
Quit joking around…and come!
No! No!
He'll think I ran away!
So what?!
Hey, hey…
Aren't we going yet?
Inoue!
Help me drag this fool
away from here!
W-Who's the fool?!
I'm gonna beat him up quickly
as soon as he shows up,
and I'll come after you,
so go on--!
Has blood gone to your head and
made you forget your purpose here?
Fool!
Rukia's life depends on this journey.
Surely, you haven't forgotten.
You can't waste time just to
see who's more stubborn!
If you understand, get ready!
What is it...Renji?
Did they move up my execution date?
It's less than 14 days to the execution.
The use of Sokyoku has
been granted.
You're being transferred to Shishinro,
Repentance Cell.
Hey…
Looks like we've come to
the edge of a village.
Are you sure this is the right way?
Hey!
Shut up! According to
the map the Elder gave us,
it's supposed to be around here.
If you have any complaints,
you take the lead!
No, I'm not complaining.
Kukaku Shiba probably wants
to keep his identity a secret,
that's why he lives in a place like this.
Unfortunately, that is not the case.
It's just that person's nature…
and personal preference.
Don't worry.
This person moves around quite a bit,
but the house is always built the same.
Once you see it, you’ll recognize it.
Once you see it, huh?
Yes, yes. Just once…
Oh, I see it!
There it is.
Wha--!
What's this?!
Wow! How neat!
Kukaku Shiba
See? You can recognize it at once.
That's not the problem anymore!
Wants to keep his identity a secret?
That's probably a lie!
He's probably not allowed to live
in town
because he builds houses like that!
That's gotta be it!
Hmm… So this time, it's human arms
holding the banner.
It's pretty neatly done.
Each time…
He changes the motif?
Let's go.
Okay!
Argh…we're going to that
embarrassing house right now?!
I don't want to be seen walking
into a house like that!
What's the matter? Hurry up!
Yes.
Hey Ishida! I know you don't
want to go, but hurry up!
What's that supposed to mean?
What's that chimney?
It's awfully big compared to the house.
It looks like the opening is closed up.
What the…?
Hold it!
Huh?
Who goes there?!
Strangers!
And one is a Soul Reaper!
Suspicious characters!
I, Koganehiko…
And Shiroganehiko…
will not allow you to pass!
Be gone!
Or you'll die right here!
Damn! Not gatekeepers again?!
What a pain this Soul Society is!
Huh?
Master Yoruichi!
A descending stairway
as soon as you enter?
This house really is weird.
I wonder how you get upstairs?
Please pardon us!
We did not know it was you,
Yoruichi, and your companions.
Please forgive our rudeness.
We're not his companions.
That's all right. It's my fault
for not notifying you beforehand.
Thank you! Such generous words
from such a great personage!
Please wait here a moment.
Y-Yes!
Yes, right away…Master Kukaku!
It's been a while, Yoruichi.
K-Kukaku is…
A woman?!
I never said it was a man.
Huh?
Who are those kids?
Actually, Kukaku…
I have a favor to ask of you.
That's usually the case
when you look me up.
Is it a difficult problem?
Most likely.
It's been a long time
since we've talked like this…
All right. Tell me,
I love difficult things.
Can you see it, Rukia?
From that window over there?
The two tools which will
be used for your execution.
That is the Sokyoku.
A prisoner who is held in this tower
can look out the window that
has been placed in the tower,
and gaze out at the Sokyoku
and repent his sins.
That is why this is called
the Repentance Cell.
Your hands…
Release!
Thank you for transferring
the prisoner here.
Let us go.
Yes.
Lieutenant Abarai…
Huh?
Lieutenant!
Here is unconfirmed information:
You already heard that there were
Ryoka in Soul Society yesterday?
Five of them…
And one of them wielded
a sword as long as his body.
A Soul Reaper with orange-colored hair.
Huh?!
I see… I get the picture.
All right, I'll take on the job.
Really?
Yeah.
If Urahara is involved,
I can't refuse even if I wanted to.
However, while I trust you…
I don't trust those kids.
I'll include my henchman
to keep an eye on them.
Henchman?
Yeah. Henchman,
but he's actually my kid brother.
He's still a brat and not that useful.
Hey, are you ready?
Oh…just a minute.
I'm opening the door, so behave!
Y-Yeah!
How do you do?!
My name is Ganju Shiba!
Please be good to me!
What? You know each other?
How many days has it been since
I saw her face looking so alive?
Ichimaru was the one who
confronted them,
so that kid probably isn't alive.
I...
I was probably right not to tell her.
Hey!
Huh?
Hey, it's been awhile, Abarai.
Aizen-san!
Can you talk?
Well…
It's been quite some time
since we talked like this.
Yes.
Since you were sent to
Kenpachi's place.
How many years has it been?
You're with the Squad 6 now?
Err…what did you want to
talk to me about?
Abarai, you and her…
you were close to Rukia Kuchiki, right?
Don't deny it.
I heard you were
chums from the old days in Rukon District.
Yes…
I won't waste any time then.
In your eyes, should she die?
No… I don't understand
your question.
Don't you think it's strange?
Her crime was the unauthorized transfer,
and loss, of her spiritual energy,
and staying longer than allowed outside.
Certainly, heavy crimes,
but the problem is how to deal with them.
The order for immediate return
and disposal of her Gigai.
The lessening of the grace period
from 35 days to 25 days,
and the use of the Sokyoku on
one who is ranked below a captain.
They're all outside the norm.
I have a feeling that this
is the will of one person.
Hold it, Captain.
What do you mean?!
I have a bad feeling.
Abarai, I may…
Attention all captains!
An urgent meeting will
now be held! Repeat!
Why you---!
Hah! Serves you right!
Lucky!
What--?!
Why you--!
How's that?!
Now I'm mad!
You bastard!
Why you--!
Did she have to go that
far to stop them?
I think I know why she always moves.
It must be hard.
What's with you?!
Fighting from the minute you
set eyes on each other…
Don't you know it's dangerous?!
You destroyed my house!
Hey!
But Sis...
No excuses!
Any complaints?!
Err…no!
No!
What's with this?
Both brother and sister…
Huh?!
Hey brat!
This is my house!
If you have a problem about
the way I do things, get outta here!
I-I'm sorry.
Okay. As long as you understand.
Your sister is something else.
I know.
All right. Everyone, stand!
Yes!
Koganehiko, go outside with
Shiroganehiko and start the preparations.
Right!
The rest, be quiet and follow me!
Wow…why is there light
when we're underground?
I didn't see any generators.
I keep hotaru-kazura in the
ceiling cracks and
on both sides of the wooden frames.
Hotaru-kazura?
Is that a plant or something that
is only found in Soul Society?
We're here. This is it.
Um…
Open it, Ganju.
Right!
Umm…!
What's the big idea?!
Don't defy her! Okay?
Heave!
W-What is this?!
It's huge!
I'll shoot you guys into
Seireitei with this.
From the sky.
Sky?!
My name is Kukaku Shiba.
I'm the best pyrotechnic in Rukongai!
With much appreciation
send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
This is the Special Hard
Spiritual Partition Penetration Device
which my sister invented that can
break through the barrier
which surrounds the entire Seireitei
and which is made
from the Sekki-Seki
which breaks down
spiritual energy completely.
Oh... Can you repeat that?
Forget it!