Are you Ouko Yushima?
He’s not responding.
Hey you!
Get up!
Time to wake up!
Good morning?!
It’s no use.
Huh?!
It doesn’t look like he’ll
ever regain consciousness.
What?
Hey!
Snap out of it!
It won’t do any good.
But with him like this,
we won’t be able to get the location
of Kageroza’s lab out of him!
We finally reached the
developer of Mod Souls,
but it turned out to be a dead end.
No, I expected this.
Huh?
Realizing he’d be
locked away to conceal
Project Spearhead’s
existence, he must have…
What’s wrong?
I found it.
Our clue to the lab.
Are you serious?
What’s that?
It’s blood.
Blood? Whose is it?
It hasn’t been here long.
It doesn’t appear to be his blood.
Which means…
Someone else was here.
Kageroza!
Yes.
But how is the blood going to help us?
We need to thank Kurotsuchi.
What?!
You’re using that device?!
Yes.
I’ll use this blood to
pinpoint his location.
But…you can’t detect Kageroza’s
Spiritual Pressure, so…
With just his blood, no.
But this blood contains
a drug Kurotsuchi Mayuri created.
This drug stops the human
thought processes.
That drug is in here.
In other words, if we look for
the location of that drug.
That’s where Kageroza will be!
His lab!
That’s right.
A Hollow!
What’s it doing here?!
What squad are you with?
Lieutenant Ise!
All squads are to stand
by in their barracks.
Those are your orders.
But…
What is that Hollow?
And we sense captain-level Spiritual
Pressure clashing everywhere.
What’s going on?
Please tell us.
Calm down.
For now, we’ll need to
deal with that Hollow!
Now go!
Y-Yes, ma’am!
I am the true head of the Kuchiki Clan!
What’s the matter?
Looks like he got you!
Need some help?
No thanks. Don’t interfere.
If you need help, feel free to ask.
I’m having way too much fun!
Let me make this clear,
I’m killing this guy!
Don’t butt in!
Hmm…
I think they have the edge.
The capabilities of the Reigai
have significantly improved.
Damn that Kageroza.
Anyhow, let’s kill one per person.
No, maybe two per person.
Quit fooling around!
Here they come!
Bushogoma.
That’s quite a nice imitation!
Bushogoma!
Sogyonokotowari.
Excellent move!
A Sogyonokotowari return fire!
This is no time for jokes.
Yeah, you’re right.
It does seem inappropriate.
I think we should pull
back for the moment.
All right.
Captains Hitsugaya, Kuchiki
and Komamura, pull back!
I’m not backing down!
Captain Hitsugaya!
It’s no use trying to run!
I’m taking you down!
Gokei, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Bushogoma!
Guncho Tsurara!
Hado 88: Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
This is the place.
It’s huge.
What is this structure?
It’s the Senkaimon used
by all the Soul Reapers
in the Soul Society to enter
the World of the Living.
Why are we here?
Beats me.
You mean you don’t know?
You don’t inspire much confidence.
Stop.
Is that a Reigai?
It seems this is definitely
the right place.
And it looks like I
have to battle it out
with my Reigai as well.
I’ll throw the first attack.
Kon, use that opportunity
to find a way inside.
H-Hold on a sec!
I’m no good with machines and
I don’t really know what to do.
The procedure is identical to what I did
at the Department of
Research and Development.
I’ll follow you as soon as I can.
Until I get there, do what you can.
Yeah, but…
Nozomi should also be there.
You’re right. Gotcha!
Looks like that’s the entrance.
That was too close for comfort.
As I expected, you came in that coat.
You knew it was me?
So much for that.
It feels sort of awkward, you know?
Crossing swords with myself.
You think so?
It doesn’t bother me much at all.
I wish you wouldn’t get in our way.
Okay, then!
This way!
Nozomi… Where are you?!
Nozomi…
Nozomi, hang on!
Nozomi!
Hey! Nozomi!
It’s me, Kon! Wake up!
Damn it!
Hey! Nozomi!
Wake up! Nozomi!
Shut up, pervert.
Nozomi…
I’ll have you out in a minute!
How do I get you out?
Get away.
Huh?
Quickly…
Get away from here.
I’m not leaving!
Why do you think I came
all the way here?!
Relax!
I’ll restore Ichigo’s Spiritual
Pressure and rescue you!
Two birds with one stone.
Get away! If you stay here, you’ll…
I said I’m not leaving!
I can’t ignore a friend in trouble!
Friend?
All right!
How do I do this?
Okay!
First, I’ll restore Ichigo’s
Spiritual Pressure!
As I recall…
The procedure is identical
to what I did
at the Department of
Research and Development.
Like I would remember!
What am I supposed to do, you idiot?!
That sounded like Kon’s voice.
I’d better hurry.
You’re not going anywhere!
A portable Gigai?!
That would be correct.
Damn I’m good.
Yeah, I am.
This is no time to be indecisive!
If I don’t hurry, Nozomi
will be fused with Kageroza!
If that happens,
Ichigo and the other
Soul Reapers will be…
No! I won’t let that happen!
But…
I said to get away quickly.
Nozomi!
Once the fusion is complete,
there’s no telling
what’s going to happen.
No telling?
What’s going to happen to you?
Once you’re fused, will
you no longer be yourself?
I don’t know.
But Ouko Yushima had sworn vengeance.
He wants revenge against the
Soul Society for not recognizing
his accomplishments.
To that end, Ouko split his
soul into two Mod Souls,
turning himself into a mere shell.
Don’t move!
Hey! What’s wrong?!
Oh no! Hurry and call Squad 4!
Hide…
Lose yourself among those
incompetent Soul Reapers
and hide your existence.
Then one day, carry on my will
and complete my research.
By splitting himself into two,
his Spiritual Pressure also changed,
allowing himself to go unnoticed.
Kageroza inherited Ouko’s
vengeance and ambition.
And you, Nozomi?
I inherited his self-control.
Kageroza and I are like
darkness and light.
Light?
Then you’ll still remain,
even after the fusion.
I don’t know.
I might be swallowed
up by the darkness.
What?!
The vengefulness Kageroza
inherited from Ouko
has become increasingly clouded,
depraved and inflated
to the point where even the
light might be swallowed up.
That’s why you need
to get away quickly.
While I still have my consciousness.
Nozomi…
Nozomi!
I said I’m not leaving!
You said you were the light.
I’m glad I met you.
You’re my light, as well.
I was always alone.
I won’t let that
light be extinguished!
For the first time in my life,
I realized that I wasn’t alone.
I promise to protect you!
We’re…
- Friends!
Hado 32: Oukasen!
Whoa!
Hado 54: Haien!
You still had a portable Gigai left?
How many do you have, anyway?
Kon…
Damn! This isn’t working at all!
Wait…
Huh?
From this point on, do as I tell you.
You know what to do?
I caught a glimpse of
Kageroza’s memory.
You did?!
But first we need Ichigo’s Reishi.
I brought it with me.
Oh my!
Looks like you’re out
of portable Gigai.
Yup, I’m all out.
If you have any last words,
I’m willing to listen.
That’s very kind of you.
But it isn’t over yet.
Is that so?
Then…
Hado 88: Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
An eighties-level Hado
without an incantation?!
Hey, it started up.
Nozomi, am I doing this right?
Yeah…
Next, flip the switch on the far right.
Gotcha!
Oh!
Yes! It’s working!
You can relax now, Nozomi,
I’ll have you out in no time!
Come on, come on!
Come on, already!
I’m afraid it looks like
we’re at a disadvantage.
But we can’t afford to lose.
You guys don’t know when to give up.
You can’t win against us.
It’s time for the Reigai
to become the real things.
Give up already.
I refuse!
Why do you keep on fighting?
For what purpose?
Don’t make me keep repeating myself!
We protect what must be protected!
That’s all there is to it.
I see.
But the same is true for us, as well.
The same? Don’t make me laugh!
You’re right. It
isn’t quite the same.
We’ll show you what
sets us apart from you.
I swore an oath…to protect!
Just a little more!
Kon!
Kon! Kon!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
Stop…
Kon…
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
S-Stay...
Stay away!
How pitiful.
Way to go, me! I’m
strong even as a Regai!
Of course!
But there’s one thing
that bothers me.
What a coincidence. Me too.
-The stubble should go.
-Wow, we think alike.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Lieutenant Ise!
It’s dangerous here. We should leave!
That’s Captain Hitsugaya!
No.
That’s the work of the Hollowfied
Substitute Soul Reaper!
What?
That’s also a Hollow!
What?!
Regardless of what anyone says,
it's a Hollow!
HOLLOW >> LIE
You’re lying!