You want to know who the strongest
man in the Kabuki District is?
You must be new in town.
You won't last long with that attitude.
Forget it.
This town is on a whole different level.
You got thugs, brawlers,
vigilantes, and rogue warriors
from all over Edo here.
It's like a haven for hooligans.
This is for your own good.
Have a drink and go back
to the countryside.
What's that?
You want me to tell you about
the top dogs before you go?
You really like this stuff.
First, there are four monsters
on a level of their own.
The Fierce and Divine
Mademoiselle Saigo.
Jirocho Doromizu the Gallant.
Peacock Princess Kada.
Empress Otose.
The four factions are in a
standoff which preserves a
fragile balance of power.
Who would be the strongest in a fight?
You wouldn't be able to
even scratch those beasts.
Saigo and Jirocho, in particular,
were heroes during the Joi War.
Well, they're too old
to go on a tear now.
If you want someone
who's currently active,
there's Katsuo Kurogoma,
a young leader in the Doromizu faction.
He's the most feared man
in the Kabuki District now.
You'll also find a few former
Joi in Saigo's faction.
There are rumors about
Kada's faction having
ties to some crazy folk.
Otose's faction?
Snack Otose
It's just a bar, really.
She's just an old lady
with a soft heart.
But if you try any funny
business on her turf,
you'll run into a certain guy.
A guy who holds his own against
the Big Three by himself.
One hell of a monster,
with hair that's completely white.
A demon...
That's too bad.
I was going to decorate your
completely white head with
some bright red flowers.
Your reputation precedes you.
The strongest man in
the Kabuki District...
Gintoki Sakata-san...
Who are you...?
I didn't realize how
strong you were, Bro!
Could you take me in...
...as one of your underlings?
A Lawless Town Tends to Attract
a Bunch of Whoohooey Folk
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
It's freezing.
It's always so cold in the morning.
Who is she?
A drunk?
Uh, excuse me.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep here.
Excuse me.
Your snot has frozen.
Yikes, it's a raid!
Wha-Wha-Wha--
What are you doing?!
Which gang are you from?
If you try to lay a finger on my Bro,
I'll make some bright red flowers.
What are you babbling about?!
Wait a moment here!
Wait!
It's too early for all this noise.
Snack Otose
I am the newest member of the
Odd Jobs gang, Pirako Chin.
It is an honor to meet
the big boss Otose.
I apologize for my behavior earlier.
I didn't realize that you were
the Bro's number one underling.
I'll make up for it by
cutting off my pinky.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
I have nothing to do
with organized crime.
And I don't want any underlings.
And I told you to get lost already!
You damn punk girl!
You're tearing out my hair!
The two of us can become the bosses
of the underworld, Bro!
When did I ever say that I
wanted to be Darth Vader!
What's with her?
Please! I have nowhere else to go!
You come from a gang?
I've heard rumors.
The Uekibachi gang was having a
business quarrel with Jirocho's people.
When a fight broke out,
there was a crazy girl who
took out the whole lot by herself.
Her name was Pirako the killer.
Huh?! A killer?!
This little twit?!
This little girl works
for the underworld?!
It's nothing to brag about.
I just happen to be good
at decorating with flowers.
Did you know?
The more evil someone is,
the more beautiful a flower they make.
And when I cut them up more, the
flowers are redder and prettier!
Uh, I'm very sorry.
I didn't mean to call you a little girl.
You said you have nowhere to go?
What happened to your former employers?
They're dead.
They were jumped by the Jirocho gang
and turned into a lovely garden.
There was a nice man
there who took me in,
and I always did what I was told,
so I don't know what to do now.
But I only know how to
decorate with flowers.
That's why I'm here.
I'm here to turn the
town where Jirocho is...
To turn the Kabuki District into a
garden of bright red flower garden!
Hey, hey, hey!
The Bro is passin' through!
Whatcha lookin' at, twerps? Eh?!
You wanna make something of it?!
Wanna make something of it?!
This is bad. Very bad.
We've picked up a really dangerous girl.
She said she's going to turn the
Kabuki District into a flower garden.
She means a sea of blood, doesn't she?
She wants to use your strength
to get revenge on Jirocho.
I-It'll be okay.
Hey! Wanna fight?
She's a killer, but she's just a girl.
She can't be stupid enough
to take on the big boss...
Look here, Bro!
Pretty flowers!
See?
She looks like a perfectly normal girl
who happens to like flowers...
Gran, you been payin' all your fees?
Eh?!
Don't make threats with
a smile on your face!
A gang needs money to run.
In return, we provide security.
They're looking for security from us!
Now listen to me.
If you want to join Odd Jobs,
forget all that dark side stuff.
You aren't Darth Vader.
You're just an ordinary girl.
You aren't Pirako Chin.
From now on, you're Birako Man.
What kind of name is that?!
Understood.
I'm Birabirako Man.
No, you have an extra "bira" in there!
Could you stop that?!
Hey, there's a cute
cake place over there!
You can learn how to be a girl
there, Birabirabirabirako Man!
Enough with the "birabira" already!
This is kind of embarrassing.
I've never been in a
place like this before.
Do I stand out?
Not at all.
You look perfectly natural here!
You guys stand out like sore thumbs.
Don't worry about it,
Birabirabirabirako-san.
You look like a very normal...
No, a very cute girl.
Huh?
You should drop the gangster act.
It's such a waste.
Oh, sorry about trying
to boss you around.
Come on, what are you doing?
Eat your cake.
If you don't eat your cake, I'll eat it.
A cockroach was chewing on my cake.
It's too dirty for me to eat.
What are you going to
do about this, dammit?
Hey! Are you saying I'm a cockroach?!
I'm actually kind of a clean freak.
Gangster stuff aside.
Gangster stuff aside?!
Morimioto Candy
So you just hate me, period?!
No sweat. That wasn't your fault.
Nothing wrong there.
That's how a normal girl would react.
Why are you defending her?!
Don't make it sound like every
single girl is anti-Shinpachi!
If you act gangster again,
you get another "bira" tacked on.
At least your name will feel more girly,
Birabirabirabirabirako Man.
How is that name girly?!
It makes her sound like
a "birabira" monster!
Enough already!
Hey, there's a cute
dried fish place, *****!
Watch your mouth!
Whoa, look at this, Birako Man!
They're all dried! They're all hard!
And wait, you're just taking
Ooh, it's so cute!
her to the places you want to go!
Why is it so dry?
What's so girly about dried fish?!
Bro!
Oh, sorry...
Bro! What's wrong?!
It's broken!
The impact broke it!
Here comes the real thing!
This is bad.
Hey, girl!
We were making progress,
Whatcha gonna do about this?
but they're going to stimulate
her gangster blood.
Gran, give me some sukonbu.
If they're from Jirocho's faction...
Bah, can't help it.
Gin-san! No violence!
I know.
I'll settle this in a mature
and gentlemanly fashion.
Excuse me, did my friend
do something wrong?
Huh? Who are you?
B-Bro!
What's wrong?
I-It's broken...
Th-The pat on the shoulder
shattered all of my bones!
You're doing the exact same thing!
What do you mean, pat on the shoulder?
You're the one who patted
me on the shoulder!
So, what are you going to do about this?
Hey!
You're making it worse!
That won't do! Calm down, Birako!
Here's your change.
Why are you pretending
to break your bones?!
Uh, you broke your arm,
while two of us broke all of our bones.
Can we call it even?
You broke your own bones!
That girl wasn't anywhere near us!
Bro, that's enough.
He's the one who's with Otose...
What?
Oh...
He's the one who took
on Big Bro Katsuo...
Katsuo Kurogoma...
So they belong to Jirocho's gang.
All of my bones have been broken...
Could you let this one slide?
B-Bro, we should go...
I'll let you go today.
Now come with me.
Huh?
I don't have any business with him,
but I'll need you to pay up
by using that body of yours...
N-No! Bro!
Please wait a moment!
Stop struggling!
You damn bitch!
Huh?
I thought your bones were all broken?
And your arm?
It seems to be in...
...terrible shape!
N-Now he's done it!
Matsuo to Kiyoshi
Bro!
Snap out of it, Bro!
Wha-Wha--
Bro!
Wake up, Bro!
What the hell are you doing?!
Why did you make the first move?!
Well, he was taking advantage
of my gracious behavior.
I just gave him a little flick.
The hell you did!
You sent him flying through the air!
You rule, Bro!
I think I'm in love.
Now we have no choice but to
fight it out with Jirocho.
Together, we can make
lots of red flowers
and become the bosses of Japan.
Damn it!
You tricked me!
Bastards!
That's not funny!
You won't get away with this!
I'm not gonna pick a fight with Jirocho!
This means war!
I ain't gonna fight a war!
Gin-san! You're starting
the war as we speak!
Pipe down!
Calm yourself!
Calm yourself and look
around for Dryaemon.
You need to calm down!
It's okay, Ginta-kun!
I have just what you need!
Ready-mix concrete!
What are you going to do with that?!
Shut up!
Matsuo to Kiyoshi
If we stick Giannosuke
and Suneorochimaru
in here and toss it in the ocean,
we can basically shut them up forever!
Lady Shizuka will be yours!
Hell no!
You'll scare off Lady Shizuka!
Pops, give me the usual dog food...
Looks like a fight's going down.
What's...
Kabuki District Council
Meeting Room
We will now begin the Ka-Kabuki
District Council Meeting.
Kabuki District
Clean Up Project
The topic today is separating trash...
Get lost, trash.
Yes!
Excuse me!
So what's this about?
The Kabuki District's Empress Otose
Why did you call us here?
I don't recall ever failing
to separate my trash.
You just did.
Why is this stinkin' garbage of a hag
The Fierce and Divine Mademoiselle Saigo
mixed in with us beauties?
You shouldn't be talking.
Peacock Princess Kada
I'm glad to see that
you haven't changed.
I apologize for taking up your time.
But you'll have to wait a little longer.
We're missing a member.
Jirocho?
There's no point.
It's been two or three years
since he was last seen in public.
I was hoping to have all four
Devas present for this discussion.
I called you here for one reason.
You are probably aware that
the town has grown tense
the past few years.
If nothing is done,
a war will break out.
I'm sure that nobody wishes
for that to happen.
Listen to yourself.
You and Jirocho are the
ones making a splash.
It used to be that the casinos
in this town were run by Jirocho's gang.
But then you built a casino here.
The same could be said of you, Saigo.
I've heard tales
that you're sheltering Joi
patriots and rogue warriors.
Huh?
Your soldiers may be dressed oddly,
but each one of them is quite strong.
You plan on using their strength
to create an empire of trannies...
What are you talking about?
I'm offering a home to those
who have no place to go.
But the fact remains that
you've repeatedly refused
to accept the demands of Jirocho's gang.
And Otose...
I have no interest in your stupid fight,
and I'll have none of it.
You may have no interest,
but you've always held great
influence in this town.
I've heard that you listen to the
problems of your customers
and offer counseling.
And your pawns in that
sketchy Odd Jobs group
provide the necessary assistance.
They've been running wild
across our territory.
I never knew that I had
pawns I could order around.
And I never knew that this town
had been divided up into territories.
This town doesn't belong to anyone.
We just live our lives here.
That's all.
However, some are not satisfied by that.
These days, we are
known as the Four Devas
who work together to run this town,
but didn't it all begin with the
rise of a new faction,
a king of hooligans?
There is no reason for us to fight.
After all,
isn't our enemy Jirocho?
I see how it is.
The three of you are teaming up
to get rid of Jirocho, the obstacle.
Well, well.
Wait up!
It's over! This is war!
This is all-out war!
Gin-san!
This is out of control!
Ginta-kun is off on a
rendezvous with Lady Shizuka.
Huh?!
The bastard used us as decoys!
I'll get you for this!
It looks like they're gone, Bro.
Things are getting fun.
What's so fun about this?
Time to bust out an old cliche.
Revenge isn't fun for anyone.
I'm sure that your dead friends
would want you to live
like an ordinary girl
instead of letting revenge
take over your life.
Bro...
Why do you keep talking about revenge?
Uh, wasn't your gang
slaughtered by Jirocho?
So you want revenge...
What are you talking about?
My gang was crushed by Jirocho,
but they're all alive.
Huh?
But you said they were
turned into a flower garden.
They quit the business
to become farmers.
They've planted a garden of red flowers.
It's a pretty place.
But it was boring, so I left.
Huh?!
Could you be any more misleading?!
We've been trying to subtly convince you
to give up on revenge because
of your dark past...
So wait?
Why are you here?
Like I said,
I'm here to decorate Jirocho
and this town in red flowers.
Enough of that.
Give it to me straight.
I mean exactly what I say.
I'm here to help the great
Jirocho bloom again.
For that,
I need the help of the strongest
man in the Kabuki District!
That's you, Bro!
Got it.
In other words, your
mind is full of flowers,
and it's a waste of time
to bother talking with you.
In that case, this is farewell...
Bro, the bond between gang
members isn't easily broken.
I don't have a bond with
a plastic trash can!
The concrete's hard now!
This is all because you kept on talking!
What do we do?!
What's going to happen?!
Well, that's easy enough.
You get served the treatment
you were gonna deal.
Y-You're...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The obstacle's here.
Jirocho...
Don't mind me.
Carry on.
I believe the three of you were talking
about teaming up to get rid of me?
We never said anything about that.
I simply mentioned that our wish
to avoid any pointless conflict
was being ruined by an
unstoppable loose cannon.
I would take him out.
Some fools in this world
can only be cured by death.
But I wouldn't arrange
a meeting like this.
Look.
Your necks are all lined up
within range of my blade.
One of the Peacock Princess's pets, huh?
Stand down.
He's merely joking.
No, he made the correct decision.
This pet was trained well to
be able to detect my hostility.
Unfortunately, I'm getting old,
so I have trouble controlling
my piss and my hostility.
I already sheathed my blade,
but it keeps trickling out...
Case in point.
You didn't notice me taking you out.
I said to stop this!
What do you think you're
doing to the boss?!
Take them!
You've shown your true colors!
We won't let you lay a finger on Mama!
You were eavesdropping on a
conversation between ladies?
You bastards ready to have
your balls ripped out?!
Stand down, boys.
Boss!
Ordinary humans have no place here.
Good grief.
How do you intend to
stop these monsters?
If you have any ideas,
I'd love to hear them.
As you saw, power can only
be restrained by more power.
Here is my proposal.
The factions of the Four Devas are
not allowed to engage
in personal fights.
The faction which breaks this rule
will be crushed by the other three.
So in the end, it'll still be the three
of you teaming up against me?
You think you can take
my balls by teaming up?
Don't get the wrong idea.
This rule is to prevent
further conflict.
The town will be a dull
place if nobody can fight.
If that's the only way to
avoid a war, then so be it.
Are you sane?
Very well.
It'll be a test of endurance.
Try not to screw up before I do.
To Be Continued
Next Episode Preview
Their past is revealed...
A battle pitting Gintoki
against Jirocho...
Ghosts Aren't the Only Ones
Who Run Wild Around Graveyards
#Eyecatch