Oh, good.
You seem to be doing well.
Yeah.
Looks like he’s brimming with energy.
I’m glad.
Now then…
I destroyed the stairway.
Yukio’s about the only person
that can possibly come up here.
Now…
There’s nothing to hold you back.
Fight with everything you’ve got!
Ichigo!
So that’s your Fullbring…
You’ve come a long
way in a short time.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
Say it while you still can.
I came here to kill you.
Chad… Inoue…
Sotenkishun!
I reject.
Don’t…
Don’t do this, Inoue…
Don’t heal his arm!
He’s...
Good job.
As usual, your healing
powers are remarkable.
Thank you!
Chad…
Are you two also like the others?
I don’t know what you mean by that.
I’m actually confused
because you’re different...
Kurosaki…
Have you forgotten how Mr. Tsukishima
has always helped us?
We were able to save Kuchiki…
And bring Inoue back from Hueco Mundo…
It was all thanks to Mr. Tsukishima!
Do you understand what’s going on…
Ichigo?
Ichigo!
Hey, pay attention.
Right now, you’re fighting against us.
You can’t afford to be
worrying about others!
Who is this guy?
Did he make this fall?
What did he just do?
I don’t see anything in his hand.
The chain on the fallen
chandelier isn’t cut.
Each of its screws came out...
What is this guy’s Fullbring?
We’re not letting you get past us!
There is a place and
time for everything.
Science fiction novels talk about
going back in time with a time machine
and splitting the future
into different timelines.
Tampering with things invariably
changes the future.
That’s because time
is believed to flow
from the past to the future.
But my Fullbring, “Book of
the End,” splits the past.
That’s possible because my power
doesn’t manipulate time and memories.
my power is the ability to
insert “my very presence”
into a person’s past.
So Ginjo’s guess was correct.
Ginjo guessed my power?
I’m surprised...
I underestimated him.
I didn’t think he was that smart.
Anyway, I know it’s sad,
but I want you to understand.
The past they experienced and the
past you experienced are
two separate things.
That’s a roundabout
way of putting it.
Why don’t you just say you’ve
changed it to something
different with your powers?
That’s where you’re wrong.
It didn’t become something else.
Everyone except you…
has lived their lives with me.
You’re the only one leading
a life from a false past.
You must be sad that it’s
only different for you.
But you don’t have to worry.
Soon, that feeling will have
never existed in the first place.
Inoue…
Chad…
Why, Ichigo?
This is not what I became strong for…
I didn’t become strong to fight you!
Wait, Chad!
I…
Brazo
Izquierdo
Del Diablo!
Damn it…
Damn it… Damn it…
Why…?
How did this happen…?!
I wanted to protect you guys!
So why?!
I… I…!
What did I regain my powers for?!
Tsukishima!
Ichigo!
“Dirty Boots”!
“Time Tells No Lies.”
Stop it, Kutsuzawa!
Damn it, not you guys too!
I have to do something …
“Doll House”!
You’re not getting past us!
Damn it…!
What the hell…?
He’s not tough at all…
What…? It’s broken…?!
You should be happy I
didn’t hit your body!
That last spin was so good.
There’s no telling what
would’ve happened to you.
What do you mean?
My Fullbring is…
“Jackpot Knuckle”!
I can control the odds and
draw out the jackpot
right from the start!
That last punch hit the
jackpot and the guard
of your sword just happened
to snap from wear and tear!
The coin I flicked earlier hit the
jackpot and the screws of the chandelier
just happened to come loose enough
for it to come falling down!
Come at me, Kugo Ginjo!
I’ll show you what a one
shot, one kill really is!
Damn…
I can’t allow Ichigo
to be cut down as well…
I don’t have time to
bother with you guys!
Let’s go!
Tsukishima!
What’s the matter?
Poor thing…
So angry that you can’t
even find the words?
Getsuga
Tensho!
He’s fast!
He’s able to unleash
Getsugatensho even in Fullbring mode…
Or rather, he learned how to…
His powers have reawakened…
Not only that,
but the speed of his attacks are
faster than I had anticipated.
He really did succeed in combining
Soul Reaper powers with Fullbring…
Damn you…!
Tsukishima!
And as expected, despair helped
him complete his power…
Oh, boy…
I think he’s complete.
Ichigo!
Keep your eyes over here!
No you don’t!
It’s time.
Time?!
What’re you talking about?
I don’t stand a chance
against the four of them…
Where’s Ichigo?
Why are you protecting him…?
Please stop it…
Chad… Inoue…
You took the words right
out of my mouth…
Don’t do this, Ichigo!
Don’t you get it?
I…have no desire to fight you!
Tsukishima!
Stop hiding behind my friends!
Come on out and fight!
Where’d he go…?
Damn it…
Ginjo…
Ginjo!
What’s going to happen?!
My “Book of the End”
inserts my presence at will into
the other party’s past…
Will Ginjo, just like all the others…
think of Tsukishima as his friend…?
Ginjo!
Are you all right, Ginjo?!
Please…
Ginjo!
Shut up…
Stop paying so much attention
to me, Kurosaki…
Ginjo!
I thought I told you, don’t
let Tsukishima get you
from behind, or it’s all over!
Are you all right…?!
Ginjo…
I don’t know.
But…
Right now, I still consider
that guy to be my enemy…
And I still think of you as my friend.
I see…
Good.
I don’t know why Tsukishima’s
power didn’t take effect.
Maybe there are individual
differences in
how long it takes for his
power to take effect…
Or maybe he deliberately
didn’t let them take
effect for a reason.
Either way…
We have to defeat Tsukishima
now, while we can…
Once his powers take effect,
there’ll be nothing we can do!
What happened to you?
What’s gotten into you, Brother Ichi?
You’re acting strange, Brother.
Brother Ichi…
You’re to blame, Brother.
Hey!
Brother…
You…
…Right!
Kurosaki.
Ishida…!
Which side is he on…?!
Ishida was also cut down by Tsukishima.
So who healed his wounds?!
Was it Inoue?
Inoue was cut down by Tsukishima.
Did she heal Ishida before
she considered Tsukishima as her friend?
If it was after she considered
Tsukishima as a friend,
it would mean she healed Ishida
to make him part of Tsukishima’s army.
Which is it?!
Ishida!
So you’re…
one of them, too? Ishida!
Ishida…
Kurosaki…come here.
I saw what’s going on downstairs.
Relax. I’m on your side.
You’re not…
What’s wrong?
Hurry, Kurosaki…
Ishida…!
Kurosaki…!
Don’t you get it?!
The guy who cut me…
is the guy standing behind you!
Kurosaki!
Ginjo…
Why?
Is it because of
Tsukishima’s power…?
Yeah.
Definitely because of
Tsukishima’s power…
But make no mistake.
I didn’t become your enemy
because Tsukishima cut me.
I let Tsukishima cut me twice
so I could return to my original self.
Your Fullbring is mine.
Just what I’d expect from
Mr. Tsukishima’s friends!
You’re all very strong!
I’ve been meaning to
ask, but who are you?
I’m Mr. Tsukishima’s apprentice!
He had an apprentice?
You haven’t heard about
me from Mr. Tsukishima?
Like how I’m useful, or adorable?
-Not a word.
In celebration of Uryu
Ishida Joining the Battle!
QUIZ: WHAT’S UNDERNEATH THE GLASSES?
It’s been so long…
so while I don’t think
you’ve forgotten…
But let’s assume you saw
me for the first time,
try to guess my true identity.
You’re wearing white, so
you’re the laundry guy!
Laundrymen don’t wear white.
You’re good at sewing,
so you’re a mother!
Huh? Who’s?!
You’re wearing white,
so you’re a squid!
Okay, let’s try to get
away from the clothes!
Eyeglasses.
You’re wearing white, so cotton!
You’re just trying to make
fun of me, aren’t you?!