Captain!
Huh? That’s odd.
Where did Captain go?
If you’re looking for
Captain Hitsugaya,
he’s supposed to be
on leave starting today.
Oh! That’s right. I forgot.
That means I’ll have to take
care of all these documents.
Captain, why’d you
have to take leave?
Yours, Kurosaki!
Got it!
Toshiro!
You sure saved us, Toshiro.
When Ryohei got hurt,
we didn’t know who we
could get to replace him.
Sure.
How long will you be around?
None of your business.
What kind of answer is that?!
Anyway, how long are you going
to keep following me around?
I’m done helping your team.
I have some business to…
Toshiro?
I knew it.
It is you, Toshiro.
Grandma Haru…
I got to know Grandma Haru
when I was stationed in
the World of the Living.
Stationed?
I don’t really get it, but…
You were doing things like that
even though you’re a kid?
I keep telling you, I’m not a kid!
Grandma Haru can see spirits
the way you and Kurosaki can.
I see.
No wonder so many
of them are gathering in this place.
Go away!
Here, Toshiro. It’s your
favorite candied beans.
You like candied beans?
You’re like an old man!
Shut up.
Mmm… These are great!
Toshiro.
Thank you for coming such a long way.
Sure.
So that’s it, Toshiro.
You came here to visit Granny?
It’s none of your business.
Fine.
Huh?
Oh, Yosuke.
Were you there all this time?
Granny, who is that boy?
He’s been staying
here for a while now.
A Whole.
Yosuke, can you say
hello to our guests?
Hi!
I’m sorry.
Yosuke is very shy.
However, he’s the most visible
wandering spirit since Toshiro.
I’m not a spirit.
Yes, yes. You’re a Soul Reaper.
Anyway, thanks to Yosuke,
I’m enjoying my life right now.
I see.
Do you have a family, Granny?
I’ve lived alone all these years.
Oh…I’m sorry.
Don’t be.
Nowadays, I have Yosuke
and many other spirits.
And sometimes Toshiro comes to visit,
so I’m not lonely.
That’s great!
The wandering spirits that come
around me are all annoying ones.
But Yosuke…
What is keeping you
from resting in peace?
Yosuke wants to see snow.
Isn’t that right?
Snow?
Yosuke got into an accident
while he and his family
were on their way to go skiing.
It was a terrible accident.
Many people lost their lives.
His parents seem to have
passed over in peace, but
this child was looking forward to
seeing snow for the first time.
That desire remained so strong
that he was unable to rest in peace
and I found him wandering about.
Is that so?
But according to the weather forecast,
it should snow soon.
Isn’t that great?
Yes!
Say, Toshiro…
Is it okay…to leave
that child like that?
What’re you talking about?
Don’t play dumb.
Aren’t spirits that haven’t
passed over at risk?
If left alone…I don’t
really understand this…
but don’t they turn
into like, monsters?
You’re right.
If he stays here,
Yosuke will probably
turn into a Hollow.
A Hollow?
What you call a “monster.”
Then won’t Grandma
Haru be in danger too?
Toshiro…
It happened right about when
I first became a Soul Reaper.
I was dispatched before
I knew what to expect from
the World of the Living
in order to gain experience.
While I was stationed here,
I simply followed orders
and spent every day
getting rid of Hollows.
Back then, all I thought about was
getting rid of the
Hollows in front of me.
That’s a fine sword you have there.
My, you’re such a tiny Soul Reaper.
Grandma Haru had spiritual power
and knew about Soul Reapers.
She looked after me.
I can see you very clearly today.
I’m in a gigai.
A gigai?
It’s a body for eating candied beans.
Is that so?
Then be sure to eat
lots before you leave.
Grandma lost her family a long time ago
and lived alone for all those years.
And, because she could see spirits,
everyone thought she was creepy
and kept their distance from her.
Spirits were the only thing
that eased her loneliness.
Grandma Haru thinks of
Yosuke like a grandson.
Tell me, Toshiro…
Did you come to do
something for Yosuke?
Ordinarily, I’d perform a
Konso as soon as I found
a spirit like that.
But since I left him alone,
I can’t allow this to
cause problems for anyone.
I have no choice but to watch over him.
You know, for a kid,
you’re awfully caring.
Who’re you calling a kid?!
So, you’ll be staying
here a while, right?
Do you have someplace to stay?
Well…
Then come to my place.
Huh?
Karin brought home a boyfriend!
-You’re wrong!
You two are perfect for each other!
Aw jeez!
Of all the times for
Dad not to be here!
It’s not what you think!
Oh, never mind!
Anyhow, Toshiro will be staying
with us a while, okay?
Huh?! Oh my!
Karin is becoming an adult!
Brother, say something!
Why aren’t you talking, Brother?
Aren’t you friends with Toshiro?!
Toshiro…
What the hell do you
think you’re doing?
What’re you talking about?!
What’s with your family?!
They won’t listen, no matter
how much we try to correct them!
That’s okay.
Yuzu’s always like that,
so don’t let it bother you.
I was just kidding you.
You and Karin took it so seriously
that I couldn’t help myself.
But Toshiro…
Don’t put Karin in danger, you hear?
So…
How long are you going
to keep following me?
Why not?
You’re going to
Granny’s place, right?
I have nothing else to do.
Suit yourself.
My, my, you’ve come again today?
I told you, I took some time off.
I see, I see.
Oh, you came with your
girlfriend again?
Hi.
She’s not my girlfriend!
Not you too, Grandma.
Yosuke.
Toshiro’s here.
Hi there!
You are such a shy child.
Hey.
Here.
You can keep it.
T-Thank you.
Tell me, Toshiro…
Where did you get that?
My Zanpakuto is an ice-snow type.
Huh?!
If I want to, I can
manipulate ice and snow.
So, did you make that yourself?
If you have that ability,
wouldn’t things be faster
if you made it snow?
My powers are not meant
to show off so easily.
Jeez, that sounds complicated.
Besides, it’ll snow soon, even
without me doing anything.
Really?
Yosuke!
It’ll be snowing pretty soon!
When it does, let’s
make an even bigger one!
Okay!
Thank you, Toshiro.
Grandma Haru…when it snows…
Yes, I know.
That is your job, isn’t it, Toshiro?
That’s what’s best for Yosuke’s
happiness too, isn’t it?
Yeah.
It’s been quite a while now,
but it hasn’t snowed even
though it looks like it might.
Yeah.
Is something the matter?
It’s Yosuke.
Considering when he became
a spirit and the strength
of his obsession,
it wouldn’t be odd at all if
he turned into a Hollow by now.
Isn’t it a good thing
if he doesn’t turn into a monster?
Come to think of it, Granny’s late…
I’ll go and take a look.
Yeah.
I don’t like the idea,
but maybe it’s best if I used my
Zanpakuto to make it snow, after all.
What’s the matter, Yosuke?
Granny!
What?!
Come on, Granny!
Granny!
This is…
Her Spiritual Pressure is weakening!
What?
What’s going on?
Grand…ma…
Could it be?
Was Grandma Haru using her
own Spiritual Pressure
to prevent Yosuke from transforming…
into a Hollow?!
What is it?!
What’s the matter?!
Yosuke!
Damn it!
Yosuke…
Toshiro!
Take care of Grandma Haru!
R-Right!
Damn it… Where’d he go?
Stay back!
Damn it!
Stop it, Toshiro!
Toshiro!
Isn’t that Yosuke?!
Isn’t there anything you can do?!
Once he’s become a Hollow…
there’s nothing I can do.
Yosuke!
Come to your senses!
You’ll be able to see snow soon!
Hang on just a little while longer!
Yosuke!
You idiot! Get back here!
What’s going on?
Grandma…Haru…
Toshiro…
Yes, I know.
That is your job, isn’t it, Toshiro?
That’s what’s best for Yosuke’s
happiness too, isn’t it?
Yosuke…
I’m sorry.
This all happened because
I wasn’t strong enough.
Yosuke…
I’m sorry.
Grandma Haru…
It’s snowing!
Yosuke saw the snow, didn’t he?
Yes, he sure did.
Right, Toshiro?
Yeah.
Toshiro… I’m sorry for
causing you so much trouble.
It’s not your fault, Grandma Haru.
Is that so?
Say, Granny.
Would it be okay if I started
coming over to visit too?
There’s a small soccer field nearby,
so I’ll bring my friends too!
My, that’ll make things very lively.
You know, Toshiro…
Do you think Yosuke stopped
because of Granny?
I think Yosuke was
battling within himself
even after he turned into a monster.
That’s why he stopped, I think.
Who knows?
I’m done with my business
here, so I’ll be going back.
I see!
Drop by again, okay?
I’ll keep your name on
our team’s game roster!
See you!
Yeah.
Now then, I still have leave days left,
so maybe I’ll drop by my Grandma’s
place in the Rukon District.
Karin’s out on a date again!
Yuzu, it’s not like that
between Karin and Toshiro.
But I see them going somewhere
together every day.
That never happened before.
What?!
You think they’ll get married
when they’re older?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Brother!
Dinner time!
Coming!
What the—?!
What’re you all doing here?!
I invited them to celebrate
the new story arc!
Huh?! I didn’t hear anything!
Knowing you, Brother,
you probably weren’t paying
attention when you heard about it.
That couldn’t be!
Whatever. But I don’t
have anywhere to sit!
Let me sit!
And so, we’ll be starting a new
story arc beginning next episode!
Keep watching!