Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allow me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
As it happened,
Orihime Inoue was taken away by
the treacherous Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
In order to prevent Aizen from
wiping out Karakura Town,
an Enriched Spirit Zone,
the Soul Reapers moved
Karakura Town to safety
in the Soul Society and took up
positions in a fake Karakura Town
created in the World of the Living.
Soul Reapers and Arrancar faced off
throughout Karakura Town.
Rangiku Matsumoto fought
together with Hinamori,
who came to her assistance,
against Apache,
Mila Rose and Sun-Sun.
The two momentarily gained
the upper hand via Hinamori's Kido,
but the situation
changed suddenly
after the three took
their Resurreccion forms.
Quimera Parco.
Wh-What…
What is that?
Quimera Parco.
It's our pet,
created from the left arms
of the three of us
in our released form.
Its name is Ayon.
What?
What is this chill…
Like I'm peering into a deep pit
whose bottom I cannot see…
Oh, I forgot to warn you.
Ayon is deadly, so be careful.
The bones in my entire body
are broken…
Both Rangiku and myself,
taken out by a single strike…
This is crazy…
There's no way we can win
against this thing…
Bakudo 37, Tsuriboshi!
This one's in even worse shape!
Oh no…
It hasn't reacted to me yet!
Will I make it?!
I'm so close to finishing…
Just a little more…
Captain… What was that?
Keep your head.
That was the Head Captain.
What?
The Head Captain himself,
fighting?
Omaeda…
Your face, please.
Huh? What is it?
Captain…I, Omaeda, won't fall
for the same trick twice!
We've come here to fight.
Even the Head Captain
is no exception.
Quit asking silly questions.
That's…mean…
Head Captain…Yamamoto!
Another one came…
One after another!
What's wrong with that?
He seems to have
injured Ayon, but…
Now he'll find out what happens
when you do such a thing.
Good grief…
Making the Head Captain
come out to the front…
Such hopeless squad members.
Forgive us, sir!
That's what you
shouldn't be doing.
If you have time
to apologize to me,
you should be keeping
a sharp eye on your opponent.
You're kidding me!
That injury is not critical enough
to kill him?
Rangiku…
It would seem…
I didn't punish it enough.
Looks like he finally snapped!
What's wrong?
Your attack didn't reach me.
What?!
A demonic beast that can
only think of killing people…
How pitiful you are.
Ryujinjakka, Hitotsume…
Nadegiri!
What?!
Good grief…
Won't you stop it already…
It burdens my heart to
have to repeatedly kill
a pitiful beast like you.
I said stop already.
Don't you understand?
Brat!
In…credible…
Your focus has
increased considerably.
Is it because you now know
your subordinates will live,
thanks to the Head Captain?
None of your damned business!
Kira.
Not yet.
Strengthen your current barrier.
I admire the spirit of
challenging me with one arm.
Damn…
…it…
In consideration of your spirit,
I'll let you get off
with just burns.
What?!
What is that?
Apache…Sun-Sun…
Mila Rose…
You have all fought well.
Even with your level of strength…
You're still number 3?
With my level?
I don't recall showing you
the extent of my strength yet.
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
You fellows…are strong.
Why thank you.
I wanted to keep dodging and
wait until the battle ended…
But that's not
going to be possible.
I'm happy to hear that…
My guess is that
among the three of you,
that girl there is third…
How am I doing?
Personally, I wish
that old man was number one
and I'd be glad
if you were second.
I see.
Sorry to disappoint…
But I'm primera.
I knew it…
Too bad…
If someone like you
is the strongest…
it makes it difficult you know.
C-Captain…
It’s about to start.
Roar, Zabimaru!
Here I come again!
El Directo!
They're coming!
Right!
You're not getting past here!
Tsuginomai
Hakuren!
The Exiquias were wiped out.
You're all that's left.
How foolish of you…
No matter how
you sacrifice yourself
to allow Ichigo Kurosaki
to go beyond here…
What awaits him is certain death.
I won't let you have your way.
Besides I never had any intention
of sacrificing myself.
I see… That's fine.
Then I shall guide you
to your doom.
I told you,
I won't let you have your way!
Kurosaki!
Still intend to keep fighting?
What?!
Garganta…is closed…
You people who were injured in
the battle against us Espadas
no longer have
anywhere to go.
You will idly spend your time here
and die by our hands…
That's all there is for you.
In short time,
Karakura Town will disappear,
and the Soul Society, too,
will be destroyed by Lord Aizen
after he creates the Ouken.
You people have
no way to stop that.
Shut up—!
We're not done yet…
Don't underestimate
my strength!
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
will stop Aizen without fail.
If that's not enough,
I will go and stop him…
I'll defeat you and stop him!
Ulquiorra!
I will defeat you, Ulquiorra!
And then
I'm taking Inoue back with me!
Kurosaki…
Get ready, Ulquiorra!
Here I come!
Wait, Ichigo Kurosaki.
What?
It appears we have interference.
I'm temporarily
suspending this battle.
Huh?! What are
you talking about?
The grown ups
have their reasons…
Nel!
And that's how it is!
We're going to take a small break
from the Hueco Mundo arc!
Again?!
All right.
If the grown-ups
have their reasons,
then it can't be helped.
And you're okay with that,
damn it?
Kurosaki, don't complain.
From the next episode, we will tell
a tale of the World of the Living
that we weren't able to until now,
and new battles await.
What's with that?!
Hey! Hey!
– Call me when I'm on again.
– Hey! Hey!
You'll all have to wait
just a little while!