Hitsugaya's advance troops
have remained in Karakura Town,
and a new Arrancar
has appeared before them.
This Arrancar is a troublesome enemy
because he clones himself.
Hitsugaya and the others manage
to drive off the first group of Arrancars
that appear and protect, Shota and Yui,
a pair of souls who are siblings.
But that is not the end of it.
According to an analysis
done in Soul Society,
this Arrancar controls
several clones at once
in order to absorb
as many souls as possible.
Let's split up and go after him!
- Okay!
Wait!
Hey!
It's all right. I'm not an enemy.
Did you see a monster?
Shota! Wait up!
It's dangerous here!
We've got to go back!
No!
Shota!
We'll look for Yui...
That's no good!
I have to protect Yui myself!
Shota, you...
Yui...
When did she...?
Yui! What were you doing here?!
I wasn't doing anything...
I just wanted to come to this park.
Now that you're here,
I'm all right now.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I...ran away...
Yui... I left her here...
And ran away!
On the day of the accident...
We got separated
from mom and dad.
Yui and I were so afraid.
Day after day,
we looked everywhere for them.
But we couldn't find them
no matter where we looked.
Yui!
Yui went to go
look for them by herself.
Yui!
Big brother! Help!
Help!
Big brother!
Big brother?!
Wait! Wait!
Big brother, help!
Big brother!
When I came to...
I was trembling somewhere
far away from the park.
Yui was...
Because I ran away, it...
I'm despicable.
So what happened afterwards?
I...really regretted what I did.
I gathered up the courage...
And I went to the park...
but Yui wasn't there.
Then it showed up again...
Where's Yui?!
Who knows?
Give Yui back!
Look for her yourself.
Why you...
You punk!
That's when you came...
Hey! Let me go!
I...I...abandoned Yui...
Despite that,
Yui still says that I'll protect her.
Ms. Rangiku...
It was tough, wasn't it, Shota?
Don't cry.
I'm not certain what to make
of what happened,
but at least Yui was saved.
And she got to see you again...
It's not too late now.
Protect Yui.
Okay!
But if Shota's story is true...
The reason why Yui
encountered the Mock Arrancar
was probably because...
Yes?
Matsumoto? It's me.
I went after the Mock Arrancars,
but they got away.
Where are you right now?
I'm taking care of a soul
who was attacked.
I asked him whether he knew anything,
but he's so terrified he can't speak.
Anyway, I'm heading back.
Understood.
We'll head back too.
All right. We'll meet up at...
Captain?!
You bastard!
I'm taking care of a soul
who was attacked.
Could it be that it transformed
into a human soul?
So that's how it stayed hidden
and attacked souls...
Oh no...
I can't follow his Spiritual Pressure either.
Captain Hitsugaya!
Ayasegawa...
I had a call from Rangiku...
Are you all right?
Things have become troublesome...
Huh?
I'll tell you the details
after we go back.
Captain! Are you all right?!
Yeah... I just let my guard down
and dropped my Soul Pager.
Thank goodness...
Where's Madarame?
He's keeping watch over the town.
Captain...There's something
that I've been wondering about.
Something you've
been wondering about?
Yes... It might have something to do
with the appearance of the enemy.
All right... I'll listen to
what you have to say.
The first...?!
Yes... Taking the date and the time
into consideration...
There is a very high possibility
that the first person
that the Mock Arrancar
encountered was Yui.
But how did she survive?
I still don't know yet...
It doesn't seem like
she even remembers.
Yui...
I'm sorry.
Captain Hitsugaya,
what do you think?
Captain?
So that's it...
There's one thing I've figured out.
Does it have anything to do with
what we're talking about?
Yes...
It seems that these Mock Arrancars
can transform into human souls.
Huh?!
By transforming into human souls,
they can hide their Spiritual Pressure
and escape the watch of Soul Society.
They probably approached human souls
in their transformed state
to catch them off their guard
and absorb their spiritual power.
They use that power
to multiply even further.
Furthermore, by cloning themselves,
it is possible for these Mock Arrancars
to absorb many souls at once.
They can gather
an incredible amount of power
in a short amount of time.
They can transform into humans...
It can't be!
I... I...
What of it?!
This has nothing to do with Yui!
Big brother...
Sorry, Shota...
We're still not sure
if that is the case, but...
That's right.
Captain!
Stop!
No!
Why you...
Yui!
He can't perform a Konso?!
Big brother...I...I...
don't know anything...
- Captain...
- It's all right.
- The Arrancar has definitely
- Don't worry.
done something to her.
Well, then...
Unfortunately, we don't know
when she'll show her true form.
She's definitely dangerous.
All right!
Have Soul Society examine this child's
Spiritual Pressure immediately.
We now have all
the reishi samples we need.
Sorry, but please hurry!
Okay.
I never expected the Mock Arrancars
to become the people they attack.
They're increasing
their power in that manner,
and waiting for
the right time to come.
We'll find and crush the main body
before that happens!
You're right.
I'll contact you as soon as
I get results from the analysis.
Until we get those results...
I'm going to have her stay
within a kido barrier.
Why?! You're locking her up?!
You can't! I feel sorry for Yui!
Shota, this is for Yui's sake.
That Arrancar has
done something to her.
No, they might even be after her.
This is a way we can protect her.
Don't you think so?
If she's in the barrier,
the enemy cannot get to her.
It's all right. We'll defeat the Arrancar
in the meantime. Okay?
Believe in us!
Yui, bear with this
for a little while, okay?
But I'm...kind of scared.
Yui...
Oh yeah.
Here!
This is a little different
from the one you had.
Sorry... This is all I can do.
Could you wait inside the barrier?
Okay!
Well... If Yui's fine with it...
Thank you.
Now that it's settled,
I'm going to trade off with Ikkaku.
No. I'll trade off with Madarame.
Ayasegawa,
you go to Urahara's Shop.
Urahara's Shop?
Tell Abarai the situation.
Yes.
Matsumoto, take care of those two.
Understood.
We don't know what
the enemy is going to do...
Don't let your guard down.
It's almost time...
My power is almost at its peak.
Did you sleep well, Yui?
Yeah.
Big brother, I want to go outside.
Sorry... I want to let you out,
but I can't.
I want to see mom and dad.
I want to see them, too, but...
It's all right, big brother...
I can get out of here with your help.
Huh?
Big brother, stand up.
O-Okay.
Big brother, give me your hand.
Like this?
What's this?
Let's go, big brother...
Well, did you discover anything?
Pretty much. Take a look at this.
Oh...This is...
It's as we suspected.
Yui, Shota... Where did they go?
Could it be?!
Matsumoto, what's wrong?
Captain!
The barrier!
What?!
There are still some traces
of Spiritual Pressure...
How was the barrier broken?
Do you suppose that the kids did it?
I don't know.
Anyway, let's look for them.
Yeah.
Captain Ukitake.
About your request...
We have the results.
Huh?
Matsumoto, you go look for them.
I'll catch up with you
after I hear what he has to say.
Understood.
So what are the results?
We've concluded that
Yui Toyokawa is a clone
created by the Mock Arrancar.
A clone?
She probably had strong potential
spiritual power as a human.
It all began when she encountered
the Mock Arrancar...
We believe that
the Mock Arrancar absorbed
Yui Toyokawa's spiritual power
by chance.
The Arrancar then had
an explosive gain in power
and developed the ability
to multiply its clones
and gather power for its main body.
He then used that method
to increase his power
in a short amount of time by
absorbing a large amount of souls.
I see...
But it seemed like that girl
was moving of her own accord.
No, the enemy is controlling her.
- There's a high possibility that it's all an act.
- Say, Yui...
What is it?
- If that's the case...
- Where are we going?
If we destroy the main body...
She'll disappear too.
- That's what it means.
- Just follow me.
O-Okay...
If Yui Toyokawa has
strong spiritual power,
then what about
her older brother, Shota?
There is a possibility for relatives
to have the same level of spiritual power.
I see!
She used Shota's power
to break my Kyomon!
The enemy is after
Shota's spiritual power!
Shota... Where did you go?
There they are!
Shota! Yui!
Ms. Rangiku!
How did you break that barrier?!
It was easy to get out of that!
Don't go! Come back!
Don't interfere...
Yui?
Yui?!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
They've come!
My, my...
It looks like they're all prepared.
Big brother...come here...
But...
Shota! Don't go!
Big brother...
Why is my body
moving on its own?!
Shota!
Yui...
Big brother...
Crap...
Yui!
Yui?!
B-Big brother...
Don't...
Yui?! What's wrong?!
Don't!
Don't, big brother...
Don't come near me!
Akon, there's a letter from
Third Seat Madarame
asking when the item he ordered
is going to be completed.
His order?
He wanted molars.
Oh! I forgot!
All right!
We'll send him this empty box
and tell him that they're molars
that are invisible to idiots.
Is that all right?
It should be.
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Hello. Today I'm going to tell you
the Arrancar's numbers.
UNDECIMO               TRECE
QUINCE              DIECISEIS
The Arrancars are numbered
according to their birth order,
starting from eleven.
DIEZ
The ones with particularly
SEIS
deadly killing abilities
are numbered from one through ten
by order of strength.
ESPADA
Those ten are called the Espada.
Just between you and me,
Ulquiorra's number is...
It's still not the time to reveal that.
You're no fun.