Which should I choose…Is this too loud?
But this is a rare chance
to go the beach,
so maybe I could take
a small chance and…
No…but it's embarrassing
to show my navel…
What's the problem?
You don't have anything
up top to show anyway,
so they're all the same!
Leave me alone!
I think I'll go with this one.
So, what are you going to buy?
Please,  just leave me alone!
Oh, Lady Yoruichi, you're wonderful!
Oh, come on! Let me help you out!
She's dashing, even when choosing swimwear!
No, please stop!
Don't be so shy!
Oh, no, no!
I have to find
my own swimwear!
Soi Fon!
I picked out swimwear
for you, too!
Huh?
PINK LAMÉ
This one!
What…no way…
that's lame…too childish…
No, wait a minute!
There's no way Lady Yoruichi's
choice would be wrong!
But…but am I okay with that?
Even if she is Lady Yoruichi,
there are times when
I have to stand my ground!
L-Lady Yoruichi! I think I'll
go with this yellow one…
I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
Lady Yoruichi…
I envy her…
Captain Soi Fon is petite,
so she has a variety of
swimsuit styles to choose from…
There's nothing cute
in a larger size…
Sis!
Huh?
I found the perfect swimsuit
just for you!
SEXY
W-Wait a minute, Kiyone!
No way! I can't wear that…
Oh, I think it's lovely.
SEXY
I've decided on this one,
– What?!
and it's a good opportunity,
so choose that one, Isane.
B-But, Captain…
Choose that one, Isane.
Y-Yes, m'am…forgive me…
And that's how it is…
The Women's Soul Reapers
Association
has come to the World
of the Living for R&R!
"And that's how it is" my ass!
Allow me to explain
what happened.
The truth is,
the pool that the Women's
Soul Reapers Association
had secretly been building in
the Soul Society was destroyed…
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Oh damn, he found it…
Stingy Byakky!
We were discovered because
you brazenly built it in
the middle of the yard!
I'm sorry.
Next time,
I will fully equip it with
a device that will
intercept Captain Kuchiki.
That's not the issue!
But…really,
what are we going to do now?
Build it in a new location?
But where?
I understand the problem.
Captain!
Call me "Executive Director" here.
Y-Yes, sir…
Do you have a good idea?
Yes, I do.
This is a good opportunity for
all of us to go for R&R
at a beach in
the World of the Living.
– What?!
All right! The beach!
Do you understand now?
What were
you people thinking?!
It's all good, Ichigo.
Because of that,
you got to come to the beach
with all these
bathing-suit beauties.
Be thankful!
Ichigo, this is a good opportunity.
You should show your gratitude
towards all the people
who've helped you
from day to day.
Isn't that right, Big Brother?
Why're you here, Byakuya?
I came because they
wanted to apologize
for building a bathing place
on my mansion grounds.
Big Brother,
please enjoy the World of
the Living beach at your leisure.
Does this constitute
as an apology?
Come now,
don't think too hard, Ichigo.
Let's all have a great time today!
Ukitake, you're all here too?
I invited Captain Ukitake.
I thought it'd be nice if he got
some outside air once in a while.
We're here because Rangiku invited
us saying she prefers it lively.
We had nothing to do, anyway.
And that's how it is.
I've been feeling better lately,
and this is a nice change of pace.
Soaking in the rays of
the summer sun feels great…
Ukitake!
Captain!
Forgive me…
I suddenly felt dizzy…
Maybe you shouldn't
have come, after all?
We should cool him down
with some ice, perhaps?
That's an idea…
Somebody, go to that seaside kiosk
and bring back some ice.
All right. I'll go.
I'm coming with you.
Excuse me.
Could you spare us some ice?
Sure!
Inoue?!
Hi there, Kurosaki!
What're you doing here?!
Working part-time.
You're making a racket, Kurosaki!
Ishida?!
Sado is here, too.
Why're you all…
Didn't you hear?
Captain Unohana
asked them to do this.
Soul Reapers are my enemy,
but I can't say no
to Unohana's request.
That's how it is, Ichigo.
We rented out
the entire beach today.
We can't spread
our wings as we'd like
in the presence of people
from the World of the Living.
You went though all that effort?
So Kurosaki, you were
saying something about ice?
Oh, that's right!
We need it to
cool down Ukitake
who collapsed from
too much direct sunlight.
Oh dear! I'll get it right away.
Toshiro! Ice, please!
Good grief…
That's why I warned him
not to over do it…
Toshiro! You're here, too?
Why aren't you
with everyone else?
I can't stand the heat.
We're having Toshiro
make the ice we use here
at this seaside kiosk
with Hyorinmaru.
What?!
Is it okay to use your Zanpakuto
for something like that?
Shut up.
You don't want the ice?
Oh, sorry! Make us some.
Reign over the Frosted Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Take it with you.
It's too huge!
Then I'll take half.
I'm going to make
a test batch of
the "curry mitsumame dasheen
frappe" I thought up earlier!
I'll share some
with everyone later.
That menu item…
sounds lethal…
Captain Ukitake,
are you feeling better now?
Sorry to cause you worry.
Thanks to you all, I'm fine now!
See?
No, don't force yourself…
Okay.
Ukitake, why did you
gather everyone here?
Oh, that's right!
The Inaugural
Beach Arts Competition?
Essentially, it's a contest about
building various objects with sand
and choosing the best one.
I will be the judge.
That's all there is.
Okay then,
please break up
into groups of two or
three people and begin.
We're at the ocean,
but we're playing with sand?
I'd rather break watermelons
or have a test of courage.
The winner will receive
a cash prize envelope
from the Head Captain!
– We're on our way!
They're so about the money!
What should we do,
Big Brother?
I'm not interested
in the prize money,
but I'm not averse to
showing off our artistic sense.
Let's go, Rukia.
Yes, sir!
Are you going to participate?
I'm fine just watching.
I'm not good at
this sort of thing, either…
Come to think of it, Shihoin and
Soi Fon aren't here either…
They said they were
going to catch fish
and went diving in the morning.
They haven't come back since.
Think they're all right?
Those two won't
have any problems.
Is there a bucket somewhere?
We have to wet the sand first…
We don't need a bucket.
Huh?
Because you see…
If we press our breasts together
to create cleavage,
we can put water there
and carry it!
I see!
Okay, shall we give it a try?
Hold your breasts like this and…
What're you doing
in broad daylight!
Breast buckets.
Disallowed!
What? Why?
Because it's not
educationally proper!
Who cares about that…
You can't do this,
so you're jealous, aren't you?
Leave me alone!
Were your breasts that big?
Uh…welll…
Wh-What're you doing?!
What's the matter?
Nanao has pads in her top!
You don't have to say it!
Okay, does that
look done to you?
Not yet!
Next we need to see who
opens the castle gates first.
You're both on!
No, forget it…
I'm not interested in
such a childish contest…
Huh?! Is that supposed to be
an excuse or something?!
Are you afraid of losing?!
Huh?!
Okay, you're on!
Go for it! I'm not going to lose!
That's what I was going to say!
What's wrong, Ikkaku?
Is Ikkaku-san buried alive?!
Let's dig him out, Renji!
It worked great!
They sure are a rowdy bunch.
Can't they work more quietly?
Rukia, do not be concerned
with what goes on around you.
Focus on your own work.
Yes! Forgive me, Big Brother.
Okay. Quite nicely done.
Should I make
the arms a little bigger?
Big Brother is so talented!
What a polished
aesthetic sense…
As I thought, I still cannot
hold a candle to him…
At the very least, I must try
my very best not to hold him back…
They may not be related,
but they're two peas in a pod.
It's hot…
In this heat, I'll collapse again
and cause everyone to worry…
Forgive me, Sentaro…
I'm going to lie down a while.
Wake me when it's time.
Yes, sir!
I wish they'd put a flush toilet
in the seaside kiosk.
Kiyone! You're back already?
Hey! What're you doing,
Kotsubaki?
Fool!
I'm building a wall of sand
so the sea breeze doesn't strike
the captain while he's sleeping!
Stupid…
What're you talking about!
You have to block the sun's rays
before the sea breeze!
I'll go pick some flowers!
We'll gently block
the sun's rays with flowers!
What?
Then I'll light incense
so the captain can
sleep more comfortably!
What do you suppose this is?
My, my, this is a wonderful
creation that appeals to the heart.
I think this is a pretty bad joke…
Everybody! Lunch service!
Fried noodles and rice balls
specially made by
the seaside kiosk.
Eat with care.
We have drinks, as well.
Uh…If you put it there…
It sort of looks like
a funerary offering…
My, my, when you add all this,
Captain Ukitake's team
would appear to be the winner.
What?
Was Captain Ukitake
in the competition?
Oh? Am I mistaken?
Beats me…
Hey, Ikkaku! Are you all right?
Damn Crab…
I'll bury you bastards…
It's ruined!
What was that?!
Lieutenant Kotetsu!
Lieutenant Ise!
Watch where you're touching!
The vine is going
inside my swimsuit!
Oh my… That's awesome!
If I take a photo, I could probably
sell it for a good price.
What an uncaring thing to say!
So it appeared, after all…
Unohana! What do you mean?!
Truth be told…
It was once rumored that
a peculiar Hollow with
immense Spiritual Pressure
appeared at this beach.
"Once rumored"?
Why did you choose a place
like that for our R&R trip?!
Forget that Ichigo!
Rescuing Lieutenants Ise
and Kotetsu comes first!
You're right!
Ishida! Chad!
El Directo!
What?!
Spiritual Pressure attacks
are useless…
What do you mean?
Those vines have the power to
absorb radiated Spiritual Pressure.
We can't inflict damage by any
means other than a direct attack.
You mean we have to slash it
with a Zanpakuto?
Damn!
I don't have my Substitute
Soul Reaper Combat Pass
or any Gikongan right now,
so I can't become a Soul Reaper!
Rangiku! Rukia!
We're here on R&R.
We had no reason to
bring our Zanpakuto.
Sorry, Ichigo.
I left Chappy at the seaside kiosk.
Renji!
I figured something
like this might happen,
so I brought Zabimaru with me!
Roar, Zabi…ma…ru!
Renji!
Ichigo, here it comes!
Where's Byakuya?!
I haven't seen Big Brother
for a while.
Where did he go
at a time like this?!
What about Ukitake?
The captain is asleep.
We have to protect
the captain at all cost!
I know that!
We have to do
something with just us!
Inoue!
Kurosaki!
Kurosaki! Sado and I
will take over here.
In the meantime, go and get your
Substitute Soul Reaper Combat Pass!
Gotcha. Thanks!
What the—?!
Damn!
Kill all enemy with your venom,
Suzumebachi.
What're you waiting for?
You're being lax, Ichigo!
Yoruichi!
We were going after
sharks in the ocean
when Abarai dropped in
from above,
so we became worried
and raced back here.
What in the world is going on?
What is this monster?
I slept well.
Captain!
He didn't wake up even once
despite all this commotion…
Is that man all right?
Oh! You started the watermelon
breaking already?
Watermelon breaking?
He's right!
It tastes like watermelon!
You finally caught on?
Big Brother! What's going on?
Let me be the one to explain.
This is a watermelon-breaking event
planned by Captains Kuchiki
and Ukitake and myself.
Exactly.
What?!
Then that story earlier?
It was a story I made up
to warm up the place.
What?
This is a special
watermelon developed
by the Department of
Research and Development
for use against Hollows.
Did she just say
an anti-Hollow watermelon?
What possible use could it have?
A day at the beach is synonymous
with watermelon breaking,
so I asked the acting
assistant chairwoman
and had them bring it here.
Is it to your satisfaction?
Perfect!
So this is a little surprise
from the captains?
Did you enjoy it, everyone?
How are we supposed to
enjoy this?
Captain…
Say, Icchi,
let's eat some watermelon!
You mean you can eat this?
Everyone, it's not over yet.
Huh?
We've prepared watermelon
for everyone.
All right then, everyone,
enjoy watermelon breaking
to your heart's content.
W-Wait a minute!
Let the watermelon
breaking game begin!
Cut it out!
Ahh, Captain skipped out!
Quiet.
I told you,
I can't stand the heat.
With all you men here,
you have no opinions
about our swimsuits?
Isn't complimenting us
the proper thing to do?!
That's asking too much of them.
Are you implying you'll say
something if we take them off?!
Stop it!
Let me go, Nanao!
Okay, I'll take it off
if that's what you want!
– You're drunk, aren't you?
– Let go!
Today's segment is about
Toshiro Hitsugaya's Hyorinmaru.
Reign over the Frosted Heaven!
Hyorinmaru!
Captain Hitsugaya's Hyorimaru
is the most powerful of
the ice and snow Zanpakuto,
and creates a giant dragon
of water and ice.
Its Bankai form is
Daiguren Hyorinmaru.
Its power is immense,
but it is a sad Zanpakuto
that ordinarily has no use
other than to make ice.
It's not sad.
You're the only one
who thinks that!