You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
To have fought this much,
and still be standing is admirable.
But the fact is that you have
yet to reach Bankai.
Do you wish to continue, Ichigo?
Why do you even bother
asking such a stupid question?
I don’t have time.
Come at me with all you’ve got!
Very well! Let’s do it, Ichigo!
P-Please stop! Lieutenant!
Please put down your sword!
Lieutenant Abarai!
R-Renji… Why are you doing this?
Just a little farther…
just a little…
Just a little while longer now
and I can be there to save you.
I will never let them execute you!
This…Spiritual Pressure…
Captain Kuchiki…
Where are you going, Renji?
I’m going to…save Rukia.
No.
I’m going!
You refuse to let me pass
no matter what?
I don’t intend to repeat myself.
He’s coming!
Senka.
A special Flash Step with a spin,
where you get behind your opponent
to destroy his Soul Chain and
Soul Sleep at the same time.
I’ve seen it countless times.
It’s your favorite move.
I knew your moves logically.
But now my body is fast enough
to counter you, at last.
Captain Kuchiki! You can no longer
kill me with that sword!
You talk a lot.
What makes you so confident?
You think you countered
my sword with that level of skill?
Scatter.
I told you… You can’t kill me
with that sword anymore!
It’s not just since
I became your lieutenant…
Long before I even joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
The one I wanted to surpass…
was always you, Captain Kuchiki!
You released your zanpakuto
without calling its name.
Does this mean that you..?
I will surpass you, Captain Kuchiki…
There’s no more time…
and your body has reached its limits.
If you continue, you may die before
you reach the Bankai.
Do you still wish to continue, Ichigo?
Ban…kai!
Hihio Zabimaru.
You… when did you achieve Bankai?
Of course, you wouldn’t have noticed.
Not someone like you
who never pays attention
to anybody below him.
I’ll say it again!
I’m going to save Rukia!
I said I wouldn’t repeat myself.
If you won’t let me pass…
I’ll take you down and go!
Impossible.
You won’t be able to make me fall
on even one knee.
I see… its pressure is at
the level of Bankai for sure.
However, it isn’t enough.
Scatter…
Senbonzakura!
Senbonzakura…
A thousand blades,
each too small for the eye to see.
When the blades fly,
they turn and reflect the sunlight,
resembling a thousand
flower petals falling.
I know it.
Unfortunately for you, my sword’s joints
are connected by my Spiritual Pressure.
Your blades can’t cut through them!
Just now,
I purposely disconnected the joints…
in order to counter all of
your thousand blades.
Why’re you so surprised?
I’m just telling you…
I can see your sword!
I got you down on your knee!
I will defeat you!
Let’s bring down the curtain,
Byakuya Kuchiki.
On the battle between you and me.
Bring down the curtain…?
Very well. Then I shall bring down
the curtain with my sword.
What?!
The sword that ends this…
will be mine!
Hado 33
Sokatsui!
He’s discarded the incantation!
He can do this much damage with
a mid-level Kido without Spirit Chant?!
You’re naïve!
You thought that I’d lose
sight of you with this?
Damn! I lost control!
You’re the one that’s naïve.
I didn’t release my Kido in order to
obscure my movements from you.
I did it to interrupt the rhythm
of your Bankai.
The weakness of Bankai
lies in its sheer size
reflecting its Spiritual Pressure.
Because of its shape and size that
surpasses the norm of a blade,
in order to control all of
its movements completely,
one must have over a decade
of training after learning Bankai.
Renji, you are not ready to
use your Bankai in battle.
So what?
I already knew all of
that when I came here.
Luckily, my zanpakuto
is pretty tough!
Losing a joint changes nothing!
Bakudo 61, Rikujokoro.
Damn!
You should have simply
put your sword down.
Do you still think
you can defeat me?
Surely, you haven’t forgotten?
That I too have Bankai.
Bankai.
Scatter.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi!
A thousand blades that rise
from the ground…
With their scattering,
infinitely more blades then rise.
Impossible to know their numbers.
Impossible to even read their path,
much less avoid them.
Nothing to do but watch,
as one watches the wind pass.
One can do nothing
but stand there frozen,
and then be swept away
from this world.
Shall I tell you the difference
between you and me?
It’s class.
A beast may see the moon reflected
on the water’s surface.
But trying to capture it will
only result in sinking into the water.
Your fang will never reach me…
Never.
But be proud of the fact
that you were felled by this blade
yet you still retain a human form.
So you can still breathe?
Do not move.
You will only hasten your death.
It’s not over…
I can still…fight!
Did you not hear me?
I told you not to move.
I shall compliment you.
You received my Bankai
and are still alive.
However, if you move again,
I will not go easy on you.
My blades will carve you into pieces.
You must have noticed.
Your Bankai is gone.
When one’s Bankai disappears
against its master’s will,
it means the master’s end is near.
Soon, you will fade away.
I shall ask you this once more.
Will you still speak nonsense
about saving Rukia?
I can’t breathe…
It’s like the Spiritual Pressure
is turning me into ash.
I can’t even lift a finger…
I can’t…
In the end…
this man and I were too far apart,
after all.
Will you still stand, Ichigo?
Of course!
What?
I swore…
…that I’d save her!
Swore? To whom?
No one…
Just on…
– my soul!
Stronger than Byakuya Kuchiki?
What a goal you have.
You’d better just stay away
from her from now on.
She understands, too.
That she’s different from us.
It’s so complicated.
Isn’t it annoying?
It’s always a lot harder to draw,
than to tear it.
And It’s much harder to tie
than to unravel.
Dammit…
Admirable.
Your fang…
definitely reached me.
Renji?
No way…
Until now, it was so powerful,
I couldn’t figure out whose it was…
The Spiritual Pressure that just faded…
definitely belonged to Renji!
Why? Why did you… Renji?!
Good morning. How are you, Rukia?
Gin…Ichimaru!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
The rules of Squad 11!
One, your zanpakuto must be
a direct attack type!
One, if you must die,
die gloriously in a fight!
One, obey the Lieutenant’s orders
at all costs!
– Now, wait a minute!
Any complaints, Shiny Duo?!
– No giving us a duo nickname!
Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya!
You are so stuck up!
Squad 13 Captain,
Jushiro Ukitake!
Your long hair is against the rules!
Squad 6 Lieutenant,
Renji Abarai!
Hey, are you challenging me?!
Squad 6 Captain,
Byakuya Kuchiki!
You are so cool…
Squad 5 Captain,
Sosuke Aizen!
Do those glasses have lenses in them?
Squad 3 Captain,
Gin Ichimaru!
Wipe that smirk off your face!