Spring…
A time when everyone
sets off for new places
full of hope in their hearts…
That's Spring.
But I had long lost any hopes
for the new season.
Mizuiro?! Where are you?
Weren't you listening to
what I said last night?!
I told you not to call
because I'm busy today!
Child, you're always like this!
You should try putting yourself
in my shoes sometimes…
CALL TIME
00:04:17
Calling your mother again?
You're such a good son.
I don't have a mother.
There you go talking
like that again…
You'll make your mother cry.
Here. Your jacket.
Today's your school
entrance ceremony, right?
Shall I drive you there?
Thanks.
Hello, hello.
Mizuiro to world.
Come in world.
Is our cord connected correctly?
My world appears to be
spinning correctly.
All systems green.
Communications…
failure.
Brother Ichi! Get up!
Breakfast time!
You'll be late for school!
All done.
Looks delicious!
I'm outta here!
What?! Big Brother,
what about breakfast?
Sorry, Yuzu!
I'll be back before noon,
so just leave it there!
Oh pooh!
I already fried you an egg!
Captain Aizen, may I have
a moment of your time?
Sure Hinamori, come in.
"Endure, no matter what"
Very well done.
It shows your free-flowing style
very well.
Thank you very much!
Oh, and this is my report
for the lieutenants meeting.
All right. I'll look it over.
Matsumoto! Are you here?
Where are you?!
What, you're not here?
But if you're not here,
why's this room reek of liquor…
Oh…Captain…
Join me for a drink?
You know I won't!
But never mind that.
Where's your report?!
Isn't today
the lieutenants meeting?!
Hey! Don't fall asleep!
Listen to…me?
Stop that…not there…
For crying out loud…
what's this woman dreaming about?!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Huh? You haven't started yet?
Thank goodness…
Just take your seat and wait.
Y-Yes!
Matsumoto hasn't come…
Probably got a hangover again.
She's always doing that!
Hey, Kusajishi!
Those are sweets I brought,
you know!
Where's your "thank you"?!
Mare-rin, the things you say
are awfully stingy for a rich guy!
What?!
Keep it down!
Ow ow ow…
Your voices boom in my head!
Keep quiet!
My, are you nursing a hangover,
too, Lieutenant Iba?
It's spring.
Yup. This is the best cure
for a hangover.
KARAKURA FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
A new uniform…
A new school, eh?
Guess I should
start feeling like…
How any normal
new students should feel…
Are you listening to me?
Anyway, this goes way beyond
the school regulations
or anything like that!
Your entire head is bright yellow!
Hey, Sado!
Yasutora Sado!
Aren't you going to say hi?
Well?
Who're you?
I'm Reiichi Oshima
from Togata Junior High!
Are you mocking me, dammit!
You boys there?!
Bug off!
I've got a beef with this guy!
Mi…zu…i…ro!
T-T-Trouble, Mizuiro!
Morning, Keigo.
You have to hear this!
There's big trouble!
You're awfully hyper
this morning, Keigo.
Mashiba Junior High's
Chad and Kurosaki?
That's right!
Seems the both of them
enrolled in this school!
Seriously!
So, why are you crying?
You…moron!
Chad and Kurosaki are pedigreed
super juvenile delinquents!
That they're in close
with the Yakuza,
that they're smuggling in drugs,
that they go into
book stores and
browse porno for
five hours at a time!
The dark rumors about them
are countless!
Those are rumors.
You've never met them,
so you don't what
sort of people they are.
What're you saying?!
This is Chad and Kurosaki
we're talking about!
What do you mean "don't know
what sort of people they are"?!
– Let's see…
– One's a wicked,
– First, each class assembles
– orange-haired fighter who dyed his
– for a short homeroom,
– hair from the day he was born, and
– followed by the ceremony…
– the other's a 2-meter-tall giant!
Oh, the class assignments
are posted.
Look, it says we're
both in class 1-3.
You can see that from here?
Your eyes are pretty good
Huh?
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
YASUTORA SADO
N-No way!
Something that must never
happen became reality!
What's the matter?
Our youth…just ended…
– Hey, that's Kojima.
– You mean yours did, right?
– Don't you think Kojima
– We have no tomorrow…
– is sort of hot?
– You sure exaggerate, man…
Yes, he is.
– He's like…not overly driven…
– So long,
– a non-aggressive type, you know.
– my fresh new high school life.
And he seems unbothered,
yet sweet.
I know.
Like he's going to heal you!
I'm not driven, only because
I don't have any expectations.
Or any anger…
My smile is nothing
more than a pose.
I can do it to anyone,
anytime, anywhere.
Oh, this is the room!
Let's see…
Where is…Tatsuki?
You're off guard!
Wow!
Very good, Orihime!
You can't catch me
off guard anymore…Tatsuki…
Yep, you pass!
You've improved your reflexes.
That's because you're
a good teacher, Tatsuki.
But please stop with
the surprise attack tests.
You'll scare everyone.
Bon jour, Mademoiselle.
Wh-Wh-Who are you?
A-Are you all right?
H-How do you do?
I am Chizuru Honsho, and I have
become a member of this class.
What'd you do that for,
you violent woman!
What?!
And what were you planning
to do to Orihime?!
Out with it!
Orihime…
Such a lovely name,
so appropriate for my new Venus…
I said cut it out, you airhead!
This is nothing!
This violence will not
make my love waver!
Damn you!
You want more, you pervert!
Stop it, Tatsuki!
You'll end up killing her!
Is something the matter?
I brought flowers today again.
Mom, that man is
talking to the flowers!
Stop that. It's rude to point!
Come on,
what's really bothering you?
Well you see…
something's odd…
Huh?
Something about the sky is odd…
and I'm afraid…
Afraid of… the sky?
Hey, what's the matter, Karin!
We're going to be late for school!
What's wrong?
Did it start raining or something?
Um, I'm really not sure, but…
The sky seems heavy somehow…
Is it the usual old person again?
If you're wondering about him,
he's right next you, Yuzu.
What? You're kidding, right?
Where?
Next, is the matter of
the vacancy position of
a Konpaku Monitoring Officer
stationed at 3600
on the World of the Living axis.
Currently, a member from our
squad is in charge of this area,
but he has been
on extended absence
due to a worsening
of his chronic cramps.
Come on! A swift kick to the back
will fix that up right away!
No, cramps are painful…
We need to let him rest…
Lieutenant Sasakibe!
Yes?
I would like to recommend
Rukia Kuchiki from our squad.
Your reasons?
Sir.
For some time now,
Captain Ukitake has
wanted to place Kuchiki
in a stationed officer position
in the World of Living
to gain experience
as a Soul Reaper.
I see, Captain Ukitake
recommended her?
Yes!
All right.
Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13
will be the replacement.
Proceed to the next matter.
Yes. In regard to the vacancy
position of lieutenant of Squad 6,
the Captain's Meeting has chosen
Renji Abarai,
Sixth Seat of Squad 11.
Huh?!
The guy's a punk!
That guy serving as lieutenant,
will scar the name of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
Mare-rin's bald head
will be scarred, too!
What're you doing?!
I'm not bald,
and I won't be scarred!
Are these…orders of transfer?
No, no!
Nothing so serious as a "transfer"!
It's resident officer duty
in the World of the Living!
You remember, a long time ago,
when you first joined us,
you came along to assist me!
Remember? That's all it is!
Uh…umm…
You see, she doesn't remember!
It was a bad experience,
so she erased it from her brain!
Right, Kuchiki!
Uh…umm…
Hey, you're bothering us!
Why don't you stay
buried in the garden!
What?! And why don't you just go
hang yourself from the eaves!
Uh…
Your resident duty station
is one Reiri radius area
with a town called Karakura
at the center…
It shouldn't be that difficult
of an assignment
with your level of skills.
Captain Ukitake!
C-Captain?!
You mustn't be up!
You need to rest!
Well, I was feeling
better today, so…
And even though it's a short
assignment of about a month,
I thought Kuchiki might
have some anxieties
about her first solo
resident officer assignment,
so I came to see her off.
Th-Thank you very much!
Stop with the formalities.
Have you told Byakuya?
Oh! No, not yet…
Uh…no…
Captain Kuchiki
will no doubt say…
"Don't report to me each time
about something so minor."
That's why I plan to leave
without letting him know…
I see.
I understand.
If that's how you feel,
that's fine.
I'll let Byakuya know.
You can leave rest assured.
Yes, sir!
With this, Renji Abarai,
Sixth Seat of Squad 11
LETTER OF APPOINTMENT
is appointed lieutenant
of Squad 6.
Congratulations, Abarai!
Uh…Thanks!
I mean…
I humbly accept,
Lieutenant Hinamori!
You don't have to be so formal…
But, well…
This is a good thing.
Now you're a step closer again
to Byakuya Kuchiki.
Ikkaku…
Isn't it about time already…
that you told your friend Rukia?
Regardless of whether
she's nobility now,
as a lieutenant,
you're more than equals…
You worked hard for 40 years.
I'd say it's about time
things return to
the way they were
between you two.
Then you'd better hurry.
I believe Kuchiki is
leaving in the afternoon
for the World of the Living for
a month of resident officer duty.
Oh no! Abarari, let's hurry!
No…
I'm not officially appointed until
the appointment ceremony
a month from now.
When she comes back,
I'll pop the news that I've become
a lieutenant and surprise her.
My rosy youth!
Why…
Why, Why did this
have to happen?!
Ch-Chad and Kurosaki?!
Wh-Wh-What's is this?
This can't be right?!
This unbelievable
way we're getting
sucked in to this
can't be happening!
Is this a nightmare?
Could it be a nightmare?!
You're too noisy…
Did you think you could get away,
Kurosaki…Chad…
It's Reiichi Oshima from
Togata Junior High!
Say, Keigo…
How're you so informed
about delinquent types?
And just so you know, their names
were all on our class roster.
Who are you supposed to be?
Are you with Kurosaki?
God no!
We've never seen or met
each other before now!
I'm Mizuiro Kojima from
Hiiragi Second Junior High.
I'm in class 1-3.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations,
Mizuiro Kojima has joined his side!
No he hasn't. No he hasn't!
Mizuiro! Mizuiro!
What're you doing?
Come back!
You're not that kind of kid!
Mizuiro! Mizuiro!
– Class 1-3?
– Hey, are you listening?!
– I'm in 1-3, too.
– Mizuiro! Master Mizuiro!
– I'm Ichigo Kurosaki
– Mizuiro-poo! Mizuiro-boy!
and this big guy is Yasutora Sado.
Ow, could you not
step on me there?
Good to meet you.
Um, could someone help me?
– And who's that?
– Please? Ah!
Mizuiro!
– Keigo Asano.
– Mizuiro!
He doesn't do well in school,
but he's a bright guy.
And he's likable and doesn't lie.
He's a hundred times
better than me.
You're incredible.
Huh?
I mean…I think it's pretty rare
for someone who could
say so many nice things
about his friend, when asked.
Kojima, are you good at excuses?
I'm so good it's sick.
Okay.
Then think one up in five minutes.
A really good one that won't get us
suspended even if we rescue Asano!
Who shall I tell of this joy.
They were different
than what we imagined.
Hmm…yeah, maybe they were…
How different were they?
Way different.
Sometimes I think…
We're all connected to this world
with countless cords.
And like the patient
in intensive care,
we desperately try to
not cut even one.
But the truth is,
no matter how hard we try,
they break at the point
they're connected.
Aren't you going to
call Nanako today?
It's difficult to reattach the cord
to its original location…
I still can't do it.
No, I don't feel like it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Hello, hello?
Calling the new world.
I'm glad I met you.
Does it appear our cords
will connect properly?
Is my world spinning properly?
System: all red.
Communications:
Good.
Oh yes…
I sense a powerful Spirit Energy…
AND SO, THE BLADE IS SWUNG
Abarai, I hear you're
going to the beach.
I have work to do, so I can't go,
but I want you to
get some photos in my place
for the Seireitei Bulletin.
Of Rangiku in a swimsuit, right?
I didn't say that…
– You don't want them?
– Please get them.
You should've just said so
at the start!
In today's segment we'll cover
Rangiku Matsumoto's Haineko.
Growl, Haineko!
Haineko's power lies in the way
the sword turns into ashes,
which then slice to pieces
anything that they land on
with a single swing of the hilt.
It is a powerful Zanpakuto,
but as Matsumoto puts it,
it is a very petulant,
lazy and stupid sword
that is difficult to handle.
It really has a mind of its own…
Who could it have taken after?
Isn't it quite obvious?