Shall I show you?
Shall I show you...
...what's under this eyepatch?
An artificial eye?
My left eye is a doll's.
It can see things that
should remain unseen,
so I usually keep it covered.
Do you feel ill?
This might not be a good place for you,
since you're not used to it.
Not a good place?
The dolls...
Dolls are hollow, you see.
Completely hollow, in body and soul.
That void connects them with death.
But hollow things seek to fill their emptiness.
Don't you feel as though this
place is drawing something out of you?
Yeah.
We should go.
It's more comfortable upstairs.
Do you live around here?
Yes.
That thing about "Yomi at Twilight"...
Is that the name of this shop?
Feel free to drop in. -Studio M
What is Studio M?
Kirika's studio.
It's on the second floor.
Kirika?
The person who makes these dolls.
The ones in the basement, too?
Yes, I think they're all Kirika's.
Why does that doll...
...look so much like you?
Who knows?
When I first met you,
weren't you holding a doll?
Yes.
I heard a girl died
at the hospital that day.
Was it for her?
I mean, um...
I think her name was Misaki, or Masaki.
Something like that.
Do you have any sisters?
Apparently, she was an only daughter,
so her parents were devastated.
Why are you...
Why indeed.
I have no other customers.
Do you have something else to ask me?
Well, yes.
A few things seem strange to me.
Like...
I warned you not to get close to me.
But it may be too late.
Too late?
You don't know a thing about it, do you?
There's an old story in this town...
...about the class 3 of 26 years ago.
I'm guessing nobody has told you.
There was a student in that class...
...who excelled in sports and her studies.
She was kind to everyone.
She was loved by teachers
and students alike.
But shortly after starting 9th grade, she died.
How?
The story I heard said she was in
a plane crash with her family.
But there are several other theories.
Some say it was a car accident.
Others claim she died in a house fire.
Regardless, everyone in the
class was terribly shocked.
They were overcome with grief.
But then, suddenly, someone said,
"She isn't dead."
He pointed at her desk and said,
"Look, she's right there.
See? She's alive and well."
Then, other students started
saying the same thing.
"It's true, she's not dead."
That behavior spread through
the rest of the class, like a chain reaction.
They didn't want to believe the truth.
They didn't want to accept the cruel reality.
I'm sure you can relate.
Everyone in the class
continued with that act,
insisting that the girl was still alive.
Even the homeroom teacher
took their side, declaring,
"It's true, she's alive.
So all of you should continue
to work hard as a team,
until the day you all graduate together."
The principal even arranged to have her seat
included in the graduation ceremony.
Is this... a true story?
Then, after graduation,
everyone gathered in the
classroom for the class photo.
The whole class, including the teacher.
But when they looked at the
photo, they noticed something.
There in the photo, off to the side,
they could see the girl
who should have been gone.
Her face was deathly pale,
but she smiled like all the others.
That girl...
The student who died...
...was named Misaki.
There's more to this story.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Yeah, I'm okay.
I just got a little sidetracked.
I'm heading home now.
I hate those devices.
You can be found, and caught, anywhere.
It's closing time.
Please go on home now.
1998 Midterm Exam Schedule
Grade 9 Exam Dates
Math | Science
Social Studies | Japanese
Once exams are over,
we start career counseling...
Having to discuss that
formally with a teacher
is so depressing.
These days, high school
acceptance rates are over 95%.
So don't worry.
There's a high school out
there even you could get into.
Is that supposed to encourage me?
That was my intent.
Where are you gonna go?
West High.
Are your grades that high?
I'm working on them.
Oh yeah?
Ah...
Well, good luck with that.
At any rate, you're stuck
with me until graduation.
Keep your strength up!
You're stuck?
We've been together since 2nd grade.
We're even neighbors.
When we were kids,
we did all kinds of stupid stuff together.
But now he's turned into
this pseudo-honors student
who can't keep up with my improv.
To me, it just looks like
you haven't changed.
I've changed a lot!
What do you know about me?
I know things about you
that even you don't know.
Like what?
That's how we're stuck with each other.
Makes sense.
So, what are you gonna do about high school?
Go back to Tokyo?
Yeah.
My dad will be back in Japan by next spring.
You'll go to a private school there?
Probably.
That's one way, I guess.
What do you mean?
Maybe I'll go to a private
school in Tokyo, too.
What school are you going to, Kouichi?
K High.
K High, huh?
Akazawa, you're going to Tokyo?
If I do, I suppose I'll live on my own.
Weren't you going to that
Sacred Heart something-or-other
girls' school?
I never said I wanted to go there!
Another one who's trying too hard for nothing.
Sakakibara?
Didn't you bring an umbrella?
No.
I didn't think I'd need one.
Um...
Would you like to walk home with me, then?
My house is just past yours.
But... I couldn't ask you to do that.
It's no big deal.
Come on, let's go.
By the way, what do you do
for class trips here?
We went to Tokyo, last year.
We went to a big amusement park,
and to the top of Tokyo Tower.
It was so much fun.
You went to Tokyo, huh?
I love Tokyo. There are so
many fun things to do.
I wish I could go to school there...
Why don't you?
My family can't afford it.
Wait, aren't class trips
usually a 9th grade thing?
Not here. We go during
the 8th grade fall term.
Although, it used to be in
the 9th grade spring term.
Used to?
Um, yeah...
I don't know when it changed.
I don't dislike rain.
Hey, Sakuragi?
What is Misaki like?
Don't...
Don't what?
Don't ever speak that name in class 3!
What?
But why—
Man, the rain's gotten worse.
Hey, do you know the story
about the class 3 of 26 years ago?
You actually believe stories like that?
How...
How do you know...
I just heard a rumor.
How much did you hear?
A popular student suddenly died,
and then she showed up in
the class' graduation photo.
That's about it.
Only the first year...
Why do you all look so serious?
Sakakibara knows about the first year...
Good morning, Rei!
Rei!
Yeah, yeah, morning.
Ah. That's a delicate issue.
Let's try to keep it as quiet
as possible, for now.
Just keep an eye on things.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Hey, don't you have exams next week?
Figure they'll be a breeze?
Not at all.
I'm doing all the studying I need to.
Okay then, sorry I asked.
Man, I'm beat!
Um, Reiko?
Do you remember which 9th
grade class my mom was in?
Nope.
Then, do you know the story about
the class 3 of 26 years ago?
Reiko?
Huh?
Um... I was asking about the
class 3 of 26 years ago.
That story's been swirling around for years.
I heard there's a continuation to it.
You don't know all of it?
You know it, don't you?
That type of story tends to get embellished.
I don't think you should
take it too seriously.
There's a right time to
find out about everything.
Ritsuko was in class 3.
Why, Rei?
Why?
Hang on.
Entry Prohibited
Yeah?
Are you all right?
Why do you ask?
I called because I thought
you were in trouble!
Akazawa looks like she's
about to blow her top!
Why would she...
Listen, Sakaki.
Don't mess with things that don't exist!
What are you talking about?
It's dangerous!
As for that story you asked about yesterday,
I'll tell you everything next month.
So, for the rest of this month, just—
It's about that girl who died at the hospital.
Did you find something?
Her name was Misaki.
Misaki, not Masaki.
The "mi" used in "future,"
and the "saki" meaning "blooming flowers."
And it turns out her surname was Fujioka.
Misaki Fujioka?
Why do you want to know about her?
Um, well...
You don't have to tell me now.
But someday, okay?
Okay.
By the way, you have exams coming up, right?
Yes.
My little brother's studying like crazy, too.
You have a brother?
Two, actually.
They're both total muscleheads, though.
They don't care one bit about books!
I don't think they've ever read
anything except manga.
Isn't that just awful?
May 26 (Tue.)
You're always done early.
Am I?
You left before the exam period
ended yesterday, too.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
So, her name was Misaki Fujioka.
The girl who died.
Misaki...
Misaki was my cousin.
We used to be together all the time.
We were much more closely connected.
Connected?
Hey...
About class 3 from 26 years ago...
What's the rest of the story?
Nobody will tell you?
No.
I suppose that's understandable.
There's something I've wanted to ask.
Something I've been wondering
since I transferred here.
Why does everyone in our class,
even our teachers, act like you—
Because I don't exist.
Listen, Sakaki.
Don't mess with things that don't exist!
That's...
It's dangerous!
But...
None of them can see me.
What if you're the only
one who can see me?
No...
It can't be...
That's...
What's wrong with her?
Put flesh.