Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends have marched into
Hueco Mundo, the world of the Hollows.
They finally make their way to
Las Noches, Aizen's headquarters.
Upon breaking into the palace,
the group decides to split up
and go down separate paths.
But Arrancars known as
Privaron Espada were waiting for them.
Where are you looking?
That wasn't even good enough
to be a warm-up exercise.
Also, a new Espada
appears before Rukia.
What is this?! Blue skies?!
Why is there a sky here
beyond these walls?!
Shall I tell you?
Follow me.
Wait!
I can finally relax now.
Sorry.
I can't seem to stand sunlight.
The sun doesn't get
inside of the palace.
I'll remove my mask
and introduce myself.
My name is Aaroniero.
Espada Number 9…
Aaroniero Arruruerie.
I-It can't be…
Sir Kaien…
Answer me!
Please answer me, Sir Kaien!
Is that really…
Is that really you, Sir Kaien?
Wait!
What am I saying?!
Sir Kaien died…
that night.
What's going on?
Sir Kaien is…
Sir Kaien is no longer here.
Yeah.
It's been a while.
You're looking well, Kuchiki.
These clothes are
really hard to move in.
Sir…Kaien…
What's with that expression?
Come on!
Aren't you glad that the popular,
Lieutenant Kaien is alive?!
It's Sir Kaien.
This warmth that feels as if I had
left my hand out in the sun…
It's Sir Kaien's.
But…
Then what was that?
A wooden sword?
Here!
I'll train you for old time's sake!
This is…Squad 13’s
former training ground?!
Why do you look
so dumbfounded?!
Quickly, take a stance!
If you're not going to
make a move, then I will!
The heaviness of this swing.
This footwork.
My body remembers all of it.
Your side's open!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Don't tell me you're
giving up after just that!
Even his unreserved,
blunt way of speaking…
“Umm… Yes, sir”?
What’s with that greeting?!
Your Lieutenant just
introduced himself!
Sir Kaien was like that
ever since I met him.
Too slow!
You would have been dead
if this were a real battle.
But it looks like
you've gotten stronger.
He hasn't changed at all!
Sir Kaien!
You sure haven't changed.
Whenever I beat you,
you always look like you're going to cry.
Sir Kaien…
It looks like you believe me now.
Umm… I believe
it was around here.
Ah, there it is!
Here!
Have a seat!
I have a lot to tell you!
That night…
My spiritual body began to
crumble after the battle.
After parting with you
at the Shiba Family house,
I broke into pieces.
That Hollow was one of
Aizen's test subjects.
Once it was destroyed,
it would be sent to Hueco Mundo
and would regenerate.
They set up a mechanism like that.
I never would have thought.
The Hollow had fused
its spiritual body to mine.
When it regenerated,
it came back in my form.
That was probably their plan
up until this point.
But for some reason,
I was in charge of our spiritual body.
Well, in short, my iron will power
was beyond their calculations!
How awkward!
I really am special!
S-Sir Kaien!
Wasn't this
a serious conversation?!
Y-Yeah… But…
You've been looking gloomy
all this time.
This is my serious expression!
All right… Don't get so upset.
Anyway…
I got my body back.
And I've traded placed
with one of the Espada.
I've been waiting for
a chance to kill Aizen.
There are blue skies
outside, right?
Aizen created that blue sky
on Las Noches's canopy.
Everything that the light
from that blue sky hits
is under Aizen's surveillance.
Is that why you brought me here?
Kuchiki…
I'm glad you’re the one
that came here.
You're probably
the only person
who can handle the plan
I'm going to reveal to you.
Let's move elsewhere.
Come this way, Kuchiki.
Yes!
What's this?
You've gotten a lot stronger
than I thought…
Kuchiki.
Has someone reached
an Espada Palace?
How unusual for you to talk to me.
Don't you dislike me?
Of course not.
Really?
If that's the case,
then be a little friendlier with me.
I've been lonely since Luppi died.
We talked a lot.
What's this?
Oh. Isn't this great?
You're controlling
the passageways?
Oh, come on.
I wouldn't do something
mean like that.
Besides…
I don't like sad stories.
What's wrong?
You have quite a bewildered expression
on your face, Kuchiki.
I'm happy. Before, you would have
died from that strike.
As your superior,
I'm glad to see your improvement.
Wh-Why?
How much of it is true?
All of it.
Did you think that I was a fake?
Is there something strange
about me trying to kill you?
You haven't forgotten, have you?
I'm Kaien Shiba…
The former lieutenant of Squad 13.
I'm here in Hueco Mundo
because I was fused with a Hollow.
And…
You're Rukia Kuchiki.
You're the woman who
stabbed me to death.
Do you understand
why I tried to kill you?
Kuchiki…
You haven't forgotten, have you?
The way it felt
when you stabbed me!
No… I won't forget.
That all really happened.
It's the truth.
Are you prepared for me
to kill you, Kuchiki?
I'm asking whether you're
prepared to put down your life
to atone for your crime
of killing me.
I am.
But…
I cannot do that right now.
I…
I ran away.
I don't think that sin will ever go away,
no matter how many years pass.
If killing me will make you
feel a little better…
I will gladly give you my life.
But…
I'm here in Hueco Mundo
for Inoue.
I've come to save a friend.
No matter what you say,
I cannot give my life to you
until I save Orihime Inoue!
Sorry! I was just kidding!
Huh?
It was a joke!
Indeed, I want you to atone
for what you did,
but I'd never think of something
as silly as killing you!
I told you…
I have something
that only you can do.
If you really want to
make it up to me,
I have something that
I want you to do, Kuchiki.
Something you want me to do?
Yeah.
I want you to bring me
all of your friends' heads.
Don't worry…
You know all of their abilities
and weaknesses, don't you?
It shouldn't be difficult
if you catch them off guard.
If you do this, I'll completely
forgive you for killing me!
Isn't it easy?
It's a small price to pay
for my life, isn't it, Kuchiki?
Right?
What's wrong, Kuchiki?
You're not going to say
it's a joke this time, are you?
Kuchiki…
Obviously…
Letting me go if
I hand over my friends…
You'd never joke about that.
Don't insult…Sir Kaien!
There's no way that
you can be Sir Kaien.
Sir Kaien would never make jokes
to test his subordinates.
Sir Kaien would
never force someone
to choose between
their friends and themselves!
I…Everyone in Squad 13 respected
Sir Kaien from the bottom of their hearts.
He's nothing like you!
After I had stabbed him,
when Sir Kaien tried to speak,
his lungs filled with blood
and he had trouble breathing.
But even so, Sir Kaien…
Thanks to you…
I can leave my heart here.
Wait, Kuchiki!
What are you saying?!
I'm Kaien…
Don't ever say that name again!
Dance Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai…
Tsukishiro!
You're not getting away!
There's nowhere
to escape anymore!
You think so?
What?!
Did you forget who
taught you how to fight?
I'm disappointed.
You got better,
but not by much.
Say that after you
get away from here!
Why you…
Kuchiki… Trying once more to kill
the man you killed… How impressive.
Don't say that!
There's no way that you're Sir Kaien!
You're pretty dense.
Well, you'll understand
while we're fighting.
When you get that same feeling
as when you stabbed me.
You bastard!
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren!
That fighting style is typical of you.
But you can't defeat me like that.
When I walk
through Las Noches,
there are times when
the paths suddenly change.
What are you talking about?
You don't get lost even if
the passageways are changed.
But Yammy often gets lost.
Oh… He probably would.
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Interim Captain?
That's right!
Lieutenants without captains,
like us,
have been given
the same authority as captains!
Oh? That's good for you.
What, are you jealous?
Oh! It's about time
for us to go see
the Head Captain,
Interim Captain Hisagi!
Oh, almost forgot!
See you later, Abarai!
– All right! Kira, let's celebrate tonight!
– Do those two understand?
– They're just getting more work.
– That sounds great!