Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends
have marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
Sado fights a desperate struggle
with Privaron Espada
Gantenbainne Mosqueda.
In the midst of battle,
he awakens the power
that has been resting within him.
Its name is Diablo…
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo.
La Muerte.
Sado defeats Gantenbainne.
But a new enemy appears before him.
Hey, are you the first one here?
His movements are slow!
I know he's
pretty skilled, though.
I should end this in a single blow!
Is that your full power?
I'm not finished yet!
Tsk!
Look at that.
You really are weak.
Chad…
He was defeated?
Huh? What's wrong, Ichigo?
I-Ichigo? You're going t-too fast!
Chad was defeated?!
That's impossible!
We're going into battle now!
Vow…that even if the earth splits,
– Believe in him. We vowed
– we will come back to this place alive!
that we'd come back alive!
Believe in him!
Right now,
that's all I can do!
I'm coming in.
It seems you've noticed.
That idiot Nnoitora was impatient.
We were ordered
to wait in our palaces.
Sado isn't dead.
He isn't dead.
Come in.
Your meal.
Eat.
I don't need it.
Staying alive until
Lord Aizen calls on you,
is also part of your job.
Eat.
Shall I force it down your throat?
Or shall I tie you down and
simply give you nutritional injections?
Sado isn't dead.
You're pestering me.
That doesn't matter.
What do you want me to say?
Do you want me to tell you
not to worry and that he's alive?
How silly.
I'm not here to humor you.
I don't understand.
Why are you making such a fuss
over whether he's alive or dead?
Whatever the case,
all your friends will soon perish.
Who cares if one of them
perished early?
They should have known from
the beginning that this would happen.
Stop.
If they didn't realize it,
their foolishness is responsible.
You should just laugh it off
and tell yourself that they were fools.
Why can't you do that?
If I were you,
I'd be angry that they were foolish
enough to come to Hueco Mundo
without knowing
the limits of their strength.
I'll come again in an hour.
If you haven't eaten by then…
I'll tie you down and
shove it down your throat.
Prepare yourself.
Master Nnoitora…
Is that you, Tesla?
Yes.
You're not going to
finish him off, are you?
Of course not.
Even if I killed
a thousand small fries,
who would acknowledge
that I'm the strongest?
The lives of small fries are worthless.
All that matters is…
What's the matter?
Aaroniero released his zanpakuto.
His Spiritual Pressure doesn't
seem like anything significant though.
Let's go.
Where to?
I found a large Spiritual Pressure.
I'm going to crush him.
Wait.
I won't…let you go any…further.
Oh? You can still move?
Don't think that you can land a blow
on Master Nnoitora in your condition.
Crap.
Now… Let's go, Master Nnoitora.
Who said you could interfere?
I'm very sorry.
But the enemy used
all of his strength in his final blow.
I was concerned about the slight chance
that something might happen to you.
That would never happen.
There isn't anyone anywhere
who can break my body.
Don't forget…
I'm the strongest of the Espada.
Wh-Wh-What's wrong, Renji?!
There's a fork in the road.
Huh?
It was a single path until now.
Now then…
Which way should I go?
Aww…
What is this?!
Don't surprise me!
It doesn't matter which path you take!
They're both kind of scary anyway.
Dondochakka?!
What are you doing?
What?!
You said that we're under
a seniority hierarchy, right?
That's right!
So don't go ahead of me!
So how old are you?
Well, that's obvious.
Hold on a second. Umm…
One…two…
– Sado's Spiritual Pressure has weakened
– Four?
– and Kuchiki's is being overwhelmed.
– One…two…
Crap. I've got to go faster!
– Huh?
Huh? What's this?!
Anyway, I'm older than you!
We must uphold the seniority hierarchy!
Wait! Wait, Ichigo!
Just assume that I'm six.
Okay?
Why aren't you saying anything?!
This defeats the purpose
of me playing the fool!
We're a team that
shares the same fate!
Hey, wait!
How far does this go?!
What's with this huge pitfall?
Where am I?
I can't stay here!
I've got to move on right away.
This is great!
I placed a lot of traps,
but I never thought that anyone
would fall for the simplest one.
Tsk!
Oh. How rude of me.
I need to introduce myself first.
I'll only say it once.
I'd appreciate it
if your mind could remember it.
I'm Espada Number Eight.
Octava Espada,
Szayelaporro Grantz.
I'm Espada Number Eight.
Octava Espada,
Szayelaporro Grantz.
An Espada. I see.
So you're one of the ten guys
who lead the Arrancars.
That voice! Dondochakka?!
That guy fell before me.
So why hasn't he come down yet?
It's coming from here!
Phew. That was close.
I was about to
be crushed by an ally.
That hurt!
My butt…
My butt hurts!
Shut up.
And that hole was scary!
Just get off of me already!
Y-Y-Y-You're…
O-O-O-Octava Espada
Master Szayelaporro!
Master Szayelaporro is
Hueco Mundo's best researcher.
He specializes in the development
of various spirit weapons!
But his research is completely
shrouded in mystery
to us low-ranking Arrancars.
Hey! You're talking to me,
aren't you?!
Then get off of me!
Let me react appropriately!
Oh, Renji?
What are you doing under my butt?
Th-Th-Th-That hurt!
Why did you kick me?!
Shut up! If you make a fuss
I'll kick you again, you idiot!
That aside,
your face is really rock-hard!
That's terrible!
I'm against violence!
Arrgh… Don't cry anymore!
It's so annoying!
My heart hurts more than my body.
I cannot stop crying!
All right.
I might have gone a little overboard.
I'm sorry.
Are you really sorry?
Yeah, I am.
Are you really, really, really sorry?
I said so!
Then an eye for an eye.
I'll kick your face…
I knew it.
You really weren't sorry!
That's because you're getting cocky!
Are you finished with your farce?
Whoa.
That's a scary expression.
Give me a break.
I'm an Espada, but my fighting abilities
aren't very strong.
It's as that big guy said.
I'm a researcher.
I can get all sorts of
spirit patterns from here.
This brings me more pleasure
than anything else.
Oh. Of course,
you're wonderful too.
Your pattern is a type
that I haven't studied.
So I'll give you
the greatest welcome.
I'd like you to accept it.
How about it?
There's no need to be modest.
Wait.
What do you mistake this for?
I didn't come here to talk to you.
I came here to crush you guys.
I don't care who you are.
I don't want your welcome.
If you want to talk,
then talk to me while I'm slicing you.
But I have no intention
of holding back!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
My ability is Glotoneria.
I devour dead Hollows
and make their abilities
and Spiritual Pressure my own!
This is the power I received
when I devoured Metastacia
when he came back
in Kaien Shiba's body!
This body is Kaien Shiba's!
In his body,
all of his experiences…
In his brain,
all of his memories…
They're all there!
I just read his memories
and experiences and acted accordingly!
It's over. I'll show you
an Espada's sword release.
Devour! Glotoneria!
That's a nice expression.
You're scared, aren't you?
Become even more terrified!
This is the power of
all the Hollows I have devoured!
Don't expect an Espada's sword release
to be like that of a regular Arrancar!
My Glotoneria can display
all the powers
of the Hollows I have eaten
at the same time!
So far, I've eaten 33,650 Hollows!
This will be just like fighting an army of
more than 30,000 Hollows by yourself!
Sir Kaien…
Master Aaroniero
released his zanpakuto.
It's all squishy and delicious looking.
How is that delicious?!
Ichigo, do you know of
anything more delicious?
Uhh… There's a lot
in the World of the Living.
All right, if you go as far as to say that,
then let's go!
Free food!
What? You're going?!
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today I will talk about the Arrancar’s
high-speed maneuver technique.
Like the Soul Reaper’s Flash Step
and the Quincy’s Hirenkyaku,
SONIDO
the Arrancars have a high-speed
maneuvering technique called a Sonido.
They're all pretty much the same.
No. Sonido is the best!
Doesn't your hair get in the way
when you use your Sonido?
I always watch my head,
so it's not a problem!
You should watch your feet, too.