Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
SEVERAL HUNDRED YEARS AGO
We are outnumbered.
The rebels are
growing in number.
How would you handle
this situation, Koga?
We don't have time
to observe things.
I shall go.
Stop.
War cannot be waged
by a single person.
But we don't have the time
to discuss things here.
This isn't like you, Father.
I told you not to
call me that here.
My apologies, Sir Ginrei.
I will be going now, then.
You always want to
rush to your death.
W-What's that?!
Who are you?
Where are you from?!
Wait! That's…
Does he belong to
the Kuchiki Clan?!
It's an enemy! Surround him!
You will curse your misfortune
for having laid eyes on this sword!
Don't be afraid!
There's only one enemy!
You greenhorn!
Here we come!
Whisper, Muramasa!
W-What is this?!
W-What's this?
My Zanpakuto is…
What's wrong?
I don't know!
My Zanpakuto is
moving on its own.
W-What are you doing?!
Me too?!
What are you doing?!
I-It's not what you think!
My Zanpakuto is moving on its own.
On its own?!
That's impossible.
W-What's this?
W-What's going on?
No way… No… No!
Raise your head, Koga Kuchiki.
Yes, sir.
Your work was magnificent.
The rebellion is still
far from over,
but we've taken a big step
towards recovery.
You are too kind.
The Soul Society is currently
in great turmoil.
But this might be a test to see if
we can permanently bring peace.
In order to do that,
the Soul Society needs
young strength like your own.
Please continue
to use your power.
Yes, sir!
I vow to give my life in order
to bring peace to this world.
Did you hear about Sir Koga?
Yeah, I heard.
He took out several dozen
rebels by himself.
That's amazing!
Rumors are that a Third Seat
position is being secured for him.
But why does he dress the same way as the
people of the Kuchiki Clan?
What? Don't you know?
Sir Koga is an accomplished
scholar and warrior.
He married into the Kuchiki Clan.
What's wrong?
You seem dissatisfied.
Could you tell me?
Okay. Then let me
ask you one thing.
Why did you launch
an attack on your own?
I was confident that
with my power,
and the power of
my Zanpakuto Muramasa,
I could change the situation.
Koga…
Do you know what people
who have great power
need to use their power?
What would that be?
Heart.
Heart?
Those with power must
control their power,
but at times,
are controlled by their power.
In order to gain balance,
you need a heart that is
not overconfident of your power.
I am well aware of
your superior abilities.
However, you still lack the heart
to make full use
of those abilities.
Take note of this incident as
a bad example of your actions.
Do not forget that you now bear
the title and responsibility
of our clan.
But…
That is all. You may leave.
Excuse me.
What troubles you, Koga?
I'm not troubled by anything.
I see some cloudiness
in your heart.
It's just your imagination.
Don't hide things from me.
We are one.
Our trust in each other
makes us stronger.
Am I not using
your powers correctly?
I don't know.
Your powers have not
reached its full potential.
There is no telling how much
power you can produce.
I see.
But let me say this.
We are a Soul Reaper and Zanpakuto
that were meant to be together.
Trust in me as well as yourself.
You're right.
Trusting myself is the way
I can maintain order.
You did it, Sir Koga.
You were magnificent.
That is my report on how
the rebels were suppressed.
What is Sir Ginrei thinking?!
What are you
talking about, Koga?
No matter what my achievements are,
he never accepts me.
In fact, he seems to
look down on me.
Don't worry about it.
You are strong and beautiful.
What's wrong?
Is it about him?
He seems to have changed lately.
There's no need to worry.
He is a sensible man.
And he has far
greater power than I.
He just needs more time to
understand things properly.
It's no good. Retreat!
We have a report that
most of the rebel forces
were suppressed after
the battle the other day.
Great work, Sir Koga.
We are very proud to be able
to work with you, Sir Koga.
You don't need to flatter me.
Our goal is not to be
popular with the public,
but to restore order
to the Soul Society.
What was that about?
I don't know if they're
big shots or what,
but I hate how
they're so secretive!
They're probably jealous
of our achievements.
You want me to help you?
That's right.
I have organized
a special task force
to deal with
the remaining rebel forces.
I want you to become its leader
and do what you can
to get the job done.
I understand.
Sir Ginrei…
Head Captain Yamamoto
had appointed me
to be the captain of
his special task force.
I see.
Try not to tarnish our clan's name.
Are you not happy to hear this?
Your, no,
the Kuchiki Clan's son-in-law,
has been recognized
by Head Captain Yamamoto!
Be careful not to misinterpret the
Head Captain's intention.
Excuse me.
Koga Kuchiki…
It seems he's leading Head Captain
Yamamoto's special task force.
We are close to restoring order
to the Soul Society.
If this continues,
it will be difficult for our
faction to override his position.
But I hear he has great power.
There might not be
anything we can do.
No, I have a plan in place.
Sir Koga!
It's over…
This battle is finally over!
You did it, Sir Koga!
What?!
Why are you…?!
Koga Kuchiki!
Our plan is for you to die
in this rebellion!
I see…
But…
Get him!
You're finished!
You cannot defeat me
with numbers!
Mukojochu! Muramasa!
W-What…
…is that?!
Th-This is…
It doesn't matter!
Go!
Don't make me laugh.
W-What?!
My Zanpakuto…
These guys…
Who are they?!
They are manifestations
of your Zanpakuto.
My voice has awakened
their desires.
What?!
You will be unable
to touch us and
will die at the hands
of your own Zanpakuto.
It seems everything is settled.
Yeah.
Don't move!
What is this?
What's the meaning of this,
Koga Kuchiki?
Those fallen beside you do
not belong to the rebel faction.
They belong to our
Unified Hegemony!
Did you attack your
own allies in the battle?!
Of course not.
They attacked me,
so I attacked them back.
What's going on?
Sir Ginrei!
Why, Sir Ginrei!
Take a look at the situation.
Koga, who has married
into the Kuchiki Clan,
has murdered
his fellow Soul Reapers!
I-It's true.
He's a demon!
In order to show off his power,
he suddenly attacked us.
Don't tell lies!
We were victims of his ambition.
You bastard!
Arrest him!
Arrest Koga Kuchiki right away!
Wait! Listen to me!
What are you going to do, Koga?
Damn it!
Stop, Koga!
Don't do anything.
Stay still for now.
Sir Ginrei! Why?!
Just don't do anything.
Koga…
Your punishment
has been decided.
You will be deprived of
the position you have held
for the past century.
And as for your Zanpakuto…
It has been deemed dangerous
and will be neutralized.
No way!
Sir Ginrei!
Are you saying that
you believe their claims?!
Do you really think that I killed
them out of my own desire?!
Do you believe that I'd think that?
No.
Do you understand?
Your superiors believe that your
Zanpakuto's power is a problem.
It is not you they fear.
They fear Muramasa
going berserk.
What?!
It's not me but Muramasa?!
Koga… I told you before.
Those with power must
have a strong heart.
You were overconfident in
your Zanpakuto's powers
and continued to believe that
your choices were correct.
Sir Genryusai was worried
about you going berserk,
so he placed you
under his direct command.
I was set up!
By those who want power!
No.
Your overconfidence
brought about this result.
Then what should I have done?!
They were after my life!
Are you saying that
I should have died?!
Restrain yourself.
There's still time until
your punishment is carried out.
Learn some patience.
That might be good for you.
You really have rushed
into your death this time.
But I need to handle
the situation quickly.
Or else he really will
lose his powers.
Why doesn't he understand me?!
Why doesn't Sir Ginrei understand
my power and my existence?!
You don't need him
to understand you.
I told you.
Believe in me…and in yourself.
Muramasa?! How?!
How have you manifested?!
Your desires, your inner anger,
have reached out to me.
My desire?!
If you call to me,
I will go to wherever you are.
I am your Zanpakuto.
Live.
And follow your desires!
Who's there?!
Let's go, Koga.
You don't need to follow
the rules of a world
that despises and
envies your power.
You should just change
the world with your power.
Let me make one thing clear,
Muramasa.
I am your master.
As my Zanpakuto, you have
no business telling me what to do!
Damn it! He's been awakened!
Let's go, Ichigo!
Okay!
What Spiritual Pressure!
He's been sealed away
for so long…
And yet he still possesses
this much Spiritual Pressure?!
You've awakened… Koga…
I've waited for this moment
for so long.
Now's the time for us
to complete our goal!
Mura…masa…
W-Why?!
In the next episode, you shall
witness our perfect team play!
We're not ready to give in to
the younger generations just yet!
And we're accepting people
to join our fan clubs!
Join now, and you'll be
invited to our secret concert!
Can you tell us
your membership benefits?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
FRUSTRATED
Honestly…
Zanpakuto manifestations
are absurd!
Don't get so mad.
I've thought this before,
but it's weird for weapons
to have minds of their own!
I told you not to get so mad!
Hey!
Do you hear something?
Huh?
– Uryu! Can you hear my voice?
– Huh? Huh?
I am Ginreikojaku!
A-Are you really Ginreikojaku?!
Yeah!
Manifestations are great!