Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who keep
a close eye on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Ichigo goes to the Visoreds.
Hirako leads him to
his internal world
where he battles his other self.
I'm Zangetsu!
Furthermore, illusions of Byakuya
and Kariya appear before Ichigo.
They ask him about
his determination to fight
and about what it means.
In the end, Ichigo's other self stabs him.
I'll become the king.
Where am I this time?
So you're finally awake...
Ichigo.
Kenpachi?
So you're next...
Kenpachi, you say?
What is that?
I've only come to kill you.
That's all!
He looks like
he's completely Hollowfied...
I'm stumped.
When Love traded off and went in,
60 minutes had already passed...
My turn is next.
Kensei...
Hm?
What was the longest time
we've taken in an internal battle?
Hiyori's was 69 minutes, two seconds.
How many minutes has it been?
68 minutes...
44 seconds.
I see...
Wh-What are you doing?!
Stop! Our battle ended long ago!
Ended?
It hasn't ended.
A battle isn't a brawl.
It's not over as long as
one of us is still alive.
I'm saying that I have
no reason to fight you!
You need a reason to fight?
Admit it already, Ichigo!
You desire battle.
You want power!
Isn't that right, Ichigo?!
Anyone who desires power
also desires battle,
without exception!
Do you desire battle
so you can get power?!
Do you desire power
so you can fight?!
I don't know.
But...what I do know...
...is that we were born this way!
We were born to desire battle!
Ichigo!
BATTLE
You instinctively desire battle.
Because there is no other way
to gain power.
Fight, Ichigo!
If you want the power to control...
Take your sword and
cut down your enemies!
There is no other path...
Before you...or behind you...
Ichigo!
BATTLE
It's a Cero! Love!
I know!
Are you going to use
your Hollow transformation, Love?!
Of course!
Even he can't block that...
Without using
a Hollow transformation,
he won't be able to avoid
that Spiritual Pressure!
What's this?!
Hachi! Let Love out
of the barrier!
Crap... It seems like some
of it remained...
Your instinct for battle...
I have no choice.
You defeated me...
I will accept you as the king.
But don't forget that
either one of us
can become the king or the horse.
If you leave me even
the slightest opening...
I will toss you out and stomp
on your skull!
This is a warning.
If you really want to control
my power,
then be sure not to die
until the next time I appear!
Hachi...
Yes.
Do you suppose Berry
is all right, Hachi?
Shh...
How do you feel?
Not bad.
I see.
Don't forget. If you leave me
even the slightest opening...
I will toss you out and
stomp on your skull!
Sorry...
I won't let you.
Kurosaki didn't come to school today
either after all.
If I focus like this I can sense
his Spiritual Pressure.
I know that he's well...
But, knowing Kurosaki,
he's probably training
somewhere in secret...
It's probably best not
to look for him.
I wonder if Kurosaki disappeared
without saying anything to Kuchiki...
OH!
Oh!
Wh-What was that just now?!
How gloomy! I'm being gloomy!
What should I do during
my break tomorrow?!
Oh yeah! I'll invite Tatsuki to
go eat something interesting!
EXAMPLE OF INTERESTING FOODS
A BOWL OF PARFAIT
A Bowl of Parfait.
EXAMPLE OF INTERESTING FOODS
SKEWERED DOUGHNUTS
Skewered Doughnuts.
EXAMPLE OF INTERESTING FOODS
BEAN JELLY STEAK
Bean Jelly Steak.
Oh yeah... Tatsuki hasn't been
feeling well lately.
Oh?
Welcome home, Orihime!
Oh! I'm back, Mrs. Shinmura!
Come to think of it,
those two people who keep
visiting your room...
are they really all right?
Why do you ask?
Well, they carried something
very strange into your room.
Huh?
Woah... That's so cool.
- I mean... What is this, Toshiro?!
- Tsk!
- She came back at a bad time...
- What's all this?!
Thank you for waiting.
This is the Department of
Research and Development's
communication technology lab.
This is the Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
All right, I'll connect you.
H-Head Captain?
You're quick as usual,
Captain Hitsugaya.
I had you prepare this
emergency channel because
we have determined
Sosuke Aizen's true goal.
Aizen's true goal?!
Yes, indeed.
Um... This looks like it's something
important, so I'll just step out!
Wait.
This concerns you humans, too.
Listen to what I have to say.
Okay...
It's been several months since
Aizen has disappeared...
As you know, we're investigating
the Squad 5 captain's room,
where Aizen lived,
Central 46's underground
assembly hall and Seijoto Kyorin,
Immaculate Tower Grove
where he hid himself,
as well as the Daireisho Archive.
Upon investigation of
the Daireisho Archive,
Ukitake found traces
of something inside.
Hey, you're working hard...
Kyoraku, huh?
Why are you here?
We have some free time,
so we came to help.
I hope we'll be of help...
Thanks.
Captain!
We found traces of
Captain Aizen's Spiritual Pressure!
I shall put it on your monitor!
This is...the Hogyoku...
and research data related to it.
Well, Sosuke was after the Hogyoku,
so I guess that makes sense.
Captain Ukitake!
Take a look at this!
This is information completely
unrelated to the Hogyoku.
This is...
What was the information
that Aizen was looking at--?
The Ouken, the royal key.
Umm...
What is the Royal Key?
As its name suggests,
it's the key to the royal family.
Soul Society has a royal family too.
We have a king,
but he leaves Soul Society to us.
It doesn't feel as if he exists.
My captain and I have never
actually seen him in person.
Indeed... Our king is called
the Soul King.
He is a symbolic, as well as
an absolute, presence in Soul Society.
His Royal Palace is in
a different space within Soul Society.
It is guarded by
the Royal Secret Service.
The Ouken, the royal key,
is the key
to the space where
the Royal Palace is.
Then Aizen wants the king...
Dead.
That's probably his goal...
But that's not the problem.
The book Aizen was looking at
doesn't reveal where the Royal Key is.
Indeed...
Each successive Head Captain
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
passes down the whereabouts
of the Royal Key by word of mouth.
Therefore, there is no book
that tells of its whereabouts.
He was looking at a document
that describes the circumstances
in which the key was created.
He discovered how
to create the Royal Key.
The Ouken Codex...
The materials needed for
its creation are 100,000 souls
and an Enriched Spirit Zone
that is greater than a radius
of one spirit mile.
An Enriched Spirit Zone is
an unusually spiritual place
within the World of the Living.
Its location changes over time
and is the easiest place
in the World of the Living
for spiritual entities to gather.
Nanao, where is
the Enriched Spirit Zone right now?
Oh, okay!
Hold on one moment...
This is...
The Enriched Spirit Zone
that Aizen is after...
...is Karakura Town.
One hundred thousand souls
and an Enriched Spirit Zone
that has a radius of one spirit mile
is so beyond reality
that it is difficult to grasp...
I'll explain it in simple terms.
If Aizen completes the Royal Key
in the way that it has
been documented...
Karakura Town, as well as
all the nearby land and people,
will be ripped away from
the world and will disappear.
N-No way...
Is there... Is there a way
to stop that?
We would stop him even
if there weren't a way.
That is why the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads exist.
We still have a short amount of time.
According to Kurotsuchi's report,
after being released from
a seal within a soul,
the Hogyoku is in a deep sleep.
No matter what methods
he uses,
it will take four months
until it fully awakens.
Unless the Hogyoku awakens,
Aizen cannot gather his minions...
He'll make his move after that.
The showdown will be in winter!
Until then, we must hone our skills...
And prepare for battle!
Yes!
And Orihime Inoue...
Aizen is after the World of the Living.
We might not be able
to handle it by ourselves...
We need help from
the World of the Living.
Yes... Could you tell
Ichigo Kurosaki?
Yes!
I shall inform Ikkaku
and the others.
I'll go, too.
Oh.
Wait one moment,
Captain Hitsugaya...
There's someone who's been
waiting here to talk to you...
You...
What's wrong?
Are you finished, Yasutora Sado?!
It's still a little too bright to
be sleeping, don't you think?
I'm not finished!
That's right!
Everyone...
Kurosaki...
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
Orihime, since we've got such
a huge monitor,
want to rent something?
I want to watch a comedian DVD!
Sounds good!
This isn't meant to be used that way...
I'll rent a kid's anime
that you might like.
Matsumoto...
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia!
From today, I will kindly teach you
about the Arrancar.
The Arrancars are Hollows
who have transformed
when their masks were removed.
But you can't predict what will be born
when their masks are taken off!
It's kind of like gambling...
It's amusing, don't you think, Gin?
You really like that kind
of stuff, don't you?