Ichigo and friends
entered Hueco Mundo
to rescue Orihime Inoue,
but one by one, the powerful Espada
took them down.
Running out of options, they were shocked to find
themselves being saved by Soul Reapers,
who were supposed
to have pulled out of this battle.
What is this?
You look like you’re about to die.
Kenpachi!
For crying out loud…
I said I could handle this by myself.
No one listens!
So you finally attacked.
We have only come to
heal everyone’s wounds.
We have no intention
of fighting with you.
I will, after all,
just eliminate you.
It would be a waste of time
to ask your name.
You think so?
On the other hand,
it would be a problem if
I don’t hear your name.
Why is that?
Why? Are you an idiot?
That should be obvious.
So when I stuff you in a jar,
I can write your name on it.
So as a show of respect to you
I think I will ask you your name…
so that you can become
my marionette.
This is bad!
Those feathers are…
Captain Kurotsuchi!
Byakuya faced Espada Number 7,
Zommari Rureaux.
And under Zommari’s
power of “Amor,”
which takes control of everything
he sets his eyes upon,
Byakuya gradually lost control
over his body.
However, Byakuya’s disdain
remained unshaken,
forcing Zommari to change
his mode of attack.
He turned his attention on Rukia,
who was unconscious following
her battle with Aaroniero.
Zommari took control
of Rukia’s mind,
and subsequently,
her entire body.
And he used Rukia to
cut down Hanataro Yamada,
who was trying to render
emergency first-aid.
Furthermore, he resorted to
a cowardly move
that Byakuya could not fight
back against.
Don’t move!
Throw down your sword,
nameless captain.
You have lost.
Bakudo 61…
Rikujokoro.
What is this?!
Damn! Damn! Move!
Control, you say?
Such a thing…
holds no meaning
at all against me.
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
W-What is this?!
Curse you…
Damn this!
I will control everything using
the Amor of my entire spirit!
Gokei, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi’s
billion blades.
It engulfs the enemy in a sphere,
and tears them apart from
every direction.
Be swallowed by
the blade’s throat and be gone.
You’re very stubborn.
Why you…
Damn you… Damn you… Damn you!
Unforgivable!
Bakudo 81…
Danku.
W-What is that?
It is a protective wall
that completely rejects
any Hado techniques
under number 89.
I was able to stop Rukia
using Rikujokoro.
Therefore I ascertained that
your power is similar to Kido.
It seems I was not wrong.
Damn!
Now accept my love!
Accept it! Accept it!
Accept it!
Your impatience limited
your field of vision.
You’ve tarnished your self-proclaimed title
as the fastest Espada.
Show me some mercy.
What’s with that look?
You’re going to refuse?
Will you kill me?
You’ll punish me?!
Such arrogance!
You still don’t understand?!
Did you ever stop to consider?!
The futility of the lives of those
whom you kill so righteously!
Have you thought about
the meaning of
killing Hollows like us as
though it was a natural thing?!
Soul Reapers kill us Hollows
as though it were a common
and reasonable thing!
Do you think you are gods?!
Under whose authority
do you kill us Hollows?!
Is it because we devour humans?
It’s a fact that we devour humans!
So who has been given the right
to protect humans?!
Did someone give you that right?!
The answer is no!
No one has given you
any such right!
You label us as evil and
try to get rid of us.
That’s because you decided arbitrarily
that justice is on your side!
Your arrogance!
That smug look!
You…
When did I say…
that I would kill you
because I’m a Soul Reaper?
I’ll kill you…
simply…
because you
pointed your sword
at my pride.
B…
Banzai!
B-Banzai!
Lord Aizen! Lord Aizen!
Banzai!
It’s over.
Come on out.
Isane Kotetsu.
Did Captain Unohana send you?
Yes.
We sensed from
his Reishi that
Seventh Seat Yamada
had been seriously injured.
She sent me to assist.
I see.
Take care of them.
How very disappointing.
A captain at this level…
You are helpless
before
my power.
Master Mayuri!
No way.
Not Captain Kurotsuchi too.
How unsightly for a captain!
That venomous outward appearance
is just for show.
Why you…
How dare you do this to me!
You’ll pay for this!
For someone who holds
the rank of captain,
you are such a disappointment.
Why…
you…
Master Mayuri!
I never imagined that
I would die in a place like this.
It’s over.
Master Mayuri!
No way.
This is so easy, that it’s boring!
I thought there would be
more to it than this!
Yeah right.
What?!
My, my…
You… Why are you still standing?!
What?
See? It’s working.
You should stop.
I’m tired of that trick.
Get up, Nemu.
Yes.
I didn’t believe he’d be
defeated so easily, but…
It’s sick that he could endure
that much.
But what’s going on anyway?!
Damn!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Damn! Damn!
Damn!
Why?!
I smashed your organs
and your muscles!
So why aren’t you dead?!
Just what is your power?!
You’re such a loudmouth.
It’s not a power.
It’s just that your power
is boring already. That’s all.
What?!
You there, Quincy…
I have a very cautious nature.
When I fight someone, I always
lay a trap during the battle.
I infect my enemy’s body
with infinite quantities of
surveillance bacteria.
What?!
Through the bacteria,
I was able to observe
every battle you had.
Therefore, just before coming here,
I created replicas
of every single organ
and muscle tendon.
That’s ridiculous!
Not even an hour has passed
since I revealed my power!
There’s no way you could
do that in such a short time.
But I can.
That’s why I’m here.
W-Wait!
What? You talk too much!
Talk too much?!
I just said one word!
Bacteria?! When did you infect me?!
During that battle?!
I don’t recall hearing that!
How much did you observe anyway?!
I hope you’re not watching
our daily lives too!
That’s against human rights!
Remove the bacteria now!
What’s with you anyway?!
And stop looking like that!
Are you listening to me?!
Silence, you fiend.
FIEND
He said it before I could!
You’re the fiend! You…
Stop it, Ishida. Don’t talk!
Don’t stop me, Abarai.
Come on, is that something
you have to ask now?
If not now, then when?
This is bad!
Careless, huh, so-called captain?!
You didn’t pay enough attention
to your subordinate’s foothold.
It seems you are under
the wrong impression.
You can capture me,
but I won’t be a hostage.
Silence! I’m not speaking to you!
Are you listening,
so-called captain?!
I’m speaking to you!
My goodness…
Everyone keeps chattering.
It’s so noisy!
Bankai.
Tear him up…
Konjiki Ashisogijizo!
What is this?!
Just where did it…
Wha—?!
This gas…
Is it some kind of bacteria?!
Damn! I can easily counteract this.
What?! Damn.
What’s with this poison?!
Impossible!
Damn!
If I only had time, I could…
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Damn!
Isane Kotetsu, why were you hiding?
I heard the Arrancar confessing
its love to you sir, so I…
Isn’t it embarrassing to have
someone witness a declaration of love?
I don’t understand
a thing you’re saying.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I came to help you eat the sweets
you received for your recovery!
Ukki, aren’t you bored from
sleeping all the time?
Well lately, the carp in the pond
have gotten quite big.
So it’s not boring anymore.
It’s the opposite in my house.
Lately, the large carp
have dwindled
and my brother has been
quite troubled by it.
That’s too bad.