Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
One week after Aizen’s rebellion
Hey! You expect us to
eat this crappy food?!
E-Everyone eats
the same thing here…
I'm telling you, there’s something
wrong with that.
What's with all the noise?
We were injured honorably in the battle.
It's Squad 11.
It wouldn't hurt to give us a better meal…
Again?
don't you think?
Oh…
Really, you Squad 4 are...
Is there a problem
with my Squad?
C-Captain Unohana?!
D-Didn’t know you were here!
I'm glad that you're feeling better.
But…
this is
the General Relief Station.
As long as you're here
your lives are in our hands.
Don't forget that.
W-We're sorry!
Save us!
H-Hey, what's going on?
Huh?
Acting as if
I'm some kind of ghost…
All right, next!
Come on!
What's wrong with you guys?!
Nobody?!
What a bunch of wimps!
Well, in that case…
I will take you on.
Oh? You've got some guts, Ichigo.
But can you handle it?
You’re still recovering, right?
I'm not gonna hold back, you know!
So are you!
And you make it sound
like I was sick.
I was just injured!
So? The word applies
for injuries too!
No, it doesn’t!
Then what would you call it? Huh?
Well, that would be…
I don't know…
See? You don't know!
Go learn Japanese, idiot!
What about you?
All you do is shave
your empty head!
Huh?!
All right! Let’s fight then!
Whoever wins is right!
All right, come on!
I'll show you that Japanese
is my favorite subject!
Hey!
Huh?
Good Morning, Captain!
Oh, it's Ichigo.
Itchy, 'morning!
Are your wounds all right?
Y-Yeah!
Thankfully, I'm completely…
…fine.
I see… That's great.
That means now I can fight you
without holding back!
Face down…
Huh? That’s the wrong guy!
Running away!
Kenny…
This way, this way!
Hey, wait!
You're not getting away! Hold it!
My, my… Rowdy as ever.
It's better than too quiet.
Why are you here so often?
What happened to
Captain Komamura?
Well…the thing is…
My Captain wants to be alone
for a while…
Friend of Tosen,
whose name I do not know…
What would you have
said to stop Tosen?
Oh…
Captain Komamura…
Do you think Captain Tosen
will ever come back here again?
Of course.
Let’s find a way to
open Tosen’s eyes.
I wouldn’t have minded being
your prisoner a little longer.
I’m sorry.
That's the thing I hate
the most about you…
So stupid.
Who is?
Whoa!
Y-You scared me!
I almost spilled over…
Spill over what?
My boobs. Like this…
You don't have to show me.
You have a guest.
Huh?
Kira.
Umm…Matsumoto…
Want some Soba buns?
I also have sake!
Huh?
No… I'm already at my limit…
What are you talking about?
Come on, come on!
Matsumoto…
Yes?
You know that time…um…
Hmm? It's okay …
Don’t bother.
But…
Yeah, you really came
at me for real.
But I didn’t even get a scratch!
Shock!
So…
It's really all right.
Now that you came to
see me like this.
Talking doesn’t guarantee
that you’d understand everything
about the person.
But you won’t be able
to understand anything
if you can’t even see
them anymore, you know.
Yeah…
I suppose you’re right.
Could you…
Could you talk to her?
She's waiting for someone
who needs her…
to talk to her.
The way I am now…
I don't know
what to say to her…
The way you are now…?
Excuse me.
All right! Finished!
We can't go back to
the World of the Living
in Shihakusho, you know!
What do you think?
Pretty nice, huh?
Isn't the design different?
It was more like…
Yeah? Well, this is for you, Inoue.
Dye didn’t come out too well,
so I tried to dress it up with lace,
and attached these small flowers
with the same fabric at the bottom.
I-It's cute…
Really?! I also made this!
This is for Kuchiki to wear when
going back to the World of the Living.
It's a one-piece much like
the one she used to wear.
This is also cute!
I think you're better at
making women's clothes, Ishida.
Huh?
Oh… Ooh…!
I'm going to show this to Kuchiki!
Oh…
What do you say, Sado?
Could you try it on now?
Hmm?!
This sure is cute.
Kuchiki is going to like this.
She's been depressed lately.
But if she sees this,
I'm sure she'll cheer up.
But I wonder why Ishida could
make Kuchiki's clothes so well…
I-I get it!
Maybe Ishida likes Kuchiki!
I'm amazing! I noticed!
I, Orihime Inoue,
Female intuition!
age fifteen and starting to
develop a sharp female intuition!
Big mistake!
Ah, it’s over here.
Kuchiki!
Huh?
Man, my legs hurt.
That Kenpachi…
Chasing me around like that…
Jeez…you’ve gotta be kidding.
Kurosaki!
Wh-What?!
Oh, it’s you, Inoue…
What's with those clothes?
There’s something wrong…
Kuchiki is…
Huh?
Renji.
Why are you here?
Because I'm your lieutenant.
“Why are you still alive…?”
That's what you're
probably thinking, huh?
No way.
If you die, how could
I aim to be stronger than you?
Captain… I…
Renji!
Shut up!
Huh?
What the hell do you want?
I was just about to say
something heartfelt, damn it!
O-Oh…sorry…
Hey! Do you know where Rukia went?
What? What about Rukia?
N-No, never mind if
you don't know.
Did you find out anything, Kurosaki?
Did you find Kuchiki?
How did you climb…?
Oh whatever.
Sorry! Renji, Byakuya!
We're leaving!
Sorry to bother you
Mr. Renji and Mr. Byakuya.
What's with them?
What's wrong, Captain?
Nothing…
It’s just… I wonder if he plans
on calling me without titles.
Where’re you going, Kurosaki?
Do you know where Kuchiki is?
I think so.
If she's not with Renji…
then she's got to be there!
I can't take it any more, Sis…!
Of course you can!
Give me a thousand more!
A-A thousand?!
P-Please Sis, my honorable wounds
haven't healed yet.
Didn’t I work hard this time?
Stop bluffing nonsense!
I heard you were practically
useless half the time!
Wh-Who told you such
a total truth!
I'll make you regret
you came back alive!
Die! Die immediately! Die now!
What do you want?
Oh...!
H-Hold it, Sis!
This is Rukia!
She’s the one that Ichigo
went to great lengths to save…
I know.
Huh?
Rukia Kuchiki.
She's the Soul Reaper
who killed our older brother.
That's why I’m asking.
What do you want?
I'm sorry!
I know I should have come sooner…
to apologize.
But I’m such a coward
who’s always running away…
I couldn’t bring myself
to face you until now.
I'm sorry… I'm really…
Stop.
That’s enough!
Don't apologize forever!
B-But…
I said that’s enough.
Wha--?!
Huh…uh…er…?
I've heard everything from Ukitake.
He told me that
it wasn’t your fault,
and that you’re living
with the biggest guilt.
So I’ve decided long time ago
that if you said just one word of apology,
then I’d forgive you.
So…
It's okay.
That's right. She…
She knew Sir Kaien.
She knows what
he would’ve wanted…
I was only thinking of myself…
I'm not even the one
most pained by this…
Thank you…
I'm really…sorry…
I told you not to apologize.
Right…umm… Sorr…
I mean, thank you very much.
Ah! So you were here!
Ichigo… Inoue…
It seems like you're finished here.
Let's go back.
They said they’ll open the gate
to the World of the Living tomorrow.
You're still not fully recovered.
Go to bed early tonight
to be ready for tomorrow.
Oh, that's right…
I think you should be
the first one to know this…
I'm going to…
stay here in the Soul Society.
I see.
That's good.
Huh?
I mean, if that's what
you’ve decided…
that you want to stay…
then that’s what you should do.
I remembered why I was trying
so hard to save you.
Hey, Ichigo!
You finally showed up!
What were you doing?!
Oh…no…um…
Kukaku, it's been a while!
You're going home tomorrow, huh?
That's quick.
Have dinner with us!
It'll please everyone!
No…um…but…we…
What? Are you going to make
me repeat myself, too?
No…um…
Thank you very much
for the invite!
Survival of the fittest
That's mine!
No, that's mine!
Too bad, I ate it!
Kukaku Shiba
Hey! Rukia!
Damn it! I really can’t find her.
Where did she go?
Inoue, where are you?
Ichigo! Where the hell are you?!
Every one sure is
full of free time…
Wh-What is this?!
I can't drink anymore…
S-Save me…
Whoa! I thought I was going to die…
What's wrong, Matsumoto?!
Did you know, Captain?
I can't breathe if I lie face down!
No.
But if I lie on my back,
they get pulled to the sides
and it hurts…
Shut up!
This is the official Senkaimon.
Of course, I incorporated
a Reishihenkanki for you.
Ichigo.
Yes?
This is for you.
What is this?
A Substitute Soul Reaper
Combat Pass.
It’s our old custom to give this
to a Substitute Soul Reaper
who is deemed useful
to the Soul Society.
If you use this,
you can become a Soul Reaper
whenever you want.
Of course, this won’t make up
for what you have done for us, but…
That's all right.
I did it because I wanted to.
But, I'll gladly accept this.
This man is…truly…
Kuchiki, here! Ishida made it!
Wow, impressive.
But…I’m no longer…
You've got to wear it!
O-Oh…okay…
It's time!
See you, Rukia.
Yeah.
Thank you, Ichigo.
That's my line.
Thanks, Rukia.
Because of you,
the rain has finally stopped.
Itchy's Spiritual Pressure
disappeared…
I see.
Why didn't you see them off?
Huh?
You may never see them again.
That'll never happen.
Huh?
You heard what Old Man’s said.
The fight isn't over!
We'll meet again.
Because we’re a lot alike,
he and I.
Kenny learned how to wait!
Don't say it like I'm a dog.
Official my butt!
It's exactly the same as before!
Yoruichi, what the hell?!
Only Soul Reapers can use
the Hell Butterfly!
Stop complaining, and run!
Look! We're almost at the exit!
Don’t stop! Just run through it!
Locked on target!
Fire!
All right! Here it comes!
Jinta Home…run?!
Tessai Death Catch!
Welcome back, everyone!
Urahara…
Welcome back, Kurosaki.
You've heard about me, right?
Yeah.
I'm really sorry…
Please stop.
It's fine.
I'm not mad.
You didn't really do anything bad.
Your motivation aside,
you did save us and
made us stronger.
I'm thankful.
So…
Please don't apologize.
Okay…
But…can I ask you just one thing?
You didn't tell me the truth
because you thought
I’d be scared and run away?
Ah, exactly right!
Now that pisses me off!
I-I didn't expect the elbow…
Also…
Please apologize to Rukia.
Though she'll probably
say the same thing.
Okay…
Now then!
Mr. Urahara, can you drop me
off around here?
Yes, yes! Got it!
See you later, Ishida!
If something comes up again,
I'll be counting on you!
What are you talking about?
Did you forget, Kurosaki?
You’re a Soul Reaper
and I’m a Quincy.
The next time we meet,
we'll be enemies.
You…
See you later!
He sure is stubborn.
That’s for sure!
But that's the good part
about Ishida.
You think so?
You're right.
Really?
You guys are so understanding.
Well then, I'll get off here!
Shall I drop you off at
your house, Kurosaki?
Yeah, please…
Sorry Urahara,
actually here will be fine…
Huh? But…
See you later!
Wai--!
Kurosaki?
What's wrong, Yoruichi?
Hm? It’s just…
It's been quite a long journey.
It sure has.
Say, Kisuke…
Yes?
What’s going to happen now?
Let’s see…
We started after we suffered
a big defeat…
So all we‘ve done is
get things back to normal.
Kurosaki and the others have got
their work cut out for them…
I guess it depends on them.
We’ll never die peacefully…
Well, that can't be helped, can it?
I sense something between
Yoruichi and Boss.
Like what?
Well…
Ow!
Kurosaki Clinic
I'm home!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Guess what’s going to happen
in the next episode.
Doctor Isshin's hardcore Medical Drama!
Kon's Steamy Pink Diary!
A horror mystery…
All wrong! Who was the last one?
It wasn't someone you know?
No. Agh, time's up…
That sure is nostalgic…
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Fish sticks?!
Oh…thank goodness…
It was a dream…
What'll I do…
I'm too afraid to sleep now…
Maybe I'll go to Kiyone's…
I wonder if she'll get mad
and say I shouldn’t visit other barracks
so late at night!
Hm?
Isane.
Y-Yes?
It's been quite a busy day,
hasn’t it?
Once you calm down,
go get some good rest…
Yes.
Tune in again!