Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Tsubaki!
Koten Zanshun!
“I reject!”
Tsubaki!
Fool…
Faltering like that…!
That was the first time
I saw such a technique.
There’s no intent to kill
in your attack.
Though you might kill
Hollows with that move,
it will have no effect
on Soul Reapers.
Have you mistaken this place
for a playground?
This is a battlefield!
Without the intent to kill…
you’ll never stop anyone!
Wha--?!
So you want an attack
with intent to kill?
Then fight me.
It’s here in my bow…
The intent to kill you love so much.
Huh…Very interesting.
Would you be a Quincy?
That’s right.
Ishida’s bow…
It’s totally different from
the one I saw!
In its appearance and
even in its Spiritual Pressure…!
That glove…
He must have been practicing
in order to use it properly.
This is interesting.
One uses an unfamiliar skill;
the other is a Quincy.
And both employ projectile weapons.
And you’ve both come to fight me.
What coincidence!
What a twist of fate.
Now I must show you.
The true form of my Zanpaku-to.
Spread your wings, Tsunzaki Garasu!
Huh!
What do you think?
Now, lament.
I am 4th Seat of Squad 7!
Jirobo Ikkanzaka!
Also known as Jirobo Wind Scythe!
The nickname, Wind Scythe,
proves that
I am the most skilled
in projectile weapons.
My countless blades
dance through space.
No one has seen my
Tsunzaki Garasu and lived!
Here, here.  How do you like it?
You can’t even follow them
with your eyes, can you?
As a fellow master of flying weapons,
you’ll fully regret having met me…
Huh?
How interesting.
Unlike the human world…
Here, the so-called strongest fighter
seems to be the most long-winded whiner.
R-Ridiculous!
That was a fluke!
Don’t be so cocky.
You still don’t understand?
Sorry, but if you’re supposed
to be the strongest,
I take back your nickname
as of today.
Where flying weapons are concerned,
I seem to be the better man.
The name, “Uryu Weasel with Scythe,”
though, doesn’t sound all too cool.
M-My hand… My hand…
My left hand…!
Amazing… Uryu…
Compared to that time he was battling
the Hollows alongside Ichigo…
He’s become
a completely different person!
Do you lament it even a little?
As a fellow practitioner of
projectile weaponry…
Your misfortune of meeting me…
Me…lament?! Damn you brat!
You do realize that I missed
on purpose.
And next time, I won’t miss.
Amazing!
That was amazing! The speed, power and
accuracy of your technique…
All of which surpass mine.
To think that I should meet
such a skillful practitioner…
I am utterly defeated.
Please, boil me, bake me,
do whatever you want to me.
Why won’t you shoot me?
Could it be that you are letting me go?
I’m a Quincy.
I have no mercy for a Soul Reaper.
It’s just that I don’t like
bullying the weak.
Hurry up and get lost…
Before I change my mind.
It seems you are
a kind-hearted person.
However…
that will be…your…undoing!
Since you couldn’t beat me,
you thought you could at least get Orihime?
Or were you planning to
take her hostage?
H-How did you know?
I don’t like bullying the weak…
But I don’t mind exposing cowards.
From the moment you showed up,
you were targeting her, not me.
Most would find it beneath themselves
to attack a lady when she’s not looking.
An honorable person with any
decent pride wouldn’t do such a thing;
that’s a coward’s way of fighting.
Amazing.
And good-bye.
You don’t even deserve
the time to lament.
Thank you, Uryu.
I-It’s okay,
you don’t need to thank me.
I…
“Didn’t really do much?”
Did he die?
No…
I shot out the Soul Chain
and Hakusui - Soul Sleep,
vital spots that control the
generation of the spiritual energy.
He’s not dead.
However, he’ll lose his spirit powers.
And once he awakes, he’ll no longer
return to being a Soul Reaper.
As a result of this battle…
that’s sufficient.
Shall we go?
Uh-huh.
I’ve heard from Yoruichi,
“A Quincy gathers the spiritual
particles around them to fight.”
I’m sure he uses that glove to increase
his ability to gather spiritual particles.
Because of its overwhelming power,
in order to avoid harming us,
Uryu was training by himself.
And he was able to master it
to that degree…
In just ten days, all by himself.
You’re incredible, Uryu.
What have I done
in those ten days?
Oops!
T-Thank you.
Yeah.
This isn’t…
Orihime!
Hang in there, Orihime!
That’s right – I promised!
Orihime!
Huh?
A-Are you all right?
Did you get hurt earlier?
Ah, oh no! I’m sorry, it’s nothing!
I just got teary-eyed looking
at the sun.
Don’t you get that sometimes?
You know, like sneezing.
Or wanting to go to the restroom
when you’re at the bookstore,
or your gums bleeding when
you bite into an apple.
Well, let’s go, Uryu!
I’m going to do my best too!
Orihime…
What?
Are you sure you’re all right?
Huh? How come?
Well…
Why am I the only one getting
chased around over and over?!
Hey stop, you side burned monkey!
Stop squirming, you lower eyelash!
You with that ugly face!
W-What did you say?!
That other guy was
kind of good-looking,
but no matter how I look at it, you have
no place to comment on my looks!
What did you say?!
We’re going to eat you, Ugly!
With this many on my tail,
I can’t even win an argument!
Oh?!
Ichigo!
Reinforcements! Just in time…
Or not!
He—y, Ganju—!
W-Wait minute!
Why are you getting chased around too?
It makes no sense to get together!
Idiot! Stop waving at me!
You’re riling up the guys
running behind you!
I said don’t come this way…
Let’s go, Ganju!
Duck!
This is Iemura.
Squad 4, Unohana Relief Crew,
Groups 1, 6 and 14 are approaching
enemy position.
Let’s hustle! This is not a drill!
Yes, sir!
That was dangerous, you fool!
Why’d you swing that blade out
of the blue like that?!
Are you crazy?!
What? I told you to duck, didn’t I ?!
The problem is that the time
between warning me and doing it
was too short, too fast!
Well, you should have
reacted right away!
Like I could have,
you moron!
Let’s see… So, now what?
We got away with
a surprise attack just now,
but just ‘cause we showed them
some muscle…
These guys don’t look like
the type to back off.
Damn.
I’m totally late.
What should I do…?
Should I go back?
But if Mr. Iemura asks,
“Where’d you go?”
it’ll be hard to answer.
Oh, but if I don’t go,
he’ll get even angrier…
Anyway, where did everyone go?
I wonder…
Oh yeah!
I’ll ask those people up ahead!
Ah, umm…
Excuse me, I’m from the Squad…4…
W-What are you doing, twerp!
Excuse me!
Damn it, stay away!
Who the heck are you?
E-Excuse me!
What’s the commotion?
Hmm?
Huh?
O-Ouch… That was terrible…
Ichigo… I’ve got an easy plan
to get us out of here.
What a coincidence.
Me too.
A-Ah… A plan to get out of here?
Ah, umm…c-could it be…
that you two are the…alleged…Ryoka?!
Hey! Open up a path, you punks!
If you punks value your friend’s life!
No way! It’s them!
Aren’t we there yet, Yachiru?!
Is it really this way?
I’m sure, I’m sure.
I’m positive it’s this way…
I think.
“I think"? Did you just say “I think”?
Oh, be quiet. Then, this way!
“Then”? Did you just say “then”?
Why are you always complaining?
You decide then!
I don’t care anymore!
Ugh… This way, right?
Yup, yup, this way, this way!
You’re positive?
You’re absolutely positive, right?
Hey! Open up a path, you punks!
If you punks value your friend’s life!
No, let me go! Let me…
W-What’s with this vibe?
Maybe they didn’t hear us…
Wanna try again?
O-Okay.
Hey. Open up a path,
you punks!
If you punks value
your friend’s life!
Hey!
Uh, y-yes…
What…
are you jerks doing?
Huh?
Well, umm, taking a hostage?
And he looks like our friend?
You’re not?
I-I’m from the Squad 4.
These guys are from Squad 11.
So, what’s the difference?
Heh, I guess it’s true
these Ryoka are outsiders.
I don’t want you to lump us together,
so I’ll tell you.
Clean out your ear holes
and listen carefully!
There are a total of 13 Guard Squads
that protect the Seireitei.
We, the Squad 11, are lead
by the strongest of the 13 captains.
As such, we are the strongest
in battle of the 13!
Oh!
Now that you mention it,
these guys all have weird hairstyles,
but yours is normal.
T-Thanks.
So, you’re from where?
I-I’m from the Squad 4.
The Squad 4 is
the rear echelon
that specializes in relief and aid.
Ouwie, ouwie, go away!
A bunch of wimps that can’t
even wield a sword properly.
Yay, he’s all better!
They’re the weakling pansies
of the 13 squads.
Oh boy, it’s heavy…
To be honest, I don’t know
why they even exist.
Hip, hip, hooray!
We can’t stand them!
They annoy us!
Therefore, we, the Squad 11…
Hate the Squad 4!
So if you want to kill him, go ahead!
You’ll be doing us a favor!
Nooo—!
W-W-Wait a minute!
Isn’t it too cruel to say
you don’t care what happens to him
just because you don’t like him?
Huh, you guys?!
Wow, that’s a rational argument.
Let’s go! Go get them!
Damn, I guess we’re going to
have to muscle our way out of here.
Huh!
W-What was that?
I-I don’t know…
Anyway!
I’m certain that it halved our enemy,
so this is our chance now!
Oryah!
Move it, move it!
I thought I sensed
Ichigo’s Spiritual Pressure…
I must have missed him.
Hey, you there!
Did you just do that, you jerk?!
What’s with the weird get-up?
Are you a friend of those guys
from earlier?
Guys? Earlier?
Probably, yeah.
Great! You think you can mock
the Squad 11 and get out of here alive?
We’ll crush you in five minutes!
Sorry, but I can’t accommodate
your wishes…
Huh?
What did you say?
It won’t take five minutes.
I’ll be done in two minutes.
Fourth Squad - General Relief Station
So, you’re not going to say
anything no matter what?
Ikkaku Madarame…
Why don’t you say something?
Please sir! Mr. Captain of Squad 12!
Such interrogation is prohibited
on these premises.
Shut up!
Sir Mayuri…
You be quiet too, Nemu!
Just shut up, okay?
Do you want to be
pulled to pieces again?
No, sir. Forgive me.
It’s not that I don’t want to say…
I really don’t know.
I don’t know the Ryoka’s objective,
destination or anything, for that matter.
Then, what?
So you’re saying that although
you’ve met and fought these Ryoka,
you were just defeated in battle
and retreated like a dog
without gaining any information?
Is that it?
Exactly.
Furthermore…
I have not seen the enemy’s face,
nor heard his voice.
So, I have not a shred of information
to give to you.
Fine…
Then you shall receive a punishment…
befitting your failure. Right?!
I’m surprised.
Since when did you get so powerful
that you can punish those of other squads…
Kurotsuchi?
Zaraki…!
Humph, well, if his captain is here,
then there’s no need for me
to interrogate him.
I’ll withdraw for now.
Let’s go, Nemu!
Stop stalling, you dullard.
Yes, sir.
Captain…
You got yourself
pretty beat up there, huh?
Are you here just to visit me?
Nope, we got lost on our way!
Oh, the Lieutenant is here too?
It’s by coincidence that we wound up here,
but we were worried about you.
Are you okay, Baldy?
I told you not to call me that,
you brat!
Then, Shiny Baldy?
You heard me, didn’t you?
Shiny, Shiny Baldy!
I heard…that you lost.
My deepest apologies.
I’ve come back despite the
shame of my defeat.
Is he strong?
Yes, indeed.
He appears to be a Soul Reaper.
He wears a Shihakusho,
short orange hair,
with a body-length sword
without a guard or grip.
He is headed
towards Senzaikyu Shishinro.
That maximum-security prison.
I gave him your description,
and told him to be on the lookout for you.
If he heeded my words…
you will surely enjoy an excellent battle,
regardless of where you meet him.
He’s strong, and I fear that
strength is still growing.
By the time he meets up with you,
he will probably be stronger still.
I see…
And his name is…?
I’m Hanataro Yamada.
It’s hard to remember!
Really? Everyone tells me
it’s an easy name to remember!
Oh, yeah? I get “Taro Yamada”
or “Hanako Yamada,”
but “Hanataro” is so hard
to remember, hard.
Gosh…
Besides, aren’t you our enemy?
Huh?
Why are you so laid back and
introducing yourself?
Ah, I guess so.
Now that you’ve mentioned it…
Why did we bring
this guy with us?
Couldn’t help it.
He was nearby,
so I accidentally carried him with us!
Accidentally?!
What do you mean, accidentally?
Do you pick up whatever is
lying on the ground?
Shut up! You didn’t notice him yourself
until just now!
P-Please, you two.
Stop fighting over me!
Who’s fighting over you?!
But, if you raise your voices,
someone might find us!
Are we all right?
It seems so.
But still, if it’s true what that
bald guy said, and even if Rukia
is in that white tower,
Oh!
the problem is which road
to take to get there.
Oh, that’s right. I have a map.
We wouldn’t want to run into
any Captains along the way, huh?
If we only knew
the enemy’s positions…
By the way…
There are no roads on this map…
What? Huh?
What’s this?
Peace!
Did you draw this yourself?
What? It’s better than having nothing.
Umm…
Shut up, we’re in the middle
of strategizing. Don’t butt in.
Actually, you can go home already.
You’re not going to be of
much use anyway.
I swear…
Rukia…
Are you talking about Rukia Kuchiki?
Just as I thought…
It’s her, isn’t it?
The younger sister of
the Captain of Squad 6,
currently held in maximum security…
Then that “white tower”
you referred to is the Senzaikyu.
I…
I know the hidden way into that tower.
Kenny, you seem pretty happy.
Huh? Are you talking about me?
Yup! I haven’t seen you
this happy in a while.
Is that so? You might be right…
He survived against Ichimaru.
He defeated Ikkaku.
And, Ikkaku said he was strong.
Ikkaku said he would
become stronger still!
Where? Where are you?
I, Kenpachi Zaraki,
am waiting for you!
Come out!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Yo, how's everyone doing?
This is everyone's idol, Kon!
Why isn't it my turn yet?
I've been ready and waiting over here!
Hey, are you listening to me?
If you make too much of a fuss,
you may never get your turn.
Oh, yes. I will always be waiting,
so please be nice to this stuffed doll.