So you see…
Her family broke up,
and Rukia is the only
relative she has left.
D-
Dad! Please let her stay with us!
It’s so sad. It’s almost
like in the movies!
Of course, Yuzu!
I’d let her stay even if
her story wasn’t like the movies!
I think I’ve seen this all before.
Feel free to ask me anything, okay?
What are…movies?
That’s the part that bugs you?
Wow! It’s as if I have
four daughters now!
It’s like a harem, right, Mom?
The words “daughters” and
“harem” are not supposed
to go hand-in-hand.
We’re a loud family,
but don’t let it bother you.
Thank you.
We’re going shopping.
Call us if anything happens.
Let’s go, Dad.
And put on your shoes!
Oops, I forgot!
What is it?
Something wrong?
No. It’s nothing.
Another one?
How many times is that today?
Nozomi, stay here and
watch TV or something!
Hey Kon, change with me!
R-Right…
Hey!!
Inoue…Chad…
What are you doing?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
Is Nozomi home?
Umm… Yeah…
She’s probably bored,
so do you mind keeping her company?
I wonder what’s wrong with Kon?
So, what is the situation?
Sir… We’ve lost all
contact with the captains.
I will rule the Soul Society
with my invasion force.
Until now, they were
holding back their power.
In other words, this is
the true power of Reigai!
Sir, wait!
If we lose you, the Head Captain,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are bound to fall apart.
We must fall back and regroup
for the time being.
However,
it’s very hard to believe that all
the captains will be
defeated so easily.
And the transmission
Kisuke Urahara received
may not be complete.
There’s no need to comfort me.
In any event, right now, other than the
lieutenants here in the World
of the Living, the only
battle-ready people are Ichigo
Kurosaki and his group.
We need to prepare for
an assault by the invasion
force as soon as possible.
We understand.
I’ve noticed Hollows
appearing in large numbers.
Now that the power balance between the
World of the Living and the
Soul Society is disrupted,
it’s inevitable that
more Hollows would appear.
Our fears have now become reality.
We’ll deal with them with
the fighting forces we have left.
Defending the World of the Living
from Hollows is certainly important,
but be very careful not to give
Kageroza’s invasion force an opening.
Yes, sir.
You don’t have to say it.
What? You killed it already?
Ikkaku, you’re okay to come out?
Who do you think you’re talking to?
By the way, how’s that
Mod Soul girl doing?
She’s… Well, she
did look a bit tired.
Is something the matter?
The very first Mod Soul developed…
was…
me.
What am I supposed to say to her now?
Here you go!
We’re doing a promotion right now!
Oh…thanks.
Here you go!
We’re doing a promotion right now!
What’s this?
It’s defective.
Didn’t even want one. This blows.
If you’re not going to do it right,
don’t make them in the first place.
Where have you been?!
Oh… Sorry…
Since you weren’t here,
I’ve had to stay a Soul
Reaper all this time.
Hurry up and swap back!
Y-Yeah…
What do I do with this?
Oh, the spicy mayonnaise?
Just mix it into the chocolate.
You’re not making any sense, Inoue.
You’re asking me about Kujo?
Yes.
Don’t pretend like you
didn’t know about it.
You’re right.
I found it odd that I didn’t
sense any Spiritual Pressure
from her when we first met.
When she healed Kurosaki’s injuries…
That was when I became almost
certain she was a Mod Soul.
Her power was like Kido,
but it was a different sort of ability.
As a possibility,
I thought it might be an
artificially created ability.
In other words, a Mod Soul.
However, there is one big
question that still remains.
When I have retrieved Nozomi,
I will be able to show
you my true power.
We’ll need to know soon.
Yes.
Okay, it’s done!
Orihime’s special…
Choconomiyaki!
Choconomi…yaki?
Does this fall under the category
of chocolate, or okonomiyaki?
Hmm… I would say…
It falls under yakisoba noodles
with special sauce, maybe?
So it’s none of the above?!
How is it?
It’s delicious.
Really?! Yay!
Orihime, come back and make dinner too.
Huh? Can I?
Sure, sure!
I’ll be a father to all of you!
Cut it out! Dirty old man!
Take this! Choconomiyaki!
Hey…
Hi.
Nozomi!
Let’s go!
She’s calling you.
R-Right.
What are you worrying about?
Didn’t I tell you?
Everything is going as planned.
Is it Nozomi?
It’s only a matter of time.
No, I’m all right.
The originals aren’t fools.
I expected wounds like these.
I will see to it that
the world learns of your wish!
How depressing!
This isn’t right!
This isn’t me!
What’re you shouting for?
Sis?!
Sis! Please!
Punch me!
Feel better?
I asked you to punch me, not kick me.
Right now, everyone at our store
gets a free “I’m the man Lion!”
I’m the man!
Hey, Nozomi!
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I was just looking.
Thanks for waiting.
We’re done with buying groceries for dinner.
All right! Let’s go home.
Okay.
Ichigo…
Yeah, another one.
Gotta go!
Need help?
I’ll be fine!
Damn!
What’s keeping Rukia?!
Duck!
You okay?
Thanks. I owe you one, Ishida.
What do you think you’re doing?
It’s a good thing I was
passing by just now.
Everything’s good.
Hey! You know, Ishida…
Why don’t you come over
for dinner tonight?
What brought that up?
You’re creeping me out.
Well, Inoue’s making dinner for us.
And…
It’s about Kon…
Something wrong?
I wouldn’t say wrong,
but he’s got no energy.
I can’t blame him.
He just found out that Kujo
is a Mod Soul like himself.
It’s tough for him to go around
behaving like he was before.
That’s why I figured the
livelier it is, the better.
So you actually worry
about such things?
How insensitive do you think I am?!
Wow! This is delicious, Inoue!
This rice!
Inoue, you’re a culinary genius!
You really think so?
Brother sure looks…energetic.
More like weird.
No energy, he says?
Are you kidding?
Well, he was a moment ago.
Hey Four-Eyes!
Are you eating?!
Being able to eat Inoue’s
cooking is a privilege
In fact, I wouldn’t mind him
losing more of that energy.
for a sewing obsessed idiot like you!
Hey Nozomi!
Are you eating?!
You won’t grow if you don’t eat up!
Especially your boobs.
Oops! Sorry! I didn’t mean that!
You’re right. He’s weird.
Late onset adolescence, maybe?
This deep-fried fish rocks!
Where’s Kurosaki?
The way it tickles the taste
buds is out of this world!
And this sauce! It’s too good!
Question her? What’s this about?
It’s about the reason
Kageroza is pursuing
her so relentlessly.
What threat does she represent?
With the showdown with
Kageroza looming,
we thought we should question her.
Neither we, nor you,
know enough about that kid.
We thought we should avoid
any more casualties arising
from our ignorance.
This isn’t just our own opinion.
We’re speaking on behalf
of the surviving Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
It’s nothing personal.
You might be right.
But…
She’s got things she’s
sensitive about too.
I’ll protect her.
Isn’t that enough?
Now’s really not the time
for noble talk, is it?!
Sorry, but it’s a fact that the
invasion force wiped out
the captains of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
We’ll be taking on that
enemy here in Karakura Town.
This time, the casualties might not end
with just us, or with you.
Ironic, isn’t it?
Ironic?
Originally, Project Spearhead was
conceived to prevent
Soul Reaper casualties.
But now, many Soul Reapers
have been injured
and have fallen in order to
protect that Mod Soul kid.
You have to admit, it’s ironic.
You may have a point.
But still…
As long as they’re
born into this world,
they have a right to keep living too.
So that’s it?
That bastard created Mod Souls?
No wonder you couldn’t trust me.
No, that’s not true.
Then what?!
You thought of me as nothing but
one of Kageroza’s creations!
Kageroza didn’t create you.
The very first Mod Soul developed…
was…
me.
That idiot!
But now, many Soul Reapers
have been injured
and have fallen in order to
protect that Mod Soul kid.
You have to admit, it’s ironic.
You’ve got attitude,
but you’re useless.
You’re just like me.
A Hollow!
If only…I weren’t alive…
everyone would be…
Lots of good things will happen
if you keep on living!
Kon!
What’re you doing?!
Hurry and get up!
Okay! Now run as fast as you can!
No!
I also want to…protect…
I want to help too!
For everyone’s sake!
What?!
You… Is that…
Is this my…
I thought you said you
didn’t have a Zanpakuto.
That’s what I thought.
What were you doing out at
such a late hour anyway?!
I’m a burden.
Don’t start that again.
It’s different from before.
Everyone tries to protect me…
But I don’t have the power
to do the same for them.
But when I thought of
wanting to protect you…
I had a sword.
What?
You’re right!
What was I so worried about?
I got all caught up on
what to say to you.
Listen up, Nozomi!
We may have been born as Mod Souls,
but don't let that
stop us from trying to live!
Yes.
Huh?
What’s this doing here?
That’s…
Did you want this?
Sure! It’s yours!
Really?!
Yeah. But it’s defective.
The mane came off.
I like it better that way.
What do you think?
You’re such a kid!
Shut up, pervert!
Hey Ishida. How’d the dinner go?
It went fine.
Right after Inoue finished cooking,
I secretly went and
adjusted the flavoring,
so it all tasted good.
Now that you mention it,
I haven’t eaten yet.
Can I have some—
I have no intention of feeding
someone who escaped into his room.
So you knew about that, huh?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I believe it’s almost
time for dinner.
Allow me to show off my cooking skills
and the power of Ryujinjakka!
Oh, about dinner… Here!
Then I’ll make some tea.
I have that too. See?
Then…
You’re well prepared, aren’t you?
Yes, I am.