Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Now then… I guess I'll begin.
Kira!
What the--!
It seems that it's already begun.
Let's go!
You're…
Thirteen Court Guards
Twelfth Squad Lieutenant,
Nemu Kurotsuchi.
It's been a while.
Y-Yeah…
What do you… I mean, why?
What?!
Well? Do you sense any Bounts?
Hmm… I can't really tell.
I can sense people, but…
I get the feeling that this cave is set up
so as not to let anyone detect
Spiritual Pressure within it.
I see… No wonder
we couldn't find them.
Let's move on!
I wonder if Rangiku and
the others are okay.
I sense a bad presence.
There are four high-ranking
Soul Reapers here.
I don't think that Rangiku and
the others would be defeated.
The appearance of my next target.
That's good…
Can you go, Gesell?
Of course. No problem.
Excellent! Now then…
That's…
Yeah. Just like before.
Damn! They've come out!
Oh! Let's get out of here!
What is this place?
They're ruins.
Probably an ancient
underground capital.
Heh! It's a perfect place
for the Bounts to be hiding.
Kurosaki! Look!
Wha--?!
Damn!
Roar! Zabimaru!!
Take this!
Hado 4!
Byakurai!
Santenkesshun! I reject!!
Thank you, Inoue!
Why you…
Damn! What incredible numbers!
There's no end to them,
no matter how many I cut!
We can't keep this up!
Let's lead them to a narrower pathway
and attack together!
Yeah…
All ri--!
What's wrong, Inoue?
Kuchiki!
Sister!
Rukia!
Renji!
Are you all right?
Yeah. Thanks!
Rukia!
I-I'm all right…
S-Sister…
I-Ichigo, behind you!
What?!
This is it!
Inoue!
That was very good, Orihime!
Tsubaki! Kotenzanshun!
I reject!
Huh?
This is peculiar!
I never thought that he would disappear
in an instant. Was he spirited away?!
I think not!
What is this?!
Oh, crap!
This is what would be called
a round up!
This is no time to be impressed!
Kurosaki!
Th-This guy…
Damn!
Ichigo!
There are too many of them!
This is bad! At this rate, they're going
to be dragged into that shadow!
Do something, Ichigo!
Ah… Is this the end for me?
K-Kurosaki…
Ichigo!
Damn!
You've really lost your powers.
So what about it?
Why are you doing this?!
Do you want power?
I…
I don't want things to end here
without being able to do anything!
I understand.
I shall lend you power.
What?!
Now then…
Shall we finish this?
Crap--!
Ichigo!
Roar… Haineko!
You…
Rangiku!
This doll uses the shadows
produced by the eyes as a gateway!
Destroy everything that can
make a shadow!
Roger!
Zabimaru!
Tsubaki, Kotenzanshun!
I reject!
All right!
These guys are all that's left!
Getsugatensho!
Curse her!
She should have died!
Well, that's fine.
They seem to have taken
some damage.
There's still more to come.
Rukia…
I'm all right.
Kuchiki, don't push yourself.
You still haven't recovered from
your wounds from the previous battle.
I've heard from Shuhei.
You took direct damage
to your soul, didn't you?
Damage to one's soul takes longer to
recover from than bodily wounds do!
But I…
Can you hear me?
My name is Ugaki. I'm a Bount.
My doll's name is Gesell.
Pleased to meet you.
You bastard!
What's the meaning of this?!
Please, listen to what I have to say.
We are absorbing countless souls
which have been gathered by Bitto.
And what happened?
We were able to amplify the power
of our dolls and ourselves
to an unbelievable degree!
We won't let you leave
those strange bugs around!
How insulting to
call them "strange bugs"!
They're the new doll that was
born from Yoshino's life.
We've gained the concentrated
extract of living souls
and have evolved even further.
But even so, we are still sad!
We are human!
We're not monsters, but humans!
Despite that, humans
treated us horribly
just because we had
slightly different abilities.
Rejection! Persecution!
We have no method of
leaving descendants.
The total number of our tribe
is decided.
We can only decrease in numbers.
You cannot understand this pain.
I don't understand!
Renji!
It's not as if we can't sympathize
with your situation!
But that gives you no right to
take other people's lives!
I can't forgive you!
Renji…
It seems my words cannot reach you.
Oh, well…
I'll teach you with your body.
I'll be waiting in the back.
Will you be able to reach me?
He's making fun of us!
Renji!
I'm going, too!
Kurosaki…
Inoue, sorry…
Take care of Rukia
and Rangiku's wounds.
Wait! I can still…
No!
Ichigo…
Only Renji and I will be
going on from here!
Chad, take care of the back.
Protect everyone if an enemy attacks
while they're being treated!
All right.
Ichigo, I think Shuhei and the others
are in the back. But be careful…
I'll catch up to you as soon as
I've recovered.
Please do!
What should we do?
That's right! We can only cheer you on
once we've come this far.
But it's better than nothing.
Don't say that about yourself.
Lirin, you all stay back here, too.
All right.
All right!
Leave this to me!
Sister…
Inoue…
And the newly appeared goddess
who has godly cleavage!
I'll take care of them all!
Yeah, I'm counting on you, Kon!
Let's go, Renji!
Yeah!
Huh?! H-Hold on a second!
Aren't you going to say anything?!
Renji.
What is it?
Are you all right?
Huh?
About that guy's taunt earlier.
Heh! Is that all?!
Well, you were worried
about that kid.
I'm all right.
Who do you think I am?!
Then that's fine.
According to Rangiku…
Gesell's main body won't come out…
if we destroy all the objects
creating shadows.
Yeah!
Not good enough.
What's this?!
This time…
You!
Kira! Hisagi!
Don't think that the same trick
will work twice!
You saved us.
Kira, you're all right.
Abarai, you too.
Kira!
Kira…
Don't worry…
You, too?
Yeah… Unfortunately, I can't say that
I'm completely unharmed.
Sorry you had to go through
so much trouble in that condition.
It doesn't matter!
It was our fault for letting our guards
down to the likes of Bounts.
They sure are persistent!
Scatter!
Thank you!
He only attacks from behind.
How dirty can he get!
Raise your head!
Wabisuke!
What's wrong, Gesell?!
My Wabisuke multiplies
the weight of whatever it cuts.
If I cut it twice, it doubles that,
if I cut it once more,
it doubles once more.
I've sealed away that arm!
What?!
Curse you!
He has one more arm.
Kira!
Yes!
You stupid Soul Reapers--!
Looks like I've got to
call Gesell back
in order to escape that ability, huh?
Return, Gesell!
We've returned the favor.
Hisagi! Kira!
Are you two okay?!
Abarai! Kurosaki!
Go on ahead of us!
Ayasegawa should be there!
We'll find a different route
and catch up to you!
But…
That guy was probably
the guard dog to this hideout!
If we get past him, we can reach
the Bounts we're after!
Renji!
All right.
What's this?
I heard that
this is a battle accessory
which was passed down between
some Quincies several hundred years ago.
The Department of Research and
Development saved it for research.
It has the power to control reishi!
If you are a true Quincy,
I'm sure it will be of help to you.
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
I get a big part in the next episode!
Nothing good has happened to me
since I came to the World of the Living.
But just watch! I'm going to show you
how cool I can be!
Renji! Urahara said to clean the room
you used before you leave.
Yes, sir.
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden After These Messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
We shall begin the regular meeting…
of the Female Soul Reaper Association.
But before that…
Why is Captain Kurotsuchi here?
Because Nemu is out.
I came as her substitute!
Thank me…
Please leave!
Oh… Don't mind me. Begin the--
Oh… No…
It's not as if I came
because I thought it'd be fun.
Leave it to me!