Greetings.
The fall days are very comfortable.
How is your health?
I am doing well.
Recently, there's been a change in my life.
I have a new roommate in my cell.
I'm not sure if he's pure evil or just a fool.
One thing's for sure.
He's the reason I'm able to continue writing letters to you.
It won't be long before we are able to meet.
I hope to tell you much about my roommate, my friend.
I eagerly anticipate the day.
Sincerely yours.
Everybody Loves Pajamas
Hey, Gramps.
Where's your partner?
Oh, he went to the restroom.
What? I told you to always get permission and
accompany him to the restroom.
Sorry, he's taking a dump, so I figured I shouldn't tag along.
Oh, it's okay.
Shachi needed to take a dump, so he tagged along.
That's not the issue here.
Oh, now I need to take a dump.
Will you come with me, guard?
Why?!
Bro, if they find us,
they won't even bother sending us to the disciplinary room.
That's right.
I want to go to the warden's room,
not the disciplinary room, Shake-kun.
It's Shachi.
We're going to find proof that he's breaking the law.
Weren't you his pawn?
Show me the way, Hamachi-kun.
It's Shachi!
It's impossible!
Do you realize how many locked doors we have to go through?!
Yes, this is Kamiya.
What?! What are you doing, you idiot?!
Damn, did they find out that we ditched our work?
You lost the keys?!
Were they stolen?!
I guess it wasn't us.
We need to get back before we're caught.
Grow a spine.
They're busy looking for whoever stole the keys.
They won't care about a couple fellows skipping work.
Let's go.
They're gonna care!
Because the person who stole the keys is right here!
Huh? Where?
It's you! Why are you acting surprised?!
I didn't steal anything.
I just picked up the keys after someone dropped them.
And I'm going to give them back.
That doesn't make it okay!
Bro, you're going all the way this time.
Yeah, time for revenge, Itachi-kun.
That's not even close to my name.
Okay, let's disguise ourselves so we don't stand out.
You're the man, Bro.
You must have stolen clothes from the guards.
Listen up.
I'm a guard in pajamas.
You're the prisoner I'm bringing in.
Nothing's changed!
How are you a guard in pajamas?!
The only difference is you're wearing a western style prison uniform
instead of an Asian one!
Don't blame me.
The guard was working a night shift so he had his pajamas on.
Why was the guard wearing pajamas like that?!
Hell, you might as well be naked!
Don't worry.
If I put on a bandanna and carry a stick...
See? Don't I look like a guard in pajamas?
Don't act like guards in pajamas are a common phenomenon!
Nobody's seen one before!
Then I won't pretend to be a guard.
I'm a pajama kid with a pillow and I don't believe in ghosts.
Why would a pajama kid be walking around with a prisoner?!
And who cares if you believe in ghosts?!
What's that in your right hand?!
What are we supposed to say if they find us?!
Hey! What are you guys doing?!
Why is a prisoner here with a pajama kid?!
What's going on?!
Don't move!
K-Keep it down!
Or this pajama kid is gonna get it!
H-Help me pajama!
I see!
He's taken the pajama kid hostage so he can escape!
Wait, why is this pajama kid even here?!
Shut up! Everyone wants to be a pajama kid!
If you keep talking, these pajamas will be torn apart!
Stop! Don't hurt the pajamas!
Why are you a bad guy now?!
Raise your hands! Outta the way!
Clear the path!
Listen to me.
If you follow me, you know what's gonna happen!
These white lines will be completely red!
About face, then march!
Then go into the locker room and change into your pajamas!
Listen to me, if you button them wrong, you know what's gonna happen!
G-Got it.
Go!
We're on high alert!
Get the prisoners into their cells!
Were they really stolen?
I-I'm sorry...
Apologizing isn't going to help!
Where's the warden?
Well, he's out right now.
They've been found out...
Damn, why now?!
Come in.
This is the warden speaking.
The warden?
Yes, I wanted everyone to gather in one place.
Who are you?!
You're not the warden!
I'm the warden.
But I'm not feeling well,
so someone else is doing the talking for me.
W-Warden!
Welcome to our land, guards.
Warden's Office
This is bad, Bro!
We need to hurry!
Damn! I can't find anything incriminating!
Bro!
I had the kids on the outside do some research.
I gave them one of the letters the old man's been getting
and told them to check the address.
Why are you bringing this up now, Bro?
They went to the address to see his son.
But they didn't find him.
He wasn't there?
No.
And it wasn't just the wrong address.
He's no longer in this world.
You mean...
His son died ten years ago.
Of disease.
He's been writing letters to someone who will never get them.
That would explain why he never got any responses.
But at some point, he began to receive frequent replies.
From someone who no longer existed...
Who was it?!
Were those letters written by a ghost?!
Our positions have been reversed, warden.
Hey, warden.
Looks like your own men hate you as much as the prisoners do.
Hey, if you don't come out,
we'll take out all our stress on the warden!
Watch closely.
We're going to beat the warden to death!
Stop!
Stop this nonsense. It's for your own good.
Hey, unlock that door.
Did you say something, old man?
For an old man who was stuck in prison for the rest of his life,
his son was the only light in his dark world.
But it was an illusion.
There was no light.
But you couldn't take that away from him.
When you're sitting behind bars, the whole world is an illusion.
So he gave him what he could.
That would explain why they only made small talk.
From your son.
You're...
Bastards, you think you can get away with touching my toys?
I'm sending you all to the disciplinary room.
I never imagined that the sick and twisted warden was
doing this for the old man.
He pretended to be the old man's son to hide his death.
If the old man is allowed to see his son,
these letters will have been for nothing.
That's why he's been trying to get me to make trouble.
To get his clemency revoked.
Why would the warden do this?
Beats me.
He probably doesn't know either.
Attention, criminals!
Open the doors and release the guards at once!
Or else you will all have your sentences increased!
You're the ones who locked us up in here!
We're just making ourselves comfortable!
Shit, they started a riot!
The warden's wish came true in an unexpected way.
The old man's clemency ain't happening now.
That doesn't matter!
Those guys aren't gonna let the warden live!
The old man's in danger, too!
Can't have that.
If he dies, there won't be anyone to prove my innocence.
Besides , I finally found evidence of his evil.
I'll make him pay for the crime of fooling a weak old man.
Bro, was that your goal from the beginning?
Thanks for the help.
Now hide.
If you mess around any more, they'll hang you.
Wait, you were using me for your own petty reasons?
It's my turn to use you.
I don't give a damn about the old man or the guards.
But I can't let our sentences be extended because of one stupid warden.
I'll act as a decoy and draw the attention of the guards.
Use that opening to deal with this riot.
Wait, that's...
Go crazy and get some more time tacked onto your sentence.
Then we can continue to have a blast in this place.
Hey, wait!
Hey, look!
It's Shachi!
Get him!
Catch me if you can.
But it won't be easy to grab the sleeve of the king of criminals!
Your sleeves were ripped off!
I'm counting on you, Bro.
Yeah, I got this, Buri.
It's Shachi!
Damn! They used the commotion to run away!
Shachi's men aren't around either!
Damn! If the hostages escape, we'll be crushed!
Find them!
Warden, a lot of men have been injured.
We need to get them medical care.
Old man, hang in there. Hey, old man!
The prisoners want me.
I'll hold them here.
What?
But you'll be...
Are you trying to get yourself killed?!
Give this to the old man.
Kuzunosuke Beri
It's the last letter.
Found ya.
Hey, what are you all doing here?
Move it!
If you don't hurry, I'll throw you into the disciplinary room!
Warden! We'll be back with help as soon as we can!
Don't die!
Warden!
Greetings.
I apologize that this isn't a letter from your son.
If you are reading this letter,
it means that I have disappeared for one reason or another,
and you are no longer receiving letters from your son.
However, you don't need to worry.
Your son is doing fine.
His work has taken him to another planet,
so it's difficult for him to send letters.
There is a lot of paperwork that has to be done
before you can receive mail from another planet.
I apologize that I was unable to continue delivering his letters.
I'm sure that you no longer remember,
but when I was first assigned this position,
I was a complete outsider.
After causing trouble everywhere I went,
my parents dumped me in prison.
The hardened criminals weren't going
to listen to a clueless young fool,
and the guards resented me for my connections.
I would often find myself going to the oldest prisoner, you.
The rules of the prison,
methods for handling nasty prisoners,
the way to strike underhanded deals,
as well as the fact that the outside light was a ray of hope
for the prisoners in their dark cells...
I learned everything from you.
I can't say that I'm a respectable member of society.
I'm aware that I have nothing to be proud of.
However, you're the reason I'm able to stand
on my own, unsightly legs.
All I could manage was to help deliver these letters.
However, I would be happy to know that they gave you hope.
There will be a significant delay before the next letter arrives,
but please don't forget that there is
someone outside who is thinking of you.
Please remember that your son is not the only person
who cares about you.
It was nice knowing you.
From the evil prison warden.
We finally shut him up.
Hey, we're not finished with you yet.
Excellent.
It's your favorite place, the disciplinary room.
Disciplinary Room
This will make the perfect tomb.
Time to pay you back for all the abuse.
Hey, I have something to tell you guys who are
never returning to society.
When entering someone else's cell, knock first.
That's prison etiquette.
Especially when you're entering the disciplinary room.
There might be a really violent criminal inside.
Son of a bitch!
B-Bastard...
Why are you here?
It's too early for you to die.
You haven't met your father yet, you stupid son.
Bastard...
Hey! Have you forgotten what he did to us?!
I haven't forgotten.
Let me handle this.
You've blown off enough steam.
If you still need some exercise, I'll be happy to take you on.
Well, warden?
Did you forget your promise to me?
If I make trouble, you'll set me free.
Now, who's the most stressed out guy here?
Let's start the first Tournament of Stress!
Bring it!
Welcome to my disciplinary room!
Warden!
Are you okay, Warden?
What? I don't see any of the prisoners who were rioting.
Over there! There's a prisoner!
Why is he in a western uniform?!
Hey, stop!
Where are you going?!
Enough.
Warden!
Set him free.
Huh?
These prison walls can't contain him.
The prison's really calmed down.
We got prison guards and prisoners sleeping next to each other.
They all need to relax.
Still, I'm surprised they haven't hanged us yet.
That's the thing.
I heard that we won't be punished.
Huh? Why not?
The warden isn't going to let us off.
Didn't you hear? The warden...
I heard that you're going to shoulder the prisoners' crimes.
I knew that it was risky to play with prisoners
since there are people like you.
What I did was nothing compared to your letter business.
You chose a kind illusion over harsh reality.
Since you made that choice,
you're obligated to keep up the lie until the very end.
But you got scared
that he would eventually find out you were lying.
So you gave up and ran away.
As a result, the old man's being allowed to meet up with his son again.
I no longer have the right to walk through this door.
You don't have the right to whine either.
You're supposed to be an evil warden.
Tell the old man the harsh truth and laugh in his face,
or keep feeding him illusions until the day he dies.
One or the other.
Make sure the old man knows your decision.
And then I'll forgive you for throwing me in the slammer.
Or else, I'll send your head flying and go back to jail.
If I'm an evil warden, you're a demon.
The old man never told me
that it was so hard to give prisoners hope.
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
True, you've been fooling the old man for a long time.
You pretended to be his son and offered him false hope.
But your feelings for the old man are no illusion.
Come on. It's time for the meeting.
Wait, I no longer...
No longer have the right to go in?
That's not true.
I have a criminal who's been
accused of falsifying documents and identity fraud!
O-Okay, get in here, maggot!
The victim is waiting in the visiting room,
you mother-licking insect!
Y-You bastards...
Yes, pajamas are the best.
I don't see anything happening.
Warden, time for some of the best prison role playing of your life.
Listen up, you have ten minutes.
Any longer and the chief will find out...
I mean, you're not allowed to meet any longer!
Got it?
Good grief.
We have so many nasty-looking guards around now.
I heard that you quit your job.
Do you have another job yet?
No, I'm searching still.
I see...
Well, I wish you the best of luck.
Try not to get yourself called an evil warden again.
Yeah...
Guard, we're finished.
Huh? Already?
Wait, old man!
I've been...
Don't say anything.
We were able to make small talk, just like always.
That's all I need.
Old man, did you...
I read the letter.
It was better than usual.
But your handwriting is still ugly.
Kuzunosuke Beri
Warden, I've always been writing letters to my son outside.
A son who turned out to have a nasty personality,
but that foolish son of mine is dedicated to his job.
I'm glad I was able to see you today.
Will you continue to write?
Yeah, I will.
It's a promise.
Yeah, whoever breaks the promise gets sent to the disciplinary room.
Ow!
Next Episode: Speaking of Crossovers, Don't Forget About Alien vs. Predator
Next week at this time:
Sket Dance!
For real?!