No!
I also want to…protect…
I want to help too!
For everyone’s sake!
What?!
Oh, you’re still here?
Dinner is ready you know.
What’s the matter?
Nothing.
You could at least knock
before you come in!
Sorry about that.
Wait, this is my room!
You’re going to be late!
Hey, wait up!
I’m coming in.
Why Captain Kuchiki…
What are you doing?
Well… I’m still
working on repairing the
invasion troops whose
cores were destroyed
in the last battle.
But it won’t be long now.
How about yourself?
See for yourself.
Then…
Yes.
Inform Captains Zaraki,
Hitsugaya and Komamura.
We’ll be heading for the
World of the Living soon.
SOUL REAPER IMPOSTER CRISIS
COMMITTEE HEADQUARTERS
According to Captain Unohana,
who escaped from the Soul Society,
the Reigai are immensely powerful now
that their powers are not restricted.
Even the Head Captain’s wounds
will take time to heal completely.
The situation is critical.
We know what the enemy is after.
Our only option is to hide
Nozomi Kujo somewhere
while we devise countermeasures.
But what countermeasures?
Do you really think all
the captains are dead?
They’re not dead.
Huh?
Captain Zaraki wouldn’t
die that easily!
But…if they’re alive,
where are they?
You bastard, I’m gonna kill you!
I’m going to fight too!
Nozomi…
Now just a minute!
Just because you got your Zanpakuto back
doesn’t make you a match for them!
Kageroza’s Zanpakuto has the
power to cut time and space
and restore it at will.
But my Zanpakuto can counter his.
I think.
You don’t sound too sure.
What power do you have?
I don’t remember everything yet.
But I just know!
That’s no help at all!
Maybe you can, maybe you can’t.
We can’t risk everything
on something like that.
First of all, why do we
have to protect this girl?
We’ll fight the enemy and beat them!
That’s all there is to it.
Where are you going?
Discussing it further
won’t do any good!
There’s no talking to that guy.
So, what’ll we do…about her?
Nozomi,
since we don’t know
what your powers are,
we cannot allow you,
their target, to fight.
But my power can…
It’s true!
I’m this close to
remembering its name.
Nozomi, at this point,
you can’t expect us
to put our trust in you.
If it’s dormant,
then let’s wake it up.
Boss…
Yes.
It seems they got caught in our trap.
Shall we proceed with the next step?
Do it.
Since we can’t expect support
from the Soul Society,
we’ll have to freeze
the space ourselves.
It’s going to be a huge job.
So it’s Kisuke Urahara’s doing.
I see.
It appears they’ve
all become separated.
This plan won’t buy them much time.
It’s not enough.
Harder!
Nozomi!
This intense training is going too far!
Keep out of this, pervert!
This is the only way to awaken
my dormant Zanpakuto!
That’s what you say, but…
Shut up!
It’s okay.
We’re doing the right thing.
Did she just…
She sucked away Chad’s
Spiritual Pressure?
It’s working.
Next!
Okay!
Over here!
Thanks for waiting.
What’s the matter, Ikkaku?
Interested?
Yeah right.
What I’m concerned about
is when the Reigai are coming here.
Let’s take a break.
Not necessary!
Don’t rush.
You’ll only fail if you
try to do it all at once.
You tell her, Inoue!
Nozomi, have some of Inoue’s
special sports drink and relax a bit.
I don’t want any!
Where are you going?
To wash my face.
No sense in rushing things, right?
Do you really think that’s
going to help you fight?
Stop already.
You’ll just hurt yourself
if you keep it up.
What?!
But I’m still…
I’ll admit that you’ve
got some sort of power.
But a real fight isn’t that simple.
Even if you get your powers back,
you’ll just be killed.
I…
intended to die.
But I was told to live.
I’m taking their words to heart.
This time, it’s my turn
to help everyone live.
To do that, I’m willing
to die fighting.
I have one wish.
To fight under him and die.
That’s all.
You fool.
Living and helping others
live is your business,
but you have to be willing to strike,
or else you won’t be able to take
what they’re trying to throw at you.
Let’s do this!
Come!
What’s this Spiritual Pressure?
Wha-?!
Renji!
The enemy’s attacking.
The Reigai got caught
in the trap Urahara
set in the Precipice World.
What?!
But Nozomi still hasn’t
regained her Shikai.
Anyway, we need to get
her someplace safe!
No, let’s continue, Ichigo.
Damn it!
Do you understand what’s
happening here?!
If the Reigai are coming,
there is no safe place.
I need to regain my Shikai
as quickly as possible!
Yeah, Nozomi’s right.
Not you too…
Jeez…
Fine, I’ll help too.
Renji…
No time to waste talking.
Right!
Looks like I’m the first one here.
Huh?
You’re my opponent?
Yeah, that’s right.
I have no intention of going along
with Ichigo and the others’ plans.
When an enemy shows up, I fight.
That’s what I do!
What was that just now?
This Spiritual Pressure is…Ikkaku?
Is he fighting one of the Reigai?
Ikkaku!
Don’t.
Do you want to waste
Ikkaku’s efforts?
Ikkaku is trying to buy us time.
To help that kid.
Madarame!
We’re here to help!
Keep out of this!
This is my fight!
Not that again!
Besides, looks like you guys
have your own opponents.
What?!
More Reigai?
Damn…
I’ll handle this one.
You guys take care of that side.
Guess we’ll have to!
Don’t die, Ikkaku!
Sorry about the wait!
Now there’s no one to get in our way.
Let’s settle this man to man!
You can’t beat me!
Oh, you took that well.
Shut up!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
Is that all?
Nozomi!
Are you all right?
You’re exhausted!
Shut up!
Ichigo, keep going!
Gotcha.
Not yet!
Okay!
Hey…
How long are you going to keep this up?
Continuing this is a waste of time.
You need to hit her with some
serious Spiritual Pressure.
What?
You’re all talk.
Time to put a quick end
to this and leave.
What’s this supposed to be?
It’s not over yet.
This is boring.
I’m telling you that
you’re no match for me.
Decide that…after you see this.
What do you mean?
Just what I said.
You both say you’re going all out,
but you’re holding back
without realizing it.
At this rate, this girl’s Zanpakuto
will never wake up.
Threaten her with
real Spiritual Pressure filled
with murderous intent.
Unless you stop it, you’ll die.
It’s as simple as that.
All right. Do it!
Hey, now hold on!
That’s way overdoing it!
I don’t care!
Nozomi…
Ichigo!
Say something!
You’re sure you want to do this?
What?!
Yeah, I’m sure!
This is…the last time!
Bankai!
Ryumon Hozukimaru!
This one’s just for you!
Oh?
Then let’s see if that can stop me!
Now we’re having fun!
You won’t be laughing soon!
What?
This Zanpakuto awakens through battle.
Here goes!
Bankai!
Damn it!
Getsugatensho!
Living and helping others
live is your business,
but you have to be willing to strike,
or else you won’t be able to take
what they’re trying to throw at you.
Strike back…
I remember now!
This is my Zanpakuto…
Arazomeshigure!
Nozomi…
Nozomi!
You done?
Damn you…
I did enjoy that a bit.
But…now…
Stop!
Huh?
What?
Did you come to be captured?
Of course not!
Rain down, Arazomeshigure!
Interesting!
Now that’s pretty awesome.
That was amazing, Nozomi.
You defeated Kenpachi’s Reigai.
It’s because of everyone’s help.
Wait, maybe I’m the
one who’s amazing!
Kon!
I’m the one who discovered Nozomi.
Which puts me above her!
So that means I’m the strongest!
Listen to me!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Crap…
I left my snack behind.
You jerk!
Don’t bring stuff
into people’s rooms!
I forgot my drinks!
Wait…
I forgot my mirror.
Look, you guys…
Go get them right now!
It’s okay, we can get them later!
-No it’s not! My house
isn’t a locker room!
-Unlike you guys, I
brought…the wrong one!
Good grief!
What is this mess?
My…
What the heck?!