Shunko!
If you ain't gonna run,
I will kill you right here, right now.
What's the matter?
You're not done already, are you?
You'd better make your
next move quickly.
I will crush them one at a time,
down to your last remaining one.
The number of methods you
contrived to defeat me
is proof of your effort
and strength.
At the same time, it represents
the number of hopes you hold.
If that is so, then what I must do
is to crush each one of them.
Now, come at me with
your next attack.
It's meaningless to argue
what is special.
If a single swing makes
one disappear,
then three more swings will make
that specialness disappear.
Yoruichi!
Pay attention.
Your back is wide open.
Psych! Just messing with you.
Maybe somewhere inside of you,
you've already given
up on this fight.
That's not...
My, my...
How pathetic.
I was hoping you'd
be better than that,
but I guess you really
are just a kid.
You're weak inside.
I couldn't possibly let Captain
Aizen fight a coward like you.
What is that stance?!
Kamishininoyari... Buto.
It's already back in place?!
Kamishininoyari Butorenjin.
You leave me no choice.
It's that range...
That Zanpakuto's
greatest strength
is that it can attack
with any timing,
regardless of the distance between
itself and its opponent.
And it also acts as a defense,
preventing the opponent from attacking.
If I could only get
inside his space,
I should be able to
break through!
You seem to be thinking
something up,
but I think it's useless.
Hey... Not bad.
So close.
I guess that's all you've got.
You probably thought you might
be able to do something
by unleashing a Hollowfied Getsugatensho
after getting inside my Shinso's range,
but you don't seem
to understand yet.
That can't be.
You were able to stop my attack
with your Zanpakuto,
so why didn't you consider that I could
do the same thing against your attack?
What wishful thinking.
You saw no need to even move?
You seriously underestimate us.
Is this a good idea?
Too bad. You failed to
strike a decisive blow.
That is, of course, assuming
your decisive attacks
are enough to critically
wound me.
Captain Ichimaru.
Matsumoto!
That's reckless.
I could only heal
you to the point
of barely keeping
you alive.
I'm not done healing you yet.
Matsumoto...
How pathetic.
Were you this weak?
Even your mask is so fragile.
Is that the best a Hollowfication could do?
At least back then...
You were more frightening.
Oh well.
You, get out of here.
What?!
Are you all right?
Like I said, who do you think
you're speaking to?!
I was wearing your half-assed
protective gear, so I tried to block him.
If hadn't been wearing it, I would've
dodged normally and been uninjured!
Well, excuse me.
What're you looking at?
You.
I'm watching you,
thinking that your
feigned sense of concern
is part of your strategy.
I thought you decided
not to be on guard.
I'm not. I'm observing.
In the Soul Society,
you were the only one with a
mind that exceeded my own.
Even if our strengths
are no longer equal,
I find you interesting.
You overestimate me.
Nowadays, I'm just a mere
small-time candy shop owner.
Hado Number 32: Oukasen!
You should know that Kido at the
thirties level have
no meaning at all.
The fact that you
used it means...
As expected.
You appear to enjoy using
the same tactic.
Don't you get it?
You can't defeat me
with your blows,
no matter how many thousands
you hit me with.
Shunko!
I said, you can't defeat me.
Shibari Benihime!
Did you really think you could
bind me with this?
Hiasobi Benihime...
Juzutsunagi!
Don't make me laugh.
Is this the best you can do?
Do you think this will...
Getsuga Tensho!
How's it look?
I don't know.
After taking that form,
his Spiritual Pressure has become
completely unreadable.
I know he's frighteningly powerful,
but when we fight him
or slash at him,
it feels like there's nothing there.
It's creepy.
It's likely only those who
are at the same level
as Aizen can feel his
current power.
That was a fine sword attack.
I now understand that
attack, as well.
What is that in there?
What's going on?
I think it's time...
you understood my powers...
Is it all right to turn around when
I'm right in front of you?
Looks like Getsuga Tensho
has reached its limit.
It didn't work on me, and neither did it
work on Captain Aizen, who was hit directly.
He doesn't even look damaged at all.
There's nothing more
you can do.
Hollowfication and Getsuga Tensho.
Neither of them worked,
so it's hopeless.
Things might be different, though,
if you still have something
up your sleeve, but...
You don't, do you?
And besides, you're
no longer a warrior.
You're not a Soul Reaper.
Nor are you a Hollow,
or a human being.
Here, in your ambiguous condition,
do you think you can
win against an
opponent to whom
those three lost?
For your own good...
Get out of here.
You don't want to
die yet, do you?
I'm not interested
in you anymore.
Captain Aizen would probably be
disappointed in you the
way you are now.
You're afraid of Captain
Aizen, aren't you?
You're able to understand
how strong Captain
Aizen is, aren't you?
That was your last warning.
If you still won't get out of here...
I will kill you right here, right now.
Dad... Urahara... Yoruichi!
Gin...
What were you about
to do to him?
Just a small test of his strength.
I see.
Open the Senkaimon.
We will head to Karakura Town
in the Soul Society.
There won't be any need to
destroy the Tenkaiketchu.
If we are to take down
the palace,
it would be to our advantage to
create the Ouken in
the Soul Society.
Yes.
W-Wait!
Captain Aizen...
Oh.
It seems I'm at the end
of the Chrysalis Stage.
Thank goodness.
I will be able to witness the end
of the Soul Society
with my own eyes.
Unlock.
I will leave you here.
You shall be devoured
when everything has ended.
What's happening? What's....
Ichigo!
What're you just standing
there for?
Open the Senkaimon!
Dad!
The Precipice World...
It feels so nostalgic.
It truly does.
The Cleaner.
This isn't good.
Let's go, Captain Aizen.
Captain Aizen, we should go quickly.
That thing exists on
the side of reason,
rather than Spiritual Pressure.
It's not something you can deal
with using Spiritual Pressure.
Captain Aizen?
What are you afraid of, Gin?
Reason exists for those who must
rely on reason to survive.
Well, shall we get going?
Towards the end of all reason.
Dad...
Let's go.
We're going to protect
Karakura Town.
Huh?
Didn't you hear me?!
I said we're going to protect
Karakura Town!
There's no way.
There's just no way.
We don't know if it's impossible!
I know!
And you know too, Dad!
There's no way we can beat a monster
with that kind of Spiritual Pressure!
I see.
Just as I thought, you do
understand that guy's Spiritual Pressure.
Huh?
Let's go.
Aren't you coming?
If you're not coming,
what're you going to do?
Are you going to cry?
Are you going to sit there and cry
because you couldn't protect
something again?!
Think hard about what it means
for Aizen to be heading to Soul Society.
Unless you go,
it means that everyone, the
people you want to protect,
and the others who are
in Karakura Town
is all going to die
at Aizen's hands.
Dad...
Open the Senkaimon.
Karakura Town is that way.
You were a bit off.
Mind not making it sound
like it's my fault?
It was your child's play
that threw us off from
our original destination,
Captain Aizen.
Yes, you're right.
Sorry about that.
Shall we take a little walk?
Wait! Ichigo!
What?! Weren't we in a hurry?!
Something's odd.
There's no sign of the Cleaner.
Cleaner?
You mean that Spiritual Pressure
train-like thing?
Yeah.
Ordinarily, a Soul Reaper can't
do anything about the Cleaner.
From the traces of Spiritual Pressure,
it appears Aizen did something.
Is it bad if that thing is gone?
If we leave things like
this, it's not good.
But...
Right now, it's to our advantage.
What?
This Precipice World,
as the name suggests,
is a place isolated
temporally and spatially
from both the World of the Living
and the Soul Society.
The Cleaner existed to keep
those who entered here
from staying a long time.
But right now, it's gone.
I'll be able to teach
you in this place.
Teach me? What?
The Final Getsugatensho!
The Final...
Getsugatensho?
Why was I sleeping here?
What do you mean by the
Final Getsugatensho?
Hey, answer me!
Hold on a second.
I got a little carried away
while saying it.
I'm trying to come up with
what it is right now!
Dad, you bastard!
Wait! I lied!
Don't worry, I'll teach you!
There you go again
with your ranting.
Don't hit your dad!
Stop, you'll kill me!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
The title is "Cell Phones."
Hello? It's me.
I told you not to do it.
Shut up.