Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Dammit! This sure is
a long staircase!
How many steps are there anyway?!
Quit griping, will you?!
All right, we made it!
No one’s around!
Security's lax here, too.
Okay, we're going straight through
to the inner area.
Seireitei Squad Five Station
In-Station Special Detention Cell
Captain…
You look awful.
Rangiku…
Have you calmed down a bit?
Umm…
I’m so sorry.
I’ve caused you trouble as well.
Huh?  Oh… Never mind me,
I wasn’t able to do anything.
Umm…
How are things outside?
It’s chaotic.
Something such as this
occurring within the station…
It’s unheard of. There’s still the
situation with the Ryoka.
Everyone’s doing their own thing,
completely losing focus.
Then, what about arresting
the perpetrator?
They still haven’t finished investigating
the crime scene.
We have no choice but to await
the General Captain’s decision.
But… But the one
who killed the Captain…
Stop it!
Don’t say such a reckless thing!
I know I just said that
everything was chaotic.
But Squad 5 is the one
suffering the most right now.
They’ve lost both their Captain
and Lieutenant at the same time.
You know what that means.
It’s not that I don’t understand
how you feel.
However…
At that time…
At the time you found
Captain Aizen, the actions you took…
Was there no other option,
was that truly what had to be done?
Couldn’t you at least consider that?
The title of the Lieutenant
shouldn’t be taken so lightly.
I’m so sorry.
I…  I…
Here.
This was in Captain Aizen’s room.
It’s addressed to you.
Captain Aizen… for me?
You’re lucky it was
our captain who found it.
If it were anyone else,
it probably would have
been submitted as evidence.
It may never have reached you.
I don’t know what’s written inside, but…
Having your captain leave
his final words to you,
that ought to be
a happy thing for a Lieutenant.
Appreciate it as you read it.
Oh, thank you very much.
Hinamori, if you’re reading this letter,
then I must not have made it back.
The Captain…
He knew he was
being targeted.
Last night, after I fell asleep…
he wrote this letter.
Captain…
I’ve caused you a lot of worry.
For that, all the words of
apology would never suffice.
Until now, I have never
spoken to you
about the apprehension I have felt.
However, I want you to understand
that it was only because
I did not wish to get you
involved in this.
Please, if possible, forgive me.
For after all this,
I still got you involved.
I am probably no longer
with the living.
Therefore, to you,
in whom I have utmost trust,
I leave this record of the truths
which I have uncovered.
This is…!
Wha--!
What is this, this…
outrageous Spiritual Pressure?!
Crap!
Let’s run for it!
I don’t know what’s up,
but I’m sure there's someone terrible
around the corner!
Before the enemy finds us,
we’ve got to run and get ahead!
Yeah!
Y-Yes…
Let’s go!
He’s finally here.
I was getting tired of waiting.
Let’s see.
Something’s wrong.
What’s going on?
We’ve been running
and running and yet,
I don’t feel any distance
between us and the enemy.
My legs feel heavy.
Damn, I’m running,
I know I’m running…
This Spiritual Pressure…
It’s like I have a knife pressed
against my throat the whole time…
Huh, hey! What are you doing?!
I-I’m sorry.
There’s no strength in my body.
I swear…
you sure are a handful.
Are you all right?
Shut up! Never mind, run!
Three of them, huh?…
Which one is it?
Not that one…
Are you the one?
What’s the matter?
How long are you going to
keep looking over there?
Eh?…
Wh-What the heck?
What’s the matter?
How long are you going
to keep looking over there?
Eh?
Wh-What the heck?
I’m sure I was stabbed.
The intent to kill?
Could just the killing intent do that?
You’re Ichigo Kurosaki, right?
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
What? Haven’t you heard
from Ikkaku?
Heard from Ikkaku?
Wait a minute…
Let me ask you one thing.
What?
Among your group,
who is the strongest?
That’d probably be me.
I see.
Then you had better
watch out for my captain.
He has no interest in weaklings,
but if what you said is true,
then you will surely be targeted by him.
Is he strong?
You’ll find out just how strong
when you meet him.
That is, if you survive long enough
to even comprehend just
how powerful he is.
What’s his name?
I’m Kenpachi Zaraki,
captain of Squad 11.
I’m here to fight you to the death.
I felt Spiritual Pressure again.
To feel it through the Sekki-Seki
walls of this tower…
What is going on outside?
Let me tell you about
one unconfirmed report.
You know about the Ryoka that
entered the Soul Society yesterday, right?
There were five.
Allegedly, one of them is
an orange-haired Soul Reaper
wielding a body-length sword.
Ichigo… Is it really you?
If you’re still alive…
I couldn’t wish for anything more.
Run away.
Run…and forget about me.
In this world, there are forces
which defy the logic of the living world.
Run, run away.
So that you may live…
So this is him.
So this is Kenpachi Zaraki,
Captain of Squad 11.
Should you encounter a captain,
don’t hesitate and get away!
The Spiritual Pressure I’ve
been sensing until now was his.
How do I get away from that?!
What’s the matter?
I said, I’m here to fight you…
to the death.
Since you haven’t replied, shall I start?
Ganju! Hanataro!
Hana…!
Hey! Are you okay…
You idiot, Ichigo!
Ganju!
Hanataro and I caught a bit
of that Spiritual Pressure.
Don’t worry.
Never mind us, you just face
what’s in front of you.
Or he’ll take you out
before you know it!
Wow!
Look at that drool!
He must have been really scared
of Kenny, poor thing!
Oopsey…
He got mad at me.
Stupid. It’s your fault.
What is she?
Where’d she come from?!
Why?
How come she's totally unaffected?
Stupid is as stupid says.
Is that so?
Hey, you twerp!
Yeah?
What the heck are you?
I’m Yachiru Kusajishi.
Lieutenant of Squad 11.
Pleased to meet you!
Lieutenant?!
She’s the same rank as Renji?
But…
Just now, I didn’t even
notice her until she landed on me.
She’s no ordinary one either.
Ganju!
Yeah!
Take Hanataro and go on ahead!
I’ll manage somehow.
Take care of Rukia!
What are you saying?
Ganju!
Please…
Damn…
My my, they went away.
Sorry, but I can’t let you
pass through here.
You don’t get it, do you?
What?!
Don’t make me repeat myself.
I’ve been waiting here
just to duke it out with you.
Your friends or
that Kuchiki what’s-her-name…
Whether they drop dead
is no concern of mine
Is that so?
Hey, not bad.
Though your stance is rigid
and full of gaps.
Your Spiritual Pressure
is something else.
Your run-of-the-mill lieutenants
would be no match.
No wonder Ikkaku lost.
But, you’re still not up to par with me.
How about it? I’ll give you a handicap.
What?
I’ll let you take the first swing.
You can cut me up anywhere you like.
Wha--?!
Awesome! Kenny, you’re so generous!
Aren’t I? I’m literally
a bleeding heart of generosity!
Stop messing with me!
What the heck are you saying?
You think I can attack someone
who hasn’t drawn their weapon?
Are you mocking me?
I’m not mocking you.
It’s just a freebie.
It’s admirable that you don’t want
to attack someone who hasn’t drawn,
but you better save that
nicety for another occasion.
Don’t be so uptight.
Let’s have some fun.
To kill or to be killed…
It’s just another way to kill some time.
So, come on.
You can go for my neck,
my gut, my eyeball…
If you want, you can
even kill me with this attack.
Stop quivering!
Come!
Ichigo…
No, Ichigo!
You’re in danger, run!
Idiot, quit squirming!
Are you a moron?
It’s dangerous to move
all of a sudden!
W-Where are we?
Where’s Ichigo?
We’re on our way to
the Shishinro.
Ichigo…stayed behind with them.
Stayed behind?! By himself?!
He can’t! He has to get way!
I have to go back and help!
Huh? Hey Hana, calm down.
It’s impossible!
There’s no way he can defeat him…
Even Ichigo will be killed!
Hana, you know that
pokey-headed guy?
He is…
He is the Squad 11 Captain,
Kenpachi Zaraki.
The name “Kenpachi” is passed
down through the generations
to the one among
the 13 Court Guard Squads
who most loves fighting
and most loves killing.
The name means,
no matter how many times he’s killed,
he will never go down.
It’s beyond the realm of
being strong or weak.
He cannot die. He’s immortal!
If Ichigo fights him,
he will surely be killed.
I see…
After hearing that,
I’m even more sure we can’t go back.
Ganju!
Listen up!
That guy… Ichigo asked us…
Ichigo asked us to take care
of Rukia Kuchiki.
We all felt that Spiritual Pressure.
Ichigo and I both know that
that wire-headed freak isn’t normal.
So Ichigo made up his mind…
to stay back and fight,
so that we can go ahead.
And that was because
more than anything,
Ichigo was determined to make
saving this Kuchiki person the priority!
Do you understand, Hanataro?
We’ve been entrusted
to carry out that determination!
Ganju…
We can’t be dawdling here!
If you get it, then let’s go!
Y-Yes!
Ichigo…
After we’ve saved this Rukia,
we’ll surely come back for you…
And when we do,
let’s all go back to
the Rukongai together.
I still have a ton of things
to tell you.
So Ichigo, until then,
don’t you dare die!
You’ve got to be kidding…
I know I swung with my full force.
Why is it that…
there’s not even a scratch on him?
my hand’s split instead?
This…
What? Hey…
Is that it?
I’m so disappointed.
What was that?
What did he just do?
He touched the Zangetsu’s blade
with his bare hands! That’s crazy!
It’s useless, Ichy!
You can’t cut Kenny.
Because to Kenny,
this thing is the same
as not having a blade at all.
What…?
Want me to tell you?
Why your sword can’t cut me?
It’s nothing, really.
When two Spiritual Pressures collide,
the one that’s pushed down gets hurt.
That’s all there is to it.
In essence…
compared to that sword
you honed with your spirit pressure
in order to slay your enemies…
the Spiritual Pressure that unconsciously
oozes out of me is much stronger.
That’s all there is to it.
I swear…
I can’t believe I spent days
looking for a guy at this level.
Even as a joke,
it’s not very funny.
Now it’s my turn.
At least, let me get the rust off
of this thing, won’t you?
I’m counting on you, Ryoka.
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Nanao! It’s finally our big turn.
Nanao, where are you?
Chad, you're gonna fight that old man?
Oh, where are you hiding?
Hmm…it seems so.
Are you sure about that?
Na-na-o!