Not bad…
Your power is now…
much closer to power you once possessed.
“Invaders Must Die.”
What…is this?!
I see…
You don’t want me to come in contact with
Ichigo Kurosaki when his
powers are still incomplete.
Especially when he’s so close
to perfecting it. Right?
Yukio.
Hey…What is this?!
What’s going on?!
Let me out of here! Hey!
No you don’t!
Save complete…
Now…
Ichigo Kurosaki, who’s close
to being fully developed,
won’t have to come in contact with me.
But maybe you made a mistake.
Shouldn’t you have confined
me in there, instead?
Sorry…
I didn’t have enough
battery life to save you.
Plus, that wasn’t why I saved Kurosaki.
Listen.
You hear that?
You see?
We’ve attracted a crowd, the
police and the fire department…
We’ve caused violent explosions…
TV news choppers might
even come flying by…
Wouldn’t that be a problem for
you, as well, Mr. Tsukishima?
“The Love Gun”?
That’s right!
You know what it can do!
You made it!
Mind making yourself scarce?
I’m not
really good at these types of things.
Get going, Mr. Tsukishima…
But if you want to make
a spectacle of yourself,
then I suggest you stay here.
All right.
See you again, Riruka.
We should go, as well.
We’ll take Ichigo and Jackie with us…
Chad! What’s wrong?!
Hey!
Come in.
Ishida…
Sorry to call you here
on such short notice…
Thank you for coming.
No…don’t mention it.
How’re you feeling?
A lot better.
That’s good…
So, what’s the matter?
About that…
I want you to heal these wounds right now.
Huh…?
Sure, no problem, but…
Why all of a sudden?
The situation’s changed.
Kurosakii…made contact with
the guy who did this to me.
His Spiritual Pressure is
different than it was before,
but it was definitely Kurosaki’s…
I don’t know why his
Spiritual Pressure changed,
but what’s certain is that I can’t
bide my time recovering in bed.
You’ve sensed that something’s
different, too, haven’t you?
Yes, I did, but…
But Kurosaki hasn’t said
anything to me yet,
so I’ve kept my distance…
But…
If the presence I sensed
together with Kurosaki
is the person who attacked you…
Then…
I think he’s the same
person who attacked me.
What?
All right, load complete.
Where are we?!
Our alternate hideout.
It’s far from comfortable, though.
What?
If you say things like that,
I’m not adding any amenities.
It’s not your money, but all you
do is complain for gosh sake…
It’s my money that’s going to end up
paying to fix previous hideout…
Sorry…
But you caused a lot of explosions…
Do I spend money to fix it up the way it was,
or rebuild from scratch?
I’d better calculate which is cheaper.
Take that up with Chad…
When he wakes up, I will.
Chad!
Why do I have to be the
one who looks after him?!
Really…
Both Chad and Jackie’s injury are nothing!
Don’t get theatrical and
faint on us like that!
If I leave them alone, they’ll
wake right up, won’t they?
For crying out loud…
Chad!
Are you okay, Chad?
Chad?
Uh, yeah…
I’m okay…
It’s not serious…
Good…
What about that guy, Tsukishima?
He retreated…
For now, anyway.
Something bothering you?
No…
If he wanted to hurt us,
he could’ve still kept
fighting in that situation…
Especially with his power.
Riruka was inside of
Tsukishima’s attack radius,
and he could’ve cut down Yukio, as well.
Was the reason he didn’t attack them
because he was actually
only interested in you…
Or…
Did he have some other reason?
You’re overthinking it.
Mr. Tsukishima knows my abilities.
He couldn’t attack me
under those conditions while
I had the terminal in my hand.
Even more so if he’s
interested in Kurosaki.
I suppose you’re right.
Kutsuzawa, how’s your end?
No problems at all.
The police, fire department,
reporters and neighbors—
they’ve all been taken care of.
Good work.
Okay then, I’ll start
working on an estimate…
Man, what a headache this is going to be…
Wait, Yukio.
Stay here and work with
Ichigo on his training.
What?!
Why me?!
There’s nothing I can do for him!
Besides, this thing’s
about to lose its charge!
There is, that’s why I’m asking.
Do it with the cord plugged in!
I’m exhausted after what just
happened, so I don’t want to!
So the truth comes out?
I don’t know how Tsukishima
found our hideout, but
it’d be reasonable to
assume he traced the Spiritual Pressure.
If that’s so, then your Fullbring,
which can completely block
off Spiritual Pressure,
will be essential to Ichigo’s training.
You can do it, right?
All right.
Training…as in an actual fighting?
That’s right.
It seems that suits you best, after all.
Just so you know, I’ve
already defeated Jackie.
Who will I be fighting next?
Me.
Strange…
You and I were attacked by the same person,
but the extent of your
injuries versus mine…
suggests an enemy with
different capabilities.
One other thing…
Did you notice a sweet smell?
A sweet smell?
What was it now…
Honey, maybe…?
I remembered something!
He called his Zanpakuto-like
power “Fullbring”!
Was it the same for the person
who attacked you, as well?
Sorry…
I didn’t have the luxury
to ask questions…
Until you mentioned it,
I thought that that sword
was a type of Zanpakuto…
Sado.
Inoue…
If you’re taking this street…
Were you at the hospital?
Yes, I was there, healing
Ishida’s injuries.
I see…
How did it go?
His wounds have healed,
but I think he should stay
in bed a bit longer.
They don’t seem to be injuries caused by
ordinary Spiritual Pressure…
I see…
I’m glad I met you here.
I wanted to ask you how Ishida was doing.
Tell me as we walk back.
Huh?
W-Wait, Sado!
Where are we going?
To where Ichigo is.
From here on, Ichigo’s training
will require your powers!
Okay, I’ll begin now.
I see…
So this is what I was being kept in earlier.
That’s right.
This is Yukio’s Fullbring,
“Invaders Must Die.”
He can trap a target in another dimension
and “control” it on a game screen.
Don’t worry.
I’ve told him not to interfere.
Ever fantasize about being inside a game?
What’re you talking about?
Admit it.
Every kid’s thought about it.
Nothing to be embarrassed about.
I can’t say I never
thought about it, but…
Is that so?
I’ve never wanted to, not even once.
Then why’d you make me say it?
Well, whether you did or not
doesn’t make any difference.
So why’d you make me say it?!
This might be a bit different
than you imagined…
I wanted to tell you that this is what
the inside of a game looks like.
It’s definitely a lot more
barren than I thought it’d be.
Barren? In that case…
How’s this? Isn’t it a lot livelier?
It’s awfully one-dimensional, though…
Yukio, you don’t have to
do anything unnecessary.
Anyway, though, since you’ve
entered this game space,
don’t you want rules fitting for a game?
What do you mean?
Nothing too complicated.
A simple “system.”
Yukio!
Can you give us a life gauge?
Okay. Matched to your current health?
No. Make it an even six each.
Okay.
Oh, there we go.
When those six life gauges are gone.
So it’s “game over”…
Exactly.
Do you need an explanation
of “game over”?
No thanks.
I can guess.
When it’s “game over,”
I’ll put up a “You Die.”
Very funny.
Ready?
Yeah.
“Cross of Scaffold.”
Just a minute!
Who’s that girl?!
This is Inoue.
Oh?
She’s the one?!
Hello…
This is Riruka Dokugamine.
Pleased to meet you…
Chad’s told me about you.
He says you can heal people’s injuries?
What’d you come here for?
Are you here to help with
Ichigo’s training?
Come on, Riruka…
That’s right.
Do you realize what you’ll be doing?
Healing his injuries means he’s
going to get injured again later!
If you heal him, Ichigo will get
injured and suffer over and over.
You’re…
worried for Kurosaki, too, aren’t you?
Huh? Uh…
No, I… I’m not!
Now just a minute!
I realize that.
But…
I got past that issue a long time ago.
If Kurosaki needs my help to
do what he’s decided to do,
regardless of what it is,
I will use my powers to help him.
What if Ichigo suffers a terrible
injury he can’t recover from?
I won’t ever let him suffer an injury
he can’t recover from.
No matter how hopeless the injury,
I will heal it completely.
He wields that huge sword as
though it weighs nothing…
Coming at you!
You’ve gotten quite a bit
better at wielding Fullbring.
But …
You still have a long way to go.
Oh…
Welcome.
Ginjo.
A visitor.
I’m letting her in.
Oh, if it isn’t the healing item.
Uh…
How do you do?
I’m…uh…
Skip the greetings.
You’re just in time for a job.
Hurry up and heal him.
Kurosaki!
Come on…
This is so stupid.
So that’s the last of it, right?
Are you sure about this…?
Absolutely sure?
Get off my back!
How many times do you need to make sure?
A father may rob his son’s future.
It’s only right to confirm multiple
times that you’re certain about this.
And I’m saying to stop
asking me again and again.
I guess you’re right.
All right, let’s move on to our last step.
Just place your Spiritual Pressure
in here and it’s done.
Okay, please do it.
Right.
Our next episode will
be a New Years special.
Wow, looks like it’s going to
be an all-star of Soul Reapers.
Who knows?
I can pretty much tell from
what we’re seeing.
You don’t really believe what’s being
shown is going to be everything, are you?
What?! It’s not?!
That, is a secret.
It is?!
Xcution Dictionary!
W-What is this?!
An extra level.
Isn’t it fun?
Oh, that’s a poisonous swamp.
Tell me that sooner!
Inoue!
I’m sorry,
I’m at level 40 right now, so to join me,
you’ll need to go to the castle,
get the secret treasure,
and defeat the monster in the hills
and reach level 35 first, okay?
Huh?
You can’t use the healing item
until you get to a higher level.
What a hassle!