You're in a good mood.
Kinda.
You are, too, aren't you?
Yeah.
We're here, Zack.
Zack?
Zack...
Zack!
Zack, wake up.
Huh?
Thank goodness.
We're here?
Well, let's go, then...
Zack, you're bleeding!
Oh, this is nothing—
Don't. You shouldn't move.
I said... I'm fine.
No.
Huh?
Ray, why...
...are you making that weird face?
Zack!
He's breathing.
He's just unconscious.
But I can't carry him any farther.
Wait here.
I'll look for some medicine or something.
I swear I'll be useful to you,
Zack!
Something seems... strange...
What's that?
This smoke... smells...
...kind of... sweet...
I have to hurry, or Zack...
What was that?
"God desires those who are
clean and without falsehood.
Ask yourself: who are you?
Are you a desirable sacrifice?
Are you an angel?
Or, if you are any other form of
being who seeks God's salvation...
Reveal and confess all your sins!"
Rachel Gardner.
Spit out your sins
And that will be your proof
What do you feel as you gaze upon the proof
The doors opened so that you can know the stains you bear
A mirror?
Look at yourself
A sacrifice, or a lost sheep
...or a demon?
The only thing God wants is
you without lies
What does it mean?
I see myself...
But that's all.
Are you just an ignorant? Or are
you hiding the true yourself?
Here is the Confessional
To leave
collect your own pieces
and know the true yourself
"Collect your own pieces and
know the true yourself..."
"Spit out your sins.
If you don't know,
tear up and drag them out."
What is this place?
All these writings are so weird.
Can you recognize your sins?
If they are blacked out, you did so yourself.
Did you erase them?
Or did you not realize they were sins?
If you lost your own sins,
make them complete again.
Accept the sins that flow forth.
Here is the Confessional.
Who are you?
Spit out your sins.
Accept your sins.
Sins?
Tear up and drag them out.
Tear up and drag them out!
Tear up...
...and drag them out!
A family... of sheep?
Ray... Ray...
Ray!
Come here.
What's the matter?
That doesn't matter.
What I need to do right now
is save Zack.
Spit out your sins...
And that will be your proof.
Another weird place...
And I'm in a hurry.
My footprints are red.
Is that blood?
I don't have time to stand around.
It's coming from inside?
Where is this sound coming from?
"What is your confession?
Does your heart truly wish to be saved?
Can you lift your sins up to
God as the sins that they are?
More importantly, you lack the
ability to recognize a sinful heart.
If you seek salvation,
declare in this place the
nature of your sins."
Declare my sins?
Stain the angel?
Not so loud...
My head... It hurts...
Who are you?
Why are you silent?
What about you?
Who are you?
I am the priest of this church.
My name is Gray.
You're a priest?
Now it's your turn to answer me.
I'm... Rachel Gardner.
Are you a resident of this floor?
Indeed.
From your perspective, I suppose I would be.
You needn't be so frightened.
I have not yet judged what
kind of person you are.
Since I do not know that,
I will not pass blind judgment on you.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking... for something
to stop bleeding.
I see. An antihemorrhagic, then?
This is something Zack needs, correct?
How do you know Zack?
That is obvious.
I know more about them than anyone else.
Sadly, however, there is nothing
here that you can use to treat him.
If there is such a thing...
I would expect it to be on Danny's floor.
But... How do I get down there?
You want to go back down?
Yes.
Then what you must do is not difficult.
With me, you can return there.
With you?
Yes, indeed.
I know the way to get there.
Can I trust what you say?
I do not lie.
But if we are to go,
I will need you to undergo a bit of a test.
A test?
It is nothing difficult.
I only want to know who you truly are.
I do not require an immediate answer.
Make the choice within your own heart.
I will wait here a while.
Make your own decision as
to what you wish to do.
I'd like a little more time.
This priest is the only lead I have.
I should go see Zack first.
That's odd...
A few rooms are missing.
Zack!
Don't try to move.
Ray...
Where have you been?
I was looking for something
to stop the bleeding.
Huh? By yourself?
What the hell were you thinking?
Well, I can't move you around too much.
Besides, you were asleep.
Dumbass! You should've woken me up!
I couldn't do that.
And? Did you find anything?
No...
But someone said that if I go back to
Doctor Danny's floor, I'll find medicine.
Huh? You wanna go back now?
Yeah, but...
Zack!
Stay still for a while!
Shut up! I'm not a little kid!
My scythe's so heavy...
The hell? This doesn't make sense.
You'll die.
The scythe's heaviness is your body
telling you it can't handle it.
Don't just tell me I'm gonna die!
You know I'm not gonna kick
the bucket that easily!
But...
Please, Zack.
Let me be useful to you.
"Please," huh?
I hope you don't think that's
gonna make any difference.
Please.
So? Is there a way to go back?
Well... I think it'll be fine.
You really think you can go there
and make it back here alone?
I think I can.
Fine. I'd just be dead weight
if I went with you now.
You're wrong!
I'm not wrong.
But if you can tell me
honestly that you won't die,
then go.
I'll just... sleep.
Okay.
If you're going down,
go as far as my old floor.
Huh?
The place where I first found you.
My room is there.
There's a knife in the room.
Bring it... to me...
Zack?
Have you decided what you will do?
I can't let Zack die.
If there's even the slightest chance...
I want to go back to Doctor Danny's
floor to get the medicine.
So...
I'll take your test.
Very well.
Please, I'm begging you...
Don't do anything to Zack.
Of course.
That smell again...
Well, shall we go, Rachel Gardner?
I see you are determined
to keep me away from Zack.
You needn't glare so.
I won't do anything to him.
Why do you wish to save Zack?
If he dies, it'll be a problem for me.
A problem? Why is that?
Zack swore to God...
...that he would kill me.
Oh? And that is your reason? Truly?
What an outlandish promise to make.
This smell...
It's coming from him.
We have arrived, Rachel Gardner.
So soon?
I mentioned a test, yes?
We haven't reached Doctor Danny's floor yet!
There will be a test for you on each floor.
They will not be difficult.
You need only turn on the electricity
that powers the elevator in the prison.
Is the power source really there?
Per Cathy's wishes, this floor is rigged
with more mechanisms than the others.
She was very skilled at using
them to manipulate people's minds
and guide them toward repenting and
seeking salvation from the heart.
Although she could be a
bit of a spendthrift...
But let us just say that
was part of her charm.
And with her gone, those who
seek repentance and salvation
may now be roaming about this floor.
Now, let us begin the test.
Go, Rachel Gardner.
I have to hurry.
There it is!
Ugh... They're in the way.
If I go in there...
The body... is gone?
I don't have time to worry about that.
She watched us from here...
I have to get rid of them.
Please... Don't get in my way.