Huh?
Where am I?
Huh?!
Why the hell am I
dressed like this?
Huh? A cat?
Is that you, Yoruichi?
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
So...
What's this meeting about?
And why are all of you
dressed like that?
What's wrong with it?
It's what we always wear.
Did you hit your head, Chigo?
"Chigo"? Who's that?
That's so typical of you.
Did you forget your name?
That's not what I meant!
My name is I-chi-go Ku-ro-sa-ki!
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's time.
Huh?
All right!
Let's go!
Hey, wait!
I'm not done talking!
Hey!
I've been planning to get this
target for a while now.
We have to do this carefully.
It'll be all right.
After all, you came up
with the plan, Urio.
It's reassuring to hear
that from you, Ori Mei.
Don't you think so, Chaido?
What is this? Urio,
Ori Mei, and Chaido?
They've been going on
like that for a while now.
Also...
Why the hell is this giant eel
pretending to be a camel?!
Are you still talking
nonsense, Chigo?
Huh?
What would Bawabawa
be if not a camel?
Are you all right, Chigo?
Listen, Chigo.
We're going to be sneaking into a
mansion belonging to Ura Vira,
the wealthy merchant
who lives in this town.
For what?
There's a legendary jewel called
the Snow Crystal that is said
to be the only one of
its kind in this world.
Tonight, we're going to steal it.
What, you mean we're thieves?
No, we're burglars.
Why did you re-phrase
it into a lamer term?!
Amazing... These treasures look
like they're from a dream.
Yeah, they really do look
Well, that's because
this is all a dream.
Huh?
Anyway, it's dangerous
to remain here for long.
Ignore the other things.
Let's find the Snow Crystal.
All right.
Find it? What does this
Snow Crystal look like?
The Snow Crystal...
It is pure white and shiny.
If you touch it, it's
as cold as snow.
It is calming and beautiful
in appearance.
It is an unparalleled treasure.
That's no different from what
you had imagined earlier.
You've never seen the
real thing, have you?
Hey, could that be it?
Huh?
Can you open it?
Leave it to me.
Whoa...
Huh?
Only a single lamp?
Don't you think the treasure
chest was pretty big for it?
Is this lamp Kon?
No, it's not Kon!
"Aladdin and the Magic Lamp."
It's a story in "Arabian Nights," or
"One Thousand and One Nights."
This dream is based
on that story.
Wait a second, Ishida.
What did you say just now?
What are you talking about?
My name is Urio.
I'm not talking about that!
Are the things happening
right now a dream?
I've been telling you that.
You sure are obtuse.
If it wasn't a dream, there's no way
that things would go this smoothly.
Right?
Yes.
Too bad, burglars.
You're trapped.
A dream... A dream, huh?
Well, that would make sense.
Ura Vira is a wealthy merchant.
He has treasures he's gathered
from all over the world.
He is the richest man
in this country.
And who exactly are you
explaining that to?
Honestly, you burglars...
Did you think that I wouldn't
be prepared for break ins?
This is such a cliché development!
Wait a second!
Laser beams?!
How easy are we on the
story set up today?!
What should we do?
There's nowhere left to escape.
Damn it!
We've got to fight.
Fight?
But we're unarmed!
We're not unarmed.
See?
How do we fight with a lamp?
I know!
Perhaps this lamp is a magical
lamp that'll grant us wishes.
All right, it's coming out!
Wait! It might explode!
Who summoned me?
Huh? Rukia?!
I'm not Rukia.
I'm Rukiruki!
I don't care about that!
Who are you?!
I'm busy right now.
If you don't want anything,
I'm leaving!
Hey! Wait, wait, wait!
Emergency, emergency!
We've got a real emergency!
You're being a pest!
What's going on?!
You're the genie of
the lamp, right?
Don't you grant wishes?
Yes, I do.
What about it?
Huh?
Good work!
Now break down the door!
Please!
We're in a real jam!
Grant us a wish!
I refuse!
Because of genie law, I cannot grant
wishes to people with tainted hearts!
That, and people with orange
hair are out of the question!
What does the color of my hair
have to do with anything?!
Dying your hair leads
to delinquency!
Are genie laws like school regulations?!
Anyway, my hair isn't dyed!
No means no!
Give up!
Aww... Fine.
You're so useless.
You're probably lying about
being able to grant wishes.
I'm not lying!
Then show me!
I can't break the law!
See?
You really can't do it!
I can!
Then show me!
I told you, I can't!
You really were lying!
Very well! I shall show you!
Tell me your wish!
Me, me!
I want to eat cake!
That's not something to
wish for in this situation.
All right!
Wow, amazing!
See that?
My power is not fake!
Even my kid sister could
make a cake!
Don't you have more
impressive magic?
I can only grant you a
total of three wishes.
You have two left.
And again!
That's it!
Chigo! We can't last any longer!
Hey, Rukia!
Use your remaining magic to
get us the hell out of here!
"Get us the hell..."?
Is that any way to ask
people for favors?!
Huh? Well... Umm...
Please.
Fine.
Here I go!
I-It's cramped.
And it stinks.
Hey, Rukia!
I'm not Rukia.
I'm Rukiruki!
I did tell you to get us out...
But why are we inside a toilet?!
I'm glad that everyone's safe!
Yeah.
For a second there,
I thought we were done for.
Wait a second.
I should have used that wish to wake
myself up from this dream.
What am I doing?
I went this far, so I'll grant
you the last wish.
What is your last wish?
All right!
Get me out of this dream right--
I want the Snow Crystal!
A-All right.
You want the Snow
Crystal, right?
Wait a second!
I summoned her, so I should
get to have my wish granted!
So that's the kind of person
you are, Chigo?
There are people like that...
Mu... So much for friendship.
Who cares!
This is my dream, so I can
do whatever I want.
What are you talking about?!
Getting the Snow Crystal was
also one of your wishes!
I don't remember ever
wanting that!
I know!
We can decide with a vote!
A vote?
Who wants the Snow Crystal?
Me!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on out, Rukiruki.
Ow, hey! Seeleschneider!
Why?
Huh? She's not coming out.
I wonder what's wrong.
Rub rub rub...
Sheesh, finally!
She sure took her time.
Huh?
It's a different genie.
What's this? Renji
is normal sized?
I'm not Renji! I'm Ren Jin!
All right, already...
We don't need you.
Just bring out Rukia!
Rukiruki...can't come
here anymore.
Huh.
Rukiruki broke the laws
of the Lamp Society,
so she's going to be executed.
Excuse me?
Rukiruki is going to be executed
tomorrow, at noon.
Why does this sound
so familiar?
And what the hell is
the Lamp Society?!
It's your fault!
Rukiruki is going to be executed
for granting your wishes!
I'll swallow my pride to
ask you this favor!
Please save Rukiruki!
This is all so sudden...
Chigo!
Don't just stand around.
Let's go!
Huh?
Why is this happening?!
So this is the Lamp Society.
That's where Rukiruki is, right?
How did I get myself
mixed up in this?
What's wrong, Chigo?
Did you get carsick?
Of course not.
That's right, Ori Mei.
Huh?
This isn't a car. It's a carpet.
The correct term is
carpetsickness.
Oh!
That's not the issue here!
Jeez.
All you do is complain.
Okay, already.
Now that we're here, there's
no pulling back!
I'll stick with you to the end!
Well said, Chigo!
I've been waiting
for those words!
Yoruichi?
Where are you looking?
Over here.
Yoruichi?!
Are you surprised, Chigo?
Then who is this?
That's just a black cat.
I'll explain things from here.
Rukiruki is going to be executed
at a place called the Solamp.
It is deep within the
Lamp Society.
But in order to reach it,
we need to get past
the Thirteen Court Lamp Squads
who defend the Lamp Society.
Damn, I don't know
where to begin!
Thirteen Court Lamp Squads?
What the hell?!
Well, everyone, let's
meet up again alive.
Roger!
Wait a second!
How are we supposed to land?
You won't die.
This is a dream, after all.
Huh?
That hurt so much I thought
I was going to die!
Why can't I wake up even
though it hurts so much?!
Don't tell me...
What is this?!
It's exactly the same
development!
I'm sorry I said it was the same!
Normal is good! Very good!
This scene?
Where's the real Zangetsu!
There!
Wait a sec...
The real Zangetsu has a design
to match this world too?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ch-Chigo!
Hey.
You fool! Why didn't you come
to save me earlier?!
I was about to die!
That's not what you're
supposed to say.
Stop it...
I told you, I can see you,
Byakuya Kuchiki.
What?!
Ambassador Seaweed?!
Big Brother...
What a lovely form.
These siblings need help.
Just hurry and take that off!
That doesn't match!
That doesn't match your image!
What is that?!
I see you like to trample
on other people's pride.
I've come this far!
I'm going to see this
through to the end!
You win this battle.
I did it!
It's over!
I finally awoke from my dream.
What is this?!
I still haven't woken up!
I need to wake up!
Well done, Chigo.
Thanks to you, Rukiruki
was saved.
Thanks. I'm grateful.
W-Well, I had no choice.
It was nothing.
As a token of my appreciation,
I'll grant you your last wish.
Now make a wish.
Oh, umm...
Could you wake him
up from his dream?
Yeah. He's fought so hard.
The last wish has got
to go to Chigo.
Guys...
Very well.
Wait!
The Snow Crystal!
The Snow Crystal?
Yeah.
It's white, cold and beautiful.
It's a hidden treasure.
Chigo.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
I'll wake up from my dream
sooner or later.
In that case, I should
grant you your wish.
Thank you, Chigo!
You're not very honest
with your feelings.
Shut up. Have her get
it for you already.
Don't regret it later.
This entire episode is
nothing but regrets.
Appear, Snow Crystal, the
Legendary Treasure!
Wow...
This is the Snow Crystal.
White, cold, beautiful, and...
Soft?
Huh?
Huh?!
A fishcake!
Thank goodness.
It was just a dream.
I had another strange dream.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
Today's episode of Bleach was made
in celebration of the manga
entering its tenth year.
On behalf of the animation staff,
I thank you all for your support.
Hold it!
Thanking everyone for the 10-year
anniversary should be my job!
The main hero!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Allow me to explain
today's world.
What the hell was that anyway?
It's what you would call
an alternate world.
Speaking of which, a common
practice to go
to an alternate world would
be falling into a hole.
Therefore, it's wise not to go near
a hole even if you spot one.
Oh, really?
Pay attention! I'm telling careless
people like you to be careful!
Like I would! You should be
the one careful not to...
Huh?