Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Such foolish talk!
You cannot defy the justice of the world
to push through your own justice!
Then what is the justice
of the world?
Did you not hear me?
As I said…
the time for words has passed!
All things in the universe turn to ashes.
Ryujinjakka.
Captain is…maybe this way.
Aha! There you are Captain!
Huh? Are you finished already?
No, they fled.
That wolf-guy suddenly screamed,
“Sir Genryusai!” and ran off somewhere.
Wolf-guy?
It seems like Old Man Yamamoto
has begun fighting somewhere…
Come to think of it,
I can blissfully feel it…
What?
You're in an awfully good mood…
What? You won without a scratch?
Yes!
Oh, but my clothes got dirty
so I had to change my clothes.
Somehow you seem more energetic
than you did before the fight.
No way! So you think
I’m more beautiful now, too?
That’s not what I said.
And don't move like that.
It's disgusting.
Sorry… I'm just so excited!
It's been a while since
I fought like that.
I'm just feeling so good…
Damn that bastard!
It’s not fair to have
a zanpakuto like that!
What is the true power
of my zanpakuto?
Don’t tell Ikkaku and the Captain, okay?
I don’t want them to dislike me.
He drained me of all my spirit energy!
Damn it!
This Spiritual Pressure…
Head Captain Yamamoto!
How long has it been since
I've seen this form?
How long has it been since I felt
this fear like the weight of the deep sea?
This transcendent Spiritual Pressure
even in its Shikai state alone…
Its heat scorches the heavens
and consumes even the clouds…
That blade turns everything
before it to ash…
Of all the zanpakuto,
it has the greatest attack power.
It is the strongest and
the oldest of the fire-type zanpakuto.
This is…Ryujinjakka!
What's wrong?
Release your swords already.
Surely you don’t wish to be burned
to ashes without a fight?
I guess it can't be helped.
Shall we, Ukitake?
Yeah.
All waves rise now and
become my shield!
Lightning, strike now
and become my blade!
Sogyonokotowari.
Flower wind rage and
flower god roar!
Heavenly wind rage and
heavenly demon sneer!
Katenkyokotsu.
Sogyonokotowari
and Katenkyokotsu.
These two are the only dual zanpakuto
in the Soul Society.
They're magnificent.
You haven't changed at all…
Thank you…
Are you ready?
Anytime.
Any pain, Jidanbo?
Are you really all right?
Yeah… I'm really all right.
Thank you all for helping me!
Don’t mention it.
Don't be so formal with us, Jidanbo!
If you want to thank someone,
you should thank that girl…
If that girl hadn't tried hard to
save you for all those hours,
your arm probably wouldn't
have been back to normal.
Ah, Orihime.
She sure was cute.
It's been five days since
those people went into the Seireitei.
I see. Five days, huh?
I hope they're all right.
Are you that worried, Jidanbo?
Then do you want to come with me?
Oh…
M-Ms. Kukaku!
Hey!
I-It's been a while, Sis Kukaku!
Yeah!
It's been a long time, Sis Kukaku!
You look cool as always!
Yeah!
Wh-What's wrong, Ms. Kukaku?
Is there something
you want from me?
You were sleeping
for five or six days…
Jidanbo, you must be
feeling gloomy.
Care to join me for a walk?
I have some business with Yoruichi.
You haven’t gotten any stronger
for someone who’s spent
so many years in hiding.
You on the other hand…
looks like you’ve let your skills
get rather dull.
I noticed there was
a Shihoin symbol
on the Tentoken flying cloak
that Ryoka kid was wearing.
You gave it to him, didn't you?
That's right.
He had to be able to fly
in order to save Rukia.
As the appointed clan of
Tenshiheisoban Defender of the Realm,
Shihoin sure has become corrupt.
The clan will lose its place as
one of the Four Great Noble Clans
if they find out you were
supporting the Ryoka.
The fall of a great family is not pretty,
including the Shiba Clan.
You sure are talkative today.
Are you excited to see your senior
that you adored after so many years?
Or are you expressing
your usual pent up anger?
Well? Chief Commander
of the Stealth Force?
Was it too much burden for you,
being my successor?
Don’t flatter yourself.
Acting like you‘re still above me.
I'm the one who's in charge
of the Stealth Force
and the Punishment Force.
Your time has passed,
Yoruichi Shihoin.
This is the difference between
you and me now.
As you already know,
when the leader of the Punishment Force
draws her sword,
an execution battle is imminent.
Any and all who opposes
the leader must die.
That includes even the former leader!
You, who threw away the title,
have no place to escape.
Yoruichi!
You sure are underestimating me.
I did throw away the title, but…
there's another title
I don't remember relinquishing.
“Flash Master Yoruichi.”
I see…
Then you leave me no choice.
I will strip that other title from you
with my own hands!
The Keisen uniform, the uniform
for the leader of the Punishment Force.
That attire takes me
back in time.
Does it make you
think about the past?
A little…
Don't hold back…
think back more.
And compare…
which one of us
is the better warrior?!
It looks like I've taken…a hit…
One for one.
It looks like we're even, Yoruichi!
So it seems.
Have you got some gimmick
in your uniform?
Your movements improved, Soi Fon.
A gimmick, you say?
That’s what you think?
Really?
Sting all enemies to death…
Suzumebachi.
I won’t let you get away.
Did you not think that may be
I’m better than you?
Did you not think that maybe
I was holding back earlier?
You thought someone like me would never
have anything to hold back against you?
I told you not to flatter yourself.
I'm stronger than you!
Pay the price of being away
from the battlefront for a hundred years
with your life, Yoruichi!
Yoruichi, do you remember
the power of my Suzumebachi?
The Homonka…
It's a death mark etched
onto the body of the target
with the first attack.
I hadn’t perfected it when
you were still around.
But over the last hundred years,
it has finally become complete!
Better run away so as not
to take a second hit, Yoruichi.
The Suzumebachi’s killing power
is in the second strike!
If I hit you in the same place twice…
You'll die!
Here comes the second attack, Yoruichi!
You’re showing your back
to your enemy and running away,
yet look at yourself!
You may be running away to buy time,
but it's useless!
Before, my Homonka used to disappear
in about an hour.
Now, there’s no time limit!
They won't disappear unless
I make them disappear!
So run all you want, but…
Anken!
Not good enough!
Do you understand now?
I am better than you.
Now that you understand,
I'll finish you off!
Are you surprised?
This is the first time
you're seeing this, isn't it?
This is a fighting technique that
combines Hakuda and Kido.
It's something I created.
You should feel privileged.
This technique has only
been completed recently,
so you're the first person I'm going
to test it on in actual fight.
It doesn't even have a name yet.
No…
It has a name.
What did you say?
It's called “Shunko.”
What are you talking about?
Do you know why that Keisen uniform
doesn't cover the back or shoulders?
It's because
there's no need for it.
When this technique is used
in its perfected form,
a dense Kido envelops
the user’s back and shoulders.
By exploding it, the Kido power
is forced to the arms and legs.
In other words,
once this technique is activated,
any fabric on the back and
shoulders would be blown off!
My, my.
I really didn't want to fight you
with this technique.
Be careful, Soi Fon.
Even I can’t control
this technique very well.
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Yoruichi has gotten all serious,
so in the next episode, I'm…
Going to strip?
No, I'm not going to strip!
I’m not like you!
You're not? How boring.
I was looking forward to it.
Then I will…
Number 1
Kon's Me Me Diary
Nothing good happens
when I'm a plushie,
so I'll leave this in here for a while…
No one may remember this,
but I'm a Mod Soul with
super kicking power.
Who are these guys?
Please help us win a kickball game.
The playground is at stake!
Huh? Help? What a bother…
We want to count on your golden leg!
Sorry, but…
We'll give you this if you help us!
Crazy and smokin’ special edition!
Just leave it to me!
Tune in again!