Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
What exactly…
Karakura High School
Huh?!
That's you, Kurosaki…
Why is my gigai here?!
Could Urahara have left it here?
At any rate, it'll be bad
to leave those there!
You'll have to return to them
before everyone comes…
Y-Yeah!
Heh! What a pain…
It's hard to return! Damn it!
Damn! It's so uncomfortable!
But, from here on…
All right, I'll explain
the next game's rules!
You've come out again!
That's a mean way to talk!
I came all this way to tell you
that there's a fake among you…
A fake?!
What do you mean?!
Look at them…
There's only two of them!
That copying guy isn't there!
Could it be that he traded places
with one of us?!
But…when?
Could it be…
I know! I know!
Don't you think that Inoue
and Chad are suspicious?
The enemy could have switched places
when they were captured.
No way!
Well…I can tell if Inoue…
Is real or not…
If you just invite me to
your godly bosom.
Shut up!
It's a trick! It's got to be!
Believe what you like,
but if you don't find
the impostor quickly,
your friends at school
will all disappear!
Hey, brat!
We don't have time to
constantly play your…
That's no good.
The game has already begun.
She's fast…
She's…definitely not normal.
Now, I'll explain the rules!
Find out who the switched person is
before the clock strikes twelve.
If you figure it out, you win!
But if you guess wrong,
we're going to make everyone
in the whole school disappear!
Disappear--?!
Yes… Oh, do you know
what I mean by “disappear”?
It means that they'll vanish and
you'll never meet them again…
Oh, you can only answer once!
Let me know when
you've decided!
Hey!
Can they really make everyone
in school disappear?
Well. They did make Inoue
and Sado vanish…
That's true, but…
But this is a much larger
number of people!
Inoue, Sado…
Do you remember what happened
after you were sucked
into that gate?
Well… I don't really remember…
We were floating in darkness…
That's all.
Hey, Ishida, can't you figure it out?
I can't!
If I were to guess…
The gate is probably connected to
some alternate dimensional space.
An alternate dimensional space?
It's a world beyond
our comprehension.
The number of people may not
make any difference.
But what I'm worried about is…
unlike the time with Inoue and Sado,
this time, they said they'd
make everyone disappear.
Disappear? Could it be that…
Yeah.
We can assume that
they'll be killed…
That's not funny!
I won't let them do that!
Who is it?!
Hey, Ichigo! Why the scary face?!
Good morning!
Ooh! Hey!
What's with that get-up?!
You look as if
you were out all night.
Did you leave me out?!
I see! So that's it!
– Look… a lot’s happened!
– No!
Orihime!
Oh, Tatsuki!
Where's your uniform?
– This person's still here?
– Oh… Well, a lot happened…
Ah…well…
He's a relative, isn't he?
Oh yeah! Right?!
Hey, what are you…
How long are you staying here?
F-For a while…
Don't you have school?
No…not really…
Then, where do you live?
What kinds of girls do you like--?
– Shut up!
As I expected of relatives!
You're really alike…
Oh no…
What was that for?
What did I do?!
Out of the way!
I'm going to be late--!
Hey…Keigo!
Orihime, let's go too!
Y-Yeah…
What are you going to do, Kurosaki?
It's obvious…
We have to find the impostor
among us in order to save everyone.
Sado?
We should go to class…
It'll be difficult to move if
people are suspicious of us.
I suppose that's right…
Nothing will be solved
if we stay here.
Also…
Kurosaki, you should also
contact Urahara's Shop.
Huh?
I'm concerned about why your body
was left on the school grounds.
Yeah…
Definitely…
Well then, do you understand
what this question is getting at?
This question points to the fact
that two contradicting factors,
logical idea and illogical idea…
If there was a chance to
take any of our places…
Damn…
How am I supposed to tell
who's the impostor?!
Is it Ishida?
Inoue?
Or is it Chad?
Hey!
That copy guy is pretty good
at transforming.
Wh-Why are you sitting here?
Why? Because I'm bored.
Get out before someone
finds you!
Don't be so uptight.
So this is what your textbooks
look like…
Just go away!
Don't come so close that
you're breathing on me!
It's gross!
What?!
I was behaving myself,
but you started getting cheeky!
Bring it on! Come on!
Kurosaki Brothers,
if you want to fight, do it over there!
Why do I…?
Damn!
You're being punished!
You too!
Is he acting a bit…strange?
Was he ever this messed up?
Could it be--?
Is he the impostor?
Renji…take it off!
Huh?
Just take it off right now!
What are you talking about?
Just take it off!
If you won't, I'll take it off for you!
W-Wait just a second!
No, I can't wait!
S-Stop it!
I'll rip it off you!
W-Wait!
No, I can't wait!
That's…
I told you to take it off!
Stop!
Forbidden love…
How wonderful!
Don't you think that Ichigo's…
acting different?
That's not it!
His gigai, his gigai!
I thought I would be able to tell
if it was actually him if
he could take off his gigai!
It would probably be difficult
to change into a Soul Reaper!
We still don't know how powerful
his copying ability is.
It's still too soon to
make such assumptions.
I don't think that was
a very smart method.
We should keep in mind that
he might not only copy appearances,
but abilities as well.
They're doing it, they're doing it…
Now then…
Maybe I'll push them a little more.
Aw man!
They've got to make
more girls' bathrooms!
I thought I was the last one…
Who is it?!
Is someone…there?
Starting now,
for the next few hours,
we'll temporarily stop all passage
to the World of the Living!
Sentaro, give the order
to close the gate!
Yes! Understood!
Close the gate!
That's right…
I asked Ukitaki to close
the Senkaimon.
Soi Fon…
Sorry, but could you come here
before they close the gate?
It's urgent!
Yes! Of course, Lady Yoruichi.
So…Today for PE,
the boys will have baseball…
and the girls will be running.
– What? Running?!
– That sucks!
Be quiet!
Uh, who's absent?
Umm, Arizawa isn't here…
That's odd…
Does anyone know where she is?
Well, that's okay…
She'll come sooner or later.
I've already got one!
If you don't find the impersonator,
they'll continue to disappear!
What? What do you mean?
Say, could it be that you…
No way!
Hey, what's wrong?
Inoue!
Inoue! Wait!
Hm? What's wrong with you all?!
We're all feeling sick,
so we're going to the infirmary!
Hey, wait! Hey!
– What's going on?
– I find that hard to believe!
I don't know either.
Tatsuki!
This is Tatsuki's…
Inoue…
Tatsuki was… Tatsuki was…
Calm down…
We're still not sure
she was taken away.
No!
Inoue?
I can't stay calm!
Aren't you worried about Tatsuki?!
Could it be that…it was you?!
I can't take it anymore!
Why did this happen?!
I can't trust anyone!
Who's the impostor?!
Tatsuki… Give Tatsuki back!
Stop it, Inoue!
Being suspicious of each other
is what the enemy wants!
Tatsuki is all right! Leave it to me!
Kurosaki…
I won't let her disappear!
That's so cool…
But can you do it?
It won't do you any good if
you can't find the impostor.
Your other friends will continue
to disappear if you hesitate!
Time's not up yet!
That's right. But now you know
that we're serious!
You have an hour until time's up.
See you later.
Hey!
They're good at running away.
Damn…!
Really, what a pain…
I'll answer it!
I just have to answer, right?!
Yes? Urahara's Store…
Oh, it's spiky-hair guy.
Huh?! Yoruichi?!
Come to think of it, she hasn't been here…
since this morning…
What? I don't know where she is.
The owner is always…
What a pain…
All right, I'll tell them!
See you later!
It's no good!
Yoruichi and Urahara have
gone off somewhere.
Renji, how was it?
I don't know why,
but I can't contact the Soul Society…
I can't get any information…
No way…
What should we do?
We don't have any options left.
Damn…
Let's all stay calm.
Maybe, we've sensed
some small inconsistencies
about the impostor…
on an unconscious level.
What do you mean?
Put simply, intuition.
Intuition?
If all our intuition matches,
then that person is the impostor!
It all comes down to intuition, huh?
Based on my intuition…
the impostor is…
The impostor is…
You, Ishida!
M-Me?! That's impossible!
W-Watch this!
Can the impostor do
this technique?!
If anyone is the impostor
it would be…
Him!
He's the most distant
to us and…
there's the least possibility
he'd be discovered!
That's stupid!
In this case, the least suspicious one
is most suspicious…
That's the way it always is!
N-No… If that's the case…
Then I'll pass the suspicion
to Chad!
I-I'm not him!
This is all your fault
to begin with!
Why are you trying
to confuse us?!
You impostor!
Damn it!
Who's the impostor?!
I can't stand this anymore!
It seems it wasn't any good…
Time’s almost up!
Take a look outside!
It's a fly ball to the pitcher!
I got it!
What's going on?!
I'm tired. I'm going to just
stop already!
Th-That's not good!
They disappeared?!
How could you?!
What are you doing?!
Hey! What are you all making
a fuss about?!
Miss Ochi!
Wh-Why you…!
A lot more have disappeared
than I thought!
Damn you!
This isn't tag!
Give your answer soon.
You'll never know
if you keep thinking forever!
O-Oh no!
They're not what you're after!
Don't involve people
who have nothing to do with this!
I can't change the game's rules.
Well, you have a one in five
chance to get it correct.
You've got no choice
but to leave it to luck!
Or are you going to surrender?
If you do that, I'll think of
a way to save everyone.
Is that true?!
What do we have to do?
It's easy!
You all must give your lives
in exchange for everyone else's!
What?!
Well, of course! Can't you do it?
People who have nothing
to do with this
are disappearing because of you.
This is a serious battle!
What was that for?!
Yoruichi?!
Hey! Yoruichi!
Yoruichi!
Didn't they come to save us?!
Why are they in a rush?
That scared me…
Chad…
Y-Yeah.
Do you have an idea of
what they're doing?
Who knows? But she sure
is tough for a lone woman.
Huh?
Say, I can't wait forever,
so make a choice already!
Yeah, sorry… I've decided!
Huh?!
Chad… It's obvious
why you don't know.
You don't know that
Yoruichi has the form of a cat
while she’s over here, do you?
That's because you've never
set foot in the Soul Society!
You're the impostor!
You've figured it out…
Very good.
But when did you notice?
I thought my transformation
was perfect.
Chad would never be scared
of something like that!
You amateur!
I see… It seems
I still need improvement.
I won't forgive you!
I'm going to make you
take responsibility
for what you've done!
I'm going to beat you to a pulp!
That's a little…
Shut up!
I'm sorry…
I let my guard down a bit.
Well now,
it's two wins and two losses.
Give Tatsuki and
everyone else back!
Everyone's safe!
Let's play the last game.
You're still making us
do this again?!
Cut it out!
Is it all right to say that?
Because if the big boy
was the impostor,
then where's the real one?
That's right. We still have him.
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Lady Yoruichi, about the canned food
you introduced me to:
I officially employed it for use
in the Stealth Force.
Isn't it useful?
Ichigo, do you want one?
I told you, it's cat food.
Silence! There's nothing wrong
with what Lady Yoruichi is doing!
No, there's a lot wrong with it.
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
– Golden!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Ukitaki, what's the meaning of this?!
Why are you closing
the Senkaimon?!
Well, according to Yoruichi,
something’s happening in
the World of the Living.
Oh yeah…
I have snacks!
Just take them.
I have candy, too!
If you'd like,
come to my room afterwards!
I'll have more snacks ready!
Why does he always
give this to me?
Tune in again!