Patras, one of the Arrancars,
does not like the fact
that Aizen rules the Hollows.
He steals the Hogyoku and escapes
Hueco Mundo with his two comrades.
They attack Urahara's Shop
in order to find out how to use
the Hogyoku from Urahara.
A fierce battle breaks out with Abarai,
who is left in charge of the shop.
It doesn't seem like you understand
what I mean even when I tell you.
So taste level two!
This is still just the beginning.
Shatter, Kyokasuigetsu!
What an elaborate thing
for you to do, Captain Aizen.
Gin, huh?
Even if they collaborated
and were up to no good...
Making them believe that
they had killed Ulquiorra
and letting them
take the Hogyoku.
There's no need to do this
in such a roundabout way.
You should just
kill them immediately.
What are you thinking?
I have something else
I need Ulquiorra to do.
If you give me the word,
I'll do it.
But that would be boring.
Oh?
URAHARA'S SHOP
What are you doing, Ururu?!
Jinta Home-Run!
Jinta!
When will the person who knows
about the Hogyoku come back?
I'm beginning to get bored.
He'll come back
when you're dead.
You show-off!
Renji!
Freeloader, are you all right?!
Somewhat...
Very well.
But I think that it's useless
no matter how much you struggle.
You two go and get Mr. Urahara!
But...
Just go!
All right...
Let's go, Jinta!
Crap!
Don't die, freeloader!
Thank you for taking the time
to make them bring him.
But will you survive until then?
Now it's level three!
Shut up!
You just keep on raising
your level little by little.
What a cheater.
If you continue to put up
a confident front,
you'll be in tears later!
Gentei Kaijo!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Oh? A bankai?
It's been a while...
Roar! Zabimaru!
This is nothing!
Wake up...
Something like this
won't kill you, right?
What a very interesting house.
I'm glad you like it!
We don't have to
hold back here.
Here I go!
Captain...
Are you already panting?!
Crap!
Honestly... Five Arrancars were
defeated by these guys?
Jeez...
How pathetic!
Matsumoto!
Come on, come on, come on!
What's wrong?! What's wrong?!
Frost unto the Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
You're not even an Espada.
I can't waste any more time on you!
Don't get cocky with that attack!
No matter how many times you try,
you can't defeat me!
You only attack by hurling yourself
at your enemy.
You boast too much.
How truly revolting.
I'm going to blow you away next!
Don't look the other way!
I'm your opponent!
It's useless.
For the record, I got one!
Level ten...
What?!
I'm still not serious either!
If this is your level ten,
then you're not really that strong, are you?!
Insignificant Soul Reaper...
You're getting carried away!
Don't think that someone like you
could ever be our opponent!
We've wiped out
Soul Reapers for ages.
And yet...
Someone like that...
"And yet," what?
Nothing...
It's of no concern to you.
I see...
But you said something
I cannot ignore!
What would that be?
You called me
an insignificant Soul Reaper!
Don't underestimate
us Soul Reapers!
Very well...
Then out of respect for your fearlessness
even in the face of death,
I shall show you my proper form...
Defile! Gerifalte!
This is my maximum level!
I fell asleep!
Lirin, rather than
"fell asleep,"
I think the correct term
is "lost consciousness."
Shut up!
Where's Renji?
Has he already been defeated?
What negative thinking.
That's no good, you know.
I sense Spiritual Pressure coming
from the basement...
- Let's go.
- What?! We're going?!
Of course!
Sorry... I can't control my power
in this form.
What?
I guess this ends my way
of passing the time.
I'm going to hit you the next time.
Don't underestimate me!
Here I go, Soul Reaper!
Please hurry!
How's Abarai?
He'll be all right.
He won't be defeated that easily.
I'm more worried about the store
than the freeloader.
Oh? You blocked it with
a segment of your blade.
It's not over yet!
I see...
So it seems...
Whoa...
A-Abarai...
It'll be dangerous
if he continues.
I want to ask you one thing.
What is it?
What do you plan to do
with the Hogyoku?
Gain control of all worlds.
Does that mean you're rebelling
against Aizen?
We don't accept him!
I guess this means the other side
is not so unified.
A Soul Reaper should never become
the ruler of Hueco Mundo!
What's with that pathetic state?
Sh-Shut up...
Anyway...
Pursuers could come
at any moment.
Do you know how to
use the Hogyoku?
Pursuers?
You don't know yet?!
Calm down.
You're wasting time on this guy.
I-Impossible!
Crap!
This is terrible.
Patras, I kind of regret taking up
your proposal.
You knew from the beginning that
sacrifices were necessary, huh?
Yes...
It can't be helped.
Besides, anyone who'd be beaten by
a Soul Reaper
won't be of any help
in furthering my goals.
You bastard...
This is for the Hogyoku...
to defeat Aizen...
Therefore, I can't
lose to you here!
I don't have any reason to lose
to you either!
Let's finish this.
Okay...
Sounds good.
Roar! Zabimaru!
I thought so...
Crap...
Allow me to commend you.
You made me change my opinion
of Soul Reapers,
though just a little.
But things must
come to an end.
Don't decide that on your own.
I think that giving up is
important sometimes.
Do you have any last words?
It doesn't seem like you have any.
Well then...
Roar! Zabimaru!
- Zabimaru!
Another illusion...
This isn't only an illusion.
Why you...!
You're making fun of me!
Renji, get a hold of yourself!
You followed me again?
You guys can't handle him.
We can't leave you alone!
Stop...
There, there, there,
there, there, there!
You're in the way!
You idiots...
I told you to stop.
We're all right.
Anyway, we found his weakness!
What?
Kurodo! Noba!
You understand, right?!
Yes!
No problem.
M-My hip...
Renji, we'll stop him from attacking.
You hit him with a big one!
Wait! If you continue,
you'll really...
You idiot! We're mod souls that
were created to fight.
We can't quit just because
we can't win.
And besides, you can't let it end
in a place like this, right?
Oh well.
Don't die!
What's wrong?! How long are you
going to stay hidden?
We're not really hiding!
We've seen through your attack!
I was wondering who it could be,
but it was just some small fry.
You just use silly illusions.
Hey! Who're you
calling a small fry?!
At least I don't just use
one stupid attack, like you do!
What?
I'm telling you...
We've seen through your attack!
Use a different attack if you want to win!
I guess I have no choice
if you're going to go that far.
I'll wipe you out without a trace.
He fell for it!
Here I go then!
How silly. Take this!
Burst! Gerifalte!
How foolish...
Wh-What?!
Impossible!
What do you think?
You're the one who was
really the fool!
You specialize in
sword-drawing techniques.
Whenever you
drew your sword,
you always immediately put it back
into its sheath.
In other words, you were storing energy
in your sheath
and using your sword as a trigger
to release that energy.
And as long as you can't put
your sword away,
you can't make the next attack.
Also, the stronger your attacks were,
the larger your movements became.
Even if you specialize in
sword-drawing techniques,
it's possible for Noba to
toss things in your way!
Why you...
Now! Renji!
Okay. Hikotsu Taiho!
Take this!
This can't be!
In a place like this?!
Lirin!
You did it, Renji.
Mr. Urahara...
Sorry I'm late.
I just got back, Abarai.
Kurodo! Noba!
You worked very hard.
We just got a little
beaten up, though.
Noba...
Lots of problems...
Abarai! Are you all right?
Captain Hitsugaya...
Yes, somewhat.
Oh my. It seems like
you had problems too.
What happened to them?
It seems they're dead.
Aizen was toying with them.
Toying with them?
Is that the Hogyoku they brought?
That's...
Aizen probably let them steal a fake.
The Hogyoku won't crack that easily.
I made it, so there's no mistake.
Aizen probably tricked them.
Most likely with
his Kyokasuigetsu.
There's no way that
they would be able to steal the Hogyoku
from Aizen so easily.
He let them take it...
But why?
Who knows?
I don't know that much.
Did you come after them?
I have no intention
of fighting you.
They may have had a different goal,
and used those Arrancars
to create a front.
There's no way that no one came after
them after all this time has passed.
Even if they left them alone,
we'd deal with them.
Even if he's
going to purge them,
it's fun for him to plan
farces like this.
He's that sort of man.
So?
Traces of that event still exist.
At the time,
most of it was guesswork,
but upon investigating it again,
I've gotten an idea of
what her abilities are.
What do you think?
I think it will be of use to you.
I see...
So where is she right now?
She's probably not in
the World of the Living.
Good work.
No problem...
Hiyori, how long can Ichigo maintain
a Hollow transformation?
It's finally reached
the double digits!
Ah! He finally
surpassed ten minutes!
No, baldy!
He's still at ten seconds!
Is that all?
Don't be so difficult!
No! I'm at eleven seconds!
- It doesn't matter which it is!
- It does!
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers...
One down.
Brother.
Karin! She's shopping!
I'm glad I'm wearing a mask!
I-I'm not your brother!
What are you saying?!
You're my brother.
Huh?
You're not Brother.
Phew...
He's getting quicker at putting
on his mask.
It's the result of his training.