Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What do you mean, Ichigo?!
Don't go making
irresponsible comments!
Stop it, Lieutenant Abarai.
I beg your pardon,
Captain Kyoraku,
but Captain Kuchiki
would never betray us!
There has to be some reason!
I don't know what the reason is…
But it's a fact that Byakuya
turned his sword on us.
My goodness…
Old Man Yama goes missing,
and now there's
Captain Kuchiki's betrayal.
Who knows what other
surprises await us.
Captain…
The one bright
bit of news is that
Captain Hitsugaya's
Zanpakuto has returned.
But in his condition,
he won't be able to fight
for quite some time.
We now know how to
regain our Zanpakuto,
but if we suffer that much
damage each time we do it…
With regard to that, there was
a distressing report from Squad 12.
Results of tests on
the samples we took
show that a manifested
Zanpakuto,
when destroyed by someone
other than its wielder,
might never fully return
to how it once was.
That's terrible!
Then what should we do
when we're fighting against
someone else's Zanpakuto?!
I guess we'll have to go easy.
They're not opponents
we can beat that way…
The enemy seems bent on having us
destroy our own Zanpakuto.
If I may…
I think we should keep
Captain Kuchiki's situation
a secret from all but
captain-level personnel…
No, keeping it a secret
would only raise speculation
and create problems
by spreading unrest.
They say you can't keep
people from talking.
How will we explain this to Rukia?
I'll do that.
Captain Ukitake…
Kuchiki will have to
accept the truth.
Brother did that?
Yes…
Byakuya Kuchiki has
joined the Zanpakuto.
Although it could be that
he had his own ideas…
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Brother…
Byakuya Kuchiki…
What's this guy doing here?
What's going on?
Muramasa,
what's the meaning of this?
Why did you help me?
Senbonzakura…
Why would a man of your caliber
turn against the Soul Reapers?
Turned against
the Soul Reapers?!
You mean he sided with us?
I acted based on my own pride.
Pride my foot!
I can't believe that!
But he helped us as well.
What?
What's going on?
What're you…going to do?
We're here because we've grown
weary of the Soul Reapers.
You'll put us in a bind
if you ask to join us.
That's for sure.
We'd lose our reason
to be acting up.
Byakuya Kuchiki,
if you are indeed serious about
betraying the Soul Reapers,
then show us proof.
What is it you want me to do?
Slay your sister-in-law's
Zapakuto, Sodenoshirayuki,
right here and now.
Just a minute!
What're you talking about?!
You want him to slay one of us?!
It seems that a Zanpakuto killed
by someone other than its wielder
never returns to
its original form.
Can this man go so far
as to do such a thing?
So that's it…
He loves his younger sister,
Rukia Kuchiki, more than anything…
There's no way he could
slay her Zanpakuto.
That's…!
You never intended to let him
join us from the start?
Of course not!
The farce ends here.
I'll settle this
with you right here!
You want her slain, you say?
Hey…is he for real?
Tsuginomai!
Hakuren!
Hado 4: Byakurai!
Is he serious?!
Even if you seriously fight me,
can you really defeat me
in your present condition?
Somenomai!
Tsukishiro!
Stealth Hoho…
Shiho 3…
Utsusemi.
Rikujokoro.
How can this be?
If it is for the sake my pride…
…there is nothing I won't slay.
This can't be!
Are you out of your mind?!
You could never
comprehend my pride.
What?! Don't mess with us!
That's enough.
Muramasa…
A Soul Reaper who's lost her
Zanpakuto is as good as dead.
Knowing that, he callously snapped
his sister-in-law's sword…
I accept your resolve.
But…
Stop it, Kazeshini.
If Muramasa says it's all right,
let's accept that.
I won't forget this!
If you show any unusual actions,
I will slay you without hesitation!
Know that I'll always
be following you!
Now then, Byakuya Kuchiki.
If you are going to be joining us,
there is something
I want you to do…
Thanks, Renji.
Don't mention it!
There might be some clues
in the captain's office.
Rukia, the captain will
return without fail.
There's no way
he would betray us.
Yeah… I believe that too.
Lieutenant Abarai.
We're ready to change shifts, sir.
Okay. Be right there!
Rukia, don't work
yourself too hard yet!
I know.
See you.
Brother…
You always sat alone, Brother…
What were you thinking about?
I must've dozed off…
This Spiritual Pressure!
Brother…
Rukia.
This is…
Brother…
What are you doing here?
Or rather…
Where have you been?
Answer me, Brother!
This is his answer!
What?!
You're…
Sodenoshirayuki!
I don't feel any
Spiritual Pressure…
Could it be…?!
Without Sodenoshirayuki,
you have no means to fight.
No way…
Do not get involved any further.
What do you mean?
He means this!
Renji!
Damn!
Captain!
What is the meaning of this?!
Is it true that you're
on their side?!
Captain Kuchiki…
I'm detaining you
as a material witness
in the Zanpakuto Rebellion case.
Forget it.
You're no match for me right now.
Shut up!
Damn it!
Roar—
I heard you used Higazekko
in a previous fight…
That would mean that you cannot
even use Shikai with that sword.
Who can't use Shikai, you say?
You two!
Whether or not Renji
can use Shikai
has nothing to do with us
now that we've manifested.
That's right.
I'll handle this.
You go to Muramasa.
Ohh…you're going to take us on?
In that case, shall we settle
our unfinished business
right here today?
Don't get conceited.
Don't think you'll give me
a good fight with your skill level.
Don't underestimate our strength!
Let's do it, Snake!
Right with you, Monkey!
Roar!
You're not getting away!
Brother!
I'm not done with you!
I don't have time to deal with you.
I see that talking
to you is no use…
Shakkaho!
So that's how you fight when
you cannot use Shikai…
But it won't work on me.
Yeah, probably not.
But capturing you might
not be impossible!
Don't mess with me!
Shakkaho!
Hado 4: Byaku…
Bakudo 4! Hainawa!
You're going to
tell me everything!
What are your motives
for doing this?!
Nowhere to run!
For you, or for us?
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
You need to explain everything!
Not just to me!
But to the other captains
and to Ichigo!
To Squad 6 and its members!
And to Rukia!
Hikotsu Taiho!
What?!
Bankai!
Scatter…
Renji!
Are you all right?
– Brother—
– I'll say it once again.
Do not get involved any further.
Brother!
Hey, hey, aren't you
going to finish him off?
Looks like you were having fun.
Why're you all here?
Is that any way to greet us?
Muramasa said to lend you two
a hand, so we all came.
Beat those Soul Reapers
to death already!
What's the matter?
You're not gonna do it?
If you won't do it…
We'll do it for you!
Get away, Rukia!
I'll hold them off here!
In your condition?
Don't be ridiculous!
Just get away!
Stop prattling!
Your lives will end here!
What is this?!
Don't move!
Hold it right there!
Yo!
Who did you say you were
gonna beat to death?
Damn you!
Rukia, are you all right?!
Byakuya…
Byakuya Kuchiki…
As proof that you are one of us,
you'll wear a mask
identical to mine.
Why?
I have Muramasa's consent.
It's a fine mask.
You can feel the spirit
of the samurai.
Why?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Excuse me.
Yes?
This isn't good!
Patients need to stay warm…
I think that's everything…
Rein over the Frosted Heavens.
Huh?