Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
This is…
I'm sure you know him very well.
It's Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto.
Who are they?
Those three are Zanpakuto.
Their powers rival each other
so they've been frozen in
that state for a long time.
Their powers rival each other…
Hey!
Don't make him change
his Spiritual Pressure!
Don't blame us if
you get blown away
by his fluctuating
Spiritual Pressure!
Yeah!
They don't really listen to me.
It's quite troublesome
for the Head Captain.
Byakuya! You…
Damn it!
What…
Wait…
Old Man Yama's whereabouts?!
Is that true?!
Well, it's just
the most likely place
the Head Captain would be.
But I found the Head Captain's
Spiritual Pressure there again.
What should we do?
There's not much point in
waiting for them to come to us.
It's not in our nature to wait,
after all.
Let's go, Ken! Let's go!
Let's go looking for Old Man!
Come on!
I think you're confusing this
with a game of hide-and-seek.
Hey.
The guy I have to slash
is probably there, right?
Yeah, probably.
But try not to slash
the General Captain by mistake.
That Old Man wouldn't quite rest in
peace if he's slashed by accident.
How about it?
Will you two be coming with us?
This is boring.
Your idea of an interesting day
is so exciting
that other people's hearts
would stop.
What a cruel thing to say.
It's true, isn't it?
When I was released
from my master,
I thought that it was the beginning
of a more interesting life.
You were easily defeated
by your master too.
What?! That was your fault!
I know that.
The same thing happened to me.
What is it?
You seem rather calm today.
Well, I do agree
that this is boring.
Who's there?!
Kazeshini?
Jeez. Don't scare us like that!
Kazeshini!
What is this?!
Oh, no…
These wounds are bad…
Yeah. I'm surprised he was
able to come back here.
What are you doing?
I'm glad you could
make it back, Kazeshini.
Rest up and heal your wounds.
Muramasa…
What is it, Kazeshini?
Let me ask you one thing.
Sure.
You told me to follow
my true instincts, right?
That's right.
My true instinct is to reap
the lives of Soul Reapers!
I know that.
My goal is to release Zanpakuto
from Soul Reapers.
Then why is there
a Soul Reaper over there?!
Byakuya Kuchiki
plays a crucial role
in achieving our greater goal.
With your help, Byakuya was
able to make it back safely.
I am very thankful.
But why do we have to get
hurt for a Soul Reaper?!
Even though we have
a greater goal,
it saddens me that people
have to get hurt.
But there's no need to worry.
As long as we have
Genryusai Yamamoto,
they cannot do anything to us.
We're close to achieving our goal.
They should be getting desperate.
Sorry, but please hold out
for just a little longer.
This certainly is Genryusai's
Spiritual Pressure…
I also sense some
powerful barrier.
Muramasa must have been
unable to control Ryujinjakka
and sealed Old Man Yama
within a barrier.
I guess we're fortunate that we
didn't have to take on Ryujinjakka.
Anyway, the Old Man
is in here, right?
Yeah. That's for certain.
But this cave is like a maze.
Also…
The Zanpakuto appear to be
using a different entrance.
If their hideout is in here,
we must be careful.
What a pain.
Let's quit talking and
just charge on in!
That's right! Go, go!
Ken! Go, go!
Do it! Go, go!
Honestly… There's no point in
making plans when he's around.
Well, now's not the time to wait
and see what they're going to do.
We should go too.
Ichigo, we're going in from
a different entrance.
Okay.
The Soul Reapers have come.
Yeah.
Damn it… This sucks.
I charged in, but it's so dark
I don't know where I'm going.
Hey, Yachiru! Which way
do you think I should go?
Let's see… That way!
I can't see which way
you're pointing!
I told you, it's this way!
Stop that, you idiot!
Don't pull my ears!
Yoruichi.
What is it?
Can I ask you one thing?
Sure.
Do you think that
Byakuya is here?
Are you that concerned
about him, Ichigo?
Yeah.
He joined the Zanpakuto and
pointed his sword
at Rukia and Renji.
But I don't know why.
My desire… I want…
to defend my pride.
That's all.
But I thought you might know
what Byakuya is thinking.
I don't know, either!
What?!
Ichigo!
Simmer down!
If you get worked up, you'll never
be able to bring back Byakuya!
He probably has
some secret plan.
But…
Oh no!
Oh?
I heard that she was the former
commander of the Stealth Force…
But she wasn't
much of a challenge.
Stealth Hoho, Shiho 3…
Utsusemi!
What's up with this?
Girls these days are all talk.
Go ahead of me, Ichigo!
Right now, saving the Head Captain
is our top priority!
After that, you can do
whatever you want!
Got it!
Oh?
We've come to a pretty nice place.
You sure are carefree.
Don't say that.
It looks like we're going to
climb up these steps
to go deeper into this tunnel.
What shall we play?
Wanna play?
Who's there?
He wants to know who we are!
He does!
Do you really not
know who we are?
Really?
– Come on, let's play!
– Come on!
I see…
If we don't play with these kids,
we won't be able to move on.
Yeah.
Even though they're Zanpakuto,
I feel uncomfortable
playing with children.
Yeah… What do we do?
Now then…
Who are you children?
Who could we be?
Who?
Are you Sogyonokotowari?
– Correct!
He figured it out right away!
How boring!
Sorry about that.
Did I kill your fun?
Then let's begin the next game!
Yeah, let's do that!
What should we play?
How about Tosenkyo?
That sounds great!
Great!
One!
Two!
– Three!
– All right…
– Go!
Now then, what shall we play?
Unfortunately for you,
playtime is over.
Don't say that.
We've known each other
for a long time.
Can't we just reconcile
our differences?
I refuse.
What with your arrogant attitude
we've run out of patience with you.
"We"?
Then that other Spiritual Pressure
I've been sensing…
I guess I wasn't imagining it.
You finally came out.
You saved me the time
looking for you.
I'm glad you could come,
Soul Reaper.
I'll get my revenge for
our last encounter!
Is the Old Man's Spiritual Pressure
coming from this way?
They showed up!
Wait!
This Spiritual Pressure…
Is it the Old Man's?
All right!
Wha—?!
Die, Soul Reaper!
Y-You bastard!
I'm not letting you go.
I'm going to reap your life!
Bankai!
You bastard!
Getsugatensho!
Damn it…
Sorry, Hisagi.
Hot!
A barrier, huh?
Jeez… This is such a pain…
Here I go!
My swords are so beautiful.
I would've never imagined.
And I never expected mine
to be children.
I wonder if there's some way I could
just keep them by my side
and not fight them.
Yeah, I want to play
with them for a while.
Please fight them.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Say! Say, say, say!
I never thought I would
run into Yoruichi!
What's so great about her?!
But letting her see me
get into danger…
How shameful!
That's your fault for being weak!
But…
Yoruichi…c-c-c-carried
m-me in her arms!
Hey!
Are you listening?!
Yoruichi!