Ichigo Kurosaki...
All of the battles you've fought
were a part of my plan.
I'm not done yet.
I thank you, Genryusai Yamamoto.
You have protected my world.
Damn...you...
Genryusai Yamamoto,
I will not spare your life.
You are Soul Society's
history itself.
I will finish you off with my sword.
Don't make me repeat
myself, boy.
His scorched arm
is cracked.
This is...
the forbidden technique which
can only be activated
by using one's scorched
body as a catalyst.
Sacrificial Hado
Number 96...
Ittokaso.
I underestimated him.
He sacrificed his own scorched
body and used it as
a weapon without hesitation!
Getsugatensho!
I'm not done yet.
What's so funny?
You failed to kill me,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What?
That was my last opening.
It was good enough.
I injured you.
Injured?
You call this an injury?
Instant Regeneration!
This isn't Instant Regeneration.
Do you really think that I'd
undergo a Hollowfication?
This is just its compulsion
to protect its master.
What do you mean?
That's...
It's the Hogyoku.
So this is your Spiritual Pressure?
How wonderful.
You've matured splendidly.
Just the way I wanted you to.
What?!
You
met Rukia Kuchiki,
and following your battle
with Uryu Ishida,
you awakened your own
Soul Reaper powers.
During your battle
with Renji Abarai,
you learned about the power
of your Zanpakuto.
During your battle with Kenpachi Zaraki,
you got a clue about your Bankai.
During your battle with Byakuya Kuchiki,
you began your Hollowfication.
During your battle with Grimmjow,
you mastered your Hollowfication.
And during your battle
with Ulquiorra,
it seems you've gained
an even greater power.
Ichigo Kurosaki...
All of the battles you've fought
were a part of my plan.
Do you want...to save
your family?
Of course!
Is there a way?!
There's just one way.
You must become
a Soul Reaper!
Give me that sword,
Soul Reaper!
My name is not "Soul Reaper."
I am Rukia Kuchiki.
I'm...
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Damn it...
There's no end to them.
What's the meaning of this?
There's far more of them than
the bait I used would draw.
It's as if they're being drawn in
by some other giant power.
Sensei...
Ishida!
It's easier to fight against a
large number of opponents
when you're doing
it back to back!
Bring it on!
Kurosaki!
The sky...
The sky?
What...?
What is this extraordinary
Spiritual Pressure?
Kurosaki's power
is increasing.
Victory!
Hey, Hiyosu.
The Stealth Force has
turned in their report.
What does it say?
It's exactly as you suspected.
It's the missing criminal.
I knew it.
Let's catch her and retrieve
the gigai she's using.
That aside, I'm surprised
you found her.
I don't know why,
but I felt like watching some broadcasts
in the World of the Living.
When I turned on the switch,
I saw this playing.
I'm so lucky!
Jeez... I guess your hobby can
come in handy once in a while.
Shut up.
So when are they sending
us her gigai?
Well, about that...
It's going to be a while.
There are formal procedures
to go through,
so they sent a retrieval team.
Really?
Who's on the retrieval team?
Well...
Roar, Zabimaru!
Look in front of you!
What stands before you...
is your prey!
It's over, you damn kid!
This is where you'll die,
defeated by me, Renji Abarai!
I won't make it!
What?!
What is this?
You're slow.
Brother Byakuya!
Yes, I'll keep pushing you...
until you can remember
that attack!
When you dodge an attack,
you don't let them cut you.
If you protect someone,
you don't let them die.
When you attack, you kill!
You see my sword?
It reflects my determination
to kill you.
Damn!
When you dodge an attack,
you don't let them cut you.
Damn you!
If you protect someone,
you don't let them die.
When you attack, you kill!
Hang on, Chad!
I'll beat this guy, and come
save you! I swear!
Sorry...
I'm not ready to die just yet.
Because if I die, I'll lose
everything I've been fighting for!
What do you know?
So you can fight.
Ichigo...
Do you believe in me?
Of course I do.
I'm entrusting you with
all my powers.
Do whatever you want with it.
And lend me power!
Yes...
Ban...kai!
Tensa Zangetsu.
No Bankai could be that small.
A mere Ryoka could
never reach Bankai.
I've got him!
Impossible!
Every single one was deflected?!
Senkei...
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Only those I have sworn
to kill can see this form.
Byakurai.
You're at your limit, aren't
you, Ichigo Kurosaki?
What?
My body... It won't move!
You're only human.
No matter how much you
endure, there are limits.
This is your limit.
It's over, Ichigo Kurosaki!
If I don't win, nothing
will change!
I want to win.
I...want to win!
I thought I told you...
It's a big problem for me
if you get yourself killed.
Impossible...
Who are you?!
Who am I?
I have no name!
You're no good after all, Ichigo!
Damn! Damn!
What's this?
You fool!
Has he already undergone a Hollowfication?
Gin...
Oh? Is it all over now?
There's no need to worry.
Everything is going
according to plan.
It all begins now.
So why did you go over
the past battles today?
We wouldn't want our
viewers to forget
what happened up until
now, would we?
And I assure you, it's not
because I had forgotten.
There were parts I forgot
about as well.
I haven't forgotten. Really.
You so did, didn't you?
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Wow, I sure went through a lot of
battles in just six months or so.
I wonder what my high school life
would have been if I hadn't fought?
Well, isn't that obvious?
Huh?
Challenge to a Fight
Hold it! Why am I ending
up fighting here too?!
Because you're a delinquent.
No, I'm not!