Gunchotsurara!
Each Espada signifies
an aspect of death.
Damn it!
Ryusenka!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Hunt...
Tiburon.
Wh-What?!
So that's all you've got...
A mere ice dragon will
sink to the bottom of the ocean
with a single blow from a shark.
You're next.
I will have my revenge
for those three.
What is the meaning of this?
I didn't think that
your speed and range
would suddenly increase so soon
after your sword release.
I'm glad I took precautions.
A virtual ice image...
I can use a trick like
this only once,
so I really didn't want to use it
until the very last moment.
Don't underestimate our strength.
I see...
As I might have expected
from a captain...
You seem to have an ability proportionate
to your rank to avoid danger.
But don't think that's
enough to save you.
What?
What destructive power!
You fool.
How can you let your guard down? It's bad
enough you're lacking in brain and strength.
Oh, I'm sorry...
Wait a second!
That's harsh, Captain!
The brain part was
unnecessary, you know!
That Halibel is putting
on quite a show.
Now the enemy must learn
the pain of her sacrifice.
Sacrifice?
Yes.
Each Espada signifies
an aspect of death.
A mortal's death results
from those ten aspects.
It is also the basis
behind each Espada's abilities,
beliefs, and reason for existing.
Loneliness.
Emptiness.
Despair.
Destruction.
Intoxication.
Insanity.
Greed.
Rage.
And Halibel signifies the aspect
of death known as "sacrifice."
That lethal power shall consume
the brat, leading to his death.
Too soft.
I've seen through that technique!
Don't underestimate me.
You should have realized by now...
My ice-snow type Zanpakuto turns
water of any kind into a weapon.
Even if that water is your weapon.
Your attacks will never reach me if
all you can do is manipulate water.
It can, and it will.
If you want to see it,
I will show you.
Come.
Do you think I'd fall for your taunts and
close the distance between us?
That's what I mean by...
you underestimating me!
You're the one who is
underestimating me.
Hirviendo.
You realized my water could
become your weapon,
but you must also consider the possibility
of the opposite being equally true.
Such is the ironclad rule of battle.
Cascada.
Captain Komamura!
Don't worry. That shock wave
was nowhere near here.
More importantly, hurry and
finish up their treatment.
Yes, sir.
But so many are hurt so badly...
There's no way I can
do this in time alone.
This force field isn't
impenetrable, either.
Captain Komamura is the only one
who can stand against them.
If they attack...
Come on out.
Did you think you could
trick me with that?
That was close.
I somehow managed to avoid it by
quickly putting up a wall of ice,
but if I got caught by that force,
I wouldn't have lasted a second.
I don't stand a chance against
her with an ordinary defense.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you finally realized your
situation and chickened out?
"If the enemy's weapon
is one's weapon,
then the opposite must
also be true," you say?
I don't need to hear
your old-fashioned lectures
for me to understand that.
Gunchotsurara!
It's the same regardless of
what technique you use.
Hirviendo.
In return for the lecture,
let me teach you something.
"The greatest danger comes when
you use your greatest tactic."
That is also an "ironclad rule of battle."
Amusing.
I'm thrilled...
It looks like you're starting
to get serious here.
What else can I do?
The idea of just getting myself pounded
doesn't sit well, even for me.
But it seems you're hardly putting
your best effort into it.
Whoa!
Boy, that was close.
If you had attacked me like you meant it,
I'd be dead for sure. Yep.
You had no intention of
slashing me from the start.
So why go through the trouble?
We won't get anywhere if all we do
is observe what the other might do.
Things will change greatly if one
of us takes the first step forward.
But that's where the problem lies.
The moment one of us
takes a big step forward...
That's what both of
us are waiting for.
Put another way,
the battle changes when one of us can
make the other take the first step in.
Aren't you getting impatient?
I'd like to see your
Cero about now.
Good grief. Why not?
I'll take you up on your invitation.
La Gota.
What is she up to?
It doesn't look like she's blindly
launching her techniques.
On the other hand,
she is aware this technique is
not enough to finish me off.
Her aim is most likely...
Is it okay for you to look away?
You seem fast when running away.
Cero!
No more running for you.
You fight such a timid battle.
Can't say I blame you, though.
You and I are both waiting for
the same thing, aren't we?
For this battleground
to fill with water
so we can strike a
single death blow.
If that's the case, so what?
It just means I have
to think of a plan.
I have no choice.
We're going nowhere if she and
I are waiting for the same thing.
I've never tried this with Bankai,
but I'll give it a go!
Did you come up with
some sort of strategy?
Actually, I don't have
to wait for the water.
Here goes!
This Spiritual Pressure!
They're so close by!
What's the matter?
Did you hesitate because
it might injure your allies?
Shut up.
What do you care?
Well, never mind.
Either your allies
become sacrifices,
or you yourself
become a sacrifice.
Feel free to make the choice.
How's this?!
Sennen Hyoro!
He did it!
So this is the best you can do?
What?!
Are you done?
If you don't have anything
more, then here I come!
Damn it!
Cascada.
If I dodge...
Then the people below will...
Damn it!
Ryusenka!
Did you think you could stop me,
using a technique like that?
The volume of water
in this battleground
has already reached a level that is
more than enough to finish you.
That last Cascada won't even compare
with the one that's coming.
Captain Hitsugaya...
No way... Captain Hitsugaya...
To...shi...ro...
So you shattered that Cascada...
But you are naïve.
Our existence is built upon
the noble sacrifices made.
Instead, you fall in battle from trying
to protect your subordinates.
My subordinates were
not simply defeated.
They left behind markers for me,
on how to carry on the fight.
If I had lost, my subordinates' sacrifices
would have all been for nothing.
I hold within me the resolve of those
who sacrificed their lives.
I know that.
I suffered a great deal
of damage, but...
It's unlikely you'll be able to fight at
full strength with those injuries.
And that's exactly why I will.
Such a waste of effort.
What is this?
My Hyorinmaru is the strongest
ice-snow type Zanpakuto.
All water is my weapon.
All the heavens are
under my control.
Hyoten Hyakkaso.
That Barragan dude sure is able
to memorize a lot, isn't he?
He didn't memorize it.
He was looking at his hands the
whole time he was talking.
He probably noted down the
lines on his palm with a pen.
Oh, is that it? He's pretty stupid...
Just like you.
What?!
Arrancar Encyclopedia
Today I'll be talking about Halibel.
Halibel's sword release
is called "Tiburon."
It has the ability to
manipulate water.
As long as it's water,
she can freely control its
temperature from hot to cold.
Although once she goes into release
mode, her clothes reveal more skin.
It's a bit embarrassing.
It's so I don't have to
worry about getting wet.
Whoa, cold!