Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Dammit! Where the heck
has Ganju run off to?
Ikkaku said the one chasing Ganju
was the 5th seat of Squad 11…
His name was…
It was…  It…was…
Huh? Well, never mind.
That means he’s the 5th strongest
from the Captain on down.
I gotta rescue Ganju.
He probably can’t manage on his own.
There’re nothing but these
same walls all over the place!
I’m getting mad!
Hey! Ganju!
Where the hell are you?!
If you can hear me,
send up some fireworks to let me know!
You dimwit!
Rats! I gave myself away.
There’s one!
The orange-haired Soul Reaper!
You’re not getting away!
Kill ‘im!
For the glory of Zaraki Squad,
even if it means death!
He’s getting away! After him!
Bastard! Stop!
Give up, orange head!
Your luck ran out when you met me!
This means a promotion!
Dammit! Ganju! Where are you?!
A hole…?
A hole!
Dammit! Another hole?!
How many are there, anyway?
It’s the last hole.
For you, anyhow.
Whaddya mean, the “last hole”?!
You’ll never convince me of that!
I’m getting away from you.
Even if I have to fall into a hole!
Would you like to try?
I didn’t tell you, but…
the bottom of the hole is
surrounded by Sekki-Seki.
In other words, they completely
block spiritual powers.
Now you know, don’t you?
Why no one who falls in
can ever get out again?
Ow…!
I see the damage I inflicted
is still there, after all…
Well, you’ve managed to elude me
all this time,
even though wounded.
I suppose I should commend you
for coming so far,
as ugly as you are.
You really make me sick!
Bastard!
I make you sick? That can’t be helped.
Ugly ones envy the beautiful.
It’s only natural.
Hey, Ganju!
Halt! Filthy Ryoka!
Is that your comrade making
all that racket?
He’s been calling your name
all this time.
Halt, I say!
Bow to your fate!
Damn! They sure are persistent!
Ganju! Ganju!
Your friend behaves in the
same ugly manner as you.
It will only summon a never-ending
horde of Soul Reapers.
Really…
It’s difficult to understand
his lack of good sense.
Ain’t you the one without good sense?
Huh?
Ichigo is there because…
he defeated your bald-headed partner.
T-That can’t be!
Our Squad 11 is the best combat unit
of the 13 Court Guard Squads!
Ikkaku is our 3rd best fighter!
How could your man defeat him?!
Your only strong skill
is seeing openings!
You ain’t seen nothing yet!
Shiba-Style…
Battle-Level Shooting Flower!
Senpen Banka!
Don’t underestimate me!
You call that a skill?!
How dare you…?
My face, how dare you…?!
Now you look more like a man!
No finesse.
You probably mean to use your
one strange skill to collapse the ground,
and kill us both.
Huh! Me, die with you?
I’d never die so wastefully!
Silence!
You’re a tough bastard.
For all this time you’ve run from me,
enduring my attacks,
and yet you still can move.
I marvel at your physical strength.
Just a while longer…
Just a little while longer…
He still underestimates my power.
The only time to use the Seppa is now,
while his guard is down!
Truly… That alone is regrettable.
If you had been born beautiful…
You would have been my very favorite...
I can’t dodge him!
What’s wrong?
Can’t you use that
floating technique anymore?
Ugly…
What good is it for an
ugly one to persist in living?
If one is born ugly,
he should at least die beautifully.
I disagree.
It seems our ideas of aesthetics
are completely different.
I was taught that, ugly or not,
the one who survives is the finest!
What?!
Bastard! You dare lay your
ugly hand on my head…!
It helped that you underestimated me
to the last.
Now for the finish!
Shiba-Style Rock-Wave Secret Move!
Renkan Seppa Sen!
W-What the…?!
Dammit!
You can’t finish me with
this puny attack!
Don’t make me laugh!
Where are you?! Where?!
H-Hey! Take this!
What’s this…?
It’s a bomb!
Noo!
What the heck. He’s over there?
It’s a little late for that.
Shut up.
Hey, they’re close! But…
it’s not this way, is it?
Since it’s a dead end.
Shouldn’t we have turned right
at the last corner?
You’re the one who said
to come this way!
Oh, Kenny! You shouldn’t blame others!
Wasn’t I close? There, go there!
This way, right?
Yep!
They’re gone, aren’t they?
Yes…
He seemed terribly strong.
It’s lucky that he didn’t see us, isn’t it?
Yes. He must be the same type as Kurosaki.
He has awesome power,
but poor detection abilities.
Now… We changed sites,
but where should we go from here?
How about that way?
I see a tower off in the distance…
Tower? Where?
Look, over there.
Didn’t touch her…
To escape from such close range…
very good.
Magnificent!
If you had met anyone but me,
you might have lived a little longer.
Lament! I’ll count to ten to
give you time to lament.
One…
I sense the collision of Spirit Pressure
here and there.
Don’t die, my friends. Live!
One…
Two…
Oh…thank you. I’m all right, Ishida.
Three… Four…
Yes…you are.
Five…
He’s not the same Ishida as a while ago.
Six…
He moved so quickly.
Seven…
For a split second, Ishida vanished
from my consciousness…
then I was saved before I realized.
Such a transformation at the
mere sight of a Soul Reaper.
It’s just as Yoruichi said.
Ishida is a Quincy.
Even now, Soul Reapers are
enemies to him.
Ten!
Now, your time for lamentation is over.
Have you done it to your satisfaction?
He’s coming!
Right!
Now comes another time for lamentation.
Come, Soul Reaper!
I’m the one you’ll fight!
It is not you who decides who will fight!
Now, I shall end your lamentation.
With your death…
Ms. Inoue! Run!
No, I mustn’t run.
I’ve got to fight and save Kurosaki!
Tsubaki!
At last, it’s show time. Aim well!
Koten Zanshun! "I reject!"
Tsubaki!
Fool… Faltering like that…!
Tsubaki…
That was the first time
I saw that technique.
There’s no intent to kill
in your attack.
Though you might kill Hollows
with that move,
it will have no effect on Soul Reapers.
M-My body won’t move…
This is a battleground!
Without the intent to kill,
you’ll never stop anyone!
Wha--?!
So you want an attack
with intent to kill?
Then fight me. It’s here in my bow…
The intent to kill you love so much.
Hanataro…!
What do you want?
This is no place for your kind!
Be gone! We never sent for
anyone from Squad 4!
Uh…I used to do the cleaning when
she was in Squad 6 barracks’ prison.
I thought the Shishinro might
need some cleaning, too…
The Shishinro can’t be opened for anyone
until the sentence is carried out!
Don’t you even know that?!
Beat it, beat it!
Oh, but…
Beat it, or I’ll hack you to pieces!
Y-Yes, sir…
What’s wrong?! Scared?
You can’t get away, Ryoka!
You’ll get us a special promotion!
Rats! I'm surrounded!
There's no way out!
Geez!
I let up a little,
and it goes to their heads!
Anyhow, what should I do?
Men! Kill ‘im!
I’m g-getting crushed!
Cut it out, bastards!
So I can run!
He’s off again! Get ‘im!
How many are there, anyway?!
Hmm…Very interesting.
Would you be a Quincy?
That’s right.
Ishida’s bow…
It’s totally different from the one I saw!
In its appearance and even
in its spiritual pressure…!
That glove…
He must have been practicing
in order to use it properly.
Learning to use it…
practicing all alone…
This is interesting.
One uses an unfamiliar skill;
the other is a Quincy.
And both employ projectile weapons.
And you’ve both come to fight me.
What coincidence! What a twist of fate.
Now I must show you.
The true form of my Zanpaku-to.
Spread your wings! Tsunzaki Garasu!
What do you think? Now, lament.
I am 4th Seat of Squad 7!
Jirobo Ikkanzaka!
Also known as Jirobo Wind Sythe!
The nickname, Wind Sythe, proves that
I am the most skilled in
projectile weapons.
My countless blades dance
through space.
No one has seen
my Tsunzaki Garasu and lived!
Here, here. How do you like it?
You can’t even follow them with
your eyes, can you?
They’re the prelude to
a brilliant death.
Before Tsunzaki Garasu,
your bow and arrows are
as helpless as a baby!
As a fellow master of flying weapons,
you’ll fully regret having met me…
Huh?!
How interesting.
Unlike the outside world…
here, the strongest fighter seems
to be the most long-winded whiner.
Ridiculous! That was a fluke!
Don’t be so cocky.
You still don’t understand?
Sorry, but if you’re supposed
to be the strongest,
I take back your nickname
as of today.
Where flying weapons are concerned,
I seem to be the better man.
The name, “Uryu Weasel with Scythe,”
though, doesn’t sound all too cool.
You men search over there.
If you find them, take them alive.
They might make interesting
research specimens.
Don’t let the other Squads
capture them first.
Yes, sir!
Go!
Hmph! They’re only humans, though.
I don’t expect very good specimens.
Hell Butterfly?
What’s the message, Nemu?
Yes, sir…
Ikkaku Madarame of Squad 11
encountered and fought a Ryoka.
What?! So the Squad 11
already has a Ryoka?
No, Ikkaku was beaten by the Ryoka
and taken to the Squad 4
General Relief Station.
The Ryoka escaped and
his whereabouts remain unknown.
Defeated by a Ryoka? My my…
Among the Ryoka, there seem
to be quite interesting subjects.
Where’s Zaraki?
Searching for Ryoka, sir.
Then he wouldn’t know about this yet.
Well, before he gets wind of it,
let’s get the info on Ryoka.
Lord Mayuri, where are you going?
To see Ikkaku.
How slow you are to guess.
Come along, dullard.
I sense Zaraki’s Spiritual Pressure.
So he’s on the move…
Ichigo… Be careful!
Get him!
There!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll alway stay close to you
Now and forever
We're surrounded!
So many Soul Reapers!
We've got to fnd someplace
to hide!
We need a plan
to outwit the enemy!
Just blast them with an
attack right through the middle!
Okay, you go.
You go.
Go, Ganju!
Uh, I've got piano practice…