Ghosts Aren't the Only Ones
Who Run Wild Around Graveyards
Boss!
You really sure about this?
If one faction causes trouble,
the other three gang up to crush it?
It's obvious that they
want to get rid of us!
I'd say that this saves time.
This is a chance to show them who the
real king of the Kabuki District is.
But that means we'll have
to deal with Otose...
My memory's been getting worse.
Who is this Otose person?
Idiot!
We're not supposed to mention the hag
while the boss is around!
The vixen is not as much
of a concern as the cub.
Focus on him.
Damn.
What is that kid doing?
You were dancing to her tune.
That's not like you.
Kada is using you to get rid of Jirocho,
who's hurting her business.
I just want to live peacefully
in this town with my comrades.
I'll dance a waltz or octopus
dance if that's what it takes.
So you can clean up this
town by eliminating him?
Even if that were true,
I could never bring
myself to love a town
that's neat and tidy.
Spoken like a true trashy old hag.
I believe that you're old friends
with the trashy old geezer?
Haven't talked to him in over ten years.
Doesn't really matter if a
dangerous old man dies or not.
But...
I'm here to turn the town
where Jirocho is into a garden.
The timing's too perfect.
Finally, it's time for payback.
Like I said before,
I always return the
favor, seven for three.
Nobody parts their hair 7:3 anymore.
You should shave your head
and opt for the bald look.
Up yours!
My hair is styled like Joe Odagiri!
Fashion trends come back in a cycle!
Hold on here.
I was egged on by this stupid girl.
I have no grudge against you, Joe Schmo.
Who are you calling Joe Schmo?!
Besides, that's not what
my boy here told me.
I know what's going down.
You promised to
help her decorate our
boss with red flowers.
How do you know that?
Why don't you tell him what you really
mean when you say red
flowers, Pirako-han?
Uh, Pirako-chan?
U-Uh, are you...
Bro, my boss was
a relative of Jirocho,
and an old friend.
He used to tell me when I was young,
about the great Jirocho,
warrior among warriors.
The warriors you see around these days
are just a bunch of wild hotheads.
But he was different.
He would save the weak
and crush the strong.
He would only employ his strength
for the sake of his particular justice.
That's what you call a true warrior.
That's too hard for me to understand.
Sorry about that.
The more I talk, the less sense I make.
Basically, Jirocho was a flowery man.
That's probably what
drew your mother to him.
Though the flowers in him
died at some point...
He abandoned his wife and child,
and crushed his wife's
family because of business.
And now he's picking a stupid fight
with a tranny and an old hag.
I just want to see the old
Jirocho one more time.
To help him take the world...
To help make some pretty
flowers bloom in my old man.
Huh? What's she talking about?
That went completely over my head.
What? What?!
There you have it.
Pirako-han is...
No, the young lady is
Jirocho's daughter!
To be precise, she's the daughter of the
missus who divorced the boss
and went back to her family.
Bullshit!
Help your old man take the world?!
That's the complete opposite of revenge!
Isn't that what I said?
I'm here to decorate him with flowers.
You were talking about making
me the big boss of Japan!
You were trying to
make me fight Jirocho!
Yakuza grow stronger by recruiting
the people they beat.
My old man can take the
world if the strongest
man in the Kabuki
district is on his side.
Once you're the big boss,
my old man will be the big, big boss!
Young lady, it's settled.
Bro, the Jirocho gang will
be making their move now.
Do you know what's happened?
There's a law in this lawless town now.
If any faction starts a fight,
the other Devas will crush them.
The first victim will probably be
the boss of a certain someone
who picked a fight with the Jirocho gang
over a helpless little girl, Otose.
But it's your call to make, Bro.
Please join us!
Or else we'll have to
drop you in the ocean,
and Otose will be targeted by
everyone in the Kabuki district!
Hey, I'm guessing that's
supposed to be a threat,
but if you kill me here,
you'll be considered the aggressors.
You an idiot?
Why do you think we put on a show
in the middle of town?!
We got plenty of witnesses!
You're the idiots!
The Four Devas aren't gonna
move because of a little spat!
A death is far more serious!
Die, baldie!
Go bald down your parted hair line!
Go bald all over your body!
I ain't gonna go bald!
Every week, I part my
hair to the opposite side
to avoid excessive damage to my scalp!
I ain't like Sanshi Katsura!
If that's not enough, how's this?
We'll say that you killed
our young leader here,
and we killed you for revenge.
Huh? No way...
Bro!
Is your boss the guy
with the parted hair?
Or is it Jirocho?
B-But...
If you move, I'll turn
you all into flowers.
Got it, Bro?
I'm serious.
D-Damn you!
Bastard!
He jumped into the water
with the concrete!
Is he trying to escape?!
Nope.
He went to save him.
That's stupid!
He can't move!
And why would he save Bro?!
Yes, he's stupid.
I was very surprised.
But that's why I wanted him on our side.
But he also chose the old hag.
Pity.
Bye-bye, Bro.
I came up with this
plan so the three of us
could deal with Jirocho,
but I never would have
expected Otose to...
Don't be ridiculous!
Otose-san would never...
Pako would never do anything like that!
We know how gentle they are!
Calm down, Assmi!
Don't call me Assmi!
It's Azumi, damn it!
Shut the hell up, Ass!
Could you add the "mi"?
You can call me Assmi as
long as the "mi" is there.
It looks like we were the only ones
serious about stopping this conflict.
When did you make a deal with Jirocho?
You think I would make
a deal with that vixen?
Were you pushed by the kid?
No, were you the one who pushed the kid?
Don't play dumb!
They might be rotten to the core,
but they aren't dirty like you people!
That's enough.
You should stop that, Saigo-san.
It's not nice to whine
and go back on your word.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Jirocho's daughter, Pirako Doromizu.
Jirocho's...
I have a question for you, Saigo-san.
Do you have any
proof that Otose-san
hasn't done anything?
My proof is the fact
that you have no proof.
Why would Otose pick
a fight with Jirocho?
And now of all times?
There's obviously a conspiracy going on.
Nobody would spend that
much effort to kill an old hag.
Besides, we have proof
that Otose-san would pick
a fight with my old man.
There's a long history between them.
Isn't that right, old man?
Here it is.
Otose-san's husband, Tatsugoro Terada,
was killed by my old man.
Oh? You didn't know?
What about this?
My old man and Tatsugoro-san
were friends when they were young.
But then they got into a
fight over a certain girl.
Tatsugoro-san was the
one who won her over.
I'm sure that my old man
wasn't happy about it.
Stop it...
That's why he killed his old friend.
So he could have the girl.
Stop it.
Do you know why he abandoned his own
wife and daughter to come to this town?
That's because the girl,
Otose-san, is here.
Didn't you hear me say to stop?
See? It's just like I said.
He cares more about Otose-san
than his own daughter.
You came here just to tell me that?
Such a dutiful daughter.
If what I'm saying isn't true,
that should mean you can kill Otose-san.
Are you running away?!
Saigo, don't worry.
Yakuza don't need trannies
to clean up their mess.
You stay out of it.
I'll settle this myself.
Wait!
I'm not done talking...
I'll spare you this one time,
since you kept whining.
Could you shut up now?
How am I supposed to shut u--
Have you forgotten?
If you go back on your word,
we'll have to eliminate you as well.
When laying siege to a castle,
what would you target first?
The weakest spot in the wall.
A seasoned soldier like yourself
should be aware of this.
M-Mama!
Te-Teru-kun is... Teru-kun is...!
Damn you!
Snack Otose
I see.
Very well.
Don't worry.
That was Gintoki.
It seems that Pirako is safe.
They learned about the
new rule right before
they were about to take
on Jirocho's gang.
Apparently, they were able
to talk things through.
That's a relief.
I was worried that we would be too late.
They kept us worried this whole time.
What are they doing?!
I appreciate everything you've done.
You haven't eaten since
yesterday, right?
Now that you mention it, I'm starting
to feel hungry now that everything's okay.
Want to grab something to eat?
Can we?
Yakiniku!
We must have yakiniku!
At a really expensive place!
Stupid!
That won't fill my stomach!
A buffet!
At a place with ice cream!
Stop fighting.
Let's compromise by
going to a gas station.
How is that a compromise?!
Go on ahead.
I'll join you once Gintoki
and Pirako are back.
Please hurry.
We'll wait for you
before we start eating.
But the ice cream doesn't count, right?
I can eat ice cream while
we're waiting, right?
Didn't Otose-san seem a little strange?
How?
When she offers to buy someone dinner,
there's usually a catch.
No, that's not what I meant...
Oh, sorry.
He's covered in blood!
Sorry!
Is this my fault?!
Huh?
It's Katsuo-san...
Hey! The bucket that
just ran past us...!
Gran!
Terada Family Grave
It's rare to see you here.
I'm assuming that you brought flowers.
Hell no.
Did you want me to bring
flowers for you, Otose?
It's been years since
you've spoken to me,
and that's all you have to say?
You never change.
If you lay me to rest
next to my husband,
I suppose I can't complain.
I heard that you took care of my kid.
Save your thanks for that idiot.
Though apparently, that
kid of yours got him good.
She's quite a dutiful daughter.
She came all the way here to clean
this town for the sake of a
stupid father who abandoned her.
We've both been dancing to
the tune of a little kid.
The years haven't been kind to us.
Well, I suppose you knew
what was happening.
The villain Jirocho
can't go against the
daughter he left in tears?
Otose...
Get out of this town.
This place will become
a battlefield very soon.
It was gonna happen even if my
kid didn't rush things along.
You'll only get in the way if you stay.
So you were planning on
starting a war, period.
Terada Family Grave
I would have hoped that
you wouldn't say those
words in his presence,
even as a joke.
Policeman and vigilante.
The two of you were both
protecting this town,
despite your different positions,
but I suppose that was in the past.
Jirocho.
You went so far as to
abandon your wife and child
so you could do this?
Times have changed.
A vigilante can't protect anything.
He died and left you behind.
Your methods are old-fashioned.
You're just a nuisance,
both you and Tatsugoro.
This town doesn't need you anymore.
This town belongs to me.
I'll give you one more chance.
Get out of this town.
I have a favor to ask.
They call me one of the Four Devas,
but I don't have any
members in my faction.
I'm sick of waiting for you to pay the rent. Take your fools and scram. Never come back to this town.
--Otose
My life is all you need.
They serve no use at all.
They just happen to be my family.
Is that your answer?
You're Gintoki?
You were a step too late.
I buried her with her husband.
Funny how it works.
I believe that you were serving as her
bodyguard to pay back a debt?
That's over now. Your job is done.
Scram.
I'll spare your life for her sake.
Ouch...
The hell was that?
Not bad, kid.
You made me draw my sword.
But are you willing to let Otose's
efforts to save your lives...
...go to waste?
You're not being very reasonable.
It's over.
I heard that Otose was keeping
a crazy monster around.
So you're the White Yaksha?
I never knew there was a freak like
you following in my footsteps.
However...
A generation managed
to survive the brutal
battles of the Joi war.
There were plenty more
like you out there.
Get lost, watchdog.
There's nothing for you to protect here.
Hey, Gran.
Are those manju?
Can I have some?
I'm starving to death here.
These belong to my husband.
Ask him.
What did my husband say?
Beats me.
The dead don't talk.
You're just asking for it.
Don't blame me if you get cursed.
The dead don't talk and
they don't eat dango.
So I made a one-sided promise.
I won't forget this debt.
Your wife doesn't have
that much longer to live,
but I'm going to protect
her in your stead.
Gran...
Next Episode
Chains of a Warrior