Trouble arises over
succession rights
in one of Soul Society’s high-ranking
aristocratic families, the Kasumiohji Clan.
Their princess, Rurichiyo Kasumiohji,
traveled to the World of the Living.
Ichigo reluctantly agrees
to become her bodyguard.
Rurichiyo, who is unaware that
her life is being targeted,
turns Ichigo’s life upside down
with her naive behavior.
One after another,
Ichigo and his friends take down
the assassins sent by Kumoi,
the provisional administrator
of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Frustrated by the string of
missed opportunities in his plans,
Kumoi comes up
with something new.
Sir Kumoi…
Why did you let Princess Rurichiyo
return to the World of the Living?
I cannot be rash and attract the attention
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Hanza Nukui, I am entrusting you
with this sword.
Get rid of Rurichiyo and
the rest in the World of the Living.
Along with everyone
who gets in your way.
Now then…
I shall proceed with my plans over here.
I’m so bored.
I wonder where Ruricchi has gone.
Master Kannogi.
Huh?
Yes?
Sir Kumoi wishes to see you.
Please come to the meeting room.
I said…move out of the way!
Don’t block people’s way
with your huge frame!
This is my house, y’know!
Oh, you’re wrong there, Lirin.
We are mere freeloaders here.
You’re flipping the logic here.
Shut up!
Stop nitpicking on every little detail!
Move!
Now you’ve done it!
Oh, but that was your doing!
This poses a problem.
One more time!
Oh! This is so much fun!
Rurichiyo, you’re so good at that!
That’s just beginner’s luck!
It’s just chance! A coincidence!
Oww! What’s the big idea?!
It is not chance!
I am good at it!
What?! Are you looking for a fight?!
W-What?
I didn’t do a thing. Yet…
Jinta…
Still…
I am surprised that you all
made it back safely.
You used the Kasumiohji Clan’s
private Senkaimon for the return trip,
did you not?
Yeah.
Just to be safe, we waited until dark
before heading to the gate.
But it was surprisingly easy to return.
It was as if…
they let us go on purpose.
More like…
they did let you go on purpose.
It’s easier to settle affairs
in the World of the Living.
That’s probably it.
Say, Mr. Urahara.
What is this about
goods running low?
I don’t know much in detail.
In any case,
products are harder to get.
We’ve never run so low on supplies.
It seems there is a decline
in the raw material itself.
Raw material?
I mean, reishi.
Of which, only one particular type
is depleting drastically.
But when I went over there recently,
there was no sign of that.
It’s all happening under the radar.
But it’s hard to believe something
like this would happen naturally.
Then someone is
doing this intentionally?
I checked many sources,
but I couldn’t get that far.
However…
However?
This phenomenon started
the same time
that princess appeared here.
You sure it’s not a coincidence?
No.
We can’t dismiss that.
The Kasumiohji Clan are
high-ranking aristocrats
second to
the four great noble families,
but I’ve heard that the family
has other special circumstances.
I don’t know what that is,
but the mayhem arising
from the run on goods
has never happened
in Soul Society.
I can’t believe that they’re
not connected in some way.
Kenryu, don’t you know anything?
Our duty is to protect
Princess Rurichiyo.
We know nothing else!
Don’t get so cocky!
Cripes! You never act
according to plan!
At least stay well informed!
Be silent!
Now, now…
Anyway, let’s just
investigate a bit longer.
This incident seems to
go deeper than I thought.
Lure them away from
Princess Rurichiyo as planned.
Now then…
Substitute Soul Reaper…
Show me how good you are.
What’s this Spiritual Pressure?
Rukia! Inoue!
Take Rurichiyo home.
Right.
What about you, Kurosaki?
I’m gonna check that out.
I’m coming with you.
All right!
Chappy, watch Ichigo’s body.
Leave it to me, pyon!
What did you just say?
I said Lord Shu Kannogi will become
the head of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Would there be a problem with that?
I cannot agree to such a thing in
the absence of Lady Rurichiyo!
Agreed!
Our Kasumiohji Clan has always
had female sovereigns.
It is an ironclad law!
A male cannot head our clan.
Lord Kannogi came to this clan
as Lady Rurichiyo’s betrothed!
Be it temporary,
in Lady Rurichiyo’s absence,
it is in the Kasumiohji Clan’s interest
to ask him to be our lord.
But still…
I am opposed!
Me as well!
The enemy’s Spiritual Pressure
has spread throughout the town.
It must be a trap.
We’ll know when we fight them.
Let’s split up!
Yeah.
His Spiritual Pressure…
It’s the same as back then.
Oh? You sensed it, after all?
Yeah… You’re the one who taunted me
back in the Soul Society, aren’t you?
I am Hanza Nukui.
Now show me just how good
a Substitute Soul Reaper is.
Again?
Yes.
Why is my life being targeted?
It is too complex to explain!
In any case, we will protect you,
no matter what!
That is no explanation!
Tell me everything!
Another time!
No!
What’s wrong?
You… That sword…
Oh… You noticed it?
It’s the same one
as that other time.
The Zanpakuto and its wielder
are one in body and mind!
Why do you have that?!
You don’t need…to know!
What’s the matter? Is that all?!
That last guy was
way stronger!
I guess I can’t win like this.
What?!
Trap them… Saiga!
Such a small repertoire.
I’ve seen that attack already!
Now, it’s my turn!
Not again!
What the hell?!
This is different from
what the small fry use.
You can’t defend yourself from my attack
just by looking away from the light.
What will we do?
Sir Kumoi is pushing his way
through everything.
The order of the Kasumiohji Clan
will be totally disrupted!
We must object, at all cost.
– What is this?!
– Identify yourselves!
They are faster than I had thought.
This is a bad spot.
I must get out into the open.
Santenkesshun!
Kotenzanshun!
Now’s your chance!
Thank you!
Let’s go, Inoue!
Right!
What is this place?
My body…
It’s useless.
Your consciousness is here,
yet it’s not here.
What?
As long as you are locked up
in the world of mirrors,
you will not be able to
move an inch.
It’s totally different from the time
you last faced this sword.
What do you mean?!
This sword acts by consuming
its wielder’s spiritual power.
In other words,
the higher the spiritual power,
the greater the power it can draw.
Depending on its wielder?!
If this sword consumes
spiritual power,
only someone who can endure it
is able to manifest its true power.
Someone like me!
Now then, let us not waste time.
I shall kill you in one breath.
As if I’ll let you…
have your way!
What?! A crack in Saiga?!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Why you…
Don’t get too cocky!
Damn… Move… Move!
It’s useless!
What’s wrong with me?! Move!
Yoruichi!
Yoruichi?!
It seems ordinary methods
won’t work on him.
Yeah. I owe you.
Oh? You still want to continue?
Check it out carefully.
The Spiritual Pressure
of your subordinates.
What?!
This is the end.
Impossible!
Did you think you could bring us down
with that level of troops?
Hold it, you!
Ichigo!
Kuchiki!
Damn it. Shihoin Yoruichi…
I didn’t expect someone
like her to be there.
And also…
Ichigo Kurosaki.
His Spiritual Pressure is…
So it won’t be that easy.
Well then…
Now, we will proceed with the installation
of the 18th Lord of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Lord Shu Kannogi, my complements
on your installation.
Do you suppose
they will come again?
I’ll take them on next time!
But I’m told that our new gigai
aren't ready yet!
What?! And I wanted to show off
my sexy appearance!
There’s no such thing.
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
I’m going to talk about
Fracciónes today.
We are able to select
personal subordinates
FRACCIÓNES
from Arrancars numbered
11 and under.
They are called Fracciónes.
Some choose one, others more.
– Master Szayelaporro!
– And mine are quite special.
You can eat them and they have
a rehabilitating effect.
See?
Hey, hey, you shouldn’t
take over someone’s segment!
Would you like one?
I can’t handle raw food.