Aizen entered
the World of the Living
to wipe out Karakura Town,
an Enriched Spirit Zone.
In order to stop him,
the Soul Reapers took up positions
in the World of the Living
and constructed the Tenkaiketchu on
the four corners of Karakura Town
to swap a fake Karakura Town
with the real one.
Madarame, Kira,
Ayasegawa and Hisagi,
who were assigned
to defend the pillars,
each faced Fracciones
sent by Barragan.
Yumichika faced off against
Charlotte Chuhlhourne.
It became a fight over beauty
between Chuhlhourne,
who touted his own beauty,
and Yumichika, who denied it.
A princess always gets her way.
If I say it's over, it's over.
W-What is this?
Rosa Blanka, the Sentence
of the White Rose.
Enveloped in this briar
covered with black,
you will die, unseen by anyone,
smothered in white petals.
Unseen…by anyone?
That's right.
In anyone's eyes…
I see.
Thank you.
Tear in frenzy,
Ruriirokujaku.
What is this? This thing!
It's futile.
Those flowers are growing by
stealing your Spiritual Pressure.
From here on,
all the Spiritual Pressure
you radiate
will become that
of the flowers.
Do you understand?
The moment those
flowers bloom,
will be your end,
Charlotte Chuhlhourne!
D-Damn it!
I'll help myself to some
of your Spirit Energy.
Thank you for the treat.
Y-You.
You're sneaky…
keeping such an awesome
technique hidden like that.
The second level of
Zanpakuto transfiguration…
This was Bankai, wasn't it?
Wrong.
It wasn't Bankai.
Ruriirokujaku is the actual name
of my Zanpakuto.
This is an odd sword, you see.
It's picky about colors.
"Ruri" is its favorite color.
And it dislikes the color "Fuji."
Fujikujaku is a nickname
I arbitrarily gave it.
This sword despises that name.
When I call it that, it sulks
and only goes
into partial release state.
Why do such a thing?
Squad 11, where I am,
is the strongest fighting squad
among the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
We're made up entirely of
a group of fools, who gathered
out of respect for Captain Zaraki,
and who live to fight.
We all feel that
"if we're going to die,
we'll go out with a good fight."
Because of that belief,
we all made an unspoken agreement
from way back that
our Zanpakuto would only make
direct attacks.
Kido-type Zanpakuto look bad
and are an embarrassment,
so just having one gets you
treated like a coward.
I don't want to show
this sword's power
to anyone in Squad 11.
Particularly not to
Ikkaku and Captain.
That's why when you
covered me with the briar,
I thanked you.
If you hadn't used that technique,
I could not have released
this sword in our battle.
Even if it meant losing to me
because of that?
Even if it meant
losing to you and dying.
You really are a piece of work.
Hey… Aren't you going to
draw your sword?
This is my weapon.
I'm well aware of the toughness
of your Hierro!
Oh? So you've fought
an Arrancar before?
Yeah.
Hey, big guy! What's your name?
Why do you ask such a thing?
I have no intention
of telling my name
to an opponent who
is no match for me.
Okay then, don't tell me your name!
I'm third seat of the Zaraki Squad,
Ikkaku Madarame!
I let my opponent know the name
of the man who's going to kill him.
That's my style!
I don't get it.
Don't get what?
A while ago,
you said you'd fight with
strength equal to a lieutenant.
Even giving you
the benefit of the doubt,
your strength right now
was about fifth seat.
What's up with that?
Exacta.
That is correct.
Correct, you say?
My strength right now is indeed
at the level of a fifth seat in
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
It pleases me that you made
the correct assumption.
Just what I would expect
of a lieutenant.
You pass.
What?
This is a test.
A test to check to see if you could
accurately measure my strength.
Unless I did that,
you wouldn't realize it
even if I fought at
lieutenant-level strength, right?
The way you talk bothers me.
The way you put it, it sounds
as if you're saying you have
a way of accurately fighting
at the strength of a lieutenant.
Exacta.
My current strength is
that of a fifth seat.
And…
The impact of his sword
is greater?!
This is fourth seat!
Third seat!
Quit fooling around!
Am I getting closer?
And…
This is lieutenant level!
Bakudo 39: Enkosen!
Are you done already?
That was pathetic, Izuru Kira!
Ah well, but that's to be expected
when you're facing Aguila.
Don't think they're just wings.
These are wings of steel,
heavier than boulders,
that smash everything
they come in contact with!
"Wings of steel," eh?
That's a good name.
It sounds strong.
However, it doesn't change
the fact that they are still wings.
Oh? Another technique?
Hado 58…
Tenran!
So you thought a tornado would
work if these were still wings?
Well, it won't!
His power and speed are
to be reckoned with.
But if I can lure him
into a cramped room…
Hado 31…
Shakkaho!
He went through the trouble
to invite me to his position.
How would you respond to that?
Quit scurrying about, you rat!
Devorar Pluma!
It's able to pierce
through the building?!
There you are!
Damn it! He's hiding behind
all sorts of things!
There's no sign that the number
of wings is decreasing.
Must be his instant
regeneration ability.
They probably regrow from
the tip where they break off.
If that's the case…
As he's running away
all over the place,
he might be thinking up
some kind of plan.
But I won't let him!
What? What is he doing?!
Where did you go this time?!
What?!
Were your legs crushed because
you couldn't get away in time?
I didn't think I used
that great a speed, though!
You saved me the trouble.
For what?
Your long-distance attacks
were tough to deal with.
All this time,
I was thinking of a way to
make you attack me directly.
You see,
there's no point in
cutting objects separated
from its target with my sword.
I don't understand what you mean.
What in the world are you going to
cut with that oddly shaped sword?!
What the hell is this?!
Damn it!
What's happening?!
My wings are suddenly…
It makes what it cuts weigh double.
If I cut twice,
it will weigh double again.
Cut a third time,
and it will weigh double again.
That is the power of
my Zanpakuto, Wabisuke.
Raise your head! Wabisuke!
In that instant where
you attacked me,
I delivered four strikes
across your entire wings.
If your wings are truly
heavier than boulders,
they became much too heavy
to fly a long time ago.
You dirty bastard,
using a cheap trick like that.
Is that how a warrior fights?!
Dirty?
Oh, that's right.
Before we began fighting,
you were shouting out
to get us both fired up.
If that's how a warrior acts,
the idea is completely
outside my understanding.
Squad 3's squad flower
is the marigold.
The flower holds the meaning,
"despair."
In other words,
it is the pride upheld by Squad 3.
A battle must not be heroic.
A battle must not be exhilarating.
A battle must be gloomy,
filled with despair,
frightening and grisly.
That is what makes
people fear battle
and choose the path
that avoids battle.
I believe that my Zanpakuto,
Wabisuke, among all Zanpakuto,
best coincides with
Squad 3's philosophy.
It continuously increases
the weight of what it strikes
until the adversary ends up
crawling on the ground,
unable to bear the weight.
Then, without fail,
as though to apologize,
the adversary extends his head.
That is why it is called Wabisuke.
What's so funny?
What do you mean, "despair"?
Fear battle? Avoid battle?!
Let me throw your exact words
back at you.
The idea is completely
outside my understanding!
Battle is about…
firing up oneself to
crush your adversary.
It's exhilarating!
You can't defeat me with that!
It won't be me who'll
extend his head in apology!
It'll be you!
Devorar Pluma!
How?
Your defeat was already
decided the minute
one wing was rendered useless.
No matter how hard a bird
tries to stand up and fight,
a bird crawling on
the ground is mere prey.
Earlier, you asked,
"What in the world was I going to cut
with that oddly shaped sword," didn't you?
Wait… Please wait a minute!
A warrior shouldn't
beg for his life.
Farewell, sky warrior.
If possible,
I hope you won't forgive me.
(Mirin=sweet rice wine)
Lieutenant, say mirin ten times.
Mirin, mirin, mirin, mirin, mirin,
mirin, mirin, mirin, mirin, mirin.
What animal has a long nose?
(Kirin=giraffe)
Kirin.
That's not right!
The correct answer is elephant!
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
What the hell are you doing?!
Shut up! Keep still!
How is it?
Delicious. What is this?
It's a confection I made
per the captain's orders,
but it just won't sell.
I wonder why?
It's this…
Yeah, that won't sell.
Substitute Soul Reapers have
a terrible sense of aesthetics.
No, I don't.