Something very scary must
have happened to you.
Rachel...
My name is Danny.
I'm your counselor.
Could you tell me what happened to you?
Where am I?
What a pretty blue moon...
But it looks like a fake blue moon.
I need to hurry back to Mom and Dad.
I came to a hospital...
But this isn't it.
"Who really are you?
You should ask yourself.
Who am I? The real myself
or the one I believe to be?
An angel? Or a sacrifice?
Know yourself and new doors will open."
The same me as always...
Rachel... Gardner.
I was at the hospital...
And the next thing I knew, I was here.
Because...
Because I saw people die.
I saw them get killed.
So I was brought in for counseling.
I want out of here.
I want to see my mom and dad.
An exit?
The girl on the bottom level has
been selected as a sacrifice.
Please begin preparations on each floor.
What did that announcement mean?
Beyond here is the play area.
Play area? What's that?
Is all of this really
the inside of a building?
Either way, I need to find the exit.
Is... someone there?
Indiscriminate Murders
Blood...
A bird?
It's hurt.
No, don't run away.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Come on now.
Let's get out of here together, okay?
That was a real self-satisfied
look you had on your face...
But now it's turning to despair.
I'll give you three seconds.
Just try to run away if you can.
And be sure to cry, scream,
and beg for your life!
Let me see more of that despair on your face!
Three!
Two!
One!
Where'd you go, little bitch?
Are you hiding?
Hey, get the hell out here!
Yeah, guess that's not gonna work, huh?
Tch, I missed...
Guess she's not there.
I have to get out of here before he finds me.
If he catches me, he'll probably kill me.
That bird is already...
No...
This bird is different.
This isn't the same bird.
It didn't look like this.
It didn't look so pitiful.
I need to fix it to look like that bird.
Don't worry. You won't feel pain anymore.
I'll fix you up to be my own bird.
Now you'll be all right.
I wonder if there's an elevator in—
I finally found you!
I'm not even gonna give
you one second this time!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry!
The hospital...
Rachel!
It's me.
Doctor Danny, the one
who's been counseling you.
What?
Doctor... who's been counseling me?
That's right. Don't you remember?
I see...
You do seem a bit confused.
Don't worry. I really am your doctor.
Doctor...
Yes?
Um... I was just being chased.
Who was that?
The one chasing you was
most likely a murderer.
Doctor, we have to get out of here!
It's okay.
He won't come up to this floor.
Trust me.
Rachel, let's look for the exit together.
I'm glad you're all right.
You didn't run away?
No, since you're here.
I knew you'd make it this far.
You were waiting for me?
How did you know I—
Anyway...
We need to find a way up.
It's too thick to break through.
How do we—
It seems like the two of us
are trapped here together.
Oh... I'm sorry.
You don't have to be scared.
It's all right.
If we just take it slow,
something good might happen.
Something good for both me and you.
Okay?
Something good?
Let's try that room there.
"Do you know what you really want?
Desire, do you know what it is?
There is no reason to fight against it,
if it's your true desire.
There is no reason for you to be here too.
But remember, don't break the rules.
For each wish, there is
a price: that's the rule."
What rules?
This place must have some rules.
Then what does it mean by "desire"?
I suppose that's different for everyone.
Mine would be... to have perfect eyes.
One of my eyes doesn't work well, you see.
If only I had eyes like yours...
How wonderful that would be.
Something's written—
Don't do that. You'll get dust in your eyes.
You need to take good care of your eyes.
They're so beautiful, after all.
Come on, let's try another room.
What is this place?
It's an operating room.
Rachel, would you give me
a good look at those eyes?
They truly are beautiful.
Just like my mother's.
And yet, your terrified expression
makes them look like normal eyes.
That makes me sad.
I want to see your truly beautiful eyes.
If I can wake up from this nightmare,
maybe that beautiful silence,
just like that blue moon,
will return to your eyes.
Rachel...
I want to live my life next to those eyes.
Doctor...
I almost forgot.
I left something very important around here.
Would you help me look for it?
Look for something?
I'll search this room.
Would you check the room in the back?
Did you forget what it is I'm looking for?
Look closely at me...
with those pretty eyes.
What did my face look like?
I'll give you a hint.
My eye is alexandrite.
Rachel, the back room is dark,
so be careful.
False eyes?
Rachel?
You still don't remember?
Try to remember the time you
and I met outside the hospital.
I don't remember ever
meeting you outside of here.
Oh! That's it!
You found it for me!
This false eye is yours?
Doesn't it make you remember anything at all?
You're still inside a dream.
Would you let me have that?
It's necessary for you and me both...
Rachel!
O-Okay...
Thank you.
I'm going to put it in now.
Wait in the other room for me, all right?
Rachel...
If you try to run away, you'll regret it.
This isn't right.
He's not the doctor I know.
I have to run.
It's so tight.
But just a little more, and...
It's open!
Where are you going?
I told you not to run away, didn't I?
U-Um...
You see, this... is my floor.
Doctor?
If you run away to another floor,
I won't be able to do anything to you myself.
No...
My desire was to continue to see your
living eyes next to me for all time...
But it's no use now!
I have no choice!
You no longer have the ideal,
living blue eyes that I want!
So, Rachel...
Give those eyes to me.
Let go of me!
Please, Doctor, don't do this.
I'm so sad!
You've forgotten who you are,
and even who I am!
Come on, don't you remember
why this is happening to you?
Rachel, please go back to
those fantastic blue eyes.
Live with me!
No... Please, stop...
No use, eh?
But your eyes are still far,
far more beautiful
than those of anyone else who's ever lived.
Let me go.
I want to go back to my mom and dad.
Don't worry.
You'll see your mother and father very soon.
Your mother and father...
are waiting for you in hell!
Hell...
Now, Rachel, your eyeballs...
Rachel?
Rachel!
Yes! That's right!
How beautiful your eyes are!
Now, come live with me, Rachel!
I'm so terribly lonely!
You...
a...
...re...
Hey, now, Danny! Your voice
sounds way too damn happy!
I just couldn't resist cutting you open!
Hey, little girl...
I chased you all the way here
to find you in a hell of a spot.
So, do you want to live?
Better run away right now, then.
Run away, struggle,
and keep hold of hope.
I'm gonna...
slice you open right here!
Huh?
Tch.
That face is no fun.
Don't you want to live?
I'm a grown-ass man, you know.
I'm not into cutting up dolls.
Huh?
A resident of Floor B6 has
attacked a resident of Floor B5.
As this violates the rules, the traitor
has been selected as a sacrifice.
Huh? What kinda dumb joke is this?
Damn. Guess I should run.
That's right...
I shouldn't... be alive.
Damn it!
It won't open! What do I do now?
I don't have a damn clue.
Huh?
What the hell are you doing,
just waltzing up like that?
Actually... I want to ask a favor.
Huh?
I want you to...
Kill me... please.