Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Group 2, take the East Sector!
Group 6, sweep the North West Sector!
Group 3, take South Sector!
Report in when the Ryoka are captured!
Damn! Where’d those Ryoka go, anyway?!
We’ll get you, Ryoka, for sure!
Naturally!
Quick, over there!
Before another group finds them!
How come everybody’s acting like thugs,
all of a sudden?
Rats. A dead end!
Ain’t you going senile?!
You’ll get it, you!
Hah! You’re idiots for following me!
What?! You’re the idiot!
Hey, calm down, guys!
The search perimeter for Squad 6,
Group 126 to 143 has changed.
You’re in the way! Move! Move!
Your new perimeter will be West Sector,
Yow! I’m sorry!
from Street 58 to Street 76.
Squad 4 shouldn’t get in the way!
Yow! It’ll spill! It’ll spill!
Don’t screw up menial chores!
Move it!
Your new perimeter will be West Sector,
from Street 58 to Street 76.
Phew.
Rukia, I’ve brought your food…
Rukia?
Rukia! Rukia?!
Who’s there?
Oh, yes’m. I’m the caretaker
for Rukia Kuchiki.
Where is she…?
You’re from Squad 4?
Rukia Kuchiki has already been sent
to the Senzaikyu penitentiary.
What?!
B-But…
What’s wrong?
Oh…um…I didn’t know…
A search has been ordered for Ryoka
who infiltrated the Seireitei.
Return to your Squad at once.
Rukia…
What was that light this morning?
From in here,
I can’t feel any spiritual energy.
Could it really be…?
Ichigo…
Don’t talk like it’s ended.
I haven’t shown you my skill yet.
It starts now, Ikkaku.
This time, you’ll be the one
who can’t hold your sword!
Fine words. Greenhorn!
Where does that
confidence come from?
Slow!
I won’t be able to hold my sword?!
Don’t make me laugh!
It’s you who won’t hold
your sword again!
Wasn’t I supposed to be slow?
Humph! You are. That was a fluke.
I’ll show you it’s not a fluke.
I told you…too slow!
Lucky!
Humph!
What’s wrong?
Talk is all you can do?
Hozuki-maru can transform at will.
A greenhorn like you
can’t keep up, can you?
That’s not true.
I’ve finally…gotten used to your attack.
This guy…
He took Hozuki-maru with
his bare hand…!
Kenny, over there, over there!
They’re over there!
We’ve been running for a while,
but haven’t seen anyone…
Don’t worry! I’ve got
super keen intuition!
Oh! Go right! Right!
It’s a dead end!
That way, then! Go back, go back!
Are you sure we can trust
this intuition of yours?
Uh! Ms. Inoue! Hide!
Found them?!
Where’d they go…?
It looks like we really caused
a big commotion.
It’ll be difficult to meet up with Kurosaki
and the others
before searching for Ms. Kuchiki.
If there was a commotion someplace,
we’d find one of them there.
Perhaps we should just jump in…
Or… What do you think, Ms. Inoue?
Huh?
Ms. Inoue?
W-Where’d she go?
Ishida-a-a!
Huh?!
What happened, anyway?!
Sorry! I went scouting,
and they spotted me!
Since they’ve seen us,
I’ll have to fight!
I’ll fight, too!
No! Leave this to me!
They stopped! Get them!
Don’t worry. You stand back.
But…
Found them!
Get them!
Yow!
We found them!
So many…!
Can you beat them, Ishida…?
Run!
They’re running!
After them! After them!
What’s that?
Is it Ichigo…? Or…?
What’s wrong, Ikkaku?
Don’t look so surprised.
I hope you haven’t lost your nerve.
If you won’t attack, I will!
I’ll say it again, Ikkaku…!
The one who won’t be able
to hold his sword…
…is you!
D-Dammit!
Heh…! What’s wrong?
It’s over already…?
Too bad!
I can still hold my sword!
If you want to make me stop,
you’ll have to cut off my arm!
Put down your sword.
No way!
Don’t! The fight’s over!
You know it! You lost!
Rubbish. This is a fight.
It’s over only when one is left alive!
Slow!
Damn… You sure…are strong…
Crap… I wasn’t lucky…
Neither of us was lucky…bastard…
Where’d he go…?!
That was close!
When will you stop running?
When you give up.
Stop, already.
I’m getting tired of this.
I’ll end it now…with my…
Fuji Kujaku.
Heh, heh. End it, you say?
I’d say…
Don’t be so hasty!
S-Stop it!
How disagreeable!
My beautiful eyes are smarting!
How’d you like that?!
The Kukaku brand hot-pepper
smoke bomb!
The Tears-of-Blood is powerf--
What’s this?! My eyes hurt!
Ouch, ouch!
My throat, too…!
What do you think of this power…?
Unbelievable! You harmed yourself
with your own strategy.
Too ugly!
I breathed it in.
W-Where are you…?!
Hah! You’re not catching me!
H-Hey. Let go!
How can I?!
How come…I’m still alive?
You’re awake?
Yo.
Ichigo…
Why are you still here?
Well, I learned something…
The released Zanpaku-to
returns to its original form
when the owner
goes unconscious.
My Hozuki-maru!
Bastard! Give it back…!
I’m not gonna take it.
I just used some of the medicine
in it to stop the bleeding.
But I used it all up on the both of us.
But it sure works great,
this medicine…!
B-Bastard! That was dirty!
Why?! Sure, I used it up,
but that’s no reason to get so mad.
That’s not it!
Damn…!
I knew something was wrong!
I didn’t die, even after losing
so much blood…!
I can’t live on like this…in shame.
Damn! If I could only move,
I’d beat you to a pulp!
Crap. What’s with you?
Shouldn’t have saved you.
Well, appreciate it or not,
it doesn’t much matter to me.
All I want are some answers.
Humph. I knew something
like this was coming.
I sure am unlucky.
What do you wanna know?
When my birthday is?
Where’s Rukia Kuchiki?
Let go, you’re heavy…
Dammit! Can’t hold on…!
No!
Please! Don’t let go!
If we fall in there…!
Those who fall in can never get out.
Can’t hold…on!
I don’t wanna die! Help!
W-What’s with this place?!
Pee-yew!
Hey, you! I thought you said
nobody could ever get out of here!
This is an ordinary garbage dump.
Never mind that…
How dare you plunge me in here!
You’ll pay!
Woah!
You made yourself fall!
Shut up!
Stop! Running again?!
I’m running!
Kuchiki?
Yeah.
That Kyokushu?
What do you guys want
with somebody like her?
We came to save her.
Haah?! S-Save her…?
How many of you came?!
At least 7 or 8, right?
No…
Five humans and one animal.
What? One animal…?
You seriously intend to
rescue her with so few?!
That’s right!
Y-You’ll never pull off
something like that!
Are you stupid, or something?!
I-I laughed so hard,
my wound opened up!
I dunno who’s the stupid one.
Ahh. Well, all right…
Directly south from here are
the stations
for each of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
H-Huh? You’re going to tell me?
Shut up! Just listen!
Or I won’t tell you!
At the west end of the stations
is a white tower.
She should be there…
I-Is that true?
You’re doubting me?!
I have no interest in whatever
you want with the girl.
Save her, if that’s what you want.
Hey, get going,
or other Reapers will find you!
Go, if you’re going!
Oh…yeah…
So long. I owe you, Ikkaku.
Don’t. It’s annoying.
Wait a minute.
Can I ask you something?
Who’s the strongest in your group?
It’s me, probably…
Is that so…?
Watch out for my captain, then.
Captain has no interest
in weak men.
If what you say is true,
you’re the one he’ll be after!
He’s strong?
Meet him, and you’ll find out…
how strong he is.
That is, if you stay alive long
enough when you meet.
What’s his name…?!
Captain of the Squad 11,
Kenpachi Zaraki.
Crap.
Another dead end?!
You were the first in pursuit.
You have no sense of direction!
Fool! We’re stuck because
I trusted in your so-called “intuition”!
Never mind! Let’s move on.
Aye, aye, sir!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll alway stay close to you
Now and forever
No sense of fashion! None!
I've always wondered…
Are Soul Reapers happy with their look?
I can't understand it!
That's why I despise Soul Reapers.
Ishida, the Soul Reapers are still
your enemies, aren't they?
That's the reason?!