Brother, where are you going?
We’re returning to the Soul Society.
Huh?
Have you forgotten, Rukia?
We came to see the choice
Ichigo Kurosaki makes.
The Soul Society was aware
that once the next Substitute
Soul Reaper appeared,
Ginjo would set his sights
on him sooner or later.
When that happened,
we would use that Substitute
to find Ginjo and
before eliminating them
at an appropriate time.
The majority of captains
shared that view.
But our contact with that Substitute
changed the Soul Society.
We shared our powers with the Substitute
we were supposed to kill
and dispatched captains
to watch his actions
rather than kill him.
Kuchiki.
Remember when you objected to the orders
of keeping watch on Ichigo Kurosaki?
That can’t be!
Ichigo wouldn’t…
He would never succumb to the
temptations of the enemy!
You were right.
Ichigo Kurosaki learned the
truth and made his choice.
That choice was the very same choice
that the Ichigo Kurosaki we knew—
the Ichigo Kurosaki you
believed in—made.
I’m glad the Substitute
Soul Reaper after
Ginjo was a man like him.
That’s right.
He hasn’t changed since
the very beginning.
The one man’s unchanging will
is what changed
the Soul Society’s
million years of rigidity.
Ichigo!
Why?
I plan to crush the Soul
Reapers who betrayed me.
And I expected you to argue
that that was wrong.
Aren’t you even going to do that?
Why won’t you?
The look in your eyes
is that of someone trying
to understand me…
Of someone trying to put himself in
my place and see things
from my perspective.
Are you telling me
that you plan to understand me,
and still reject everything that I am…
Ichigo?!
Ichigo…
Would our roles switch
if you were the one who
had appeared first?
Would you have become like me?
Would we, Ichigo?
If you had come first…
would we have been…
No!
Riruka…
Are you stupid?
You were really going for the kill!
Out of my way!
Don’t die!
Don’t die, Ginjo!
Ginjo!
Face it!
Face up to it already…
We…couldn’t save Ginjo…
Ginjo is the one who saved us…
But the one who saved Ginjo…
Is Ichigo.
Are you all by yourself?
I see.
Then we’re alike.
Come with me.
From today on, it’ll be the two of us.
Why, Ginjo?
You taught me how to use my powers…
You taught me how to fight….
So why?
Why didn’t you teach me
what to do when you died!
Shishigawara…
Oh…I see…
I get it…
You have a bad habit of kicking things.
You have no business lecturing Riruka.
Jackie.
You’re alive. That’s nice.
I may as well be dead.
Jackie, your Fullbring…
Yeah.
I see.
That’s good, though.
You were the only one
among us who truly
detested her abilities.
On my way here, I found Giriko’s
watch and dead body, so
I buried them together.
I detested my abilities so much.
But now that I’ve lost them,
I kind of envy Giriko for being
able to die with his powers.
Maybe it’s because
somewhere along the way,
I realized that our Fullbrings were
all that connected us together…
That sounds stupid.
I’m leaving.
Ichigo!
Oh, you’ve come to.
I’m…alive…
Yeah.
Mr. Urahara came right after it happened.
But…
Except for you, we couldn’t
find anyone else…
I see.
Thank goodness…Riruka…
You…
When I heard they didn’t
find anyone, I…
What?
After giving it a lot of
thought, I couldn’t…!
In my mind, Mr. Tsukishima,
you’re the strongest!
You mustn’t die, Mr. Tsukishima!
You’re the strongest, Mr. Tsukishima!
You can’t die!
You’re invincible, Mr. Tsukishima!
I see now, Ginjo…
I’m able to finally understand
now that you’re gone.
Maybe you already knew.
Thank you…Shishigawara.
Wha-?!
What’re you saying?!
It’s only right that I
help you, Mr. Tsukishima!
After all, I am your apprentice!
Oh!
Mr. Tsukishima, it’s morning!
What a beautiful morning!
-Thank you.
It’s a sight for sore eyes!
I wasn’t alone.
Captain!
Captain Ukitake!
Reporting, sir!
Ichigo Kurosaki
has successfully defeated Kugo
Ginjo in the World of the Living!
The captains dispatched to
observe the battle have
also safely returned.
Retrieval of Kugo Ginjo’s
body is complete.
I see…
Captain!
I’m all right…
What about Ichigo?
Sir, Ichigo Kurosaki is safe.
Thank goodness…
Riruka, time for breakfast.
It’s got Tessai’s special pickles
that he makes only for guests.
Riruka?
I’m coming in.
Thank you, Ginjo,
for inviting me to join Xcution.
Thank you, Chad,
for believing us.
Thank you, Orihime, for
crying tears for me.
And Ichigo…
I can say this with peace of mind…
Goodbye.
Forget me, okay?
Because I know that regardless
of how I say goodbye,
I know you’ll never ever,
forget us.
Reporting, sir.
Lieutenant Kuchiki of
Squad 13, who had been
clearing up affairs in
the World of the Living,
has just returned.
Why’re you reporting that to me?
Sir…because…
What?
Huh? Really?
Yes, sir.
Ichigo Kurosaki?
Understood.
What’d he come here
for all of a sudden?
Ichigo!
Hey, Renji!
How’re you doing?
Good…
Hey, wait a minute!
What brings you here?!
Well, you know…
Rukia!
What’s going on? Why is he…
He says he wants to speak
directly with Head Captain Yamamoto.
What?!
He just received permission.
Hey, just a minute!
What could it be about?
As a fellow Substitute Soul Reaper,
he must have a lot on his mind…
It wouldn’t be the least bit
strange if he were furious with us.
Do you mean he came to
return his Combat Pass?
Well, that I couldn’t say…
It’s a sticky situation, though.
What’s this?
Are you guys all here to greet me?
Not everyone.
Kurotsuchi and Ukitake aren’t here.
Anyway, come inside.
The Old Man is waiting for you.
Kensei!
You’re a captain now?!
Shut up! I said go on in.
I’m sure you didn’t
come here to chitchat.
Rukia, I think we should…
Lieutenants Abarai and Kuchiki,
have a seat at the end.
Yes, sir.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
You fought admirably.
Oh, let’s forget about that.
I didn’t come here today
to be praised for my efforts.
Then what did you come for?
Yeah.
It’s about Ginjo’s body,
that you had Renji retrieve—
I want to bring it back to the World of
the Living and give it a proper burial.
Ichigo…?
Are you crazy?
Do you realize what you’re asking?!
Hirako!
He’s right!
The man is a heinous villain who
stole the powers of many Soul Reapers
and murdered them one after another!
How could you…
That’s not what I meant!
Listen, Ichigo…
The guy messed up your
family and your friends.
Can you forgive a guy like that?
Or rather…should you?
Ichigo…
Asking to bury Ginjo is synonymous
with asking for his pardon…
That’s…
It’s not about forgiveness.
My family and friends are
back to the way they were.
I’m still alive.
And he’s…
Just a Substitute Soul Reaper.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Can I assume you’ve
said those words after
considering all the ramifications?
Screw the ramifications!
I simply want to do that for him as
a fellow Substitute Soul Reaper…
Since I am going to continue to be one.
What?!
So that’s it.
I will grant your request.
Okay, then I’ll be going.
Oh, by the way…
From now on, when a Soul Reaper
comes to Karakura Town,
at least let them know that
this is a Combat Pass.
I knew I’d find you here.
Kyoraku.
Looks like Ichigo’s going back.
What about the Combat Pass…?
He says he’s taking it with him…
Just to be sure, I asked him…
He says he trusts us, so
he’ll hold on to it.
Oh…
I see…
He’s matured, hasn’t he?
Yeah.
We just didn’t realize that…
We couldn’t help it.
When youngsters grow up,
it happens so fast that we older people
never see it coming.
Thank you…
See you around, Rukia.
I wonder how many times
I’ve heard you say that?
This isn’t going to be the last time,
so who cares how many times I say it?
You’re right.
Kurosaki!
What took you, Kurosaki?
Big Brother!
Yuzu, Brother Ichi is over there.
Hey, Ichigo!
Welcome home!
ICHIGO KUROSAKI / 17 YEARS OLD
HAIR COLOR / ORANGE
EYE COLOR / BROWN
OCCUPATION / HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
& SUBSTITUTE SOUL REAPER
See you again…