I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers
who keep a close eye
on the countless souls, good and evil,
that fill this world.
Aizen, who has brought chaos
upon the Soul Society,
has begun to set his plan in motion.
Arrancars, created by Aizen
using the Hogyoku,
a material that removes the boundaries
between Soul Reapers and Hollows,
appear in Karakura Town.
Bankai!
Ichigo prepares to battle
Ulquiorra and Yammy,
sent to Karakura Town by Aizen,
but the voice of the Hollow
within him
makes it impossible for him to fight.
Ichigo is saved by
Urahara and Yoruichi.
We'll report to Lord Aizen...
that the wannabe Soul Reaper
he has set his eyes on...is trash.
Not even worth killing.
It's all because I'm weak.
I don't know what I can do
other than apologize.
Yo! How you doing, Ichigo?
R-Renji?! Ikkaku?!
Yumichika, Rangiku...Toshiro?!
That's Captain Hitsugaya to you!
What...are you all doing here?
Orders from above.
We were ordered to enter
this world to prepare
for a full-on battle
with the Arrancars,
and join up with
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
Arran...? What's that?
Huh...? Were you fighting without knowing
who your opponents were?
Fighting?
Fool!
It's those guys who beat you up
the other day!
Rukia...
Miss Kuchiki...?!
Wait a sec...
She just came through the window?!
Well, she hasn't been in school
for a while...
Idiot... This has nothing to do
with her not coming to school!
But...who the heck is that
redhead and skinhead?
Wh-What the hell was that for, Rukia?
Huh?!
Why you--!
What's with that sorry look?!
Come with me!
I knew this would happen.
Yeah. He's always so much trouble...
Well, that look on his face would
make anyone want to do that.
You think so?
I thought that gloomy look on
his face was pretty stimulating.
What are you talking about?
There's nothing to get stimulated by!
I wasn't asking you for
your opinion, Yumichika.
Then who were you asking?!
Ikkaku?
Why me?!
Listen, you guys...
quiet down, will you?
Hey... Take a look at that...
What's wrong with Kurosaki?
Did he faint?
Oh, no... Isn't he dead?
I'm telling you,
those guys are bad news.
With that red hair and those tattoos...
Don't let them bother you, Renji.
It's just human silly talk.
A blonde with big boobs and
a silver-haired elementary student...
A bob-haired narcissist and
a baldy with a wooden sword.
Huh?
Hey...
Who just called me "baldy"?
Step up...
You'd better not let it bother you.
It's just human silly talk, after all.
Hold it right there!
I'll slice you to ribbons!
I'll help you out, Ikkaku!
Can someone take over
this job, please?
Hey, Rukia! Where do you think
you're taking me?!
Shush! Just shut up and run!
Okay! There!
Hey, what's here...?
Oh! A Hollow?!
That's right. Go get 'im!
Huh?
O-Ouch...
Damn you!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and fight him!
You call that fighting?!
What?!
Normally, you wouldn't have
any trouble at all
defeating a Hollow like this one!
Quit complaining.
You don't have to tell me what to do!
Damn you... I'm gonna...
I'm getting closer for sure.
If I keep getting closer like this...
I'll swallow you up...!
- Then...
- Stop! Stop it!
...you'll disappear!
I know...
Ever since you got beaten
by the Arrancars,
you haven't transformed into
a Soul Reaper, have you?
What are you so afraid of?!
Huh?!
They got Chad! They got Inoue!
So what?!
Are you such a sorry person
that you'd lose heart over
something like that?
Are you afraid of losing?!
Are you afraid because
you can't protect your comrades?!
Or is it...that you're afraid
of the Hollow within you?!
If you're afraid of losing,
just become stronger.
If you're afraid because
you cannot protect your comrades,
just become stronger,
and swear to them that
you will protect them.
If you're afraid of the Hollow
within you,
then become stronger
until you're able to destroy it.
Even if no one else believes in you,
just beat your chest and
shout that pledge!
That is the kind of man
you are in my heart!
You're noisy...both of you!
Here I come!
Inoue...!
K-Kuchiki?!
Hey! It's been a while!
Or...maybe not...
You've gotten over your injuries?
Yeah... Thanks to you, I'm fine.
No... I didn't do anything.
How long can you stay here
this time?
I'll tell you about that later.
Come on!
Kurosaki...
Inoue...I...
I'm sorry I was so weak!
I...
I...will get stronger.
I'll get stronger...
and next time, I swear...
I will protect you.
Thank goodness...
He's back to his usual self.
Thank you... Kurosaki.
Thank you, Kuchiki...
Welcome back!
I'm telling you, it's the truth!
If you mix ginger ale and
lactic acid soda,
two parts to one,
at that beverage bar...
It's amazing!
It'll taste like hair tonic!
Isn't that amazing?!
Oh? Isn't that amazing?
Just leave it to you, Mr. Asano.
It's probably your tongue...
What?! Why're you suddenly
so formal?
Was I so irritating that you wanted
to put some distance between us?
Hey...Mizuiro! Don't ignore me...
Our classroom seems
a little noisy.
Huh? Yeah, you're right!
Okay! I'll go and scout the area!
Hey! Who in the world is
stirring things up without me?
Huh?
Huh? What the heck are
you looking at?!
I'll grind you up, make meatballs,
fry you crisp
into a minced fish and
eat you up! Damn you!
Quit it will you, Baldy?
Huh? What do you think
you're doing, Matsumoto?!
Slapping my head like that...
Shut up! If you keep it up,
I'm going to tell Yachiru.
Uh...come on...listen...
Don't do that, will you?
You should have listened
to me to begin with!
The rest of you,
don't dawdle, will you?
It's time we all left,
you blockheads!
You're not including me when
you say "blockheads," are you?
Oh, of course not...
You're not one of them, Captain.
Lately, Captain, your persecution complex
has been showing.
That's a naughty uniform, Sister!
Hey...is this guy okay?
Never mind him!
Now, time to withdraw!
If you lie around like that,
you look like a fixture, Mr. Asano.
You're still being formal...
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Sister...!
You haven't changed, have you, Kon?
This stomping foot
hasn't changed, either.
This is, without a doubt, Sister...
I...I am so happy!
Quit fooling around.
Hurry up and go on in, will you?
This little room hasn't changed, either.
Quit it, will you?
Leave off the "little."
Don't compare this with
Byakuya's place!
Sorry... It just slipped out.
Yeah, right...
Hey! Don't sit on my bed!
Well, why not?
Gee, you're stingy.
Shut up!
You can just sit on the floor, idiot!
- Boy, you're so stingy...
- What's going on?
I wondered why no one
was downstairs.
What are you two doing?
Shh! This is terrible!
Ichigo's brought a girl home!
He brought a girl home
back when he was in
middle school too, remember?
Like Tatsuki...
She's not like Tatsuki!
She's more...uh...girlie!
Tatsuki's gotten more curves since
she entered high school.
R-Really?!
Don't you start slobbering, Stupid Dad!
Anyway, as long as he doesn't bring
home someone at Orihime's level,
I won't be surprised.
Humph! Karin!
That's right! There's no way
Ichigo would be so popular.
Quit all the racket, you guys!
See, he got mad!
I'm sorry!
Humph!
Getting all excited at my expense...
Your family's just as funny as ever.
Shut up!
Never mind that. Just tell me
what the heck an Arrancar is...
Okay...
Why are we being targeted?!
Hold it!
Huh? That voice?! Renji?!
Where are you?
If you want to know about that,
we'll tell you!
Hey!
Yo, Ichigo! Long time no see...
well, maybe not.
You guys... What have you done
to my room light? Huh?!
I thought you'd see the light!
What's that...?
Now, don't get all serious like that.
Let's try to enjoy all this, shall we?
That uniform is
a dangerous weapon, Sister!
Is that the latest fad?
No, he's always like this.
INTERNAL MEDICINE / PEDIATRICS
KUROSAKI CLINIC
The Arrancars are a group of Hollows
that have removed their masks,
and have gained the powers
of both Hollows and Soul Reapers.
Until recently,
they were few and imperfect
but now that Aizen, with his Hogyoku,
has come into contact with them,
mature Arrancar have been born.
That's what those two
were the other day.
You're with us so far?
Yeah, I understand...
If not for the sketchbook
I'd understand it better.
In the beginning,
Soul Society planned to take
a wait-and-see attitude
until Aizen decided to take matters
into his own hands.
On our side,
three of our captains pulled out
and went over to the enemy.
Besides, things were in an uproar
due to that Bount incident.
But meanwhile, the Arrancars were
completed quicker than we expected
and they were sent into this world,
so we couldn't sit back any longer.
And that's when
we were quickly selected.
Who made the selections?
General Captain Yamamoto.
The Central 46 has been vacant
since Aizen eliminated the leaders.
During its vacancy,
the General Captain has
the decision-making authority.
So, the one who knows you best,
Rukia, was chosen...
No! I was chosen for my abilities!
And out of the combatants
they could mobilize,
I was selected for being
the closest to Rukia.
Then I was told to choose
those other than the captains
that I trusted most,
so I asked Ikkaku to accompany me.
Then Yumichika said
he had to come along and
Rangiku, who heard the uproar,
said she wanted to come
because it sounded interesting.
Rangiku wouldn't be swayed,
so Captain Hitsugaya was forced
to come along to supervise.
And so we're here.
Is this a picnic?!
Anyway... Aizen's definitely got
his eye on you, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Aha! It's Captain Hitsugaya,
the only one who refused to go up
into the ceiling with us!
Were you waiting up on
the roof all this time?
That's not good!
You know how you stand out like
a silver-haired elementary student.
Shut up!
It's true that an Arrancar is born
when the mask is removed
from a Hollow.
But removing the mask of
your run-of-the-mill Hollow
wouldn't get you much
of anything.
If you're serious about declaring war
on Soul Society
it'll naturally be something greater
than the Menos.
Greater than the Menos?
What? That sounds like you're saying
there are Hollows stronger
than the Menos.
Yeah... Well, more precisely,
there are three classes within
the Menos.
The first is the "Gillian,"
the lowest class within the Menos,
and they are many.
Their characteristic is that
they all look the same.
The Hollow you banished
in this world,
soon after you gained the power
of a Soul Reaper was of this kind.
I guess you could call them
the small fry.
That one...was a small fry?
They're huge,
but their movements are sluggish
and they are no more intelligent
than beasts.
It doesn't take much for
a captain to kill one.
The problem begins with
the next level.
The second class is the "Adjuchas."
They're somewhat smaller
than the Gillians,
and there are fewer of them,
but they are highly intelligent and
much better fighters than the Gillians.
They control the large numbers
of Gillians.
And the third are the Vasto Lordes.
They are the top class within
the Menos.
They are equal to humans in size.
There are said to be only a few of them
within Hueco Mundo, but...
I'll give it to you straight.
These Vasto Lordes are stronger
than our Soul Reaper captains!
The power gained by the Menos
by turning into Arrancars is
an unknown quantity.
But now that three of our captains
have defected to lead the Menos,
this is a fact...
If Aizen now has more than
ten of these Vasto Lordes
under his control...
It'll be the end of Soul Society.
We have returned...Lord Aizen.
Welcome back... Ulquiorra... Yammy...
Now, tell me of your achievements
in front of your 20 brothers.
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
In the next episode,
I will hold a dinner show at my palace
in Hueco Mundo.
You can look forward to
Ulquiorra's report
on the World of the Living.
I am at your service, Lord Aizen.
Uh... Where will it be held?
That is a secret.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Tetsuzaemon...for a long time now...
I haven't received any orders to
go to the World of the Living...
I wonder why...
Well...
it takes a very serious situation
to warrant sending a captain.
I have even prepared a gigai
so that I can go to the World of
the Living at any time.
Captain Komamura's gigai...?!
I wonder why...
Well...