Don’t think you can stop me
with your current power!
What do you mean?
Look at this world!
This world of yours used to be filled
with skyscrapers, full of hope!
Now it has sunken low to look like
the small town that’s dear to you!
The rain that continued to fall
on this world has subsided,
but in its place, everything
has sunk into this ocean!
This all happened, Ichigo, because you
lost hope and stopped moving forward!
I will drag out the root of your
despair right here and now!
It’s been a long time, Ichigo.
What’s with that look?
Don’t you recognize me?
Y-You?
Why?!
You were supposed to be gone
after our last encounter!
Did you forget?
I warned you:
If you really want to
control my power,
then be sure not to die
before the next time I appear!
Damn it.
I thought I crushed you
for good back then.
Well, too bad for you.
It’s even pitiful.
Why do you look like that,
wearing that weird mask?
That’s right…
This is your first time
seeing this form.
This is how you looked when
you defeated Ulquiorra Shifar.
I looked…like that?
That’s right.
This is the form you feared.
You feared this form wherein your destructive
impulses crushed your soul.
It made you unable to complete
a full Hollowfication.
So…
So what do you want
me to do then?!
Am I supposed to fight that
guy now and defeat him?!
Wrong.
He is not the opponent
you will fight.
It’s both of us.
As one.
What?
What’s…going on?!
We were one…
to begin with.
Both of us…
are your power.
Here I come, Ichigo!
Arisawa!
Impressive.
You’re this close to me, yet you are
still able to maintain your existence.
Who…are you?
Run, Asano!
Get going!
Or is there something
you can do here?!
It’s no use. I can’t
move my body.
What should I do?
It’s no use.
Michiru… I should put her down.
There’s not enough time anymore.
You seem to be in distress, girl.
At times like this, you
should call for a hero.
Spirits are
always with you!
Thank you for waiting, viewers!
Your Don Kanonji!
My Don Kanonji!
Everyone’s Don Kanonji is back!
I…have…returned!
And who might you be?
You don’t know me?
Such an ignorant boy!
Don’t watch much television, do you?
Fine! Then I shall
tell you my name.
I am the one and the only…
What’d you come here for,
Don Kanonji?
No!
I was just about to do my
own special introduction!
How cruel can you be, girl?
So cruel!
For your own good, go on home.
There’s nothing you can do here.
I believe
you're at the limit of withstanding
my Spiritual Pressure.
Or rather…I should compliment
you for withstanding it this long.
Listen to me! Run
away right now!
There’s nothing you can do!
Run?
Is that something to
say to this hero?
Ignorant girl.
I’ll have you know that
children do not call a hero
that runs away a “hero”!
Cannon Ball!
Super Spirit Cane…
Kanonji Buster!
Stop it.
If a mere human like you touches me,
you will cease to exist.
Kanonji!
I made it in time.
Don’t think you can stop me
with your current power!
If you don’t take this seriously,
you’ll die.
He’s not bluffing!
Is he really trying to kill me?!
Are you done?
Not so fast.
Done? Hardly.
No matter how many times I get knocked
down, I’ll keep getting up
until you tell me what the
Final Getsugatensho is!
Interesting.
Do you really think I’ll teach you
with such half-hearted resolve?!
If you don’t want to teach me,
then I’ll just have to
force it out of you!
Looks like you’ve finally decided
to fight seriously.
But you won’t even be able to
land a single blow against me.
Take this!
I made it in time.
Aizen…
Gin…
Rangiku.
Who…
Who are you, girl?!
It’s dangerous!
This is no place for
a girl like you to be!
Civilians should stay back!
Run.
I’ll stop them, so you guys
get out of here this instant!
Wh-What are you talking
about, girl?
I, Don…
Shut up already!
Stop jabbering and carry those
kids on your back and run!
Do you want me to rip off that
mustache, burn your hat and
grind those weird shades into your face
until no one will recognize you?!
R-Roger that!
I’ll leave this place to you, girl!
But!
If you find yourself in
danger, call a hero!
Call out, “Save me! Don…”
Ouch!
No! That didn’t hurt!!
Farewell!
Who could she be?
Is she a friend of Ichigo’s?
Their kimonos look similar.
She’s beautiful.
That Ichigo.
He never told me he had
such a beautiful friend.
By “made it in time,” were you referring
to saving those humans?
Or were you referring to me destroying
Karakura Town and creating the Ouken?
Well, either way,
you were wrong.
What’s the matter? Do you
find it hard to talk to me?
Captain Aizen.
Please forgive my former acquaintance.
I’ll take her away.
I don’t mind. I have time.
You’re welcome to talk at
length with her there.
But we would be in your way.
Not at all.
My, my…
As always, he is such
an amusing child.
You arched your body
at the last second.
A useless effort.
He’s strong.
His speed is incredible!
I had no time to block it
with my Zanpakuto.
So now you realize the difference
in our strength.
“Force it out of me”?
Don’t make me laugh!
You’re only running away!
Shut up!
I have to get it out of you
no matter what it takes!
How pathetic!
What?!
Ichigo!
Be gone from this world of yours!
Let go of me!
You’re staggering.
Why’d you come?
I lost track of your
Spiritual Pressure,
so I took the Senkaimon
to get the jump on you.
After all, I had a better grasp of where the
real Karakura Town was transported!
I didn’t ask how you got here.
I want to know why you came
here in your shaky condition.
Isn’t it obvious?
Because you’re here.
Finally,
I can ask you directly.
Why did you decide to
work under Aizen?
Why?
Why did you betray Kira,
who trusted you?!
Are you seriously
asking me that?
You say I betrayed him
in spite of his trust?
Are you really talking
about Izuru here?
Man, why did you have
to come here, anyway?
You know, Rangiku…
You’re a nuisance.
Damn…
Is he trying to kick me
out of this world?!
I don’t have the
time for this!
Getsugatensho!
So you’ve come back.
Sorry.
But you know I don’t
give up easily.
You’ll have to deal with
me a little longer!
A little longer, you say?
Yeah!
I can’t afford to spend any
more time here than that!
I’m coming at you
with all I’ve got!
What changed?
Can’t tell.
But…
Everyone is waiting for me!
Kanonji, I'm fine.
I can walk.
No. You mustn’t overexert yourself, girl.
I said...
I’m fine!
Ouch!
Why won’t you listen the
first time I tell you?!
Oh… Strong hit.
Arisawa!
Asano!
I told you to get away.
Where did you get that sword?
Mr. Afro was lying collapsed over
that way, so I borrowed his sword!
I’ve never done kendo
or anything of the sort,
but I figure it’s better
than having nothing!
Who’s Mr. Afro?
I’ll explain later.
Anyway, let’s get going!
Where’s Chizuru? And Kojima?!
Didn’t you go looking for them?!
I found Mizuiro!
He’s over there!
Honsho’s with him too!
Now’s not the time for questions!
We have to get away from here!
I can feel that guy’s presence.
He’s closing in on us!
They’re waiting for you?
However, that’s none of my concern.
Yeah, that may be so. You did say…
The fate of what you
want to protect
is none of my concern.
What you want to protect is
not what I want to protect.
But the thing is…
What I want to protect
hasn’t changed.
It may be different from yours,
but that’s not the issue!
I… I will protect what
I want to protect!
And that’s what Getsugatensho is for?
That’s right.
What?!
His sword… Something’s different.
One question, Ichigo.
You said earlier that no matter how many times
you get knocked down, you’ll keep getting up.
I did. What of it?
All right.
Then let me test you!
Test what?!
Not yet?
Ichigo!
Arisawa! We have to run, quickly!
But where can we run?
He’ll catch us right away!
No…
You have a plan?
To escape without a plan…
That is where love leads to.
As the two continue their escape,
they soon fall in love with each…
Die.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
I am Don Kanonji!
A hero who fights evil!
That is when a mysterious
girl appeared before me.
Idolizing me, the girl gained powers,
and is now head over heels for me!
And so, she seduces me.
Quit telling them lies!
Oh, girl! Stop, girl!