Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
It seems they made it!
How are we going to get away?
We're going to do this!
Heh, so that's it…
Let's go!
Here’s an added bonus!
What's wrong?
Kurosaki…
What are you doing?!
Run away quickly!
Rain?
C-Could it be--?!
What's wrong?
I just realized something terrible!
Kon! Calm down!
What's wrong?!
There’s a possibility that among us…
among us…!
There's a rain man!
Now's not the time to confuse us
with superstitions!
I'm not the rain man!
Don't pay attention to that story!
You're persistent!
Th-That!
A-Again?!
Sure is a nice rain.
The perfect conditions!
That's why we told you…
You can't run away from water…
Hey, lackeys!
Huh?
Why didn't you notice this earlier?!
It's no good…
That doll is difficult to track
while it's combined with water…
Really. What a troublesome opponent…
Why you…!
Don't you think it's about time
we get them…Ban?
I think so, Ho.
Here we go!
They combined!
And they’re becoming bigger…
Here it comes!
Inoue! Chad!
Take Ishida and run away!
There.
Roar! Zabimaru!
It came back!
I guess it really wasn't any good.
Sha! Red Flame Cannon!
Did that get’em?!
It's no good!
Damn!
Kurosaki!
Ichigo! Ren--!
No!
Chad! Inoue! Run away!
Ichigo!
Stop already!
That's enough! Just leave me!
If you have the time to complain,
then just go!
We can't allow everyone
to be caught!
Kurosaki!
Inoue, let's go.
Huh?
Ichigo is all right.
Let's protect Ishida!
That seems to be
a valuable marionette…
It's just old.
I don't think it has any value…
Kariya is worried.
Don't you think you should return?
I don't follow anyone's orders.
Even if it's an order from
the man you love?
Even love grows old…
It definitely grows old,
especially if you think
you're being controlled.
It appears Kariya…
is making his move soon…
I don't care.
Bounts are self-reliant.
Just let him do what he wants…
Why is Kariya so soft on you?
You seem so slow to me…
You're much more of
a boy than you look.
The world doesn't move
on just momentum.
Unnecessary ambition will destroy you…
No comment.
Really?!
I’m off for the night!
Starting tomorrow,
I’ll be working hard!
That storeowner sure was kind
to let me work here.
He even let me have
the remaining packed lunches.
By the way, Ganju…
Huh?
Why'd you come here?
Big Sis felt a strange presence
so she told me to investigate…
Is that so?
Then that's the same as me.
Captain Unohana also ordered me…
We both have it rough, don't we?!
Yeah…
Hey, Hana…
Yes…
This Spiritual Pressure…
Could it be?!
Red Flame Cannon!
Ghoul!
Günter!
Close!
What should we do?
At this rate, the Quincy will get away.
You're right.
We're saved!
What's going on? It suddenly cracked!
That's because those twin Bounts left!
That way!
They went in Ishida's direction!
What?!
Sado, where are we going?
At any rate, it's bad
if we're in this rain…
Let's go to the usual factory.
If we go there,
Ichigo and the others should realize
and follow us.
What's wrong?
They're coming!
Huh?!
Oh no! They got ahead of us!
How terrible!
Ishida!
Santenkesshun!
I reject!
Inoue!
You can't run away.
That's right, there's no escape.
Kurodo! Noba!
Take care of Ishida!
Huh?! Just the two of us?
We always have a chance.
But not you.
Not in this rain…
Go!
It's useless!
It'll turn back to normal,
no matter how many times you try!
Ban! We can't separate!
Oh!
Oh?!
Ban!
Sado! Now!
Right!
Let's go!
But what happened all of a sudden?
I don't know.
Those twin brats…
What's wrong?
They never attacked separately…
Come to think of it…
It feels as if…
they control that doll by
combining their powers…
They're using that
resonance phenomenon
which twins are said to have, huh?
That's why they can combine
their dolls into one…
Together, they're complete.
If that's the case…
Is that Koga?
It's dark.
I can read. This is fine…
You're the same as always, I see.
Dry your clothes. You'll catch a cold…
I'll pour you some tea
at ten o'clock.
Don’t trouble yourself.
By the way, what happened
to everyone else?
You're the first one…
A place with no water?
This place is leaking!
Sorry…
It's better than outside.
Sado.
Hmm?
Ishida has a fever…
This is bad…
Everyone… Just leave me here…
No way!
Thanks for your concern, but…
I don't want to be a burden
on you any longer!
Ishida.
There's a limit to how pathetic
I can get!
Then come with us!
We'll make you even
if you don't want us to…
Ishida!
We've got…
a Quincy!
Whoa!
You can't use that.
Ishida!
Is it all right?
Don't you care what happens
to this Quincy?
Chad!
Inoue!
Kurosaki!
Ishida!
We're too late!
Let go of Ishida!
Why? Are you stupid?!
Besides…
you should run away quickly if
you care for your lives.
What did you say?!
We still haven't shown you
Ghoul and Günter's true abilities,
have we?
Ghoul and Günter tell us
they want to kill you.
What's this?
I can't breathe…
Oh…Sister!
This is terrible!
Hey! What are you doing?!
We can go
anywhere there's water!
A human body is 70% water, isn't it?
Ghoul! Günter!
Tear their bodies…
Into pieces from the inside!
Ichigo!
Kon! Do something!
Don't say unreasonable things like that!
There's nothing I can do!
What should we do?!
Let's go!
Where?
Let's try!
Try what?!
It should be over soon.
If we get serious…
Huh?! Ban!
Ho! What's going on?
Ichigo!
Ban!
Sister!
Ban! Ban!
Ho!
Where are you?!
Where'd you go?!
All right, this is good!
Keep it up!
Can you take them further away? Noba!
This is the best I can do…
Just a little further!
You!
All right, we're back.
You saved us, Noba…
They're one person in two…
They were controlling two dolls by
sharing their thoughts via resonance.
Conversely, if one loses consciousness,
they can't resonate…
So neither one can control their dolls.
Isn't that right, Noba?!
That's right!
Ban! Ban!
Ban! Wake up! Please wake up!
Now's our chance!
You've lost! Give up!
What?
I can do this! I can!
I can do this by myself!
Zeige dih Ghoul!
Shakkaho! Red Flame Cannon!
Do it, Ghoul!
Here it comes!
It's useless!
We don't have enough firepower!
Shakkaho!
Where are you aiming?!
I can do this by myself!
Damn!
It's around here.
Let's go, Hana!
Yes!
Huh?!
Seppa!
Ghoul!
This technique!
Could it be?!
Ah! There you are.
I thought you were here!
Looks like it.
Huh?! You!
Hey! Ichigo, it's been a while!
Ganju!
It's been a while.
Hanataro?!
Why are you both here?!
That doesn't matter!
Besides that,
did you say that you didn't
have enough firepower?
Firepower is a Shiba family patent!
Fireworks, huh?!
That's it, Ganju!
Hit an extra large one
against that thing!
All right! I want to eat that
packed lunch I got from the boss!
Ghoul! What are you doing?! Go!
1B	01:45:23:11	01:45:24:06	Number One
Here I go!
Move, Ghoul!
Ta…ma…ya!
You idiot! It went out!
Well, just watch.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Wh-What's this?!
What's going on?!
They've turned to dust!
Even though they looked like children,
they were probably past
their limits as living beings…
Losing their dolls may
have pushed them past that point…
Huh?
What's wrong, Inoue?
Where's Ishida--?
Master Kariya, welcome back.
Yes, good work as usual.
Not at all.
You suck up!
Udagawa, where are Ho and Ban?
It seems that they were defeated.
Their presence has disappeared.
I see…
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Ishida, that bastard!
Where did he disappear to?!
Even if he's lost his Quincy powers,
he still has the important job
of doing maintenance on us.
We've got to save him.
Is that all I'm good for?
Don't worry.
I don't have enough clothes
to wear in the human world.
I won't go back!
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
H-Hisagi… I-It's painful…
Kira… I may not be able
to go on any longer…
If I die…
take care of my subordinates…
No… Hisagi, get a hold of yourself…
Their livers are weak.
They drink too much sake!
Tune in again!