Orihime has been abducted
by the Arrancars.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo,
the world of the Hollows.
They crush the Arrancars
standing in their way and
finally make their way to Las Noches,
Aizen's headquarters.
Let's go, Renji!
Don't boss me around, idiot!
Meanwhile, Aizen shows Orihime
the Hogyoku as proof of his trust in her.
Orihime secretly
makes a decision.
Thank you for coming
to save me Kurosaki.
But I know what
I have to do here.
It's probably something
that only I can do.
I have to use my power to
return the Hogyoku
back to the state it was in
before it existed!
Awaiting Ichigo and his friends
in Las Noches
was a path that split five ways
and disturbing Spiritual Pressures.
They follow Rukia's suggestion that
they each take separate routes.
We're going into battle now!
Believe…that our blades
cannot be broken!
Believe…that our hearts
will not yield!
Even if we lose our way,
our iron will is one!
Vow…that even if the earth splits,
we will come back to this place alive!
Ichigo…
Ichigo!
N-Nel?!
Why'd you come?! Leave!
Nel wanted to see you, Ichigo!
Listen to me!
Crap!
All right, come on!
Catch and release!
Super acceleration.
Nel wanted to see you, Ichigo!
Nel wanted to see you!
Wh-Why you…
Ichigo!
Jeez… I guess it can't be helped.
Don't cry…
Ichigo!
What happened to
everyone else?
Oh, we left Bawabawa outside!
He can't live without eating sand!
I didn't mean him.
You know…
Don what's-his-name…
DON WHAT'S-HIS-NAME
No, not that guy.
Who is that?
I mean the guys that
were with you.
Oh! Dondochakka and Pesche
are right behind Nel.
They're gone!
They've gone missing!
Dondochakka and Pesche
have gone missing!
This is terrible!
What should Nel do?!
– Where'd they go?! Where?!
– No…
– Where?!
– If anything,
– They're gone!
– you're the one who's gone missing.
Ichigo, what's wrong?
Be quiet!
Come out!
I said, whoever's hiding there,
come out!
Crap!
You're not getting away!
Who's trying to get away?!
Oh!
Umm… Hey… Are you all right?
Tada!
Tada…
Hey!
Hey, wait!
What's with that reaction?!
Well come on…
Shut up…
Stop repeating yourself.
You've just seen
my magnificent entrance!
Magnificent?
You slipped just now.
You're pretending
to be so calm!
I'm not pretending…
I'm completely calm.
Anyway, at least make that little one
by your side look at me!
Oh well…
That's the difference between
our senses of style.
It has nothing to do with you,
who’s about to be defeated.
Now prepare yourself,
Soul Reaper!
Arrancar Ciento Tres!
I, Dordoni, will crush you here!
Is that a kind of boiled celery?
No, it's not! What am I,
a side-dish that goes well with rice?!
Anyway, you only got
the “C” part right!
Ciento Tres! One hundred three!
I'm Arrancar Number 103!
One hundred three?
That's a big number.
Yeah.
Didn't you say that those with numbers
have two-digit numbers?
Yes… They're supposed to
be two digits.
I've never heard of three digits.
Hey! What are you
whispering about?!
Hey! What's with
those pitying glances?!
You seem kind of…really weak…
What?!
Just see if I'm weak or not!
Don't regret it afterwards, niño.
Be amazed at
my physical prowess!
What the…?!
Those are some
strange movements!
Why you…
Crap! What are you, an octopus?!
What's wrong, niño?!
You aren't hitting me at all!
It's ridiculous for you to take on
Lord Aizen with that level of skill!
Shut up!
Useless, useless, useless!
Whoa!
Serves you right!
Shut up!
You were punished for
laughing at others!
Nel?
Hey, are you all right, Nel?
Just kidding!
It just hit Nel’s mask.
It doesn't hurt at all!
Wh-Why you…
Not bad, niño.
But you've shown me
your moves.
With that level of skill, you can't…
You bastard!
I was really worried about you!
It's your fault for
making fun of others!
Why is it my fault?!
Listen to me!
Oh! You're still alive?
He's excessively energetic.
Shut up! This is nothing to me!
Say, could you just end this
and let me pass?
We're in a hurry.
I won't let you!
Anyway, your attacks
haven't even hit me!
So why the superior attitude?!
Don't get cocky!
Oh well…
This time, I'll get serious!
What's this?
You're spying on them?
That's not a very good hobby,
Mr. Tosen.
How unexpected…
You also came here because you were
curious about their actions, too.
Didn't you, Ichimaru?
Come on… It was a joke.
Don't give me such a scary look.
Tosen, do something about him.
Wonderweiss!
That troublesome kid has
taken quite a liking to you.
Those who are pure
are drawn together.
I still can't figure out exactly
in what regard he's pure, though.
I see…
No wonder he isn't friendly to me.
Any normal person
would be wary of you.
Anyway, look.
They split up.
Oh, you're right.
They'll have a lower chance
of success if they split up.
Do they know what
level of skill they are?
Yeah.
Furthermore, they're passing
through an interesting place.
Oh… The Lair of the Tres Cifras.
Ichigo!
You're kidding, right?
Tres?
Yes.
You just came here,
so you probably don't know.
I'll tell you.
Getsugatensho!
Tres Cifras…
meaning triple-digit numbers,
are a sign that they were demoted.
Those who have been
stripped of their rank.
In other words,
all those who have
triple digit numbers
are Privaron Espada.
My, my…
Didn't your mama ever teach you…
not to judge people by
their appearances, niño?
We're known as
the Privaron Espada.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
Privaron Espada…
It means “Fallen Espada.”
Yes…
In other words…
All those who have triple-digit numbers,
including me, were once Espada.
Our skills are on par
with the Espada.
Do you understand
my strength now, niño?
Wha--?
What is this power?
Why you…
What's wrong?!
He got faster?!
Wait up!
What?!
You didn't think that was
my true power, did you?
Wh-Why you…
There's no need to
check your footing.
Your reactions are slow.
Your defense is weak.
You can't even handle
a change in footing.
I can't do this!
It's as if I'm fighting a baby! Eh?!
Your Bankai…
Use it, niño.
I won't lie to you…
In your current state, you won't be
able to defeat me no matter what you do.
I don't want to.
Why?
The Privaron Espada
aren't Espada, right?
That's right…
Then even more so!
We need to defeat
all of the Espada!
I can't be using my Bankai against
guys who aren't even Espada!
That’s why I'm going to defeat you
without using my Bankai!
I see.
I understand your feelings, niño.
Then let me tell you one thing…
Don't underestimate me.
Whirl! Giralda!
Crap!
He can release his zanpakuto
without even drawing it?!
What are you doing?
Take a stance.
Wha--?
Here I go.
Giralda!
I'm still not finished.
You…bastard!
Getsugatensho!
Ichigo… Ichigo!
Is that all you've got, niño?!
Ichigo's going to die?
Pre…view…
Hmm…
I guess Wonderweiss can't
do this by himself.
You didn't need to test him
to know that.
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
PRIVARON ESPADA = FALLEN ESPADA
The Privaron Espada are those who
have been removed from the Espada.
Their number is also dropped
from a single digit to a triple digit.
Why did I have to be
removed from the Espada?
I told you that you were shifted out
because you were too weak.
No I'm not!
There's got to be some high-level
political judgment at work!
Captain Aizen probably
hated you
because your facial features
are too intense.
Niños just don't understand!