The body... is gone?
I don't have time to worry about that.
She watched us from here...
I have to get rid of them.
Please... Don't get in my way.
Out of my way.
Now I can get through.
Rachel, what a terrible thing you've done!
Cutting down all those
suffering, wailing people,
just because they were "in your way"...
Without the slightest
change in your expression.
So as long as Zack can kill you later,
the end justifies the means?
You truly are a sinful girl, Rachel.
Was that...
I see you've succeeded in
switching the power on.
Yes.
By what means did you activate
the switch to this floor?
Were there no pursuers that blocked your path?
There were... but I shot them all.
Why did you do that?
They were in my way.
I see.
Well, then, on to the next floor.
They're dried up.
The switch for this floor is in the
water temperature control room.
Why do I have to do this?
So that I can ascertain what
sort of person you are.
I have to go down and find
that medicine quickly.
You have been brought up
as a subject of debate.
Me?
Yes.
It's because you are irregular.
Irregular?
What is he trying to find out about me?
Whatever it is, it makes no difference.
The body is gone...
Come with me.
What an awful mess.
Eddie was a kind child.
He must have been extremely angry
at having his graveyard destroyed.
Because of his kindness, perhaps,
he always ended up with the
short end of the stick.
But even more pitiable are those
who were resting in these graves.
They had found peace through
Eddie's compassion,
and should have moved on to the
next life, but it was not to be.
Again...
Why do I keep seeing people
who should be dead?
The control room is beyond.
Now, go.
A stuffed hand that moves?
Is it a toy?
Gross.
Help... Help... Help...
How annoying.
Is she a lost sheep... or a demon?
This place is exclusive for my things
I saw that, Rachel!
I saw you stomping on all
those screaming hands!
Another one...
That was cruel. So cruel.
Did you really feel nothing as you
listened to their mournful cries, Rachel?
You didn't consider being kind to them?
You didn't try to think of
what would make them happy?
I guess all you think about is yourself.
You don't even see any
other kind of happiness.
That's why everyone you know...
...and Zack, too... will end
their lives suffering.
End their lives suffering...
Zack, too?
No. I have to hurry back.
I hit the switch.
Yes, so I see.
And by what means did you activate
the switch to this floor?
I opened the refrigerator
in the control room.
Did no one try to get in your way?
There were some moving stuffed hands.
But I crushed them.
Did they not cry out when you did?
No.
What makes you say so?
Because...
They were stuffed.
Are you certain they
appeared that way to you?
Very well, then.
If they appeared that way, it must be tru—
Can we just hurry up and
go to the next floor now?
Very well.
Here we are.
This is where you want to be, yes?
Yes.
Danny was very fastidious, as well
as methodical and conscientious.
He could master any task, one after another.
I'm sure he kept his medicine
shelves well-organized, too.
However...
His fastidiousness had
recently grown excessive—
Excuse me.
What is it?
There's something I need
to get from Zack's floor.
That will not be a problem.
Once you find the medicine,
come to the elevator that goes down.
Okay.
I've been through this floor before...
But something's always felt off about it.
So you're gonna help me get out of here.
Once we get out, you might make
a better face for me, right?
When you do...
I'll kill you.
This is where I made that promise with Zack.
That's right.
Even if the things I see look different,
our promise is...
What was that?
I have to find that medicine, fast.
Doctor Danny's body is gone, too.
I have to find the medicine.
No medicine?
It's all gone.
None here, either.
What's the matter?
You seem to be in a rush.
I have to get back to Zack.
Did you find the medicine?
It's gone.
Gone?
You said there was medicine on this floor,
but there wasn't.
It seems as though you doubt me.
Don't make such a sullen face.
I don't understand why there's no
medicine on this floor, either.
I can, however, hypothesize.
Are you not the reason yourself,
Rachel Gardner?
Have you never thought
that all these unfortunate
occurrences are your own doing?
I don't know anything about that.
But I have to get to Zack now.
Do you not want to go down to the next floor?
You might at least find
bandages on Zack's floor.
What will you do?
I'll go down.
Very well.
I will be useful to you,
Zack.
Sorry about that. Are you okay?
Y-You should hurry back home now...
I have no home to go back to.
Tch.
Is someone in there?
Shut up.
A child?
Are you alone?
Are your mother and father with you?
Unfortunately, I'm blind, so I can't tell.
Are you hungry?
What were you doing out there?
Ah, it doesn't matter.
I'm sure you have a reason.
If you have nowhere to go, you can
stay here as long as you like.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Because I'm lonely.
Huh?
If you don't want to be here,
you can leave whenever you want.
I never said I didn't want to.
What is this weird chill I feel?
This is the easiest way to take care of it.
Killing the old man won't
make this chill go away.
Hic... Damn...
Whoopsie!
This didn't help.
That chill still isn't going away.
Can't use this anymore.
Where were you?
Blood?
I killed a guy.
I wanted to kill someone,
so I went and killed someone.
I see.
And what do you want to do now?
You must be tired.
Get some sleep.
Where'd he go?
I can't read, you idiot.
The old bastard's taking forever.
Seriously?
You're kidding...
Really?
How awful...
What a cruel thing to do.
This was all the old geezer had on him.
It's chump change.
Man, we killed him for nothing.
The hell are you lookin' at?
Huh?!
You look pretty happy.
It's happy-looking people like
you that make monsters.
What the hell? Talk about
a creepy little brat.
And what do you want to do now?
I wanna destroy happy people
who are laughing like jackasses,
so they fall into despair!
Yeah... I'm a monster.
Why'd you have to get yourself killed?
Ah...
You're alive.
And so weak...
Shall I put you out of your misery,
Zack?