Sosuke Aizen, the man who revolted
against the Soul Society
and brought the inhabitants
of Hueco Mundo under his control.
His true goal is to create the royal key
that opens the portal to
the Royal Palace of the Soul Society
known as the "Ouken."
Aizen is attempting to
accomplish this in Karakura Town.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads and
Ichigo Kurosaki learn of his intent,
and anticipate a winter showdown.
They begin training to gain the strength
necessary to confront the Espada.
However, at the same time…
Aizen realizes
Orihime Inoue's true power
is to reject all forms
of phenomenon,
a power capable of overstepping
the limitations set by God.
He then orders Ulquiorra to kidnap
Orihime from the World of the Living.
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Renji,
and Rukia break into Las Noches,
determined to rescue Orihime.
But what awaited them was a battle
that far exceeded their expectations.
I'm going to go at full strength!
Bankai!
Bankai, huh?
Impossible…
My, my… I couldn't even stop it
with two hands.
I'm a little surprised.
Was that your best?
How unfortunate.
Give up.
Who's going to give up?
You're the leader of
the Espada, aren't you?
That means that if I defeat you,
this battle is pretty much won!
I see…
That's unfortunate.
Four?!
Yes… Quatro Espada, Ulquiorra Shifar.
Of the Espada,
my strength ranks…
Fourth.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you do defeat me,
there are three Espada above me.
You can try a thousand times.
You will not be victorious.
This is it.
If you can still move in that condition,
leave this place immediately.
If you can't move, then die there.
Heal him.
That's good.
I've been waiting for this moment!
Grind… Pantera!
What's this?! Sound pressure?!
All this power, just from yelling.
Damn it!
Is that the best you can do,
Ichigo Kurosaki?!
It's over, Kurosaki.
Don't die…
Don't die, Kurosaki!
You don't have to win.
You don't have to try.
Just don't get hurt anymore.
Desgarrón.
It's my strongest technique.
It's over, Kurosaki!
You make me sick.
You're going to lose to me!
You're all cowards.
Fine… I'll eat you all.
Become my flesh and blood
and watch what happens.
I…
I am the king!
You're not the only one
who wants to win.
I'm going to defeat you!
I'm going to defeat Ulquiorra!
I'm going to defeat Aizen!
Rukia!
Chad!
Ishida!
Renji!
And Inoue!
I'm going to bring them all back!
I can't lose to you, Grimmjow!
Damn…
K-Kuro—
Wounds…
Are you wounded?
Inoue?
I'm glad that you're not hurt.
Well, you know me.
I was born robust.
Even when I was small,
I never caught colds.
Huh?
H-Hey Kurosaki!
What are you doing?!
What do you mean?
We're going down.
In this rubble,
it'll be way easier to carry you
than look for stairs.
B-But…
What is it?
Something bothering you?
I-I'm heavy.
Huh? Don't worry.
You're not as heavy
as I expected.
W-Why you…
That's not how you should
speak to a lady!
There are certain ways to
tell a lady about stuff!
Even if she's heavy,
you tell her she's light.
Even if she is heavy!
P-Please stop, Nel.
It's making me sad.
Now then…
I'm going to rescue
Chad and Rukia now.
W-What about us?!
Are you going to leave us?!
No way. Make sure you follow me.
It's more dangerous to stay
in a place like this.
Grimmjow…
Kurosaki…
Like I'm gonna lose.
There's…There's no way
I'd lose to the likes of you!
Enough, Grimmjow.
You've lost.
I don't know if you're a king
or whatever.
But killing off whoever displeases you
and becoming a king who's all alone…
What's so great about that?
If you don't like me,
I'll fight you as often as you like.
So…
just stop for now.
Quit joking around!
You're…
You just don't know when to give up.
Hurry up and die.
I'll have him for myself.
Who the hell are you?
Are you an Espada?!
I asked who you are! Answer me!
Nnoitora, you bastard.
What? You're still alive?
Huh?
What're you doing?
That's my line.
He can't move.
Why would you attack him?
What a miserable sight
you are, Grimmjow!
You lose to your opponent,
then he protects you?!
What's your name, Soul Reaper?
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Kurosaki, eh?
I'll remember you…
Even if it's just for an instant
before you die!
This guy…
He's so thin, and yet…
He has ridiculous brute strength!
It's heavy!
Kurosaki!
Tesla!
Yes, sir.
Inoue!
Where do you think you're looking?
Let Inoue go!
Interesting words.
That's coming from someone
who thinks he could
win as long as the girl is free.
Well, let me show you.
This is my rank. Get it now?
That piece of trash you barely
managed to defeat back there…
Well, I rank higher than him.
It's over for you.
Sorry, I forgot your name.
Why are we running away? Why?!
Isn't it obvious?
Our goal is to rescue Inoue!
Not to defeat the Espada.
We're not under any obligation
to wait for him in a room where we can't use our powers!
I agree!
And now, it looks like
we'll have to save
Rukia and Sado as well as Inoue!
It appears so.
W-What?!
This is…
Welcome back.
Now then…
Shall we start Act Two?
Next time, I shall show you
my super illusion.
Do enjoy the fascinating
Szayelaporro in action!
Well then, we'll counter with
Ishida's dismemberment magic!
Do you have the tricks set up?
Nope!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
I have news!
What's up?
Did you win the lottery?
That's not it!
STARTING WITH THE LAST EPISODE
DUE TO THE GROWN-UP ISSUES.
Our broadcast time is
changing starting today!
Shouldn't we have changed
the title of this segment?
Just leave it as is.
It's not like the content of
the show is any different.
You're awfully cranky.
Who knows when I'll be appearing
in the show next?
The same goes for you too, right?
Well…
I can't say it.
I can't say I'll be getting
an appearance soon.