Why can't it just go straight to the top?
Creepy-looking place.
It's locked.
Huh?
There's nothing else in this room, either.
You expect me to have
the answer if you don't?
I thought you'd say that.
Aren't you good at unlocking stuff?
Try something.
Huh? Don't you have something in there?
What's in it?
Thread, a needle, and...
Are you one of those people who
can pick a lock with a needle?
I don't have that talent.
Besides, there's no keyhole.
Then what's the point in having a needle?!
Move over! I'll smash it open!
They're iron bars.
Shut up! We can't know anything until we try!
Go ahead.
That's hard!
It's iron.
You should've said that sooner!
I did.
Get back!
Is someone tryin' to make
Swiss cheese out of us?
Hi, Zack! Sorry I'm late!
You guys took so long to get here
that I fell asleep.
Still...
I'm amazed that didn't kill you.
What incredible intuition you must have!
Huh?
I had a feeling you'd
make fantastic criminals.
The anticipation woke me right up.
I don't give a shit how you woke up!
Just let us through this door right now!
Yes, of course.
You pass!
I am... the judge.
Oh, you sinful evildoers!
I will torment you until
your sins are forgiven!
I am...
the one who has been permitted to do that!
I thought she'd never shut
her damn ear-piercing mouth.
Why the hell do I have to be punished?
Criminals...
What? You say something?
Let's go!
It's locked.
Hey! Weren't you gonna let us through?!
I thought you were slow,
but I see you're pretty impatient.
I haven't finished putting on
my makeup yet.
Huh?!
There's a procedure criminals have to go
through before being punished, you know?
Just start getting ready
to accept your punishment.
I'll open up a room
you can use.
Every criminal needs
a mugshot.
You two need to take yours, too.
And don't forget to wear your name boards.
Why the hell do we have to take pictures?
We have to if we want to move forward.
Tch!
You don't like being in pictures?
Huh?
Oh, hell! Fine!
What does this say?!
It's your name.
Don't waste time. Hang it around
your neck and stand there.
Yeah, yeah.
Hurry it up!
Stop moving.
Who cares?! We just need
to take a picture, right?!
It'll blur.
What the hell? Are you taking this serio—
Stand still.
I just push this here?
Yeah.
We're different heights,
so you'll have to adjust the tripod, too.
And don't push the button
too hard or it'll...
...blur.
It's blurry.
Who cares? We got the pictures!
Give 'em here!
Yo! We took the pictures!
Those are pretty crappy drawings.
Aw, that's mean! I did the best I could!
Those drawings are the wonderful
punishments I came up with just for you.
I'm going to give you a choice.
There are many ways to
make a judgment, you see!
Many harsh punishments
await the two of you ahead.
Wouldn't you rather...
stay in a cell forever, Zack?
Who the hell would willingly stay in a cell?
Oh... And I was all ready to keep
you in there until you died.
We wouldn't die right away?
Stop reacting to everything she says!
Ignore her!
They're all dolls.
Looks like another messed-up room.
It's locked.
What's wrong?
You're not going to smash it?
Huh?
That's iron. I can't smash that.
Don't "Huh?" me! You're the one
who said I can't smash iron!
Didn't you say you'd make yourself useful?
Come up with a way to move forward!
All right.
You look around for something to use, too.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey! Hurry up and find a way out of here!
I can't figure out the mechanism.
What?!
If you can't find anything, why don't
we just smash all these dolls?!
Nothing warrants that.
Huh? "Warrants"?
Well, nothing warranted smashing
those bars either, did it?
Tch!
Ugh, this pisses me off!
This is the kind of shit
that really tires me out!
There are plenty of chairs here.
You want me to sit on one of those dolls?
That ain't my style!
Hey, here's a nice one.
I don't think you should sit in that one.
Quit nitpicking everything!
But that chair...
What's wrong with it?!
I think... it's an electric chair,
used for executions.
Whoa! What the hell?!
What's going on?!
Yo! Do something about this!
Hi!
I'll be joining you through this screen.
I am...
the judge of this floor.
My name's Cathy!
Take a good look, so you
won't forget this face!
Oh, gosh! So Zack was the
one who sat in that chair!
You stupid bitch! Let me off this thing!
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to do that.
What kind of judge wouldn't
punish a criminal?
Since you're basically a monster,
let's see how much of my
punishment you can endure!
I'm so excited,
my heart is pounding!
Now, here we go!
It's showtime!
Oh? Did he die?
Zack?
That hurt, damn it!
Amazing! Anyone else
would be dead after that!
You're a killer and a monster!
That makes you the perfect criminal!
Shut up!
Quit acting so happy!
Let me off this thing so I can kill you!
Okay, then...
If Rachel can solve the
mechanism's puzzle, I'll set you free.
But until she does, I'm going
to keep the electricity flowing.
Don't do that. He'll die.
Goodness, no! It'll just tell us how
monstrous and stubborn a criminal Zack is.
Doesn't that sound fun?
Besides...
A sinner has no right of choice.
Okay, then! The judgment will now begin!
I hope all of you in the audience
will enjoy the sight of this
heinous criminal writhing in pain!
Yo, Ray! You get it, don't you?
You promised, right? So make yourself useful!
And while you're at it...
Let me kill that psycho, sadist bitch.
The loathsome stares of those
looking at the criminal...
Those stares are what
gauge a criminal's worth.
The eyes of the onlookers will
mete out your punishment.
And begin!
Zack, are you okay?
Hurry... the hell... up!
In here, the eyes of the
onlookers mete out the punishment.
The eyes of the onlookers...
These dolls are the onlookers...
Make it quick!
You know what it'll mean if I die... right?!
If you die, you can't do anything.
That's a problem.
I'll try.
The criminal cries out in agony,
begging for death out of his own regret.
That wailing, suffering display of rage
is the beauty of it.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you... I'll kill you...
I'll kill you...
I'll kill you!
Zack...
If you're alive, say something.
Zack?
Took you long enough!
Do you how intense that shock was?!
You're alive.
Damn right I am.
I didn't know what I'd do if you were dead.
Amazing, Zack! I can't
believe you didn't die!
It's that tough, stubborn will to live
that makes monsters so fascinating!
Move.
The moment you die is going to be so—
Huh?
Out of respect for Rachel's efforts,
I'll let you pass.
There's more than one punishment.
I have as many punishments as you have sins!
That sadistic bitch.
I'm gonna kill her.
Hey, let's move... on...
The hell is all this?
The eyes of the dolls were the mechanism.
My scythe gets used for the
weirdest shit, I get electrocuted...
My life sucks.
You're the one who sat in it.
Shut up!
You need to notice this stuff better!
That's obviously dangerous.
We're not gonna get anywhere by wussing out!
I think we should be a little more careful.
It's faster to keep moving
instead of screwing around.
We're locked in.
That shouldn't be surprising anymore.
Damn, but it stinks in here.
Nothing in this giant safe but a stupid wire.
Talk about your oversized garbage.
That's hard!
Hi!
Greetings, Zack!
It's the bitch.
I'm going to explain how this room works.
Listen well if you don't want to die.
I got a little extravagant
when I set up this room!
It's completely airtight,
so no air can get outside.
And the window glass is reinforced,
so you can hit it, but it won't break.
And I'm going to
fill this room with something wonderful!
If you breathe it in long enough,
it'll grant you a peaceful death.
Poison gas.
Of course, I'm not saying
there's no way out of the room.
Plus, I'm showing mercy
by providing a gas mask!
Do your
best to get out, okay?
Oh, right. It'll be boring if
you last too long without dying,
so I've set a time limit.
And...
When time is up, I'll give you the gift
of a poison gas so powerful
that the mask won't work!
Now, then, have
a delightful time.
So what do we do?
She said it's not as if there's no way out.
Guess it beats having nothing.
You put it on.
You should put it on.
Huh? You need it more than I do.
But if you die, it'll be a problem for me.
Also, it'll get in the way
of searching the room.
And what if you die?
I don't know.
Don't give me that!
If you die, I can't get out of here!
Think about it.
Okay. When it gets too hard
to breathe, we'll trade.
You better tell me when it does.
So, how do we get out of here?
There must be a hint somewhere.
I suspect...
This corpse must be here for a reason.
There's writing here.
So we just need to move the body?
Something's written there.
"The man with the unsightly foot.
Foolish murderer who stomped out
life with your right foot...
If the awareness of your
sin causes you to suffer,
you need only get rid of your right foot.
When the punishment is matched to the crime,
it may even invite a light to shine in Hell."
Get rid of the right foot...
When the punishment matches the crime...
A scale...
I said to tell me before it
gets too hard to breathe.
So what do we do?
Put that on the scale.
What do we do next?
If we can measure the weight of the crime,
something should happen.
Nothing's happening.
I don't think that's true.
There must be a mechanism somewhere.
Rachel...
Nothing suits a criminal better
than writhing in agony.