All right, bring it on!
Gran Caida...
Get 'em!
It's too flashy to be
called "assassination"!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
I'll take my sadness with me...
kanashimi mo dakishimete
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Shudder in fear...
Rot...
Arrogante.
Wh-What?
His footstep is rotting and crumbling
away the rooftop!
I told you earlier...
I signify aging.
All things near me
age...and die off.
Suffer the Dying Breath...
Respira.
Omaeda!
Cut off my arm!
Captain...
Hurry!
Do you want me to get killed?!
Omaeda!
Damn it!
How amusing...
It seems even Soul Reapers
are afraid of death.
Are you all right?
Stay away from me.
You gross me out.
He's a monster.
I've seen all sorts up until now, but
none of them come even close.
This guy's way more dangerous
than Aizen.
We can't go near him...
We can't touch him...
There's no way for us to attack,
let alone defeat him!
But that's not the
real problem...
He caught up with
Captain Soi Fon.
That means...his attack is such that no one
in the 13 Court Guard Squads can escape.
Omaeda...
Y-Yes?
I believe you said that your
duty is to assist me.
Even if you tell me to run, it's
my duty to assist you Captain!
Y-Yes! I did say that!
Because we'll need both our
powers to defeat him!
I see... Then...
you fight him.
Understood!
Wait, what did you just say?
He's yours for a bit.
You mean one-on-one?
What else is there?
No, no, no, no.
That's impossible...
That's definitely impossible!
Didn't I just say "both of us"?!
What're you talking about?!
A minute ago you told me
to run, remember?!
Well?
If you're not going to come at
me, then I'll come for you.
You see? You see?! Did
you hear that, Captain!
Captain?!
Make sure you protect
your right arm...
so you can cut off the part that turns
to bone and make your escape.
Okay, he's yours.
Wait, Captain!
Captain!
Cero.
The issue was which of us takes
the first step forward, wasn't it?
Things won't play out the way
you want if you keep running.
I used a Cero.
Isn't it about time you
showed me a Bankai?
I don't know...
It looks like the guy over there presented
something called a Resurrección.
How about it?
If you show me that, I'll consider
an appropriate response.
You sure are easy-going.
You and me both!
All right, bring it on!
HIRARI
Keep it coming!
I'll kill you!
Yes! That's the spirit!
Give me back my sword!
That, I cannot!
Die, you white-maned freak!
You're not putting
your legs into it!
HIRARI
What's the matter?
- Worried about that child?
- Give it back!
Give me back my sword!
- It's not that...
- One more time!
Don't worry. Ukitake won't do
anything funny with that child.
You should concentrate
on our battle.
I said that's not what it is!
I just don't get it...
That child is your subordinate...
A Fracciónes, was it?
Can't say I really understand what the relationship
is between them and an Espada.
At least I think there's no difference
between you and us
when it comes to feelings you have
when your subordinates die.
What're you trying to say?
I was thinking that if that child was on the brink
of danger, even you couldn't remain so relaxed.
Damn it!
Give me back my sword!
Are you suggesting taking
care of her first?
Didn't I tell you? Ukitake won't
do anything funny to her.
Not bad...
Cero!
What can you do alone?
In any event, I can't get
too close to this guy.
I have to keep an adequate distance.
No matter how I look
at it, this is reckless!
One-on-one against this guy?!
What is Captain Soi
Fon thinking?!
Try and make this
interesting for me.
Shut up! Mocking me like that...
I'll show you a thing or two!
Except I don't have any plan!
Oh what the heck!
Smash'em, Gegetsuburi!
It appears you wish to rot
away your Zanpakuto.
Very well...
Time out, time out!
That's right! Even my Gegetsuburi
will rot away if it gets near him!
Ouch! Ouch!
Weren't you aiming for me?
The way you're self-destructing, it would
seem you couldn't do a thing.
Moron! I'm not self-destructing!
I'm warming up!
I was stronger than I thought,
so the fragments hurt, that's all!
Wait, that's it...
Let's see if you can
keep up with me!
How boring...
All you're doing is running
away, after all.
What I have to do is lure him someplace
where it's easy to fight him.
There's no need to fight him up in the
sky where there aren't any obstacles.
Over here!
Get'em!
Good thinking...
You can't attack with your Zanpakuto,
so you attacked using other objects.
But something like
this is useless.
I already know that!
How about this?!
How many times
must I tell you?
Do you really think you
can hurt me with this?!
From the very start, I never thought something
like that would have any effect!
I don't think this will kill him, but it should
be enough to buy some time.
In the meantime, I need to hide somewhere
and come up with a plan that works.
What?
Buy enough time, you say?
You say interesting things.
No way!
Time has no meaning
against my powers.
The frightening thing
about aging,
the aspect of death that I signify,
is that I can even control time!
It's time you suffered
the Dying Breath...
Respira!
I'm not done yet!
HIRARI
You must realize it by now.
You can't even take this
sword back from me.
I'm afraid that's the
reality and the fact.
So what of it?!
Are you Fracciónes intensely loyal
to the Espada to that extent?
Even if you are,
stop this already.
Your duty is not to die
here needlessly.
You don't call that loyalty.
What is loyalty?!  You
make me sick!
You reek of lectures, old fart.
Old fart?!  You have a foul mouth.
I don't approve of that.
Address me properly
as, "mister."
I don't know anything about loyalty
and stuff like that, but Stark and I...
are different than the other
Espadas and Fracciónes.
Man, oh man.
I thought that Cero had me.
I really like this kimono a lot.
But I did get a good look...
When you sense that child is in danger,
you show a corresponding response.
That's not like you, Captain.
That cheap taunt is not what
you were originally after.
Maybe not...
But as far as I can tell, your
relationship doesn't seem
the same as between other
Espadas and Fracciones.
So what if it isn't?
Is hitting on that point
your M.O.?
Who's to say...
I can't be sure, but I'm thinking that's
definitely the key to the two of you.
You'll know soon enough...
That is, if you're worthy of it.
Respira!
Damn! If that hits me, it'll...
That was close! That one
really almost got me!
Haven't you realized?
If you're going to hide, then all I have to do
is eliminate the places where you can hide.
By doing that, I'll flush out that captain
who's hiding somewhere.
Yeah, I wish she'd hurry
up and come on out!
Anyway, all I can do now is run!
You're working hard at running
away, you mound of flesh!
Sh-Shut up!
You must be jealous because
you're nothing but bones!
I can't do anything directly
using Gegetsuburi...
For crying out loud!
Why isn't my Zanpakuto a Kido-type
that shoots fire or ice?!
That's it! Kido!
Kido can reach him!
I've figured out your weak point!
Bakudo 21, Sekienton!
I ended up blinding myself.
Now that I think about it, I can
hardly use Kido, damn it!
That was close... I got carried away
and almost made him angry.
This isn't going to work!
It's obviously not going to work!
I'm really going to get killed!
C-Captain!
Help!
What a pathetic cry...
Imbecile...
I couldn't even leave you
in charge for a moment.
When we're done with this battle, I'll beat the crap
out of you until you're more ugly than before.
Okay, that should do it.
Looks like you have nothing more
to offer even if I let you run free.
Time to finish it.
What the heck is that?!
Gran Caida...
A guillotine that's
too good for you.
Rot away...and die!
Ban...kai!
Jakuho Raikoben!
Is that what a Bankai looks like?
C-Captain!
That's the first time I've seen it.
So that's Captain Soi Fon's Bankai!
What's with that shape?!
How is she supposed
to fight with that?!
That's a ginjotan!
The steel sash you
wear under armor!
Why does she have such a heavy
thing wrapped around her body?!
With that wrapped around her, even Captain
Soi Fon's mobility would be limited.
If possible, I wanted to end this
without using this Bankai.
This Bankai goes against my pride
as a member of the Stealth Force.
It is too huge.
I cannot hide with it,
and it is too heavy to
move freely with it.
And its attack...
It's too flashy to be called
"assassination"!
Take this!
I'm not going to lose
to you, old fart!
There's spinning tops here.
Let's play with these.
I told you kids games
won't work on me!
I'll give you candy then!
There's strawberry, milk, and green tea
flavor. Which one would you like?
Um... Then I'll have the...
Quit falling for it, Lilinette.
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers.
I wonder if Captain
Ukitake is all right?
Hey, don't you think we should be
fighting for Captain Ukitake?!
You're right!
I'll get ready!
Captain...
Or maybe he's already...
Or worse yet...
Hey, I'm ready!
Camera, camera!