Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
That's why I told you not to ease up…
on your Spiritual Pressure.
So it's over…
How boring.
Do you want to fight?
Do you want to win?
Or do you want…to live?
Which is it?
I want to win.
I cannot hear you.
There's no meaning…
in just fighting.
Just surviving…
has no meaning.
I want to win. I…
want to win!
Fine.
Then I shall take you.
This is…?!
What are you doing?
B-But unless I do this,
I'll fall again!
You needn't worry about that.
Back then, your Hollow transformation
made this inner world lose its stability.
That's why it happened.
But it's different this time.
Take a look.
Even amidst the fierce fighting,
your inner world does not even quiver.
Hold it… hold it…
Are you saying that my mind is normally
in this up-down-sideways state?!
It seems you have grown
a bit stronger.
Wow…totally ignoring me, huh?
Stand, Ichigo!
Hey, that's dangerous!
Who'd throw an unsheathed sword
like that?!
Hang on to it. It's your sword.
Huh?
But this is…you…I mean Zangetsu…
Asauchi…
It is a nameless Zanpaku-to wielded
by a low-ranking Soul Reaper
who was unable to join Squad 13.
Yeah…but my Zanpaku-to
is Zangetsu.
Zangetsu…
the one that was broken
by your opponent earlier?
This one?
I cannot give this to you!
Wha--?!
What're you doing?!
Get outta the way!
W-Who are you?!
Aw c'mon, you know me, partner.
From now, we will test
whether you deserve to wield me.
If you wish to hold me once more,
take me away with your own hand!
Your enemy is yourself.
Hah! Take it away, huh?
Sounds good.
Do it, partner!
That is…
if you can!
I can't counter him!
Amazing!
I didn't know Zangetsu
was such an amazing sword!
The atmosphere's nearly burning away
from the spiritual aura.
It's like a monster!
The usual Zanpaku-to seems like
a wooden stick compared to it!
What can I do with something like this?!
Dammit!
What's the matter, partner?
If you just stand around,
I'll kill you!
What?!
Sheesh, missed…
He swings the Zangetsu with
the cloth wrapping from the hilt…
What's with this fighting-style?
I never even thought…
of something like that!
Hah! You're pathetic!
You had this awesome sword,
so how could you get bloodied like that?
I can't understand it.
Can you become a friend
with someone you just met,
simply by asking his name?
What?
Because that's what you're doing!
You think you've mastered Zangetsu
just by calling its name.
You're so full of yourself…
You don't even try to draw out
its full power or try to understand it!
You believe that as long as
you train yourself,
you'll get stronger!
He's right.
I didn't even try
to understand that Zangetsu.
The Zanpaku-to isn't a tool…
Each one of them has a name,
they're alive.
And yet…
My Zanpaku-to doesn't have a name.
This is its true form.
Oh yeah? I'm relieved.
Then I guess that means your sword
won't get any stronger.
Relieved, what a joke!
Cut the crap!
I'm no different.
As it is, I'm no different from that bastard
who didn't care about
his Zanpaku-to's name.
I want to know…
Now then, let's end this.
I'll show you…
what it means to master Zangetsu.
To you, who could never master it
until death!
Show me, old man Zangetsu…
Even a little at a time…about you…
I want to know about you,
the source of my strength.
And let me…
once more…
fight with you!
You're giving me one more chance?
Thank you, old man.
He's gone.
Oh well.
Was that good enough?
Yes, thanks for coming.
Don't mention it.
After all, he is the king of this world.
He has to win.
Well, I'm done here, right?
Let me go back.
Yes.
He's strong… Zangetsu.
Nurture him well.
That power is going to…
be mine eventually.
Ichigo…
I hate the rain.
And it rains in this world, too.
If your heart is troubled,
the skies will become cloudy.
If you grieve,
it will rain ever so easily.
I wonder if you can understand…
The fear of being rained upon
in this lonely world.
To stop that rain,
I shall lend you any strength.
If you have faith in me,
I will not allow any rain
to fall upon this world.
Ichigo, trust me.
You are not fighting alone.
What?! That kid's pulse
which had disappeared is…
And this Spiritual Pressure…
His bleeding…
has stopped!
I can't push down…
Sorry, but I don't have time here.
I'm gonna end this quickly.
End it quickly, huh?
Can't allow that.
Not after…
it's gotten so much fun!
I love it!
How come you revived?
How come you're suddenly
much stronger?
I've got a bunch of questions
bothering me!
But forget them for now!
Let's just have fun with this fight!
Dammit! I'm the one charging!
So how come he won't go down?!
This isn't right!
Something's wrong with you!
You love fighting that much?
Aren't you afraid of being cut,
of dying?!
Something's wrong with me?
Something’s wrong with YOU!
You're so strong,
why don't you love fighting?!
Enjoy it!
Relish in death, in pain!
Isn't that the price we pay?!
What is going on?
W-Who are you?!
Yumichika?!
Hey! So long!
No!
Was it the explosion?!
The fireworks made it like that?
Don't laugh! Fine, I'll put this on!
What?
I was just thinking that
the Captain seems to be having fun.
You're right. Who's his opponent?
His strength is amazing.
It's Ichigo. That kid has gotten stronger
from the time we fought.
He's like a different person.
Maybe Captain is on the defensive?
This is bad. Even the Captain might…
Fool! No way he'd lose!
This is the ultimate! A draw!
No, it's just slight, but you're better.
Since when…have I felt such elation?!
How come…he's going easy?
I think, with you…
I can fight with all my might!
Lieutenant Kusajishi,
I have an urgent message!
Yes, later…
Huh? But this is a Level 1 missive
signed by both Head Captain Yamamoto
and Captain Hitsugaya of Squad 10.
Hmm…then, later.
Lieutenant, please!
I was ordered to deliver
this message to everyone immediately, sir!
Shut up!
Kenpachi is fighting.
So don't bother me!
What the hell?!
The moment he removed his eye patch,
his Spiritual Pressure jumped up!
That's dirty! You have another trick
after fighting this long?
What're you hiding in that right eye?!
Hiding? In my right eye? Hah!
As if I'd stoop to such a low trick.
I asked Technological Development
to make this,
a monster that consumes
spiritual energy.
I'm gonna pump it all out…
all this spiritual energy…
in order to kill you.
That's all it is.
Can you hear it, Ichigo?
The cries of his sword?
Yeah…
He cannot hear it.
When two who do not trust
each other fight,
they only destroy each other.
And one who only believes
in himself cannot understand this.
Ichigo, can you trust me?
That goes without saying.
I'm putting all my power in your hands.
Do what you will with it.
And lend me your power!
Yes.
Oh… After all this time,
your Spiritual Pressure still increases?
This is fun.
Of course, it increases.
I'm borrowing Zangetsu's power
and fighting alongside him.
I will never lose to someone like you…
who only fights alone!
Zangetsu?
Is that the name of that Zanpaku-to?
Borrowing the power of your Zanpaku-to
and fighting alongside it…
Nonsense!
Zanpaku-to are mere tools for fighting.
That's the line of a weakling
who has no confidence
in his own strength,
so he "borrows" the power
of the Zanpaku-to!
And that is…
not my line, Ichigo!
He's coming, Ichigo!
I'm near the limit of my ability
to stop the flow of your bleeding.
We will finish this in one blow.
Sorry…everyone…
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
This is an announcement to
recruit members for the Zaraki Squad!
All those who were moved
by the Captain's fighting, gather round!
If you join now,
the Lieutenant will give you a nickname!
Send your applications to
Ikkaku Madarame,
or Yumichika Ayasegawa!
We'll be waiting!
No soliciting!