Orihime has been abducted
by the Arrancars.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, and Sado
have marched into Hueco Mundo,
the world of the Hollows.
They crush the Arrancars
standing in their way
and head to Aizen's headquarters,
Las Noches.
They come across odd Arrancars named
Nel, Pesche, and Dondochakka,
and wind up traveling with them.
Ichigo and his friends hurried on,
but the Guardian of the White Sand,
Runuganga, appeared before them
and blocked their way.
Faced with an enemy who is
not affected by physical attacks,
Ichigo and his friends were in trouble.
But at that moment…
Why did you go off to
Hueco Mundo on your own?!
Why didn't you wait
for us to come back?!
That's because I didn't know
if you were coming back…
We'd come back!
No matter what!
Renji and I were planning on
doing so from the beginning!
Why didn't you wait for us?!
Why couldn't you trust us?!
We're your friends, right Ichigo?
But even though
Runuganga was defeated,
he appears before Ichigo
and his friends once again.
That guy's still not dead?!
It can't be…
I smashed him into pieces.
I won't let you take another step
towards Las Noches!
Runuganga is made of sand!
It's not strange for there to be
more than one of him!
So this is the second body?
Dance…
Sodenoshirayuki.
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren!
What are you doing, Rukia?!
S-Sorry… I couldn't help myself.
You're picking on him!
Crap!
What's that?
Ow ow ow ow…
Is everyone all right?
Yeah. Somewhat…
It looks like we're all right.
Thank you, Bawabawa!
Nel is falling, falling!
That hurts!
That’s my line!
Move out of the way, evildoers!
Step aside!
That was close…
Thanks for the save, evildoers!
Yeah.
That was a perfect landing!
Jeez…
Anyway… Where are we?
Underground, right?
We fell from there, huh?
What's this?!
What's wrong, Ishida?
This is a tree!
A tree?
Yeah… It's the same as the ones
growing above ground.
I see…
The trees above ground are
the tops of these giant trees.
SURFACE
SAND
UNDERGROUND
These reach the surface?
That aside,
it's incredibly wide here.
Yeah. I can't even see
where the walls are.
What's wrong?
Th-This is the Forest of Menos.
The Forest of Menos?
What is the Forest of Menos?
I thought so…
What do you mean, Ishida?
It was far away,
but when we were falling,
I saw a group of Menos.
Possibly…
In this world,
the Espada and Arrancars
live on the surface
and Gillians and lesser Hollows
live underground.
Right?
Th-That's right.
Which means…
This place is crawling with them.
Nel… Do you know
the way to the surface?
Nel only heard rumors
of the Forest of Menos.
This is the first time
Nel’s ever been here!
Nel doesn't know
of any way out.
Aw, it's no good!
We’re all going to die!
It really is a forest of death!
Yeah!
Don't worry, Nel!
We're going to die!
We've come here,
so there must be a way out!
Itsugo…
You're right…
As long as there are Hollows here,
there must be a way in and out.
Evildoers, that's a pretty
clever thing to say!
I'm impressed!
It doesn't please me
to be praised by you.
All right! Now that it's decided,
let's move on!
Hey, Ichigo!
Rukia's not here!
Huh?! When did she disappear?!
Probably when we were
swallowed up in the sand!
Where am I?
Ichigo!
Crap! Where are Ichigo
and the others?
Crap! Why are there
so many Hollows?!
I keep defeating them,
but their numbers don't drop
and new Hollows keep coming.
I have to rejoin Ichigo and
the others as soon as possible.
Ichigo! Renji! Where are you?!
What's that?!
Somenomai!
Tsukishiro!
If I can just get there…
Menos Grande!
A Cero!
Hey, Rukia!
Rukia! Answer us!
Kuchiki
– Hey, Soul Reaper!
It's no good…
We can't find her anywhere.
We fell from the same place…
I don't think that
she should be far.
Oh. I know!
What is it Kurosaki?
Rukia's incredibly light, isn't she?
So…
– Do you suppose she was blown far away?
– Oh no!
That's it, Ichigo!
That's got to be it!
That's why we couldn't find her
when we searched nearby!
Just what do you think Kuchiki is?
Wh-What?! What's going on?!
Oh yeah?
Ichigo, Bawabawa says that he's
going to climb a tree and look for her!
Ah, Bawabawa!
What a good boy…
All right, go!
And take a good look!
Look for that vile Soul Reaper
with your sharp eyes!
That's a good idea!
Hey… He's calling her vile…
He doesn't have eyes, either…
Stop commenting on everything…
There's no end to it.
Wait!
I want to see what this underground area
looks like as a whole.
Let me get on!
I'm going, too.
– Give it your best, Bawabawa!
– Give it your best!
I'm surprised that they
can keep this up.
Thank you for saving me,
but could you let go of me already?!
Let go of me!
I told you to let go of me!
Are you listening to me?!
Sorry…
What?!
What are you doing?!
Bear with me…
We'll arrive at my hideout shortly.
This man…
I'm going to jump.
The forest seems kind of noisy.
There are several
odd Spiritual Pressures.
So? What should we do?
They'll die if we leave them alone.
Hey…
We've received a notice
from Las Noches.
Oh?
It looks like things
have gotten fun.
Hey…
Is that a light made of Kido?
You really are a Soul Reaper.
Where are you assigned?
What's your squad?
Did you leave your squad?
Hey!
Say something…
My name is Ashido.
Ashido?
And this…is the Forest of Menos.
The Forest of Menos?
This is where Menos live.
It is a world that is far away
from the rules of Soul Society.
What are you doing?!
You don't want to talk, huh?!
He's strong…
His fighting style is random,
yet it has incredible strength.
Hey!
Can you see anything?
No. It's no good!
That's odd…
When we were falling,
I could have sworn that I saw
a group of Menos in this direction.
But I don't see them
anywhere now.
Where did the Menos go?
What the…?!
Take a look at that!
– What are they making a fuss about?
– Renji, let's go!
– All right!
– Ishida, it's Hollows!
Chad! Ishida!
Crap!
– These guys…
– You're in the way!
What's this?!
What's going on?!
What is this?!
What?
They're coming!
Ichigo!
What is it, Nel?!
Hide!
Ichigo, run away!
It's dangerous!
That's right!
Leave those evildoers.
But…
They're…Menos…
I see! That's what
that howl was for!
I see… So that's it.
Bawabawa, please don't move!
My aim is…
Getsugatensho!
Are you all right?!
Yeah. You saved us!
Roar! Zabimaru!
They just keep coming.
We might be eaten at this rate.
All right! Our only option is
to bravely withdraw!
But Ichigo is…
Listen, Nel.
You just have to
make yourself believe
that we never knew
those Soul Reapers to begin with!
But we already know them…
That's why I’m saying
to stop knowing them!
It may already be too late.
Nel?!
Ichigo!
We've been caught!
They're going to eat us!
I’m coming right…
Ichigo!
Why're there so many of them?!
They're the same ones
I saw earlier!
Crap!
Did you bring me here
so that you could kill me?!
That's all you've got, huh?
In that case…
At this rate,
we're going to be eaten!
But what would be
the best way to cook us?
I would probably have a strong taste if
I were simmered and made into a broth.
I should be deep fried to
savor the sweetness of my flesh!
Nel would taste great
as a sashimi.
You sure have got
a lot of time on your hands.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
This is getting bad, bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad, bad, bad!
SEIREITEI NEWS
EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT
Is Rangiku's article ready yet?
Not yet!
What?!
I brought you my article!
What is this?
They're pictures of my captain
that I took in secret.
Make a special feature to
include them with the issue!
You'll be sure to
double your sales!
No. We can't remake
this issue at this point.
I've already contacted your printers.
Take care of the rest! See you later!
I'm going to be up all night!