I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Whatever action you planned
is too late.
Even if it’s only you,
I will save you!
But you can die right here!
Who is that?
A Soul Reaper.
What?!
Don’t worry.
She came from a place called
Soul Society in order to save us.
Soul Reaper…
What are you doing?
Huh?!
Well… Err…
You’re a very young Bount,
aren’t you?
Y-Yes.
I understand it’s very rare for
Bount powers to awaken
in a young child like you.
Everyone has hope in you.
Huh?
Do your best.
We intend to do all we can
so that you can live free of worries.
Oh… Y-Yes…
Shortly thereafter, the Soul Reapers
returned to Soul Society
to plan our salvation.
We were left behind
to continue building the city,
waiting patiently for
the Soul Reapers to return one day.
I was very young,
but I helped the grown-ups around me.
The adults placed all their hopes
on the Soul Reapers.
But their hopes were cruelly dashed.
What?!
Hey, hang on!
Take them all into custody!
Kill any who resist!
R-Run!
Don’t let even one get away!
Get them!
You find him?!
No!
Find him! Do not let him
get away from us!
You there! Are you all right?
She’s that Soul Reaper
from before, but…
I will distract the Soul Reapers,
so you must escape during that time.
Huh?
If you go outside,
there are sure to be other Bounts.
Run away with your comrades.
But then you…
I’ll be fine.
Take this…
The Bounts have much more power
hidden within them.
This will help to draw out that power.
I’m really sorry.
You’ll be forced to endure suffering now,
but I’m sure one day…
So you must live!
Lady…
Now, hide…
That’s the last time
I saw that Soul Reaper.
I somehow managed to escape
from that cave.
And together with the Bounts
who survived,
I began a life of wandering once again.
But we were like food thrown
into a den of wild animals.
We Bounts who
possessed spiritual power
became ideal prey
for the Hollows.
Pursued by Hollows,
my despair and bitterness towards
the Soul Reapers grew steadily stronger.
Who are you…?
I feel power growing inside me.
That was my first experience
merging with a doll.
There had always been Bounts
who could naturally summon
the power to control dolls.
Together with them,
I fought…and fought…
and fought my heart out.
By utilizing this power, we could readily
confront the Soul Reapers.
I realized that with this power,
we could create a paradise for Bounts.
But the attitude of other Bounts
towards me gradually changed.
And when I realized it, I was alone.
Even so, I stayed with my comrades.
Until that time…
On that day, the Bounts had decided
to use the strength of the Quincies…
– …to go to Soul Society.
– What are you saying?! Stop!
It’s already decided.
Going to Soul Society means…
you’re clinging to the Soul Reapers!
We don’t have to do that!
We can create our own paradise
in this world with our own strength!
The existence of Bounts in
this world is abnormal.
Even if we use our power to build
a place for ourselves,
it is doomed to eventually fail.
It’s better that we return
to our original place.
For Bounts,
Soul Society is the paradise.
Not one of them listened to my pleas.
And the fighting began…
But, in the end,
the Soul Reapers hindered this plan.
Unable to find a meaning to this battle
I got hit from a blast and was injured,
and before I could do a thing,
the battle was over.
I gave up on the weak Bounts.
But…I couldn’t forgive the Soul Reapers
from Soul Society!
I gathered the strong Bounts who survived
and swore to destroy Soul Society.
Activating the dolls
used to come accidentally…
so I set out to refine and perfect its use
and began classifying the Bounts.
In that process,
many Bounts lost their lives.
But the ones remaining
were truly committed to attaining strength.
And I rose,
in order to destroy Soul Society.
To think I had forgotten all about you
who had given us false hope
and eternal suffering.
I wonder if it’s due to the power
of the Jokai Crest?
But it’s over.
For the weak Bounts
who clung to your words.
For Soul Society who
used us mercilessly.
I will turn everything into nothing!
You are…the Quincy!
Kariya, your opponent is me!
Kid… What can you possibly do now?!
What?!
Amazing.
That Quincy has completely
mastered that artifact.
What’s the meaning of this?
Didn’t you reach your limit with
that thing in the battle with Yoshi?
This ancient artifact amasses
reishi quickly, and multiplies it
in order to assist a Quincy with
weak spiritual powers.
Simply put, it accumulates reishi
even if the wielder does nothing.
Until now, all I did was attack
and adjust the outgoing power.
Doing just that is sure to
make it reach its limit.
Unable to handle the load of reishi,
it would eventually
discharge spontaneously.
However, there’s another method.
This artifact can be used solely
as an amplifier
with me using my own power to
adjust and control the reishi.
Then the stress on the accessory itself
is lessened
and I can still battle, even in this state.
Extreme battle conditions
made me realize this.
He mentioned that he uses that artifact
because he lost his own spiritual power.
But to be able to do this much
in such a condition is…
What’s so funny?!
With so much power,
why do you side with the Soul Reapers?
Aren’t Soul Reapers enemies
to the Quincies?
Don’t get the wrong idea.
I am not an ally of Soul Reapers.
I’m here to stop this senseless fight.
Humph… Such noble words.
Yoshino lost her life in order
to bring you down.
She said, “Kariya hates not
only Soul Reapers, but Bounts too.”
“Someday, his all consuming hatred will
end up destroying the Bounts too.”
Yoshino understood that
what you were doing
was totally meaningless to the Bounts.
But in the end,
no one was able to stop you.
Perhaps it’s all too late.
Still…I will stop you!
I wonder if you can?
I will!
It’s over!
Don’t underestimate me!
The quality of the reishi in Seireitei is
much higher than that
in the Rukon District.
As long as I have this power,
your attacks are useless!
A crack in the artifact!
It seems the stress placed on
that bow isn’t completely erased.
No problem.
I just have to bring you down
before this bow breaks.
Can you do it?
I have all the reishi within
the Seireitei.
Same here.
In order to release a powerful arrow,
you need to have some aim.
And on the other hand, it doesn’t have
much power for any other kind of attack.
And it seems you don’t have
much time left.
If things keep going like this…
What’s the matter?
Your attacks are becoming crude!
This is it, Quincy!
Kariya!
What?!
Wh-What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Why you…!
Rantao!
Now! Shoot now!
Why you--!
Hurry!
But…!
Never mind me! Shoot!
Right now, I’m momentarily
intercepting the power of the Jokai Crest
as an intermediary to increase
my Spiritual Pressure!
I cannot continue this for long!
There’s no way
I can do such a thing!
Shoot!
Don’t let this Bount add more…
to his sins!
Yes, that’s the way.
Why you--! Let go!
Rantao!
What about Kariya?
He’s still alive.
You…purposely lessened the force.
Don’t worry, I’m going to
inflict the final blow right now.
No!
This is…her Spiritual Pressure
is going out of control?!
Is it a reaction to the earlier power?
No… If I don’t do something,
Rantao’s body will disintegrate and…
That’s it!
This artifact controls reishi…
Rantao! Hang on!
I can use this artifact…
to remove the spirit energy
that’s going out of control inside you!
You…mustn’t do that!
Your artifact is nearing its limit.
The remaining power…
must be used to destroy Kariya.
Never mind me!
I used this power
fully prepared for this.
So…!
Rantao!
So hurry!
Otherwise, Kariya will recover.
Now… Now is your only chance!
Wh-Why you--!
Quincy!
Rantao! I can’t let you die like this!
Quincy…
I’ve reached my limit.
We can’t stay here.
Let’s go somewhere safe.
Do you think you can run away?
It seems you’ve lost
the perfect chance to kill me.
You managed to escape death,
but this is it.
Die!
Looks like you’re in a bind.
Kurosaki!
Brat!
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Boy, that girl in the tea shop
was so cute!
Tea shop?
The one in Rukon District?
You know about that girl,
you unhealthy-looking male?
She’s a he. Isn’t that so, Hisagi?
Everybody knows that.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
To think the Bounts came this far.
We must re-evaluate our security.
Yeah.
Lieutenant Kira!
We’ve arrested a suspicious person!
Is it a Bount?!
Please come this way!
Huh?!
You’re…!
Yo! Sorry to keep you waiting.
The ultimate helper is here!
– He’s here too?!
Yes…
Be sure to tune in next week!