Shusuke Amagai,
originally from the Expedition Unit,
is appointed as
the new captain of Squad 3.
In spite of possessing awesome power,
Amagai is a humble man,
choosing to fight together
with his squad members.
Supporting his method,
the squad members
gradually gain momentum.
One day Kira discovers
an unexpected side
to the mild-mannered
and trusted Makoto Kibune.
Seeing this, Kira comes to feel
a strange discomfort towards Kibune.
I knew of its existence,
but this is
the first time I’ve ever entered this place.
Me too.
Well, people don’t use
fighting arenas anymore.
But since we have access to it,
Mr. Kibune felt we could
use it for our training drill.
Sorry we're late.
Huh? Where’s Captain Amagai?
Oh, about the captain…
Can I have a moment
of your time?
What is it, Amagai?
Here on the Captains’ Council,
I’m the youngest member and
it may be deemed inappropriate,
but I would like to
express my opinion.
Speak.
Sir!
It was just after I had been appointed
as the captain of Squad 3…
A request for a Restrictive Current
shutdown was submitted
to the Department of
Research and Development
in order to battle the Menos
in the Precipice World.
Yet, the Restrictive Current
still occurred.
Our squad faced the
danger of being consumed
by the Restrictive Current.
Fortunately,
my squad members survived.
What is this all about?
Excuse me?
If you have a complaint,
express it elsewhere!
I don’t have time to listen
to the problems of another squad,
nor am I interested!
Yes!
That is what I would like to
express my opinion on!
What?
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are comprised of independent squads
each with their own
unique qualities.
I understand that.
But, from an organizational
point of view,
there is no interaction between members
and the cooperative spirit is weak.
Am I wrong to say
this Precipice World incident
has exposed the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads’ weakness?
So, what?
You want us to get all friendly and
fight together joining hand in hand?
I wouldn’t go that far.
I think we should at least
conduct joint training exercises.
No way!
I’m not interested in
taking part in such games!
Don’t make me laugh!
No…
It may not be
a laughing matter.
What?!
When you think about it…
Aizen, Ichimaru, Tosen…
All three of these rebels
probably took advantage of the
gaps and misunderstandings between us.
To strengthen and
unify our squads…
What Captain Amagai is
suggesting makes sense to me.
Don’t be discouraged, Amagai.
You expressed your opinion well.
But…
I was hoping to get
a commitment to joint training.
As a man…
It is truly regrettable!
He hasn’t drunk much, has he?
No, he hasn’t.
Then, why?
Just the smell of alcohol seems
to have made him drunk.
Don’t rush, Amagai.
It’s got great potential.
Huh?! Really?
Yeah…
It may seem daunting,
but most of the members
understood what you were proposing.
Plus, Ukitake nicely
elaborated on the topic.
Captain Ukitake…
I owe you!
– H-Hey!
– Hey, hey…
W-Wait, Amagai!
Yes, yes, I’m all right.
I see… Now I’m
even more motivated.
I will work on our
next strategy right away!
Cheers!
Oh my…
What do you think?
About him?
Yeah.
I like him and his recklessness.
Yeah…
That’s why…
Huh? What?
That’s why I get the feeling he’ll
become isolated from the other captains.
Joint training?!
Yeah.
That new Squad 3
Captain suggested it.
Huh? I personally don’t
think it’s necessary.
Joint training, huh?
-It will be a pleasure to work with you!
It might be surprisingly fun
doing it together.
I don’t think so.
Come on!
You won’t know until you try!
I do know!
It sounds fun though!
It looks like...
Ukitake and Kyoraku are lending
a lot of support to Amagai.
I hope it doesn’t create a strain
between him and those opposing him.
Unfortunately,
I’m told the joint
training exercises were rejected.
We in Squad 3 are the
only ones doing those coordination exercises.
It was our chance to show
the other squads what we could do.
Looks like we’re back to
doing miscellaneous chores.
The other day,
I had to clean Squad 7’s toilets.
That’s nothing.
I’m Squad 11’s errand boy.
They complain about me being thirty
seconds late and things like that.
Well, at least it’s not
as bad as Squad 4.
You’re right.
Compared to the miscellaneous
team of Squad 4…
Huh?! Don’t tell me…
Squad 4 made me do laundry!
– Huh?!
What’s going to happen to us?!
There’s no reason
to be so pessimistic.
The captains of Squads 8
and 13 agreed to support
Captain Amagai’s suggestion.
The Captains’ Council decision
may soon be reversed.
Oh!
That’s reassuring!
I’m glad to hear that.
It appears you lack
the will as well.
What is it? Lieutenant Kira…
Is there something on my face?
Uh… No…
Actually…
Third Seat Kibune,
I saw you entering the Kasumiohji house.
Huh?
Me?
Really, Third Seat Kibune?!
It couldn’t be!
There’s no way
I could have entered such a place.
You’ve mistaken me
for someone else.
Huh?! But…
Besides, why would an average Soul Reaper
like me have contact with such
an aristocratic family?
That’s true!
Don’t surprise us like that!
Was I mistaken?!
No, I’m sure of it.
Urgent message!
Menos have been detected
entering the Seireitei!
Squads, go to your guard posts
and prepare to intercept!
Menos?!
I repeat!
Menos have been detected
entering the Seireitei!
That…can’t be!
Squads, prepare to intercept!
What’s going on?
What’ll we do?!
Uh… What do you mean?
Isn’t it obvious?!
Let’s attack, sir!
We can’t afford to fall
behind the other squads!
But…the captain…
This is our chance
to show our strength!
Right, Mr. Kibune?!
Okay! Let’s go!
– Yeah!
No!
Let’s wait for the captain!
But…
Moving out aimlessly
would be meaningless.
Let’s wait until
Captain Amagai returns.
No…
If we’ve trained,
we can move even without the captain.
Or is there some reason?
Are you going to ignore
the enthusiasm of your
squad members and not move
until the captain gives
orders, Lieutenant Kira?
That’s not the point.
I’m saying we shouldn’t move
needlessly until we
get more information!
Is that so?
Don’t you think we can do it?
Third Seat Kibune is right!
We can do it!
– He’s right!
– Let’s attack!
– Let’s go!
– Lieutenant Kira!
– Let's attack!
– Lieutenant!
It can’t be helped!
Third Seat Kibune,
please take charge!
What?!
That’s right!
I’ll follow your lead!
– Me, too!
This is what the members
are saying.
Do you still intend to say no?
Uh… But…
It appears you have
no intention of acting.
As it stands,
I will have to lead then.
Let’s go, everyone!
– Yes, sir!
You guys!
Don’t let anyone get past us!
We, Squad 11,
will be getting the prey.
Huh?
Why did you
suddenly appear, Iba?!
That’s what I was going to say!
We’re in a hurry!
So are we!
Stop being so persistent!
Same to you!
We have business
to deal with over there!
We’re the ones
who have business!
For now, go to your guard posts.
But, don’t overextend yourself.
It’s odd to not have received
any eye witness information yet.
And you captain?
I’ll leave you in charge
of this area.
Captain!
Lieutenant!
NON-SQUAD 12 MEMBERS
KEEP OUT
Wait a minute. What’s this?!
It’s unusual for Menos
to enter the Seireitei!
Please stay out of our way
as we capture it!
Huh?
Squad Alert!
Menos have been detected in
the northeast area of the Seireitei!
Move in that direction!
I repeat!
Menos have been detected in
Did you hear that?
Northeast!
the northeast area of the Seireitei
Let’s go! Don’t fall behind!
Move in that direction!
According to the messenger,
they should be around here.
It doesn’t feel like there are
Menos around here at all.
Third Seat Kibune!
I really think we should
pull back at once.
We don’t have visuals of the target,
and besides that,
we don’t know what kind of
special properties it may possess.
Lieutenant Kira!
We’ve come this far,
what are you saying?!
That’s right!
If we take them down,
Squad 3 will be recognized!
But…
Lieutenant Kira, I think you
should refrain from saying anything
that might confuse
your squad members.
Besides, I thought you
were against attacking.
What are you doing here?
You…
As reported, as of now there are
conflicts occurring
between squads in several locations.
I understand, thank you.
Captain.
What do you think, Nanao?
Well, something seems
to be wrong.
There’s no enemy in sight,
yet there’s tension in the air.
You are right.
Well? Shall we go home?
What are you talking about?!
Menos have entered the vicinity!
Menos?
Are they really there?
Huh?!
You think so too?
– Huh?!
Are you saying it is all a ruse?!
There’s a high probability.
Why is that?
We only have information
but no confirmed sighting.
Besides,
the only thing I can feel
is the Spiritual Pressure
from each of the squads.
I think somebody
played a trick on us.
– Oh…
– As expected of our captain!
Hey, that was my line, Kotsubaki!
Don’t steal it!
Shut up!
You were copying me!
I’m not copying you!
You numbskull!
What was that?!
In any case,
someone sounded an alarm.
As well as provided
false information.
Everyone, including captains,
lieutenants and a lot of Soul Reapers
believed it and took action.
This proves how easy it is to draw
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
into confusion against
an enemy that does not exist.
The question is…
who was behind this?
It was I.
Genryusai Sensei?!
So, what do you suggest
we do, Lieutenant?
Withhold our attack!
But if you insist on going…
What a strange person.
Very well.
Let’s go at it.
Stop!
Sorry, everyone.
I left you all behind.
Captain, where were you?
I was done in by alcohol
and fell asleep.
Again?!
This guy is…
Never mind that, Kibune.
Yes.
Even if the troops
give their approval,
when I’m not here,
Kira should give the orders.
Don’t overstep your boundaries.
I’m sorry.
Captain Amagai…
Sorry, Kira.
If only I could
handle liquor better.
Next time, be more confident
and take the lead.
Yes, sir.
What’s wrong?
There it is!
Here!
Let’s go, you guys!
Squad 11 is the first to go!
I don’t think so!
We’re the ones
who are ready to go!
Hurry!
We can’t let our prey get killed
before we catch it!
Come on! What’s going on?!
What’s going on?
It’s a dead end!
What’ll we do?!
Those five Menos…
I created them myself
using the Tenshintai
to see how each squad would react to the
spread of false information.
Until now, everything was
going as expected.
All that’s left
is to see what Amagai
does amidst this chaos.
Don’t panic!
Do as you were trained and there
won’t be any problems!
– Y-Yes, sir!
Tell the other squads
how we usually move!
I’ll give the order!
– Understood!
Sorry, everyone!
From here on,
do as Squad 3 asks you to!
Squad 7 fall back!
Iba?!
Madarame, Squad 7 is pulling back.
You do the same!
Why?!
Just pull back!
It can’t be helped.
Squad 11, fall back for now!
Okay, Aida!
Have Squad 6 move to the right!
Yes, sir!
Please do so!
All right!
Next! Kano!
Squad 10 to the left!
Yes, sir!
Okay, Kira!
Squad 11 to the center!
Yes, sir!
Now!
I know!
Roar Zabimaru!
Next! Inose!
Squad 7 to the back right!
As you can see, the five dummy Menos
were destroyed with quick formations
following orders from Squad 3.
I see.
I approve the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads' joint training.
Boy! That felt great!
Indeed!
From now on Squad 3
won’t be treated so poorly!
You know?
With Captain Amagai,
Squad 3 is in good hands!
That’s for sure!
Right, Captain?
Well…now that I feel relieved,
the alcohol is rushing in again.
Kenryu, we have not
been going to school lately.
Is it okay for us not to
commute every day?
It’s okay.
Ichigo Kurosaki and the others
have also been with us this whole time,
and they are fine as well,
are they not?
Actually, it’s not fine.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
No!
Golden!
Here are the heroes who’ve been
selected for after school lessons this week.
Make sure you attend.
I’m in the group.
Hang in there, Keigo!
Shut up!
You too, Kurosaki!
Huh?!
But, I did all right on
the test the other day!
Ow!
You…miss school…and leave early.
Your…attendance…rate…is poor!
TORU IWASAKI
SATORU YAMAKAWA
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
I’m sorry.