I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Oh!
It’s the captain!
The captain is back!
Captain!
I’m fine.
I brought down the Bount.
The South District is frozen over
from my Hyorinmaru.
It will melt shortly,
so go and retrieve the Bount.
Is it still alive?
No. I don’t know if there’s a corpse,
but we can’t leave it there.
Eventually, we’ll have to
give it a burial.
Yes sir!
Is Matsumoto back?
Yes sir! She’s with
Lieutenant Abarai of Squad 6,
getting medical treatment for
those who were injured.
Also, one more thing…
What is it?
The Substitute Soul Reaper
is here, too.
What?!
Captain…
Welcome back, sir.
What of the Bount?
I managed to take care of it.
Yo, Toshiro.
I’m using your place.
You’re doing it on purpose,
aren’t you?
How many times must I tell you?
It’s Captain Hitsugaya!
What’s the big deal?
It doesn’t matter.
It does matter!
Besides, why are you here?
We happened to run into Rangiku
while chasing after Kariya.
Yes!
Ishida was hurt and we needed
a place for him to rest,
so it was perfect timing…!
Since we don’t have a home base
in Seireitei.
It was a stroke of good fortune that
we met up with everyone.
Sorry, we came uninvited like this.
Anyway, that’s the story.
I know it’s an inconvenience,
but can you let us rest here a bit?
I guess I have no choice.
Ishida…
No… I’m okay.
Are you in pain?
I was the one who brought
the Bounts to this world.
Whatever injuries I incur,
I’ll take full responsibility.
Inoue would know how to treat
a wound like this.
It can’t be helped.
Orihime is outside the walls
of Seireitei.
Due to the Bount invasion,
there are injured all across Seireitei.
Squad 4 has their hands full.
But I’ve sent word, so someone
should come in time.
You’ll be all right.
You can’t fight,
but your life is in no danger.
That won’t do!
I…came here to fight!
Don’t be hasty.
We’ve gotten word that
Soi Fon and Kurotsuchi
have taken down one Bount each.
Counting the one I brought down,
Kariya’s the only one left.
I must hand it to you, Captain!
That metal doll gave us
so much trouble,
yet you beat it so easily!
It wasn’t easy.
Not only that…
During the battle, that Bount was
definitely acting strange.
He was even going easy on
his attacks against the squad members…
What happened to Kariya?
He seems to have gotten
some unknown power.
I think he called it the “Jokai Crest.”
He said he’s gonna blow up
Seireitei with that power.
Kariya’s actions were unusual
even for that other Bount?
If only we could’ve
stopped him then…
It’s over.
No use mulling over it.
By the way,
what happened to Ichinose?
We received word that
Captain Zaraki brought him down.
Kurosaki!
Everyone, are you all right?!
Please wait!
Inoue!
Kira!
Jidanbo’s injuries are taken care of,
so I came after you guys.
It just so happened that Squad 3
members were guarding the gates.
So I brought her.
Thanks.
Sorry to put you right to work,
but can you tend to Ishida’s wounds?
Yes, sure.
Inoue, thank you…
I don’t need to get back to 100%.
Just…can you do it quickly?
Hold on!
Rangiku?
Ishida, weren’t you listening
to what’s been said?
I understand how anxious you are,
but calm down a bit!
Yes, yes, yes!
Rest is essential in a battle, too.
Everyone’s been on the move
since last night!
You’re right.
If something happens,
we’ll get word right away.
It’s no use getting anxious.
And who’s available now?
Yes, sir! Mainly Squad 11.
Since Squad 11 is without
its captain right now,
they hadn’t received orders.
They weren’t involved in
the afternoon confusion,
so they’re the healthiest squad
around right now.
That’s right, I hadn’t sent
any orders to Squad 11.
Dammit! I wanted to fight
the Bounts myself.
I hear there’s only one left!
Same here!
I wanted to pay them back
for what they did in
the World of the Living.
And the captain just left
and hasn’t returned.
It seems he fought with
a Soul Reaper named Ichinose
who sided with the Bounts.
He’s probably quite happy and
sightseeing in the Rukon District.
Ichinose, huh?
I owed him some payback.
That bastard…!
Well, the last one standing
is a bigwig.
I’ll find this one with
my own hands for sure!
Reporting!
Seireitei… The North District…
There’s nothing suspicious
in any of the blocks.
The other squads are exhausted
from the afternoon skirmish.
If we find him now,
we get to do whatever we want!
So find him, no matter what!
We have an urgent message
from Captain Kyoraku of Squad 8
and Captain Ukitake of Squad 13.
Wasn’t Captain Ukitake
in poor health?
Yes. I’m sorry, but he went
to the Central Library
in order to find data on the Bounts.
Hmm… Well, no matter.
And what is this urgent message?
The data Rantao left behind
has been discovered.
It has an entry about
an explosive power
that was sealed in the Jokai Crest.
I see.
Which means…
that man, Kariya, wasn’t lying.
According to the data,
in order to totally draw out
the power in the Jokai Crest…
a short period of time is necessary
after activating the Jokai Crest.
And how much time is that?
About one day…
So that’s what Kariya meant
when he said everything will
be decided in one day.
Yes, sir…
Hmm…
To think he’d even use that
as a part of his tactics.
We must not let down
our guard against him.
We must take this Kariya
into custody quickly.
I will send directives to each squad.
It seems we don’t even have time
for a captains’ meeting.
Yes sir!
Tell Captain Ukitake
and Captain Kyoraku
to continue checking the data.
Understood, sir!
Captain Soi Fon’s recovery
was slower than expected,
so she is on standby at her quarters.
I see.
Captain Kurotsuchi’s ability to return
to battle is also very questionable.
Captains Kyoraku and Ukitake
have secluded themselves
in the Central Library
to gather information.
What of Captain Komamura?
He is guarding
General Captain Yamamoto.
All right. I understand the situation.
Good work.
Thank you. If you’ll excuse me…
Isane!
Rangiku?!
Make sure you taste my cooking!
I’m still on duty…!
Are you saying
you won’t eat my cooking?!
Who’s there?!
You’re…!
Rantao!
A gun that fires kido?
How did you find me?
A Bount sensor?
Right. I’m the one that knows
the most about Bounts.
Why haven’t you given that
technology to the Soul Reapers?
Because…I intend to settle
everything by myself!
Interesting thing you have there.
It looks like it packs a punch,
but it’s not enough to bring me down.
What’s the matter?
That mark…
Impossible…!
After the konpaku experiment failed,
we were sent to
the World of the Living.
Shortly before our arrival,
there were reports in
the World of the Living about
a large number of humans
possessing strange powers.
They were Bounts.
The Bounts were confused
about their strength,
yet they tried to live among
the normal humans.
But due to their strength,
they weren’t able to remain friendly
with humans for long periods of time.
And finally, they began
to be persecuted.
I tried to get close to the Bounts
in order to save them…
Because they were victims
of our experiments.
Do not fear me.
I am your friend.
I rounded up the Bounts
and advised them to
stay together and hide.
I will return to Soul Society
and make arrangements so that
you will be under the protection
of Soul Society.
Is that possible…?
Yes. It’s true that this will
not be an easy task.
It will probably take several years
before protection of the Bounts
becomes a reality.
I understand.
We will wait here until you return.
But something totally unexpected
awaited me
when I returned to Soul Society.
The Central 46 of that time
decided that everything
regarding the konpaku experiment
as well as its by-product, the Bounts,
would be buried in secrecy.
Why are you going to turn
your backs on the Bounts?!
We acknowledge that
the konpaku experiment was inhumane.
If you believe that,
why won’t you save them?
They possess amazing power!
If we ignore them,
they may even become
a danger to Soul Society!
Bounts who cannot control reishi
cannot pass through the Dangai,
Precipice World.
They will never be a threat
to Soul Society. However…
That is not the case in
the World of the Living.
Our duty is to regulate
the balance of konpaku.
There is a possibility the Bounts
threaten that equilibrium.
You don’t mean the Bounts will be…?
Do you actually believe
such a thing can be allowed?!
No, we don’t.
We must live with the burden
of our mistake
and strive to never repeat
such a mistake again!
I cannot…I cannot turn my back
on the Bounts!
Take them all into custody!
Kill any who resist!
What?!
In order to save the Bounts,
I went to the World of the Living
without permission.
There are still comrades further inside!
All right!
I’ll do something.
Go on and get away!
Thank you!
Hey you! Are you all right?
Who are you?!
Aren’t you…Rantao?
I…
Rantao… You belong to
the Bount Investigation Unit!
The Investigation Unit has already
returned to Soul Society.
What are you doing here?!
She’s running away!
Where do you think you’re going?!
After her!
She’s a traitor!
After her! After her!
I will distract the Soul Reapers,
so you must escape during that time.
Huh?
If you go outside,
there are sure to be other Bounts.
Run away with your comrades.
But then you…
I’ll be fine…
Take this.
The Bounts have much more power
hidden within them.
This will help to draw out that power.
I’m really sorry.
You’ll be forced to
endure suffering now,
but I’m sure one day…
So you must live!
Over this way!
Don’t let her get away!
Now! Run up those stairs
and get outside!
In the end, I was captured
and taken to Soul Society.
And Seireitei held me
solely responsible
and put a seal on the case.
Subsequently, the Bounts
took advantage
of the powers hidden in
the item I gave the boy,
and perfected the method
of controlling dolls.
With their new power,
the Bounts planned their revenge
and tried to attack Soul Society
countless times.
However, they were rejected
each time by the Soul Reapers
and their numbers dwindled
to almost nothing…
and even the record of their existence
was erased from Seireitei.
But I have never forgotten the Bounts.
Then you came to Soul Society.
You are that boy…
Don’t you remember?
How you got that mark?
That mark is sure to have appeared
when you activated
a certain item.
The one who gave you
that item was me!
I have lived to save you.
There is no Soul Reaper remaining
who remembers the past!
Soul Society has changed, too.
Now, I can…
What a thing to bring up now!
It’s not a lie!
If you use the power
of the Jokai Crest
which was sealed in the Seireitei…!
The power of the Jokai Crest?
I absorbed that energy into
my body long ago.
Impossible!
I’ll use that power to destroy
the Soul Reapers.
What?!
This Spiritual Pressure is
coming from Rantao!
Is she in a battle?
The only Bount remaining is Kariya.
So Kariya is sure to be
where Rantao is!
Whatever action you planned
is too late.
The only Bount remaining is me.
Even if it’s only you,
I will save you!
So stupid! You created Bounts.
I intended to deal with you after
you had seen Seireitei destroyed
and repented for what you had done.
But you can die right here!
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Ishida suddenly disappeared!
Let’s go find him.
We don’t know when
a Quincy arrow will explode.
What if we find it the instant
before it blows up?
We’ll forget it and run far away.
Good idea.
Horrible things just flow
right out of your mouths, don’t they?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I’m hungry.
All right, everyone!
Squad 10’s famous specialty!
Just made!
Come and eat!
Yay!
Just as you requested, Orihime,
I made lots of bean paste dishes, too.
Thank you!
This stinks!
Hey! Don’t just stand there.
Hurry up and take your portion!
Why is Hisagi serving everyone?
Shuhei seemed to have time,
so I asked him to help!
Huh?!
Aren’t you just being used?
Do as I say!!