Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
I cannot believe this!
Do you realize what you have done?!
Look at this!
This was broadcast nationwide
the other day.
Nationwide!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Do you know how much dishonor
you brought upon this school
with the airing of this footage?!
Mr. Kagine!
Kurosaki and Kuchiki were on television,
so I can understand why they
were called in.
But there's no reason
why Inoue and I should be here.
Weren't you there, too?
By coincidence.
We met them by accident
and were not involved!
Why you--!
Trying to save your own necks!
And so, we're going back to class.
Let's go, Orihime.
Oh...then me, too.
Not you!
You were with him,
but did nothing to stop him.
You're just as guilty!
W-What's the fuss
just 'cuz we were on TV?
"Just 'cuz"?!
Haven't you realized that
you're here precisely
because of that lack of
awareness?!
I'm flabbergasted!
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault...
I couldn't stop Kurosaki who was
so determined to get on TV...
It's my fault.
I really tried my best, but...
Ohh... Don't cry, Kuchiki.
I understand.
It's not your fault.
I don't care what you do to Kurasaki,
so please spare me...
Hmm?
Hey, you brats!
Do you know what will happen
if you run away?!
You boys!
And now, even Kuchiki has disappeared!
Principal!
Now, now, you don't have to
scold them so severely,
just because they
were on TV.
I cannot believe you all!
All's well that end's well.
It's all thanks to you, Rukia.
Oh please...
Stupid, don't compliment her.
She tried to sell me out.
But thanks to her act,
you were able to slip away, too.
That's right.
It was just an a…c…t.
I wouldn’t dream of selling out
a friend like Kurosaki.
Why you--!
By the way, Kurosaki,
may I speak with you?
Huh?
Please excuse us, everyone.
What was that?
Kurosaki and Kuchiki...
Huh?
Are they seeing each other?
No way!
At least, Kuchiki wouldn't.
But something's suspicious...
No way!
Huh?!
There's no Hollow.
What's going on anyway?
Maybe that cell phone
is broken.
Strange...
There was an order that
a Hollow had appeared.
Hey, spirit!
Huh?!
You didn't exterminate
a Hollow by any chance, did you?
H-Hollow...you mean that
scary bug-like thing?
I-I was so scared...
I thought I was
gonna pee on myself!
Stay away from me!
I'm asking you what happened!
Wait, Ichigo.
Did someone defeat
the Hollow and save you?
And if so, who was it?
I-I was so scared,
I had my eyes closed.
I don't know!
Wha--?!
Why you...!
Well, it's Konso time.
Let's go!
Huh?! What's a Konso?
W-What's that sword for?!
Third place?
You always do so well.
Wow! Orihime,
you're that smart?
She doesn't look it though, huh?
Wonderful!
You are my Hime, after all!
Oh....
Well, besides the girls doing well,
no one betrayed us by getting into
the top 50.
Look carefully.
Huh?
W-W-What?!
23rd place?!
No way!
How can you be up there?!
Shut up.
I study because there's nothing
else to do at home.
Nothing to do?! No way!
I always ask you to hang out!
I get it!
That's what you were doing
when you turned me down!
You pervert! Nerd!
A person like you deserves
thick glasses like these--
No thanks.
So you actually study, Ichigo?
Well yeah...
It can be tough when you
have orange hair like this.
I see. I guess there are
all kinds of things in life.
A person like you deserves
a nerd headband--
I said I don't want it!
Fine! I get it!
I'll never ask you to hang out again!
Hey Chad, c'mon and join me.
You're not in the top fifty, right?
Huh?
What?!
I-I never thought you guys were so evil!
Not once!
I'll never play with you guys again!
Uh-oh...you made him cry.
If we're evil, what about
the guy who's number one?
Ametatsu Ishida?
Never heard of that name.
It's Uryu.
Uryu Ishida.
You know him?
He's in our class.
Huh?
Forget it, Orihime.
He never remembers
a person's name or face.
Let's go.
Hmm... was there such a guy?
He's not there!
Urahara!
Why don't you answer when I call
you at times like this?!
You always show up when
you're not needed.
And you call yourself a businessman!
Hmm...
I wanted him to take
a look at my Soul Pager.
I can't tell if it's broken or not.
Found him!
Let's go sing some karaoke.
The worker there--
Kurosaki!
Come with me a moment!
Rukia is quite aggressive.
I think they really are
seeing each other.
It's a Hollow.
A Hollow? I hope it's really
there this time.
Shut up! Let's go!
Sorry!
After all this...!
There was no Hollow again!
Shut up!
Get back into your body now!
Damn!
Do something about that
useless cell phone!
Are you saying that it's my fault?!
I just relay whatever comes
through the Soul Pager.
So hurry it up and fix that thing!
I want to as well.
Breaking up?
How unsightly.
Good evening, Kurosaki...Kuchiki.
Who are you?
How do you know our names?
Kurosaki, you can
see spirits, right?
W-What're you saying?!
A new Hollow has appeared.
What?
H-He's right. It's an order.
Which way?
Over there.
You don't know such a basic thing
and you call yourself a Soul Reaper?
Go!
It disappeared.
Just what are you?!
Uryu Ishida. A Quincy.
I hate Soul Reapers.
What?
Don't you understand?
I'm telling you...
Ichigo Kurosaki...
I hate you.
Damn! Just what is that guy?
You don't know such a basic thing
and you call yourself a Soul Reaper?
Why do I have to
be insulted like that
by someone I met for
the first time?!
I'll get that bastard
the next time we meet.
That bastard?
Umm...what did he say his
name was?
Ishida... err... Willy?
Nope. That's that celebrity
no one likes.
Ishida...
Ishida again?
Inoue! Oh...no...
Uryu Ishida, right?
Huh?
Yeah him! You're well informed, Inoue.
I'm really not.
But Ishida and I are in
the Handicrafts Club.
So I know his name,
at least.
Handicrafts Club?!
See? That's Ishida.
T-That's him.
And he's in the Handicrafts Club?
Yup. Look.
Conveniently, Michiru brought
a torn stuffed animal.
Very convenient turn of events indeed.
Watch.
I-It's fixed! Thank you, Ishida!
No problem.
It's no big deal.
Huh? I'm sorry.
He'd be nice if he didn't
say things like that.
He sure is weird.
Say, Ichigo...
Did something happen
between you and him?
Just something minor.
It's no big deal.
I see...
You plan on following me home?
Ichigo Kurosaki?
Damn, you knew?
When did you notice?
From the time you and Inoue
watched me from the door.
Hmm... I'm impressed.
You're something else.
Your spiritual energy is
always leaking out, like a fool.
Even a monkey would notice.
What?!
I think you're lacking the ability
to detect those with high spiritual energy.
The proof lies in the fact
that you didn't notice
my existence until today.
Sorry about that.
I'm bad at remembering people's faces.
I'm not talking about that.
From the time you entered school
I knew that you had unusually high
spiritual energy.
Also, that you became a Soul Reaper
around the middle of May.
And...I know Rukia Kuchiki's
true identity.
Spirit Ribbons!
Yes, Spirit Ribbons.
The compression and manifestation
of spiritual energy
in the atmosphere.
And...
What's this…?!
Your Spirit Ribbon.
You don't know?
Soul Reapers' Spirit Ribbons have
different colors.
Let us duel, Ichigo Kurosaki.
You or me...
I'll show you who is
the stronger.
And also, that Soul Reapers
aren't necessary in this world.
Urahara Store
It's a duel! Rock, Paper...
Scissors!
Look away, then show!
Rock, Paper...
Scissors!
Look away, then show!
I guess it's your turn
to sweep, Jinta.
I didn't lose!
I haven't lost yet!
I said it's two out of three!
You never said that! Never! Owwee!
Oweee!
Quit complaining!
One more time, I said!
What...are you doing, Jinta?
Oh...nothing...Te…Eh…Mr.Tessai!
Huh?
You have some business today, Kuchiki?
Huh? What's the matter?
Is Urahara here?
It's Kuchiki!
What can I do for you–?!
"What can I do for you"?!
I called you time and time again,
but you never answer!
So I've come!
Oh, I'm sorry.
We've been quite busy lately.
Say, what happened to
that spiky-haired guy?
Well, I don't like him,
so it's better that he stayed away.
Hey Jinta!
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
A duel? You and me?
That’s right.
Hah! That's ridiculous!
What?
Why do I have to do such
a stupid thing?!
I don't know what kind of grudge
you have against Soul Reapers,
but it’s got nothing
to do with me.
How unexpected.
You're trying to get out of it?
Don't try to goad me into it.
Besides, it would be no contest.
I see. I just remembered.
You're a Soul Reaper who received
your powers from Kuchiki...
You're a substitute Soul Reaper.
Without her authority,
you can’t even lift a finger.
What?!
Quincy?
I haven't heard that name
in a long time.
It has a nostalgic ring to it,
doesn't it?
It's been nearly 200 years
since we heard that name.
What's it mean?
Quincy...
A tribe which once existed scattered
throughout the world,
which specialized in destroying Hollows.
They became extinct about
200 years ago.
Extinct?
Yes... Humans who had powers like
Kurosaki sensed the existence of Hollows
and began to train
to fight against them...
that's how the tribe started.
Like Soul Reapers,
their mission was to
destroy Hollows.
However, there was one
distinct difference
between them
and Soul Reapers.
And that was, whether to
kill Hollows or not.
The Soul Reapers seek to purify
Hollows with their Zanpaku-to
and allow them to cross over
into the Soul Society.
But Quincys sought to totally kill them.
When you think about it,
it was a very human thing to do.
Hollows devour human souls.
They hurt and kill
our friends and family.
So why would you want to send them
to the Soul Society peacefully?
It was only natural that
they opposed it.
So they always tried to kill Hollows.
They believed that they were
avenging their comrades.
But due to that belief,
they were destroyed.
Fine!
Let's do it.
We'll have a duel!
Hey Ichigo!
Huh?
You may've been obeying Rukia's orders,
but how dare you stuff me in
that bag?!
Let’s change.
Hey, wait! Not again?!
Got it!
Slimy...
Kon, watch me.
I'm gonna kick his butt!
Huh?
All right, explain it to me...
the rules of this battle.
Hurry!
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
I'm Rukia Kuchiki, the prettiest girl
in Bleach!
Rukia's Q & A Corner
I'd like to read you some
letters today.
First from Momoko in
the Nakano District.
"Rukia, what is the secret
to your beauty?
This is not the place for that!
– I'm waiting for your letters!
– No way!