I think I’ll go for a dip
in the outdoor bath!
Rangiku…
I’m coming to be "killed."
Drive it that way!
We’ll drive it away from the town!
Lieutenant!
Were any of the townspeople injured?
No!
Good.
I’ll let you handle it from here.
Lieutenant, where are you going?
To my next job.
“Editor-in-Chief”
Abarai hasn’t turned
in his manuscript?
No, sir.
Have you contacted him?
We haven’t been able to reach
him since yesterday.
That bastard.
What shall we do?
It’s our job to figure that out!
Y-Yes, sir!
For now, go to Squad Six's Barracks
and see how he’s coming along.
Yes, sir!
Man, they’re all useless.
I see you’re busy as
always, Hisagi.
Kira, I’m sorry. Mind
waiting a minute?
Sure. I’m not in any hurry at all.
Hey, send this to the printer.
Yes, sir.
Now then… So this is the Men’s Soul Reaper
Association’s budget for this term?
I don’t think there are any issues
with anything in there,
so please put your stamp
of approval on it.
As an officer of the association,
you know I can’t do that.
I’m telling you, it’s fine.
The Vice-Chairman, Third Seat Iemura,
is a very meticulous man.
Well, all right.
There don’t seem
to be any issues.
“APPROVED”
Thank you for doing this.
Well, I’ll be going now.
Wait, Kira.
It’s been a while.
What do you say we go for a drink tonight?
I’ll be happy to join.
Any seats available?
Yes. Wait just a second.
If it isn’t Lieutenant Hisagi.
Captain Unohana.
What brings you here?
It’s ladies' night out!
Huh?
Come to think of it,
I haven’t yet thanked you for the
other day, Lieutenant Hisagi.
Thanked you? Did you
do something, Hisagi?
Well, when we all went on a
picnic, he made lunch for us!
What?
I may not look it,
but I’m a good cook.
It was a 60 out of a 100 points!
The meal was ordinary.
It lacked creativity!
It needed more…
Lieutenant Kusajishi!
We’re sorry.
It tasted all right, honest.
“All right,” eh?
Well, we must be going.
Bye bye!
Now, let’s get going.
Yes, let’s!
Ladies' night out?
What do you suppose they
were talking about?
Hisagi, you take on
too much work!
You’re busy enough already
being a Squad Lieutenant
and running the Seireitei Bulletin.
Why accept the Executive
Chairman position
for the Men’s Soul Reaper Association?
I don’t mind. I do it
because I enjoy it.
No, it’s not okay!
And why are you making lunch for the
Women’s Soul Reaper Association, anyway?
That’s…because they depended
on me. What was I to do?
It’s not easy being
a talented man.
I’ll bet you did it to get Matsumoto’s
attention, didn’t you?
W-What are you talking about?!
Work isn’t something you
do for its pros and cons.
Besides, if you do your best,
there’ll always be someone
who will take notice of you.
Is that how it works?
You sure it’s not just them
taking advantage of you?
Oh, shut up.
Excuse me! Can we
get another bottle?
Coming up!
And therefore, in order to
solve the disappearances
that have been occurring
in the Rukon District,
it’s been decided that you three
will be sent to investigate.
Yes, sir!
So I get to be the leader
of this group, right?
There is no need for one.
Huh? But no matter how you
look at it, I’m the leader here!
How did you come to
such conclusions?
Hisagi, keep an eye on Matsumoto
to make sure she doesn’t
do something crazy on her own.
I’m counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Captain, that’s mean!
When do I ever do crazy
things on my own?
Always!
Now, now, Rangiku. Calm down.
Captain Hitsugaya put
his trust in me.
People do take notice of one’s
hard work. I knew it.
Boy, the captain can be so rude!
The skies are looking like rain,
so we’d better hurry.
What? But I’m a bit tired.
Let’s rest a bit.
You rested just a while ago.
We’re almost at our destination,
and it’ll be difficult to move
once the sun sets.
Man, I wish I could’ve come later
with Isane and the others.
Lieutenant Kotetsu is leading
the rescue party,
so she has a lot of material
and people with her.
That’s why we’re
going on ahead.
I know that.
Cold!
Let’s hurry!
Oh! I hate this!
If we’re in the field shown
on this map,
then our destination is somewhere
around here.
There’s no need to rush.
It’ll take time for Isane and her group
to catch up with us anyway,
so let’s take our time to look around
and investigate along the way.
Hey! I think the rain has stopped!
Lovely, isn’t it?
Shuhei, stop looking so serious over
there and take a look around you.
Uh… Sure.
Wait a second.
We’re in the boonies of the
Rukon District with no one around.
Is it possible that Rangiku is
enjoying her time alone with me?
And that smile…
Is something wrong, Shuhei?
Uh, no… Nothing wrong, ma’am!
Stop thinking silly thoughts,
Shuhei Hisagi!
W-Wow… Sure is a soothing
sight for the soul, isn’t it?
Do you like it?
Huh?
Uh…Y-Yes.
I mean, it’s a lovely landscape.
Yes, it is. We’ve kept this landscape
this way for a long time.
Uh… I see.
Shuhei!
Rangiku?
Are you from these parts?
Yes. I run an inn over that way.
Oh, is that so?
What do you say, Shuhei?
Since we’re here,
want to spend the night?
What?!
You have a room, right?
Yes.
W-W-Wait a minute!
That wouldn’t be right, Rangiku!
Oh come on, what’s the problem?
We’re going to be here on a mission anyway.
What’s wrong with staying at an inn?
I don’t want to sleep outdoors.
Yeah, but…
Show us the way.
Yes.
Let’s go! Shuhei!
W-Wait…
Wow…
This is quite a nice room.
Excuse me.
Let me make your tea.
We’ll manage.
Oh, thank you.
It’s okay, I don’t mind doing this.
We’re guests here, so why
not let her make the tea?
But…
Let her.
O-Okay.
What’s gotten into Rangiku?
Could she be jealous?
Now that I think about it, when the proprietress
and I first started talking,
she suddenly wedged
herself in.
No, but…
Shuhei, why are you so out of it?
Have some tea, too.
R-Right!
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Hot!
I’m so sorry.
Was the cup too hot?
Oh, it’s fine.
This is nothing.
I see… My sincerest apologies.
Oh no! We have to cool it down!
Are you all right? Does it hurt?
Um… No…
Proprietress, could you
get us some water?
Yes! Right away!
Uh… Rangiku, your…hand, it’s…
Shuhei, you mustn’t let your guard
down with that proprietress.
Huh?
Just do as I say, okay?
Okay.
Just as I thought, Rangiku is conscious
of the proprietress.
Which means, she thinks of me as…
Whew! I'm so full!
Huh? What’s the matter?
You weren’t hungry?
No, that’s not it.
Drat. I was so conscious of her
my food wouldn’t go down.
You need to eat.
Or else, you won’t be of use
when trouble occurs.
I don’t want that to happen.
You won’t be of use when
trouble occurs.
I don’t want that to happen.
R-Right!
Excuse me.
I’ve come to take
away your trays.
Thank you. I’ll be finished shortly.
Shuhei, you don’t need to
try to be so nice to her.
We’re the guests here.
I know, but…
That’s all right.
Please take your time.
Say, there’s an outdoor bath outside
this room. Is it usable?
Yes, it is.
You’re welcome to use it.
Yes!
Please enjoy.
The bath’s just right.
I knew it. Rangiku is jealous
of the proprietress.
It proves how interested
she is in me.
No, no, no!
Wait! Calm down, Shuhei Hisagi!
We’re here on a mission.
Don’t think of such perverse thoughts.
Work comes first!
Get your act straight, Shuhei Hisagi!
I need to confirm the agenda
of this mission!
I think I’ll go for a dip
in the outdoor bath!
I’ll go for a dip.
In the outdoor bath.
In the…
Here they are.
What’s a hot spa inn
without yukata?
I’m going in first, Shuhei.
Right…
Shuhei, I think you already
know this, but…
If you peek, I’ll kill you.
R-Right!
Calm down, Shuhei Hisagi.
Let’s sort out the situation.
The weather worsened,
and the sun set.
By perfect coincidence,
there was an inn.
So, we decide to
stay the night.
Okay, so it’s simple logic.
I get it, I get it.
It was totally out
of my control.
Rangiku, too, had no choice but
to stay the night with me.
That has to be it.
And as for the proprietress,
it was nothing more than Rangiku showing
concern for me as a colleague.
By the way, Rangiku!
Where is my room?
Surely we’re not going to stay
in the same room, are we?
We’ll be together.
I asked earlier to have the
bedding set out together.
What?!
What? You don’t want to
share a room with me?
N-N-No, that’s not it at all!
Then there’s no problem.
The water feels so good.
What’s the matter?
Why are you sighing?
Uh, um… How’s the weather?
There’s a lovely moon out.
I-I see.
The breeze feels nice, too.
Nothing beats an outdoor bath.
Th-That’s nice.
Why don’t you come in too?
You must be tired, right?
What?
You haven’t taken any
days off recently.
Working is fine, too, but you need to rest sometimes,
or you’ll wear yourself out.
Rangiku is worried
about me.
Just as I thought,
people do watch!
It isn’t just Captain Hitsugaya!
Rangiku understands
how I feel as well!
I’m so glad I did my best.
WHY DON’T YOU
COME IN TOO?
She just said, “Why don’t
you come in too?”
Does that mean…she wants
me to join her?!
Wait, just a moment ago, she
said she’d kill me for that.
If you peek, I’ll kill you.
Or should I not take
it literally?
If you peek, I’ll kill you.
I think I get it. Could that “I’ll kill you”
have meant she was inviting me?
I’ll…kill…you.
No, no, it couldn’t
be…but…but…
What should I do?!
Rangiku?!
Rangiku,
I’m coming to be “killed.”
Growl!
Haineko!
Shuhei! Come here quickly!
What’s going on?!
A Hollow?!
This was the culprit in the
string of disappearances!
What?
Growl…Haineko!
Reap...Kazeshini!
You did it, Shuhei!
I don’t get it. What’s going on?
The proprietress of this inn
was the culprit responsible
for the disappearances.
What?!
At first, I wasn’t certain,
so I came here to investigate,
only to have her suddenly
appear before us.
I didn’t see that coming.
And what’s more, she was definitely sending
you some strange Spiritual Pressure.
Strange Spiritual Pressure?
Didn’t you feel it?
Not at all.
I knew it.
You see, only men have
been attacked.
Handsome ones at that.
That’s why I had you come
with me as a lure.
It turned out to be
the right decision.
What?! Nobody told me
anything about that!
They say to deceive your enemy,
you have to deceive your friend first.
I wanted to do this after Isane and the
others arrived and we were set up,
but the enemy snapped
at the bait.
Huh? What’s the matter?
That’s cruel, Rangiku.
Sorry, sorry.
But you were the only one
who could pull off this role.
There aren’t any other
good-looking guys with great skills.
And you just forgave her?!
When Rangiku said that,
I didn’t feel bad about it.
Do you think she meant that?
Maybe she’s still pulling the
wool over your eyes.
Kira, it’s not good
to be so cynical.
You sure?
Kusajishi.
Hey, listen.
Kenny busted the wall,
can you help us repair it?
Why me?
Because I heard that if we ever need
help, we should ask you, Hisa-hisa!
That’s probably Matsumoto who’s
spreading that around.
Yup! And also…
Shuhei is the only person
I can count on.
That’s what she said!
I see.
So Rangiku’s counting on me.
It’s not easy being
a talented man.
What? Hisagi?!
Okay! Where’s the site! Let’s go!
He is hopeless.
Hisa-hisa sure does prove his title
as the Best Male Soul Reaper!
Wow, that’s impressive.
Guess I have a lot to learn from Hisagi.
Yup, he is! In our last
ladies' night out,
he got our unanimous vote as
the most useful errand boy.
That’s his title?!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers.
Shuhei!
Yes, Rangiku?
Can you carry these to
the Squad Barracks?
Gladly!
Shuhei!
Yes?
Stamp these for approval,
will you?
Gladly.
Shuhei!
Y-Yes?
Can you wash these for me?
He seems to be losing his
health lately. I’m worried.
It’s your fault!