Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Where am I?
I ain’t…dead?
I see you’re awake.
Yoruichi…
I see. You saved me.
Thank you.
You should thank your own life force
to have survived those serious wounds.
Wounds?
That's right.
I was cut up pretty bad.
I forgot!
That’s right!
Fool! Don’t move!
Don’t you know how badly
you’re hurt?!
Chad’s in danger.
I gotta save him…!
Calm down!
Chad is fine!
So are Inoue and Ishida.
Huh…?
He was lucky to have fought who he did.
Chad was injured,
but he’s alive.
Inoue and Ishida were able to get away
from the enemy with nary a scratch.
I see.
Stay put in this barrier for a while.
Maybe you’re right.
After all, half of your innards
were crushed.
If this wasn’t covering your chest,
you would’ve been sliced in half.
I had…that?!
I was surprised…
you were still carrying
this thing around.
Did I really have that on me?
What? Weren’t you carrying it?
No, actually…
Even when I fought Renji,
I had a feeling this thing saved me.
So I wanted to keep it
as a good-luck charm.
Huh?! H-Hey!
Ichigo, let’s throw this away,
after all.
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
But that thing saved my life.
I want to keep it as
a good-luck charm.
No!
Hey you…!
So it sank in the underground aqueduct.
Oh, Hanataro’s in Squad 4.
He’s the enemy,
but he’s a good guy.
He healed the wounds
I got from Renji, too.
How come I have this, though?
I was so sure he threw it away.
I’ll keep that.
Huh?
Why? I finally got it back.
Hand it over! No excuses!
Y-Yes, sir. Please take it.
I doubt that it’s possible, but…
we can’t be too careful.
Still, you’re amazing after all, Yoruichi.
What do you mean?
You’re so tiny,
yet you carried me here.
It’s easy when I turn
into my original form.
Oh, right. Your original form…
What?
Original…form?
Right.
I haven’t shown it to you
and your friends yet, have I?
All right. Since we’ve come this far,
there’s no need to hide it.
I’ll show you…
my true form!
A-A…w-woman…?!
I see you’re pretty shocked.
Can’t blame you.
You probably thought
I was a man by the way I spoke.
No matter how many times
I reveal my true form,
it’s always fun.
Everybody gets shocked stupid.
B-But ain’t you a cat?!
Cats don’t talk. Use your head.
Now, then…
Enough surprises for now.
Now I’ll show you…
how I carried you.
First, about this thing…
Put somethin’ on! Clothes…!
Oh, sorry, sorry…
I haven’t worn clothes in a while,
so I forgot.
You’re a lot more naïve
than you look, though.
Is this the first time
you’ve seen a woman naked? Hmm?
Shut up!
Are you sure? If you don’t look at
a firm, young female now,
you might never see one again.
Bug off!
Look!
Ugh…no…bleeding…ugh…
Are you okay?
With all that screaming,
no wonder your wounds opened up.
Shut up! Put on your pants!
Most people put on their pants first!
Ugh… Agh! Bleeding!
Clothes are so uncomfortable.
So you used this to fly
and bring me here?
That’s right.
There’s not another like it,
not even in the Soul Society.
Awesome, isn’t it?
But why is it that
you have such a valuable object?
You change forms, heal wounds,
and possess a priceless object.
Yoruichi…
What are you, anyway?
I am…
T-This Spiritual Pressure is…!
Him!
It’s coming from the Shishinro,
Repentance Cell.
Stop, Ichigo!
Ganju and Hanataro are headed there!
I gotta save them!
What can you do, in your condition?!
Who else is gonna save them?!
Fly!
Ichigo!
The fool!
I sensed a faint Spiritual Pressure
moving toward the Shishinro,
so I wondered what powerful presence
had slipped in, hiding his force.
But it’s only a tick.
No! Rukia! You can’t go!
Let me go, Hanataro!
I must stop that Shiba man!
He’ll be kill…
Rukia!
My stay in the cell has weakened me…
I can’t move!
He’s damned powerful. Bastard!
Just facing him makes me tingle.
Measly tricks won’t work against
a superior power like his.
It’s now or never!
Take this! Tears of Blood--!
Begone.
My sword is not for the purpose
of killing vermin like you.
Hold it!
It seems you did not understand me.
I told you to be gone.
Shut up! We wouldn’t run
in fear because of you!
Not Shiba men!
I see. You’re from the Shiba clan.
O-Oh, no!
Forgive me for easing up on you.
I can’t let you leave here alive.
What’s he going to do?
From so far away?
No! Big Brother!
Scatter…
Thousand cherry blossoms
Wha--?
The blade vanished!
Ruuuun!
Ganju?!
Please stop! Brother!
Phew!
My, my. How dangerous.
Why not leave it at that,
Captain Kuchiki?
C-Captain Ukitake!
Yo, Kuchiki! You look thinner.
Are you okay?
What’s the meaning of this, Ukitake?
Hey now, you tell me.
Unleashing your Zanpaku-to
in a place like this
is a level one forbidden offense.
Even if it’s to repel Ryoka,
what were you thinking?
Wartime exemption allows
the use of Zanpaku-to.
Wartime exemption?
Has the Ryoka infiltration become
so serious?
A Ryoka killed Aizen?
W-What Spiritual Pressure is this?
Clearly, it’s of a captain’s level!
But it’s unfamiliar to me!
This Spiritual Pressure…
It can’t be!
Ichigo…
I-Ichi…
You okay, Hanataro?
Sorry I let you go on ahead.
It was rough on you…
No, not at all. I’m fine.
Rukia…
I’ve come for you.
What kinda look is that?!
I came to save you!
Try to look a little happier!
Let’s go, Brother.
Just move one step from there.
Just…Just try coming after me!
I…
I’ll never forgive you!
You’ll die, someday.
So stay there and live
as long as you can.
Fool!
I told you not to come!
I said I’d never forgive you if you did!
You’re all cut up…!
Fool!
Yeah, you’re right.
So…
yell at me all you want later.
After I beat him!
Ichigo…!
What?
After I came this far,
you’re not making me leave, are ya?
But…
I ain’t leaving! Forget about it.
I came this far just to save you.
It don’t matter
if you want to be executed!
I’m saving you,
even if I hafta drag you out!
From here on in,
I’m ignoring all your opinions!
Got that, stupid?!
Wha…?!
What's your problem?!
You can’t listen
to the one you’re saving?!
What kind of a tyrannical rescuer
are you?!
Shut up! The rescued shouldn’t complain!
Just tremble like you’re supposed to
and say, “Save me!”
“Save me”?
I do not tremble!
You’re still the same, aren't you?
You still don’t listen to anything I say.
What do you expect?
All you do is worry about me.
Worry about yourself now,
for a change.
Ichigo…
Don’t worry. I won’t die.
I think I’ve gotten a little stronger.
Byakuya…
Who is he?
He's not the one…
He's not the man who flashed
through your mind.
He’s nothing.
Just an ordinary Ryoka.
I’ll kill him.
That will be the end of it.
And this trifling fight will be over.
You sure are taking it slow.
Rukia and I did all that talking,
but you never attacked.
Who do you think I am?
Are you saying I have to look
for an opening to kill you?
Don’t talk so big, boy.
A-Are you all right, Hanataro?
Y-Yes…
Oh? You aren’t perturbed
by this Spiritual Pressure.
You seem to have improved
a great deal.
I don’t know how you acquired the powers
of a Soul Reaper again.
You could have stayed peacefully
in the human world.
But you came here to throw away
the life so narrowly saved.
I ain’t gonna throw it away.
I’m gonna defeat you and leave.
I told you not to talk so big, boy.
Gone?!
Flash Step!
I can see you…
Byakuya Kuchiki.
How’s that, Mr. Kuchiki? Surprised?
I can read your movements!
Don’t get swell-headed over
a lucky blow.
You fool.
Wanna see…if it was just luck?
Amazing! Simply amazing!
Ichigo is fighting Captain Kuchiki
as his equal!
Yes, Ichigo’s growth is amazing.
His read of Brother’s Flash Step alone
was astounding.
But Brother’s power is more than that.
The Flash Step is mere child’s play
for Brother.
I must stop them before Brother
fights in earnest.
Or Ichigo will be…!
I see.
It seems you’ve improved more
than I thought.
You leave me no choice.
Before it goes to your head,
I’ll show you…
The power gap that
you could never bridge,
never in a thousand years…
No, Ichigo! Run!
Scatter…
That’s…!
You…!
It’s been a long time, eh?
Byakuya boy.
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Yoruichi, how’d you transform
into a cat?
Did you use a special power?
I just wore a cat costume.
I see. So that was it.
I see, I see. A costume.
That’s pretty easy to transform--
– What?!