Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
You seem to think…
that you already know my strength
just by fighting me once…
Let me tell you something.
When the ranked Lieutenants
and above are sent outside,
our powers are severely limited so that
we don’t adversely affect the human world.
My strength right now is
five times greater than before.
So no matter how strong you become,
there’s no way you can defeat me!
So that means that attack there…
was the best you’ve got?
Didn’t even affect me! Not at all!
Thank you!
If 11 of these are what I’m dealing with,
I think I can handle it!
You idiot…
Ichigo, you…
Are you all right?
Yeah, this is nothing.
I-It's amazing. I can't believe it…
That he can remain standing
in his condition.
Damn…
My vision is getting blurry.
And my legs are shaky.
Quit shaking, dammit!
You talk big,
but it seems standing is
about all you can do.
It's over!
If you didn't exist…
If she didn't meet you…
Rukia wouldn't…
have to go through all this!
Oh!
Get away, Ichigo!
I won't let you get away!
Ichigo!
It's impossible…
It's impossible, after all.
Taking on a Lieutenant…
Kira…this…
It's Abarai's Lieutenant insignia.
He disappeared in the middle
of the meeting.
I was worried,
so I went to the Squad 6 barracks…
and this is what I found…
in front of his room.
Are the Captains aware of this?
I haven't told them.
I see.
I thought about telling Captain Aizen,
but I didn't want Abarai
getting punished because of that.
Until we know what's going on,
that was wise of you.
Kira, what could this mean?
To remove this before he left…
It must be very important.
Abarai's been mulling over
the Kuchiki case a lot.
In any case, I'll look for him, too.
Stubborn bastard.
You want to save Rukia that badly?
Idiot!
Not “want.” “Will”!
Quit messing with me!
Rukia's crime became more serious
because you stole her powers!
Do you understand?
It's YOUR fault!
It's your fault that Rukia will be killed!
I know that!
That's why I…
will save her!
I finally see it.
His limit is three attacks.
Now listen up…
For anything that can be
called an attack,
the stronger the attack,
the more limitation will be put
upon the number of the attacks.
Limitation?
Indeed.
Just like a gun can
only be fired six times.
A missile only once.
Repetitive attacks are always
limited to certain numbers.
Which means…
when he extends his Zabimaru is one.
And after that, he uses it extended twice.
And…
After the third thrust…
his Zabimaru will return
to its original state.
Let's test it.
It doesn't have to be
the same number each time.
What's crucial is the
maximum number of attacks.
When a battle is intense…
the enemy will always use
the maximum number of attacks.
You bastard!
One!
If you can figure out what that
maximum number is,
that will be your chance.
Two!
The most important thing is…
the last of his repeated attacks.
The moment before the
repetitive attacks start again.
Three!
Damn!
At that moment,
your enemy will be completely open.
This is the end, Renji!
I told you, you cannot defeat me!
He countered me!
Why?
You look shocked that
I countered your attack.
Looking for an opening
between thrusts is good.
And your timing was perfect.
So… Why weren't you
able to beat me?
There's one answer.
You are slower than me.
You can't overcome
the difference in our power.
It's as simple as that.
Understand?
You cannot save Rukia.
Ichigo!
That terrific Spiritual Pressure just now…
I hope Ichigo is all right.
Abarai's Spiritual Pressure…
Huh?
This Spiritual Pressure is…
Follow me!
I-Ichigo…!
He's alive… Ichigo is alive!
Damn right! He dodged the blow.
You are truly stubborn.
Why you…!
You really tried to kill me just now!
Of course! I’m now driving you
to the corner.
I'll keep pushing you and pushing you.
So that you can use it
anytime, anywhere.
This attack.
Don't be ridiculous!
That was a fluke.
No way can I keep using it
whenever I want.
You have to use it
whenever you want.
Now listen, you have just begun
to summon your true Zanpaku-to
and learn to fight.
You have potential.
But right now,
you're only at
the level of a Third or Fourth Seat.
In order to stay even with
a Lieutenant or higher,
you'll have to be able to use it at will.
Easier said than done…
It took everything outta me then
and I don't remember much
about when I did that.
I know that.
That's why.
That's why…
Why you--!
Yes, I'll keep pushing you…
so that you can remember…
that attack!
The target has hit the rocks.
Healing Squad dispatching!
Dammit! He's pitiful!
What's the matter, boss?
Not yet.
Dammit! At this rate, I'll really…
I'm disappointed, Kurosaki.
I'm so disappointed.
Your sword exhibits only fear.
When you counter,
it's because you fear being killed.
When you attack, you fear killing.
And when you try to protect someone,
you fear letting them die.
Yes.
The only thing your sword
speaks of, is dumb fear.
And that's not it.
What you need in battle is not fear.
Nothing will come of that.
When you counter,
you don't let them cut you.
If you protect someone,
you don't let them die.
When you attack, you kill.
See? Can't you see?
The reflection on my sword…
is sheer resolve to kill you.
That'll do.
His Zanpaku-to…
It's howling.
They're crying out.
They can't wait to cross swords.
See, you've got it…resolve.
I-Ichigo…
He intends to continue fighting?
But he's different.
He's totally different from before.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Renji.
I’ve got resolve.
This time, I WILL get you!
What's with him?
All of a sudden…
Was it like that last time?
No, it's different.
That time, he was just exuding
spiritual energy at random.
This time…
it's calmly controlled.
And without a doubt…
it's much stronger.
When you counter,
you don't let them cut you.
Why you--!
When you protect someone…
you don't let them die.
When you attack…you kill!
Why you--!
He did it!
He got me…
What was that just now?
Zabimaru…
Damn it!
I’ve got resolve.
Resolve…
It hurts.
My body feels heavy.
My legs…
won't move.
My arms…
won't rise.
Damn it…
Have I lost?
Damn…
Dammit…!
Rukia… I…
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Next time, Abarai's shocking past
will be revealed.
A youth's bittersweet memories
and a sentimental secret story!
Don't miss it!
Kira! Hinamori!
Don't give a preview that
can cause misunderstandings!
Hey, that sounds like fun.
Don't you take it seriously either!