Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Why?
Why have I been abandoned?
Orihime!
Oh, I'm glad you're okay!
Huh?
It's because someone attacked
a girl in high school yesterday.
Jeez!
I was worried that it might have
been my precious Orihime!
It's scary, isn't it?
Who's doing it?
Is someone just assaulting
people randomly?
You're the assailant!
Okay, sit down!
I'm going to introduce
a new transfer student!
KYOKO HAIDA
Sister…
This is Kyoko Haida!
She's your classmate now!
I want you all to
get along with her!
Pleased to meet you.
URAHARA'S SHOP
A high school girl was attacked?
That's right.
It seems there was a pink bear
on her cellphone.
How did you find about that?
That a weird detail to know.
That's a secret.
Let's just say, it takes
a thief to catch a thief…
Oh?
So do you think this has something
to do with the sword beasts?
The sword beasts are unstable,
so it's very difficult to
track their spiritual pressure.
I'm not certain, but a sword beast
may be involved.
A Zanpakuto is
attacking humans…
This isn't good.
Hello.
Huh?
Oh, hello.
Could you tell me your name?
I'm Orihime Inoue.
Pleased to meet you.
Orihime!
What are you doing?
Lunch is going to end soon!
Oh, okay. I'm going right now!
Care to come with us,
Miss Haida?
Huh?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
I just heard from Ms. Ochi that
Miss Haida is incredibly smart,
and is great at sports.
What? That's amazing!
Come to think of it…
She solved that difficult problem
in math class easily today.
So did Ms. Ochi tell you
why she transferred here?
She said she didn't really know.
As mentioned in our report,
we found a high school age girl
in the back alley of 3-chome,
and have taken her into custody.
She is in a state of shock,
but she is in stable condition.
Is it the spiritual pressure
of a Sword Beast?
No.
It seems different from
a Sword Beast.
What's going on?
We might find something out.
Let's go down.
Okay.
That's…
Whoa!
It's like she plays for the NBA!
She really is great at sports…
I'm sorry! Are you all right?!
Time out!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to shove you.
Are you all right?
Can someone take her
to the infirmary?
We're almost at the infirmary.
The nurse is really great.
She'll make you
feel better right away.
It's just a little further.
And it was just terrible.
Are you all right, Miss Haida?
I knew it.
Huh?
I knew that you were special.
Special?
That power…
You're a special human
with special powers.
You are worthy of me.
Worthy?
I have special powers too.
We both have special powers.
I'm saying that
we should be friends.
I'm not a special human.
Like you said, I do have
a strange power, but that's it.
Besides…
That's what people
call "special"!
In that case, should I tell
everyone about your special power?
I'm sure that all of your good
friends will be terrified of you!
Why?
Why would you say that?
Kyoko!
Mai…
We were always together.
She was the only one
I could call a friend.
Kyoko!
Things about school,
things about home,
things about
the people we liked…
She was a friend that
I could talk to about anything.
We trusted and
accepted each other.
Even if I wasn't a normal person,
I never doubted that
she would accept me.
That probably won't
be on the test.
Huh? But…our teacher
said it would.
Really? But this one's
going to be on the test.
I can tell.
You're kidding.
You said that you
wanted this, right?
Oh? You did that for me?
Thanks!
See you later.
Mai!
Kyoko?
Are you going out with him?
He's bad news.
Huh?
No one knows about this,
but he has lots
of other girlfriends
and he's careless with money.
Sorry for saying this.
But I can't stand to
see him deceive you.
So don't go out with him.
Mai?
I'm scared.
Huh?
You're creepy, Kyoko.
Umm…
Stay away!
Mai…
No…
Don't come near me anymore!
Miss Haida…
Miss Haida?
Hey…
Can't we be friends
regardless of
whether or not we
have special powers?
Huh?
Let's be friends.
Miss Haida?
This is…
Why?
Miss Haida!
Was that a Zanpakuto?
Rukia, just now…
Yeah.
It was just for a moment,
but that was the same spiritual
pressure we sensed last night.
Let's go, Ichigo.
It's near Karakura High School.
What did you say?!
I hope you weren't
taking her seriously.
If I hadn't shown up
at that moment,
you would have made
the same mistake again.
Those who are always surrounded
by friends have it so easy.
They can't understand
the feelings of people
who have been abandoned,
like us.
But…
What is it?
She said that she
wanted to be my friend.
She didn't really mean it.
You think so?
Of course. Have you forgotten?
You and I have
been traumatized
by the experience
of being abandoned.
That's why we were
drawn to each other.
I understand your irritation.
Express your feelings.
There is no need to hesitate.
If you hesitate,
your heart will be crushed.
You want to kill that girl
Mai Suzuki, don't you?
No, I don't!
I'll carry out your wish.
Wait!
Stop.
What are you doing?!
Hey, could you take over
my cleanup duty today?
– What?
– And then, that girl…
Huh?
Was that?
What are you going to do to me?
Stop!
Why?
Kyoko, I was trying to
grant your wish.
Why are you interfering?
No… This is not what I want.
Please forgive me.
I was wrong.
Mai… It's all right. I…
Stop! Help me!
You're got it all wrong!
Listen to me, Mai!
Listen to what I have to say!
No!
Mai!
No one will believe me.
Good bye.
Your heart is completely
synchronized with mine now.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
You're mine now.
Miss Haida!
It's you!
What have you done
to Miss Haida?!
Bring her back!
Silence!
Ichigo!
Rukia!
I thought it had
an odd spiritual pressure.
It was because
it was fused to a human.
Who are you?!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I'm a Soul Reaper Substitute!
I see…
I've heard things about you.
What should we do?
We must be careful.
But…
If she's been completely
absorbed by the sword beast
and has lost her human heart,
we have no choice but to kill her.
Wait!
What is it?
Miss Haida hasn't lost her heart.
What?
She's suffering.
Stop the nonsense!
Yeah, it's faint, but I feel it.
What should we do?!
Please!
Release Miss Haida's heart!
That's out of the question.
Then will you take her place?
I might let Kyoko Haida go
if you say you'll be mine.
You should already know.
What?
No one can belong to you.
Neither me, nor Miss Haida,
nor anyone else…
It's just an illusion you created.
What do you know?!
My master despised me
and died without me by his side.
I was trying to die without
anyone ever finding me.
I won't listen to your ideals!
I will absorb everything I can!
I will gain power and show
everyone what I can do!
Stop being selfish!
Miss Haida!
She's suffering.
Inoue!
– Huh?
– Use your Sotenkishun!
You should be able to separate
the sword beast from its host!
Okay!
Sotenkishun!
I reject!
Now, Ichigo!
Getsuga…tensho!
I wiped Mai Suzuki's memory.
Miss Haida!
Miss Inoue!
Let's walk home together.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You want to stop by a sweets shop,
don't you, Miss Inoue?
What? How can you tell?!
By the look on your face.
Where's Ishida and Chad?
Chad found a stray cat and
took it to the animal hospital.
Uryu has the stomach flu.
What? I was with him
all day yesterday.
This is bad! I need to gargle
and wash my hands.
I think it's too late now.
Wait, what's this? Oh no…
I feel like I'm getting stabbed…
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
YAKITORI
Lieutenant Sasakibe…
Why do you look so gloomy?
To tell you the truth…
Gonryomaru manifested himself
because he didn't like how
I disappear into the background.
Recently, I was thinking
about that too…
What?
When did you get here,
Lieutenant Sasakibe?
No one notices me…
I understand!
I'll do something about it!
TO BE CONTINUED