Hey...
Take this.
Dunno if you can actually use it, but...
Zack...
This time, I will be useful to you.
I have to find Doctor Danny
and get that medicine.
A rabbit?
I have to hurry.
Where am I?
Rachel...
You came back.
Eddie?
Don't get in my way.
You want to die, don't you?
I can't die yet.
No.
You need to die right here.
Please, Eddie. Let me out of here.
Eddie!
I have to hurry, or Zack will...
You're in the way.
What's going on?
A mirror...
You're in the way.
Zack?!
Even if he did swear to God,
do you have knowledge that
God would choose his promise?
And if God's choice does
not match your wish...
What would you do then?
There is no God in this world.
No...
No! No!
Stop it!
I want Zack to kill me.
I don't want to let Zack die.
But if God doesn't accept that...
If there is no God...
what am I supposed to do?
Why are you here alone,
Rachel Gardner?
What of Zack? Did you leave him behind?
Where's Doctor Danny?
Let me see him.
I did see him earlier, but I
don't know where he is now.
Don't lie!
I am not lying.
But because his actions
have been quite uncalled for,
I did relieve him of a few of his medicines.
What? So the medicine...
I have assumed possession of it.
Please...
I want the medicine.
Do you think you can obtain it
that easily, Rachel Gardner?
Give me the medicine.
You would point at me the knife
that you left Zack without?
How do you know this is Zack's knife?
Of course I know.
It was I who brought him here.
Zack's body is riddled with wounds.
He was deceived...
...by none other than you.
No...
Danny was an intelligent, prudent man.
That is why he was more familiar
with this place than anyone else,
and why he never acted of his own volition.
And what about Isaac?
He is very simple and pure.
And for the sake of your wish to be killed,
just look at how he has suffered.
All of this has happened
since he met you, has it not?
I... didn't do anything.
I find it a mystery, Rachel.
Just who are you?
You have no answer?
Perhaps you do not believe in God at all.
That's not true!
Then why do you give no answer?
Because you cannot answer,
Rachel Gardner.
In your desperation to be desirable to God,
your heart was steeped in falsehood.
You are a witch who has deceived us angels!
No! I'm not!
In that case, I will pass
judgment upon you now!
The witch trial shall start.
God desires the untainted,
and you stand here today
under suspicion of being a
witch who deceives us angels.
You are a witch, and you
formed a contract with Issac.
Is this not true?
It's not.
My promise with Zack...
...was a promise sworn to God.
It's not a contract.
You would hide behind God as a shield?
In that case, you must not forget...
...that it is God who will decide!
Now, are there any who wish to give
testimony regarding the defendant?
Yes! There's one right here!
Let me tell you just what
a terrible little girl...
...this criminal is.
Okay, then, I can give you...
...lots of reasons why Rachel is so wonderful.
But since she's so stubborn,
I kind of want to do
something mean to her, too.
It seems I'm the only one here who
can testify as to who she really is.
Rachel! I'm on your side!
Doctor...
Very well.
Who will give their testimony first, then?
Father...
I'd like to go first.
No fair! Let me go first!
I can't do that.
The one who's suffered the most here...
...is me!
R-Right...
Then, Catherine Ward, present your testimony.
Sure! Just leave it to me!
Listen to this, everyone!
The person you see here looks like
no more than a sweet little girl...
But on the inside, she's black as midnight!
Without a doubt, she is...
...a bona fide witch.
I'm not a witch.
So shameless!
You're so good at telling blatant lies
with a straight face, aren't you?
Everyone!
Take a look at this!
Zack, do as I say.
She used Zack as a tool!
Isn't she awful?
That's not what it looks like to me!
This won't pass for evidence.
You people...
...need to keep quiet!
Order in the court.
Catherine Ward, do you
have further testimony?
Of course I do!
I was torn away from my role as judge
by this little witch's hand.
Isaac Foster was a criminal
that tamed by this girl.
It was so pitiful to watch that I
went down to the floor they were on.
And then this girl...
...went and shot me!
A judge being outmaneuvered...
...and shot by a criminal is something
that can't be allowed to happen.
You are an unbelievably cunning woman
in the guise of a shameless criminal.
You can be nothing but a witch.
I never intended to outmaneuver—
Quiet, bitch!
I'd like to see the rest
of your video, Cathy.
What are you saying now?
Would you show us the rest?
Cathy, how do you explain that expression?
You look pretty happy there.
That's right, Eddie!
Cathy was happy!
You can't hide it.
This is my area of expertise.
The true nature of
Catherine Ward, the judge, is...
Shut up! That's not what it was!
What aggravated me the most
was that this woman...
this woman's criminal nature
made me so happy!
That's your own problem.
That's rich coming from
the criminal of criminals,
the one who tore me from my role as judge!
So what is it you want to see done?
This girl is a witch.
I want her sentenced to water torture.
Go on, scream!
Let me see your face trembling with fear!
Make me feel even more
excited than I did then!
What's the matter? You're scared, aren't you?
Don't hold back! Beg for help!
How?
How can you keep that look on your face?
Cry out and scream, you witch!
That is enough!
Father, her punishment is not yet fini—
It is not your place to punish her.
Stand down.
But she's still—
Next to testify will be Edward Mason.
Can you give testimony regarding
the defendant's crimes?
Yes, Father. I sure can.
I can tell you what I love
about her... and what I hate.
Then begin.
Okay, so, Rachel is really cute!
I like her voice better than anyone else's.
And she's just like me!
You buried that bird from
Zack's floor, didn't you?
Yes.
See? We really are the same!
I knew we'd get along perfectly!
And she said she wanted to die,
so we want the same thing!
So I tried to approach her in various ways.
I made her a grave, wrote her a letter...
I even prepared a coffin
filled with flowers for her.
But Rachel...
...was a bit stubborn.
She wouldn't listen to anything I said.
This is a trial.
No one wants to hear your
sob story about lost love.
Shut up! No one asked you!
I wanted Rachel.
Everything I did was for Rachel.
But it wasn't the same for her.
Everything she did was just for herself.
You're cruel.
You're cruel!
You said so sweetly that
you wanted to be killed,
but it was all for yourself!
You're so selfish! So self-serving!
And you're stubborn! Really stubborn!
I don't understand why it has to be Zack!
And then I got cut down by Zack and
ended up in a grave all alone!
You got rejected.
I love graves,
but that wasn't what I
wanted to happen at all.
But then, I finally realized the biggest
difference between me and Rachel.
She doesn't know what happiness is,
so she ignores all happiness!
Isn't it possible that makes you a witch?
No.
You're a witch.
This is what I want!
I want Rachel...
...sentenced to death by spikes.
What's the matter? Are you angry?
Please, say something!
Talk to me!
I'll do anything!
Why do you ignore me?
If that's how it is...
Then just fall right now!
That is enough!
I-I'm sorry...
But... But it's your fault, Rachel!
The witch has swayed your heart,
Edward Mason.
No! I...
I can see your heart as it
strives to accept this witch,
while fearing her at the same time.
Rachel, say something!
Talk to me!
Next to testify will be Daniel Dickens.
It's finally my turn.
Doctor, where's the medicine?
You seem very calm.
Are you relieved to see me?
Danny! Do you have any
intention of testifying?
Yes, Father, of course.
After all, no one else has bore
witness to Rachel's true heart.
I need to tell everyone what
truly makes her so charming.
It's ridiculous that I have to tell them
something that should be so obvious.
No one here understands Rachel.
It all began in the counseling
room where I first met her.
At that time, I had been searching
for the perfect eyes...
Eyes that were alive, but forever dead.
And then I met her.
Recalling it now makes me feel so happy.
There are no other eyes as beautiful
and mesmerizing as these.
Like a peaceful spring
in the deep darkness...
Her eyes, blue yet dark,
absolutely stole my heart.
And then I realized...
...that her eyes were the perfect living, yet
forever dead, eyes that I'd been looking for!
After all, she is... Her heart
is undoubtedly abnormal!
Her soul is hopeless, beyond salvation!
Daniel Dickens...
Her soul can never be saved!
Daniel!
Danny!
If you want to know why,
it's because her soul is—
Stop.
Her soul can't be saved.
She's the one who does
the stealing, after all.
Without mercy or compassion,
all she does is steal to
fill the emptiness in her.
That's all her soul can do.
Ah, what beautiful eyes!
Can I look at them?
Yes! These eyes!
You're the real you right now!
You'll be fine as long as you're with me.
Let's live together, Rachel.
Daniel Dickens!
Forgive me.
Have you finished your testimony?
I can speak in far more detail
about what makes her so charming.
Enough! I don't need to hear any more!
The witness may stand down!
It'll be fine, Rachel. Remember what I said?
The real you
is not a soul that should be stolen.
These testimonies have been decisive.
Rachel Gardner, your verdict has been reached.
You heard their testimonies, did you not?
Danny's, in particular, was quite clear.
He has looked after you
longer than anyone here.
He spoke the truth, but denied nothing.
He adores you.
That's not my fault.
Doctor Danny made his own choice to—
Do you not think you are the
one who has acted selfishly?
Eddie's testimony spoke to that.
He told us how you live only for your
own goals, with no thought for others!
No...
And Cathy, after being deceived
by you, found herself bewitched.
Such a proud woman,
and look how she ended up.
No!
I will now proclaim the verdict.
Rachel Gardner is a witch!
She will now be burned alive!
I'm not!