I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Everyone…
Zeig Dih, Dalk!
It's okay to get them, right?
It can't be helped.
What happened?! Answer me!
Damn! I told them to wait…
At any rate, let's go after them!
Are you all right?!
Get a hold of yourself!
I-I'm very sorry…
We tried to capture him, but…
The Ryoka suddenly…released his doll…
28	01:03:02:21	01:03:03:20
I'm going to call
the med squad right now.
It'll be all right.
The enemy is still nearby!
We’re going after him!
This fighting style seems
to belong to the Bount
that Kira fought in
the World of the Living.
He's powerful… Be careful!
Yes!
Captain Hitsugaya! Rangiku!
Renji!
Well, well. Everyone's together!
Abarai, why are you here?
We followed
the Bounts' Spiritual Pressure.
The Bounts' Spiritual Pressure?
Oh, that's right! We had you around!
I’m around indeed! That’s my job!
What's the meaning of this?
Oh, you weren’t told about it,
were you, Captain?
This is the mod soul with the Bount sensor
that Ichigo and the others…
were using in the World of the Living.
Pleased to meet you…
A mod soul?
Why is it in something like this?
Well, it'll take a while to explain…
Are Ichigo Kurosaki and the others
using this to search for the Bounts?
Yes… He's a lot more useful
than he looks!
How rude!
All right.
Abarai… Sorry, but could you
lend him to me?
Huh?
What?! You're going to carry him?
Buddy-buddy!
It's not as if he doesn't match you.
No! Matsumoto, you're going to carry him!
Aww, how boring…
Umm… I don’t mind lending him to you,
but what should I do?
Sorry, but take care of
my injured squad members.
Yet again, I can’t fight?
Don't rush, don't rush…
Oh? This time I'm with a lady?!
Well now, it sure is more thrilling
than being with a stuffy man!
Well, excuse me!
Oh? Are you jealous?
Is this way all right?
Yes! There is no mistake!
What should we do?
Surround him!
We don't know how much
they learned about Soul Society…
But we're probably more familiar
with the geography.
Understood.
Squad 10, calling all groups!
The Bount that we're tracking
is currently at North District 2
Center Street Number Two.
Target is heading south!
Groups 1 and 2,
change course and head around
through East District 6!
Groups 3 and 4,
take a detour and close off all roads!
All other teams are to hurry from
North District 3 to the target!
All squads begin the siege!
The encircling net is getting tighter.
Say, what should we do?
Oh my… His Spiritual Pressure!
What's wrong?
It suddenly weakened!
What?! Where is it?
That way!
It's in the direction of East District 7.
Hey! The Spiritual Pressure
didn't disappear, did it?
Yes! It just weakened and
is on the move!
Could it be?
Why are we walking down here?
I'm going to rust…
We can buy some time by doing this.
I want to let loose more!
I'm still not satisfied!
That's good enough.
Right now,
we have to search for Kariya.
We can't leave him alone.
Oh my, how unusual…
What?
You referred to him without a title!
There are times like that.
Did you get into a fight?
It's not that simple!
Then what?
It's a difference in the way we live…
Hide!
Oh!
Did you find him?
No!
Be careful!
Right!
Their hands have
reached down here as well…
What are you going to do?
Are you still going to run around?
No. We will break through,
no matter what.
And for that, we must strike!
How is it?
It seems that he's going through
the underpass.
As expected of a captain,
even if you're small!
You take notice of things
that others wouldn’t!
Once he's noticed,
he'll probably surface…
It would be great if we could track him
in the underpass.
Groups that are investigating
the West District,
go to the underpass as backup!
This is Group 3!
Changing course to
the northwestern roads!
Going as backup!
We've discovered the Ryoka’s doll!
Where?!
West District 6 Street Number Three,
the third road heading from the north!
All right! Lure the target to
a wide road and wait for backup!
Let's go!
Yes!
Oh my… I was just getting excited
about this.
How worthless.
Group 3! Someone answer!
The Spiritual Pressure disappeared again.
It seems that the battle ended…
with our loss.
No need to say unnecessary things!
Yes…
All squads, don't be rash!
If you encounter the target,
restrain yourselves!
Tell them to be sure to wait for backup!
This is Group 6!
We have arrived at
South District Street Number Four!
Any sign of the Ryoka?
No…
There it is! I've captured
the Bount’s Spiritual Pressure signal!
Which way?
Umm… It's that way, so…
it's around the area of
South District Street Number Four…
What?!
That's the place we're communicating
with right now!
Group 6! Target confirmed!
He's in your area!
Understood!
He's nearby! Don't let your guard down!
Right!
Requesting all groups to South Street
Number Four as backup!
It seems there's a butterfly for
each of the teams…
Dalk, I want you to crush
those butterflies.
All of them at once!
My, the poor things…
But fine. I'll try!
Captain! The Hell Butterflies!
What?!
This is Group 7!
The Hell Butterflies are…
suddenly…
Woah! It seems that he has discovered
our means of communication!
Our communication with
all groups has been cut off!
Please respond! Lieutenant!
Hello, boys! Let's play!
Dalk!
Here I go!
This is horrible!
Hey! Are you all right?!
He's still breathing!
Over there and over here, too!
At any rate,
they haven't been finished off…
Why is that?!
Take care of them!
Captain!
Mod soul!
What about
his Spiritual Pressure?
Yes! It's headed this way!
I see…
Captain, what are you going to do?
He knew we were moving
as an organization…
That's why he's probably waiting.
Waiting for the commander to come
once all of the subordinates
have been defeated…
Are you planning to go alone?
That's right.
Matsumoto, take care of the rest!
All right.
Please be careful.
Good luck.
Are you the captain?
Yeah… You’ve sure done it.
I held back.
I don't like laying my hands
on young people…
Then I’ll thank you for that.
But I'm not going to hold back!
Here I go!
I have no choice.
Zeig Dih, Dalk.
Hello!
Okay…cute boy!
I'm going to play with you!
My, my. You sure are impatient.
No! You’ve scarred me!
You're pretty good.
But you shouldn't do that.
A disobedient child shall
be captured and punished!
Frost unto the Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Here I go!
I caught you!
Huh?
No! What is this?! It's cold--!
Dalk!
Dalk! Return for a moment!
It's difficult to separate and
combine while you're frozen!
I'm all right! I can still fight!
I'll deal with it somehow!
Stop, Dalk!
Prepare yourself!
Don't ignore me, Boy!
Dalk, pull back!
It's all right! I can do this by myself!
My burning heart won't lose…
to a hunk of ice!!
Dalk!
Sorry… I lost…
No… You did well.
Thank you.
I'm glad that I was with you.
It's different from the report…
What?
I heard that a Bount will disappear
when he loses his doll, but…
Why?
What is it?
There were various roles within our tribe.
My role was to train the young people
to become full-fledged Bounts.
There were some who grew up well
and there were those who didn't.
I just remembered something
from long ago…
What is this all of a sudden?
And that's not answering my question!
Yeah, that's right.
The reason why I haven't collapsed
is because…
Dalk still isn't dead!
What?!
What's that?
It's Dalk.
This is her core.
She lives within this steel.
As I expected of a captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
It seems I can't go on further
without using my full strength.
I have something that I must do.
I'll eliminate you if you say
you're going to get in my way.
That's your own reasoning!
Quite a bit of Dalk's power
remains in this ax.
I'm going to pump my Spiritual Pressure
into it and strike you!
Let's go, Dalk!
This is--?!
This Spiritual Pressure…
It seems this is where
the real battle starts.
Then I'll get serious, too!
Bankai!!
Daiguren…Hyorinmaru!
As I expected of a captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
However…
I can't lose just yet!
You still want to continue?
I must go after Kariya…
You’re body can't endure
the reishi you've gathered.
Then I've got to settle this
before it breaks!
Let's go, Dalk!
This is it, huh?
I lose…
What were you planning to do
once you caught up to Kariya?
There wasn't anything I could have done.
Whatever the case,
that is a dispute between
Kariya and me!
Where were you planning to go?
A future with no wars…
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Ikkaku, we finally received the order
to search for the Bounts!
Finally! All right, let's cut loose!
Umm…
We can do whatever we like…
to the Bounts we find, right?
Umm…
Yeah! It's first come, first served!
Hello?
I'm going to get them first!
What?!
Should I let them know that
there's only one enemy left?
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I haven't appeared in the main story lately!
I couldn’t help but come!
Kon!
Forgive me…
Kon, come back!
I can't be sipping tea at
a teashop at a time like this!
I won't forget the days
I've spent with you…
KON, YOU’RE DISAPPEARING!
THE NEW SPRING
AND SUMMER COLLECTION!