Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
This Spiritual Pressure…
Is it the Old Man's?
All right!
Here I go!
Snap!
How dare you do that!
It looks like things
won't be so easy.
How lame.
I thought that you were tougher.
Is this all you've got?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's hard for me to fight women.
I see, but I can't just go on
matching your pace.
You're not paying
attention to this side!
This is really difficult.
Hey! Stay still for a little!
No way!
Stop us if you can!
Don't run around
with those things!
Whoa…
I can't play with you
for much longer!
Are you referring to this?
This?
That's right.
If you hand those over,
I'll play tag or whatever
you want to play.
So hand those over to me.
You're going to play with us?
Yeah. If you hand those over.
Really?
Really.
Come on, you're good kids.
It's a promise, okay?
– Pinkie promise!
That's right. Pinkie promise!
You're good kids.
– Yay!
He fell for it!
What bad kids…
It's about time you died.
How sly of you!
What's this?
I thought I could
have a little fun,
but is that all you've got?
Hey, hey!
You can't defeat Ken
if you stay on defense!
Shut up.
Stay out of this, Yachiru.
But it's true!
This is no fun to watch!
They're not giving it their all.
Just keep quiet and watch.
Yachiru is right.
Do you really want to settle this?
We can win by not losing.
Oh?
You weren't planning on winning
from the beginning, huh?
I'm so bored of this!
I'm glad you could come,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Muramasa…
I knew you'd be here.
It seems that we are
destined to cross blades.
It might be a good idea
for us to settle this here.
I don't care about that.
Everyone is relying on me
to save Old Man Yamamoto.
Sorry, but I can't play
with you for very long.
I'm going to settle this quickly!
Oh? I look forward to that.
Getsugatensho!
This Spiritual Pressure!
Ichigo must've
encountered Muramasa.
That aside, these two
are fighting strangely.
They're coming after me,
but I don't think that even they
think their attack level
is effective.
I should test them.
What's wrong?
You can't do anything?
Can't do anything?
That's not true.
Are you still trying to act tough?
That's all I would need to do.
You have no intention of
cutting me, do you?
What are you saying?
Two swords with different ranges.
Using that difference is how
I fight using my Zanpakuto.
In other words,
that's how you fight.
But you haven't tried to
take advantage of that.
The short sword uses its speed
to confuse the enemy
and the long sword
delivers the final blow.
This is how Zanpakuto like you
are supposed to fight.
But only the short sword
is attacking
and the long sword isn't
doing anything at all.
It's as if you're avoiding
my attacks.
It's not that I can't do anything.
I think you're just
defending yourself
in a way that I can't do anything.
My, my…
It sure is troublesome
to have a skilled master.
Mister! This way!
Follow our clapping!
Come out.
I'll get angry if you don't.
That's fine!
Try and get angry!
– Go!
Hado 31, Shakkaho!
All right!
I caught you!
Damn it…
Doing this is just
prolonging their pranks.
Prolonging?!
Don't you understand,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
That's not enough to defeat me.
You cannot move on
until you defeat me.
Come on…
Hit me with everything you've got!
Okay.
Here I go!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Who knows?
What does it matter?
Anyway, let's end things here!
If you can do it, that is…
Bring it on.
Growl!
No!
You're not going anywhere!
Hado 31!
Shakkaho!
Snap!
Your goal was never
to get rid of us.
You wanted to lure us here
and keep us around.
That's your goal, isn't it?
More, Ichigo Kurosaki…
I thought I told you to
hit me with everything.
Show it to me!
Your true Getsugatensho…
Since you figured it out,
I guess I have no choice.
What?!
Sorry, but even if you slash me,
I'm going to keep on going.
You two stay away!
We can't do that!
We're not letting you
go any farther.
Got that?!
You kids sure don't listen.
Don't worry.
There seems to be a lot going on,
but none of it concerns me.
I'll stay here.
Let's let loose!
Thank goodness!
Hado 58!
Tenran!
Bakudo 30!
Shitotsusansen!
What are you doing?!
Their goal was to
separate us from Ichigo.
That I understand.
But what do they want
with Ichigo Kurosaki?
Judging from Muramasa's
Spiritual Pressure,
I don't think he's
attacking to kill.
If anything,
he's waiting for something.
It's as if he's trying to
make Ichigo settle things.
If Muramasa is trying to
do this on purpose…
Muramasa's true goal is…
He's waiting for…
Ichigo's greatest technique!
Getsuga…
Don't, Ichigo!
…tensho!
The barrier…
So this is why!
What's going on?!
I don't understand!
Muramasa's goal
was to get you to
use your Getsugatensho
while Hollowfied.
What?!
It seems he fused
your power with his own
to create a massive
amount of energy.
He was trying to destroy
Genryusai's barrier with that.
Destroy?!
Didn't he create that barrier?!
It seems we've made
a grave mistake.
That's right.
It seems he's gotten
the better of us.
Sensei…
His goal is to gain access
to my mental world.
Your mental world?
Th-Then Muramasa…
infiltrated you?
You planned this scenario to arrive
at this moment, didn't you?
You truly are
a Captain-class Soul Reaper.
You're quick to understand things.
That's right.
My goal is to learn the memories
resting deep within
Genryusai Yamamoto.
In order to do that,
I need to enter his mental world.
But when I appeared,
he set up a barrier
and severed himself from
the area around himself.
And at the cost of
losing consciousness,
he prevented me
from entering his mind.
I had expected that.
So I manifested
the Soul Reapers' Zanpakuto
and caused chaos in Soul Society
in order to create a plan
to destroy Genryusai Yamamoto's
barrier in the meantime.
I made all of
the Soul Reapers and Zanpakuto
believe that my goal was to
cause a Zanpakuto rebellion,
and that I had confined
Genryusai Yamamoto.
Then I let things cool down
and left you to save
Genryusai Yamamoto.
N-No way…
Everything went
according to my plan.
I thank you, Soul Reapers.
And Ichigo Kurosaki.
You bastard!
What's the meaning of this?!
Our goal was a lie and
you were using us to
achieve your own goal?
Would there be a problem
if I said that was the case?
A big problem!
Now that I know everything,
I have no intention
of complying with you.
You tricked us…
That's not fair!
Liar!
Wait.
Calm down!
The Zanpakuto are fighting
with each other!
Sorry, but I've gotta go.
I don't care to talk
to you any longer.
Do whatever you like.
We'll do that!
What?!
What are these flames?
Ryujinjakka…
This is terrible.
Even Old Man Yama's Ryujinjakka
has fallen into his hands.
Farewell, Genryusai Yamamoto
and Soul Reapers.
There is nothing you can
do against me anymore.
Sensei!
What exactly is Muramasa?!
Muramasa…
He is a Zanpakuto with
the power of Mukojochu.
He can enter an enemy's Zanpakuto
and control it however he wants.
He is especially unique!
And his true goal must be
immediately be stopped by
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
What is a Mukojochu?
A mukojochu is
actually a worm that
lives parasitically in
the human body.
Muramasa's ability has a similar
name because it allows him to
get inside of people's mental
worlds, in the same way that
the mukojochu worm gets
inside of people's bodies.
A worm?
Oh?
Hey! Don't compare me to a worm!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Yoo-hoo! Sado!
Say, which outfit would
be easiest to fight in?
It's been a while, so I forget!
Huh?
Anything is fine.
Take a look, Sado!
It's the outfits I'm going to be
wearing from the next episode…
I thought I'd focus on changing
the length of my cape!
– Or would you prefer
– Come on, Sado,
– this embroidered one?
– choose one!
Anything is fine…