Ichigo and his group had been
defeated by the formidable Espada
when the captains of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads arrived.
Under orders from Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto,
they came to Hueco Mundo to
engage the Espada in battle.
Kenpachi, who appeared
in front of Ichigo,
battled Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora Gilga.
The battle between
the two warriors,
who both find joy in
fighting strong opponents,
gradually increased in intensity.
However, Nnoitora's Hierro,
boasted as being the hardest
among all the Espada,
could not be cut despite
repeated attacks.
Kenpachi searched for
somewhere to cut
even as he was being pressured
by intense attacks.
Your sword cannot cut me!
That's all there is to it!
There are many types of
people in the Soul Society.
I've come across annoying
guys like you who say,
"your sword can't cut me"
on several occasions.
But…
I still haven't met someone whose
eyes and throat can't be cut!
How many times are you
going to make me say it
until you're satisfied?
You can't cut me!
You can't understand it, can you?
It's impossible for someone
who's had his head run through
to not be dead.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
You're exactly right.
Bastard!
That's where his…
It simply passed through my head.
Do you understand?
That was the limit of what
you could do, Soul Reaper.
What the hell are
you laughing about?!
Sorry about that.
I was just so happy that
I couldn't help but laugh.
Happy, you say?
Yeah.
It's no fun if I'm
not only unable to cut you,
but you won't die
if I cut you either.
But at least now I know that
if I cut you, you'll die.
And that's enough.
Now I can look forward
to cutting you!
I told you,
you can't cut me!
Idiot!
You still have quite
a bit of power left.
Kenpachi is…
taking the fight to him!
Yup! This is how it should be!
Idiot!
How many times
do I have to tell you.
You can't cut me—
He finally cut him!
Zaraki!
What's the matter?
Are you surprised now that you
were suddenly able to cut me?
But don't get the wrong idea
because of one lucky strike.
Kenny is finally acting
like himself again.
Kenny is just getting started!
What is…that Spiritual Pressure?!
What's the matter, Inoue?
Come on, one more round.
Come at me.
Don't get carried away!
Kenpachi!
Damn it…
It seems…
I'm finally getting the hang
of your hardness.
"Getting the hang of"?
Did he say,
"getting the hang of"?!
Does he think he can
cut me just with that?
I've been a bit
out of practice of late.
My muscles shrank, and I seem to
have forgotten how to control them.
Thanks!
Thanks to you,
I got a good warm up.
Let me return the favor…
with this!
Damn it!
Kenpachi?!
Look out!
Incredible!
No…way…
Fool…
You ripped off my eye patch,
so I wasn't able to hold back.
What is up…with that…
eye patch…of yours?
It was a seal.
A seal?
I kept a seal on
my Spiritual Pressure
with this eye patch
and kept it under control.
So I could savor the fight.
You're still standing?
Are you alive?
Or is it just that
you haven't died yet?
You idiot!
I'm not…going to die!
Not by the likes of…
the likes of your sword!
The wind…
An immense Spiritual Pressure
is gathering.
Kenny…
I…
I'm not going to die!
Pray, Santa Teresa!
His arms…they've doubled.
That's not fair!
And his wounds…have closed.
You're kidding me.
Those were wounds
inflicted by Kenpachi
after taking off his eye patch!
Kenpachi!
Hey…
How's it feel to see an Espada's
sword release for the first time?
Say something, Soul Reaper!
Nice Spiritual Pressure.
It's been a while
since it's felt like my blade is being sharpened
by Spiritual Pressure!
Is that so?
Then try and cut me with that
so-called sharpened blade!
What?
Is that all you've got?
That can't be!
Kenpachi…
Ken…ny…
That sword had nothing behind it,
Soul Reaper!
He's out cold.
Is it over?
Oh well, I guess I'll
clean up the leftovers.
Yachiru!
Wait, Inoue!
What was that?!
Was I just repelled?!
That ability…
Did Inoue have that
among her Shunshunrikka?!
Santenkesshun!
Huh? What's that?
You'd better look behind you.
Kenpachi!
That's one arm to start.
Damn you!
Careful. If you attack me,
Kenny will get angry!
I'm not angry, stupid!
So you were playing dead?
That was low.
Shut up!
I was thinking.
If you've got four arms,
any of them could block my sword.
That's no fun.
I was trying to figure out how
I could keep you from blocking me.
But…I thought about it,
and I couldn't come up
with any good ideas.
That's why…I decided to cut off
each of them one at a time.
If you cut them all off,
he can't fight, Kenny.
What?! You're right.
I made a mistake.
I'll leave one arm.
You'll leave one arm?
What's with that?!
How stupid.
Don't worry about it.
That arm was the last one
you could cut off.
No, to be more accurate…
Huh?!
You'll end your life,
killed by these four arms,
without ever having cut
even one of them off.
Because you're…
weaker than me, Soul Reaper!
You're a lightweight!
Getting blown around like that!
You're terribly hard to hit
with my attacks!
Or are you afraid and
simply running away?!
Huh?!
Damn it!
What's the matter?
You've had enough already?
You fool.
Didn't I tell you?
You can't cut off a single arm.
You're just going to be slashed
to death by these six arms!
Kenpachi!
Kenny…
It's a wonder you two didn't get
lost in the Garganta, Yachiru.
Byakki smelled very sweet,
so we just followed that.
That must be…
Yeah, his Ambassador Seaweed
bean paste cake.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Please!
Iba?!
What brings you
here so suddenly?
I've heard that animal programs are
popular in the World of the Living!
Can you do something to get
– the captain on one of those shows
– Now… Let's do it.
to improve Squad 7's popularity?!
What?! You mean…
CUTE!
Something like this, right?
Oh my!
I think it's a different
kind of popularity.
I must say,
it's quite a fine program.
– What?!