We'll need their help
to defeat Kintoki.
You must take back your friends.
Help them remember the man
called Sakata Gintoki.
I knew you'd be there for me.
You've finally remembered Master Gintoki.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Well, yeah...
I guess.
Thanks for everything.
Take care, Odd Jobs.
Having trouble?
Want me to lend you a hand?
Leave it to Odd Jobs Kin-san
and he'll save the day.
Kin-san's Kintama
No, thank you.
Otose-sama needed me to run an errand.
You're pretty slow for a robot.
Why don't you stop meddling
and go get some maintenance done?
Master Gintoki would never be
so forceful with a woman.
That's why he can't score any girls.
I've overcome that weakness of his.
Since you're refusing my advances,
and now that people
are starting to talk,
I won't spare my ace.
Be a good girl and listen to me.
You should know.
It's better for everyone
when I'm in charge.
You're just a piece of junk.
If you can't even say
"I won't spare my rod"
so it turns into a dirty joke,
you'll never be better
than Master Gintoki.
I've already used my rod.
Damn, you're using some old oil.
That explains why you can't
understand what I'm saying.
Don't blame me.
I have to eliminate all loose cannons.
I will win the hearts of every
citizen and unite the team
so I can lay down my
roots all over this town.
That is the mission I've been given.
Don't worry.
The dog and Gintoki will
suffer the same fate.
I'll erase your existence
from everyone's memory.
Master Gintoki can't be erased.
Your weak points were in
the instruction manual.
You will no longer be able
to brainwash anyone.
If your mission is to erase
Master Gintoki and replace him,
my mission is to live
with Master Gintoki and his
friends until I perish.
Really? Too bad then.
Why don't you ask your Gin-san to
come now, in your final moments?
Master Gintoki...
Your worthless leader can't hear you
if you whisper in such a puny voice.
You are just
a piece of
junk.
Master Gintoki is
far more sadistic.
H-Hey! Hang in there, Tama!
Can you... Can you see me?!
Hold on!
I'll take you to old Gengai!
I don't care if he's brainwashed!
I'll crush his balls to get
him to wake up and fix you!
So hang in there!
Give me some time, Tama!
Hey, Tama! Say something!
Hey! You promised!
You said you would
always be on my side!
Machines aren't supposed to lie!
Every homeless person needs
a dog and a loud radio!
I'm sorry. I lied.
It wasn't from a K-drama...
It was the smoke shop owner
who dropped by from time to time.
That doesn't matter!
Please save my data.
Yeah, I will!
When I go to sleep...
Hold the reset button while
turning off the power!
Then I will never forget...
About you, about everyone...
About the rent you owe...
You can forget that part.
So could you let me have one
last look at your face?
Don't say that stuff!
Tama!
Wake up!
Open your eyes!
Open them!
Got it!
I got a rare shot of
Master Gintoki crying.
What kind of setting is
that for playing dead?!
That's a pathetic sight
to remember you by.
Y-Yeah...
So forget you ever saw that.
The next time we meet,
I'll be smiling like a main character.
I'm holding you to that.
20 yen remaining
H-Hold on!
What do you mean, Tama-san
was taken out?!
Who did it?!
Who else could it be?
Pachi-boy, we're going
to avenge our friend.
Hey there, handsome fella.
Yes, I'm a handsome fella.
Oh, sorry. I'm out of
money for the month.
No, we have a question for you.
Have you seen this man around?
No, I haven't.
I see.
Who is he? Did he skip out
on a bill at the bar?
Let us know if you see him.
What's going on?
Cabaret girls searching for
someone instead of working?
Oh, haven't you heard?
Look over there.
They're from the Yagyu family.
Why are they here?
And over here.
The Hyakka, the Yoshiwara guards?!
Plus...
Kin-chan
Hey, now. We've got fugitives
searching for other fugitives!
What's going on?
Why are all these people here?
That guy hurt one of Kin-san's friends.
You mean Odd Jobs Kin-san?
Tama was taken out.
And my balls were literally taken out.
I have to make him pay.
This isn't a matter of
honor or reputation.
I'm willing to use any dirty tricks to
chase him down so I
can avenge our friend.
So can you guys lend me a hand?
I will use all the power I have
throughout the Kabuki district
to bring down Sakata Gintoki.
It was a dumb move to hurt
one of Kin-san's friends.
If you see this man, please contact
He's basically antagonized
the entire Kabuki district.
Doll House
Well, let me know if
anything comes up, Gramps.
How am I supposed to contact a
person who doesn't have a phone?
Write XYZ on the bulletin
board by the station.
Don't bring City Hunter into this.
Anyway, be careful.
He's got a grudge against Kin-san.
We don't know what he'll
do to Kin-san's friends.
Hammer.
You sure about this?
That was your chance to split
the head of one of his allies.
Oh, I'll split heads.
If you tell me
that you can't fix my friend.
What about you?
You're sheltering an enemy.
Nobody would break Tama,
then ask me to repair her.
Besides, I know that humans
are easily swayed.
A machine's soul is harder than steel.
Tama trusted you, so I
have to do the same.
Stupid old man.
That's why you were
brainwashed by your own piece of junk.
Coming from a main character who
was usurped by that piece of junk.
What do you plan on doing?
That piece of junk has the
Kabuki district locked down.
Doesn't matter.
There's only one thing for me to do.
You'll be fighting against
your former friends.
They're the hardest
foes you'll ever face.
That's the point of this trap.
You don't have a chance.
That would be the logical conclusion.
Unfortunately, we beasts and animals
aren't very good at quantification.
Sadaharu, we're down to one
person and one animal.
Is one plus one two?
Right.
We'll never be just two.
Can't quantify human emotion, eh?
Reckless, foolhardy, rash.
That's what you're about to do.
But it's possible that
could be his weakness.
He was created to be perfect, so
he can't understand an unpredictable
and unquantifiable fool like
you, Sakata Gintoki.
I guess I forgot to give him the most
important quality a leader needs.
I have to stop him.
Idiot plus two.
You're on board now, old man.
Yeah, and I promise to bring
another idiot with me.
So Gin-boy, don't let
yourself become zero.
You're the only one
who can stop Kintoki.
Find him!
We must punish the villain who
injured our lady's friend!
Curses, where is he hiding?!
Could it be...?!
Costume Play
I have no choice!
I must search every
single establishment!
The rest of you go that way!
I'm going in!
Where do you think you're going?
The Fast Samurai
Lady! Do not stop me!
It's time to take off!
The flight attendants
are waiting for me!
And you call yourself a warrior?
There are others around.
Don't embarrass me.
I have witnessed the
shame of the Yagyu!
Kyubei-dono, you're too late!
We've already checked the
cosplay establishments!
I don't have a single leg hair left!
Attention please!
Uh, you're the one who
should be ashamed!
A true warrior would send his
leg hair flying for a friend!
Wait, why are you providing service?!
I'm using myself as bait
to draw in the enemy!
You won't get him!
You'd only get a UMA that way!
Boss, we found someone!
Wh-What?!
Well? Interested in
working in Yoshiwara?
He landed someone!
He landed someone
completely unexpected!
I'm in no position to criticize,
but why are you people even here?!
Sorry, I'm not familiar
with the customs up here.
Found ya!
You little cutie, you!
And then we... pan!
What kind of dirty business are
you trying to pull here?!
Cut it out already!
I'm supposed to be the one
acting like an idiot,
but I haven't gotten a chance!
Say something, Lady!
Sorry, it was my fault.
Lady...
Pull yourself together!
What's wrong with everyone?
We're hesitating.
Otae-dono...
We're not sure what to do.
Something feels off about
Kin-san's request.
What Kin-san is saying doesn't
match what we've seen.
He didn't look like someone
who would hurt Tama-san.
Especially after he risked his own life
to save Sarutobi-san,
a complete stranger.
Y-You don't trust Kintoki-dono?
I trust him.
But that's why we're confused.
We don't understand why Kin-san
would ask us to do this.
Of course, we're happy
that he trusts us.
But Kin-san...
The Sakata Kintoki I
know wasn't so open.
He never said a word
when there was trouble.
He would always sneak off by himself.
It didn't matter how many
enemies there were.
He would show up with a smirk
while picking his nose...
U-Up there!
Yo, what's up?
Why are you looking at the sky?
Is there a solar eclipse?
How dare you show your face here?!
I'll only ask you once!
Were you the one who hurt Tama-dono?!
If that's what your golden god says,
you're free to believe him.
I'm here to flick a booger at him.
Go! Grab him!
Sadaharu...
You haven't forgotten
our promise, right?
Don't look back, no
matter what happens.
Just run forward.
You don't need to worry.
This is business as usual.
Let's go back home
where they are.
What?!
He's running straight
through enemy lines?!
After him! Don't let him get away!
Wait! Don't hurt Sadaharu-kun!
Furry paws can do no evil!
Aim for the guy!
B-But he's bouncing around
like he's at the rodeo!
It's hard to get a read on him!
Don't look back, no
matter what happens.
Just run forward.
Let's go back home
where they are.
That was an obvious decoy.
Did you really think we
would fall for that?
I'm the decoy.
And as expected, I landed the big fish.
Drop your sword.
Come with me and—
Sure.
I dropped my sword.
Is it my turn to make a request then?
Can you move out of the way?
Once it's all over, you can drag
me to hell or the bedroom.
Wh-What? Do you take me for a fool?
Boss!
Wait!
Don't move!
Don't touch him.
He's my target.
I told you to stay out
of this, Sarutobi.
You think I can't kill a
man who saved my life?
Laughable.
I won't let you hog all the glory
and win points with Kin-san.
This job is too big for you.
I'll take his life after he saved mine.
That's the kind of dirty
job I specialize in.
Sarutobi...
Out of my way, Tsu-ki.
There's no reason for you
to get your hands dirty.
I understand that everyone is unsure.
Should we trust Kintoki
or trust what we've seen of this man?
However, this job
requires firm resolve.
You should stand down!
What's that?
I found him first. I'll do this.
Get lost. I've got it covered.
The two of you can't handle this.
Let me take care of it.
I can do this!
I've got this!
I'll kill him!
I will!
No, me!
I got this!
I do!
No, me!
Me!
Blah!
You've got me all mixed up now!
Um, you're being very
considerate of each other,
but you're not being
considerate of me at all.
Okay, we'll all take turns sticking
our blades in this barrel.
The person who lands the
final blow gets credit.
That'd be a lynching!
Heh, I guess I
wouldn't mind having
three beauties around when I die.
But you don't need to feel
guilty about my death.
Why don't you all wear blindfolds
and pretend you're trying to
smash a watermelon
when you aim for me?
This way, you won't know who was
the killer, so there's no guilt.
Why are you still trying to help us?
Don't worry about it.
Well, hold on while I bury myself.
Wait!
I don't think so!
After him!
Don't let him get away!
Now!
Fire!
Boss!
Upsie-daisy.
Boss! Boss! Are you okay?
W-Wait!
What do you think you're doing?
No idea what you mean.
See ya.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Wait!
Stop!
Are you...
Got him!
Now, guys!
I got him!
Bastards!
Looking for a rally partner.
Smash hit to your heart.
Wanna get sweaty together?
Lady!
Crap!
There's nothing wrong.
I just see a girl's pretty hand.
This must be Gin-san's underwear!
This must be Gin-san's swimsuit!
Wait a second...
Didn't you hear me tell you to wait?
What are you trying to do?
Who are you fighting?
You can barely hold a sword, so why...
It almost seems that
you aren't fighting us,
but protecting us.
Looks like...
I underestimated this town.
We got a whole crowd out in force
to avenge one person.
Look at me now.
But I have to admit that
I feel pretty good.
This town is a good place.
Step away.
I'm going to kill this man.
You should listen to me.
I'll do this.
Why won't either of you back away?
Please... Go away...
Not when you have that
look on your face...
Lady...
Boss...
What's this?
Making women cry?
You're a real piece of work.
But don't worry.
I'm here to wipe your ass.
It's time to settle up.
Pay attention, guys.
This is the last moment of
the Kabuki district's enemy.
You're finished,
Gintoki.
Don't take another step.
What's this about?
You girls are too stubborn for me.
I'm not going to try to stop you.
Instead...
I won't try to stop you either
since we're thinking the same thing.
My memories are a jumble right now,
so I can't know if I should
trust gold or silver.
So instead, I choose to trust...
...the tears of a friend.
To be continued...
The Meaning of a Main Character
Next time, on the last
episode of Kintama:
The Meaning of a Main Character.