Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
W-What is this?!
It's huge!
I’ll shoot you guys into
the Seireitei with this.
From the sky.
Sky?!
My name is Kukaku Shiba.
I'm the best pyrotechnic in
Rukon District!
Pyrotechnic?
Right!
Koganehiko! Shiroganehiko!
Raise it!
Y-Y-Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Huh?!
What is that?!
What's happening?
The floor…
is rising!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
The ceiling is…opening!
Is this for real?!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes...!
Are you kids scared?
This is the special Kukaku Shiba
Super-sized Fireworks Stage.
The Flower-Crane Cannon!
Don't say it before I do!
I-I'm sorry…
What, speechless?
What kind of joke is this?!
You may be a fireworks expert
or whatever,
but as if you could shoot us
over with that--!
What is this?
The Reishu-kaku, Spirit Core.
Place your palms on it and
focus your spiritual energy!
Huh? Like this?
How do you focus
your spiritual energy?
Huh? What are you saying?
Like this!
If you're a Soul Reaper,
surely you know how to
use your Kido.
Actually…
Huh?!
This boy is the newbie Soul Reaper
I told you about earlier.
He can't use Kido at all.
What?!
Like this?
Geez! How hopeless!
Ganju, show him!
Yes!
Hey, give it here!
Why you--!
Kid! Wanna fight?!
Yeah… Take it if you can.
I'd rather die than be
shown by you!
Cut it out!
Sorry…
Huh?
W-What's that?!
This is the Cannonball.
Cannonball?
Now listen up.
You think that the only thing guarding
the Seireitei is that barrier,
but you're wrong.
That barrier is made from
an ore known as Sekki–Seki
that is rare even in Soul Society.
This is a fragment of it.
As you can see,
it completely breaks down
spiritual energy.
That's why it's impossible
to bore a hole through
the barrier with spiritual energy.
On top of that…
even when cut,
it emits a wave that breaks down
spiritual energy from all sides.
Which means...that the Seireitai has
a spherical barrier around it
from the sky to
the underground.
And so…that’s where this comes in!
S-Sis…I'm tired--
Deal with it!
This is the Special Hard Spiritual Partition
Penetration Device that I invented.
In other words,
if all of you combined put your spiritual
energy into this Spirit Core,
you can create a temporary cannonball
that will break through the barrier.
And then…
I'll shoot that cannonball
with the Flower-Crane Cannon
and it'll pierce straight
through the barrier.
Any questions?
Err…well…
All right, you are dismissed!
Go to the underground training room
and practice concentrating
your spiritual energy!
Yes, yes!
Take them!
Yes!
Let me go!
What the hell?!
Don't touch me! Leggo!
Put me down!
Listen, if any one of you
loses concentration,
you'll blow up right there!
What?!
You all need practice!
Practice hard!
Hey, you never mentioned that!
Hey, good job.
S-Sis…
Go down below and
help them practice.
Hey, Sis…
Are you really gonna help them?
What do you mean?
I'm against it!
Helping a Soul Reaper!
What'll I say to Brother?!
Sis, I…
Ganju!
I told you…
Don't ever speak of it again!
Sis…
If you understand, go!
Listen…
Never show such
a weak face in front of them!
This is the first time
I've had to wear the
Lieutenant badge.
Of course it is!
It’s the first time I've been
ordered to wear it like this!
"Lieutenants are to
put on their badges
and wait in the aid’s room #2."
This is getting interesting.
Abarai… Iba…
Hinamori. No one else
showed up yet?
Yes, I think so.
Lieutenants are scattered all over
Soul Society working diligently.
It might take about half a day
for everyone to gather.
My Captain can't be reached at all.
What a pain.
Huh? Who is your
squad captain again?
You know, the Hitsugaya boy.
Oh, that little prodigy. That’s tough.
Abarai…
Huh?
Have you seen our Captain Aizen?
N-No, I haven't.
He's been acting strange lately.
Even this morning.
But he won't answer when
I ask him if anything's wrong.
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry.
Huh?
Nothing's the matter.
Even this summons will probably
be cancelled soon.
Dammit!
In your view, should she die?
What is it? Just what the hell
is going on, Captain Aizen?!
Training Room
No! That's wrong, Ichigo!
It's not "wohhh."
It's nuahh!
Nuohh!
No, no!  Nuahh!
No!
Kurosaki…
It's nuahhh?
Nuahhh.
Nuahhh!
I don’t understand!
Explain it better!
Sorry, Brother.
I've decided to help
that Soul Reaper,
like the one who killed you.
If you were alive,
and saw me not helping them,
you'd scold me, wouldn't you?
You…who loved Soul Reapers
and died as a Soul Reaper.
Now, please Orihime.
Oh! You're doing just fine!
Ishida!
It's quite narrow,
but the shape is there.
Hmm…The shape probably
reflects his personality.
Next! Chad!
Oh, this is…a bit unstable,
but very powerful!
And finally, Ichigo.
This is terrible!
Absolutely terrible!
What is that...
...supposed to be?!
I can only conclude that
you have no talent.
No talent at all!
Shirogane!
I said I don't understand!
You! Teach me some useful pointers,
damn it!
Uh, Brother…dinner's ready.
Huh? Hey guys!
Dinner is ready!
You must be hungry.
Now that you mention it…
You didn't get to eat in
Rukon District, did you?
Those guys can't use spiritual energy.
So they don't get hungry.
Go and eat.
But…
Never mind me.
Go and eat.
I'll come, after I figure this out.
Really? Okay then…
Yeah.
Inoue, you're coming, too right?
Oh, I'm not hungry at all yet,
so it's okay.
Heh…I'm lying.
I am a bit hungry…
Oh, how embarrassing.
Inoue.
Go. I'll be fine.
N-No… I want to practice some more.
I'm really not hungry.
Inoue!
Please…
All right.
Okay…
Since you're asking me.
I'm going then.
H-Hey Inoue!
C'mon, Ishida. Chad, too!
Dammit!
Is she that important to you?
Huh?
This Soul Reaper you're going to save.
Not really.
Huh?
Give it here!
Then did you, like,
promise to save her?
No.
Then it must be money.
She promised to pay you
if you saved her.
No way I can use money
from here in my world!
Then why?
Why are you so determined?!
I owe her!
She saved my life.
And I haven't repaid her yet.
She gave me her power to
save my family and me…
even though she had just met me.
Because of that, she was arrested…
and she's about to be executed.
I don't want to turn into a pathetic guy
who'd turn his back on her.
What?
Give it to me!
Huh?!
What're you doing?!
Give it back!
I'm going to practice, too!
Cover your ears!
Don't you dare listen!
I'm going to review the trick
I developed myself.
Huh?
Visualize this…
Draw a circle in your heart…
as dark as possible,
and as heavy as possible.
Then…imagine yourself jumping right
into the center of the circle.
This is the basic image
that works for all Kido.
So easy.
It's so easy I could cry!
I didn't even have to practice it!
Sorry to bother you.
What a ham!
Such terrible acting! Idiot!
Draw a circle…
in my heart…
Thank you for the meal.
Yes.
Huh? Inoue, are you done?
Y-Yes, I'm full--
See? My stomach is full.
Y-You don't have to go that far.
Forget I ever asked.
Actually…I was going to
take it to Ichigo.
That's right, Kurosaki still hasn't…
Oh! It's breaking apart!
No! The object!
The Great Kukaku arm pillar
is going to fall!
It’s Kurosaki…!
Let's go!
What happened?! Hey Ganju!
I-I'm sorry, Sis…
I just showed him once.
I never imagined it would
turn out like this!
You fool! Gather your spiritual energy
together already!
I did it!
You did it, Ichigo!
Yeah!
You idiot!
Don't lose your concentration!
Huh?
Weren't you listening to me, fool?!
I told you!
If you lose concentration,
you’ll blow up!
Yes, you did.
I'll say, you…
You're just as guilty, idiot!
Both of you, no food tonight!
Why?!
Why put me together with him?!
Shut up! Got a problem?!
Owee! Okay, we understand.
Okay, we understand!
You're here.
Captain of the Squad 3…
Gin Ichimaru.
What's going on?
I get called so suddenly…
and look at this crowd?
The captains who control Soul Society…
are all here for me?
Maybe not.
The Captain of the
Squad 13 isn't here.
Did something happen to him?
He's absent with an illness.
Again? I hope he gets better soon.
Quit joking around.
You know you weren't summoned
here for that.
I understand you went and
played with the Ryokas by yourself.
And I hear you failed. Explain yourself.
You should have no trouble dealing
with four or five Ryokas.
Oh, they didn't die then?
What?
Oh, I thought they were dead.
My intuition has gotten dull.
You can stop that monkey business.
There’s no way that
captain-level guys like us
would fail to tell instantly whether
an opponent's Hakudo has ceased or not.
There they go again,
stupid squabbling among old fools.
Come on! You make it sound like
I let him go on purpose.
That's precisely what I'm saying.
Shut up, Kurotsuchi.
I'm talking to him now.
Or do you want to be done in by me?
What did you say?
So stupid.
Oh boy…
tempers are running high.
Enough of this!
But I think the reason why
you have been summoned
has been made clear.
Acting alone,
and letting the target escape…
Well? How do you defend
your actions…
Ichimaru?
I can't.
What?!
There's nothing I can say
to defend myself.
I made a simple mistake.
I won't make excuses.
I'll accept whatever punishment--
Just a minute, Ichimaru.
First, let me ask you something.
Urgent alert! Urgent alert!
Intruders in Seireitei!
All Squads get into position!
Repeat…!
Intruders?
Those Ryokas?
It can't be…
Ichigo...
With much appreciation
send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
Four students and one cat
into Seireitei!
Got it! I'm off, Sis!
Attention, please!
The Cannonball will be shot very soon.
Guests, take your seats now or else!
I'm really worried.