No!
Calm down!
I'm a Soul Reaper.
Are you all right?
What happened?
With all these missing
Soul Reaper incidents going on...
Are you sure you want
to do this, Kuchiki?
Going out without a gigai...
If something happens to you,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Then don't make me transport
your merchandise for you!
Boy, you've been such
a huge help.
Thanks to these recent incidents,
I can't use my usual
route anymore.
That put me in a real bind.
That explains why there's
so much here.
Right now, I'm willing to give
you some good deals!
No thanks!
Boss!
We're all ready to go, sir!
Okay. I'm done here as well.
Ready to go?
We're about to leave on our
Urahara's Shop employee vacation!
Well, you see,
we had nothing to do
because we were sold
out of merchandise,
so I planned a vacation.
But now that we have
all this merchandise...
We should get right to work!
I guess we'll go on that
vacation, after all.
R-Right...
Now if you'll excuse us,
we'll be on our way.
Kuchiki...
I went around to several of the
places where the incidents occurred.
There was evidence that the
Soul Reapers were attacked
and probably eaten.
I see.
Then they were attacked
by Hollows.
No, they weren't.
At the sites,
there was absolutely no residual
Spiritual Pressure from Hollows.
However...
Had enough, Soul Reaper?
Tsk! You're pathetic.
I don't even feel like eating
a Soul Reaper like you.
Dance Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai...
Tsukishiro!
So it was targeting Soul Reapers,
after all.
Phew... I'm saved.
I know you.
You remember me?!
Indeed!
I am the one, the only,
Soul Reaper
in charge of Karakura Town!
Zennosuke Kurumadani!
This is the guy who
took over for me?
This...has no effect on me!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
It's just as Urahara said.
It's different in some way
from that of a Hollow.
You're...
I've found you!
Hado Number 33: Sokatsui!
That technique... I'm sure of it!
I knew if I went on a rampage
in this town, you'd appear.
And I was right!
You know me?!
What? You don't remember?
It's me! Me!
See?
Y-You're...
Shrieker!
Correct.
You can't be! That's not possible.
I thought...
you fell into the depths of Hell!
A Zanpakuto can only
wash away sins
committed after one's death.
But for Hollows who
committed major sins
when they were still humans,
Hell will open its gates!
You! How did you get out of Hell?
How? I'm not going
to tell you that!
Get her!
I won't fall for the
same trick twice!
Oh?
Nice moves.
Though I don't recall
you being that good.
Don't underestimate me!
I had simply lost my
powers back then!
I will assist you!
Fool! Don't!
What?!
I'll start with you!
No way!
Stay here!
I've been waiting for you!
Here!
I'm going to make
it a painful death!
This can't be...
His power and speed are at
an entirely different level!
What?!
Now I've got you!
A chain...
This chain
can't be cut by the likes of you!
Die!
Too slow!
Somenomai Tsukishiro!
That takes care of his clones.
What?!
How is that possible?
I didn't sense the presence
of any of his clones.
Where did those bombs
come from?
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to run away?
Good morning, Tsuchinamazu!
What?!
This is...
Now's our chance to get away!
Th-That was an escape technique?
What?!
Kurumadani!
He has leech bombs
in his body, as well!
My entire body is like a bomb!
Damn!
Hurry... Get away...
Hey!
I'm different from the
way I was back then!
What...are you?!
You don't know what
this chain is?
This chain is from Hell.
And I am a Sinner of Hell!
"Sinner"?!
That can't be!
There's no way a Sinner
could escape from Hell.
But I did!
To get my revenge on you!
What just happened?!
What are you doing?
Shut up!
Renji!
Are you all right, Rukia?
Why are you here?
We got a report from the Department
of Research and Development
about some weird Spiritual Pressure
being detected in the World of the Living.
What the hell is this guy?
He's a Sinner of Hell.
A Sinner?
You're kidding.
Bastard!
Don't interfere when things
were just getting good!
Don't get so carried away!
One Soul Reaper down!
Bankai! Hihio Zabimaru!
Hikotsu Taiho!
That won't be enough to kill me!
I'll keep returning from
the depths of Hell!
What the hell just happened?
I don't know.
But...
We will now begin the emergency
Captains' Meeting!
Captains Zaraki and Kurotsuchi
don't seem to be here yet.
Never mind them.
I summoned you all here
on short notice.
Fill in the absent captains
with the details later.
Now then, we received
word a short while ago
that a Sinner of Hell appeared
in the World of the Living.
Sinner of Hell?
"Sinner"? That's a reference
to a resident of Hell, right?
The souls of people who die
are sent to the Soul Society,
the home of souls.
However, souls of people who
committed heinous acts
during their lifetimes
are unable to enter
the Soul Society and are
instead plunged into Hell.
Then...
As Sinners, they are
tied in chains
and condemned for all
eternity for their sins.
This is the first time in the history
of the Soul Society that a Sinner,
a resident of Hell,
has found his way back
into the World of the Living.
Does it mean something
is amiss in Hell?
How could that be?
There's the gatekeeper in
Hell called Kushanaada,
whose control is absolute.
Yes...
However, I've heard that there
are powerful beings
with mysterious powers
who make their home
deep in the bowels of Hell.
If they are able to freely find
their way into the
World of the Living,
we've got a bit of a problem.
The situation is grave.
We will start by dispatching
Renji Abarai and Rukia Kuchiki,
who first encountered the Sinner,
as advance troops to the
World of the Living!
In the event the need arises,
I will provide them
with procedures to
infiltrate Hell and to make
an emergency return.
Shall we request
the assistance of
Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki, as well?
No, we mustn't.
Give strict orders to both
Abarai and Kuchiki
that they are not to involve
the Substitute Soul Reaper
under any circumstances!
Szayelaporro...
Oh, it's you, Aaroniero.
I noticed there was another person
falling along side of me.
But it was you.
I have to say that's
one tough cylinder.
Were you hoping it would break?
No...
I'm saying that if it had cracked,
I could open it up and investigate
the liquid inside.
You bastard!
I don't know what this place is,
but it's convenient that
Lord Aizen isn't here!
You can live on inside me after
my Glotoneria eats you!
Wait!
You just said it...
"I don't know what this place is."
Right now, shouldn't we investigate
where we are, rather
than kill each other?
I don't really care either way.
I can investigate that
after I kill you.
You don't seem to comprehend
the difference in our powers.
I am Espada Number 8,
and you are 9.
You'll lose.
What?!
You two are funny.
What is this place?
If you want to know, I'll tell you.
This is Hell.
Who are you?
Why don't you come
down and talk?
You guys are hilarious.
I told you. This is Hell.
The two of you are already dead.
What kind of nonsense is that?!
I see.
Thank you for jogging
my memory.
It appears I did die.
Because of that damned
despicable Soul Reaper.
While I'm at it, let me ask you...
Is there a way to get
out of this place
you call Hell and return
to Hueco Mundo?
Of course not.
Really?
If there is a way, it's better
if you didn't keep it from us.
I am Shuren.
Do you know?
The only way to survive here
in Hell is to do as I say.
What?!
Taikon.
Gunjo.
Garogai.
Our guests appear dissatisfied
with Hell.
Please teach them
to appreciate it.
Aaroniero!
A Gran Rey Cero, eh?
This is the power of
an Espada's Cero?
How disappointing.
I have no more use for you.
Don't get so cocky, Sinner!
Their level of power was nowhere
near enough to open it.
Gunjo, what about the man
we sent to the World
of the Living?
Yes, sir! He returned safely.
He was no longer of use,
so I silenced him.
The experiment was a success.
I see...
Our dark days are about
to come to an end.
As I suspected,
it looks like it has to be you.
I will bring you down,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I'm glad you're safe, Rukia.
Thank you for your help, Renji.
Now let us return to
the Soul Society.
Right. I'm glad no one else
got hurt besides us.
Yes... Let's just hope nothing
else happens.
Kurumadani Ze-
The Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers!
Let's have fun in Hawaii!
Let's have a blast using the money
we put away and saved!
Yes. We'll enjoy the beach
and shopping.
This is everything.
Huh?
What is this cat?
Where'd it come from?
Hey, Kisuke! What's going on?!
And here I thought we could
save on Yoruichi's airfare.