Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
There is a disturbance
in the West Fugai area!
Precautionary orders three to eight!
I repeat…
There is a disturbance
in the West Fugai area!
Precautionary orders three to eight!
The Bounts who came to
Soul Society have defeated
two lieutenants of the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads who tried to fight them.
They then disappeared into
the vast Rukon District.
Meanwhile, we used Kukaku's home
as a starting point,
and split up and
began searching for the Bounts.
It’s not easy finding the Bounts
since they have the ability to
hide their Spiritual Pressure.
At that moment, the female Bount Yoshi
appeared before Rukia
as she headed to Seireitei to
rejoin her Squad.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads sensed
their Spiritual Pressure
and headed to their location.
But that was just a trick
in order to destroy
the Shishinro Repentance Cell,
a symbol of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Rukia was thrashed around.
And when Rukia was about
to be killed,
Byakuya Kuchiki saved her.
During that time…
We received information that
Kariya is hiding in Kusajishi,
the worst area in the Rukon District.
We headed to Kusajishi to find out
if the information was true, but…
So you're…Jin Kariya…
Yeah…
It seems like you're just doing
whatever you like…
Are you here to avenge her?
It doesn't matter.
I just have to kill
Soul Society's enemies,
no matter who they are…
You're not going to take a stance?
You, too… You can come at me
whenever you want.
I see…
I see that Bounts have speed
equal to the Flash Step.
You grazed me.
I'm going next!
I've got you!
I hear that the Bounts
control puppets…
That thing I can't see
is your puppet, huh?
Well…I wonder…
Then I just have to cut you
down along with your puppet.
As I expected of Byakuya Kuchiki…
You're far better than
the rumors say you are.
I'm glad I met you…
What?
Byakuya Kuchiki,
the current head of
the Kuchiki family,
one of the famous four
great noble families…
And said to be the strongest
in the family's history.
It’s natural for someone with
my level of skill
to want to challenge you.
And…
Your strength is satisfying enough…
What do you plan to do?
My plan, huh?
The invincible
Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
which protect Soul Society.
You're the most famous
of all of them…
If you're defeated…
The people of Seireitei will
be shocked.
Stop talking nonsense…
I'm serious…
There's no way that
I would come here
if I weren't convinced
I could defeat you.
But you're far more naive
than I heard you were…
When my comrade tried to
finish off Rukia Kuchiki…
I’m told you were desperate
to protect her.
Furthermore, you've come
by yourself
to avenge your younger sister.
I never thought that you would
fall for such a cheap taunt…
How silly…
I thought I told you,
“I just have to kill
Soul Society's enemies.”
Well, that's fine…
Whatever the case,
you're going to die here as
part of our great plan.
There is no use in talking…
You're the one who's going
to die here.
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
So this is the famous Senbonzakura…
It's a beautiful technique…
But seems it won't work on me.
And now…
Allow me to attack.
Come to me, greater winds…
Come into me, greater strength…
I thought so…
The thing you were
controlling earlier was…
The wind!
Wind Tanz!
Die.
Hado 33!
Sokatsui!
Hado 4! Byakurai!
The Senbonzakura's thousand blades
have been split so small
that it cannot be seen.
When they dance,
they catch the light,
which makes them look
like countless flowers falling…
But…
My doll is wind…
There is wind in this world…
In other words,
there is a limitless amount of air.
If I gather it, it can create
a power that rivals your blade!
It's simple number theory.
Senbonzakura, Kido,
and direct attacks from zanpakuto…
They're wonderful attacks,
but they can't cut me.
Soon, you'll be the one
on the ground.
You think so?
Stop acting tough…
The reckless valor to face
the Senbonzakura bare-handed…
I commend you for that…
But…I can cut off your head in
a single swipe at this distance.
I'll cut off your head before you can.
Now, we can't separate
from one another.
Wind Tanz!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
One arm is but a small price to pay
if I can defeat Byakuya Kuchiki.
Are you insane?
Getsugatensho!
Hey, Byakuya…
Why are you having
a tough time after turning down help?
Heh! What pathetic guys!
G-Ganju…
Now now, Ganju hasn’t done
anything, remember?
Bonnie was the one
who defeated them.
Oink! Oink!
Don't worry about the details…
Besides that…
That Spiritual Pressure
just now was…Ichigo…
Yeah… It's Kurosaki!
Huh? Where's Ishida?
He was here just now…
He probably headed in
Kurosaki's direction!
Wait!
Huh?
Let's leave it to those two!
But…
It's all right…
Ichigo and Uryu won't die
that easily!
Ganju…
Besides, we need to know
what's going on in Kusajishi first.
Hey, you!
Eep--!
I-I'm sorry…
I want to know more about
those skilled newcomers
who appeared in Kusajishi.
Y-Yes… It was a guy called "Kariya"…
I thought so…
So what is he doing?
H-He says that he's going to
turn Soul Society upside down
and is gathering people…
Say what?!
Do you know anything else?
R-Right now,
they're at the gambling
house bookie’s place.
He said that if we go,
something good would happen…
That's all I know…
I see. Thank you!
Ganju, what are we going to do?
We've just got to go…
But if they're gathering people,
it'll be dangerous…
Indeed…
Oh well…
I guess I'll talk to him…
By “him,” you can't mean…
The Bull of Kusajishi!
Brother! That’s dangerous!
What do you plan to do
when you meet him?!
Shut up!
It's faster to hear about Kusajishi
from guys from Kusajishi!
But if Bull is with the Bounts…
It's all right! Bull's not the type
to be coaxed by the Bounts!
And?
Kariya says that he wants
to fight with you.
Fight against who?
The guys from Seireitei.
Are you guys serious about
attacking that place?!
It's not worth risking
my life over…
No… We can win.
How can you say that?!
We have a plan.
What kind of plan?
I need your approval
in order to tell you…
Will you fight with us?
All souls should be sent to
Soul Society equally…
But, in reality, this world
is ruled by a part of it.
The power of Seireitei.
There shouldn't be poverty
in Rukon District…
This place, Kusajishi,
is a place where you never know
when you'll die…
And where blood is washed
by blood…
We had similar experiences
in the World of the Living.
No, in a way…
We lived in far worse conditions…
so we understand
your feelings.
Don't you want to see
the light of day?
Don't you want to live
your lives the way you want…?
Without looks of scorn from
the rest of the world?
Well…
Of course!
Everyone wants that!
Right?!
Kariya is going to turn
Soul Society upside down!
He will!
Come with us to a new world!
Fine…
But I want proof that
you're serious.
Anything's fine.
Show me how serious you are.
Ichinose…
Draw your zanpakuto!
Huh?
Try and cut this arm.
What?!
Wh-What's this?
We are invincible.
You have nothing to
worry about…
We're going to kill Seireitei itself…
Along with you, we're going
to dissolve Soul Society
into the shape it should be!
Lirin… This is dangerous,
so stand back…
Ichigo, what are you going to do?
It's all right!
What's with that?!
I'm worried about you!
Sorry…
Humph!
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Hey…
You appeared pretty quickly.
Yeah…
Byakuya, are you all right?
How unnecessary…
Heh! Shut up!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I'll treat you as an enemy
if you interfere.
What's this?
Soul Society is filled
with good reishi.
It raises the power of us Bounts.
We Bounts are invincible as long as
this world is filled with reishi.
You're healing your wounds
by using reishi, huh?
You bastard…
Here I go.
Bankai!
What terrifying speed.
They're so fast that
I don't know what's going on…
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
You're in the way.
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Amazing! Rukia's older brother
and Ichigo are so fast
that I can't see them at all!
Heh. He can't beat the combination
of Bonnie and me!
I'm the self-proclaimed
“Sonic Noble of Rukon District”!
You're interfering. Out of the way!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
That person is called “Hawk,” isn't he?
Yeah…
Come to think of it,
I never introduced you to them…
FEVER
First is “Fever.”
His real name is Mitsuru Ishino.
DOESN'T HAVE ANY
SENSE OF RHYTHM
“Dumbbell.”
Sadatomo Saionji.
NATURALLY GOOD AT
TAKING CARE OF ANIMALS
DUMBBELL
TOP
“Top.”
Kenji Yamashita.
WEAKEST AT FIGHTING
ALSO WEAKEST
AT ARGUMENTS
HAWK
Last is “Hawk.”
Taichi Miyamoto!
NUMBER ONE HENCHMAN
GOOD AT COOKING
Did you give them those names?
Yeah! Aren't they cool?!
HONEY  MANNY  NANNY  MINNIE
It's the same as his boars…
Four wheel drive!