Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Irregularities detected along
western perimeter.
Security alert in Areas 3 through 8!
Repeat!
Irregularities detected along
western perimeter.
Security alert in Areas 3 through 8!
What?! What's going on?
What's happening?!
The wall is catching up to us!
The place we just ran through
is collapsing!
If you have time to look back,
you have time to run!
It's all over if the Restrictive Current
swallows you up!
Ishida!
What's happening?!
The fool!
It's that crazy get-up he has on!
Hold it!
Do not use your Zanpaku-to.
The current entangles the spiritual body.
If you use your Zanpaku-to,
you will get caught too.
T-Thank you…
Huh?!
Let's go!
Put me down, Chad!
I can run on my own!
Hey, guys.
Something's...
Something's coming!
What is that?!
It's the Cleaner!
It appears once every seven days!
And this had to be the day!
Anyway, run! It's incredibly fast!
Hurry! We're close to the exit!
It's no good!
We can't outrun it!
Hinagiku! Baigon! Lily!
Santen Kesshun! I reject!
Is everyone all right?
Wow! Ichigo!
The way you land is so artistic!
Shut up!
Cripes…
That was something else.
This is more than I expected.
I never thought I'd use
my extra cape so soon.
H-He brought a change of clothes…
I'm so glad…
No one seems to be hurt.
What's there to be glad about?!
Owwee!
Were you not listening to me?!
We're lucky the Restrictive Current
made contact
with just the shield area.
If it had been
the Six Flowers themselves,
you'd be dead now!
I-I'm sorry.
So what?
Don't be so hard on her.
As it turned out, thanks to Inoue,
we came through without a scratch.
You do not understand
how serious this is.
I-Is this the Soul Society?
Yes.
This place is known as the Rukon District,
the Drifting Spirit Town.
This is where souls first live
upon coming to Soul Society,
and is on the perimeter of Seireitei
where Soul Reapers live.
It's the poorest place in Soul Society,
but also the freest,
and has the largest population
of souls in Soul Society.
Hmm… But for all that,
there's no one around here.
Huh?
What's that?
It looks so different on that side.
Oh that…
I got it! That's where the Soul Reapers live…
the Sei-whatever…
Awright!
Y-You fool! Don't get too close!
You'll die!
Huh?
It's been a long time…
since someone tried to pass through
the Seirei Gate without a travel permit.
You're a rare guest...
Welcome, kid!
So the Ryoka have landed
outside the Seirei Gate.
Since they're on that side,
there's no need for us to go.
Well… Especially since on that side…
Jidanbo will be there.
Now come at me from anywhere…
Kid!
So huge!
Who is he?!
He's too big to be human!
Just what is he?
His name is Jidanbo.
He was chosen from among
the best in Soul Society
to guard the White Road Gate,
one of the four gates of Seirei Gate.
Guard? Which means we
have to beat him to get inside?
Yes. But that won't be an easy task…
In the 300 years that
he has been on duty,
no one has been able to break
through the White Road Gate.
He is legendary for his power and strength.
So how do we fight a guy like that?
That's where your intelligence comes in.
I think, first, a meeting is in order
to come up with a strategy.
Hey Ichigo…
Hey! Chad! Orihime!
Come back! Come back, both of you!
Ichigo, wait…
I'm coming to help!
W-What is that?!
He's crazy!
I don't like your manners.
You must be country bumpkins.
Now listen up.
We have rules in the city.
First, wash your hands when
you return from outside.
Two, don't eat food
that's fallen on the floor.
Three, when you fight,
it's one-on-one.
My first opponent will be that kid…
with the candy hair.
You wait here quietly, until I'm done.
Inoue…
Huh?
I'll wait for my chance and
open up a hole in this wall.
The instant I'm done, aim and
shoot your Tsubaki at him through the hole.
What?
Are you still scheming something?
He has surprisingly sharp ears…
Yeah.
Hey! Chad! Orihime!
Ichigo! Are you all right?
You're not hurt?
No, I'm alive and kicking!
Wait over there, we're…
About that, Orihime…
Can you and Chad just stay put?
Huh?
What're you saying, Ichigo?
That's…!
Never mind. Don't worry, just wait.
No, I refuse!
Uryu!
Our time is limited!
Instead of just you, we have to
attack together, and get going.
Oh, so you're there, Ishida?
I've been here all the time!
Quit saying irritating things
at a time like this!
Geez, will you all shut up?
Can you do it?
Umm… Probably.
Probably?! What're you saying?!
Huh?
Do you understand the situation?!
Cripes…
Look, don't worry.
How can I not worry?!
I'll tell you something interesting…
My Soul Reaper strength was
supposed to be restored in ten full days.
But I got it back in five.
So what do you think
I did the remaining five days?
W-What were you doing?
Fighting. For five days and nights,
I fought that hat-and-clogs guy…
one-on-one.
I get it… You learned
the secrets of fighting…
Nope…
Huh?
He didn't teach me a thing.
But…
Stamina and guts…
I got 'em even if I didn't want 'em.
Are you done talking?
I don't remember asking
you to wait.
You are a country bumpkin, after all.
You don't know your manners.
When someone waits for you…
you say, "thank you"!
What's happening?!
What?!
Just what are you?
Isn't it bad manners to attack
before your opponent is ready?
Whoa!
H-He's laughing.
You're gutsy.
Good! It's been decades since
someone stopped my thrust.
All right! This is great.
Today, I get to give it
everything I've got!
Among those who tried to
pass through here,
there have been only three,
including you,
who were able to stop my first thrust.
However…not one has been
able to stop…my second thrust!
Hmm… Good, you're still standing.
I'm gonna keep coming! Take this!
Jidanda Ten Strikes Festival!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six! Seven!
What's happening?!
Seven! Eight!
Err…Six! Eight!
Now it's time for the finish!
W-What…?!
W-Why…?!
Why are you…still standing?!
He's standing!
Kurosaki is still standing!
Kurosaki!
I get it!
What Ichigo learned from that guy
was not about stamina or guts…
or even the secrets of fighting!
Without a doubt, he has spiritual power
beyond the norm of Soul Reapers…
But he's still clumsy at
wielding that power…
What he lacked when he confronted
other Soul Reapers…
was experience!
And once he got that, he's…
Are you finished?
He's…!
Then it's my turn.
He's gonna be so strong,
it'll be scary!
Not yet! Not yet!
I'm not…finished yet!
Another axe?!
Try this! My final lethal attack!
Jidanda Banzai Strike Festival!
Sorry, but I'm gonna destroy those axes.
W-What?!
That Kurosaki…
What'd he just do?!
That giant…
went flying!
Hah! Man, that was close!
I slipped and fell on my butt!
Huh? What's that look?
I'll bet you think I went flying.
Hah! What're you saying?
I can't be blown away, never happen!
That's why country bumpkins
are such a pain.
Just wait, I'll use my axes again and…
A-Axes…?
Hmm… Jidanbo's axes were
destroyed in one blow.
What?! Those giant axes?!
Hey, say something.
M-My…axes!
Huh?!
They're broken! They're broken!
My axes are…
broken!
Now, he's crying.
What's going on?
It sounds like a siren.
Er…hey…I'm sorry about this.
For breaking your axes…
I didn't have to break both of them,
I know…
Bad of me…
Y-You're…not bad.
You and I are enemies,
but you're concerned for me, a loser…
What a big heart…
You're really great.
Err… Well, when someone cries that much,
anyone would want to console him.
Meanwhile, I'm acting like
a kid over mere axes…
I'm an embarrassment as a man!
It's… my loss!
Huh?
A complete loss!
As a warrior…as a man…
I lost to you completely!
It's been 300 years since I became
the guard of the White Road Gate.
I've never once lost!
You are the first man to defeat me.
Pass!
I, Jidanbo, grant your permission
to pass through the White Road Gate!
Huh?
Y-Yeah!
Can all of us really pass?
Yes. I lost to your leader.
I have no right to stop you.
What?!
Kurosaki is our leader?! No way!
Why're you so upset?
Your name is Kurosaki?
Yeah, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ichigo, huh? That's a cute name.
Shut up! Ichi means "one" and
go stands for "protect"!
It's not cute!
Take care, Ichigo.
I don't know why you are
passing through this gate…
But on the other side, they're all strong.
I know that.
All right. As long as you know.
Okay, I'll open the gate so stay back.
Don't get scared.
I'll give it one heave.
Ohhh…!
Wow!
Wow...!
A-Amazing…!
I never thought that thing
could be lifted…
What's the matter?
Why're you standing there like that?
Did something happen?
Who's that…?!
Captain of Squad 3…
Gin Ichimaru.
With much appreciation
send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
A mysterious wild boar gang attacks!
The only one who can stop this
outrageous bunch is you!
And so, I leave it to you, Kurosaki!
Right! Pararira pararira...
Hey, don't run away, you guys!