Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
Kira, Yumichika, and Hisagi,
who were assigned to
defend the Tenkaiketchu,
faced Fracciones sent by Barragan,
with each emerging victorious.
However, Ikkaku,
who guarded the remaining pillar,
was defeated by Poww.
As a result, Karakura Town began to
return to the World of the Living.
Poww thought he had won the battle,
but Squad 7 captain,
Sajin Komamura, appeared at the base
of the destroyed pillar to take on Poww,
who turned himself into a giant
using his sword release.
Komamura performed Bankai to bring out
his Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh.
What is…
this guy?!
What is this?
What in the world are you?!
Oh yeah.
I haven't identified myself yet.
I am Sajin Komamura,
captain of Squad 7.
I'm ashamed to say,
as you said,
I'm a maggot-like fellow.
They're dead, all of them.
Those idiots!
We're terribly sorry,
Lord Barragan!
We will do away
with them immediately,
so please have a seat and wait!
Who were you going to do away with?
Are you going to do away with
Komamura and the others?
Or did you mean all of us?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
Depending on your reply,
I will start by doing away
with you guys.
Well actually,
I'm going to do away with you
even if you don't reply.
You little!
What're you doing?!
Don't.
Okay, shall we get on
with the real battle?
Man, this is making
my shoulders stiff.
When Old Man Yama's
all worked up,
it makes me that way too.
I know.
When this is over, shall we give
Sensei a shoulder massage?
We haven't done that in a while.
No, no…
It's my shoulders that are stiff.
What're you talking about?
I've never seen you
with stiff shoulders.
Omaeda!
Y-Yes, sir!
You look stiff.
Afraid of your first real battle
in a while?
That's not true!
I'm trembling with excitement!
You're so pathetic,
I can't stand to look at you.
I can't ask for
a better opportunity.
Find a good place
along the way and die.
Huh?!
What're you saying?!
I'm not afraid, and I'm not stiff!
What I mean is,
I'm absolutely not going to die!
I see. Then don't die.
I won't! I don't need you to
tell me that!
It's about to start.
Anything bothering you?
What're you talking about?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Keep your focus,
Matsumoto!
Yes, sir!
Kill them.
Don't let a single ant
escape alive.
There's no place for you
to return as losers.
Don't disappoint me.
Don't let me walk
a path that is not
stained with the blood
of our enemies.
Say it!
Who's subordinates are you?!
– Yes!
– We are the Fracciones
– of His Majesty
– Emperor Barragan Ruizenban!
– We will crush every enemy and
– stain the battlefield with their
– blood and flesh for you to see!
That child next to you.
Would you mind moving her
away from here?
Why?
I cannot fight at full strength
with her here.
Isn't it the same for you?
What?!
Quiet, Lilinette.
That's fine.
You don't need to fight
at full strength.
I won't fight at full strength,
either.
What do you mean by that?
That sort of thing doesn't
suit my personality.
You think we can just
pretend like we're fighting,
and wait until
the others finish fighting?
What are you talking about?
Nice…
Yes, I like it!
I prefer it that way, too!
I don't like getting hurt.
Unfortunately,
we can't afford to do that.
I see.
That just sucks.
These guys jumped
right into our midst…
Are you playing with us?!
I find it unpleasant.
You three,
regardless of what they look like,
those two are captain-class.
Don't let your guard down.
Crush them by using
your full strength from the start.
Yes, ma'am!
Captain!
I'll handle these three.
You take on the Espada
behind them…
Can you do it?
Yes.
All right. They're yours.
You're not getting by us!
Wait!
Everyone!
Put your entire spirit on the line
and crush them here!
Even if your flesh
is torn from you,
use pieces of your bone
to form an ironclad wall!
We mustn't let them even step
one foot into the Soul Society!
Attack!
That bastard!
How dare he attack Master Halibel!
Wait, Apache!
Do that later!
But Mila Rose!
You're fine with that kid
injuring Master Halibel?!
Fool.
Master Halibel drew her sword.
Anyway,
that kid with the white hair
doesn't stand a chance.
If you still insist
on helping her,
take care of this woman first,
then go.
Come to think of it, earlier
this one had the gall to say,
"I'll handle these three."
My, you have surprisingly
good hearing.
I thought everything about you,
your ears, face and figure
were all bad.
What was that, damn you?!
– Don't mess with me!
– She's goading you.
– Just 'cause you have some big jugs
– Don't fall for it each time.
– doesn't mean you're all hot!
– It's a real drag.
That's right.
What that female gorilla says.
What did you say?!
Who're you calling
a female gorilla, you cow!
Stop it, both of you.
It's shameful.
Becoming agitated is exactly
what the enemy wants.
I know you can't help
your low intelligence,
but do you mind not making
trouble for me, too?
– Damn it, Sun-Sun, who's side are you on?!
I'm okay with
getting rid of you first!
That's right!
My, how interesting.
– I was just thinking that
– Hey,
– having both of you around
– we're talking to you!
– is like being shackled
– Always talking down to us,
– with a ball and chain.
– I've had it!
Huh?! Say that again, damn it!
I'll say it all I want.
You two are like
a ball and chain.
I'll kill you!
Stay right where you are!
I'm going to yank your hair out!
Out of my way, Apachi!
– Are these gals even worth taunting?
– Let me!
You see?
Huh? What're you looking at?!
Nothing.
It's a little late to look serious.
If this were many versus one,
surrounding me would be
standard practice.
But the moment the three of you
gathered in one location,
you already lost the advantage
of three versus one.
Growl,
Haineko!
What was that?!
Quit playing around!
What're you going to do
with this sand-like stuff?!
That hurt!
What'd you do that for?!
You shouldn't foolishly
touch something unfamiliar!
Such flagrant indiscretion,
I must say.
What?!
Apache!
What do you think?
That's the power of "Haineko."
The blade turns to ashes,
and a single swing
of the handle
slashes everywhere
the ash covers to pieces.
You can think of all of the ash
around you as my sword.
There is nowhere
to escape!
Be careful.
It'll chop you from the first one
who touches that cyclone of ash.
– Soft.
Aren't you being a bit soft?
You actually thought you
could beat us with that?!
Haineko!
Damn you… I'm not going to lose!
This is a joke!
Huh?!
Aren't you worried?
Your second-in-command is
getting his butt kicked.
I don't care.
He's a fool who only
thinks about
money, food,
and the family business.
Getting beaten up a bit
will be good medicine.
Oh yeah?
That's pretty cold of you.
Is that how things work
between you two?
I don't like a cozy atmosphere
within my squad.
In order to train,
it is appropriate
for subordinates and superiors
to be at odds with one another.
Yeah?
Damn it!
Bakudo 30...
Shitotsusansen.
It's over, Arrancar.
I didn't even have time
to ask your name.
Kill all enemy with your venom,
Suzumebachi.
Hey kid!
You're a hundred years too young
to challenge Master Halibel!
Her voluptuous breasts
will crush you!
Our captain is used to
being crushed by my breasts,
so that won't work at all!
What?!
Don't say things that will
give people the wrong idea!
Beginning with this segment,
we will be introducing
the Zanpakuto of the Soul Reapers.
Our first introduction will be on
Byakuya's "Senbonzakura."
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
When released, Senbonzakura's blade
becomes a thousand blades
resembling cherry blossom petals
that slash apart the enemy.
Its Bankai form is
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
It is impossible to escape
from its all-direction attack.
Come to think of it,
during Shikai, you're still
holding the handle, right?
What about it?
Doesn't that make you look lame?