Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
The execution is tomorrow…
When I heard that, I was surprised, but…
strangely enough I wasn’t sad.
It must be because of
the dream I had last night…
That dream about
the night I’ll never forget.
Please wait here a moment.
The captain shall be arriving soon.
Um...
Yes! What is it?!
I’m just an ordinary
new squad member.
Could you please address me
less formally?
Ah… Yes! I’ll be careful in the future!
Who’s that girl?
You know, from the Kuchiki clan…
Hah! A new pet cat, huh?
I heard she was exempt
from the graduation exam
as well as
the squad entrance exam…
Just a pastime
for the great nobles…
They’ve got to be kidding!
We’re here busting our butts…
It’s the same here, after all …
Hey, hey! What are you guys doing
loitering around here?
This isn’t a show!
Get back to your posts, damn it!
I’m the Lieutenant, Kaien Shiba!
Nice to meet ya!
Umm… Yes, sir…
“Umm… Yes, sir…”?
What’s with that greeting?!
Your Lieutenant
just introduced himself!
You’re supposed to state your name and
say, “Pleased to meet you too, sir,” right?!
What’s your name, damn it?!
I’m Ru…Rukia Kuchiki, sir.
Oh…? And...?
P-Pleased to meet you too, sir!
Good!
All right, Rukia!
An ordinary greeting,
an ordinary yelling,
an ordinary subordinate-superior
relationship…
I welcome you to the Squad 13!
Our captain isn’t
in the best of health,
so I’m pretty much
in charge of things here!
So I wouldn’t mind if you sometimes
call me “Captain Kaien” by mistake!
Umm, I’ll think about it.
But that ordinariness was, without doubt,
just what I was seeking.
Brother, my squad entrance process
was completed without incident.
What Seat are you?
Ah…well… My deepest apologies…
With my abilities, I’m afraid…
I couldn’t get an officer’s seat
upon entry…
I see.
You may leave.
What’s with the long face, you!
Eek!
What’s with you?
Every time you see me, you go “Eek!”
You’re going to hurt my feelings.
Hey, here’s your share, drink up!
Y-yes, sir…
Knowing you, even if I asked
why you’re depressed
you probably wouldn’t tell me…
Don’t you forget this.
As long as you’re a member of this squad,
I’m on your side no matter what.
So cool!
You stink!
Wow! You’re so cool, Sir Kaien!
You stink! You stink!
Did you hear that?
“I’m on your side.” “On your side!”
Gotta love him, huh?!
Got him wrapped around your finger!
Kiyone! Sentaro!
You guys went off and got drunk again
didn’t you, damn it!
Kuchiki! Don’t let it bother you!
I’m from Rukon District, too!
When I first came here, there were those
who gave me a hard time about it!
But for snot-heads like that,
you just have to
rub the snot right back at ‘em!
Snot-heads!
How annoying!
What a bunch
of loudmouthed drunks!
You guys need to
come back to your senses!
Sir Kaien, you’re too rough sir, too rough!
Shut up! You’re still on the clock, damn it!
Oh, don’t be a square!
I felt comfortable…being by Sir Kaien.
Take this!
Well done!
As always, Sir Kaien!
Our Lieutenant took it down!
Mission accomplished!
Ah-Ouch…
Lady Miyako…
Are you all right?
Y-Yes, it’s nothing really!
I see… That’s good.
He—y!
Hey, Miyako,
I didn’t know you were here.
Just in case
you let the Hollow get away.
I thought I should come
to take care of things.
I wouldn’t get beaten that easily!
Kuchiki, sorry, but could you call
Sentaro and Kiyone?
We’re pulling out!
Yes, sir!
Lady Miyako, thank you very much.
Take care.
Yes!
Sir Kaien had a wife…
Although a woman, she had risen
to the rank of the 3rd seat.
Despite being a woman warrior,
she was intelligent, kind…and beautiful…
I admired her…
I wanted to be like her…
She was my ideal…
Then one day,
Lady Miyako received orders
for a reconnaissance mission.
It seems we don’t know a thing
about this Hollow.
None of the Soul Reapers attacked by it
has survived.
Don’t get reckless.
My, I never thought
I’d hear those words from you.
Quit kidding around.
I cannot forgive a Hollow
that disturbs a soul’s peace.
As a Soul Reaper of the proud
Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
I must stop their evil deeds.
Lady Miyako…
Don’t worry. It’s just a
reconnaissance mission.
I’ll leave the rest to you guys.
Well then, we’ll be going.
Are you all right?
Yes… Don’t worry.
Excuse me.
Kuchiki, any report
from the reconnaissance team yet?
No sir, they still have not returned.
I-It’s terrible!
The reconnaissance team!
Miyako!
She’s unconscious,
but her life is not in danger.
And the rest?
They’re all dead.
All dead…
Sir Kaien…
This sure is terrible…
The entire reconnaissance team’s dead,
except for Lady Miyako…!
Is Lady Miyako all right?
Yeah… They said
that her life’s not in danger.
Well, that’s good…
She’s definitely someone
that Squad 13 couldn’t do without.
Yeah…
Hm? My, Lady Miyako,
should you be up already?
Wh-What’s happening?! Lady Miyako…
What was that?!
La…dy… Miyako…
What, what happened here?!
Oh, no…!
Stop it, Miyako!
O-Oh, no!
What in the world…?
Sir Kaien…
Captain…
She couldn’t have gone very far yet.
Wait, Kaien! Hold it!
If you chase her now, you’re doing exactly
what the enemy wants you to do!
But still, I must go.
It controlled Miyako,
and used her to kill off
those subordinates who cared for her.
It sullied her pride.
Please let me go…Captain!
Fine. Then I shall go with you.
Captain…
Rukia, you come too!
Yes, sir!
You two, take command of this place
and prepare the battle stations!
Understood!
Let’s go!
I smell them…
The smell…of those foolish prey…
That’s…!
Kaien!
Sir Kaien, I’ll go first
and check it out…
Captain…I beg of you.
Please let me go by myself.
Okay…
So you are the first, eh?! Boy!
Hey, you…!
How many Soul Reapers
have you eaten so far?
I wonder…how many…?
Sorry, but I don’t remember
the count.
Have you regretted it…even once?
That’s a silly question, boy.
I too, like you, have a heart.
There isn’t a night that I don’t have regrets
after eating a Soul Reaper.
Even now, I’m having regrets…
I was just regretting
that I should have used
that woman Soul Reaper more
before consuming her.
So you controlled Miyako
and made her kill her comrades…
Controlled?
No, not quite.
At that time, I was inside that woman.
It’s too bad…
that I couldn’t show you the part
where I devoured that woman
to revert to this form…
Want to come? Come!
Come, come! I’ll eat you up!
You’re fast! But…
You touched me!
Rankle the seas and the skies!
Nejibana!
What?!
You fell for it…!
When someone touches my feelers,
their zanpaku-to vanishes!
That’s impossible!
Never heard of such a power…
Sir Kaien!
Captain! But, why?!
We must help Sir Kaien!
If we help him,
what will become of his pride?
If you help him now,
it will probably save his life.
However, at the same time,
you will surely be killing his pride forever.
So, what about his pride?
What’s pride compared to one’s life?
Listen well, and remember this.
There are two types of battles, and
as long as we place ourselves in battle,
we must always be aware
of the difference between the two.
Battles to protect lives and…
battles to protect pride…!
Right now, he is fighting for pride!
His subordinates’ pride…
His own pride…
And above all…
for his beloved wife’s pride…
What’s the matter?
Aren’t you going to ask
your friends for help?
Shut up…!
I can handle you all by myself!
Is that so? Then I shall do unto you
the same as I did unto your beloved wife.
I will control your body from within,
and against your will
I shall slay your comrades!
Amusing, isn’t it?
Sir…Kaien…
What is it…?
Did you call me, girl?
Sir Kaien…
Why do you keep calling my name?
Are you that worried about me?
Are you that much…
in love with me, girl?
If you love me that much…then…
I shall eat you first!
Captain…
Run, Rukia.
Hurry up! Do you want to die?!
Why…?
Why did this have to happen…?!
Why…? Sir Kaien…!
What’s the matter?
Why won’t you attack me?!
I know why!
You’re thinking of a way to drag me
out of this body, aren’t you?!
It’s useless!
I am a spirit being, and he is a spirit being.
Now our spirits are united.
It can never be undone!
I see…
Then you leave me no choice.
I shall kill you
along with Kaien’s body!
Damn you! Are you crazy?
You’re going to kill your own man?!
Yes, I will.
I cannot allow the likes of you
to possess Kaien’s body!
You won’t get away!
At a time like this…
You idiot!
Why did you come back?!
At the time I came back,
I didn’t even have a plan.
Captain…
Thank you so much…
For letting me…fight…
Yeah…
S-Sir Kaien?
Did you…intentionally…?
Rukia… I made you go along
with my selfish request…
and put you through a horrible time…
Sorry about that,
it must have been harsh…
Thanks to you…
I can leave my heart here…
No… I haven’t done a single thing
to be thanked for…
The only person I saved was myself…
I’m detestable…
I’m not worthy of being saved…
I’m not worth
shedding blood over…ever…
Byakuya!
It’s terrible! Rukia’s execution has…
I heard.
I see, then…
And what about it?
What did you say?
The execution is tomorrow.
If that’s the decision, then I simply obey it.
Do not interrupt me
with such needless talk.
Excuse me.
H-hey, you!
Enough joking around!
It really is tomorrow!
At tomorrow noon,
your sister will be…
Don’t get so excited.
You’ll shorten your life, Ukitake.
You’ve already let
one of your men die before, haven’t you?
In any case,
she is a member of my house.
Whether she dies or gets killed,
it’s none of your business.
I would like you to refrain
from any rash actions.
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
I plan on following
Captain Ukitake anywhere!
That’s not fair, Kotsubaki!
I respect the captain too!
Well, I stalk the captain 24/7!
Well, I always check the captain’s plans
and get there ahead of him!
Isn’t that a crime?!