I'm glad you aren't in child form.
H-He did it.
He did it!
The captains...
finally did it!
Hey, Kira!
Why can't you be a little happier?
You look unmoved as always!
O-Okay...
Oh?
You're able to get up...Hinamori?!
Hinamori!
H-Hey...
Where are you going, Hinamori?!
Guys...
You guys...
What are you all doing?!
Hi-!
Hinamori?!
Damn it!
When?!
When?
What an interesting question.
You know...my Kyokasuigetsu's power
is Complete Hypnosis, right?
It can control all five senses and lead people
to hallucinate all sorts of things.
Since when?
I'm asking you when you
used your Kyokasuigetsu!
Then let me ask you this.
When did you think that I
wasn't using my Kyokasuigetsu?
Shiro...
Why?
Wait!
Captain Hitsugaya!
You're full of openings.
No...way...
I won't kill you.
Your powers should allow you
all to remain conscious,
even with the wounds
you have received.
Just watch
the outcome of this battle
as you lie on the ground
unable to do anything.
G-Guys...
Aizen!
Old man...
The Head Captain
finally shows up.
But it's too late.
You're the only remaining
Captain who can still fight.
Your death will mean the end of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
You've missed your opportunity.
You shouldn't have come out.
Don't get cocky, boy.
Do you think you're powerful
enough to cut me?
I don't think about
whether I can.
Because I already have.
Silence!
I've caught you, Sosuke Aizen!
How interesting.
You've caught me;
what are you going to do?
Is the arm you're holding
really my arm?
I'm sure you know my Kyokasuigetsu's power.
Are you saying that this is part
of your Complete Hypnosis?
I see... If I go by what I see and
what I touch then that may be true.
However,
I will never mistake the
Spiritual Pressure
of the zanpakuto stabbing
me in the stomach!
You said that I had missed
my opportunity.
It's the other way around.
An opportunity has opened up.
What's that?!
Ennetsu Jigoku...
All of your battles up to this point
were meant for this very moment.
You were setting this up
while your subordinates were
being defeated, huh?
How devious.
Devious is fine.
You will die with me in
this blazing inferno.
Stand back, Ichigo Kurosaki!
You are not a member of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
I cannot let you get
dragged into this.
Old man?!
Stand back this instant!
What about the other
squad members?
They're going to be engulfed by
this blazing inferno of yours.
They have all come
here prepared.
We will die to exterminate
great evil.
That is the will of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
Behind you, old man!
Why?
Why did Ryujinjakka's
flames disappear?
Shall I tell you?
Your Ryujinjakka is the most
powerful zanpakuto.
There is no mistake about that.
If I fought you head on, your fighting
power would surpass mine.
But by discarding
all other power
and specializing in
a single aspect,
I can combat even the
strongest zanpakuto.
His name is Wonderweiss.
Could you tell me your name,
my new comrade?
Wonderweiss...
Wonderweiss Margera.
I have an important
role for you to fill.
He is our only Mod Arrancar.
And
the name of his Resurrección is Extinguir.
Wonderweiss's role is to seal
away your Ryujinjakka.
And nothing else.
Wonderweiss has lost his
speech, intelligence, memory,
and reasoning to gain
that single ability.
Lost them?
You mean you robbed
them from him.
This is all the will
of the Hogyoku.
You cannot do anything
against the power that
Wonderweiss has traded
everything for.
Farewell,
Genryusai Yamamoto.
Go, Wonderweiss.
Do you think you can kill me if
you seal away my Ryujinjakka?
How naive.
I'm astounded by how
foolish you are.
How do you think I remained
the Head Captain
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
for over 1,000 years?
No Soul Reaper born in the
past 1,000 years has been
stronger than I am. That's why.
I wasn't holding back.
You're quite a tough fellow.
Now then...
If my Ikkotsu could
not defeat you...
This is going to hurt.
Are you fine with that?
Ah yes...
Your speech has been
wiped away.
No preliminary action
for your attack, eh?
You really are a modified improvement!
You're fast...
But...
You're still a boy.
You really are tough.
And your attacks are strong.
But you're young.
Your attacks are too straightforward.
What?
Is that all?
I'm glad you aren't in child form.
I can kill you without remorse.
Sokotsu (Dual Bone)
Sokotsu.
How pitiful...
He didn't take away
your feelings, did he?
What a cruel thing to do.
Cruel?
Souls who have become Hollows
have no purpose.
They just devour souls
for the fun of it.
How is it cruel then, to
give them a purpose?
You crushed his soul into pieces.
You're the cruel one.
I'm not going to get into a foolish
argument with you about that.
Say whatever you
like while you can.
It'll all end soon.
A foolish argument, huh?
You disregard my
words. That's why
you miss what I say.
What do you mean?
Remember what I said.
I said that Extinguir
was created for the
sole purpose of sealing
away Ryujinjakka's flames.
That means
he prevented you from creating
any new flames,
by sealing it within his sword.
But were those the only
flames you created?
Wasn't there more?
Flames, which you had
already released.
Now then...
Where do you suppose
those flames were sealed into?
You have a sharp mind,
Head Captain of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
You're well aware of
what would happen
if all of the power you produced
were discharged at once.
Containing such an explosion
is an impressive feat,
Head Captain of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
If you didn't use your
body to contain it,
your flames would have blown
away your barrier and this
small town and everything around
it would have been turned to dust.
I thank you, Genryusai Yamamoto.
You have protected my world.
Damn...you...
Genryusai Yamamoto,
I will not spare your life.
You are Soul Society's history itself.
I will finish you off with my sword.
Don't make me repeat myself, boy.
You're foolish!
Hado 96...
Ittokaso.
Here I come, Aizen!
Wait, Ichigo Kurosaki!
What?
You're exerting your energy
in the wrong place!
One's sword skill cannot improve
without a controlled mind.
You will re-do it from
here next episode.
Are you serious?!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Renji! You're awake!
Damn it!
What happened to that
bastard Yammy?!
My brother and Captain Zaraki
are out there right now.
Captain Kuchiki is fighting?!
All right, I'm going too!
Wait!
Captain Kuchiki!
Allow me to assist!
-You're in the way.
-Get lost!
Y-Yes, sir!
I'm gonna get killed!
I told you.