Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Where the hell are those guys?!
Ichigo!
Kon! Where the hell were you?!
What're you talking about?
You're the one who took off without us!
Hey, do you know where
Yuzu and Karin are?
Don't worry, they're back at home.
I just saw them there.
Really?
And you? Where were you
looking all this time?
Good, now I can go look for Ishida!
Take care of my kid sisters!
Ishida…!
Sheesh! If I knew they'd make us
help clean up,
I wouldn't have come to see.
Instead of lecturing us,
make the ones responsible do this!
It's because you made such a fuss.
What about you?!
What?!
What?
But all of them were
acting strange.
Huh?
What's Hime doing?
Hime! If you stand there looking
so cute and spaced out…
I'll kiss you!
What the hell are you blurting out
all of a sudden?!
– What?
– What?!
U-Umm… There's a TV show
I want to watch,
so let's call it a day and go home.
Huh?
Hurry, hurry. Tatsuki, you too.
H-Hey, Orihime!
Please…hurry! Let's go!
The first thing I thought was,
"I wish I didn't notice."
Then I thought,
"We have to get away from here."
One thing I know for sure…
that thing is dangerous.
Every cell in my body is tingling,
trying to tell me...
to run away!
Don’t create a panic,
and keep looking calm as
though nothing is wrong.
Come on, you two! Hurry!
Huh?
It disappeared.
I'm sorry, Orihime.
I have to change,
so you two go on ahead.
Wait, Tatsuki!
I'll catch up in no time!
No, it disappeared!
Tatsuki, um…!
You can see me, can't you?
Damn!
Damn! Damn!
Dammit!
Ishida!
20...!
Sensei, this is for you, too…
I will…
win!
What's the matter, Hime?
Is there something up there?
Run…
What?
Please run, Chizuru! Hurry!
I won't let you get away.
What's happening?!
Not the windows again?!
Hime, are you all right?
Chizuru!
Ohhh!
What'll I do?! Chizuru!
Oweee…!
What? Shedding tears?
So cute…
Geez, I don't know what happened,
but I seem to be fine. Okay?
But…
I'm fine. Though I do
like your crying face…
I prefer your smiling face.
Huh?
C-Chizuru!
W-What?!
My hand is acting on its own!
No! Why's this happening?!
What's going on?!
What's going on anyway?!
What's happening?!
What did you do to Chizuru?!
Hime?
Hmm… I just used
a little of my power.
Power?
I don't like violence.
That's why I use these seeds
from my forehead to take control of others.
And make you humans
fight amongst yourselves.
That's…!
Now, everyone, let us start!
What?!
What’s going on?
What's...?
What's happening?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Take that!
Tatsuki!
Sorry, Orihime.
I didn't notice it earlier.
That thing over there.
So you can see it, too, Tatsuki?
I can't see it.
But I know where it is.
Where the thing that made you cry is.
Hey, you big blob over there!
You picked a fight with
the wrong person!
It's been this way for a long time…
that anyone who makes
Orihime cry, will get it from me!
Move!
Next!
Hah! You're all such wimps!
Get your hands off me!
Get away, Tatsuki…
Chizuru!
S-Something’s happened to me…!
Tatsuki!
How do you feel?
The seed I shot into you will soon
take root and control your body.
In other words,
your body is mine to manipulate.
Now cry.
Shut up!
What?!
I said, shut up!
Let go of Orihime!
Huh? Do you realize the position
you're in right now?
You have almost
no control of your body.
See? How's that? Huh? Huh?
What are you doing?!
Let go! Let go!
I said, let go!
I have no need for you!
Die!
Tatsuki!
O-Orihime…don't cry, Ori…
Orihime, you have such pretty hair.
It's a nice, warm color.
What's with that hair?
You're such a show-off!
Nooo!
Why did you cut your hair, Orihime?
I just felt like it.
Why're you spacing out like that?
Huh?
Come on, let's go home.
All right.
It's because of you that
I was able to grow my hair long again.
I'll never cut my hair short again.
That's because this long hair
is proof of my trust in you, Tatsuki.
Thank you…
for protecting me until now.
So please…
Don't cry!
Ori…hime…
Tatsuki, this time, I'll protect you.
What?!
Tatsuki said, "You picked a fight
with the wrong person."
But that's not it.
You picked the wrong person
to hurt!
I will not forgive anyone
who hurts Tatsuki!
J-Just what are you?!
Using strange powers…
What is that?
Huh? What?!
What?
You didn't notice us?
No, she noticed us…
that we exist.
Huh?
After all, we've always been
the closest to you.
Huh?
Hello…Orihime.
H-Huh?!
We are the Shunshun Rikka—
The Six Princess-Shielding Flowers.
We were born in order
to protect you.
We are your powers.
Oh…
Fairies! Airborne fairies
are talking to me!
That's a cute reaction.
But we're not fairies.
Huh?
Like I said, we are the powers
inside your soul.
We are a part of you.
Furthermore,
only you can see us.
Oh, although… people like
Ichigo Kurosaki can probably see us.
Kurosaki? Why?
Well, it's because of him
that we were born.
Huh?
You talk too much!
Hey woman…
You don't need to understand
who we are or where we came from.
You seem so arrogant…
even though you're so small.
Shut up! In any case,
learn how to use us right now!
Use?
Yes!
Our power can put up
a "shield" to reject.
In order to activate it,
you must use your "heart" and
your "Kotodama – Spirit Chant."
K-Kotodama?
Hold it!
It's coming!
What've you been mumbling
about over there?
Huh, young girl?
Huh?!
Let's do it, Orihime!
Call our names!
I'm Hinagiku!
I'm Baigon!
I'm Lily!
Huh? Huh?!
Stay calm.
You must summon them
with your Kotodama.
Repeat after me.
Hinagiku, Baigon, Lily!
Hurry!
Santen Kesshun!
I reject!
What?!
Huh?!
Their power rejects what
is "outside the shield."
They put up a shield between
you and your enemy,
and reject any attacks
directed at you.
And…
our power is to reject
what is "within the shield."
We make a limited space
with our shield
and we can reverse any damage
that has been inflicted inside the space.
Now say our names.
I am Shuno!
I'm Ayame!
Shuno, Ayame!
Then recite the Kotodama.
Soten Kishun! I reject!
Tatsuki…
Woman! There's no time for tears!
I'm up next.
Huh?
My power is to reject what is on
either side of the shield.
I put up a shield inside the enemy,
and reject his material bonds.
In other words,
I can cut the enemy in half.
Now say it!
My name is Tsubaki!
Tsubaki!
Koten Zanshun!
I reject!
Ridiculous…!
I did it!
Orihime!
– Orihime!
– Orihime...!
Oh dear… I guess using all of us
so soon was too much for her.
But, Orihime really did well.
Huh?! The man's not here.
Are you sure this is the place?
I’m sure of it. The man was
beaten up and lying here…
Hey Karin!
Liar!
I'm not a liar!
He really WAS hurt and…
Say no more, Karin.
Father understands.
I've been so busy lately,
and have had no time for you.
That you would go so far as to lie
to get attention from your father…
Now Karin…
jump into my arms!
Come hug me as hard
as you can!
Huh?!
Shut up, idiot.
Let's just go home.
This place gives me a weird feeling.
Owwee!
You're hopeless.
So all's well here.
Good.
URAHARA STORE
Huh? Chad?
You're up? Good morning.
Good morning.
Um…where is this place?
Dunno…
Oh, you're up at last.
Who is that?
I don't know. But…it seems
we were saved by him.
Correct. Now then,
where to begin?
Dammit! That Ishida!
I'm definitely going to
make him cry!
I'm not able to kill in
one shot now.
But what's going on?
There're far too many for
that small amount of bait.
It's as though they were lured
by an even greater force.
But it doesn't matter.
Sensei, I swear I will avenge
your death.
Path of Destruction Four:
Byaku Rai!
Damn!
These Hollows are small fry!
If I can't even beat these Hollows,
does it mean my powers
haven't returned at all?
Is that Ichigo?!
How I longed to see you, Sis!
You're Kon, aren’t you?!
It feels so good to get
kicked like this, too.
Don't be an idiot!
But if you're in Ichigo's body,
that means he transformed
into a Soul Reaper, right?
Err… Sis, behind you…
Huh?!
Good, you seem okay, too.
Rukia Kuchiki. It's my first time
speaking to you face to face.
Totally ignored.
I get it now. So this is your doing?
Absolutely. This is a battle between
me and the Soul Reaper.
What?
But I won't let anyone in town die.
Even if Ichigo Kurosaki is defeated,
I will give my life to protect
the people of this town.
He, the Soul Reaper,
will watch me
as I protect everything and
everyone from the Hollows.
If I cannot do that…
this battle is meaningless.
What the hell do you…?
Just a minute.
Y-Yes, all this about Soul Reapers
and Hollows…it's so sudden.
Then will you deny the fact
that you were attacked earlier?
Well…
Ichigo Kurosaki is fighting Hollows
as a Soul Reaper as we speak.
And the strong spiritual energy that
he released has influenced you.
That's what it means.
However, it's all up to you,
whether you open the gate that
has appeared before you or not.
Boss...
The Sky Ridge has begun to converge.
And the preparations?
All set.
Well then, let's go.
Will you come?
I shall show you…
what is beyond the gate.
I found you…
Ishida!
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Time for Isshin Kurosaki's
Fatherly Love 101!
Now everyone, all together...
A father's love is strong!
A father's love will win!
A father's love is beautiful!
A father's love is-!
How many times must I tell you,
this is a preview!
The next episode...is great.