Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Welcome…
Soul Reaper substitute.
Are you the leader of the Bounts?
We accepted your invitation
and came!
Ichigo…
Yeah…
I am Jin Kariya.
Pleased to meet you, Ichigo Kurosaki.
How do you know my name?
I know…
Is the lady next to you
the Soul Reaper Rukia Kuchiki?
Rukia…
What's wrong?
Are you surprised?
Being surprised means you're afraid.
–What did you say?!
–Rukia, don't let them get to you!
That's right.
Nothing they say can get to us.
They’re not falling for it.
Noba! Th-This is bad!
Bad! Bad! This is really bad!
Bad! Bad! This is bad!
His eyes…
What a disgusting glare…
Ichigo…be careful.
I know…
We came to get Ishida back.
We can't give him back to you…
We need the Quincy.
Even if he's important to you,
that's not what Ishida wants!
Then what are you going
to do about it?
We'll take him back by force!
Can you?
I can!
Rukia!
All right!
Zeig dih, Friede!
You’re not getting away!
I’m not letting you go through here!
You…
Ichigo!
It's all right! Take care of Ishida!
Be careful!
Seven against one, huh?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
We Bounts are independent.
We would never fight in a group.
Especially against the likes of
a single Soul Reaper substitute.
I'm good enough by myself.
What?
You don't believe me?
All right.
Kariya…
Can you remove your crest?
Crest?
The crest is our source of power.
It allows us to summon our dolls…
Bounts don't have any attack power
if they don't have their dolls…
I shall take the time to…
watch your fight.
Now, if the other Bounts attack you,
you can attack Kariya without worry.
He has no way to block
your attacks.
I don't really understand
what's going on,
but at any rate,
I'm going to cut you down!
You're full of openings.
I've got you!
Will Ichigo be all right by himself?
He's not an idiot.
He knows that this battle is
for buying time to find Ishida.
Even so, we don't know
the Bounts’ abilities very well.
We should gather and analyze
more information…
–to make a plan…
–Aww… Shut up!
He can analyze that
while he's fighting!
Why do you think we've come along?
How trivial!
I don't like the way you said that.
I was worried about him!
Really! We can always use Noba's ability
to go directly to Ichigo!
Ah!
When we find Ishida,
we'll use Noba's space displacement
to escape this mansion.
It's possible within this area, isn't it?
Not a problem.
Wh-What is this?
This conversation makes me
look like the only idiot!
Isn’t everyone being a little rude?!
Hey!
Most of the Bounts in this mansion…
are concentrated in that room
back there, aren't they?
Yeah!
There's one more further in…
He's probably keeping watch
over Ishida…
Who is it?
A Soul Reaper?
That deduction is wrong.
The Bount you sensed is a traitor
who is being held with the Quincy.
Is it the Bount who saved Ishida?
That's right.
Are you…allied with the Bounts?
Ex-Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
Eleventh Squad,
Maki Ichinose.
Ex-Eleventh Squad?
That's right…
During the time of the last captain.
A run-away Soul Reaper, huh?
Why are you here?
Well…
–What?
–No way!
Making me see hallucinations
as you move through space
to attack me from behind.
A good idea,
but it's just a childish trick.
He's…strong…
You're a Soul Reaper, too, aren't you?
Thirteenth Squad, Rukia Kuchiki.
Why are you in a gigai?
How about drawing your zanpakuto…
Unfortunately due to certain circumstances,
I can't use it now…
But…
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
I'm surprised…
You can do Eishohaki?
You don't seem surprised at all.
Eishohaki weakens the power of Kido.
And yet you have this much power.
Plus, you aren't using your true power.
I'm not sure what the idea is,
but this isn't your true power, is it?
I would hate for you to
overestimate me.
That was my full power.
Well, in my current state…
My power hasn't entirely returned…
Well, that's fine then…
Why are you helping the Bounts?
Do you know how to become a captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads?
What?
That's right.
The method that spread
Kenpachi Zaraki's name
throughout Seireitei…
Zaraki…
became captain of the Eleventh Squad
with only his own power.
And with that, the ideal which
the previous captain and I had built
ended as a fleeting dream.
Everything…
was destroyed in that instant!
I didn't want to follow Kenpachi Zaraki
like the other squad members…
Is that why…you ran away?
Jin Kariya gave me
a reason to live again.
I lost everything, but I was able
to pick up my zanpakuto again…
For him.
He lives forever…
and is searching for what lies beyond
that by breaking all the restrictions.
I plan to lay everything I have on the line
once more for this man.
Is that why you're helping him?
It seems I've said too much.
Sorry, but…
I can't let you pass.
This Spiritual Pressure.
Kurosaki and the others are here?!
Open up!
Open this up!
Kurosaki, don't do anything rash!
I have to get out…
What? You're going to make
a snake come out of there again?!
Friede!
Even your sword cannot cut Friede.
So it seems… Then I guess
I have to attack you directly!
How?
Like this!
Flash Step, huh?
I won't miss next time!
That's pretty good…
How sloppy.
I don't plan on helping a weakling.
I know.
Is everything in place?
Of course.
What are you whispering about?!
I'm already finished.
What?!
Damn!
What is this?!
Snake Net.
What did you say?!
It's Friede's absolute field.
You can't run away anymore.
Do you know the term…
“spinal reflex?”
It's what happens when you
touch something hot
and react without the signal
reaching your brain.
What about it?
That's what this Snake Net is!
Even if you try to approach me
with Flash Step…
You can't match
Friede's reaction speed.
You can't escape anywhere.
How do you know about Flash Step?
It was inevitable that Soul Society
would try to stop our actions.
It's only natural that we learned
about Soul Reapers, isn't it?
What?
That's enough talk.
Go, Friede!
I know.
It's useless.
It's over!
How trivial.
Kariya, I'm sorry.
I damaged your mansion.
It doesn't matter.
Oh my, are you finished?
How sloppy…
What should I do?
Shall I chase down
those who ran away?
Ichinose’s on the move.
Let him handle them.
Ichinose, huh?
Besides that, his other friends
are still nearby.
Understood…
Heh…
Don't think I’m dead just yet!
Why you…
From what you said,
it seems that Rukia and the others
are in danger…
Then I've got to finish up here
and head over there!
What can you do in that condition?
Your attack isn't affecting me
as much as you think!
I see…
What incredible Spiritual Pressure.
Is that what protected your body?
Pretty much…
I can envelop my body
in strong Spiritual Pressure…
to nullify my opponents' attacks.
I didn't fight in Soul Society for nothing!
I'd like to tell you that it's quite a feat,
but there's no way to escape
from Friede's field.
I'm going to crush your body
with an attack that surpasses
that Spiritual Pressure.
Sorry. I don't plan on running away
or giving my body to your snake!
Friede!
Yeah. Here I go!
I'll tear you into pieces!
Getsugatensho!
What is this?!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
Ichigo!
Master Kariya!
Wait!
Hado 33!
That Spiritual Pressure was
a Getsugatensho…
Darn!
Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
What should we do?
Anyway, just run!
Come to think of it,
this is your hideout.
I'm not bothering anyone!
I didn't have to hold back with
my Getsugatensho.
You repelled Udagawa's technique
with only raw power…
What an amusing man…
Why you…
What a reckless guy…
Still…
This is…
Friede…
This was my favorite mansion.
It's ruined.
I'm sorry about that.
Shall I tear it apart?
I wouldn't like that…
What's with his confidence?
What's this?!
What are you doing, Udagawa?
Kariya…I'm taking your crest.
Udagawa…
Koga…do you think that things will
go well doing things Kariya's way?
Kariya's method is too roundabout.
Do you think you could do a better job?
Of course.
I don't trust you.
Kariya was in charge until now
because he had power.
But his crest is right here.
I was waiting for a chance
to steal his crest…
but I didn't think
it would be so easy.
What is this?
A fight among allies?
That's incorrect.
I told you earlier that
Bounts are independent.
We rarely help each other…
We are few in number,
but in order to advance to a new stage,
we need an excellent leader…
–Someone like me, not Kariya…
–That's impossible for you.
Stop acting tough!
I have your crest right here!
What about it?
Kariya, are you delirious?
I said that your crest,
the source of your power,
is here in my hand!
In other words,
you are now powerless.
It's possible not only for me…
but that Soul Reaper substitute boy
to defeat you!
Udagawa, why are you so panicked?
I am always calm!
You're the one who's actually panicked.
Now kneel down to me as your leader!
Your crest is…
Don't make me keep saying it.
So what?
Kariya!
What?
The only thing that can block
a doll's attack is a doll…
Could it be…?
Did I say that I removed my crest?
Curse you!
Ichinose!
A Soul Reaper?
What?!
Don't interfere!
Wh-What's this?!
It's over.
This is…impossible…
What's with that zanpakuto?
Nijigasumi.
My zanpakuto.
Nijigasumi?!
Master Kariya, I'm glad you're safe…
There's no problem.
Hey! Why in the world is
a Soul Reaper here?
It seems that you beat
Kenpachi Zaraki…
What?
Ex-Eleventh Squad, Maki Ichinose.
What did you say?
Why are you helping the Bounts?
You're going to die.
There's no need for you to know.
Come on!
I see…
I have to beat it out of you, huh?!
Here I go!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Lirin, how does
a Bount's Spiritual Pressure differ
from a regular Soul Reaper
or a Hollow?
It tastes different.
A Soul Reaper's Spiritual Pressure
is refreshing.
A Hollow's Spiritual Pressure
is smooth and rich.
A Bount's Spiritual Pressure
is a bit thick. Something like that.
Understand?
Not at all.
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
We shall begin our regular
lieutenant meeting.
Today, we shall hear our first topic
from Lieutenant Kusajishi…
Umm…uhh…
Are bananas considered as
a snack to bring…
on Hollow extermination missions?
What do you think?
That fruit is an excellent source
of nourishment.
We should probably consider it as
different than a snack.
Yea! Byak-kun,
you really understand things!
Why is Captain Kuchiki here?
I'll slice you if you don't tune in again!