Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
THREE
I’m tired…
I drank too much… Damn.
Idiot! It’s not the sake’s fault, is it?
It’s all those cigarettes you smoke!
Huh? Shuddup!
Don’t try to pick a fight with me just
because you lost yesterday, old man!
You want me to kill you?
What?! Bring it on!
Draw your sword!
I’ll sweep you up before
I sweep the streets!
Sweep me up?
Who the hell talks like that anymore?!
Die old man…! Huh?
What--?
What is that sound?
– Good morning, Captain Zaraki…!
Thank you for giving us
the honor of sweeping the streets…
If you two are gonna goof off try not to be
so obvious about it, idiots!
If you leave even a little piece of lint,
I’ll kill you.
Gentlemen! Do your best!
Why’s that bastard Aramaki
accompanying the Captain?
More importantly, weren’t there two people
riding on the Captain’s back…?
So…
Which way now, woman?
Um… Probably…
It’s this way!
That hurt!
What was that for, Yachiru?!
That wasn’t very nice.
You think it’s this way too.
Right, Kenny?
Maybe you should leave it
up to Orihime.
The Lieutenant’s probing ability is
a pretty good match to Captain’s…
Shut up, you pinball!
I’ll kill her…
Come on, keep your cool…
Anyway, you were kind
of asking for that one.
Oh, whatever…
I’m just going to go with my instincts.
All right! You go, Kenny!
FOUR
Oh…
A butterfly has just flew in.
How cute… Heh-heh…
I wonder if it’s spring here.
He sees a butterfly and talks to himself.
It must be terminal.
You can go chase after it,
if you want, Uryu.
D-Don’t tease me!
I don’t chase butterflies!
Anyway, I wish you wouldn’t call me
by my first name.
I don’t remember being on
such friendly terms with you!
What?! I don’t remember being
on friendly terms with you, either!
In that case, don’t use my first name.
Anyway, you’re acting too friendly.
Being friendly is part of
the Shiba clan legacy.
– You got a problem? Stupid fool!
– I’ve never heard of such legacy!
Shh!
– What?
– What’s wrong?
Can’t you hear that?
Now that you mention it…
What are you doing?!
He’s gone mad! Gone mad!
Don’t you think they’re steadily
headed this way?
It reminds me of a scene out
of a typical samurai drama…
It’s sto--!
W-What? What?
What’s going on?!
What is this?!
Y-You are…?!
I-It's…!
Kenpachi Zaraki,
Captain of the Squad 11!
Oh…?
You! You’re the bowl-cut
narcissist pervert from that time!
And you are…?
I’m sorry,
but I can’t remember ugly faces.
What did you say?!
Let me tell you,
after I got bandaged up,
everyone tells me
I’ve gotten more handsome!
And besides how could you recognize me
with my face covered?! Idiot!
So, he doesn’t deny being ugly…
I-Inoue?!
Ishida! Sado! Ganju!
You’re all safe?! I’m so glad!
Yachiru…! Please stop that!
Fall…! Fall down!
Master Byakuya…
It is time. Please get ready
to leave for the Sokyoku.
All right…
I’m off, Hisana…
This is awful…!
I beg your pardon, my Captain!
This Tetsuzaemon Iba fell asleep
sitting on the toilet!
I shall kill myself to atone…
Never mind…
The preparations have all been made.
Don’t try to be responsible
for everything, Tetsuzaemon.
Uh? N-No…I didn’t mean…
Don’t hide it.
You’re worried, aren’t you?
That I might still have doubts
about this execution…
And that’s why you have been trying
to buy some time,
so that I can think it through
until I’m convinced, right?
So you knew…
Don’t worry. I have no doubts.
My loyalty and dedication to
Head Captain Yamamoto are absolute.
Despised and made an outcast
because of my appearance,
he was the only one
who believed in me.
I would spend the whole of my spirit
to repay that debt to him.
I have no doubts.
If he approves of it,
even death is right!
What about you…?
Tosen…
Of course, I am the same as always.
These sightless eyes see only
the paths not dyed red with blood…
I believe that you and I
walk the same path, Komamura.
Two
What an annoyance!
What a pain!
It’s bad enough that we have trouble
with the Ryoka sneaking in,
and then some kind of
a murder happening.…
Now we’ve got some people arguing
whether the execution is right or not!
It’s the decision of the superiors,
so there’s no sense in arguing it!
Are they idiots, or what?!
Don’t you think so, Captain?
Ridiculous…
Huh..?
I have no interest in right and
wrong nor good and bad.
All I have are the pride as a captain
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
and the missions to accomplish.
I kill enemies… That’s all there is.
Oh? Is that right?
You too, Omaeda…
Don’t misread where you should stand.
Don’t forget…
If you cross me…
you too are my enemy.
Yeah… I’ll remember that…
Captain! I was looking all over for you?
Don’t just lie there.
You must hurry and prepare yourself!
Nanao…
I have a little problem…
Will you listen to it?
What is it?
You see, I put this blade
of grass in my mouth
thinking it’d make me look cool…
but I guess it was poisonous
or something.
The inside of my mouth is burning…
Spit it out!
Nanao…
What do you think I should do?
Why are you asking me?
No matter what I say…
you always do just as you wish.
Don’t worry.
I’ll walk a few steps behind you
so I wouldn’t get mixed up in any trouble.
Oh, dear…
Then I’ll be the only one again…
to get scolded by
Old Man Yamamoto.
Huh…? What…?
Uh…well… How should I put it?
Guiding someone,
you almost need luck…
Sure, you could run into dead-ends
ten or twenty times
before finding your way, right?
See? Didn’t I tell you?
That’s why I said I didn’t want
the Lieutenant to lead the way!
Ouch…! Hey, Lieutenant!
She’s biting! She’s really biting me!
Captain…
Yeah…
Being sneaky like that…
A shameful bunch, you are.
Show yourselves.
Hiding your Spiritual Pressure
to hide yourself
is no way for a captain to act.
You have the nerve to talk like that.
Are you aware of what you are doing?
Where are you running off
to with these Ryoka?
Did you lose your self-respect
when you were defeated, Zaraki?
C-Captain Komamura… Captain Tosen…
Lieutenant Iba… Lieutenant Hisagi…!
Don’t lose your head, Aramaki!
We still outnumber them.
I-It’s not a matter of numbers!
Quit whining.
Who said I’d let you fight?
Four to one.
That’s not really enough
to test my blade on.
Four to one, you say?
Are you saying you’ll take
on the four of us yourself?
I know how good you are.
But, I think you’re being a little
too sure of yourself, Kenpachi Zaraki!
You talk too much.
Just hurry up and fight already!
I’d rather have all of you at once…
May be if you attack me
from all four sides…
then one of you might actually
be able to cut me!
Uh…Captain Zaraki…
What should we do…?
You’ll get in my way. Get lost!
He didn’t have to put it that way…
Come on, Whiskers…
Kenny looks so happy.
You mustn’t get in his way!
Whiskers…?
You changed my nickname.
Kenny! We’ll continue on
our search for Ichigo, okay?!
Yeah… I’ll be right there.
Jiggles, Muscles, Monkey, Pencil!
Let’s get going!
Oh, but…
Pencil? Is that me…?
– Never mind…just hurry up!
– O-Ouch, Yachiru!
– You’re going to pull my arm out!
– Running is awesome!
“I’ll be right there,” huh?
Are you trying to provoke us?
Or do you really believe it?
Either way, it looks like you’ve lost
not only your pride,
but your sanity, too, Zaraki.
Humph! Sanity?
Sorry, but I’ve never had
a such bothersome thing from the start!
Yachiru, wait! Yachiru!
Huh…?
Are you sure it was okay to
leave Mr. Zaraki by himself…?
Of course!
No matter who his opponent is,
there’s no way Kenny would lose!
Yachiru…
That girl…!
She fears nothing…
calling the Lieutenant by her first name?
Right? What do you think of that,
Third Seat Madarame?
Huh?
Captain, in this situation…
Please allow us to go first.
Stupid… I told you four to come
at me together, didn’t I?
I knew it! Underestimating us…!
In that case,
there’s no choice but for
us two to go, right, Captain?
Wait a minute!
Why aren't you on your way
with the rest of the group?
Listen up, you there!
Don't you dare expect that
you mere lieutenants can
go up against our captain!
I should be enough for
someone like you, damn it!
Right, Captain?~
In other words you two
want in on the fight...
Oh, well...
I'll give them over to you,
so take the fight elsewhere.
If you get in my way,. I'll
get rid fo you two first.
-Roger!/N-Roger!
Well Well...
Fighting over whos gonna give or not give,
whether you're gonna take us on or not...
In the short time I haven't
seen you, you've grown cocky,
Ikkaku!
A coward who transferred to another squad
just because he couldn't
become a lieutenant in ours
has no right to lecture
me about how to talk, Iba!
Ikkaku...
Anyway, we can talk later.
We're moving away from here.
I have no wish to be killed
by our captain, you see.
Same here.
I'm getting out of here,
too.  You don't mind do you?
Do whatever you want.
It'll be the same anyway.
Well, now... We can finally
get down to business
thought the number has been cut in half.
But I guess it's probablyg ood
enough to wake me up at the least.
You still talk.
That's why I say your just...
too arrogant!
Here I come!
Take two steps back, Komamura.
I will break all his limbs.
Suzumushi Nishiki...
Benihiko.
It's over.
Not even Kenpachi Zaraki could
have possibly survived this.
What? Is that it?
No-No way!
How can he still be standing
aftering being hit by my Tenken
and Tosen's Benihiko...?
My, my...
I take back what I just said.
This won't even wake me up.
Well, I guess I'll be going.
Yeah...
Yoruichi...
Will he...
really be all right?
We're out of time...
Can he really reach Bankai today?
Let's go, Ichigo...
One more time!
Letm e make this clear.  Just
because the time in drawing near,
I have no intention of going easy on you.
Of course not!
I don't intend to let you do that either!
Renji...
Do you remember the first
time you stood up and walked?
Huh?
Of course, I don't remember!
If you don't remember it,
it means you're not conscious about it.
If that's the case, why did you stand up?
Humans beings are born
knowing how to stand up.
All Birds know how to fly.
And fish know how to swim.
That is called Instinct.
Because it is a natural instinct,
What is what I am reminded of.
He probably knows instinctively...
that he has that power.
That is why I believe...
that he will be the one to reach Bankai!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Yo! How is everybody doing?
I am your idol, Kon!
This is the last installment
of the Soul Reaper Guide Book!
Last on the list is that legendary man...!
The new Illustrated Guided
to Soul Reapers Golden
Will begin right after the
next episode! Stay tuned!
You mean there's more?!