So that’s the last of it, right?
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely sure?
Get off my back!
How many times do you need to make sure?
A father may rob his son’s future.
It’s only right to confirm multiple
times that you’re certain about this.
And I’m saying to stop
asking me again and again.
I guess you’re right.
All right, let’s move on to our last step.
Just place your Spiritual Pressure
in here and it’s done.
Okay, please do it.
Right.
He wields that huge sword
as though it weighs nothing.
Coming at you!
You’ve gotten quite a bit
better at wielding Fullbring.
But…
You still have a long way to go.
Kugo.
A visitor.
I’m letting her in.
Oh, if it isn’t the healing item.
Uh…
How do you do?
I’m…uh…
Skip the greetings.
You’re just in time for a job.
Hurry up and heal him.
Kurosaki!
I-Inoue?
I see…
Chad brought you here, didn’t he?
Kurosaki…
That’s right.
I know you didn't want Inoue to get involved,
but you’ll need her help from here on.
Hey, Chad…
I know.
I didn’t come here to assist Ichigo.
I had Yukio make a separate
room with a higher setting.
I’ll be training there by myself.
If we’re going to fight Tsukishima,
then I can’t be standing
around doing nothing.
All right… Do as you wish.
I will.
We’re outta here, Mr. Tsukishima.
And we’re taking Kurosaki with us.
But if you want to make
a spectacle of yourself,
then I suggest you stay here.
Damn it…
Chad! What's wrong?!
Hey!
I was cut for sure…
Yet no one seemed to notice
that I had been cut.
There's no wound…no pain either.
Even I'm tempted to question
if I've really been cut.
Inoue was right.
His ability is inexplicable.
I don't know what he did to me,
but the only way to take him
on is to become stronger.
I must get stronger…as fast as I can…
What’s taking so long?
Isn't he healed yet?
Please wait just a bit longer.
I can't wait.
You’re good, right, Ichigo?
Yeah.
Wait, Kurosaki!
No, Inoue! Look out!
A Santenkesshun?
You’re going to block my “Cross
of Scaffold” with that thing?!
You're wrong.
How so?!
Shitenkoshun.
It diffuses the impact of an attack
by exploding the moment it’s hit.
And at the same time,
it automatically responds with
a reactive attack of its own.
A detonation shield, eh?
Now that’s nasty.
Call it what you want.
If you don't want to get hurt,
then don't attack when I tell you not to.
Inoue…
When did you?
It's been seventeen months
since you lost your powers.
It's not as though Sado and I
did nothing during that time.
We had faith.
That one day,
you’d regain your power to fight.
So both me and Sado…
made a decision.
That when that time comes…
we won’t be a burden to you.
Don't worry about us.
We want you to focus on
getting your powers back.
I see…
Thanks, Inoue.
All right!
Let's keep going, Ginjo!
Yeah.
He figured that my reach
makes in-fighting difficult,
so he changed tactics by moving in closer…
Guess again!
Why do you think this has
a hilt on the blade?!
It's to compensate for the
disadvantage of my reach!
Is that right?
Still…
he's fighting with much more
efficiency than earlier.
Which means I was right to bring her here.
He’s at his best…
when somebody he has to protect is near him.
But still…
Riruka…
How come you're crouching over there?
Umm…
There was nothing to lean on, so…
Yukio! Make a table and a chair!
I'm going to have my snack here. Hurry it up!
Huh?!
He can do that?!
No way.
What?!
Can you do that for me too? Please?!
Sure.
What the hell, Yukio!
Riruka, you should learn
to ask nicely like her.
Now’s a good time. Why
not have her teach you?
Just wait till I get out of here…
Huh?
What're you looking at?
You can look, but you can’t have any.
It's so good!
That’s right! Be thankful
and don’t eat it too fast.
Uh-huh!
Hey! You ate it already?!
You only get one!
Oh, fine!
Eat it. Just eat it!
My god! How audacious are you?!
Now I want to know what
your parents are like!
You’re right. I'd like to as well.
What? You don’t have parents?
Nope.
I heard they were really abusive.
My brother thought they
were going to kill me,
so he ran away with me when I was a baby.
Oh.
So your brother who’s raising
you now is your parent?
Well, I'd like to see his face!
Sorry. He’s already dead.
A distant aunt is paying for
my living expenses right now.
If my grades drop, so do my funds.
But thanks to her, I make sure
to study, so I’m kind of glad.
I'm leaving!
You’re boring me with your stories!
Huh?!
How can you talk about
something like that with
a smile on your face?!
There must be something wrong with you!
No…
Because I've already been saved.
I'm able to laugh and talk like this…
all thanks to Kurosaki.
Are you stupid?!
That's not what I was asking!
And besides, I wasn't listening to
what you were saying earlier either!
I'm sorry…
See you!
Wait! Are you really going?!
Look, there're still some donuts left.
No thanks!
I was tired of eating them anyway!
If you want them, help yourself!
Thank you!
You really are a nice person, Riruka!
You’re such an idiot…
Strange…
I don't feel anything from his sword.
I thought it was because
I wasn't used to fighting him
at first, but that’s not it…
I don’t feel anything
no matter how many times I strike him.
And it’s also different from what
I felt against Gin Ichimaru…
In his case, his mind
wasn’t focused towards me.
But this guy’s different.
He's looking straight at me,
but it's like there's a lid on his mind.
I don't feel a thing.
Tsukishima was the opposite.
He barely looked at me, but I felt
his intent to kill all over me.
Is it because it’s a Fullbring
sword and not a Zanpakuto?
Is that why I can’t
sense what’s inside him?
Or is it because I don’t
completely trust him yet?
You’re too distracted.
This is supposed to be a battle, remember?
I guess I'll just have to drag you back.
Kurosaki!
You want Ichigo to become strong, don't you?
Then be quiet and watch.
It seems that during the time
he lost his Soul Reaper powers,
he also lost the resolve to face battle.
Hold on, Ichigo.
I'll drag you back into the battlefield.
Why?
Just what the hell are you?!
Shut up.
Quit whining. It's irritating.
Just what are you after?!
Are you…
Are you really on my side?!
Hey, what are you talking about?
I told you our purpose at the beginning.
Our goal is to have you regain
your Soul Reaper powers.
We’re teaching you Fullbring
as a preliminary step.
And this is how you're doing it?
Sorry, but after what
you’ve just done to me,
I’m having doubts about
trusting you as my ally!
Like I said, what’re you talking about?
What?!
If you don’t fully trust me…
Then why did you even agree
to this training I proposed?
Did you think trust didn't matter
as long as it helped get your powers back?
You thought you could escape from us
even if we suddenly turned on you?
Without your powers?
Don't make me laugh.
The reality is that, right
now, you've lost your sight
and are quite helpless.
Damn you!
You fool…
It was over for you
the moment you stepped
into this field with me!
Bastard…
What's the matter? Do you want to die?
Dodge for your life, coward.
Yukio.
Inoue! What's wrong?!
I wonder what happened…
Why don't you see for yourself?
Ginjo!
It's useless…if that’s all you’ve got.
Kurosaki!
Koten…
Don’t bother.
Your voice won't reach outside from there.
And no matter what you try,
that cage is unbreakable.
Look on the bottom right of the cage.
You cannot break or go through that cage.
It's a restricted area.
That's the rule of this game.
Sorry.
I can't hear what you're saying.
Where is he? Left or right?!
Nice try…
Hey, you’re dodging better than I expected.
Even if I can't see…
I can tell your movements
by your presence and sound.
Presence and sound, huh?
What's wrong?
You said you could dodge me.
From my presence or sound, was it?
Don't make me laugh!
As if you can dodge me like that!
I’ve been going easy on you!
I’ve let you evade me!
Did you think you were dodging
me with your own skills?!
It's over.
I’m going to kill Chad and Inoue.
You saw this coming, didn’t you?
The moment you realized
I wasn’t on your side.
I can’t speak!
And I can’t see him!
Don't worry.
I'm going to kill you, too.
Wait Ginjo!
Stop!
I can see Ginjo?!
No, that's not… It’s
not him I’m seeing.
That’s his…
Spiritual Pressure!
Kurosaki!
Well done.
It's complete.
What?
The moment Fullbring is complete,
somebody has to make sure to contain
that power by putting their life on the line.
Because the soul squeezed into
the item is released all at once,
without that person,
the wielder’s body cannot
withstand the force.
That's why I needed you to complete
Fullbring in front of me…
Ginjo…
Sorry…
I was a cheesy bad guy, I know.
Welcome…
to Xcution.
I put up quite a good act as a villain!
You were terrible.
First of all, you talk too much.
That won’t cut you for
being the final boss.
Who cares?! As long as I looked evil!
Second, you were playing dirty.
Only a small fry that gets killed in
the beginning would do such a thing.
Oh, come on…
Xcution Dictionary.
What's this?
Yes... All I need now is that
one, and this level is cleared!
You think it'll go so smoothly?
Huh?!
A ball?!
Why?!
Too bad.
Start over!