I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
DEPARTMENT OF
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT
I never thought that we'd be
guarding a place like this…
There are a lot of bizarre things
in the Department of Research
and Development.
Seems there are a number of
dangerous tools in there, as well…
I see…
Hey!
Who’s that?
A ryoka?!
DEPARTMENT OF
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT
It’s a fine day today.
I leave it to you.
Understood.
Lieutenant, what could it be?
I don't know…
But something with immense energy
is coming this way.
Lieutenant!
It seems the ryoka has invaded.
We're going to intercept them!
What the heck is
this Spiritual Pressure?
It's different from before!
Yeah… It's difficult to tell
because of all the battles
happening around us,
but one of the Bounts’
presences disappeared.
But this is a different one!
What's wrong?
It's probably…
Is it Kariya?
So he's finally come out…
Which way?
That way!
All right!
Chad!
Ichigo…
Are you all right?
Yeah…
No problem.
You sense the Bount, don't you?
Yeah… It's Kariya.
Ichigo!
Let's hurry!
How pathetic!
Isn't there anyone good around here?
Damn! Get her!
Nieder!
Leave it to me!
The Quincy boy, huh?
Tsk! What an obnoxious boy!
So you're luring me in…
That's pretty interesting.
You just don't learn.
Why don't you give up
on revenge already?
This isn't revenge.
What about you?
Why are you doing this?
There is no meaning to this battle.
Huh? What are you talking about?
For that matter,
aren't Quincies and Soul Reapers
supposed to be enemies?
Why are you allying yourself
with the Soul Reapers?
I'm not allying myself
with the Soul Reapers…
I just want to stop pointless battles.
You're not making any sense…
I will put an end to this battle
on my pride as a Quincy!
Well, fine.
If you want to die so badly,
then just do as you like.
Rantao…you know about
Ishida's artifact, don't you?
How long will it hold up?
I don't know.
It may become useless today…
It may be tomorrow…
If it goes off accidentally…
It may blow away everything…
within a radius of
several thousand meters…
I made up my mind…
I'll do this,
no matter what happens…
I can't allow them to roam freely!
Here I go!
Enjoy yourself!
This is my true power!
Hyapponjin!
Take this!
My, my… That wasn't good at all.
Damn!
It can't be helped…
He’s just a boy…
Don't underestimate me!
Oh my. You're pretty fast.
Why did you stop fusing with me?!
Shut up!
I hate being physically fused with you
throughout the battle!
I know what you mean.
How mean!
So what are you going to do,
Quincy Boy?!
With that kind of attack,
I can only dodge at best…
At this rate…
If you're not coming,
then I will!
That's a pretty gentle attack.
Damn! What a time for
me to lose power.
Compared to before…
it's definitely unstable.
If it’s like this,
there’s no point even if it hits…
My power went negative
on my third attack…
That's why it hardly
had any power…
When I release…
When my energy
becomes positive,
that's when I have the power
to destroy my opponent…
But…
when that energy
swings towards positive…
This arrow will be triggered
and blow away everything around it…
Of course, it will also blow away
the person who fired it…
What's wrong, boy?!
What's with the long face?
What are you brooding about?!
Can I do this? Is it possible
for me to control this arrow?
No! I've got to do this!
That should…
What?!
This is my true form!
I boast perfect protection
in this form!
Your attacks are now meaningless!
It seems that arrow's power
is different every time…
In other words, he can't control it.
But if I didn't come out just now…
it would have been a bit close.
Stop with the blasé explanation!
Damn… Just when I was able
to fire at high power…
No. Don't give up.
I mustn't forget this feeling…
And keep on firing…
Come on!
That's good!
Damn!
Hit…
Hit!
What a fool…
Using a weapon that
he can't even control…
Come on, come on, come on!
Say…
If you really want to fight me,
bring a better weapon now, won’t you?
Really. What a fool…
You're naive…
Where…are you going?!
There should be
a Bount Crest here.
Crest?
The original.
The first crest created…
I've never even heard
of that crest.
I'm not asking you where it is.
I just came to take it.
What are you going to do
once you get it, Kariya?!
You're…
This man…He's dangerous…
I know… I know that
a lot better than you do…
Kariya! What do you plan to do
with this crest you’re talking about?!
Defeat me if you wish to know.
Damn!
Where'd he go?
He ran away!
Hey!
Tell me!
Where is the crest that
he's searching for?!
I'm very sorry…
I don't know.
Even if we don't know
where it is,
we can just follow
Kariya's Spiritual Pressure…
I see!
All right. Let's go!
It's resonating!
It seems like it's in this room…
Where is it?
Kariya!
Bankai!
Tensa Zangetsu!
I won't let you do as you please!
This is a problem.
I've got to deal with you before
I can take my time to look for the crest…
Run, Chad!
Chad!
Kariya!
I can't let you…
keep beating me!
What is that?!
This is…
I never thought it was in here…
It was hidden in
a place like this…
This is the crest
I was searching for!
Mein wappen,
unter der erde schläft!
Vereinige sich mit mir,
und werde mein kraft!
Ichigo!
Kariya! What did you do?!
In this moment,
I have gained the ultimate power.
What?
Ultimate…power?
For eons, I investigated
and researched ancient records,
And I had Ichinose search for it…
He was able to track it
to the Department of Research
and Development…
The name of this original crest
is the Jokai Crest.
It is a crest that can purify
and erase everything.
Jokai Crest…
This is where the soul experiments
that created
the Bounts were done.
What?!
When the experiment was
canceled after the accident…
The incredible energy that
made up the entire foundation
of the experiment in the Jokai Crest
was sealed away…
And now…
I have become one with that energy…
Do you know what this means?
It means that
I can blow away Seireitei
at any time by releasing
the energy of the Jokai Crest.
What?!
Like I’d believe something
like that!
Believe what you like!
I never said that anyone
should believe me!
Those eyes…he's serious!
R-Really?
So what are you going to do?
It's fine if you attack me,
but I'll release the Jokai Crest
when you do…
Attack me if you dare!
Tell the foolish people of Seireitei…
I'll give you a one-day grace period.
Until then,
tremble in suspense!
Hey! Wait!
Ichigo!
Chad!
If what he said was true…
I wonder if he died.
Oh my. It seems that way.
Well, we were able to
come here, thanks to that kid…
I'll thank him for that at least…
Where are you going?
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Kariya got away from us again.
I really should have come
in my gigai.
There's a gigai that Master Mayuri
is using for his experiments…
in the Department of Research
and Development.
I can borrow it?
A squid-type, an octopus-type,
or a starfish-type.
Which one would you like?
I don't want any of them!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Ow!
Huh? it's Mayuri Kurotsuchi!
What's wrong? You look terrible!
Carry me inside.
Should I carry you…here?
Owww! Hey!
You're going to tear me apart!
Then how should we carry you?!
By piggyback.
Ready! Rock Paper Scissors!
You two…
Rock Paper Scissors!
If you don’t…
…want me piggyback…
Rock Paper Scissors!
…then just…
…tell me straight out!
Rock Paper Scissors!
On my honor as a Quincy!