Ginjo!
Well done.
It's complete.
What?
The moment Fullbring is complete,
somebody has to make sure to contain
that power by putting
their life on the line.
Ginjo…
Sorry… I was a cheesy bad guy, I know.
Welcome
to Xcution.
O-One...
One hundred!
That’s it! That’s my limit!
I’m not doing it any more!
What?
You tired already?
What do you mean “already”?!
How many sets of a hundred pushups
are you gonna make me do?!
That was only your fourteenth set.
Only?! Are you crazy?
You trying to turn me into
a wrestler or something?!
Stop whining with just fourteen sets.
Why don’t you do one more
set to match your name?
You had to say that!
I hate those kinds of puns!
Liar.
I know you wear a T-shirt
that says “15” on it.
How do you know that?!
That stalker network of
yours gives me the creeps!
Kurosaki’s working hard...
I’m coming in!
Riruka, you came in
before I answered again.
Shut up!
I’m leaving your breakfast here!
Oh, wait!
Let’s eat together, Riruka!
I just had some donuts, so no thanks!
It seems like…
all she eats are donuts…
Okay, I’ve finished loading it.
Thank you for everything, Yukio.
Don’t mention it.
I do this all the time.
Okay, I’ll be leaving then.
What about Ichigo?
He’s not going to school today.
He said he completed his Fullbring
and just has a few kinks to work out.
Then it looks like he
might be done tonight.
Sado, what made you decide to go back
to school all of a sudden?
Did something happen?
You haven’t been coming all
this time, so…you know…
If Tsukishima’s aim is
preventing the reawakening
of Ichigo’s powers,
was it really necessary to attack
Ichigo's family and you?
Wouldn’t that have
been counterproductive?
Could he have actually been trying to
corner Ichigo to induce
him to acquire Fullbring?
For what purpose?
I don’t know.
But it makes more sense that way.
I think the key to answering
that question…
lies in Tsukishima’s powers.
Have you noticed anything different
since that day, Inoue?
Yes.
Remember how I said
I could remember Mr. Tsukishima
inside my old memories?
He’s a very dear person to me…
That’s what I find myself
thinking sometimes.
I see.
Then we can’t leave things as they are.
In any case, I think it’d be a good idea
for us to sort through
what’s happened so far.
I agree.
Hey, you!
What? You’re not here?
You put me through all this trouble and
now you disappear without a word!
I’ll bet you’re just an airhead
that all the boys fussed over-
Dear Riruka,
Breakfast was delicious.
Thank you so much!
Let’s have donuts together again.
S-Stupid!
Well? How’s Ichigo Kurosaki doing?
He’s doing well.
He’ll be a Fullbringer by tonight.
Oh yeah?
What? Not interested?
It’s not that.
But won’t Mr. Tsukishima sense it, too?
Yeah…
He’ll probably start making his move.
What do you mean by “start
making his move”?
Yukio, let me out.
Isn’t Ichigo what Tsukishima is after?
That attack said it all—even
I could tell that.
And prior to that, there were a number of
strange incidents happening around
Ichigo that looked like
Tsukishima’s doing.
Saying he’ll “start making his
move” doesn’t make sense.
He’s already taking action.
What?
Women are such nitpickers.
What was that for?!
I think you deserved that, Kugo…
Whatever.
Thus far, he’s only messed with Ichigo
to fan his sense of imminent danger.
But now, Ichigo’s Fullbring
is about to become complete.
This time, he’ll attack like he means it,
that’s what I’m saying.
Attack?! Why?!
What is it that he wants to
do with Ichigo’s powers?
Who knows?
What?! You’re so unreliable!
But even Tsukishima should have a hard time
dealing with Ichigo once
he’s acquired Fullbring.
If Tsukishima wants Ichigo…
His first move would be
to eliminate those who are
trying to protect Ichigo
and then isolate him.
That means we’re in danger, too.
Yeah…
And Chad and Orihime Inoue
would definitely become targets, as well.
Orihime!
‘Morning, Tatsuki.
Good to see you again, Chad.
What happened to you?!
You haven’t been coming to school at all!
You okay?
Solid as always.
Now if only Ichigo would…
Kurosaki said he won’t be coming today.
What?!
How come you know about
Ichigo’s business?
Ichigo’s doing his best
to get himself together.
Did Ichigo get involved
in something again?!
You’re in the way.
That’s none of your business.
Come on, we’ll be late for class.
Orihime, you too!
You mean those two are targeted?!
Then why’d you let them leave here?!
We had no choice.
We can’t keep them locked
up here for our convenience.
I’m guessing they’ll look
into Tsukishima on their
own to help Ichigo.
Huh?!
But right now, we can’t take the risk
of joining them in trying to determine
Tsukishima’s objective.
We must protect Ichigo at all cost
in order to achieve our goal.
But…
I’m sorry, but it’s the best we can do.
Yukio, I’m going to rest for a bit.
Sure, I’ll handle things.
Inoue!
How’d it look?
I went around the campus,
but didn’t sense that Spiritual
Pressure from anyone else.
That means it was only from
Tatsuki and the other two.
Those three definitely
had traces of contact
with someone possessing
strong Spiritual Pressure.
We can’t prove it, but was it Tsukishima?
Oh no!
Does that mean he did something
to Tatsuki and the others?
It’s okay, Inoue.
Nothing seems out of the
ordinary about them.
But what’s certain is that he’s
always lurking around Ichigo.
Mr. Tsukishima is?
What is it?
No… I’m all right.
Let’s go.
Yeah.
What was that…
Why?
Who’s that girl?
Beats me.
Maybe she’s looking for someone?
Jeez…
These things make it harder to see.
That girl’s causing
me nothing but trouble.
Stop that, you’re acting silly.
Admit it,
You care about “that girl.”
You’re wrong!
I just came to buy donuts.
And I just happen to pass by the
school that Chad and that girl go to…
So I just thought maybe I should
check things out for a bit…
Did you just say “Chad and that girl”?
It’s nothing.
Who are you?
By “that girl,” did you mean Orihime?
I might’ve…
I came to see her.
Where are they? Chad and that girl…
They already left…
Huh? Then where are they now?
I don’t know what business
you have with them,
but I’m not going to tell someone so suspicious…
Tell me.
It’s important!
KARAKURA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Thank you very much.
Sado…
Well?
Did you find out anything?
Ishida was told he couldn’t
leave the hospital yet,
but he’s been gone since around noon.
I’ll try calling Ishida.
Okay.
Riruka?
Huh?
What’re you doing here?
It's not what it looks like!
I came to buy donuts when…
At the hospital?
It doesn’t matter where I buy them!
Never mind that!
What’re you two doing here?!
We came to see our friend…
You mean, Uryu Ishida?
Oh, I see…
So the two of you are racking your
meager brains to investigate Tsukishima?
Why do you think that?
Don’t patronize me!
You must’ve realized…
Tsukishima is making contact
with Ichigo’s classmates.
You can’t fool me.
We had no such intention.
But Kurosaki’s been
working desperately hard,
so we thought we might lend a hand…
Are you guys stupid?!
You’re up against Tsukishima!
Didn’t Ginjo tell you?!
He’s the kind of guy who kills
Substitute Soul Reapers
and even his friends!
And you’re trying to investigate
him by yourselves?!
You guys are way over your head!
You’re right.
I’m not very strong,
and I’m not sure that
doing this will even help.
But Kurosaki has always protected me.
That’s why I can’t
do anything knowing that
Kurosaki might be a target.
I want to help him…even if only a bit…
What’s the matter?
No, it’s nothing.
Anyway, give up your crazy idea…
of trying to find Tsukishima.
That’s all I’m saying!
Riruka.
Thank you.
What was that for?
You’re creeping me out!
...is not available.
At the tone, please leave your message.
It’s no use…
Let’s head back to where
Ginjo and the others are.
We should be able to contact
Ishida before it gets dark.
We can come up with a new plan after that.
Like Riruka said,
investigating that guy by
ourselves is dangerous.
Sado,
what’s wrong?
No…it’s nothing.
I wonder if there is any other way
to learn about Mr. Tsukishima…
Sushigawara?
The guy who was with Tsukishima
when you were attacked?
It certainly seems likely that he knows
about Tsukishima’s powers…
But isn’t he also a Fullbringer?
Yes. But…
He didn’t seem all that strong.
Here?
If he said he was from
Miyashita High School,
MIYASHITA HIGH SCHOOL
then this is the place.
I don’t have a good feeling about this…
Excuse me.
We’re looking for someone.
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
Hey!
What do you and your bimbo want?!
You mocking us?!
Jeez, what’re they doing…?
I warned them not to…
If they cause a scene,
Tsukishima will notice them.
Yes, I will.
What’re you doing out here?
Riruka…
Come back here, dammit!
Why is this happening?!
I sort of figured they weren’t
the type to talk with us.
You were right. They wouldn’t listen…
I thought it was a good idea, though.
We couldn’t learn a thing
about Mr. Tsukishima.
What’s wrong?!
When did we become friends
with Mr. Tsukishima?
What’re you talking about?
Didn’t we go with him to the Soul
Society to rescue Kuchiki…?
No, that’s not right…
Inoue!
What is the matter with me?
Shall I tell you?
Hi there.
Riruka tells me you’ve
been looking for me.
So what’s up?
Mr. Tsukishima, you didn’t…!
I did…
But don’t worry about it.
It was all in the plan.
Impressive!
In just this short time,
you’ve increased your power tremendously.
I did it to defeat you!
Oh, it’s Yukio.
I thought all he did was play
video games by himself,
but he’s learned how to
play together with others.
Shitenkoshun!
Sado!
I’m okay.
We can beat him with just our powers…
Not bad at all.
You might be quite useful to me.
What?!
Brazo Izquierdo…
Del Diablo!
Now, Inoue!
Tsubaki!
Mr. Bunny is done.
Orihime.
Did you wait for me, again?
Why?
Inoue! What’s wrong?!
Why is this happening?
Inoue!
It’s time to wake up now.
Who am I?
Bastard! What did you do to Inoue?!
What, you say?
The same as what I did to you.
Okay, Ichigo! Show everyone your
completed Fullbring power!
Huh? Why should I?
You’ve become stronger. Admit
it, you’re curious too, right?
Not really.
I don’t feel like showing
it off at this moment.
But I want to see it right now!
Show it to me!
Pretty please!
Xcution Dictionary!
Ichigo!
Your Fullbring is nearly
complete! Congratulations!
Uh…Yeah…
I made this to celebrate the occasion!
See? It’s a Fullbring doll.
It comes with a carrying strap too.
I even made you into a
character in the game.
Thanks…
Today is an auspicious day!
Ichigo!
This celebration is for
you! Try to look happier!
Uh…Yeah…