The pendulum swings back.
Our story, which has progressed deep, deep into the future
will stop temporarily and
turn back to the past
for just a short time.
And so, with frightening speed,
we must go far into the distance.
It must be known.
And yet, it must not be known.
There, we will find
the truth of the mask.
Good morning!
'Morning.
Good morning, Lieutenant!
Are you ready, Captain?
Oh, just come on in.
Excuse me.
Huh?
You're in your usual garb!
It's festival time.
I told you to dress up
to the nines, Sosuke!
You're dressed
normally too, Captain.
I don't count since I'm a captain.
Trying to only make me
dress up funny won't work.
First of all,
it's not a festival.
It's a ceremony.
It's an auspicious occasion.
So it's like a festival.
It's different.
You are so picky.
By the way, Captain…
What is this music you're playing?
It's new music from
the World of the Living.
Nice, huh?
I don't really know.
Then why'd you bring it up?
Hello!
I'm Captain Shinji Hirako
of Squad 5!
Can someone open up?!
Cripes! Squad 1's barracks
are always so intimidating.
It makes me nervous.
That's why I hate coming here.
Is that the face of someone
who's nervous?
Just because these ceremonies
are a bore to you,
please don't make such a fuss.
Oh shut up!
You can't see my expression
from there, Sosuke.
It's open. Please enter.
I know that!
Yo, baldy Shinji!
That face of yours
is as flat as ever
and ready to be
stomped on, huh?
Hiyori! How dare you?!
What? Don't expect me to say sorry!
I haven't said anything yet!
Then, I really don't
need to apologize!
Say you're sorry, idiot!
You're hopeless.
What's the big idea, Love?!
You think it's okay
to pound the head
of a lieutenant from
another squad?!
Your captain's not here.
Someone has to look after you.
Don't talk to me like I'm a kid!
I'm under no obligation to
apologize to a guy like that!
See that face?!
Man, he irks me!
Okay, I get it.
Oww! Lemme go!
Come on! You big ape!
Captain, that's enough
from you too.
Please don't make such faces
in front of the squad members.
Is everyone here?
Just about.
Squad 11 isn't here yet.
He cut out.
Looks like he still doesn't listen.
Jeez, he may be
a tenth-generation Kenpachi,
but what a tiresome guy.
Why'd they promote such
a pig like him to be captain?
Captain!
They had no choice.
For generations, the captain of
Squad 11 has been a Kenpachi.
That's the custom.
If anyone's to blame for that,
it's the previous Kenpachi
who lost to him.
You're right.
It's so pitiful, I could cry.
Oh? I don't approve of
criticizing people.
Oh.
You're early today,
Shunsui.
What're you saying?
I'm always the first here.
I slapped his butt and
woke him up today.
Don't talk so casually
to other captains.
I don't see Hikifune.
She's not coming today?
It seems she's already
getting started with that side.
What was the hurry?
It's not urgent.
She could've taken her time.
I'll say.
But man…there's been such
a turnover of captains lately.
Rose just joined Squad 3
the year before last.
And next, it's Squad 12.
Are things gonna be all right?
Well, change is inevitable
in everything.
And it's just our turn.
When you think about it,
the only ones who've been captains
for over a hundred years
are myself, Ukitake
and Old Man Yama.
Right?
Not even.
There's also Captain Unohana.
Oh! That's right!
I'll get scolded for
forgetting my great senior!
Whoa, now I'm scared.
What are you so scared of?
No… Nothing.
Just about talking how it's
such a nice day, it's scary.
Right?
Y-Yes.
Our captain is such an idiot.
Really.
Squad 3 had a retirement.
Squad 12 had a promotion.
Unlike Squad 10, they didn't have
a death in the line of duty.
It's peaceful and a good thing.
– Yes.
Promotion?
Hey Sosuke!
Pardon me.
I couldn't help but listen in.
That's okay, Sosuke.
What is it?
We lieutenants haven't
been told anything.
Was Captain Hikifune of
Squad 12 promoted?
She didn't retire?
Yes.
Promoted from captain…
Does that mean to Central 46?
To be promoted from
captain to Central 46…
I've never heard of it happening.
Not Central 46.
She went to…
the Royal Special Task Force.
Squad Zero.
Royal Special Task Force?
What's this?
Are you all blocking the corridor?
Pardon me!
Congratulations.
If you have
a congratulatory message,
say it to him in person,
Captain Unohana.
What?
The newcomer is that guy
from Squad 2?
You call that erasing
your Spiritual Pressure, Kisuke?!
I let you notice on purpose.
You're too cocky.
As usual, you're such
a power fighter, Yoruichi.
Get real!
I was just loosening
the tightness in my shoulder.
But you're not the type
to get stressed out.
I'm at that age where
one has lots of worries.
Worries?
Isn't that the farthest thing
in this world for you?
Ouch!
And what about you?
How is that coming along?
Oh…
Well, I've filled the outer moat.
I see.
I'm counting on you,
division leader.
Right.
Oh yes. What did you
want to see me about?
Oh… The Head Captain
summoned me.
Huh?
I recommended you for
captain of Squad 12.
Huh? What do you mean?
There will be
a captain's exam soon.
Welcome back, Lady Yoruichi!
Lady Yoruichi?
I'm tired. I'm so tired.
Lady Yoruichi!
Lady Yoruichi,
you make too much of that man.
Too much, too little…
I don't make anything of him.
Please don't joke.
I always know what's on your mind!
It may be presumptuous of me,
but I'll speak my mind anyway.
I also think it was a mistake
for you to put him in charge of
one of the five units
of the Stealth Force,
the Confinement Troops.
The Confinement Troops
keeps an eye on
and apprehend
dangerous elements.
It is a crucial department.
He is not suited to
be in charge!
I have a message from the Captain.
Third Seat, you are present,
aren't you?
Respond!
Third Seat!
I'm so sorry. I was taking a nap.
W-What is this smell?!
Huh?
Oh… I've been cooped up in here
for quite a while, so…
I've been doing some research.
He's unclean and silly.
He's a lazy ordinary boor!
He's not a go-getter,
that's true.
Still…
Why are you so
hung up on Kisuke?
I am not!
What I want to say is…
Oh, just let it go.
That Lady Yoruichi!
He may be an old acquaintance,
but she's being too easy on him!
I must keep warning her!
What does he think of
his position as a Soul Reaper?!
Wandering around
day in and day out.
Go, go!
Besides shirking his duties,
he has no public morals!
Misappropriation of funds!
Drinking sake during the day?!
Once she learns
how he really is,
Lady Yoruichi will surely
change her mind about him.
I will tear away
his sheep's clothing
and open Lady Yoruichi's eyes!
Excuse me!
Yo!
Perfect timing.
Oh, hello!
Kisuke here is going to
take the captain's exam.
Lady Yoruichi!
You don't mean to allow him to?!
I do.
And I think you should
accompany him.
Huh?!
Normally, only captains
are allowed to be present,
but I made a special request.
W-Why must I go?
No need to hesitate.
I know that you have
feelings for Kisuke.
Huh?
W-What are you saying?!
Don't be embarrassed.
I've known all along that
you've been tailing Kisuke.
No, you got it wrong!
Please don't belittle me!
I tailed him because I wanted proof
that he is lazy and incompetent.
I wanted to confirm that he's
not worthy of your recommendation!
Please read this.
And I'm sure you will
change your mind!
Oh look, Kisuke.
Your daily activities are
recorded here in great detail.
Oh, that's amazing.
He shirks his duty as a member
of the 13 Court Guard Squads
and wanders around
Rukon district in search of fun.
He produces no results!
Is this the behavior
of a Third Seat?!
If you want to vindicate yourself,
speak up!
No, you're absolutely right.
Wha—?!
You don't change,
do you, Kisuke?
Oh well…
Soi Fon! Good work.
You're absolutely right about him.
Yes!
This love journal is filled
with so much love!
I told you! I don't have
any feelings for him!
Now, now.
Come off it, Soi Fon.
You're much too serious.
Pardon me!
Platoon leader!
Did you locate them?
Yes, sir!
Is it about that matter?
Pardon me, but some people I've
grown attached to have been found.
May I go there first?
It can't be helped.
I'll go to the exam site myself
and get things rolling.
Right!
Please wait, Lady Yoruichi!
If he doesn't make it
to the exam in time,
he will ruin
Squad 2's reputation
and smear
your name as well!
Oh, don't worry.
As if we can trust you!
Kisuke, come immediately!
Excuse me!
Wait!
Lady Yoruichi!
We're going, Soi Fon.
Get ready.
How is it going?
They're inside.
But I think our presence
has been detected.
It can't be helped.
I expected this.
They're watching
our moves as well.
It's a matter of who
gets impatient first.
You're…
What's going on?
Who's in there?
Deserters.
Deserters?
I guess the air in Seireitei
didn't suit them.
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Just a threat.
He won't come out yet.
But I do have a promise
to keep with Yoruichi.
What are you going to do?
I'm just going over there.
Wait!
You don't intend to go alone
to face this massive
Spiritual Pressure?!
– Urahara…
– Stay back please.
Okay, let's go.
They can take care of the rest.
I think I'll make it in time.
Kisuke Urahara, reporting!
Let us see the abilities
that Captain Yoruichi
of Squad 2
recommended so highly.
Yes, sir.
I think the newbie is here.
The Old Man says
to line up and wait.
Huh?!
Umm… Don't tell me
I'm the last one?
Jeez… Looks like we got
a pretty loose one this time.
You're right.
Ukitake…
How old is Captain Unohana?
Oh…I think…
What are you discussing?
Oh…I was just
asking him about
the future of
the Court Guard Squads…
Oh then, let us talk
about it in my room.
– Huh?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
What do you think
about this drawing?
SUBSTITUTE SOUL REAPER
HIDEOUT IN THE WORLD
OF THE LIVING
Huh?
Same as usual.
Right!
These are my illustrations of
my report to Soul Society!
Oh…
My reports on the daily activities
of the Substitute Soul Reaper
will be easy to understand!
Great idea…
Don't you agree?
Hold on a sec!
What'd you just say?!
Starting next episode,
we'll be delivering
SUBSITUTE SOUL REAPER
WORK JOURNAL
the "Substitute Soul Reaper Work Journal"!
No one said a thing about it to me!