Are you guys done?
Ichigo went flying, so I guess we are.
I didn't go flying!
I just slipped!
No way was that enough to call it a match!
Fine!
Why you...
Good grief.
Man, how'd I get stuck joining
these guys' training session?
For someone talking like that,
you were pretty into it.
And you're not even in Squad 11.
Same goes for you.
I just want to make it clear, Ichigo.
I definitely made a winning strike earlier.
No, you didn't!
You didn't even graze me!
You have a bruise on your forehead.
You've got a bruise there yourself!
No, I don't!
My, don't the two of you get along well.
-No, we don't!
Well, in regards to this training,
Renji's experience puts him as the winner.
What?!
The point is, this wasn't
a battle with Zanpakuto.
Okay.
Then let's settle it once and
for all in the next round!
Sure. Fine with me!
Oh...
Have some.
Thanks.
Hey, Seizo!
Tea over here too!
Right away!
I sense a faint Hollow Spiritual Pressure!
Let's go!
- Right!
So why are you coming along with us?
It just happened, you know?
I'm going with the flow!
You're not even in Squad 11.
You sure have odd interests.
Neither are you.
We were too late.
Looks like the Hollows attacked as a group.
When they sensed us coming,
they ran off together.
It's rare for them to be so organized.
Oh well.
Hey!
For now, our priority is
to rescue any survivors!
You can't be serious!
I was hoping we could kick some butt!
Quit grumbling, and hurry up and do it!
For crying out loud.
Up...
They should've called Squad
4 for a job like this.
Nope, we have Seizo.
So there's no need for Squad 4.
Hey Seizo! Over here too!
Coming!
Work hard and do our share too.
It's sad to be a part of Squad 11,
but only useful at times likes this.
Okay.
You're all done.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
That completes first-aid
treatment for everyone.
Except for that bruise on your forehead.
I don't have one!
You're welcome to use this.
Oh...
Seizo! Get over here!
Coming!
Thanks.
What's the matter?
That fellow.
Huh?
You mean Seizo?
He alone seems different from the rest.
I was wondering why he's in Squad 11.
Now that you mention it,
he's quiet and doesn't really stand out.
But he was like that since the time
I was a member of Squad 11.
What're you guys jabbering about?!
Hey, Ikkaku.
Seizo has always been the quiet type, right?
Huh?
Wouldn't know.
Excuse me.
Thanks for this earlier.
Here.
Sure. Thanks for bringing it back.
Um... Do you need any help?
That's okay.
No one in Squad 11 can do
this sort of work as fast as I can.
Oh, I see.
Besides, wouldn't you have more
fun training with the others?
Fun?
Yes. I can tell.
When you were in there training with them,
you looked truly happy.
No, that was just me getting
caught in the flow of things.
But I have one word of advice.
They use wooden swords, not
Zapakuto, in their training.
Sword skills are what's important,
not just your Spirit Energy.
Sword skills?
A tree with weak roots
is easy to topple over.
Even more so when it has thin branches.
Roots, you say?
A sword is, after all, nothing
but the tip of a branch.
What I'm saying is that
putting your strength
into the sword is meaningless if your roots,
your lower body, aren't
firmly planted in the ground.
I see.
You're totally overdoing it.
Sorry about that. My true skill showed.
Where'd you pick up how to do that?
It's skills.
That so?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Hey, Seizo!
Coming!
TEA HOUSE
Seizo?
Oh, you mean Seizo Harugasaki.
That's his family name, huh?
So, what about him?
Well, how shall I say this?
Squad 11's members are
rough, vulgar and crude.
That's all there is, you know?
I find it difficult to
ignore what you just said.
At the very least, I'm
different, aren't I?
Let's put that aside for now, okay?
No, it's not okay!
But that man is very mild-mannered.
The people around him treat him terribly.
That's because he's physically weak.
Squad 11 is a combat squad.
Even the younger members treat
someone who is weak badly.
It's true that
he doesn't have much Spiritual Pressure,
but somehow he doesn't
feel like an ordinary fellow to me.
He joined us the same time as Ikkaku.
Ikkaku?
Back then, he was regarded
as a promising Soul Reaper.
His sword skills were a sight to behold.
His sword skill was
dynamic, yet steady.
He was a straightforward Soul Reaper
who never resorted to tricks.
Away you go!
Their skills compared favorably,
but his straightforward
fighting style didn't match up well.
He lost to Ikkaku repeatedly.
You don't get it, do you?
You can't take me on and hope to win
without using some sort of ploy!
I know that it's impossible!
But I won't give up, no
matter how many times I fail!
I had no idea.
Why is someone with such skill
now being treated like some lackey?
It happened when the two were part
of a team to take down a Hollow.
Our scout hasn't come back.
Madarame, I'll go.
Cover me.
Don't be ridiculous!
I should be the one to go!
How many times have you lost
when we went head-to-head?!
I didn't lose.
Those were draws.
I've heard of sore losers,
but you're something else.
The Hollow!
Takashige!
Damn it!
Wait, Madarame!
The weak follow the strong!
That's the Squad 11...
rule!
That was easy.
What the heck? I can't pull it out!
Your Spirit Energy...is mine!
That Hollow possessed the ability
to suck away Spirit Energy.
Seizo lost most of his Spirit
Energy to that Hollow.
Since then, his Spirit
Energy has never returned.
So that's what happened.
Once he lost his Spirit Energy,
he could not fulfill his
duties as a Soul Reaper,
especially as a combatant.
Yet he refused to transfer to another squad.
I heard what happened.
You're...pretty awesome
with the sword, I hear.
Nope.
You talked about roots,
and how happy I looked.
You sounded pretty patronizing,
so I began to wonder.
Isn't it you who's unhappy having
to do work like this?!
Oops, sorry.
It's okay.
You want to wield a sword
and fight too, right?
Why are you just smiling and
doing odd jobs for everybody?
And what's with Ikkaku?
It's his fault that you
lost your Spirit energy.
Wouldn't know.
So what's with that attitude?!
Third Seat Madarame is too far above me.
And I have no strength to fight.
I am no longer a concern
to Third Seat Madarame.
He is not even interested in what I do.
But even so...
The truth is, in three days,
I will be discharged from the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
What?!
All I can do is leave quietly.
If you have only three days left,
then it's all the more reason!
Enough already!
You want me to have a match
with that bastard Harugasaki?
Yeah.
You've gotta be kidding.
I'm not interested in a weak bastard.
Maybe so, but wasn't he strong once?
That was a long time ago.
And first of all, there's no
way he'd have a match with me.
Shouldn't you be trying to
convince him instead of me?
For crying out loud.
No, as I told you,
I have no such intention.
Why not?!
If you decide to fight,
I know Ikkaku will be willing as well!
Even if I did, I'd only disappoint him.
I want him to remember me
as I was back then, when I
had confidence in my skills.
Please understand.
You've done enough, Ichigo.
Renji...
Seizo...I'm sorry.
Lieutenant Abarai, please!
Don't let it bother you.
I understand.
Then let's have a match!
If I lose, I'll back off.
But if I win, you'll do as I ask!
You don't understand a thing, do you?!
You ask for a match, but...
I've told you. I have
no strength to fight.
I know.
The match isn't going
to be one of strength!
Huh?
Doing the laundry, putting
bandages away and cleaning.
The one who finishes first wins!
But I would definitely have the advantage.
We won't know until we try!
Here goes!
Seizo wins.
Damn it!
It wasn't even close.
I'm sorry. Please give up.
No! We're doing it again tomorrow!
Huh?
Ichigo, you...
I never said I'd give up after one try!
You don't get it, do you?
It's no use, no matter
how many times you try.
I know that it's impossible!
But I won't give up, no
matter how many times I fail!
You don't get it, do you?
You can't take me on and hope to win
without using some sort of ploy!
I know that it's impossible!
But I won't give up, no
matter how many times I fail!
Yumichika?
We're heading out.
The Hollows have reappeared.
Come with us as logistical support.
Yes, sir!
Sorry, looks like a match
is out of the question!
Ichigo!
Right!
Damn you!
They're getting away, Ikkaku!
Like I'm going to let them!
Okay!
The logistical support team
will attend to casualties!
Those of you who can move, we're
going after the Hollows!
Let's go, Ichigo!
Right!
Go! We'll handle things here!
Sorry!
Are you all right?
This wound is nothing!
I'm not a weakling like you!
Fools!
They never realized we had split up.
What?!
We run away very fast, you see.
Once we lost them, we
came back for our meal.
Relax.
We'll take our time to chew you well
before swallowing you.
Hollows...
Five of them.
It'd be impossible for me to fight them.
I know that it's impossible!
But I won't give up, no
matter how many times I fail!
Is that your weapon?!
There's no way you can fight
the five of us with that sword!
I know that it's impossible!
But I won't give up, no
matter how many times I fail!
I never expected you to give us
so much trouble with your
meager Spirit Energy!
But this is the end of the line!
Prepare to die!
So this is where I die.
But that's okay.
Thank you, Ichigo Kurosaki.
You have made me regain my honor
as a Soul Reaper in my final moments.
Here I come!
Madarame?!
You've returned!
No...
It's you who has returned!
Now cover my back!
You came to see me off?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Take care, you two.
You too.
Well then...
To Squad Member Seizo Harugasaki... Bow!
Say, Ikkaku...
Where did Kenpachi go, anyway?
Now that you mention it...
I haven't seen either the
Captain or the Lieutenant around lately.
What?! Are you sure that's okay?
It's probably that time
of year where I need to
have Captain Unohana make an
announcement for a lost person.
They have seasons for that?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Squad 11 is a bit filthy,
wouldn't you say?
It's like loincloths are
a must-wear fashion item!
So true. Ikkaku and his
kind are so stifling.
Oh, Fifth Seat Ayasegawa!
So are you!
I'm positive that inside,
you're as stifling as the rest!
You don't get it, do you?
Isn't that gap exactly what beauty is?
Tell me, Ikkaku...
Am I filthy? Am I stifling?