Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends have
marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
Ishida arrived to save Renji,
who was in danger.
But Szayelaporro, who has gathered
the Spiritual Pressure data on Ishida,
proves to be a tough opponent.
I've already analyzed
all of your abilities, Quincy!
Don't stand around doing nothing!
You can still fight, can't you?!
Ishida ends up being saved by Renji,
who breaks into the battle.
The two join together
to fight Szayelaporro.
Even if the difference
in our power is great,
you'll hurt a little if you
get hit at point-blank range.
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
It's exactly as we had planned.
Hasta aquí…
It's over, Szayelaporro Grantz.
Damn…
I'm honestly surprised that
you can stand after taking that.
Wait! Where are you going?!
Where am I going?
I'm going to change my clothes.
It's embarrassing to fight in these
worn-out clothes, don't you think?
Meanwhile,
Grimmjow takes Orihime to Ichigo,
who is wounded from
his battle with Ulquiorra.
An incredible Spiritual Pressure is
swirling around Kurosaki's wounds.
I can't…reject it.
Who did this?
Ulquiorra…
I'll teach him the punishment
for attacking someone else's prey.
Are you all right?
What's wrong?! What happened?!
Too close! Too close! Too close!
I keep telling you that
when I see your face up close,
I feel like my heart is going to stop!
I'm worried about you.
That's so mean!
POW!
I told you not to get close to me!
Okay.
What an impressive stand-up routine.
We can't lose to them, Uryu!
Come on!
It's our turn next!
Huh?
Uryu? Uryu?
“U” for Uryu!
Shut up.
You don't have to call for me so loudly.
I can hear you.
All right.
You've done well.
Let's make this into a game of shiritori.
Huh? Over there?
I can't seem to sense Szayelaporro's
Spiritual Pressure nearby.
Bastard…
Do you suppose he
really did go to change his clothes?
Probably.
Can you run, Abarai?
Yeah… That's not a problem.
Then, next is “s” for snail!
Huh?
Are we going to do something?
You two really are dumb.
We're getting out of here, of course!
Ulquiorra…
What are you doing, Grimmjow?
What’s wrong? I’m asking you…
What do you think you're doing?
Healing the wounds
of the enemy I defeated?
You're not going to answer?
Fine.
Anyway, Lord Aizen has
entrusted that girl to me.
Hand her over.
I refuse.
What?
What's wrong?
You’re sure talkative today,
Ulquiorra!
I know, Ulquiorra.
You're afraid to fight me.
You're afraid to fight to the death!
You deflected it, huh?!
I expected that one shot wouldn't…
Damn…
Wh-What was that just now?
Aizen gives us Espada something
called a “Caja de Negación,”
which is used to
punish subordinates.
I used that.
Caja de Negación?
It'll trap most guys in
a closed dimension forever.
But it's not something that's
made to work against other Espada.
Taking his Spiritual Pressure
into consideration,
he'll probably stay trapped
for two to three hours.
Now that you know,
get to healing him.
I don't want to.
I'm not asking you whether
you want to heal him or not!
Heal him!
No!
If I heal Kurosaki,
you're just
going to hurt him, aren't you?
I won't do it!
You bastard!
Let go of her.
– Kuro—
– Inoue…
Heal me.
Huh?
Heal my wounds.
And…
His as well.
Stop!
I've done nothing to
get your sympathy.
Me neither.
But you want to fight
on equal terms, don't you?
Or…
Are you going to use those wounds
as an excuse when you lose?
Bring it on!
Let's have a fair fight to the death!
I accept your challenge!
Come on.
Don't make that face, Nel.
But Ichigo…
Inoue, don't you worry either.
I'll win for sure.
Ichigo…
Let's move elsewhere, Grimmjow.
Fine.
Kurosaki…
Let’s go!
Ichigo… Ichigo…
It'll be all right. Kurosaki will win.
Y-You don't know that for sure!
He said that he was going to win.
E-Everyone says that!
And they usually lose!
You don't know who's going to win!
You think so?
That's right! Ichigo is probably afraid!
People who are afraid always
say that they're going to win!
Kurosaki wouldn't say that.
Huh?
Kurosaki wouldn't
say that he'll win
because he's afraid or because
he's trying to fool himself.
Kurosaki is a kind person.
Whether he uses
powerful words or not,
he always says them
as if he's making a vow.
When he first appeared
to me as a Soul Reaper…
If you want to kill Inoue,
you'll have to kill me first!
And when we went to
Soul Society to save Kuchiki…
We just have to defeat them, right?
He was always like that.
He does that to reassure us too.
But if anything,
I think that he's making
a vow to himself.
a vow to himself
and saying it aloud
to make it come true.
So it's all right.
When Kurosaki says that he'll win,
that's when he'll win for sure.
Really?
So…
So…let's wait for him…and believe.
Getsuga…
This is good! I've been waiting for this!
The chance to crush you at full power!
You been waiting for this too,
haven't you, Ichigo Kurosaki?!
I'm not fighting you
so that I can crush you.
Don't be soft! Say it!
Say that you want to beat me to a pulp!
I'm the guy who
slashed up your friends!
You want to rip me up
into pieces, don't you?!
I'm asking which is the stronger one!
This is bad!
Ichigo, let's retreat for now!
D-Damn it…
Rukia!
I won't forgive you!
You have to learn why I keep this scar!
Getsugatensho!
Let's begin.
I'll put you down and
show you who's stronger!
What's with that look on your face?
It seems like you really
have no intent to kill me.
You're so pathetic.
What?
Let me ask you this, Kurosaki.
Why did you come here?
That's obvious!
To save Inoue!
Then why didn't I see you even
attempt to run away with her
when you saw her?!
Were you relieved that
she appeared to be unharmed?
You're so dim-witted.
You don't even know
how she is on the inside.
Did you do something to Inoue?!
That's a good expression…
Kurosaki!
You said that you came here
to save that girl, right?
You don't seem to understand,
so I'll tell you!
You're wrong.
You came here to fight.
You can see it.
The path your instincts show you.
You're a Soul Reaper! I'm a Hollow!
The loser will be slaughtered!
That's what's been done
for thousands of years now!
Is there any other reason to fight?!
Come on!
The last one standing can leave alive!
That's all!
You've got a good look
to you now, Kurosaki.
But…
That's not good enough!
That's not the side of you
I really want to fight!
Take this!
This is the most powerful Cero,
which only Espada are allowed to use!
Inoue…
Wait, Grimmjow!
Gran Rey Cero!
Kurosaki…
Ichigo…
You've finally shown yourself.
That's some good
Spiritual Pressure, Kurosaki!
I'm going, too!
Grind! Before that…
What's wrong?
If you're going to do your release,
then just do it!
Shut up!
I'm making sure that
no one's going to interfere!
You've gotten pretty cautious.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hisagi here.
Kira here.
Excuse us!
You two, model for me for a moment!
– What?
All right, pose!
That's good!
Yes, just like that!
How manly!
Then… Just because… That too!
– What?!
What do you think?
They were well-shot, don't you think?!
I can't print this!
PUBLICATION BANNED