Kumoi’s plot to assassinate
Rurichiyo is set into motion.
He gives his trusted retainer
Hanza Nukui the Bakkouto, Saiga,
and sends his assassination squad
to the World of the Living
to carry out the mission.
Nukui forces Ichigo and
his friends to split up,
then challenges them individually.
Trap them… Saiga!
Such a small repertoire.
I’ve seen that attack already!
Now, it’s my turn!
Not again!
What the hell?!
This is different from
what the small fry use.
You can’t defend yourself
from my attack
just by looking away
from the light.
Saiga, the sword Nukui
uses to battle Ichigo,
is the same sword that
a previous assassin wielded.
But it displays different
powers than before.
The Bakkouto is a blade
that’s able to
transform its powers
depending on the wielder.
As if I’ll let you have your way!
What?! A crack in Saiga?!
However, Nukui and his men,
having underestimated the strength
that Ichigo and the others possessed, are defeated.
So it won’t be that easy.
Well then…
Kumoi… What is it?
Lord Kannogi, how are you faring?
Yes, all is well.
Or, should I say…
I don’t know what
I’m supposed to be doing.
I’m just whiling the time away.
That is fine.
You can leave
the Kasumiohji Clan matters to me.
Now excuse me.
Huh? That’s all?
I feel like I’m being watched.
Jeez, I’m so bored!
And Ruricchi still hasn’t come back.
Is it really all right like this?
Thank goodness Lord Kannogi
is a very ordinary youth.
How shameless of you
to return here.
Pardon me.
No matter.
It seems the Substitute
Soul Reaper’s power
was far greater
than we surmised.
And? What will you do?
If I may be given
another opportunity,
I will give my life to be rid of
the Substitute Soul Reaper
and the princess.
Then show me your resolve.
Yes, my lord!
This fusion with your sword,
which exceeds all limits…
Do you understand
what it means, Hanza?
I am fully aware of what I did.
Your resolve…
I, Gyokaku Kumoi,
have personally witnessed it.
Fulfill your mission and
bring me the heads of
the Substitute Soul Reaper
and the princess!
Yes, my lord!
If I may make a request…
What is it?
I wish to borrow swords
for my men.
Jinnai Douko.
I am Kuzuryu.
I am known as Genga.
And these men are…
Yes, my lord!
They are, without exception,
the finest men in the underworld.
You men…
This sword sucks
the life out of its user.
Knowing this, do you still
have the nerve to use it?
Absolutely.
Is there a reason why
we should hesitate?
We are confident that we have
what it takes to wield that sword.
Fine.
All I seek are results.
I made the barrier stronger.
I’ve also put up an optic barrier so that
the house isn’t visible from the outside.
Not visible? You mean,
it looks like this is an empty lot?
Huh?!
Rurichiyo’s house is gone!
When did it disappear?!
Isn’t that going too far?
Nothing is too far when
one is protecting the princess!
I’m just saying, what’ll happen
if this causes a panic later?
It can’t be helped.
After all, we don’t even know
the extent of their power.
A Zanpakuto that evolves by feeding
on the wielder’s Spiritual Pressure, huh?
Yoruichi has gone back to Soul Society
to gather information.
I hope she learns something useful.
Princess, what is the matter?
Oh yes! There are some
delicious sweets here.
Kenryu, Enryu,
and even Ichigo and his friends.
Why such tight security around me?
No… It’s…
It seems the World of the Living has
far more night thieves than we thought.
I am very, very sorry for
causing you to worry. Yes…
I see.
I am going to bed.
Good night!
I’ve been so busy lately.
Now all the housework has piled up!
This incident seems to
go deeper than I thought.
It looks like…
things are getting messy again.
Weren’t you going to sleep?
Ichigo…
What’re you doing?
I am just gazing at the stars.
So you can make
those expressions.
What kind of expression?
How can I put it?
It’s as though you’re breathing.
Breathing?
Really?
What’s so funny?
You make it sound like
I do not usually breathe.
I see. I guess that
didn’t sound right.
The World of the Living is nice.
Even if I climb on the roof,
no one scolds me.
That’s ‘cuz you’re a princess and
no one wants you to get hurt.
You are right.
If I get hurt,
someone will be punished.
I can’t even get hurt.
I always have so much
I want to do.
But each time,
someone suffers because of me.
Even when I tried
to learn archery…
What if something happened
to the princess?!
– We are very sorry, please forgive us!
– Because of me,
the archery attendant and
my maid were punished,
and the boar was hunted down.
Because I left
the mansion unseen,
the gatekeeper was
relieved of his duties.
I didn’t notice
when I was little,
but so many have been
punished because of me.
If I had known that sooner,
I would have behaved more.
But I didn’t know.
Isn’t it shameful?
It’s hard when you don’t get scolded,
but others do.
Still Kenryu and Enryu often
look the other way
and cover up for me.
And so, this means
that flower may bloom,
but they eventually fall off.
And next… Huh?
Such skill!
Oh!
Oh! Kenryu, buy the whole store.
Not possible!
Buy it! Buy it! Buy it! Buy it!
I want it, no matter what!
I want it! I want it!
Oh? What are you
going in such a place?
Oh, it’s nothing! Excuse us!
It’s delicious!
Found you, Enryu!
I am grateful to both of them.
However…
What is it?
It’s nothing.
This Spiritual Pressure…
Is it them?
I shall get my revenge
for last time…
Substitute Soul Reaper!
What is the matter?
Let’s go back.
Did something happen?
It’s nothing serious.
But don’t move around.
If you were invited to
a friend’s tea party,
sorry, but cancel it for today.
Lady Rurichiyo!
Kenryu…
Please do not leave my side.
It’s all right.
You’ve got all of us here with you.
I shall get the Substitute
Soul Reaper’s head.
You get his friends.
Do you have to get
personally involved?
Shouldn’t you leave
the Substitute Soul Reaper to us
and go after the princess?
No… He owes me for the crack in
Saiga’s mirror during our last battle.
In any case, his Spiritual Pressure
is something only I can handle.
Fine.
I think the others will
amuse us quite sufficiently.
Don’t get too cocky, Genga.
They’ll be easy, Bro.
Several of them are on the move.
Are they luring us?
Interesting.
Let them lure us.
Let’s go, Genga.
I’m with you, Bro!
We’ll go too.
Rukia!
Ishida and Sado went on ahead!
They’re going to ambush them?
Yes. It seems they’ve followed
our lead and separated too.
They must be quite confident.
Yeah. And they probably
have those swords too.
A barrier?
They thought they
could fool us with this?
Lady Rurichiyo!
The barrier has been broken!
Ichigo!
Right!
Rukia, stay with Rurichiyo
and these two.
All right.
Ichigo…
Lady Rurichiyo,
please do not leave my side!
But…
No buts! You stay with Kenryu.
Got that?
So here you are,
Substitute Soul Reaper!
You saved me the trouble
of looking for you.
You…
Princess!
Ichigo!
Don’t come out!
No, Princess!
Let me go, Kenryu!
No, get inside. Hurry!
I said let me go!
What’s going on?
I thought you were after Rurichiyo.
Ichigo!
Stay back, Rukia.
For some reason,
this guy wants to challenge me.
Ichigo!
It’s dangerous!
Please stay indoors!
There’s no guarantee that
it’s still safe inside!
You are right, however…
If anything should happen
to Ichigo Kurosaki,
their next target will be…
They’ll come after me next?
Oh…well…
In other words,
these are the night thieves
who have come to the
World of the Living after me!
Y-Yes, they are.
Let’s change locations.
Fine.
Let’s go!
Kurosaki!
Ishida and Sado too.
Ichigo…
Who’s there?!
You are Rurichiyo Kasumiohji?
You’re a friend of the Substitute
Soul Reaper, aren’t you?
You reek with the smell of blood.
Here I come, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Bankai!
They forced their way through,
after all.
Don’t worry.
I had lots of time to
change into my Quincy outfit.
You don’t look that different.
It’s really different.
To be specific…
It’s gonna take too long,
so don’t bother.
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today’s topic is Las Noches.
LAS NOCHES
This is our base of operations
in Hueco Mundo.
I’ve told the Espada to stay put
in their own palaces,
but I guess some
sneak around outside.
Oh?
When I think about all the traps
placed inside my palace,
I can’t dare go out.
Shall I show them to you sometime?
It's probably all nasty stuff.