Ichigo and Rukia enter the Soul Society
in pursuit of Rurichiyo.
They disrupt the marriage ceremony,
but are confronted by
Soi Fon and Squad 2,
who were secretly assigned to
guard the premises, and a fight breaks out.
As a result, they become fugitives
on the run from the Soul Reapers.
I never expected to meet up in
a place like this.
After being persuaded by Shu,
Amagai agrees to side with Ichigo.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are thrown into confusion
while trying to capture Ichigo.
Meanwhile, Kira, who is pursuing Kibune
for his recent suspicious activities,
happens to come across the place where
the real Rurichiyo is being held,
and he battles the Kasumiohji’s assassins.
Upon defeating the assassins,
Kira is confronted by Kibune,
who reveals his true nature.
I must say, everything you do
is always too late.
The princess left long ago,
Lieutenant Kira.
As I thought.
Everything that’s happened
is your doing…
Third Seat Kibune.
Group One will cover from here
to Section Five East.
Group Two to Section Eight South,
Group Three go from
Section Four West to Fifth Street.
Group Four go around to
Section Three North.
What about Section Two North,
Central Street?
No need.
That’s under Squad 8’s jurisdiction.
But, it’s not that far from
Group Four’s assigned section.
That’s an order.
If you move in a section outside
of your jurisdiction,
you’ll only get into trouble
with the other squad.
– Yes, sir!
Let’s go!
The chaos within the Seireitei
has been contained
thanks to the work of
the Punishment Force.
Deployment of each squad to
their assigned sections has been completed.
Now commencing a widespread manhunt.
Oh?
You’re still here?
Kyoraku.
What are you doing here?
Our squad isn’t ready to deploy yet.
What’s wrong?
You have a glum look on your face.
I went to talk with Genryusai Sensei again.
But he would not listen.
Old Man Yama is a stubborn one
after all.
I wonder.
Is there a reason that
the Kasumiohji Clan is off limits to us?
I also did some investigating,
but you know…
it seems they’re not
an easy clan to deal with.
What does that mean?
They’re high-ranking aristocrats,
yet they rarely present themselves
in front of the public.
And they aren’t associated with
Central 46 that much either.
But I must say, Ichigo sure brings
trouble with him every time.
It’s no laughing matter.
If we get attacked from
the outside at a time like this…
Oh, if that’s the issue
Squad 12 is on it.
It seemed Captain Kurotsuchi was
not too eager to get involved
with the mess going on within
the Seireitei anyway.
So it all worked out.
For now, we just need to do our jobs.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh, a Hell Butterfly.
What happened?
It seems that while Kira
was going after Kibune,
he found Rurichiyo Kasumiohji.
What?!
Where?
On the premises of the Squad 3 barracks.
Then that means…
As we suspected,
there’s a high probability that Kibune
is somehow involved with all of this.
Amagai, I’m sorry, but there’s no time
to get depressed about this.
Let’s rescue Rurichiyo!
Yeah, I know.
In any case, this is misconduct
caused by my squad.
We must hurry! It’s that way!
Shouldn’t Squad 3 be located
straight in this direction?
Yeah but…
We’ll end up passing through
the section assigned to Squad 9.
Since when have they all become
assigned to sections?
It shows that
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
won’t be disjointed forever.
There’s a little space in between
each assigned section.
If we move through those areas,
we won’t encounter anyone.
Got it.
Let’s go!
Hey Kenny,
aren’t you going after Itchy?
Nope.
Why not?
I don’t feel like it.
You were also present during
Ama-Ama’s Captain’s Exam, right, Kenny?
Yeah.
If Ama-Ama is on the run with Itchy,
wouldn’t they find
you responsible, Kenny?
I was just tricked into it by the old man.
I don’t care about that guy.
Captain Amagai!
You all received word from Kira, right?
Yes, sir!
Just what is going on?
I’ll explain later!
In any case,
let’s head to the fighting arena!
– Yes, sir!
Captain!
Those guys!
They were carrying someone!
Could it be Ruricchi?!
Rukia, look after Shu!
Wait! I’ll come too!
Huh?
Aida, Inose, Kano!
You guys, go to Kira!
– Yes, sir!
Kuchiki, take Sir Kannogi with you
and follow behind us!
Yes, sir!
Let’s go, Kurosaki!
Okay!
It was you after all…
Third Seat Kibune.
So you fended off my attack.
I guess I should say,
it’s just what
you’d expect from a lieutenant.
I gave them Bakkoutos,
albeit a scaled-down version.
But it seems it was too much
for these men.
The Kasumiohji Clan. Are you…
Lieutenant Kira.
I’m sorry, but please die now!
Lieutenant!
Third Seat Kibune?
What are you doing?
Why are you two fighting?
Where’s Captain Amagai?
He’s going after the princess
with Ichigo Kurosaki!
I see. The message made it in time.
But what is going on here, sir?
Stay away!
Huh?!
Kibune is our enemy!
You can’t be serious!
Third Seat Kibune!
Is what Lieutenant Kira says true?
You’ll be in trouble depending
on your response!
You small fish are shameless.
What?!
I’ll kill you all together!
Rampage, Reppu!
All of you, get out of here!
Too late!
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Your dull-edged sword is
useless before my Reppu!
You… What did you do?
My Wabisuke doubles
the weight of the object it slashes.
Slash it a second time,
and it doubles again.
Slash it a third time,
and it doubles yet again.
You can no longer use that weapon now
that it’s become super-heavy.
Kibune, you will now tell us
what your objective is.
What are you trying to do by working
with the Kasumiohji Clan?
First of all, what is the Kasumiohji Clan?
Whatever the Kasumiohji Clan
does is none of your business.
However, they possess tremendous power!
All I want is to use that power
and become even stronger!
To become the strongest Soul Reaper!
Wha—?!
What tremendous power.
Not even Wabisuke works.
What’s wrong, Lieutenant Kira?
Don’t tell me you’re dead already.
Kibune’s Zanpakuto is strong.
At this rate…
You didn’t die this time?
But it’s useless to hide!
Come out quietly!
Do it and you will have a swift death!
After all, your powers are
no match for mine.
Third Seat Kibune…
Come out! Izuru Kira!
You said you wanted
the Kasumiohji’s power, didn’t you?
From what I saw,
you already have enough power.
Where are you? Coward!
You have that much power.
Why couldn’t you use it for good?
Power, you say?
Do you have any idea how much
I had to sacrifice to attain my Reppu?
What would you know?!
There!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Reppu!
Too late!
Crap!
What was that just now?
You! How dare you!
Kibune…
What is that?
“What,” you say?
This is a Bakkouto!
Bakkouto?
Yes!
This is the great sword created
with the secret technique of
the Kasumiohji Clan.
That vicious Spiritual Pressure…
It is just like those assassins.
It’s not the same.
That only substituted for the lack of
fighting skills for lowly individuals
who couldn’t even use a Shikai.
But this Bakkouto utilizes
my Spiritual Pressure and can grow endlessly.
Your techniques will
not work against me!
Why do you possess such a thing?
“Why,” you ask?
It’s obvious.
To have power!
Power?
That’s right. Power.
It’s about power!
I have power.
But no one recognized it.
Back when I was in
the Soul Reaper Academy,
I was always at the top of
my class in academics.
Yet I never got a call from
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
during my academy years.
Why can’t I join
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads?!
Other high achievers in the past
all got in at the time of their graduation!
You are indeed a high achiever.
But that’s not the only qualification.
You need to think hard
about what you lack.
What am I supposed to be lacking?!
In days of idleness,
I continued to train painstakingly for years.
After attaining a Shikai,
I was finally accepted to a squad.
And no matter what the situation was
I killed Hollows more than anybody.
But…
My style of fighting was brought
into question within the squad.
Instead of being promoted
I faced the danger of being banished
from the squad.
Why do you sacrifice
your fellow squad members?
Because they lack power.
Then isn’t it the responsibility
of those who have power
to save those who don’t?
Though I managed to avoid
being discharged,
I was still sentenced to probation.
I was never to become a Seat Officer.
While other less skilled members
moved up in ranks,
I had lost my place within the squad
and received orders to join
the Expedition Unit.
In my despair,
I stayed with the Expedition Unit
and continued killing Hollows.
To get back at those
who didn’t recognize my talent.
And finally, I encountered this power.
With this power, no one will ever
be able to ignore me.
But it’s not enough!
I need even greater power!
With that power, I will make
every Soul Reaper recognize me!
That sword…
It has consumed his heart.
Izuru Kira!
Guys like you who have no talent,
yet get promoted to lieutenant…
I will sweep all of you away!
Weakness is a crime.
Someone like you doesn’t deserve
to be where you are.
When the previous captain went
out of control,
you couldn’t even stop him!
Powerless people like you
don’t deserve to stand above me!
It’s useless!
The killing blow.
Old Man Yama sure is persistent.
I received another reminder
to deploy my men.
I was hoping to see
how things play out a bit longer.
But I’m starting to run out of excuses
to hold off the deployment.
How about we try,
“they just left a moment ago”?
This isn’t like talking over the phone,
you know.
Quincy Encyclopedia!
Today is about the costume
worn by a Quincy.
The costume design can vary
depending on contemporary times
and individual tastes.
However, it’s fundamental design
remains unchanged.
We take pride in our costume.
And so, I present to you
Ryuken Ishida in his costume gear!
I have no intention of showing it.
What are you holding out for, huh?!