Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
This one's not the one, either.
I found it.
Come back here!
You always turn your back
towards reality!
Face reality!
What are you trying to say?!
You were betrayed!
By the person you trusted most!
I was by your side watching that,
unable to say anything.
And it really annoyed me!
I see.
I can't stand it anymore.
You're going to destroy
yourself if this keeps up.
Even though I was by your side.
What a thing to say.
So what do you want to do?
I want to put you poor thing
to sleep forever.
Sleep?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot you've already been
asleep for quite some time now.
Does it hurt?
Yes. That's the pain of reality.
It's nothing like the naive world
you believe it to be.
I'm going to make you
discard those ideas!
Stop being so overconfident,
old lady!
What did you say?!
Hinamori!
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
How long are you going to
think you're good looking?
Women have an expiration date.
And you're past expiration.
You brat!
Enough is enough!
Try and make me!
Owowowow!
What are you doing?!
I was just trying to
help you look sexier.
Of course,
you couldn't please anyone
since you're already expired.
Perhaps you shouldn't
push yourself, old lady!
Unforgivable!
There's one more thing
I want to tell you.
All of the friends you trust
are just an illusion.
You just believe
they're your friends.
Everyone just acts as if
they're your friends
because they have
their position to think of.
Take Rangiku Matsumoto
there for example…
The only thing she's
interested in is herself.
As proof, she's not paying
any attention to you.
Why are you getting so upset?
If you weren't an old lady,
you wouldn't care!
It's really unsightly!
Die!
Good bye, old lady!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh and blood…
– All creation, the flutter of wings,
– It's useless, useless,
– who crowns us names!
– useless!
Disintegrate,
you black dog of Rondanini!
– What are you trying to do?
– Look upon yourself and burn!
Tear out your own throat!
Bakudo 9! Horin!
What do you think
you're aiming at?
Pay attention to me!
Shakkaho!
Where are you aiming?!
Old la—
Bakudo 9! Horin!
Oh, no!
Hey… What?!
Don't press yourself against me!
I'm not doing it because I want to!
– Ouch!
We did it, Hinamori!
We sure did, Rangiku!
What's the meaning
of this, old lady?
Don't tell me, that was all an act?
Of course.
I'd never take a brat
like you seriously.
In order to go up against
your Zanpakuto powers,
we needed to
catch you off guard.
You were only paying attention
to your own enemy,
so we were able to pull it off.
You two suit each other!
You've got to be kidding me!
You should try to
get along a little better.
Shut up!
But listening to you…
I feel sorry for you two.
What?
You only think about yourself
and never think of others.
That's not true!
Is that so?
Don't pay any attention to her.
She's just sore because
she's an old lady.
Quit calling me an old lady!
You think so?
I want to grow old.
Huh?!
Being young isn't appealing.
Being young means that
your heart is shallow.
So whenever you admire
someone or you're betrayed,
you feel as if you're
flying or drowning.
Your emotions get
the better of you
and you lose sight of
where you belong.
Growing old means that
your heart is gaining depth.
You're able to step away
from your wild emotions
and keep those thoughts of
flying or sinking within you.
That's what it means to grow old.
"Expiration date" sounds shallow.
Don't use it when referring
to a woman's age.
You…
What are you talking about?
Children like you
can't understand.
Yeah, yeah.
That's very admirable.
Yeah. It's absurd, isn't it?
Hey, what is it?
Why are you getting sulky?!
That's my own business!
Yeah, you just do
whatever you want!
What?!
You have no business
telling me that!
Jeez, you're not cute at all!
Shut up!
Your name is Hyorinmaru!
And I, Toshiro Hitsugaya,
am your master!
Don't make me laugh.
A child like you
cannot be my master.
Are you serious?
You've forgotten me?
Do you really think I'd
believe such nonsense, boy?
Did that weird guy, Muramasa,
do anything to you?
That's none of your business.
But when I was released
from my master,
I lost all of my memories.
All of your memories?
Right now,
I'm working for Muramasa,
but my goal is to find
my true master.
Your true master?
That's right.
Because of my enormous power,
the person who uses me must be
the most powerful Soul Reaper.
It's probably not a child like you.
It's true that my power
hasn't peaked…
But that doesn't change
the fact that I am your owner!
If you insist on saying
that you're my master,
then show me proof.
Bakudo 63!
Sajosabaku!
It's useless.
What?!
Toshiro!
Damn it!
Stop, Hyorinmaru!
I'm the one you're fighting!
Hado 31!
Shakkaho!
I said it's useless.
Don't you get it?
Zanpakuto…
I hear that the Zanpakuto were
released from the Soul Reapers
to fulfill their desires.
If that's the case, Hyorinmaru,
what is your desire?
My desire?
That's right. Your desire.
What does your soul want?
Have you forgotten even that?!
That would be…a place to
call my own…a home.
A home?
I might be searching for a home.
A home… My home…
They're afraid of me.
I haven't done anything.
But everyone is afraid of me.
Is it my silver hair?
Is it my bluish green eyes?
Or is it my cold disposition?
I'm going to buy some amanatto.
You're out of it, aren't you?
Grandma has gotten pretty thin.
Grandma began getting thin
when I began to have those dreams.
Sweets
Your change is 3 kan.
Thanks.
If that's all you want,
then get going.
Hey, you!
That's no way to treat a customer!
Are you going to disregard him
just because he's a child?!
I had no idea this shop
lacked common courtesy!
Oh… N-No…
How long are you going to cry?!
If you're a man, then give him
a piece of your mind!
Whose fault do you think this is?!
And I'm not crying! Let go of me!
I said, let go!
Oh! Hey!
Hey, you!
That dream…
I hear a voice.
It's echoing.
It feels like it's crushing me.
It feels like it's surrounding me.
It feels like lightning is
coming down on my hand.
Who the hell are you?!
Boy! You are my…
What are you saying?!
I can't hear you!
My name is…
I can't hear you.
Hey!
You're the lady
I met earlier today.
Shut off your Spiritual Pressure
when you sleep.
Your grandmother seems cold.
Gr—
Become a Soul Reaper, boy.
What?!
A strong kid like you needs to
learn how to control your power.
Let me tell you this.
If you continue on like this,
your power is going to
kill your grandmother.
What are you saying?
You can hear a voice, can't you?
Rein Over
the Frosted Heavens…
Hyorinmaru!
You can use my power?
Boy… How?
You still can't remember?
Then let me show you.
I don't know what'll happen if I
use this attack in Shikai, though.
Ryusenka!
Getsugatensho!
Toshiro!
Remember.
Remember the person
who heard your voice.
Remember your home!
Boy… Are you
going to wield me?!
My name is…
Hyorinmaru!
Master…
You remembered.
But my name's not "boy."
My name is Toshiro Hitsugaya.
There's no time.
You'll have to do for now.
Captain!
Please let me borrow
Hyorinmaru just this once!
I've always wanted to
walk a handsome man
on a leash as my pet!
No.
I'll let you borrow
Haieko in exchange!
What?
You are, like, totally annoying.
Absolutely not!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey.
Did you solve the problem?
Ah! I'm through detention!
What is this?!
Sis isn't even here!
I was planning to spend
some time in paradise!
What do you have against me?!
If anything…
Your body is a Soul Reaper and
Soul Reapers are my enemy.
You're still saying that?