Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
What happened?! Hey Ganju!
I-I'm sorry, Sis…
I just showed him once.
I never imagined it would turn
out like this!
Huh?!
I did it!
You did it, Kurosaki!
Yeah!
You idiot! Don't lose concentration!
Huh?
Weren't you listening to me, idiot?!
If you lose concentration,
you’ll blow up!
Didn’t I tell you that?
Yes, you did.
That’s right!
I tell you, you’re--!
You’re just as guilty, idiot!
Both of you, no food tonight!
Why put me together with him?!
Shut up! Got any complaints?!
Yoruichi…?
So, Ichigo has finally completed
a Cannonball?
Huh…? What’s wrong?
Nothing to worry about.
He’s only sleeping.
Now, I want you all to sit over there.
Ichigo is asleep,
but we haven’t got much time.
I want to talk to you about
what you can expect
after we invade the Seireitei.
You must--!
Practice hall
Fate of three sparrows,
fate of four dragons…
Blocked in from five directions,
unable to return six miles,
Wind of the Heavens,
Orangutan, Spoons,
Cane of elm…
A thousand sprinkles of ash,
a thousand bits…
of wisdom…
S-Silvervine?!
What… What the heck was
I dreaming about?
How should I know?!
I sure slept well…or, did I?
What am I doing sleeping here?
“How should I know?” I said. Idiot!
What the heck are you doing, anyway?
It’s none of your business!
Get lost, will you, dandelion?!
What--?!
So, you’re finally up.
It’s time for us to leave.
Huh? Leave…?
Okay, so you’re all here?
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Yoruichi, your tail looks like one
of those flexible toothbrushes!
Oh…!
Huh?!
What?
Do you have
a problem with it?
N-No. It’s a beautiful tail, as always…
Don’t you remember?!
You’re responsible for that!
Huh? Me?
We…
It took the three of us…
to finally get you to let go, but…
Ooh…
My tail…the tail I was so proud of…
You’d be smart to stay away
from that subject!
G-Got it…
Hey! What happened to Ganju?
Huh? I dunno…
He was muttering about
something downstairs.
Hold it!
The hero always arrives last.
What’s with that getup?
It’s my very own battle costume.
Don’t I look cool?
Cry and beg all you want,
but I won’t lend it to you.
How do you like that?
Battle costume?
What’s it for,
if you’re just seeing us off?
A Soul Reaper killed my big brother.
Ganju! Why you…!
Just shut up and listen, Sis!
My brother…was a genius.
He managed to pass the Soul Reaper
Academy entrance exam in one try.
At that time, his spiritual power
was at Level 6.
That’s the same level as a lieutenant
of the 13 Court Guarding Squads.
Then, he finished
six years’ curriculum in one,
and he became a member
of a Squad.
In just five years,
he became a lieutenant.
But my brother was killed…
betrayed by his Soul Reaper comrades!
I was still a kid back then,
so I don’t remember the details,
but there are two things
I’ll never forget.
Their faces…! Two faces!
The ogre-like face of that Soul Reaper
who dragged my badly injured
and dying brother home.
And the face of my brother as he
happily gave thanks to that Soul Reaper.
Why did my brother do that?
Why did he seem so happy?
To this day, I don’t know.
But there’s one thing I can say…
My brother didn’t blame Soul Reapers.
He didn’t hate them.
I never knew he had such
a painful experience.
Why?!
Why didn’t my brother
despise Soul Reapers?!
Why did he continue to trust
in the Soul Reapers?
You’re not like the other Soul Reapers.
I owe her…
She saved my life.
And I haven’t repaid her yet.
I don't want to turn into a pitiful guy
who'd turn his back on her.
I have a feeling.
If I go with you,
I might discover something.
That’s what I think.
That’s why I’m gonna help you.
I’ll go as far as I can, to see what
a Soul Reaper is really like!
Ganju…
Y-You’re really something, Big Bro!
You’ve grown up fine!
Humph! Looks like you’ve
made up your mind.
Looks like I work with you.
Damn you…
Everyone…
are you ready for the Cannonball?
Yes!
Huh? By the way…
Huh?
Yoruichi, can you make
the Cannonball?
Huh? I wonder…
Let me try it.
Don’t tell me…
this is your first try?
Well, put that down there.
Humph!
Something like this is
as simple as breathing in and out.
Wow! It took us so long
to learn to do it!
Do you resent it?
Do you resent that I could
easily do something
that gave you so much trouble
to accomplish? Huh?
Ganju.
Were you able to master it?
I guess…
Then we’ll go with Flower-Crane
Cannon Launch Method Two.
Can you handle it?
Sure!
Don’t you chicken out and run off
in the middle of it now, damn brat.
Sis…
If you’re gonna go,
you’ve got to put your life on the line.
Y-Yes!
Are you ready?!
There’ll be no more delays,
you brats!
Now, get in there!
The sun will be rising soon.
That will be the signal to begin
the launching ceremony.
Listen… Once we’re in the Seireitei,
we have to stick together.
If you encounter any Captains,
don’t think, just run.
Our goal is to save Rukia,
and nothing else.
Don’t, by any means,
take any useless risks!
In the distance!
Copper-hued greed desires
36 degrees of dominance!
It has begun!
Pour in your spiritual energies!
72 pairs of illusions,
13 pairs of horns,
The monkey’s right paw
captures a star!
Held in the embrace of 25 suns,
the cradle of sand will flow with blood!
Flower-Crane Cannon Launch
Method Two!
Kagizaki!
You have done it, Lady Kukaku!
It’s a success!
Go with care…
Ganju.
Ohh…!
There wasn’t as much of
a shock as I expected.
Idiot… It’s only the beginning.
Huh?
Huh? What’s that?
It’s the next part!
The Flower-Crane Cannon Launch
Method Two involves two steps.
The First Spell controls everything
from the launch to the directional setting.
The Secondary Spell then controls
the acceleration and axis adjustment.
After that, you gradually
improve the accuracy!
Oh…
Don’t get in the way if you want
to get there safely.
Uh…Sure!
There’s something
I want to tell you all.
In order to enter the Seireitei,
we have to stabilize this cannonball.
We must keep the spiritual energy
output by each person
at a constant level.
To do that, if you keep
your hand on this thing,
you’ll be able to see how much
energy the others are releasing.
I want you to adjust
your energy release accordingly.
Right.
Okay.
One mistake and it’ll be the end.
I’m counting on you!
I understand.
Yes.
Flower-Crane Cannon Launch
Method Two!
Secondary Spell!
Fate of three sparrows,
fate of four dragons,
Blocked in from five directions,
unable to return six miles,
Wind of the heavens,
Orangutan.
Spoons, Cane of elm…
K-Kurosaki…
You’re releasing a little too much!
A-Am I? S-Sorry.
Kurosaki! Lower it some more!
I-I know!
I’ve lowered it a lot already!
Ichigo…
I said I know!
A thousand sprinkles of ash,
a thousand bits of wisdom…
Ichigo!
The measure of white clouds…
I said I know!
Approaching the great darkness,
Not stepping on scarlet shadows…
I’m turning it down now. Hold on!
A thousand sprinkles of ashes,
a thousand bits of wisdom?!
You idiot!
You made me read the same line twice!
So what?! Is that supposed
to be my fault too?
You’re making so much
noise flapping that trap of yours
that I lost my concentration,
you numbskull!
Stop it, Ichigo! Ganju…
This is no time to be doing that, is it?
She’s right. Stop it!
Stop it, I said!
Stop it, both of you!
Hey… Outside…
It’s Seireitei!
What’s that?!
Urgent alert! Urgent alert!
Intruders in Seireitei!
All Squads get into position! Repeat!
Urgent alert! Urgent alert!
Intruders?
Could it be those Ryoka?
Intruders in Seireitei!
All Squads get into position!
Hey! Wait, Kenpachi!
Ken-chan…!
Yachiru!
What is it? The enemy?
You’re going to kill them?
Yeah. It’s the Ryoka!
I don’t know how,
but it’s someone who fought
against Ichimaru and survived!
I want to fight him!
There is no choice…
This meeting of Squad Captains
is dismissed for now.
I shall inform you later how Ichimaru
will be dealt with.
All Squads will report immediately
to their battle stations!
The warning certainly came…
at a good time for you.
I don’t understand very well…
what you’re trying to say.
You think you can get away with it?
You’d better not…take me too lightly.
W-What is that?!
I doubt it will be able to get through
the Soul Shield Membrane…
I’ll order everyone to draw back,
just in case!
I-It’s coming this way!
Get out of here!
We’re going to crash!
We have no choice!
Everyone, pour in all the
spiritual energy you’ve got!
It crashed!
It ran into the Shield and stopped!
To crash there and not be destroyed…
Could it be a body of spiritual power
of such great concentration?
Come on…!
W-What’s going on?!
We got through the shield all right…
but why aren’t we falling to the ground?
Don’t get separated!
The Cannonball dissolved
when it hit the shield
and it’s only temporarily holding us up!
That means…
It will eventually create a whirlpool,
then explode and vanish.
Oh!
If we are separated at that time,
we will be blown apart by the shock!
Wha--?!
Ohh!
It’s begun!
Ohhh!
Damn…! I’m not gonna get…
blown away!
Don’t come near me!
Go away, if you don’t like it!
Will you two cut it out?!
Grab onto whoever is nearest to you!
Don’t let go, no matter what!
Damn it!
What do you mean by that?!
Let me sit on your shoulder.
Yoruichi!
Ishida…!
Chad…?!
Chad…!
Chad!
C-Chad!
Don’t worry. He will surely survive!
But if you want to be able to search
for him down there,
you must consider
your own safety first!
Damn it…!
Ichigo…!
Inoue…!
Damn… They split up into four!
Which one is it?
The strongest one…
Which one is it?!
With much appreciation
send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
What's going on?!
I'll go and take a look.
But my Zabimaru is gone!
Do you know where it is,
Hinamori?
I think someone was using it
to slice some pickled radish.
Roar, Zabimaru!
Chop up that radish!
Hasn't your character changed
a lot, recently?