Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends have
marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
Ishida encounters Cirucci Sanderwicci,
one of the Privaron Espada.
He uses the Seeleschneider,
the only bladed Quincy weapon,
to fight Cirucci's sword release.
A Quincy battle is about gathering
the reishi from the surrounding area
and fighting with it as a weapon.
Seeleschneider is the strongest
embodiment of that idea.
Your reishi is pretty much mine.
Y-You've got to be kidding!
Seeleschneider is not a sword.
Quincies don't use any weapon
other than bows.
Meanwhile, Sado was
engaged in fierce combat
with Arrancar Number 107,
Gantenbainne Mosqueda.
Cientos!
Stand, Yasutora Sado.
I know that you're still
hiding your power.
You're strong. Guys like you
shouldn't fight like this.
Swear, in the name of God
that we'll fight fairly.
No response, huh?
That makes me sad!
Sorry.
I wasn't exactly hiding it.
It's just that…
ever since I came to Hueco Mundo,
I sensed something
about my power
that's different than when
I was in the World of the Living.
I was puzzled
by that something,
and I wasn't able to
get a grasp of my power until now.
But I've finally grasped it.
I can use my full power
from here on.
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante.
This is my right arm's true form.
That's nasty, Pesche Gatiche!
Don't sneeze out your mucous!
What are you saying?!
This is not mucous!
It's my liquid that makes
everything it touches turn slippery!
Huh? This is Infinite Slick?
Infinite… What is that?
You forgot again?
That's the name you gave it!
Ah! That’s right!
Just as I expected of you, Ichigo.
Your observations are sharp!
I'm Uryu!
Now, now,
it doesn't matter who you are.
You're so nitpicky.
It's not okay!
Come to think of it,
didn't you run out of Infinite Slick
in that last battle?
That's what I thought,
but it seems it was
stuffed up somewhere!
Ah! What a waste!
Do you plan on collecting it?
It’s not something
you could reuse again.
What's wrong?
Hmm…
This is problematic.
Take a look.
This isn't Infinite Slick.
This really is my mucous.
Stop, don't come near me!
That's dirty!
What are you saying, Uryu?!
We're friends who
share the same fate!
Why do you only get my name right
at times like this?!
Wash your hands!
Where?
How should I know?!
Why? Wait!
Uryu!
This is…
Sado's Spiritual Pressure?!
But it can't be.
I caught you.
Thanks, Ichigo!
I didn't notice it until now.
No. I probably
didn't want to notice it.
When I came to Hueco Mundo,
I felt the power within me stir.
It's something I never felt
when I entered the Soul Society.
That stirring continued to get stronger
as I approached this place.
Then…
When I was hit by your attack,
I finally felt that stirring calm down.
I thought that maybe that stirring
was a stir of excitement.
I thought that when
I came to Hueco Mundo.
My power stirred with excitement
as if it had come home,
and recovered itself from
the rough welcome of its comrades.
There's something
I've been wondering about
ever since I got this power.
My power isn't like that of
Soul Reapers or Quincies.
Then what am I?
I finally found that answer.
Rather than
Soul Reapers and Quincies,
it seems my power
is closer to that of Hollows.
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante.
This is my right arm's true form.
And…
Its true power.
Did you get slower?
Tsk!
Bastard. What power.
Not only that, but his reactions
have become fast enough
to keep up with my Sonído!
I should be able to block this.
I can block this.
You really did get slower.
This guy is incredible.
Damn!
He's gotten faster again.
What should I do?!
I think that…
In this world,
there are no comparable powers.
Power always changes.
It's animalistic.
Small leads are always created.
Just like with you and me.
So what of it?
The one who broadens
his lead the most wins!
That's a good theory.
But we're still not sure
who's going to win!
I can't completely block it!
True form…
True power, eh?
Indeed, it’s worth boasting about.
But you haven't forgotten,
have you?
I have my own true form.
Isn't that right, Dragra?!
Dios, ruego nos perdone.
Sorry Gantenbainne.
There is one thing
I didn't tell you.
This arm is indeed
my right arm's true form.
And Abuelo's spirit indeed
dwells in this arm.
Abuelo taught me how to
use power to protect others.
You must learn what
your big, strong fists are for.
Yes. I just didn't understand.
Ever since I gained my power,
the power that dwelled in my right arm
was the power to protect others.
And during my training,
I finally found the power
within me to attack.
This is it.
Its name is Diablo…
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo.
Diablo…
The devil?
Diablo's a pretty exaggerated name!
Isn't it, Yasutora Sado?!
Why you…
Not bad.
In battle,
I always fight at full strength.
I know no other way to fight.
Is that so?
Then I guess
I'll go at full strength, too.
La Muerte.
I was able to grasp my power
because you fought me
at full strength, Gantenbainne.
Thank you. Thanks to you,
I can fight on.
I'll leave you alive.
I wish you luck.
Anyway…
What's the meaning of this?
Isn't this place within those walls?
There was supposed to be
a giant domed roof within these walls.
Why is there no roof?
Also, outside of these walls
it was forever night.
The moon didn't even
move from its position.
Why is it suddenly daytime?!
R-Run away.
What's this?!
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Nothing.
What are you doing?!
You're slow, Ichigo!
I'm Uryu!
Furthermore, you're suddenly
running ahead of me!
It's a seniority hierarchy!
What hierarchy?
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Let's go!
Hey, are you the first one here?
Stop!
Run away, Yasutora Sado!
He's no problem!
His movements are slow!
I know he's
pretty skilled though.
What are you doing,
Yasutora Sado?
Run away.
Rather than see what he does,
I should…
End this in a single blow!
What's this?
Is that your full power?
Renji, Nel is going to
tell our fortunes for us!
She doesn't have to.
The red-haired bad guy
should watch his step.
How terrifying.
Don't believe it.
It sounds so phony.
The Complete Quincy.
Today, I shall talk about
the Seeleschneider.
The Seeleschneider
is shaped like a sword,
but structurally,
it's more like a chainsaw.
Reishi oscillates at three million
revolutions a second along its blade.
Its reishi vibrations loosen the bonds
between the reishi of the object it cuts
so its user can steal reishi
to create his own weapons in battle.
In other words, you benefit
at someone else's expense, right?
My hand slipped.
Hey!