Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who
keep a close eye
on the countless souls, good and evil,
that fill this world.
Hitsugaya and the others
manage to defeat
the Arrancars who attacked
Karakura Town,
but they suffer a lot of damage.
In order to defeat his inner Hollow,
Ichigo goes to the Visoreds.
He retrains himself with Hirako
and the other Visoreds
to prepare for the coming showdown.
Meanwhile, Ukitake has been
investigating the actions
of Aizen and his followers before
they disappeared from Soul Society.
He discovers Aizen's true goal.
The showdown will be in winter!
Until then, we must hone our skills...
and prepare for battle!
Time's up.
It was dangerous
not giving me a warning!
If the time that you can sustain
a Hollow transformation
has gotten longer,
you should tell me!
Who's the one who's not giving
any warning?!
You're the one who said to
endure it as long as possible!
Now's not the time
to be complaining!
Next, next!
I told you that's too slow!
How's he doing?
His time has extended
by 0.5 seconds.
Wow. That's a big development.
What? That's all after doing this much?!
He doesn't have the talent, does he?
I'm surprised that everyone
hasn't gotten bored of him.
We don't have a choice...
For now, we've got to continue.
INTERNAL MEDICINE - PEDIATRICS
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Brother still hasn't come home...
Forget about him!
He'll come back when
we've forgotten about him.
When we forget about him?
Karin, do you always forget about him?
It's just a figure of speech.
Yes. There's no need to worry!
When you're at that age,
you feel like rebelling
against everyone around you
and you feel like getting out!
What do you mean?
When I was in high school,
I considered the whole world
my enemy and left home.
I wandered to the school at night.
I went to a far-off ocean and
- let out a youthful scream!
- I'm going to do this!
Is Brother doing that too?
He's probably somewhere
looking at the ocean
from which summer has
been long gone...
and fulfilling the desires of
his heart during mating season!
I keep telling you that
you mean "adolescence".
Is that so?
Well... I don't know if
that's really the case,
but this is Brother we're talking about.
He'll be all right!
Now let's eat dinner!
Yeah... Okay...
That aside, why isn't Rukia
coming home?!
You're more worried about her
than your own son?!
Rukia called me to say that
she's busy with school work,
so she's staying over
at Orihime's place.
Rukia!
I thought that
I got another daughter.
I'm so sad!
Shut up! Stop making a fuss
and eat already!
Then Abarai will be at
Kisuke Urahara's place for a while?
Yes... He made up some excuse
about why he's there.
Do you suppose he likes it there?
It's the second time
he's freeloaded there,
so it looks like
he's pretty used to the place.
He said that he was training Chad.
Surprisingly, he might be
enjoying himself.
Considering the power
of the Arrancars,
we can never have
enough fighting power.
So what should we do?
Do you really need to ask?
We've got to strengthen ourselves
or we won't be able to win
this battle.
That's right...
It's annoying, but the Arrancars
really are strong.
Bring it on!
I can have fun battles that way!
This is definitely something
you would like.
Yeah... Matsumoto, if you don't improve
your techniques,
you won't return to
Soul Society alive!
I know that!
Oh no! Look at the time!
If I don't hurry, the shop will
be filled with people
and I won't get to take
my time choosing things!
What? A shop?
I'm going to check out the town
for things to buy...
I mean...for anything strange.
I've got to always be attentive
to my surroundings!
You just said that
you were going shopping!
Bye, Captain. I'll be back!
That jerk... She doesn't listen to
what people say at all.
I've come all this way to
the World of the Living,
so I've got to enjoy it!
Oh! This is cute!
Excuse me!
Hmm... What should I do?
They're all cute, I can't decide...
Hmm... All right, I made up my mind!
Excuse me!
Yes?
I want all of them!
Ah... The World of the Living
really is great.
There are lots of fashionable clothes,
and further more,
things are way cheaper than
in Soul Society!
Oh! This place also has
a lot of great things!
All right! I'm going to look in here, too!
W-Welcome...
Ooh... They've got a lot of things.
Oh!
This is cute.
Excuse me. I'd like this!
Thank you very much!
You don't need to bag it.
Thank you for keeping things simple!
Here you go.
Oh, 10,000 Yen?
I'll get you your change!
What is this?!
There's activity in Karakura Town,
North Block 11.
Is it a Hollow?
What's this?
It's just an ordinary Hollow, right?
If that's the case,
then there's no need for us to go.
That's right. Rangiku is nearby too...
Then let's leave it to her.
But it's been really noisy...
How odd. What could that noise be?
Aw... I'm the closest!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hold on a second! I'll be right back!
Huh?
Oh. It's nothing!
Take care of the rest!
All right, beshi!
What? What?
It's nothing, beshi!
Huh?
It's just your imagination, beshi!
H-Hold on!
What is this?!
It's gone?
What is that?!
A soul?!
Come on! I'll defeat you!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Shut up! You're in the way, old lady!
Old?! Oh!
That brat!
Hey, stop that!
Out of the way, old lady!
You're interfering!
What are you saying?!
That's not something you can handle!
What...is this Spiritual Pressure?!
This Spiritual Pressure...
It's not a Hollow...
It's...
An Arrancar!
What are you?!
Your Spiritual Pressure is
pretty murky for an Arrancar.
You're in the way!
Don't interrupt my meal!
Run away!
Shut up!
What are you doing?!
Run away!
Hey! Let go of me!
Yahoo!
Ikkaku!
You bastard!
The finishing blow!
Ikkaku!
How boring... It wasn't even
a warm-up exercise!
It looks like he was no match
for Ikkaku.
Captain! Yumichika!
The Hollow's Spiritual Pressure
pattern suddenly changed,
so we hurried on over.
Matsumoto, you let your guard down
too much!
Sorry... But this boy...
You're an old hag,
but you're being scolded by a kid?!
"Old lady" is one thing,
but I won't let you call me an "old hag"!
Was that an Arrancar just now?
Yeah... But his Spiritual Pressure
was murky.
He wasn't fully mature.
Whatever his level was,
he was an Arrancar.
We should assume that
Aizen sent him intentionally.
Intentionally, huh?
I'm going to report to
Soul Society immediately.
I'm going to perform a Konso
on this cocky brat.
What's a Konso, old lady?
I never said that you could
call me "old lady"!
Wait, Matsumoto...
I want to ask him about the Arrancar...
You can perform the Konso afterwards.
What?!
Well... If you say so, Captain.
Oh? You're a captain?
That's right.
I don't believe it!
You're almost the same age as me!
Maybe we should perform a Konso!
Oh...wait! Ma'am?!
I hear that physical contact is important
in the World of the Living, beshi!
No, hold on... This place is...
Don't worry about that, beshi!
Well, it does bother me!
Just do it, beshi!
What's a "beshi"?!
Wait one moment!
I'll grab it right now...
Welcome back, beshi!
You came at a good time, beshi!
Stop...
Thank you for waiting.
You have some naughty lips, lady.
Here it is! This is it!
A new Arrancar was sent to
the World of the Living?
No... Captain Hitsugaya wants us
to find out
if there is any indication of that.
That means that Aizen has been
showing some sort of movement.
What should we do?
Analyzing the report comes first.
I'll do it from here.
All right.
I don't understand all this
about konsos or Soul Society!
What are you old men talking about?
O-Old men?!
How can you call me that?!
It means, to kids you look like
an old man, right?
Don't let it get to you.
No! I can't forgive him!
The sound of the words "old man"
is not a beautiful one!
Oh well...
Hey, boy.
You're blinding me,
you chrome dome!
Chrome dome?!
Put on a wig!
What the hell did you say?!
I've done nothing to you,
and yet you just abuse me like that!
Shut up!
We have something
we want to ask you.
So be good and answer
our questions, okay?
Humph!
When we're finished talking,
you'll go to a place called Soul Society.
Humph!
I won't go there!
It's all right. It's not a scary place...
I'll never go!
Those are the rules!
I said that I'm not going,
so I'm not going!
I still have things I want to do.
Come on! I'll defeat you!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Let's ask a different question.
Did you hear a whistle
when that Mock Arrancar appeared?
Come to think of it, I did!
Well?
I heard one...
Did he tell you anything?
Nothing! He just growled at me
and attacked!
I see...
Even if we ask him anything more
we won't find out anything new, will we?
It seems like they just happened
to meet there by chance.
So it seems...
Oh well... Let's perform a Konso.
Huh?! No!
I still have things I have to do here!
I don't want to go anywhere!
These are the rules...
Don't be stubborn!
No!
Stop it, stupid! Let me go!
Captain!
Hold on a moment!
I think this boy is confused by
what just happened.
We can wait through the night
before sending him!
Old lady...
It's not "old lady," it's "lady"!
All right...
Matsumoto, I'll leave this case to you.
Thank you very much!
My, my... What a weirdo.
Anyway, as long as we don't know
what Aizen's goal is,
we can't be too careful.
Don't let your guard down!
- Yes.
We're going to go.
If I have this, even I could...
Even you could what?
Hey!
Don't take other people's things
without permission.
Tsk! Old lady, you sure are stingy...
My name is Rangiku Matsumoto!
It's not "old lady"!
Call me "Ms. Rangiku"!
Okay...
What were you planning to do
after taking my sword?
It doesn't concern you!
It does concern me!
It's our job as Soul Reapers
to protect souls like you!
This is as important to us as our lives!
You wouldn't like it if I took
something important from you
without permission, would you?
No...
Now apologize.
Huh?
If you do something bad,
you apologize by saying "I'm sorry."
It's only proper!
If you don't...
A-All right.
I'm sorry...
Where's the "Ms. Rangiku"?
Ms. Rangiku...
Good.
Come to think of it,
what's your name?
Then where's your family?
Why were you there?
Why won't you say anything?!
Then...
What is this thing
that you have to do here?
There's someone I'm looking for...
Who?
We have to meet!
So who is it?
The town is dangerous right now!
Huh?
That monster earlier.
You don't know when
those will appear again!
There's no way you can handle them!
At least tell me your name.
Shota...
It's Shota Toyokawa.
I see! Shota, huh?!
It's that sound!
That murky Spiritual Pressure!
It's the same as that
Mock Arrancar this evening!
Don't you think that Matsumoto's
soul candy is behaving oddly?
It's behaving oddly and
talking strangely.
Really? Isn't it always like this?
Who gave you your soul candies?
Our lieutenant...
H-How suspicious.
The Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today, we're going to talk about
the Arrancar's Zanpakuto release.
VOLCANICA
An Arrancar's Zanpakuto is
the center of its power
DEL TORO
and is sealed away in the form
of a sword.
DEL TORO
when they release their sword,
they're releasing its true form.
TIJERETA
By the way, Grimmjow's true form is...
Someone always interferes
whenever I try to release my Zanpakuto.
Who should I get to interfere with him next?