Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What's wrong?!
My Zanpakuto
can't be this weak!
Don't be hasty!
We've only just begun!
That's not going to work!
Stop right there!
We've surrounded the area.
Sorry, but that's the situation.
Don't think you can
get away from me.
Bankai!
That was!
Byakuya?!
Captain Unohana.
More injured are coming in!
We don't have
enough staff on hand!
I see…
Isane, go help them out.
Yes, ma'am.
Captain?
What is it?
Excuse me.
I will be going.
We lost our chance to capture
several Zanpakuto at once.
It's very unfortunate.
Got to give credit
to those Zanpakuto.
And we still have
yet to receive reports of
coming across captain-class
Zanpakuto in battle.
Meaning, more powerful Zanpakuto
are bound to show up.
That certainly is depressing.
Anyway, we've got to
prepare ourselves.
I know.
Don't be so worried.
Everyone is doing their best.
Yeah.
Also, one more thing.
Is it about Squad Six?
Yeah.
Right now, Lieutenant Abarai
is doing his best,
but without the knowledge of
what their captain is doing,
their Squad Members
are getting anxious
and are unable to work
the way they want to.
Well, not only is
their captain missing,
we also have
an emergency on our hands.
I wonder what he's thinking.
What a difficult person.
Thanks for waiting.
Are things okay on your end?
Yes.
I have ordered the squad members
to get some rest.
Then I guess it's our turn.
Let's hurry.
Okay.
Where did he go?!
Was that really Byakuya?
Damn it! I'll definitely find him!
Huh? He's not here either.
Where did he go?
You were being pushy,
so he probably ran away.
How cute.
He's so bashful.
I don't think that's it!
What's that?
Hey!
What?
Wait up!
I thought it was him…
You were just imagining things?
Don't do that.
Where has my darling gone?
I bet I'll be able to find him
faster than you.
Then you should wear glasses.
Your eyesight seems pretty bad.
Oh, thank you.
You should do something
about your head.
Your brain seems pretty bad.
You think so?
Did you know?
Quiet goody-goody types like you
have terrible personalities.
Did you know?
Forceful women like you
are quite petty.
What did you say, you fatty?!
Shut up, you fatty!
How am I fat?!
Can't you tell
the difference between
a nice body and a flabby one?
Stop being a sore loser!
And how would you
know about my breasts
when you haven't
even seen them?
What the?!
How long have you
been there?!
Where's Muramasa?
Muramasa? I haven't seen him.
You're looking for him? Why?
What's his problem?
I don't know what
he's thinking at all.
See. You really are flat-chested!
That hurt!
I'd like for you to
call me slender!
Come back here!
That's…
Is that Ichigo Kurosaki?
Come to think of it, Muramasa
was very interested in him.
What?
I'm going to play
with him a little.
Hey!
What?
Good evening.
Hey!
You went ahead of me again!
Who are you guys?!
You're Ichigo Kurosaki,
aren't you?
What of it?!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm going to take him!
What do you mean by that?
I really hate that about you!
What about me?
Whenever you see a man,
you immediately have to claim him.
It's indecent!
That's right. Is that bad?
Growl!
What do you think?
Do you know what'll
happen if it touches you?
Getsuga…tensho!
Hmm… That's a nice thing
you've got there.
Could you stop using vulgar
expressions like that?
Why don't you stop hating me just
because you lack good looks?
Who's lacking?!
You, of course.
You're just jealous of
my body, aren't you?
Your head is really empty,
isn't it?!
What? What's your problem?!
– Who's got a problem?!
– Well… Umm…
Then the first one who brings him
to submission wins.
How's that?
I don't like how you
said that, but fine!
It's not about how I say it.
It's about strength.
Is this for real?
I don't have time to be doing that!
Don't run away!
You're not getting away!
You're a disgrace as a man
for embarrassing a woman
by turning down her advances!
Growl!
Keep running like that!
It makes this even more fun!
What is this?
I guess I have no choice…
Stop!
You two!
Rangiku!
Ichigo, mind if we
trade off with you?
Huh?!
We've got to defeat these two.
Please!
Okay.
Just as I thought, it's a Gillian.
And he was such a fun toy.
This is really off putting.
What are you saying?
This is a real drag.
You're really annoying, old lady.
I never knew you were
some cat monster.
I regret taking you seriously.
What?!
You seem to be doing
whatever you like.
Yes. That's because I'm free.
This is really great.
When I'm with an old lady like you,
I start to feel old myself.
I hated that!
So you're Tobiume…
I missed you.
Well, I didn't.
What? Why?
You showed so much
concern for me.
I thought we trusted each other.
Tobiume… Come back here.
No.
What?
I don't want to be with a weak
person like you any longer.
If you don't want to come back,
I hope you're ready!
Are you ready?
An old lady like
you can't beat me!
Aren't you going to come at me?
Do you think I'll come back to you
if you keep waiting like that?
Why do you always think in ways
that suit your own view?
That's why people
use and betray you.
If you wait, do you think
that person you admire
will come back to beg
for your forgiveness?
Take that! And that! And that!
If you don't run away quickly,
you're going to be bald!
I have a nice head shape.
I think I'd look good,
even without hair.
Enough of your cockiness.
You should run away quickly.
Or are you unable to move
because of your fat ass?
Were you always this talkative?
I had no idea.
Growl!
Take that!
You can't run away anymore!
Bakudo 37!
Tsuriboshi!
Rangiku!
Owowowow…
What are you doing?!
You're in my way!
Could you go somewhere else?!
You're the one
who bumped into me!
What?! Maybe you're
not careful enough!
– What's wrong with them?
– I almost had her back there,
– It looks like
– and you ruined it!
– they don't get along.
– Like that's my problem!
– That's right!
– Do you have a problem with that?!
Good grief.
Where are you, Byakuya?
Have you hidden
your Spiritual Pressure?
What's this?
I sense some sort of presence,
but I can't tell if
it's far or near.
What is it?
This presence…
Where have I felt it before?
There!
Who the hell are you?!
You're Ichigo Kurosaki,
aren't you?
Yeah. How do you
know my name?
You seem fairly skilled.
What of it?
Muramasa said to keep
away from you.
Me? Why?
That's what I want to know too.
Bankai!
A Bankai?
Yeah! What of it?
Is that sword a Zanpakuto?
Yeah.
A Zanpakuto…
What is its name?
What do mean?
What's wrong?
You are not my master?
What are you saying?
If you aren't my master,
I have no business with you.
Hey.
Don't you know whose
Zanpakuto you are?
No.
I don't know who my master is…
And I don't know my name.
You…
Sennen Hyoro.
What?!
Farewell.
Hyorinmaru!
It's Hyorinmaru!
Toshiro!
Your name is Hyorinmaru!
And you are my Zanpakuto!
Hyorinmaru, have you
lost your memory?
That's right.
I can't remember anything.
What a coincidence.
I can't remember anything, either.
Who am I?
I remember the first three bars…
Yours is simply from
having too much booze.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Huh?
This is the hot-water supply room.
Oh.
Sorry. I'm completely lost.
It happens when you're with
a squad other than your own.
That's so true.
Kyoraku?
You see I got lost too.
And I wound up in
Unohana's private quarters.
What?!
What a problem.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.