I shall wipe you out.
Stop it, Kurosaki!
If that is your wish,
then I will oblige.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Don't mock me!
You're not getting away!
That's impossible...
With his bare hands...?!
Damn it...
I never thought I...would be defeated
by a Hollowfied human...
It's...ludicrous...
Do it.
Any further resistance
is meaningless.
Haven't you given up yet?
El Directo!
Well? Do you finally understand?
I have no limit to my powers.
My branches can grow without limit
and give birth to countless soldiers.
Damn it!
He can even use the soldiers
he created as a shield...!
There's only one way...
But how do we create
that opportunity...?
Hey, Rukia!
Weren't you the one who said,
"Leave him to me"?!
Tsk! We're not going to get anywhere
if we keep on fighting like this!
Sado!
Renji!
I'll use Hakuren to stop
the soldiers' movement.
Sado, smash the frozen
soldiers to attack him.
Renji, you'll deliver the finishing
blow with Zabimaru!
Okay, got it!
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del Gigante...
Hikotsu Taiho!
What?!
That team play just now
was quite brilliant.
First, you froze my soldiers
to create an
opening in the wall, and then attacked me,
without a moment of hesitation.
It was a wonderful combination indeed...
But you were mistaken.
Regardless of what
techniques you use,
they will prove ineffective, for I can
create an infinite number of soldiers.
It's over...
As a show of respect for how
you've fought up until this point,
I will use my greatest power
to wipe you out.
What is this?!
Juhaku!
It would seem you were the
one who made a mistake.
Curse you! You were
after these branches!
Exactly.
The series of attacks just now
was nothing more than a ruse to
draw your attention away from me.
If your power is the ability to grow soldiers
like fruit, then the answer is simple.
All we had to do was freeze the
branches that created them.
It's obvious that fruit doesn't
grow from frozen branches.
You shouldn't have displayed
your power for me to see.
Damn it...
Wh-What?!
What was that?
It's...
Yammy...!
Yammy?!
The Espada Captain Hitsugaya
talked about?!
Yeah...
But that's odd...
I fought this guy once before,
in the World of the Living...
He was quite a large
fellow back then...
but he wasn't this huge...!
You mean he got bigger?!
How could that be?!
Is he having a growth spurt?!
No...but he's definitely different...
He seems twice as big...
Damn it...
That four-eyes... You're not
getting away with this...
You're definitely not getting
away with this!
I'll kill you!
Now what?!
It's coming from above the ceiling!
This Spiritual Pressure...
Is it...Ichigo?!
That's enough, Kurosaki.
The battle's been decided.
He's an enemy, but there's no
need to chop up his corpse...
That's enough, Kurosaki...
Didn't you hear me, Kurosaki?!
I said stop it...!
If you do that, you'll truly...
not be human anymore!
Stop it, Kurosaki!
Ishida-kun!
Help...her...
Help her...
I will...help her...
I will help her...
It's my fault.
It's because of what I said
that Kurosaki-kun tried to help me.
Why?
I trained because I didn't want to
be a burden to Kurosaki-kun.
I came here because I wanted
to protect Kurosaki-kun.
So why...?
Why did I rely on Kurosaki-kun
at the very last moment?
Wait, Kurosaki-kun!
Kuosaki-kun!
Kurosaki-kun!
My arms, legs and torso are regenerating,
but it's all just a sham.
My organs that he blew away
will never come back.
If it hadn't ended with that blow just now,
that would be me lying there dead.
The hole...closed...?
High-speed...regeneration...
Ku-Kurosaki...kun...?
Didn't I
get a hole blown through
my chest...?!
Kurosaki-kun...
Inoue...are you all right?
Ishida...!
You've finally...snapped out of it...
That wound... Did I do that?
You're a hard guy to kill.
Ulquiorra...
Pick it up. Let's finish this.
Am I the one...who
stabbed Ishida...?
Like I care.
Was it also me...who cut off
your left arm and leg...?
If that's so, then cut off
my left arm and leg.
Kurosaki-kun!
The entity that was fighting earlier
was me in Hollowfication,
with no consciousness.
That wasn't me.
If we're to settle this,
I have to be in an identical condition
to yours, or we won't be evenly matched!
Hold on, Kurosaki!
Do you know what you're saying?!
Kurosaki!
Fine.
If that is your wish,
then I will oblige.
Tsk. So this is it.
Kill me.
Make it quick...
I have no strength
left to even walk...
If you don't kill me now, this duel
will remain unsettled forever.
I refuse.
What?
I said I don't want to!
This is...
This is no way to win!
To the very end...you just
won't do as I want...
Just when I was finally
beginning to become a bit
interested in you people.
Are you afraid?
It's over.
You will die here, all alone,
with no contact with anyone.
I'm asking if you are afraid.
I am not afraid.
Because everyone came
to rescue me...
My heart is with theirs...
Such nonsense.
Because your friends came for you,
you are not afraid?
Do you really mean those words?
Yes.
What is "heart"?
If I rip open your chest,
will I see it inside?
If I split your skull,
Are you afraid of me,
girl?
I'm not afraid...
I'm not afraid.
I see.
I see now.
In this palm...
is a "heart."
The Yammy that fell down
from the tower...
Who does it belong to?
If we find someone's belongings,
we must return them to the owner!
But if that is the case,
then we are
obligated to receive five to
twenty percent worth of Yammy.
Th-That, I wouldn't want.
Complete Quincy
What do you have to say for this?!
I-I'm not the one who did it!
Unforgivable!
A-All right!
I'll hand over Ichigo,
once everything is over!
Do whatever you want
with him, for all I care!
Of course you will!
St-Stop taking it out on me!