Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
The thing that Kariya wants is…
a clean world ruled by Bounts.
He wants to create a new world!
What?!
When a Bount is powered up by
sucking the souls of living humans…
their Dolls gain even greater power
by a multiplier effect.
And soon, we will rule the world!
No way! I won't let you
use Keigo's life for that purpose!
It's useless.
Realize that you can't beat us, boy.
I won't!
Those eyes are dangerous.
Power without ideals is dangerous.
Please understand, boy.
Damn!
I won't let Keigo die!
It seems evident that I was born
under a star,
destined to witness the death of young
ones with bright futures ahead of them.
Farewell, boy.
Oh my. Is it all right to do it?
Yeah…
Who is it?
So…you're a Bount.
Thirteen Court Guards'
Third Squad Lieutenant…
Izuru Kira!
Aaah… H-H-Hold on!
What's this all about?
Let me down!
I've brought Yamada!
S-So what's this all about?!
I still have to tend to the register.
What's this?!
Sorry. I told him to hurry.
You can see our current situation…
This is horrible.
His pulse is very weak.
Please put up a barrier and
gather spiritual energy!
Understood!
I'll take care of the rest somehow!
As I expected from a member of
the Emergency Relief Team!
I'm relieved that you were sent here.
Now here I go!
I'm not finished yet!
This isn't child's play!
Cut it out!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh, all creation,
flap of wings.
The one who carries the title of human!
Tsubaki! Kotenzanshun!!
I reject!!
In the name of truth and temperance…
Dig your claws into
the wall of sinless dreams!
Hado 33! Sotatsui!!
Impossible! We had her, but…
Oh my God!
Close.
Too bad!
Kurodo!
You!
Inoue!
Ooh… Hold on a second--!
The technique is not perfected yet!
See? I told you so.
You should've waited.
Hm? What is it?
Humans are no good without
confidence in their abilities.
Want to take a small break?
Are you ordering me around?
Not really, but…
Well…
Regulate your breathing and
meditate for a few seconds
and gather power at your center
of gravity!
Yes, yes.
Shut up! Just work already!
Kurodo, are you all right?
Kurodo!
I'm all right. We mod souls
are pills, after all.
We won't die, no matter
what happens to our gigai.
Well… It still hurts a bit.
Anyway, now's our chance to escape!
Is that good enough?
Yes!
Yes…
There's no point if we let
the enemy escape.
What?
Quickly, run!
Right!
Fools! I'm not letting you get away!
Ooh! That's it.
This is the right timing!
This is what I was waiting for!
I wonder if I look beautiful!
You're beautiful.
Here it comes!
What?!
I'll take your place!
You--!
Old ladies should stay out of this--!
Old lady?!
Mabashi… What are you doing?
Everything's just wonderful.
It feels as if I've become
an all-powerful, all-knowing god.
Don't show off, you brat!
You're drunk on the taste of
your first living soul!
You sure are ugly…  Old Lady.
Wha--?!
He's here!
Zeig Dih, Ritze!
Is that a doll as well?
That's a doll too.
Their power is mysterious.
What do you plan to do with that?!
Go, Ritze!
Yes, sir.
I'm going up!
Are you out of your mind?!
I'm an ally.
I'm going down!
When push comes to shove, you pay no
attention to how you present yourself.
How unsightly…
You really are ugly, Old Lady.
Is there anything else
you wish for me to do?
Hold on a second.
Yes, sir.
What are you going to do?
You're really out of your mind!
Do what you like!
I can't keep up with you!
Oh my, is that it?
So it seems.
Mabashi! I'll get you for this!
I never thought that woman would be
so frightened. What's with that doll?
Inoue…
Step aside.
Kuchiki…
Hado 33! Sotatsui!!
Is there anything else
you wish for me to do?
Well…
Ritze, you can play with them
for a while.
Yes, sir.
I'm going forward!
I'm going diagonally right!
I'm going diagonally left!
Left and right?
An elevator only goes up and down!
Then, I'm going down!
Look out! You don't know
where she'll spring out!
I'm going up!
I've just arrived at the roof!
How is it, Ritze? Having fun?
Yes! Is there anything else
you wish for me to do?
That should be enough playing.
Ritze, let's begin!
Yes, sir!
What?!
H-How terrible!
She's incredibly fast!
I can't see her…
Damn… Where is she?!
Rats! I can't use kido like this!
Ritze sure is cute.
Inoue!
No!
What is this?
You did it!
Wow! Wonderful! Japanese
samurai Mifune! Sonny Chiba!
Thank goodness.
You're so awesome, Kuchiki.
Inoue!!
Kuchiki!
Are you all right?!
Get a hold of yourself!
Rukia!
Kuchiki!
What's so funny?!
You'll know…soon.
Kuchiki?!
Kuchi…ki?
That's good, Ritze.
You're so cute.
Ichigo?! Where's Ichigo?!
What should I do--?
That's it!
Ichigo, hold on--!
Kira…why are you here?
Tenth Squad Captain Hitsugaya
dispatched four Lieutenants.
Stand back.
I'll deal with them now.
Oh my… Yet again, a different type.
They're fighting over me.
I'm so happy to be born a woman.
Soul Society has already decided
to subdue the Bounts.
Prepare yourself!
My… How rigid.
But… That's also quite cute.
Here are my feelings to show for it!
Raise your head! Wabisuke!
It's useless. I have more hands
than you do!
That expression when you're cornered…
It makes me excited…
Huh? It seems…
my body is kind of heavy.
Wabisuke makes whoever it cuts
twice as heavy.
Your steel body has finally reached
its weight limit.
How horrible…
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Now!
Sorry! I have to get this guy to
Urahara's Shop.
Out of the way!
And If I tell you…that I won't?
If you won't move…
I'll cut you down!
Even if this guy is a Bount,
he's still human!
What's wrong?
Why are you hesitating--?
Then I'll…
Go first!
What?!
What incredible power!
I won't let you interfere any longer!
This is for Keigo!
I'm going to cut you down!
You didn't believe that an unarmed
human could have this much power?
We Bounts have eternal life.
We have to have mental strength
to withstand eternity.
I have used that to train myself
to the limit.
In other words, this is…
A human's potential power!
What's an arm or two?!
I won't hold back anymore!
I'll snatch that away from you.
I just have to wait until
you stop breathing, or…
I could snap your neck in one twist.
It's at least merciful
to not let you suffer.
Oh? I never expected you to
have that much strength left.
No way, Old Man!
I'm going to defeat you!
Cain…
What's wrong?
I might have…lived too long.
People are born…grow…and age.
I've already lived more than enough.
But…the lives that should live
always slip right past these hands.
Cain, get away from him.
Cain!
Old Man…
I'm not ready to die yet…
I'm not ready to die!
Cain!
Cain! Cain!!
Dalk!
D-Damn… I won't lose
to the likes of you.
I can't move.
Are you all right?!
Of course!
You're young…
so young, you still haven't
lived long enough.
Hey! Old Man!
Wait a second!
We're not through yet!
Dalk, that's enough.
I'm so heavy, I can't stand it.
Yeah, I know. Good work.
Don't rush your lives, kids.
It's not shameful to hold on
to your lives.
Farewell.
Hey! Old Man!
I can't go on any longer…
I'm going to die.
Ow! Who is that at a time like this?!
Huh? Lirin?!
What are you doing here?
You're all beat up. Pay a little more
attention to your appearance!
You call yourself a woman?
Let's hurry to Urahara's Shop!
O-Ow! A-All right! Argh!
Stop saying that!
Kuchiki?!
What in the world's going on?
Say, first off…could you
tell me your name?
Rukia…Kuchiki.
I see… That's a nice name…Rukia.
Worthy of being my new lackey.
Lackey?
So, Rukia, will you work for me?
Yes, sir.
Rukia, what are you doing?!
P-Please stop, Rukia!
Kuchiki--?!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
We've come all the way to
the World of the Living, so let's go buy gifts.
Konpeito for Lieutenant,
an electric razor for Ikkaku,
and Captain, I wonder if he'll be happy
if I take Ichigo as a fighting partner.
Despite your looks, you sure think up
some mean things.
Come now. This is how I always think.
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers after these messages!!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
It's gone--!
Everyone's snacks are gone!
I was looking forward to them!
What's going on?! It's noisy!
U-Umm, Mayuri…
Do you know what happened
to the snacks left here?
There's no way that I would know!
Wh-Who was that?
Could the snack have been…
It was baked sweet potatoes.
L-Leave already!
Phew!
You can tune in again!