I'll get it!
I heard Nakao was hit by a boat.
Then it's a lie that people won't
die if they leave Yomiyama!
Yeah, I guess.
So, we have nowhere to run?
What should we do?
Hey, should we still go on the class trip?
No way!
It makes no sense to go on
a class trip in the summer
of a year when it happens.
It'd be safest to stay
locked up at home.
Maybe...
Why is this even happening to us?
It's so unfair.
Yeah.
If only that transfer student
hadn't spoken to Misaki...
But I...
I protected them.
I left it for them...
...in the classroom.
You girls be careful.
We will.
How did Nakao seem that day?
He had a bad case of car sickness,
and threw up a lot.
Anything else?
Well...
He couldn't swim straight.
I see...
Maybe that's what happened!
What do you mean?
I spoke with Mr. Ohba, a city police
detective, about what happened.
And he had a nagging suspicion...
that Nakao may have been dead
before the boat hit him.
The condition of his head
when he died was inconsistent
with the timing of his
collision with the boat.
The herniation caused by
a cerebral contusion
had already progressed significantly.
You mean, before he went to the beach?
According to his family,
they heard a loud noise from
the stairway that morning.
When they went to check it out,
all they saw was Nakao
hurrying out the door.
He must have hit his head then.
Most likely.
So the event that led to his
death took place in Yomiyama?
A safe assumption.
When he left Yomiyama without
having his head checked at the hospital,
his death was assured.
Hey, Misaki?
Yes?
Never mind.
I'll say it after I find out for sure.
All right.
Did you find that class
photo from 26 years ago?
Not yet.
It's your fault.
It's your fault!
Inoya
The classroom?!
Seriously?
That's what Mr. Matsunaga said.
He must mean the class 3
homeroom in the old school building.
But what did he hide there?
All right, well, at least
we've got the location.
I'll just...
Wait.
I don't want to tell anyone else.
Why not?
If Nakao hadn't gone to the beach,
he probably wouldn't have died.
Still...
I don't want to get
anyone else involved.
I don't want anyone else to die.
We shouldn't tell Akazawa or
the countermeasures committee just yet.
If we find something,
and if we need their help
at that point, then we can.
Makes sense.
I wouldn't want to see Akazawa die.
So, when should we go
to the old building?
We can't go right now?
I have plans with my
family this evening.
Tomorrow would work.
Then, how about first
thing in the morning?
Come on, anything but morning!
All right, then... noon?
A lot of club members
will be around then.
And since the second
floor is barricaded...
Then... evening?
Hard to look for stuff at night.
Fine, 3 o'clock it is.
Okay.
Works for me.
Mochizuki, the art club meets
in that building, right?
Yeah.
Do any club members come
in over summer break?
No, never.
Then we can meet in the club room?
Sure!
I have a key,
and no one would question me being there.
Teshigawara, please don't
show up dressed like that.
Huh? Why not?
You'll stand out.
That's the price of being fashionable!
Inoya
Hey, do I spy Kouichi and Teshy?
What's the go-home club's
ace doing at school?
Nothing special.
We're meeting up with Mochizuki.
You two here for club stuff?
We wanted to see Mr.
Chibiki about something.
In the auxiliary library?
Not for that.
Mr. Chibiki is the drama club's advisor.
No way!
The guy who wears nothing but black?
That's surprising.
He actually gives pretty
solid acting advice.
And he looks sort of cool when he's
acting. It's fascinating.
So?
Why exactly are you here?
We're looking for a clue
to stopping the calamity.
We don't know what it is,
but if we do find it, we intend to
tell everyone else about it.
Seriously?
Something like that exists?
We want to stop the class 3
calamity ourselves, if we can.
You guys wanna come along?
Hey!
I'll pass.
Me, too.
Goodbye, Kouichi.
Later.
Bye.
Misaki!
Where's Mochizuki?
I don't know.
I just got here.
Why are you here?
I had nothing to do,
and I didn't want to stay at home,
so I thought I'd come in and draw.
Oh.
What about you?
And Mochizuki's coming, too?
What brings you three here?
Well...
I guess you could call it... exploring?
Sorry I'm late!
And where do you plan to explore?
Uh...
Well, Teshigawara said
we should meet up here...
No, I...
Um, that's it!
Sakaki said he had
to look for something!
It's sort of important.
Do Not Enter
Look, we don't know what might happen,
so I'd rather you stayed in the club room.
I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
You really are weird, Misaki.
Aren't you scared?
No, I don't think so.
Which room was class 3's?
Probably the one in the middle.
There are five classrooms.
By the way, didn't this old building
have seven mysteries of some kind?
I wouldn't know.
I don't give a rat's ass
about some urban legends.
So, you don't believe in
ghosts and curses and stuff?
As if!
They're all just coincidences
or tricks of the eye.
Except the calamity, of course.
Isn't "the secret of the auxiliary library"
one of the seven mysteries?
The library?
They say you can occasionally
hear moaning coming from it.
You ever heard it?
No.
I've heard there's an old
archive in its basement
containing secret writings that can't
be revealed to the public,
and that a librarian once locked
himself inside to guard them.
So basically, that librarian is still alive,
and you can hear him moaning
from the basement?
Bet it would just turn
out to be Chibiki.
I hear moaning in there, sometimes.
Are you serious?
Really?
Just kidding.
Let's let in some fresh air.
You are not fine at all.
Yes, I am. See?
You look fine to me.
I wouldn't want anyone to see us
and make us into another
one of the seven mysteries.
Let's keep the windows closed.
Teshigawara!
Gimme a break...
You seem fine.
Take care.
Yeah.
I'll call you.
Later.
I'm not finding anything.
I don't think it'll be in a place
where it's easy to find, like in a desk.
But surely it wouldn't be
where no one could find it.
Then there'd be no point in leaving it.
That's true.
It's probably not on the
floor, or in any desks.
What about in there?
All I see are cleaning supplies.
What's that?
Find something?
Something's written on it.
Let's see...
"To the future students who
are undoubtedly suffering
from the senseless disaster of this class."
Bingo!
This is it!
Mr. Matsunaga must have written that!
A/V Room
I'm sure there's one in here,
but is it okay to use it?
As long as no one finds out.
I found it!
Okay, let's play it.
Um...
My... My name is Katsumi Matsunaga.
I'm a student of the
9th grade, class 3 of 1983.
When I finish recording this,
I plan to hide it somewhere
in the classroom.
If you're listening to this tape,
you're most likely in class 3, as well.
I wonder what the
likelihood of that is...
Ayano
It's possible that you
guys are also terrified
by the senseless disaster
that I... that we...
Never mind.
I have two reasons
for leaving this tape.
One is to confess a sin. My sin.
I want to tell someone what I did.
I need someone to listen.
The other is to give you some advice.
It's about the extra student who gets
mixed up in the class,
and the calamity that
happens as a result...
How it can be stopped.
In other words...
Actually, I should start at the beginning.
Our class went on a trip.
We all left on August 8,
for three days and two nights.
Our homeroom teacher, Mr. Koga, had
suggested that we visit a local shrine.
There's an old shrine in this town
called Yomiyama Shrine.
He said that if we all prayed there,
he was sure the curse would be lifted.
There were 22 students in all,
myself included.
We only half believed him.
On the second day,
we climbed the mountain
to visit the shrine.
It was so old and run-down,
like it had been abandoned by the world.
Even though it bears
the name of the city,
it looked like it hadn't
been maintained at all.
So we decided to clean up the
grounds while we were there.
At the time, we hoped that maybe
this would lift the curse.
And after we prayed,
our teacher confidently declared,
"Everything will be all right now."
But it wasn't.
It wasn't that easy.
As soon as we left the shrine,
the clear skies suddenly turned overcast,
and it began to rain,
complete with lightning strikes.
As we hurried down the mountain,
the first victim was
a boy named Hamaguchi.
He was kind of dumb.
He was the only one
who'd brought an umbrella.
And we were on a mountain,
in a lightning storm...
He was walking
in front of me, when...
For a second, my vision went white,
and I heard a huge crash.
Hamaguchi had been struck by lightning.
I still remember the smell
of his flesh burning...
Anyway, the students panicked
and bolted,
leaving Hamaguchi behind,
desperate to get off the
mountain as quickly as possible.
But moments after we all took off,
blindly running through the rain...
The second victim was taken.
A girl named Hoshikawa.
In her panic,
she slipped and fell off a tall, sheer cliff.
All we could do was call for help
at the foot of the mountain.
But in the end, we couldn't
save either of them.
Praying at the shrine
had no effect whatsoever.
Now, this is the important part.
Right after we finally reached
the bottom of the mountain,
that's when it happened.
And by it, I mean...
I...
Crap!
That was close.
I was in a cold sweat.
Yeah, same.
The tape!
Oh, no.
Idiot.
You've gotta be kidding!
We didn't get to hear the important part!
What should we do?!
All we need to do is fix the tape.
It can be fixed?!
I think it's possible.
Great! Thanks, buddy!
We've gotta hear the rest!
Do you mind if we leave it with you?
I'll give it my best shot.
Brother!
Glass eye.