Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
A cursed parakeet?!
Well, all his past owners had
terrible things happen and died.
Are you serious? That's bad!
Do you want him, Shigeo?
Not after you tell me that!
Why don't you go dump
him someplace?
But…that's cruel!
How about you, Chad?
He's cute, y'know?
Stupid, stop it!
Chad has a weakness
for cute things like…
Wha--?!
We shall continue to devour…
In order to fill the emptiness
of our existence,
we must continue to devour.
A Soul Reaper's soul is
exceptionally delicious…
Once you taste it,
you always crave it.
C-Chad!
A-Are you all right, Chad?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Fine?! You're bleeding!
Thank you for saving me.
Huh?
My name is Yuichi Shibata.
What's yours?
W-What the hell?!
It's like it understood
what just happened!
This parakeet is cursed!
What's your name, Mister?
Yasutora Sado.
I'm 15 years old…still.
Hey! Chad is interested in it!
Geez… I can't believe my injuries
healed in a day.
Surprised?
I was among the best in
my Kido class.
That was easy.
Kido class? So what…?
Soul Reapers go to school?
Huh? Well yes…
But Ichigo…
How do you drink this?
Huh? You just poke
a straw in it and drink.
Straw?
Hey, you're together again.
Huh?
You guys are quite close, huh?
Mizuiro… Fool!
Do we look like friends?
Am I wrong?
Oh well, if you say so.
But Ichigo, you should be more
aware of what people will think.
Stupid, if I cared about
what people thought,
I'd have dyed my hair black.
That's true.
So this is it!
But where do I poke this?
Hello Kuchiki!
Huh? Helloo! Err…Kojima.
Right! I haven't introduced
myself yet.
I'm Mizuiro Kojima, age 15. I like…
Picking up girls.
Huh? No way!
That's mean!
He looks like a dork,
but he's a real flirt.
Watch out for him.
Stop it! You'll ruin my reputation!
Besides, I'm only interested
in older women.
That's why she has to be careful.
Huh?
Never mind.
What's this?!
There's the beautiful new transfer,
Kuchiki!
What are you doing here?!
Ichigo lured her here.
No way!
What?! Ichigo, why you…!
Good job!
T-Thanks. You're so happy
you're crying?
I'm so glad you've come, Captain!
To this garden of masculinity!
Hello.
Awright, everyone!
We're partying it up during lunch!
With milk coffee and
yakisoba bread?
Shut up! It's the spirit that counts!
And Kuchiki…
If you're ever in need,
don't hesitate to come to me!
Really?
Of course!
Oh, Chad…
Mmm...
Are you injured?
Hey yeah, what happened?
A steel beam fell on my head yesterday.
A steel beam?!
As for my hand, I had
a collision with a motorcycle.
And the rider got hurt bad…
so I just carried him to the hospital.
N-No wonder you were late.
But geez, what is
your body made of?
Huh? What's with the bird?
Hello, my name is Yuichi Shibata.
What's your name?
Hey, this is amazing!
It really talks!
My name is Keigo Asano.
Can you say that?
Chad, where'd you get the bird?
Yesterday.
Someone gave it to me.
Hold it!
You were just about to tell us,
but got lazy and cut it short, didn't you?!
That's a bad habit you have.
Now, explain!
I didn't cut it short.
Oh yes you did! Listen you…
Don't worry.
Huh?
There's definitely something
in that bird, but it's not evil.
It's probably a lonely spirit.
But we cannot leave it alone.
We should perform a Konso tonight.
Got it. Another sleepless night.
Don't complain.
Yeah-yeah…
Still…
He sensed a spirit and worried
about the safety of the others…
Perhaps he's beginning to
understand
what it means
to be a Soul Reaper.
Here.
Thanks.
It was during 8th grade…
Huh?
...when I first met Chad.
Back then, my hair color got
people's attention
and got me into fights.
It was when I got into
this little scrape.
Who the hell are you?!
Die!
Chad never fights back,
no matter how much
people goad him.
He's an odd one.
Yeah.
This juice is good.
Yeah?
I'm home!
Kurosaki Clinic
Internal Medicine - Pediatrics
Outta the way! Move!
Huh? What's the matter, Karin?
What's your hurry?
H-Hi Brother!
What's going on?
An accident!
There was a car accident
at the intersection.
Car accident?
You won't take him?
Do something!
There are patients who need more
than our first-aid level of treatment!
Now listen! Tell your director
it's a request from Kurosaki!
Then you'll find some free beds!
Understand?!
Dad…
Damn useless people!
Anything I can do to help?
No!
Get back in some corner and
stay outta the way!
Dad, one more patient!
Huh?
Man, he's a big one.
Ichigo, come here and get to work!
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
Chad!
Oh, that's a terrible wound…!
This is bad!
It looks like a burn.
What hit you?
This feeling…
You'll have to take it
easy for awhile.
No.
Huh?
I'm…okay now.
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way you're fine
after losing so much blood!
You see?
Yuzu! Karin!
Get a bed ready.
Yes! Let's get you to bed, okay?
Did you feel it?
Of course.
I felt it even in here.
I didn't sense anything
from the parakeet.
But his injury...
smelled of Hollow.
Kurosaki Clinic
Internal Medicine - Pediatrics
'Morning!
Brother, breakfast is ready.
Where's Karin?
She didn't want breakfast.
I don't think she feels well.
Her? Not feeling well?
That's unusual.
Ichigo!
Bad news!
Chad has disappeared from his room!
Ichigo!
Rukia!
Well? Any clues about
where he went?
No, how about you?
No luck either.
There's no news at the Soul Society
about a Hollow.
I can't find anything
on the radar either.
Usually, Hollows hide themselves
between this world and the Soul Society,
except when they
commit foul deeds.
Even if Hollows are after Chad,
we won't be able to
get the location
unless they show
themselves in this world. Got it?
You expect me to understand
with those kindergarten drawings?
A Hollow is targeting Chad.
It'll be too late if we wait
until he's attacked!
There has to be something…!
That's right! The parakeet Chad had!
We just have to follow
the soul that possessed it!
That's not possible!
All right…
Ichi...go? What's this sensation?
Mister…you're nice.
Hmm?
I need to apologize to you, Mister.
To be honest, everyone who
owns me gets bad luck.
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I…
Don't worry about it.
So Mister, forget about me…
and abandon me.
Mister…
I can't do that.
Ichi…go…
I must tell him…
How can this be…?
It's such a weak soul,
even I cannot sense its presence.
And he's trying to find it from
this distance?
This is…?
I found him!
This way!
Those were..
Spirit Ribbons, visible rays
of spiritual energy.
Only high-level Soul Reapers
are able to see them.
Has he progressed that much
in this short time?
I guess we lost him.
Mister, you don't have
to do this anymore.
It's all right, I don't mind.
Being tough is my one good trait.
Watch out!
He found us! Let's get away!
Mister…
Don't worry. This is nothing.
There!
It's Chad!
That idiot!
Why's he running?!
It's dangerous alone!
Ichigo!
Karin!
What're you doing?
You're still so weak!
Karin!
Ichigo!
Take her home first.
I'll go and save him.
What're you saying?! I can't…!
Don't complain!
If you leave her there and go,
you'll be distracted when
you fight the Hollow.
I can't have that.
Understand? Now go!
Rukia!
You…haven't gotten enough of
your powers back to fight a Hollow.
Don't take chances.
Fool.
There's no way I'd make
you worry by messing up.
See you!
Yeah!
Are you all right, Karin?
Hang on! This isn't like you!
Ichigo...
I...saw it...
Last night...the memories of the spirit
that possessed the parakeet.
I think it's because I was
the closest in age.
The strongest memory that
remains in that child's mind.
It came flowing into me.
That child... His mother was killed
right before his very eyes!
Please...Ichigo!
Please...save...
that child!
Please!
Dammit! I can't overtake them!
If I were not in this gigai,
it would be easy.
Why is it that the physical powers
of a gigai are the same
as for an average human being?!
Those dolts at the technology
development bureau!
No...I'm starting to run
out of breath!
What a nice smell!
You smell delicious!
Let me devour...
that soul of yours!
Hmm... You won't die in just one shot?
And it seems you can see me, huh?
Just...who are you?!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh, all creation,
flap of wings...
the one who carries
the title of human!
In the name of truth and temperance,
dig your claws into
the wall of sinless dreams!
Destruction Spell 33...
Pale Fire Crash!
It worked!
Good, at least this much
of my powers are back.
What was that noise?
She's being attacked.
The lady who was after us
earlier is being attacked
by the one who is after us!
Y-You...
Stay here.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to save her.
No, you can't! It's too dangerous!
No, I don't mean I'm in danger
of being hit by a car
if you leave me in the road!
No, Mister...
You can't see ghosts!
No! He'll get you! Wait!
Mister! Mister!
Ridiculous! It didn't even scratch him!
Hah! I know that trick!
It's a Soul Reaper spell, right?
But yours is so weak.
I felt nothing.
Dammit!
As I thought, my Kido hasn't recovered
enough to use a spell of that level.
I get it, you're a Soul Reaper.
No wonder you smell so yummy.
A Soul Reaper, huh?
How nice!
I've devoured two Soul Reapers
who tried to help that kid pass over.
They were delicious!
By kid, do you mean the spirit
inside that parakeet?
Yes.
It seems you keep chasing
after that soul.
Why is that?!
Well, if you'll let me eat you
without resisting, I'll tell you.
Why you--!
Hey...
Tell him...
That if he passes over,
he'll be able to see his mother.
Tell that boy...
Don't let that boy be
all alone anymore.
Please Ichigo...
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Urahara Shop,
where Soul Reapers often visit...
Urahara Kisuke, the shop owner
who carries a dangerous scent on him...
And the thing that is taken out
of the store invites another tragedy...
That preview is one week too early!
Besides, the story isn't that sad...
Oh no, we're out of time again!