Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
You’re not going to sleep yet?
You’re going to make yourself sick.
Yeah, just a little bit more…
How’s Tsubaki’s recovery?
Not yet…
That time, I…
Tsubaki! Koten Zanshun! I reject!
Tsubaki!
Fool…! Faltering like that!
Tsubaki…
I had already lost my will to fight.
Sorry, Orihime.
Healing one of our own requires
a certain knack.
I’m so sorry…
It’ll be okay, Orihime.
Your Shunshun Rikka
have incredible powers.
Indeed! Any doubt in your heart
directly influences our powers,
so you need to be strong, Orihime!
But…
We’ll practice some more!
So that you can ditch
the Kotodama Spirit Chant,
and summon us by just
the attack names!
If you can do that,
we will be able to protect you faster!
Y-Yeah…
W-What is it?
Just wait a little longer…
I’ll be better in no time.
U-Uh-huh!
Are you ready?
Yep… I’m ready. Let’s go.
This may have been for the best…
Being with her these past days,
it’s become very apparent.
Orihime is definitely
not suited for combat!
She hates seeing others get hurt
more than anything.
Even if it is the enemy…
A person like that shouldn’t fight.
For that kind of fighting will only bring
harm to herself and her comrades.
Hey! You guys!
Wait a minute!
What are you guys doing over here?!
What squad are you with?
Squad Eleven.
Oh? That’s odd…
I’m with Squad Eleven, too, but…
In our squad that specializes
in combat,
this is the first time I’ve ever seen
a dimwit walking around
without carrying his zanpaku-to!
Oh no! So each squad
had distinctive traits!
That’s Squad Twelve’s emblem.
Not ours…
Guess you wouldn’t know, huh?
Who the heck are you guys?
Damn… I had hoped
we could keep going quietly,
but I have no choice!
That was close, you guys!
Were you hurt?
Of all things, doubting your own comrade,
what a jerk!
This guy’s drunk!
T-Thank you very much!
It’s okay,
we’re in the same Squad Twelve,
so it’s expected
that we help each other.
These guys will pick any excuse
to come next door to mess with us. Damn it!
When you’re rushed,
it’s possible to forget even
your sword sometimes!
Here, this way!
– We’ll walk you back to quarters.
– Sounds good!
Wait… Think about it…
Isn’t it strange for them to
help us in this situation?
Even though he was drunk,
what that man said was perfectly logical.
For what reason would these guys
go out of their way to help us?
Orihime! Get away…
Wh-Why…
Captain! This isn’t what
we agreed upon!
Our role was to just talk to them,
then bring them back to quarters.
– Oh, no.
– Then why this...
– A released bomb shouldn’t return.
– How could you do this, Captain?!
Captain--!
A shield?!
Thank you.
If you hadn’t screamed out…
I…
No, we survived
because you’ve been
practicing all this time.
Wh-What about the others?
Unfortunately…
But, that’s not something
you should feel guilty about.
The one who should feel guilty,
however…is you!
Oh…!
This is an interesting technique!
That shield…
Is it the work of that woman
behind you?
I have no intention of answering you.
How interesting!
That’s the first time
I’ve seen that technique!
How about it, woman!
Won’t you work for me as
a research subject?
Don’t be ridiculous!
I said I have no intention
of answering you!
Should you work for me,
I won’t do you wrong!
Rest assured!
I’m gentle with the ladies.
She’s crying…?
Why is she crying?!
Is she afraid? No!
Be careful!
If she were afraid,
she wouldn’t have risked danger
just to save me!
Then why? Is she crying for
those guys that died just now?!
Besides, why did she save me?!
I’m the enemy!
What’s in it for her to save me?
I…I just don’t get it.
I know! I’ll offer you
my best working conditions!
I’ll limit drug therapies to
eight times a day!
And mechanical experiments up
to five times a day!
I’ll even do my utmost to refrain
from performing surgeries
which may be life-threatening!
How about it?
Rather exceptional terms for
an experimental subject, I should think.
He’s fast.
Oh… A Quincy, huh?
Such a rarity. It’s been years
since I’ve seen a live specimen.
But I’m sorry, I’ve finished researching
your kind already.
So I’m no longer interested in your kind.
Step aside there!
Finished researching?
What do you mean by that?
What are you?
What? You Ryokas don’t bother
to investigate first
and just storm
into your enemy’s base?
How careless…
At the very least,
you should commit to memory
the names of the thirteen top people,
I should think.
Captain of Squad Twelve,
as well as the second-generation
Chief of Research and Development,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
You don’t have to
remember that though.
Pretty soon,
you won’t know anything anyway.
This guy…
Orihime!
Run! Hurry!
No!
I’ll fight too!
Hey, you from Squad Eleven!
Take Orihime and run!
Y-You’ve got to be kidding!
Why me?
You don’t want to die, do you?
If you drag your feet,
you’ll be caught in the crossfire!
Take her away by force,
if necessary! Otherwise…
I’ll shoot you!
Hurry!
D-Damn it!
Come on, Missy!
No!
Did I say you could run away?
Did I say you could go after them?
My, my… I’m not interested in you.
Let–me–go–!
– Please let me go!
– Ouch, ouch, ouch! Oh, no, I can’t!
I, Makizo Aramaki,
a ten-year member of Squad Eleven,
also known as Maki-Maki!
I am a compassionate man
who won’t leave behind women
and children, even if I were asked to!
Why, you…
Sorry about that.
I have no intention of getting caught up
in that freak Kurotsuchi’s fight or
getting shot by that four-eyed jerk…
So I had to be a bit rough there…
Maybe I was a bit too rough…
Maybe I should apologize
when she wakes up…
My, my… It takes quite an effort
to get this set up…
He took his own arm off?!
It hurts… It sure does hurt…
It hurts…and it hurts…
So much that my mind’s
about to melt.
It seems that the woman
has gotten away.
Oh well. If there’s even a single strand
of her hair left on the ground,
that’s enough to track her down.
I can’t wait to capture and
examine her until she turns to mush.
I hate to lose even a minute
or a second.
Monster…
There are two enemies…
If Kurotsuchi is the captain,
then is that woman behind him
his lieutenant?
She hasn’t moved even though
her superior has a bow pointed at him…
does that mean…
her combat abilities are low?
If so…then I should start
with the captain!
That guy…?!
Pretty good…
Nice moves you’ve got there.
The previous one and
the one just now…
That was the “Hiren Kyaku,” right?
An advanced Quincy move that
involves moving at high speed
by creating a current of
spiritual energy beneath the feet.
I never expected a young person
like you to have been trained in it.
You’re pretty good.
Seems you’re quite talented…
I couldn’t outrun him…!
However, it’s a bit of a bother to
have you running around me like that…
After this, I need to capture
that woman and conduct my research.
I’m busy, you see…
So at this time…
I’ll have to use a method
with the least effort…
to kill you.
Claw out…
Ashisogi Jizo.
What are its abilities?
If they’re the type that
absorb attacks…
Then I can’t attack it head on!
Damn it!
Wha--?!
This one’s attacking!
L-Let go!
It can’t be…!
No way…
He really attacked his subordinate…
Isn’t she a part of his team?
Why…?
You idiot!
I thought I taught you to hold on,
even if your arms were ripped out!
M-My deepest apologies.
Oh well… It’s not like I expected much
from you in the first place.
At least we got this far.
From here, it’ll take no more
effort than strangling a baby.
He really sacrificed
his subordinate just to kill me…!
You’re sweating quite a bit.
It must hurt. Without even crying out
you bear your pain…
You’ve got some will.
It’s not the first time you
were cut by a sword?
It’s my second time…!
Oh…so you’re quite experienced.
How nice…however…
Geez, what a noisy one.
My deepest apologies…
Sir Mayuri… May I have some
of the Hojiku-zai as well…?
The wounds seem to extend to my lungs…
At this rate…
I may not…
be able to sustain my life-force…
What…?!
You! Are you insulting me?!
Eh?! Are you?!
Your body! With just that cut?!
You’re saying it’s no good?!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Isn’t she part of your group?
She’s really going to die!
And are you insulting me also?
You think she’ll die from just this?
This body which I created?!
With a wound of that degree!
You think she’ll cease to function?!
You’d better be careful
of whom you insult!
You… Created…?
That’s right. Let me tell you her name.
Nemu Kurotsuchi.
By melding the quintessence of
my gigai techniques and gikon techniques
I created this masterpiece.
So don’t go parading your creepy sense
of justice around here.
How I decide to use this thing,
for a stranger such as you,
it’s none of your business!
Stop it!
It…it won’t move!
Just realizing it now?
Pretty dense, aren’t you…
From whatever it cuts, this robs
the mobility of its four limbs.
That is the ability of this “Ashisogi Jizo.”
A paralyzing poison, huh?...
Don’t be ridiculous.
It’s not something that primitive.
Of the countless signals fired
from your brain,
it selectively severs just the signals
controlling the movement of your limbs.
Such a sophisticated drug
is what it produces.
It’s not paralysis.
It robs only the movement of the limbs,
in other words…
Not an ounce of pain is lost.
Hey, Nemu! Get up!
You’re going to strike the final blow!
Nemu! Oh yeah, that’s right…
You were cut with this also,
so you can’t move either!
Damn! You’re useless!
Cut it out…
What?
I said, stop it!
Persistent, aren’t you?
Or is it something else?
Showing mercy to wounded women,
even if they were the enemy,
is that the pride of the Quincy
that you all are so fond of?
What?
You are fond of it, aren’t you?
Because you all keep saying
that line until the moment you die.
By the pride of the Quincy,
I cannot do that!
I won’t allow that!
It’s so annoying!
Each and every one of you!
Regardless, with one thrust of this,
any words of resistance
will become meaningless.
You…
Now hold on.
This is the story of my hardships...
When I became
the Chief of Research and Development,
the Quincy were already
a rare breed…
We had put surveillances
on the surviving members.
Well, purposely delaying rescue
of that which you guard,
just to obtain the konpaku,
Can you understand?
Just how difficult this was?
But even with all that effort, there weren’t
any decent research specimens.
The last specimen I had
was a grubby old man.
He kept calling his apprentice’s
or grandson’s name the whole time.
It was so creepy…
Do you want to see his picture?
It’s after the experiments,
so his original form wasn’t maintained.
What was the name of his apprentice?
Goodness…
It seems once my experiments
are concluded, I lose all interest…
What’s that?!
The name of his apprentice…
Do you want me to tell you…?
The name of his apprentice is…
Uryu… Uryu Ishida.
This person is Soken Ishida…
He was my teacher…
As well as my grandfather!
Oh… And?
I’m glad Orihime isn’t here.
This is one battle that
I wouldn’t want her to see.
By the pride of the Quincy,
I will kill you!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Lately, it feels like my appearances
have been diminishing…
Do not fret.
Yoruichi.
You shall have no appearances
in the next episode either.
Ishida is going to do his best
by himself.
Leave it to me.
If you do not master
the Bankai soon,
perhaps you may never
have another turn.
I-I’ll do my best!