Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Wind Licht Schneide!
Getsugatensho!
Ichigo…
Kariya!
Too slow!
Byakuya! Cut it out!
Are you trying to get me killed
as well?!
I told you that you're in the way.
Y-You bastard!
What?!
Damn… How is he able to
keep up with me?
I'm not nearly as fast
as you are, but…
you could say it's my years
of fighting experience.
There's that.
What?
I know which way you're going to move.
I know…
It seems that your wind defense
can't protect you against everything.
No matter how good your defense is,
it's possible to harm you…
if I use an attack that's more powerful.
You're better than I thought.
But…you still won't be able
to defeat me.
I told you… Soul Society is filled
with concentrated reishi.
We Bounts are immortal here.
Then prove your immortality.
What the hell?!
Wh-What is it this time?!
What? You're…!
Huh? Huh?! Why?!
That's the face of
that old lady, Yoshino!
It can't be…
I finally found you.
What?
Who…are you?
My name is Rantao.
What?!
No way!
Rantao…you say?!
Yes.
Rantao… The creator of the Bounts
who was exiled from Seireitei!
You're still alive?
Wait a second! Are you really her?
And…that face…
The attitude of the Soul Reapers
has changed quite a bit, hasn't it?
What?
So vulgar.
What?!
Isn't it enough proof that
I know about the Bounts?
Huh?
I'm the only one who knows about
the Bounts other than
the Soul Reapers of Seireitei.
All the information on Bounts,
except for a small section…
should have been destroyed.
You're…a Bount, aren't you?
You know that I'm the real Rantao.
You can feel it, can't you?
I knew you'd come some day.
I've waited for
a mind-numbingly long time.
Indeed… It took a long time
to get here.
We Bounts have suffered
a painfully long time.
And…are you the one
who forced this upon us?!
You're much more emotional
than you look…
And more short-tempered
than you sound…
Are you going to kill me?
Wait!
There are a lot of things I want to
ask you if you’re really Rantao.
I can't let you die here!
Who said I was going to kill her here?
What?
She has to watch us
achieve our goal.
What happened as
a result of her actions…
I'm going to kill her…
after I destroy Seireitei.
You bastard!
Byakuya!
I told you… I'll kill anyone who's
an enemy of Soul Society.
You're not getting away!
It seems that I can also break…
your so-called wind defense!
Kariya, let's pull back for now.
Koga…
Dalk! Cause a disturbance!
Oh my. There are so many
handsome men!
But I'm sorry. I can't play with you today!
Lirin, do you know where they are?
It's no good… My sensors couldn't work
properly in those explosions!
Damn!
Hey!
What?
Aren't you going to chase Kariya?
He has already disappeared
into the distance.
Are you saying that's it's pointless
to go after him?
Until the next time.
Jeez. Oh well…
So…
Are you an enemy?
Or are you an ally?
There are more people than
I thought there'd be…
Ichinose, at this rate they'll continue
to double in number…
and will quickly grow
into a huge crowd!
I guess this means there were a lot
who were dissatisfied with Seireitei…
Huh? Where did Kariya go?
I don't see Koga anywhere either.
They'll be back soon.
Ichigo, someone's coming!
What?
Ishida!
Kurosaki!
You're safe…
Wh-What?!
Yoshino?
No… It's Rantao,
the one Yoruichi talked about.
What?!
That outfit… A Quincy?
What in the world…is this?
A Soul Reaper and a Quincy, huh?
That's a pretty amusing combination.
If you're going against the Bounts,
I'm not your enemy.
Then could you tell us about the Bounts?
Before that…
I'm going to
tend to your wounds.
My home is nearby.
We can talk there.
There, there. All right, Bonnie, stop.
Stop!
I think… He should be somewhere
around here…
Ganju, what are you going to do?
Well, just watch.
What's this?
He's the Bull of Kusajishi.
What do you want, Ganju?
Hey! It's been a while.
That hurts!
Deal with it! I'm almost finished!
There. You're healed.
O-Oh!
My wounds are healed!
Of course they are.
Don't underestimate a technician!
So…what should I begin talking about?
How much do you know
about the Bounts?
You were using human souls to
do experiments
to create a life that never dies.
I heard that from the leader
of the Bounts, Kariya.
Kariya…I see.
That man earlier, he's the Bounts'…
Yeah…
The success rate of our experiment
should have been very high.
But there was an accident
during the experiment…
that affected the cycle of rebirth.
That's what created the Bounts,
wasn't it?
That's right… The Bounts had no place
in the World of the Living.
Even so, they tried to rely
on Soul Society, but…
Soul Society didn't allow that.
Allowing Bounts in would mean
accepting their existence.
That would mean admitting
that they had created
a subspecies as a side effect
of the experiment…
After being refused entrance…
the Bounts tried to force their way
into Soul Society.
And…that's when the Quincies
became involved.
Soul Society took that chance and
nearly annihilated the Bounts.
The ones who managed to escape or
were living elsewhere during that battle…
are Kariya's group right now.
If you've gathered that much information,
what were you doing until now?
You created the Bounts.
Couldn't you have gone to the World
of the Living and done something?
You're so concerned about
the Bounts…
As a researcher,
didn't you feel attached
to the Bounts even if
they were created by accident?!
My Soul Reaper power was
sealed away
when I was exiled from Seireitei…
This includes going to
the World of the Living…
I can't even escape this place.
What was that power you used
to get between us?
After many years
and much research…
I was finally able to get back enough
Spiritual Pressure to fight.
However…That's also limited…
But why were you the only one
exiled from Seireitei?
The ones from Seireitei who exiled me…
were relieved to learn that
the Bounts
didn't have the reishi
conversion ability.
Did they think that everything could
be settled in the World of the Living?
I predicted that the Bounts would
use any means they could
to come here.
That's why I suggested we publicize
everything and accept the Bounts.
And this is the result…
You…
Quincy.
I've caused you a lot of trouble.
Kariya used your power
to come here, didn't he?
Y-Yes…
That's fine…
But why? The Bounts used
the Quincy power.
Does that mean you are the Bounts’ ally
since you helped them?
But from what I can see,
you seem to be their enemy.
What's the meaning of this?
Well…
Well, a lot has happened…
Ishida, right?
Do you know what kind
of tool that is?
What?
That artifact is…incredibly dangerous.
If you use it recklessly…
I know. But I have to use this power
to defeat Kariya.
No matter what happens…
You say that you're prepared?
I see…
But be careful.
Make sure that you don't cause trouble,
not only for yourself,
but to those around you as well.
H-Hey!
I'm all right…
But…
Didn't you think I looked strange?
Strange?
I'm quite older than
most Soul Reapers.
What?!
In other words,
I did things to myself as well…
in order to wait for
the Bounts to come…
Sorry, but I'm going to rest
for about half a day…
Half a day?!
That's right…
Wait! I still have things to ask you…
When I recover. Until then…
It looks like she fell asleep…
Jeez. I was still talking…
She says she's a lot older
than she looks.
It can't be helped…
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to go back
to Kukaku's home?
No, we still have things to ask her
when she wakes up.
We're going to rest here, too.
That sounds like the best thing to do.
How was Byakuya Kuchiki?
Not bad… I think fighting him made
for a good declaration.
Was that your true goal?
You've been inquiring
too much lately, Koga…
That's probably because
I'm in high spirits.
Ichinose!
Yes!
Where are the other three?
They are watching the movements
of Seireitei as planned.
I see… It's almost time.
Yes.
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
It sure is great that Rukia has
such a cool older brother.
He's reserved, calm, refined,
and incredibly wonderful.
You mean he's inarticulate,
insensitive, and arrogant.
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
I told you that you're in the way.
I thought that you went home…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
A souvenir?
Yes.
I heard that you regretted
there weren't any combs
that were right for you.
So when I went to
the World of the Living…
Oh?
It looks quite different
from a regular comb…
Oh?
Yes… This is quite a rarity…
I'm glad he's happy…
PET SHOP
Orihime Inoue knows good stores…
HOW RUDE OF YOU TO ASK MY AGE!