Shimura Ken
Father, it's been a while.
Father, I have something
to tell you today.
I think it's time to begin.
I will become the character
I was created to be.
It's time to restore the Kodokan
Dojo you left us, Father.
Sorry to make you wait 260 episodes.
It's not that I forgot my character.
And I wasn't tired of the role.
I had to save up money first.
I promise to make the dojo better
than when you were still around.
Please support me.
Oh?
Are you Otae-chan?
The Sound of a Beam
Can Pierce Every Heart
Kodokan Dojo
What?! You want to
recruit new students?!
S-Sis, I thought you forgot the
original purpose of your character!
Weren't you going to
focus on your night dojo?
Please, do I really look like
such a heartless woman?
Do your best and let
nature take its course.
I went to Tsudaya the other day,
and I received a signal
that it was time.
It's because you rewatched volume 2
of the DVDs and remembered!
I acquired a fair amount
of money in episode 200,
so I think now is the ideal time.
What are you babbling about?
Nobody's gonna pay money to learn
how to use a sword these days.
The age of using swords has ended.
It's now the age of much
younger wives using Kato-chan.
When did we start talking
about Kato-chan and Ken-chan?!
Kids don't dream about becoming
samurai or ninja anymore.
They want to become
Kato-chan's wife or part of
a backup band working up
to becoming an idol.
My Future Dream:
Backup Band
We don't live in an age
of evil conspiracies!
That's why this dojo is needed.
A part of ancient Japanese
culture is fading away.
It's our duty to protect it by passing
this knowledge to the next generation.
But do you even know what
a kendo glove smells like?
Those things should get a new job
as the straw used to wrap natto.
And in anime, the mask makes it
impossible to tell who it is.
And when people thrust,
you'd think they were striking to kill.
Isn't it our duty to end that
practice with our generation?
Are you really a swordsman?
It's true that there are aspects
that no longer apply,
so I believe it's important to evolve
and adapt certain practices
while maintaining the tradition.
The school of Tendo Mushin
needs a slight renewal.
Renewal?
Yes.
To the school of Tendo
Mushin beam sabers!
Tendo Mushin Beam Sabers
What happened to tradition?!
But beam sabers will resonate with
kids, and maybe with the Amanto.
Uh, that's not the issue here.
And who's going to teach
them how to use beam sabers?
That's all worked out already.
Huh?
I've found the perfect person.
He knows the School of Tendo Mushin
and he can use beam sabers.
Huh?
You'll be so surprised, Shin-chan.
Hey, long time no see.
You've gotten pretty big, Shin-bo!
Ha—
Hajime-nii!
Whoa!
You've gotten pretty strong, too!
Hajime-nii, you're alive!
That's great! Just great!
Huh? A former instructor?
Yes, this was back when
our dojo was busy.
The name's Obi Hajime!
Obi Hajime
If that's a pain to say, call me Obi-one!
Obi-one
No, that would be an even bigger pain.
Sounds like you've been
taking care of Otae-chan
and Shin-bo while I was gone.
Let me express my gratitude.
Thank you very hamnida!
Thank you? Hamnida? So
which country are you from?
Obi-one-niisama has been wandering
around space for a long time,
so he's picked up some words
from different planets.
Soz for being so hard to understand!
Uh, how do you pick up a
word like "soz" from space?
Gin-san, Hajime-nii is really amazing.
He became an instructor at
our dojo at a young age,
and his skill was known around Edo!
Once his talent was recognized,
he was chosen to study abroad
and took off into space.
But the teleportation device at the terminal
exploded while he was there,
so we thought he would never return.
When the device blew up,
I was miraculously teleported
to a planet way out there.
While there, I figured I might as
well learn how they used swords,
but before I knew it, I was
the strongest one around.
I would then move on to the
next planet, and so on,
until people started calling
me Galaxy Sword Master.
Galaxy Sword Master
People stopped challenging me.
It got boring, so I came back to Edo.
Wow! Galaxy Sword Master!
You're awesome, Hajime-nii!
Nah, I'm still nothing
compared to your old man.
Hey, what's a Galaxy Sword Master?
His character is dumb
and his title is dumb.
He was one strong samurai.
I never thought the
dojo would shut down.
Shin-bo, Otae-chan...
Soz for not being here to
help when you needed me.
If I can help you with the beam saber
that I mastered out in space,
I'll do whatever you ask!
I'm getting excited!
Watch it!
Let's work together to
revive your old man's dojo!
And we'll make Kodokan the number
one dojo in the universe!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Weren't we reviving it?
Hey, hey! Come on
down! Have a looksee!
School of Tendo Mushin Beam Saber
We're starting up a new school in Edo!
The School of Tendo Mushin Beam Saber!
We're moving into the age of beams!
You can do anything with beams!
Remove the wrinkles and
moles from your face!
Pierce the heart of your favorite girl!
Let's beam it up together!
Uh, so why are we
beaming it up with you?
This is bad, Gintoki-dono!
Nobody's stopping!
Uh, why are you telling me this?
How 'bout it? Let's spar
a little to show them
what beam sabers are about!
Wait, I've never used a beam
saber before and I don't want to.
How can you say that when you're
going to be a founder of
the School of Beam Saber?
What?
Don't play dumb. You and Otae-chan
have this going on, right?
What's that supposed to mean?
I've never seen that gesture before!
And this guy's shooting
beams out of his pinky?!
You know what I mean.
You've been sticking your
beam inside Otae-chan's...
Please stop it, Obi-one-niisama.
We have no such relationship.
That's the Otae-chan I remember.
You've already mastered
the art of the beam saber.
You mean she's mastered
how to jam it in your ass!
No kidding. You're the one who
doesn't understand, Hajime-nii.
Sis wouldn't want to
hear her first love say...
Wait, so he's her first love?
He's her first love?
Seriously? That's what
the boss lady likes?
Keep your mouth shut!
Want me to slaughter you?!
Uh, excuse me.
We want to join
the School of Beam Saber!
As if we wanted these freaks!
If it's that awesome, Kyubei-kun,
I'd love to try this, uh...
What was it called,
Kondo-kun? Beachy Diarrhea?
No, that's not it.
Wasn't it Beach Sandal, Kyubei-kun?
Wait, when did they become friends?!
The stalkers have teamed up
because her first love is here!
But before we join, we'll
need a demonstration
to see how awesome this really is.
That's right.
Would you be willing
to spar with us first?
Sure, I'd love to do that.
I can't wait!
It's been years since
I fought a samurai!
They're not fighting like samurai!
Die!
Way to blurt out your intent!
That's no good, you two.
If you fire those in the middle
of town, people will die.
Huh? What about me?
I'm just fine.
Though, I'm only half human now.
Kenofi, Kenofi, come in, come in!
No good. He's not responding.
He's running solo again.
That guy is so much trouble.
Forget about him.
I believe that this
planet is his homeland.
Let the man say his farewells.
Whew, we managed to recruit enough
students to get started.
Welcome New Students
Tendo Mushin Beam Saber
Welcome to the School of
Tendo Mushin Beam Saber!
Soz about what happened back there.
You guys were so strong that
I couldn't hold myself back.
But this means that we have
the seven strongest samurai
to get this school started off.
We're going to make the School
of Beam Saber the best there is!
Right, Instructor Sakata?
Sure, Instructor Obi-one.
I can't even be bothered
to complain anymore.
Anyway, tonight we celebrate
our new beginning!
Do you want beer, Hajime-nii?
Nah, give me some shochu with gasoline!
Please, Obi-one-niisama.
You're such a joker.
Uh, excuse me, Instructor Obi-one.
I have a question.
What's up?
I now understand how
amazing beam sabers are.
The thing is...
Even if we train under
the School of Beam Saber,
I don't see how we can learn to do that.
Don't worry.
It's easy once you've learned the trick.
Right, Instructor Sakata?
Sure, you know how
one day, you take the
training wheels off your bike,
and suddenly you can ride it?
It's just like that.
Wait, I'm positive that you can't
do that stuff, Instructor Sakata!
You still need your training wheels!
Honestly, I don't see how a
human could ever pull that off.
And that mechanical arm...
You said that you were only half human.
What did you mean by that?
You think there's something
special about this arm?
This is just a mechanical arm to
replace the one I lost in the accident.
That's not nice, Kyubei.
You shouldn't start accusing
people because they beat you.
It takes strength to
admit your weaknesses.
Now you have to write the word "jobber"
a hundred times before tomorrow.
And you have to write the
word "moron" a hundred times.
How do you spell that?
Like this, Instructor!
Gintoki
If you don't trust me,
I'll show you my body.
I meant exactly what I said back there.
After wandering around the galaxy,
half my body is no longer
that of an Earthling.
The other half hasn't
forgotten the spirit of Edo.
What do you think?
Don't you mean you're
half Edo and half robot?!
That's what I said.
The beam saber didn't
come from my right arm.
It came from the mechanical
right side of my body.
What the hell?!
Huh?!
What's going on?!
What happened to your body, Hajime-nii?!
O-Obi-one-niisama...
What? You didn't realize
that I was a cyborg?
Man, you guys don't pay attention!
Right, Instructor Sakata?
Huh? What?
Gintoki  Gintoki  Gintoki
Gintoki  Gin
We're having hamburger
steak tomorrow. Really?
Cyborg! This guy's piss drunk!
You're a cyborg, Hajime-nii?
Yeah. You see, when I was
caught in the explosion,
the right half of my body
was mortally damaged.
I'm embarrassed to admit that, well...
I already died once.
Wh-What?!
We'll make him half that.
Y-You already died once?!
And half this.
Th-That means...
Luckily, the technology on the
planet was advanced enough
that they could revive me
by mechanizing half my body.
I would become the strongest
swordsman in the galaxy.
I returned from hell to achieve the
dream that had once... died...
Hajime-nii!
Hey! Did he go back to hell already?!
Pull it together!
What's wrong?!
Give me shochu with gasoline!
Oh, no, I thought he was joking.
I'll go buy some gasoline, so Shin-chan,
take him to the bedroom!
S-Sis!
Otae-san!
Gengai-san, how does he look?
Unfortunately, the problem
isn't that he's out of gasoline.
Who fed him this junk?
This matter doesn't exist on Earth.
As far as I know, nothing like this has
been discovered in the universe yet.
That's boss lady's...
He must have eaten something
bad out in space.
Obi-one-niisama is such a slob.
Whatever. I got him to spit up the junk,
so give him some shochu with gasoline.
That's the only thing his body can take.
U-Uh, Gengai-san!
Is Hajime-nii...
His human heart has stopped beating.
All life-sustaining operations are
performed by the right side of his body.
In other words, the machine
is keeping him alive.
I thought he was finally back.
This is terrible.
He can't live without
that machine... That's just...
Shin-chan...
No matter how much he changes,
he'll still be the same person.
And you can't let him see
that look on your face.
Have you forgotten the promise we made?
Geez, how many times
do I have to tell you?!
Whether you're swinging your
sword or doing anything else,
you must maintain your form!
Pretend that there's a rod
sticking through your body,
and you can only move by
rotating around that rod!
I don't understand, Sis!
There's no rod in my body!
Geez, I told you to stop crying!
You're the son of a samurai, Shin-chan!
But...
Don't make excuses!
Those kids are at it again.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Crap, it's the master!
Father!
Help me talk some sense into him.
All Shin-chan does is cry,
and he won't stop.
And everybody's laughing
at how loud we are.
It's embarrassing.
Both of you are too loud!
You siblings cry all the time.
Why's that? Are you getting paid?
I'll pay you more, then, so laugh!
Ha—
Hajime-nii...
Listen up, you two.
Tears are handy for washing away
troubling and sad feelings.
But when you grow up, you'll learn
that there are things so sad, they
can never be washed away by tears.
That there are painful memories
that should never be washed away.
So people who are truly strong
laugh when they want to cry.
They endure all of the pain and sorrow
while laughing with everybody else.
You can cry all you want right now.
But one day, you must become
samurai strong enough not to cry.
Oh, so that's why you're
always laughing.
I-I want to become strong like you!
Really?
Then stop practicing the sword for
today, and start practicing laughing!
More, Otae-chan!
Not good enough, Shin-bo!
Like this!
All three of you are too loud!
Darn, crying won't make
this pain go away.
No matter what's happened to him,
we were able to see
Obi-one-niisama again.
We were able to see his smile again.
Isn't that
enough?
Sis...
Where did you go?
We've got trouble right now.
Earth may come to an end.
Oh, I don't see a problem
since my life's already over.
My love has come to an end,
so everyone else's lives might as well end.
He clearly wants attention right now.
I sure as hell don't want
to listen to him gripe.
It'll just be a waste of time, so let's
tell him what's up and get to work.
Lady!
Hey! Where have you been?!
Edo is in big trouble!
We've got big trouble here, too!
I'm disgusted with myself.
I was trying to kill someone
that Tae-chan truly cared about.
I'm tainted! I'm the one
who deserves to be killed!
Calm down, Lady!
Turn on the TV first!
The human race is about
to be killed off!
Don't touch me!
Oh, she noticed.
Machine Hall
Did you call me out here because
there's some kind of problem?
Actually, I noticed something
when I was checking his body.
I couldn't do anything
about it, so I ignored it.
Planet Beam?
They're known for developing
interstellar wave beam cannons.
Basically, no other planet
could compete with them
at making beam cannons,
but a few days ago,
Earth started a proposal to
ban the manufacturing and
exporting of beam cannons
because of the danger,
and the proposal seems likely to pass.
Those guys see that as a
big thorn in their side.
These people claim to be terrorists,
but I'm guessing that...
It appears that you Earthlings do not
understand how beneficial
lasers can be in daily life.
So we've sent a wonderful
present to help you understand.
Huh? What did they just say?
The mechanical half of his
body contains a time-triggered
interstellar wave beam cannon.
Its targets are the
planets of the Alliance.
If the cannon is fired, the rest of
the galaxy will declare war on Earth.
To Be Continued
Big Announcement
We have a big announcement
about the second movie.
Gintama the Movie ----
In theaters on ----- !!
Next week, the scratched-out
areas will be revealed.
Hey, dads. Don't try to
spread butter on the screen.
That's not what this is for.
Two Brothers
Next time: Two Brothers.
Planet Beam is threatening Planet Earth,
and Obi Hajime was their advance party!!
The Shimura siblings are
unsure about what to do,
but Gintoki has made his choice.