Aizen had snatched away
Orihime Inoue to Hueco Mundo.
It was believed that Aizen was
going to awaken the Hogyoku
using Orihime's ability
to reject phenomenon.
The Soul Society
responded to this
by dispatching captains of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
However, Orihime had only been
brought there to lure the captains.
Aizen's true objectives
were to create the Ouken
by wiping out the Enriched
Spirit Zone of Karakura Town,
and to take over
the Soul Society by force.
Aizen sealed off the Garganta,
the opening that
led to Hueco Mundo,
trapping Ichigo and
the others there.
He then took Gin and Tosen with him
to invade Karakura Town.
Genryusai, however,
saw through his intentions,
and ordered Urahara
to make the captains
capable of fighting
in Karakura Town.
Urahara built a device
called a Tenkaiketchu
that would act as
a huge Senkaimon,
and used it to swap
the real Karakura Town
with a town replica
built in the Soul Society.
It seems we made it in time.
Made it in time?
Now why would you say that?
I'm well aware that what lies there
is not Karakura Town.
But that means nothing to me.
If Karakura Town is
in the Soul Society,
we'll just kill you here
and create the Ouken
in the Soul Society.
That's all there is to it.
Until then…
I will leave Las Noches to you…
Ulquiorra.
Yes, sir.
My job…
is to protect my friends.
KAGAMINO CITY
(22 KM EAST OF KARAKURA TOWN)
12:13 p.m.
Are you all right, young lady?
Oh boy, looks like
the Spiritual Pressure got them.
Man, I'm telling you, that's some
insane Spiritual Pressure.
If we don't get
the heck out of here,
we could end up like them.
Umm… Your panties are showing,
young lady.
Who are you, mister?
Huh? Me?
Yeah.
My name is Eikichiro Saido.
I'm just a petty
Soul Reaper who was
recently put in charge
of this district.
So you're a petty person?
Ouch!
That's okay.
Listen, if you stay here,
you'll end up dead,
like those monsters.
Get away now while you can.
Okay.
Oh boy.
Looks like it's going to begin.
Well let's see how this contest
turns out, good or bad.
AT THE SAME TIME
70 METERS ABOVE
KARAKURA TOWN
His Spiritual Pressure
is monstrous,
just the way
I remember it!
If it scares you,
you can run away.
Coward.
Should we go after
the leader first?
No, Aizen's powers
are very special.
In order to concentrate
our attacks on him,
we should defeat
those around him first.
Who do you suppose is the strongest
among those three Espada?
That's hard to say.
We'd have to ask Aizen.
The problem is that while
we're fighting the Espada,
there's no guarantee that Aizen
and his men won't interfere.
You're right.
Stand back, everyone.
Render all things in
the universe to ashes.
Ryujinjakka.
Get down, Ukitake!
I know!
Jokakuenjo.
Aizen and the others
won't be able to
get past this wall of flames
for a while.
Now then,
shall we crush them?
The Head Captain's
pretty drastic, isn't he?
Just goes to show how
upset Old Man Yama is.
Aizen.
Jeez… That's hot, hot.
Head Captain sure went overboard.
What'll we do now, Captain Aizen?
With all this,
we won't be able to join in.
We'll do nothing.
It just means that
this battle will end without the
need for us to get our hands dirty.
That is all.
AT THE SAME TIME
LAS NOCHES TOWER 5
Are you afraid?
Lord Aizen has considered you
unnecessary.
There is nothing to
protect you anymore.
It's over.
You will die here, all alone,
with no contact with anyone.
I'm asking if you are afraid?
I am not afraid.
Because everyone
came to rescue me.
My heart is…
with theirs.
Such nonsense.
You say you are not afraid because
your friends came for you?
Do you really mean those words?
Yes.
Getsugatensho!
When I first heard that
they came to rescue me,
it made me a little glad.
And awfully sad.
I came here because
I wanted to protect all of them.
Why did they all come here?
Why couldn't I make
them understand?
I wondered.
But when I sensed that
Kuchiki had fallen,
and when I saw Kurosaki
fight in front of me,
I felt like all of that
didn't matter.
All that mattered was I didn't want
Kurosaki to get hurt.
I wanted everyone to be safe.
When I felt that way,
I realized,
that must've been
how all of them felt.
If someone in that group
had disappeared like I did,
I would surely do
the same thing they did.
I take it you are the intruder,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I am Rudobon,
captain of the Exequias.
I have come for your life.
I said I will have your life.
You will stop here.
Sorry, but I don't have time
to deal with the likes of you.
That's just fine.
I, too, have no time to
waste on you alone!
Damn! How many are there?!
Coming at you one more time!
Renji!
El Directo!
Chad!
You fools.
Letting a minor unexpected turn of
events easily get the best of you.
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Rukia!
Idiot!
Save the reunion for later!
Go quickly, Ichigo!
Gotcha.
Jeez… He's so high maintenance.
Do you think you can defeat me
with that level of strength?
You, too,
are nothing more than a minor
unexpected turn of events.
This is absurd.
Your fate and that of your friends
is already set.
Even if your friends come,
it won't overturn the fact
that all of you will die.
Sharing feelings with those
who are about to die,
that is how you humans
comfort yourselves.
It is one of your instincts
to help you
escape from fear
and hopelessness.
Sharing feelings doesn't
exist in the real word.
It is nothing more
than a meaningless illusion
you humans have.
You may be right.
Perhaps it is impossible to feel
exactly the same emotions.
But by cherishing each other,
our hearts can be that much closer.
Don't die!
Don't die, Kurosaki!
You don't have to win.
You don't have to try.
Just don't get hurt anymore.
That's what it must mean to
"be of one heart."
Heart, you say?
You humans use
that word so casually,
as though it's in
the palm of your hands.
My eyes see everything.
There is nothing they do not see.
If they do not see it,
it does not exist.
I have fought until now,
convinced of that.
What is "heart"?
If I rip open your chest,
will I see it inside?
If I split your skull,
Roar, Zabimaru!
El Directo!
Hakuren!
Aren't you guys overdoing it a bit?
We haven't appeared in a while!
We have to show all we can,
or we'll lose out!
Now I feel sorry for the Exequias.
The Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
Hey!
What're you doing?!
It's not my fault!
The closet is too small!
For crying out loud,
what do you have packed in here?!
What are these?!
They are the Gigai
I'm keeping for everyone!
Substitute Soul Reapers cannot
refuse a request for a favor.