Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
I knew it! You don't even know
your Zanpaku-to’s name.
And you think you can fight me
as an equal?
Well, it's 2000 years too soon!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Look in front of you!
What stands before you is…
your prey!
It's all over, punk!
You will lose to Renji Abarai,
and die on this spot!
BLEACH 17
Sorry, kid.
But that's what's known as
a difference in strength.
The Zanpaku-to changes
in size and shape
depending on its wielder's
spiritual energy.
And this is the manifestation
of my spiritual energy!
Well kid, I think it's about
time I got going.
I don't like the air here.
One attack will show him
the difference in strength,
make him realize that
he has no chance,
and back down while his wound
is not serious.
That was my hope.
But Ichigo would never give up
because of such a reason.
I knew that.
Are you ready?
Can you still move, Ichigo? Then run!
Please, hurry!
No answer?
Run!
What are you doing, Rukia?!
Hey! Let go!
Are you trying to deepen your guilt?!
Let go, you fool!
Run, Ichigo!
Stand! Stand and run!
Ichigo!
What? You still have
the strength to move?
Fine. I was just thinking that
it's no fun
to finish off someone who
can't move anymore.
Well then, fight hard and die!
Ichigo, if you can stand,
get away! Run, Ichigo!
Ichi--?!
What's the matter?
If you won't attack, I will!
What is this sudden increase
in his Spiritual Pressure!
What the hell…?!
What's with this kid?!
He was about to die earlier!
Where'd he get all this power?
What's wrong?
Your moves have slowed
down considerably.
Idiot! You just got faster!
I don't understand this,
but it feels good.
I don't even feel
the pain from the wound!
And I don't feel like I can lose!
Why you--!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Renji is being pressured! Ichigo?
You're good at dodging around!
What's happening?!
How much higher can
his spiritual energy go?!
But that's about to end.
Heavy…
I won't make it in time…
W-What the--?!
My Zanpaku-to…
No… he didn't do anything.
Was it him?
Impossible…
He can't do a thing from
that distance.
Huh?!
Is he coming?
What happened just now?
Did he get me?
I can't even tell if
I was hit from the back…
or the front.
It hurts…
You're slow.
Even when you fall.
Brother Byakuya!
It's been awhile since I saw it,
but he's awesome, after all.
I had to strain to follow
his second attack.
But his first one…
I couldn't even tell
when he drew his sword,
or put it back.
If I couldn't see it coming…
He probably doesn't even
know what happened to him.
Still…
What was that extraordinary
Spiritual Pressure he demonstrated earlier?
What's the matter, Renji?
No… You didn't need to help me
with a kid of this level, Captain.
Don't say that.
If all I did was watch each time…
I'd get rusty.
No, this man is… And I am…
Ichigo!
Stop!
Let go, Renji! Ichigo is…
What are you saying, fool?!
Look hard!
The kid is dead!
Don't you understand?!
By just touching him, your sentence
will increase by 20 years!
Why would you multiply
your crimes for a dead person?!
I'm the one
who got Ichigo involved in this.
It's my fault he's dead!
So what's wrong with
my coming to him?!
So even if it would make
your sentence harsher,
you can't stay away...
from this kid?
Brother…
I understand, Rukia.
This kid…looks a lot…
like him.
I understand, Rukia.
This kid…looks a lot like him.
"He's dead," you say?
"Looks a lot like him"?
Quit talking about me
like I'm not here!
Ichi--!
Let go.
I can't hear you.
Look at me when you speak!
This kid can still move?! No way!
I see… You don't need that arm, huh?
Huh?!
W-What're you doing, Rukia?!
You're just a human…
You're just a human!
How dare you grab
my brother like that?!
Know your place, kid!
Let us go, Brother!
Through his actions just now…
I, Rukia Kuchiki, have opened my eyes.
Please take me back to
the Soul Society.
I will atone for my sins.
Wait you…!
What're you saying?!
Rukia, you…!
You don't know when
to give up, do you?
Quit squirming around and die!
There is no need to inflict
the final blow upon him.
Leave him and
he will eventually die on his own.
Let us go, Brother.
Wait, Rukia!
What kind of joke is this?!
Look at me, hey!
Hey!
Do not move!
Take even one step from there…
Try to come after me...
And I'll…I'll…
I will never forgive you!
You will die anyway…
so stay there and live,
even if just one second longer.
Fine. I will not inflict the finishing blow.
With the two attacks just now,
I've shattered his Soul Chain
and Hakusui - Soul Sleep,
the vital spots of the soul.
He should die in less than an hour.
And even if he does survive,
his powers will be lost,
Soul Reaper power, as well
as his spiritual energy.
Renji...
Yes.
Open!
I can't speak…
I can't move…
I was protected…again…
Rukia!
It hurts. My body feels heavy.
It's cold.
It doesn't hurt.
Oh no, am I about to die?
I probably don't feel pain
because I'm on the verge of death.
That's right… my body was so cold earlier,
but I'm feeling warmth now.
It's warm.
Oh, good reaction! That's good.
Y-You're too close!
Boss! Kurosaki is awake!
Boss!
I've seen you before!
You're Hat-and Clogs’ friend!
Why are you under
the covers with me?!
Get off!
Huh?!
Huh? I'm not dead?! Why?
And this isn't my house.
Where am I?
Now, now. You mustn't be up, Kurosaki.
Your wounds haven't closed yet.
You'll die if you move around too much.
Hat-and-Clogs?
I see. So this is your house.
Correct!
So you saved me?
Huh? That tone is unexpected.
It sounds as though
you didn't want me to rescue you.
Oh yeah… Ishida was there, too.
What happened to him?
Is he here, too?
No, he went home.
He lost a lot of blood,
but his wounds weren't too serious.
Even if he lay there like that,
he wouldn't have died
for a couple of days.
So I was able to treat
most of his wounds there.
He was worried about you
when he left.
Ishida? No way!
I asked him to rest here awhile…
Thank you very much.
But I'm all right.
But rather…
please take care of Kurosaki.
If there's anyone who can defeat
those guys right now, it's not me.
The only one who can save Rukia…
...is "him." So he said.
Only me?
What does he expect me to do?
Rukia has gone back
to the Soul Society!
How do I go after her?!
How do I save her?!
No way can I do that…
No way!
Do you really believe that?
There's a way to get to the Soul Society…
Is there a way?
How? How do I get there?!
Tell me!
Of course, I'll tell you.
But there's one condition.
Condition?
Yes. For the next ten days,
study how to fight with me.
S-Study?! What?
You want me to train?
I don't have time!
Rukia may be executed
over there at any time!
We have to get to
the Soul Society and…!
You just don't get it, do you?
Huh?!
What I mean is,
if you go there now, you will die.
Can you beat them?
If you fought with them now?
This time, I let you try
and fight them.
That's because I figured you would
understand that better than words.
With your level of strength now,
you won't be of any good
in the Soul Society.
You are weak.
A weak person entering the enemy's den…
that's called suicide.
You want to save Rukia?
Don't make me laugh.
Don't use others as a reason
for walking straight into death's arms.
The Soul Society usually
has a one-month waiting period
before an execution.
This holds true in Rukia's case, too.
Execution?
It's different from the way
humans are executed, though.
I have ten days to bully you.
Then seven days to open
the gate to Soul Society.
And 13 days after we arrive
in Soul Society.
We will have lots of time.
Can I become stronger in ten days?
Certainly! That is if you truly wish to
save Rukia from the bottom of your heart.
Your feelings are stronger than steel.
Abandon any doubt you have.
Ten days. Can you play a game
of life and death with me?
Of course!
I felt as though…the rain stopped.
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
Renji Abarai shows you the
"Proper way to use the Zanpaku-to"!
First, you call out the name of
your Zanpaku-to to release its power!
Then you slash and swing!
Slash, and slash, and slash, and slash!
Cripes! That’s not explaining anything!
Do the preview!