Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
It's no good.
I can't sense any
Spiritual Pressure.
DEPARTMENT OF RESEARCH
AND DEVELOPMENT
W-What's the meaning of this,
Captain Kurotsuchi?!
Nothing really.
I'm just going to use this sample
to figure out what caused
the Zanpakuto rebellion.
Nemu.
Yes, sir.
Shall we begin?
W-W-Wait a second!
If you cut him open,
what'll happen to my Zanpakuto?!
I don't know.
We're testing that right now.
Now then…
Hey, stop! Seriously, stop!
What is it?
Even if he is a sample,
he's the only Zanpakuto
we've captured at the moment!
Shouldn't we treat him
a little better?
You sure are noisy.
I guess we have no choice.
Nemu.
Yes,
Master Mayuri.
Why me?!
What was that, "tsk," just now?!
How can you stab at me
with such lack of emotion?!
And I'm not the one you
should be cutting open!
You should be doing that
to my Zanpakuto!
YOU BASTARD!
WEREN'T YOU TRYING TO SAVE ME?!
Shut up!
It's better than getting
cut open myself!
Oh?
You can share your thoughts
with your Zanpakuto
even if its mouth is covered.
The connection
between a Soul Reaper
and his manifested Zanpakuto
is very interesting.
R-Right?!
Soul Reapers and Zanpakuto!
Such a relationship
isn't easy to understand.
It would be such a waste
to experiment on us!
That's not true.
Huh?
He's dead.
What is this?!
What are you saying?!
What are you going to do
about my Zanpakuto?!
According to my report,
when a Zanpakuto is killed by
its owner, they go back to normal.
That's right.
But it appears that
is not the case
when someone other than
its owner kills them.
Huh?! You're ignoring me?!
I'm the owner,
but you're ignoring me?!
Please be quiet in the lab.
Be quiet?
You seem to be after my life!
Be quiet.
Stop that! Whoa!
– Be quiet.
– That's dangerous! Hey!
Good grief…
This is interesting,
but it looks like I'm going to
have a lot of bothersome work.
Hey! Let us out of here!
Are you listening?!
You're really wicked women!
How could you lock up
your Zanpakuto in here?!
Yeah, what she said!
Don't you care about
your Zanpakuto?!
They're really noisy even
after we catch them…
Say something!
– Please take them to
– Hey, quit pushing, will you?!
– Squad Four's barracks.
– I can't help it, okay?!
– Yes, ma'am.
– It's because you're fat!
– We will take the responsibility
– What?!
– to transport them there.
– I'm glamourous!
What?!
You're going to leave us
to other people?
Where are you going?!
You monsters!
– You old ladies! You old maids!
– You sadists!
I'm not listening,
I'm not listening.
Rangiku.
Yeah. We shouldn't be
wasting time here.
Let's go.
Okay.
Rangiku…
Hitsugaya… I mean,
Captain Hitsugaya…
Yeah. I know.
I can't sense my captain's
Spiritual Pressure.
I don't think he was killed, but…
Let's hurry!
Okay!
Huh?
That surprised me.
Are you all right?
I'm all right!
That didn't hurt at all.
I'm not all right! Underneath you!
Oh, Ichigo.
Is that where you were?
That explains why it didn't hurt.
Just get off of me! You're heavy!
Hey!
That's a rude way to treat a lady!
Toshiro?
Yes. Is my captain all right?
Don't worry.
My master hit me with everything
he had and restored my memory.
Let him rest for a while.
Honestly…
My captain sure is hopeless.
But Hitsugaya must
be quite relieved.
It still has not accustomed
to my body…
Hey… So we meet again.
I knew you'd come,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I think we might be
connected by a deep bond.
A deep bond?
That's right.
Your power will be useful
in achieving my goal.
You know, don't you?
Your excess power doesn't
have anywhere to go.
No, I don't know.
I only know one thing.
That I will defeat you.
That is our bond.
How foolish.
This technique…!
Is he trying to take control
of Zangetsu again?!
Do not be afraid!
His voice is not mind control,
but suggestion.
It works on our subconscious,
but now that I know his voice,
his suggestions won't work on me!
I guess this means you're
no longer afraid to face me.
What's wrong with him?!
Not only is he acting weird,
his Spiritual Pressure is unstable.
But you've forgotten one thing!
This again?!
W-What is this?!
I can't…move my body.
Damn it!
It's useless!
What?!
What's going on?!
Is this body not enough
to keep going?!
What?!
Y-You're…
A Zanpakuto?!
It looks like it.
Whose Zanpakuto are you?!
You don't want to
answer me, huh?
Even if I don't,
you'll figure it out right away.
Scatter…
This Spiritual Pressure!
Th-This is…
Scatter…
Byakuya's?!
Bakudo 39! Enkosen!
No!
I haven't forgotten this power!
Byakuya's Zanpakuto,
Senbonzakura…
I see you remember,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What is this feeling?
Yeah… There was a sudden
rise in Spiritual Pressure…
I felt this before…
Could this be…
Yeah, it's Squad Six's captain.
H-Hey!
Oh, excuse us!
What?
What's going on?!
Why are you doing this?
Stand back.
I get it.
You have the same
Spiritual Pressure as Byakuya.
You're the one who
attacked me last night.
You don't want to answer me?
Oh well… In that case…
Above…
Do you think that's
enough to hit me?!
Of course not!
Not good enough!
This brings back memories…
…of my fight with Byakuya!
Getsugatensho!
He's coming!
You're pretty good! In that case…
Gokei Senbonzakura Kageyoshi!
What?!
Kageyoshi has a billion blades…
They surround the enemy in a sphere
and cut in every direction.
This is the first time you've
dealt with this, isn't it?
I got him.
Ichigo!
Impressive, Ichigo Kurosaki…
You can still stand
after that attack.
If I don't kill him, he'll kill me!
But is that all right?!
No, I've got to do it!
Sorry, Byakuya!
If I defeat your Zanpakuto,
forgive me!
Why are you hesitating?
If you're not going to
come at me, I'll go to you!
I'm not hesitating.
Senkei Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Getsugatensho!
In the small instant you hesitated,
my Spiritual Pressure won out.
I wonder about that.
What?!
Sorry, Senbonzakura.
I don't know how things
would have turned out
if you were with Byakuya,
but you can't
defeat me by yourself!
Fine! You have humiliated me!
I shall make you regret that!
You just don't get it!
You're the one who
doesn't get it!
That's enough.
Byakuya!
Captain Kuchiki!
Captain Kuchiki had gone missing.
Why is he here?
Sorry, Byakuya…
I'm fighting your Zanpakuto.
Step aside, Kurosaki.
Are you going to fight him?
It's probably appropriate
if you fight him, but…
That's not what I meant.
What?
Hado 33, Sokatsui!
W-Why?!
Captain Kuchiki?!
What's going on?!
Hey, Byakuya!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I cannot let you kill this man.
What?
Why?
Why are you taking
Muramasa's side?
Don't tell me you surrendered
to that Zanpakuto?!
Surrender?
I would never surrender
to a Zanpakuto.
This is my own decision.
The Zanpakuto
followed their desires
and made their intentions known.
You and many
other Soul Reapers
witnessed the Zanpakuto
release themselves.
This is the same thing.
I am following my own desires.
This Soul Reaper says
interesting things.
Then let me ask you, Soul Reaper,
what are your desires?
What is your intent?
My desire…
I want to defend my pride.
That's all.
Kurosaki… Don't interfere
with Muramasa anymore.
Or else…
…you will die!
Byakuya!
Master Mayuri, Captain Kuchiki
has apparently betrayed us.
Now's our chance!
I've always wanted to
experiment on him.
Let's go catch him!
Get a basket,
a stick and some bread crumbs!
Don't you think a photograph of
Rukia Kuchiki would be effective?
It's perfect!
How so?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I never expected them
to be our masters.
Yeah…
I would have preferred them
to be handsome guys.
Not those old ladies.
"Ladies"?
Your Hinimari is also—
What are you doing?
She's not an old lady!
I won't allow you to call such
a wonderful person an old lady!
Huh?
Then why don't you
– just go back to her?
– Stupid, stupid, stupid!