Chains of a Warrior
We appreciate your cooperation.
It won't be long before the Jirocho gang and Lady Kada control the Kabuki district.
Nonsense.
You're merely using me to help your father take over the world.
I could say the same about you, Lady Kada.
As a result, the collar around my old man's neck has been released.
That old hag took away the flowers and freedom my father once had.
I'm sure that my old man will now...
Pay more attention to you?
I have a feeling that you're the one who can breathe easy now.
You must be overjoyed to know that the woman who stole your father from you is dead.
Man, this is why I hate women.
They're always so suspicious.
Anyway, I'll need you to take care of Saigo's kid.
Who knows when that sheman will betray us?
Pirako...
Jirocho doesn't see you.
You can eliminate every obstacle in the way.
You can spend your entire life serving him.
He will never turn to you...
Man...
Could you cut it out, Lady Kada?
If you don't shut your mouth, I'll have to make some flowers, you hag.
Greater Edo Hospital
Madame Catherine, you should get some rest.
You have been standing there for two days.
I do not require any rest.
Shall I take your place, Madame Catherine?
Kagura-chan, shouldn't you get some rest too?
I'm not skanky enough to go to sleep in someone else's house.
Besides...
What if I wake up to find out she's...
She'll be fine.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
You should go home and get some rest.
She would be upset if she learned that everyone was ruining their health.
You have no home to return to.
There's no place for you here.
Saigo-san!
That fool.
I kept telling her to escape...
Saigo-san...
Was that phone call...?
I'm not going to apologize.
There was nothing I could do.
And there's nothing I can do now.
The day after tomorrow...
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
Your place will be destroyed by the Four Devas.
The day after tomorrow.
You have until then to pack up and leave this town.
Wh-Why is this happening?!
Didn't you hear me?
There's no place for you here in this town.
The entire Kabuki district is against you.
Did they take your kid hostage?
Gin-san...
They appear to be testing me.
There are things I'll do anything to protect.
Saigo-san...
Pako, can you take care of them?
Don't worry.
I'm closing up shop.
The rest is up to you.
You bastard!
Otose-san was left for dead!
Her bar was destroyed!
And you're just gonna turn tail and run?!
You're telling me to fight?
Don't make me laugh.
I couldn't even take Jirocho one-on-one.
When did you become so pathetic?!
Damn you, Sakata!
If you're gonna leave, you can leave by yourself!
I won't! I won't...!
Do you know why Gran went by herself?
To protect us.
If you still insist on dying,
you're free to stay behind and get yourself killed.
Odd Jobs and Gran's bar are being closed down.
We're just strangers now.
Free to do as we please.
I'll be doing just that.
Wait!
Gin-san!
Sorry.
I doubt I can protect anything now...
Gin-san...
Master Gintoki...
Kabuki District 1st Street
Doesn't it feel like there aren't many people around these days?
Didn't you know?
There's a war brewing around these parts.
A war?
The factional rivalry between the Four Devas is heating up.
Everybody's too scared to come near this town.
Is it really that dangerous?
We've managed to survive everything that's come before.
This is no different.
Puppet House
But there are rumors that Otose's dead.
What?!
She got in a fight with Jirocho's gang.
And it sounds like Katsuo, one of their young leaders, also died.
But there's this rookie who's filling in for Katsuo.
I heard that she persuaded Kada and Saigo to help crush Otose-san.
I still owe her for lending me money when I was in debt.
I owe her for helping me out when I got in a fight with my wife.
Why don't you go protect Otose-san's bar then?
Don't be stupid. I'd be throwing my life away.
In this town, the wicked live longer than the kind.
Who knows when the three remaining Devas will turn on one another...
It's probably time to get out of this town.
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
The Kabuki District, a town which accepts the clean and unclean.
I was unable to predict that we would be chased out of this town.
Madame Otose loved this town of good and evil.
But now, we can never...
Why must we abandon Otose's bar? Our bar...
Don't say that.
If we die, Otose-san will have risked her life for nothing.
Otose-san will be moved out of the Kabuki district hospital tomorrow.
We'll be able to visit her every day.
Anyway, we'll have to stay away from the Kabuki district.
As long as we're alive, we can always start...
Start over...
S-Start...
Huh? That's strange...
Why am I crying?
Huh?
So you couldn't take on the Four Devas.
I didn't think our boss would actually attack Otose.
You probably thought you could calm things down by saving my life, but tough luck.
Nobody can stop this war.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't trying to save your life.
I just needed you to spill your guts.
Let's get those guts out of you.
What?! What do you wanna know?!
Why were you surprised that Jirocho attacked Gran?
You didn't know?
The boss and Otose have known each other since they were kids.
You could say they were childhood friends.
The boss was a pretty naughty kid,
but Otose was there to straighten him out every time he tried something.
Even after he got into organized crime,
Otose was the only one who stood by him and tried to straighten him out.
As a result, the boss became a vigilante who was popular enough to be considered a leader of the town.
Jirocho, man among men, would never have existed without Otose.
At the time, nobody could defeat the boss in a fight.
But, there was one man who managed to triumph over the boss once.
Tatsugoro Terada, a cop who was also a leader of the town
and Otose's husband.
A man who was strong in a fight and stuck to his ideals.
Everyone had to love him.
Cop and vigilante.
They got in a fight once because of their different positions,
but they both fought to protect their town.
It wasn't long before they became friends.
But there was one problem.
They were in love with the same woman.
The boss backed down because he wanted Otose to be happy,
since he figured a vigilante wouldn't be able to provide that happiness.
But Tatsugoro got himself killed, which left Otose alone.
And he died in the middle of a battle,
taking a bullet that was meant for the boss.
Doromizu Gang
When the boss returned from the war, his wife and daughter were waiting for him.
But the boss paid no attention to his daughter.
He was willing to do anything, no matter how underhanded it was, for the sake of business.
He said that he didn't have the right to be a father or a vigilante.
Who was it, what was it, that drove the boss to give up all he had to stay in this town?
Now that he's struck down the old lady, I'm not really sure.
That said, I'm one of them.
If it's for the boss who took me in, or his daughter,
I'm willing to have a hole in my gut.
That's my duty.
But was this really the right thing to do?
Will this really make them happy?
They're never gonna be happy...
...'cause I'm gonna crush them.
So you were putting on a show for the kids.
You don't stand a chance by yourself.
I can't go back on my word.
Joe Schmo, take care of Gran.
What?! Why?!
You always return the favor, seven for three.
Shouldn't you stay here to watch this old woman pass on?
Gintoki...
I don't want to see...
...you die.
Gran, I promise to pay off the rent.
So sit tight.
How did it feel to cut down the woman you loved?
How did it feel to manipulate a bunch of old men and women?
That's harsh.
I did it all for your sake.
Next, you'll have Saigo destroy Otose's bar.
What a waste of time...
Did that vixen put you up to it?
Of course not.
This is part of the plan.
There are many people left in this town who were involved with Otose.
We'll use this chance to flush them out.
Saigo happens to be one of them.
Will it really work?
And you don't need to worry. The old woman's buddies aren't in this town anymore.
The watchdog's chains have been snapped.
You intend to keep your promise to not harm anyone else?
It's no use.
That person was never chained.
You took him to be an obedient dog who could be chained?
I guarantee that Bro will come.
You were watching?
I was watching.
When you failed to finish off Otose too...
When you cut her down so she wouldn't be dragged into this war...
You don't need to worry.
I understand that there's no point in focusing on Otose.
It's not that simple to explain what it is that chains you to this town.
I figured it out.
You're just like him.
But I'm going to protect her in your stead.
Jirocho...
Take care of her... Take care of our town...
Both of you are chained to this town by the same thing.
A promise made to a certain man.
An iron vow of your own choosing.
The chains of a warrior.
Both of you are animals bound by the same chain.
But...
One has experienced loss, but accepted the responsibility and continues to protect this town.
The other has experienced loss,
but has abandoned the responsibility and chosen to protect this town by using force to conquer it.
Two beasts whose interests clash, despite sharing the same goal.
Now, who will be the last man standing over the Kabuki district?
Don't worry.
I've already made up my mind.
I'll be joining you on your rampage.
I promise to help you take over this town.
So once this is finished,
you'll come back to me, won't you?
You...
Where do you think you're going?
With Otose-san's mementos of her husband...
Why are you here?
You're the one who said we could do as we please.
Take us with you.
We can help you fight.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm just here because Gran told me to pick this up for her.
Enough already...
Neither of you get it...
If you shoulder the burden alone and leave us behind...
How are we supposed to be happy you saved our lives?
How are we supposed to be happy that Gran saved us if she's gone?
If you're gone, life won't be any fun!
Life doesn't need to be fun.
I just want you to live.
I don't want to go through that again.
I don't want anyone to die.
Aren't you supposed to be Gintoki Sakata?
The man who's let so much slip away, who's failed to protect so much...
...but swore that he would never run away from his responsibilities!
Didn't you promise her husband?!
Once you've decided to protect something, you'll protect it to the very end!
Isn't that what makes you Gintoki Sakata?!
So what if Otose-san's life was in danger?!
This isn't enough to kill Otose-san off!
Isn't enough to kill us off!
Isn't enough to kill you off!
Because you're going to protect us!
Because we're going to protect you!
Isn't that what Odd Jobs is about?
Isn't that how the three of us protected so much over the years?
We have not lost anything yet.
So you must not lose your soul.
Catherine-san, Tama-san...
Master Gintoki...
You have protected us many times.
No matter how dire or hopeless the situation was...
We trust you.
So it's your turn to trust us.
We can do this together.
We can protect Otose-san's home, our home.
Kabuki District 1st Street
Protect the town which brought us together.
Sorry, pops.
I bought these for you,
but there probably won't be any left over.
In return, I'll make another promise.
We promise to protect everything which was dear to you.
Thanks, pops,
for leading me to these assholes.
What's with that group of men or women or both or neither?
It's the Jirocho's gang and Saigo's people!
Th-There's gonna be a war!
Why is this happening?
Don't say anything.
Mama's the one who's hurting the most.
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
Let's get started then!
Make a lot of noise for Otose!
Wait, young lady!
The store banner is up!
Otose
H-How can this be?!
Th-This early in the morning?!
They work too hard!
You're missing the point!
Why is the store banner up when Otose and everyone else is...?
Could it be...
Y-You're...!
Sorry, but could you come back later?
The place is booked.
I feel like drinking by myself.
Without any interruptions.
What are you...?
Don't come any closer.
The hell are you talking about?!
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to keep your stinkin' pig feet out of this place.
Pako!
I knew you would come, Bro.
Eh?!
You're gonna take on the entire Kabuki District?!
The entire Kabuki District?
Don't make me laugh.
You fools aren't even part of this town.
You're no different from the dogshit on the side of the road.
All I need from the Kabuki District is right here.
Our Kabuki District...
...can be found...
...right here.
Crush us if you can.
We're not letting any of you into our town.
Pako!
Please stop this!
We don't want to fight you!
Funny.
It's very strange.
It makes me sick to have to fight friends.
Yet I felt relieved when I saw your face.
Of course.
It wouldn't be right if you weren't here.
What are you...?
Assmi, it would be rude to say anything.
That's right!
There's nothing left to say.
Bro and Saigo-san are both protecting what's dear to them.
You shouldn't be talking.
Not when you're the one who took what was dear to me.
I'm not going to apologize. After all...
I'm here to protect what's dear to me.
I'll steal and destroy what's dear to others...
...if that's what's needed to take him back.
I must pity you, daughter of Jirocho.
The swing of a samurai's blade can silence a thousand words!
Warriors,
let us hold our conversation in a whirlwind of blood!
The Otose Family will be paying our respects.
Let's go, bastards!
To Be Continued...
Next Episode: Iron Town