Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Captain!
Oh, what took you
so long, Nanao?
Took me so long, you say?!
Just what exactly
are you doing, sir?
Having a drink as I view
the plum blossoms.
Since it's still a little early for
the cherry blossoms to
come into full bloom.
I think these petals have
clouded your brain.
You can enjoy yourself after
we've slain the Sword Beasts.
Now let's go.
Nah, I'll pass.
Would you go in
my place, Nanao?
What're you saying?
I know.
Why not go with these two?
Don't be ridiculous.
Why should I leave a drinking party
to go and do back-breaking work?
If you want to take somebody,
take this one.
She seems to have
nothing better to do.
Yes! That's a good idea.
It's set, then.
Nanao, the two of you
take care of it, okay?
Huh? But…
I feel like he ordered me
to babysit her…
So, um…Katenkyokotsu…
That doesn't sound right
since there are two of them.
What should I call you?
Are you listening?
What?!
Nanao!
What's wrong?
Rangiku…
I'm sorry…
My…
What's this?
You have such a cute girl with you.
Is she Captain Kyoraku's
love child?
She's one of
Captain's Zanpakuto.
I know that.
Don't give me such a scary look.
Is he making you babysit her?
No, not really, but…
Captain Kyoraku ordered the two
of us to slay the Sword Beasts…
Huh?!
Hey! Just a minute!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
She'll be all right, won't she?
Yeah, of course.
After all, you and she are
both my Zanpakuto.
That's not what I meant.
I meant the lieutenant…
She'll be fine.
Nothing to worry about…
I hope so…
It was around here…
Damn…
Young girl…
Aren't you going to apply
the finishing blow?
It's as though she's
toying with him
without applying
the fatal strike…
This girl…
has she no emotions?!
Bakudo Number 4, Hainawa!
Slaying Sword Beasts
isn't a game!
If you won't apply
a finishing blow,
then I will end it!
Stop it!
Hado Number 4, Byakurai!
A falling out, eh?
How convenient!
Darn!
So that's what happened…
I'm very sorry.
Well, can't do anything about
the one that got away.
Besides, if that Sword Beast
is wounded—
it couldn't have gone far.
There's nothing to worry about.
But…
However.
What exactly are you
"very sorry" about?
Huh?
It's more than just about letting
the Sword Beast escape, isn't it?
Well, that's okay…
You can work alone,
or she can work alone—
do it any way you want.
If working together is impossible,
you don't have to work as a pair.
Impossible?
That's right.
You don't have to force yourself.
It's not impossible.
Huh?
I was given orders, and I intend
to fulfill my mission with her!
No, you don't have to be so…
Excuse me.
Good grief…
She's a proud young woman.
That lieutenant is confused.
You do realize that, right?
Unlike the lieutenant
who is all business,
that girl sees battle as a game.
Catch a dragonfly and she
would pluck off its wings…
Catch a butterfly and she
would drown it in water…
Catch a cicada and she
would rip off its legs…
It's like a child playing.
Innocent and ingenuous,
but merciless and cruel
at the same time.
I prefer colorful pastimes,
but that girl happens to be
rather dark and malicious.
It would be hard to accept her after seeing
what she is
capable of, right before your eyes.
Especially for that lieutenant
who seems very straight-laced.
Not to mention that the Zanpakuto
belongs to the captain
whom the lieutenant looks up to.
I can't blame her for
being confused…
But still, they are
both dear to me…
Say…
Sorry…
This girl goes into
no-questions-asked fighting mode
the moment someone
approaches from the back…
What happened earlier
was partially my fault.
But let me add that
there are issues
with the way you fight, as well.
Anyhow, I'd like to work
together with you again
to slay the Sword Beasts…
Why did I have to insist that
"it's not impossible"?
Hi!
Hey! Don't scare me like that!
You're the one who
scared me, Rangiku!
So, what's the matter?
You look like you have
a lot on your mind.
– Is it a man?
– No, it isn't!
Oh, it's Captain Kyoraku's
Zanpakuto girl, isn't it?
Yes…
I'm not sure if I can
get along with her…
I get it.
It's like the relationship
between a bride and
her mother-in-law, right?
No, that's not it.
I get it.
It's like the relationship between
a daughter and stepmother, right?
No, that's not it.
I get it.
It's like the relationship
between an ex-girlfriend
and current girlfriend…
You're getting colder.
Why don't you excuse
yourself from that mission?
I can't do that!
I have my pride.
All right!
Let me take care of this!
I'm rather good at helping
difficult younger kids open up!
Uh, right…
Katenkyokotsu!
What're you doing?
She's not very friendly, is she?
I told you so.
Being that she's
Captain Kyoraku's Zanpakuto,
I thought she'd be friendlier.
Her master is a charming man.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Come have some fun
with us big girls.
"Us"?
You're coming, too.
Me…too?
You look adorable!
Doesn't she look
much more sexy?
Rangiku, I don't think it worked.
That's odd…
Girls are supposed to respond
to fashionable clothing…
But that one was
based completely on
your own personal taste, Rangiku…
– Please instruct us!
This ought to work.
Girls like her are just shy…
But in reality,
they're attracted to older men.
That goes for both Zanpakuto
and Soul Reapers…
Rangiku, Rangiku…
Looks like that didn't work either.
SWEETS SHOP
This is happiness!
Sweets make a woman happiest!
Delicious…
It's hopeless.
She's more than I can handle.
Give up, Nanao!
Could it be?
No, that's not possible…
A girl like her couldn't possibly
enjoy a setting like that…
But she is, after all,
the Zanpakuto of
Captain Kyoraku, so…
A party?
You say a party, but…
What's the point of having a party
under a cherry tree that
hasn't blossomed yet?
You don't know how to appreciate
the beauty of things, do you?
Forgive me.
That's okay,
those are minor details…
Nanao says she
wants to throw a party.
Just being able to drink with
Nanao will be very satisfying.
You alcoholic captain…
Huh? Did you say something?
Nothing, sir.
Captain, please try to
not drink too much.
Okay.
Why're you so concerned
about that girl?
I mean,
all you have to do
is complete your
Sword Beast-slaying mission, right?
There's no need to commit
yourself to her to this extent.
At first, I thought
she was a creepy girl…
But gradually,
I began to feel sorry for her…
Sorry for her?
She's a Zanpakuto…
She was born to fight, so she
probably doesn't need emotions.
But she…how should I put it…
I don't quite get it, but…
Well, give it your best shot then.
You there, young lady.
The name's Nanao.
Mind pouring a little for me?
That's not a little.
I'd like you to pour for me, too.
If you pour my drink,
I think I might get drunk…
You don't have to worry,
Captain Kyoraku.
You're already drunk.
I'm sure you're too
young to drink, right?
W-Wait?
Why?
Wait…please…
Wait! Wait!
Please?
You like flowers?
Excuse me a second.
Okay, done!
Yes…
Cute!
What?
Why did you come here?
Could it be…because you
want to see other flowers?
C'mon. Come with me.
I'll show you where there
are many more flowers.
See?
About the time when
plum blossoms fall,
peach blossoms begin to bloom.
Wait…what're you doing?!
No sword. Leave it here.
I knew it…
If I approach her normally,
she is rather cooperative…
You wanted flowers, didn't you?
I'll pick one for you.
How nice to meet you here…
You're!
Letting me go saved my life.
So as payback…
I'm going to have
a lot of "fun" with you!
Oh, no…her Zanpakuto!
No you don't!
You want this toy?
How about you play
with me instead?
You see, I'm lonely…
Pay attention!
I won't finish you off just yet.
I had to put up with
your fun last time,
so this time you'll be
putting up with my fun…
Hado Number 31! Shakkaho!
That was all I could
manage in my condition!
Since you saved me last time,
I thought about
letting you off easy, but…
It looks like you
still want to play!
You're… in the way!
Wait there…
I'll play with you
all you want later…
Take this!
How unpleasant to see a fight
go down under peach trees…
You know?
You're!
If you try anything, she'll…
Huh?
Why?!
Unfortunately for you, my girls
want to come home and play with me.
So, how'd it go?
Did that girl change in any way?
No…
But I think maybe…
that was never really necessary.
Oh?
Do you really think so?
Huh? What?
For…me?
Thank you…
Nanao, didn't you think I was
even cooler than usual this time?
Huh?
You're welcome to
fall in love with me.
Or did you fall in love
with me all over again?
It's saying things like that
that makes you uncool!
Oh…
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Hi there.
Today, I'll tell you all about
how the Espada killed time
while the producers were
shifting the story around.
Stark was sleeping.
Well, I saw that one coming.
Barragan played chess.
He looks very serious…
Halibel is…
What?
That's me!
If you spy on a woman's
private life, you'll get hurt.
Y-Yes, ma'am…
I'll be more careful…