Ichigo agrees to become
the bodyguard for
Princess Rurichiyo of the Kasumiohji Clan,
a high ranking noble family.
And now he must battle
the assassins sent
by Gyokaku Kumoi, who
plots to take over.
Kumoi gives the assassins
the Bakkouto,
which are made through
secret Kasumiohji techniques,
and they attack Ichigo and his
comrades with their special powers.
In the face of their
powerful Bakkouto,
one assassin's Spiritual Pressure
is completely exhausted,
another is unable to
unleash its full power,
and they are all
ultimately defeated.
Oh, Lord Kannogi.
That certainly becomes you.
Tell me…
Is Ruricchi really coming?
I don’t want to go through
the wedding ceremony alone.
Please do not worry.
Princess Rurichiyo will
most certainly return
before the ceremony.
Really? You seem
confident about that.
I am. So do not worry.
Wedding ceremony?!
Yes…
The wedding preparations are
continuing in the Kasumiohji Clan
for Rurichiyo and Shu Kannogi.
Who is this Kannogi?
Sir Shu is Lady Rurichiyo’s fiancé.
Fiancé? She has
someone like that?
That’s the aristocracy for you.
There is talk that Shu Kannogi
has already been installed as
the head of the Kasumiohji Clan.
So now, they’ll rush through
the ceremony and make it official.
But Rurichiyo is with us.
How can they get married?
A stand-in, perhaps.
After all, most people won’t
know the difference.
Prominent nobles of Soul Society
will receive invitations.
On the day of the marriage,
the gates of the Kasumiohji
Clan will open,
so that the common people
can get a glimpse of the bride.
They’re taking all the steps necessary
to thwart our actions!
That Kumoi…
He resorted to such dirty tactics!
When is the ceremony scheduled?
The day after tomorrow.
So there’s a little time.
Which means he may try to lure us into
a trap and take Princess Rurichiyo back.
That’s a possibility.
He’s controlling the situation and
minimizing the actions we can take,
driving us into a corner.
We can’t make any move freely.
Inoue is doing her best
with Ishida and Sado,
but the enemy’s evil
Spiritual Pressure
lingers around the wound openings.
It’s taking time for her to reject it.
This sword… Did you say
it was called a Bakkouto?
Yeah.
It’s a sword that
eats up the wielder’s
Spirit Energy and converts it to power.
Kisuke…
You aren’t familiar with it either?
I hope you don’t think
I know everything.
What is it, Enryu?
No… Lady Rurichiyo isn’t here.
How can you tell from just that?
Lady Rurichiyo.
So here you are.
Don’t worry.
Let’s leave it to Orihime Inoue.
They will recover fully.
Now…
We must not get in the way.
Let us leave.
Lady Rurichiyo?
It’s all right, Rurichiyo.
I know!
Rurichiyo, can you help me
wring out the towels?
Huh?
All right? Please?
Please use this.
Thank you, Rurichiyo.
I am sorry.
Huh?
I am so helpless.
That’s not true!
This wasn’t your fault, Rurichiyo!
So here you are.
They say something and
smoke like high places.
You were on the roof
the last time too.
I had forgotten.
Ishida and Chad didn’t get hurt
because of you.
Don’t worry.
You are wrong.
No, I’m not.
You are wrong!
If I were not here, they would not
-have gone through such suffering.
-You’re wrong!
They didn’t come after you.
After all, that Nukui guy
came to fight me personally.
I know.
Huh?
Even I know that
they were not bandits!
Kumoi sent them!
Kumoi wants to take over
the Kasumiohji Clan,
and he wants me dead!
Rurichiyo, you…
I have known that Kumoi
was after me for a long time.
I also know that you all kept quiet
so that I would not worry.
I am very grateful for that.
But… But…
Rurichiyo…
We all made the decision on our own
and chose to protect you.
None of us could
ignore your dilemma.
Besides,
I’m a Substitute Soul Reaper!
It’s part of my job
to keep people like you
from wandering around.
Ichigo…
So don’t cry!
I am not crying!
We’ll be all right.
Ishida and Chad may take
more time to recover,
but Inoue will do something.
So don’t worry.
Thank you, Ichigo.
Huh? Hey!
What’re you doing?!
Forgive me.
Unlock!
Oww…
Rurichiyo!
I am grateful for your effort.
However, I cannot trouble
you all any further!
I will take action myself and
take back the Kasumiohji Clan!
Rurichiyo!
What’s wrong, Ichigo?!
What happened?!
Oh!
Lady Rurichiyo!
What’s the meaning of this,
Ichigo Kurosaki?!
I’ll explain later!
We’re going after her!
What’re you doing?!
Hurry and open the Senkaimon!
I know that!
Unlock!
Huh?!
What?!
What’s the matter?
The gate won’t open.
What does that mean?
Lady Rurichiyo has locked it
from the other side. I’m sure of it.
Isn’t there a way to open it?!
Without a key, it’s useless!
Damn it!
Ichigo!
Think about the situation.
If you use that gate,
you’ll only fall into the enemy’s trap!
Then what do you
expect us to do?!
Calm down, Ichigo!
Why did Princess Rurichiyo
decide to return to her clan?
She knew that Kumoi
was targeting her.
What?!
And she blamed herself for
everything that’s happened.
Oh no!
So that’s it, huh?
But what does she plan to do
by returning all on her own?
Could it be?!
She intends to subdue Kumoi
by proceeding with the marriage
and taking over
as the head of the clan!
They’re not that naïve!
Rukia!
Open your Senkaimon!
Right!
Unlock!
Kurosaki!
Be careful.
Inoue, look after Ishida and Chad!
Let’s go!
So they’re off.
Well, knowing Kurosaki,
I expected that much.
However, the opponent
is a high-ranking noble.
It won’t be that easy.
Princess!
The princess has returned!
What?! The princess?!
This is urgent!
We must go out to greet her!
What?!
Princess?!
– Princess!
Welcome back.
This is a relief.
Welcome home,
Lady Rurichiyo.
Hold it!
I am Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13.
And the others?
He is Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki.
The others are Sir Kenryu and
Sir Enryu of the Kasumiohji Clan.
We don’t have
a request for passage.
Please wait while we verify this.
We don’t have the time!
Hold on, Ichigo.
We must comply.
Ruricchi, you’re really back.
I became the lord
in your absence.
I’m sorry.
It matters not.
I have no desire to become
the head of the clan.
But we’ll be together from now on!
What shall we do?
Maybe cards or fan toss?
Oh, you prefer handball,
don’t you?
How come it took so long
to pass through the Senkaimon?!
We tried to go through without a pass,
so it couldn’t be helped.
Thank goodness we
got through without a hitch.
The ceremony is tomorrow.
We’re running out of time.
Damn it.
What will we do when
we get to the mansion?
We can’t create too much
of a disturbance.
Leave that to us!
I will get Lady Rurichiyo out.
I am the chief chamberlain, after all!
Is that important?
Certainly! I am the top retainer
among the princess’s aides.
So I’m able to enter freely!
Open the gate!
Chief Chamberlain of
the Kasumiohji Clan,
Ryusei Kenzaki and
Ruzaburo Enkougawa wish to enter!
You…had names like that?!
What is the delay?!
Open the gates!
What is the meaning of this?!
Silence! You two are suspected
of abducting Princess Rurichiyo!
Submit to arrest!
Damn…that Kumoi!
We cannot allow ourselves
to be arrested here!
Of course not!
Then what’ll we do?!
Well…
We retreat for now!
Huh?!
– Hold it!
Hold on!
Hey, I thought you
were a big shot!
Why run away?!
We’re not running away!
We’re falling back to regroup!
Same thing!
– Hold it!
This way!
– What's going on?
– Where are they?!
– I don’t see them!
– Where'd they go?
– No way!
– Find them!
We gave them the slip.
I’m surprised you have
a place like this prepared.
This is commonplace in
a noble’s mansion!
Is that so?
I don’t know.
What will we do now?
We can use
the secret passages to get—
No, hold it.
What is it?
Judging from earlier, the entire mansion
seems to be under heavy guard.
That’s because it’s the day
before the wedding ceremony.
Then rather than search blindly,
we should wait until tomorrow,
when we’ll know exactly
where Rurichiyo will be.
Wha—?!
If we did that, then—
No…
That’s probably better.
It will be an official event.
For Lady Rurichiyo to openly order
Kumoi as the head of the clan.
No one will be able to ignore her.
In our efforts to protect her,
we treated her like a child,
and ended up pushing her
into a corner.
She endured so much,
and we couldn’t protect her.
Rurichiyo made up her mind
and came here.
She wanted to confront
her destiny head on.
Well then,
I say let’s wager on her resolve!
All right.
Kenryu, you can show us the way
inside the mansion, right?
You can count on me!
Wait for us, Rurichiyo.
The marriage ceremony of
the 37th Lord of the Kasumiohji Clan,
Lord Shu Kannogi and
Princess Rurichiyo has been completed.
Lord Shu, the new lord
of the Kasumiohji Clan,
and his bride, Princess Rurichiyo,
will arrive shortly!
Stand in your place and wait!
Look at that, Ruricchi!
They’re all rejoicing
over our marriage.
Rurichiyo!
Let’s go!
Wh-Who are you?!
Intruders!
Rurichiyo! Listen to me!
Huh?! What?!
Rurichiyo! Rurichiyo!
It’s me, Ichigo! Hey!
They’ve fallen into the trap.
– Ruri—
– That’s as far as you go, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Captain Soi Fon?!
W-What?!
Rurichiyo!
In the documents we filled out
to pass through the Senkaimon,
there was a line for a sponsor.
Who did you name?
My brother.
If anything happens,
he’ll be put on the spot,
so be careful.
Anyway you look at it,
it’s kind of obvious we’re going to
cause trouble for him this time.
Crap!
There’s nothing to do.
Jeez, I’m tired of just lying
around doing nothing.
You guys!
You’re too lax!
They can call us up anytime!
Hey, Red Pineapple.
Who you calling Red Pineapple?!
I’m ready to show off
my secret weapon anytime!
I can’t wait!
– Man, I wanna pee!
– Are you sure you guys are ready?