I don't want to kill you.
How dare you!
Welcome...
to the inverted world.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Suzumushi Hyakushiki...
Grillado Grillo!
I can see...
I can see!
I can see, Komamura!
I can see, I can see,
I can see, I can see!
So this is the sky!
So this is blood!
So this is the world!
And...
So this is you...
Komamura.
You are much uglier
than I imagined.
When?
When did you become like this?
What's wrong, Komamura?
Why aren't you coming at me?
So I'm ugly, am I?
I recall you loathed your
ugly appearance.
Did it bother you that much to
hear those words
coming from me?
That's not it.
Then what?
I pity you.
What?
You cannot see as
well as you did
before you changed
into that form.
I cannot see as well, you say?
Don't make me laugh!
In that case, what do you see?!
What can you see
that I cannot?!
Tell me, Komamura!
What's wrong?
I thought you could see things
better than I could?
Your sword has an
interesting shape.
Nice, isn't it? You can't
borrow it, though.
But...
I don't sense anything different.
Perhaps I misheard what you said
about controlling one's senses.
What are you talking about?
Things are already different.
Oh, my... What's this?
Do you smell something good?
It's too late to hold your breath.
Welcome...
to the inverted world.
Tosen...
I don't want to kill you.
But if you truly cannot
see anymore...
I will kill you in the
name of justice!
Justice...you say?
How dare you!
You cannot see as well
as you did before.
Do you understand what
I mean by that?
I'm not talking about your sight.
When you were blind...
No...
Even before then, you were able
to see many more things!
What do you know about me?!
When?!
When did you close your eyes
to the world before you?!
Silence!
Are you mocking me?!
Now I can clearly see
your ugly appearance!
Indeed, you can see
me right now.
But right now,
you cannot see the essence
of my being.
Which would be...
my heart.
Heart, you say?
Don't act as if you understand.
Heart...
A heart?!
In that case...
Can you see it?!
Can you see
my heart?!
Why did you
become a Soul Reaper, Komamura?
To repay a debt of gratitude toward
the one who saved my life.
A debt of gratitude, huh? That
sounds like something you'd do.
What's your reason, Tosen?
Me?
Mine is...
for justice.
She loved this world.
So I became a Soul Reaper
to bring justice to it.
I didn't want the justice she
sought to bring to disappear.
I decided that I would give
my life to carry on her dream.
That's why I became
a Soul Reaper.
Tosen...
I noticed a small lie within
the words you said back then.
You talked a lot about
how she loved the world.
But you never said that
you loved the world.
Then I realized...
That this man actually
hates the world.
I fully understand.
In fact, I was glad
you felt that way.
Anyone would think the same
if they were to lose a loved one.
I was glad to know you
were not some saint
who could say that he still
loves the world despite that.
That is why I decided to
become your true friend.
If you're sad, you
can share it with me.
If I'm happy, I will
share it with you.
If you stray from the
path, I will scold you.
If you make a mistake,
I will forgive you.
If you're in trouble,
you can rely on me.
I will help this man, who hates
the world, love it once more.
Los Nueve Aspectos...
Tosen...
Shall we end this, Komamura?
Justice
is not something you can
see with your eyes.
It is also not something that
can be described in words.
I'm sorry, Tetsuzaemon.
I'm sorry, Hisagi.
I'm sorry, Tosen.
I cannot kill you.
You really aren't Captain
Tosen anymore.
When you couldn't see, you could
have easily dodged this attack.
Reap...
Kazeshini!
Why is that man not going
to be executed?!
I request an audience
with the Central 46!
Please!
Why?
Welcome...
to the inverted world.
This is the power of Sakanade.
It reverses your opponent's
sense of direction.
It's like a trap in a puzzle game.
Isn't it amusing?
Then again,
you probably don't
play video games.
Do you?!
This certainly is interesting.
Everything is reversed...
Up and down, left and right.
And even front and back.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
It seems you didn't notice.
Up and down, left and right,
and front and back are reversed.
And...
The direction you're facing
and the direction
which you're being attacked
from is also reversed.
Up and down, left and
right, front and back...
The direction from which
you're taking damage.
Can you really fight while reversing
all of that inside your head?
It's impossible.
No one can do that.
Whether you're a Soul Reaper,
an Espada, or a human,
the sense you use
the most is sight.
You fight by using
visual information.
But Sakanade makes it impossible
to fight based on sight.
Even if you're able to react, it's
impossible to control your reflexes.
Unfortunately,
the stronger you are and the
more used to battle you are,
the more your body will react
to the things you see in battle!
I'm over here!
What's wrong, Aizen?!
I'm getting the better of you!
I've got you!
Not bad, Aizen.
Even though everything
is reversed,
you managed to dodge my double
and triple bluffed attack.
You're really impressive.
But...
It ends here.
This is the end, Aizen!
So that's it?
It was all nothing more
than a visual illusion.
What?!
You were talking about battles
that rely on sight.
Did you really think I was
fighting that way?
Wh-What do you mean?
There's nothing to be
surprised about.
You judged where I was
based on how you saw me
fight using your five senses.
If I change your senses
a little, the rest is easy.
Your power is a far cry from my
ability to control all five senses.
It's child's play, Shinji Hirako.
Who is this?
That's odd...
This wasn't how it was
supposed to happen.
Who is this?
I can't see...
I can't see anything.
Anything...
Komamura...
Hisagi...
Don't speak.
Your Hollow powers are
allowing you to breathe,
but your throat is slashed.
You don't need to speak.
Tosen...
Before we fought,
you said that you knew we would
cross blades someday.
To tell you the truth...
As we were fighting,
I felt the same thing.
The same probably
goes for Hisagi.
Our relationship was
a fleeting one.
It was our fate to cross blades
and come to understand
each other.
I won't ask you not to hate me.
I won't ask you not to hold
a grudge against me.
Just don't throw away
your life for revenge.
Just like when you
lost your friend...
If I lost you, I would have
a hole in my heart.
Thank you,
Komamura.
Hisagi...
Let me take a look at your face.
I am still able to see due
to my Hollowfication.
I want to see your face
while I still can.
Cap-
Captain!
Aizen!
I won't forgive you, Aizen!
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
Fu... Looks like they've finally
settled the score down there.
Don't sleep in the midst
of a battle you fool!
Captain Soi Fon, I've
defeated Aizen!
Quit dreaming! He's still alive!
There you go with
the lies, Captain.
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Ichigo! What super
perfect timing!
No, wait a second...
Welcome...
to the inverted world.
It's not my cue yet.
Aaagh! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hurry up so I can make
my entrance, Hirako!
Damn it!
Ichigo! I'll get you for
this, you bastard!
Huh?