One day, a large number of Hollows
suddenly appeared in Karakura Town.
Ichigo and Rukia left
to exterminate the Hollows,
and in the midst of battle,
they encountered a strange trio.
Ishida and the others arrived to help,
and the Hollows were
promptly dealt with.
Ichigo went after the strange trio
only to find that they had disappeared.
However, he meets them once more
in a totally unexpected place.
They have moved in next door,
behind the Kurosaki Clinic.
Furthermore, the following day,
it turns out that they are
to be Ichigo’s classmates.
What?!
She’s cute!
He’s huge!
What is that?
A giant?!
That girl has to be
in grade school!
Two adults and a child!
I am Kenryu.
This man on my left is Enryu.
And this person here is…
I am Rurichiyo Kasumiohji!
Pleased to make
your acquaintance!
– Huh?!
Say, Rurichiyo!
Where’d you move from?
Very far away.
How come you three
transferred together?
We’re related.
Where do you live?
That’s a secret.
What’re your body measurements?
You even go after girls like her?!
But, she’s so cute!
How come only you are answering
all the questions, Kenryu?
Lady Rurichiyo is a person
of high nobility.
It is a waste of her time
to reply to those beneath her.
Beneath her? Aw, come on.
Don’t exaggerate.
You there.
Do not get too friendly
with Lady Rurichiyo.
Huh?
If you become too
friendly with her…
you’ll lose your life.
N-No way.
By the way, Ichigo…
What is it?
What? How come she’ll talk to Ichigo,
but I get threatened?
F-Forget what I just said.
Ichigo! School is
a strange place indeed.
Why?
Everyone is dressed alike.
Are they Soul Reapers?
Nope.
Lady Rurichiyo is
directly addressing you.
Answer more politely!
Not so close, guys.
Ichigo! I am thirsty.
Say, do you always talk like that?
Do I sound funny?
Well, this isn’t the feudal age.
F-Forget what I just said.
There’s nothing wrong
with the way you speak.
In fact, I like it.
To each his own taste.
Yup, I think it’s cute too.
Bring me something
to drink, Ichigo.
Why me?
Go! Be grateful that Lady Rurichiyo
herself is ordering you.
Why you…
Come on… Go buy her
some juice at least, Ichigo.
Be kind to transfer students.
Oh, okay.
This is getting to be a chore.
Serve me well, Ichigo.
What’re those guys doing?
Oh, Ichigo.
Are you going home?
We are also heading home now.
Lady Rurichiyo!
Let us go together.
You’re going the same way?
Well, yeah.
Oh then, we’ll be together
part of the way.
Let’s go!
Ichigo, let us go!
This will not do!
We chose today’s route home
after careful investigation.
We cannot waste any time
lingering with others.
Huh?!
Please heed our request.
No! I am going home with Ichigo!
I will buy you a sweet snack on
the way home, so please bear with it.
The sweets in this world
are delicious!
Really?
Ichigo, I shall see you again!
Something’s up, after all.
They’re being way too careful.
You are a wonderful cook, Kenryu!
Thank you very much.
It has been a while since I had
as much fun as I did today.
I’m glad to hear that.
Can I go to school again tomorrow?
Yes, of course.
Oh, I’m looking forward to it!
I can see Ichigo Kurosaki
again tomorrow.
Huh?!
Lady Rurichiyo, he is…
He is a fine man.
And strong.
No, no!
You must not warm up
to him so easily!
He is far beneath you!
If you become too close to him,
there may be serious consequences!
Consequences?
Such as what?
Well…
That is…
I know. Both of you
are such worrywarts.
Now then,
I shall have my dinner!
Yes.
It looks delicious.
What?! The same class?!
Are you serious?
Yes.
They ingeniously used
Memory Replacement
to transfer to our class
without raising any suspicion.
Ichigo, do you think they’re…
There is no mistake that
they have business with you.
But if so, why?
Rukia… Weren’t you
checking them out?
Yes, but there was no sign
that they used the Senkaimon.
And that gigai,
I’m certain it’s from Urahara.
But they refuse to answer my questions,
claiming it’s a trade secret.
This is starting to smell very fishy!
Ichigo! Let’s sneak into their place
and find out once and for all!
Forget it, that’s a pain.
Huh?! Why?
Aren’t you curious?
Mr. Urahara is leaving them alone.
So there probably
isn’t anything wrong.
We all have our circumstances.
Let’s leave them alone for a while.
Ichigo…
You’re right.
Huh?! Aren’t you worried?!
I’m so worried I can’t sleep!
Ichigo!
It’s from next door!
Is it his Spiritual Pressure?
In any case, this Spiritual Pressure
isn’t normal.
Let’s go, Rukia!
What’s the ruckus?
Can’t a person sleep in peace?
You! What are you doing?
Your Spiritual Pressure isn’t
the same as earlier today.
What’s going on?
I’m a Substitute Soul Reaper,
so I can’t ignore this.
Explain yourself.
Otherwise…
What?!
It’s here!
What?! This Spiritual Pressure…
Why you…
Damn it!
Kenryu! Who is this guy?
Ichigo Kurosaki,
I leave the rest to you.
Huh?!
Hey you!
He ran off.
Those guys…
Just who are you?
You don’t seem to be
from the Stealth Force.
Wait!
Where do you think you’re going?
So it’s Rurichiyo and
her men he’s after.
Seems that way.
Why are you after
Rurichiyo and her guys?
Speak up!
Ichigo!
What was that?!
I lost consciousness for a second.
What’s the matter, Ichigo?!
Rukia!
What the hell is that anyway?
You mean his Zanpakuto’s power?
Watch out, Ichigo.
The light reflected off from his blade…
It’s not just a smoke screen.
I know that.
Ichigo!
Don’t look at the light!
Damn it!
His swordmanship…
Are you an assassin?!
Assassin?
Rukia!
Ichigo! Capture him alive!
We’ll make him tell us
why he’s after Rurichiyo!
I know!
Damn you!
Ichigo!
Ichigo! Don’t look at the light!
Keep your eyes on the enemy!
Easy for you to say!
Ichigo!
I can bring down a guy like you
without looking at your face.
Your Zanpakuto reflects
the light from the moon
and it seems to knock out any opponent
who looks at it for an instant.
In order to do that, you must always
come around to face me directly.
Once I figured that out…
Sorry, but you’re
no longer a challenge.
Now, you’re gonna talk!
Why are you after
Rurichiyo and her men?
Answer!
Like I’ll let you get away!
W-What?!
Did he kill himself?
What?!
It seems Rurichiyo and her men
are involved in a dire situation.
I see you got rid of the assassin.
Ichigo Kurosaki,
I must praise your good—
What was that for?!
That’s for running off
and leaving us to fight.
This time, you will tell us
your predicament.
I’ll ask Inoue to come.
I should call Ishida and Chad too.
Lady Rurichiyo Kasumiohji is…
Kasumiohji?
As in, the Kasumiohji Clan?
You know them, Kuchiki?
They are high-ranking aristocrats
next to the four great noble families.
Come on.
Why didn’t you remember that
the first time you heard
the name Kasumiohji?
Kuchiki… Kuchiki?!
Kuchiki as in the Kuchiki Clan?!
Well, yes.
Oh, forgive our rudeness!
I never imagined
I’d find someone
belonging to the Kuchiki Clan
in a place like this!
And you guys!
Why did it take you this long
to recognize the name, Kuchiki?
Kurosaki… Things won’t move forward
if you keep on questioning!
It’s not my fault!
No need for the formality.
Don’t bow.
Lady Rurichiyo is the legitimate heir
of the Kasumiohji Clan.
It would have been fine
if her parents,
the previous heads of the family,
were alive.
Lady Rurichiyo’s mother,
the previous head of family,
died shortly after giving birth to her.
Then her father immediately
followed in death from an illness.
We have been her stewards since
she was born, and we raised her.
She hasn’t taken over as head
of the household yet?
She was so young.
We thought it better to wait
until she was older.
But that turned into a problem.
There is a man
named Gyokaku Kumoi
who is currently the provisional
administrator of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Lately, vassals have begun to
disappear from his service.
It seems he gets rid of vassals
who don’t agree with him.
There are signs that Kumoi is
taking advantage of his position
and is trying to take over
the Kasumiohji Clan.
A coup d’état?
And recently, strange things have
been occurring around Lady Rurichiyo.
Don’t tell me…
Yes.
Kumoi is finding Lady Rurichiyo,
the legitimate heir to
the Kasumiohji Clan, a hindrance.
Hence, the child’s assassination.
How cruel.
Do you have proof?
We thought it was
too dangerous to ignore,
so in order to
protect Lady Rurichiyo…
We didn’t tell even
the closest vassals,
and left under the cover
of the night mist.
We passed through the Senkaimon
that is expressly for the use
of the Kasumiohji Clan
and escaped to
the World of the Living.
That’s why the Soul Pager
couldn’t find a record of it.
As you know,
Soul Pagers cannot access data
relating to private Senkaimon.
Huh? What’s wrong?
Ichigo Kurosaki…
We have heard of you,
even in Soul Society.
Your strength is amazing.
I bore witness to it.
Huh?
Assassins are certain to come
after Lady Rurichiyo again.
They belong to
a special assassination squad
secretly assembled by Kumoi using
the Kasumiohji Clan’s political influence.
Ichigo Kurosaki, please become
Lady Rurichiyo’s bodyguard!
H-Hold on a minute!
Please!
If news of the strife within
a noble family is made public,
the Kasumiohji Clan
will face disbanding.
That is why we
cannot appeal to
the Soul Reapers of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
Luckily, you are
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
not a legitimate Soul Reaper.
Yeah, but…
Please!
We alone cannot defend
against Kumoi’s assassins!
What if we capture the assassin
and present him to Kumoi
as proof of his treachery?
He will only deny
knowing the assassin.
Besides, when they fail their mission,
they commit suicide.
Furthermore,
they use ominous techniques
and are extremely skilled.
Ichigo, do it.
I’ll help too.
Miss Kuchiki, you too?!
We cannot possibly ask you.
No. I belong to the Kuchiki Clan.
I’ve experienced first-hand, the trials
and tribulations of an aristocratic family.
I cannot ignore your plight.
I guess I have no choice.
Thank you!
There’s one other thing.
Lady Rurichiyo is not aware
that she is being targeted.
And we don’t want her to know.
We don’t want to hurt her
with such knowledge.
Hence, we want her to remain totally
unaware of the real situation.
What?! That’s…
Forgive us!
Cripes…
Lost to a Substitute Soul Reaper?
Yes. This Substitute Soul Reaper
seems to be very skilled.
Why would someone like
a substitute aid the Princess?
We must speed things up,
or there could be problems.
Very well. I’ll leave it to you.
Taking over a clan is quite a chore.
Ichigo, is it true that you’re
gonna be a bodyguard next?
Yeah. Things turned out
that way before I knew it.
All right! I don’t like the idea
that it’s a small little girl,
but I’ll do my very best too.
You can rely on me!
Then, you can stay
and watch the house.
All right… What, again?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Yeah!
MEN'S SOUL REAPER ASSOCIATION
MEN’S LAVATORY
Vice-President,
what is the agenda?
Huh? You’re asking me?
Did you forget the…
We are discussing
the Soul Pager today.
Quit that Hiroshima dialect.
You can’t even use it properly.
Men must have the special Soul Pager
with twist-on headbands.
You too, idiot!
It’s gotta be gold.
You can even embed jewels.
MANUFACTURED BY
OMAEDA JEWLRLY (LIMITED)
Too expensive! Don’t advertise
your own family business, idiot!
TO BE CONTINUED