Uh, Gin-san? What was that about?
How could you screw up the
end of the opening sequence?
Don't blame me.
There's bound to be a mishap when
you do the same thing 23 times in a row.
I thought the opening
was reused every time.
You weren't supposed to say that.
I'm too embarrassed to show my face.
How am I supposed to do this next week?
I feel the same way.
Me too.
Say, since this is so embarrassing,
can we cut to commercial?
Recycling Shop
Earth Defense Force
What's this?
Isn't that obvious?
Doraemon
A VHS player.
Buy it off me.
There's a tape stuck inside.
It comes with a video tape.
Nobody buys or sells
VHS players these days.
Man, don't you get it?
It says Doraemon on the
tape, but it's not Doraemon.
There's no flying or
four-dimensional pocket.
Just a nasty pocket with a whacked Gian.
Your head is whacked.
Anyway, I can't leave this
sitting around at home.
I mean, Gian is sticking out.
I'll just recycle this.
If you don't want to buy it, I'm
willing to trade it in for something else.
Like a DVD.
If you want to play straw
millionaire, go somewhere else.
Oh, I do have a Blu-ray player.
Huh? What did you just say?
I'm saying that I have a Blu-ray
player that I'll trade for that.
R-Really?!
Blu-rays are better than DVDs, right?
You can see the pores
in Shizuka-chan's skin!
You can see Shizuka-chan like
you've never seen her before.
Really?! Are you sure about this?!
Yes, I am.
But...
There's a Gian recital
going on here, too.
Blue and Red Ecstasy
What's that, Gin-san?
B-Blu-ray...
Blu-ray?
Why do we have such an
expensive machine here?
I straw millionaire'd myself a
broken Blu-ray player out
of a broken VHS player.
Uh, so you traded trash for trash?
But it's like a tissue used
to wipe this dumb girl's nose
versus a tissue used to
wipe Otsuu-chan's lipstick!
The latter wouldn't be a tissue anymore.
It would be a holy shroud.
Hey, how about I stuff my
shroud down your throat?
But this thing is useless.
If only I could get
this disc out of there.
It won't even budge.
What's on that disc anyway?
How would I know?
The former owner jammed it in there.
You can't pull or push it, but it spins.
There's something written on the disc.
The Cursed Blu-ray?
What's this?
Beats me.
I've heard of cursed video tapes.
The ones where you die
if you watch them.
I've heard about that.
A ghost comes out of
the TV and kills you.
It's coming for me!
But I've never heard of
a cursed Blu-ray before.
Well, video tapes are too dated.
Ghosts also have to
keep up with the times.
Th-This isn't funny!
I don't want to see a
high-definition ghost!
Damn that bitch!
I'm gonna return this thing!
Ah, Gin-san!
You didn't unplug it!
I put it in!
That's great.
Let's watch it then.
What are you babbling about?!
Do you want to die?!
It was probably just a prank.
That cursed video tape was just a story.
Just turn the TV off!
Man...
Turn around then, Gin-san.
I'll turn the volume down.
Huh?
The remote isn't working.
What?!
Hey! Wait a second!
This is...
Oh, I can see something.
Hey, isn't that a well?
This is, you know,
where that person lives!
This is really bad...
There it comes!
It was all true!
We're so screwed!
Uh oh, it's going to jump out
of the TV and kill us all!
Shinpachi!
Grab a pot lid!
Hold it back!
Don't let it get out!
That's not how it works!
Gin-chan, it's coming closer!
Destroy it! Destroy the TV!
W-Wait, Gin-san!
It...
It stopped moving.
K-Kotatsu...
Kotatsu?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Is that some kind of deadly curse?!
Ah! She's leaving.
I don't get it, but she's
going back to the well!
Did I turn it off?
Hey! She just said, "Did I turn it off"!
So she meant kotatsu as
in the heated table?!
She went back to make
sure she turned it off?!
Uh, what kind of ghost would
go back to check on a kotatsu?!
And is there a kotatsu down there?!
Anyway, this is our chance!
Come up with a plan
before she comes back!
Ah, she's coming back!
She already finished checking! Damn!
Huh, she stopped moving again.
P-Plug...
Hey!
Now she's going back to
unplug the whole thing!
That's one oversensitive ghost!
Though I understand the feeling!
It happens!
She can't come out of the TV if
she can't even make it
outside of the well!
Maybe she's been cursed by the kotatsu!
Maybe she should just flip the breaker?!
Ah, she's back!
She's having trouble getting up.
She brought the kotatsu with her!
She was so worried that she
brought the kotatsu out with her!
And this is the wrong season
for a kotatsu anyway!
That's not gonna happen!
She can't bring that thing
out of the TV with her!
Our TV's too small!
It won't fit through!
You have to lead with the corner!
Oh, well. I guess I'll give her a hand!
Hell no! Don't help her!
And how are you supposed
to get inside the TV?!
I feel bad for her though.
She's about to cry.
Uh, it doesn't seem like
you'll be killing us,
so could you leave?
We'll play this Blu-ray
again in a few days,
so you can give it another shot then.
Uh, did you hear me?
She's making herself comfortable.
She's watching TV from inside the TV.
What's she trying to do?
Don't give me any crap!
I told you to leave!
This is our TV!
If you don't scram, I'll Bubble
Fiction: Boom or Bust your ass!
You'll be off to a pretty crappy world!
I-I'm sorry...
I don't mean any harm.
Could you spare one channel
for me to spend the night?
Screw that!
Why should we let a ghost
use one of our channels?!
Y-You've got it wrong.
I'm not a suspicious ghost.
Look.
See, I'm not a ghost.
Y-You're...
That's...
I-I'm an angel.
An imaginary angel.
Blu-wraith.
You're obviously not an angel!
You look the same as you did before!
More like you became an angel by
removing yourself from reality!
What's that thing hanging
from your neck?!
Don't worry. I can't leave the TV.
These defiled wings
can't carry me anywhere.
I can only look up at the
sky from my rectangular box.
Blu-wraith is getting all blue on us!
She's doing justice to her name!
I was created by a mad
scientist from another planet
as a program to place in
Blu-rays for invading cities.
When the Blu-ray is played,
I become an electronic virus
that possesses every
system and destroys all.
That's not very angelic.
I'd call you a demon.
But before I could be played,
the professor had to sell me to a
recycle shop to pay off his debts.
Ever since, I've been known
as the cursed Blu-ray
and sent from planet to planet.
So you're the cursed Blu-ray
because you curse appliances,
electric devices?
P-Please...
I have nowhere else to go.
Let me stay in this TV.
One channel is all I need.
Let me stay in this Braun tube.
This is all too sudden.
Are you sure you want to stay
in this cramped and dirty 1LDK?
You could stay in a fancy 3D home.
I-I guess you don't want a
dirty Blu-ray like me around.
Huh?
Of course...
Everyone's had their turn with me
from recycle shop to recycle shop.
I've been abused by so many players.
Nobody would want to play
this slutty Blu-ray.
Sh-Should you really be
so blue about nobody
wanting to play you?
She's a Blu-ray.
I can no longer fly anywhere
on these slutty wings.
I can't make it to
channel 5 or channel 4.
I belong on the dark Video 1.
She just revealed that
she wants to be on Video 1.
If that is too much to ask for...
Ah! Wait!
I don't need these wings.
After all, they broke long ago.
Maybe these wings will carry me away
if I make them bright red.
Hold on! Calm down!
Video 1!
Video 1's what you want?!
What? Can I?
Only until you find another home!
And promise that you
won't leave Video 1!
Th-Thank you. I'm so happy...
H-Huh?
That's odd.
I shouldn't be able to cry out of my right eye, yet.
Very odd! Very red!
I want to show my appreciation.
But I have nothing to offer.
It's okay! It's okay,
so change channels!
Let us control the TV!
Oh, that's right.
I promise to return the
favor, so wait for me.
Uh, what are you going to do?
Why are you flashing your right wing?!
And please don't switch to Video 1
before I've shown my appreciation!
What are you going to give us?!
Don't do it!
You only have one wing left!
It doesn't matter.
I will never fly again,
but my corpse can serve as a
launchpad to send you high up.
Gin-san, is a color TV
supposed to be so blue?
Video 1 is off-limits for now.
The transition to digital TV
is finished, so stick to that.
Let's watch something to cheer us up.
Is it time for Laugh Away?
Who's going to be on
Telephone Shocking tonight?
Blu-wraith
Did you cut off your wing?
Yes.
Did you cut your hair?
Gin-san, I've never seen this
person on Tamo-san Hour before.
I cut off my wing.
Who brought her on?
Why isn't Tamo-san saying anything?
Oh, we have flowers.
Congratulations on your appearance
on Laugh Away?  - Blu-wraith
And there's only one bouquet.
From herself.
Introduce me to your friends.
No reaction.
This is as bad as when
Akira Emoto was on.
Stop it!
Stop making our TV blue!
Change!
Change channels!
Oh! Someone's making a run!
It's Right Wing! Right Wing!
Well ma'am. I would consider
that domestic violence.
No...
I wanted my husband to
pay attention to me.
So I snapped my wing off.
Today, we'll be making angel
wingtip with blue cheese.
Everything's the same color!
A very black blue!
Fifty thousand, I'd say.
Gramps, you're part of the
make-me-blue movement?
Stop it.
Drop a zero.
That zero might save your life.
You want this to blow up again?
Tsk.
Still, you're an oddball.
Why would you put a GPS on a scooter?
With a Blu-ray player to boot.
I'm at a crossroads in my life.
A very blue crossroads.
Don't let that Blu-ray player
get you into an accident!
Hey, I moved you over.
You understand?
You better earn me the 50 grand back.
I-I'm sorry about causing
you so much trouble.
I couldn't fit on a
video tape because I was
supposed to be capable
of destroying entire cities.
I'm really sorry.
I will hang myself in apology.
Uh, you already hanged yourself.
Listen to me.
No more hanging or wing snapping.
You're gonna pay me back
by serving as my navigator.
A fool like you should still
be able to read a map, right?
Th-Thank you.
You have set me free from my cage.
Y-You're like my wings...
I-In that case,
I no longer need this defiled wing.
Stop! I told you to stop that!
You really want to rip your wings off!
Take better care of your body!
I feel better when I see blood,
because I may feel blue.
But my blood is still red.
Okay, we have our destination!
Tell me the way to the hospital!
I'm on a delivery, so do a proper job.
This is where we're going.
Bring up the map!
U-Understood.
The blue wing is our current location.
Our destination is the red wing.
The whole screen is covered in red!
Who said anything about blood?!
Sorry, I wanted to help you
calm down and drive safely.
How is this supposed to calm me down?!
I can't tell where I'm
going with all this blood!
You should give me a more
realistic demonstration!
That's not what I meant!
Like this?
Yes, like this!
And tell me stuff like how many
meters many until a turn to the right.
Turn right in 25 meters.
Turn right in 50 meters.
Turn right in 75 meters.
Uh, why do I keep turning right?
I'm back where I started?
Do you know what you're doing?
I'm sorry...
But I only have a right wing to turn....
Nobody said to turn your wing!
I-I'm sorry...
It will be another 125 meters
before I can snap the next bone.
Nobody wants to hear about
your broken angel wing!
Give me my damn directions!
Y-Yes...
Nobody cares about me.
Turn left.
And then...
Continue forward.
Are you trying to kill me?!
What do you mean?
If nobody cares about my
life, I'm already dead.
What a pain!
This navigation system
is a pain the ass!
Y-Yes...
My navigation is too heavy.
I am nothing but a chain on your legs.
Goodbye.
Take care.
The hell are you on?! I'm riding
on the scooter you're in!
F-Fine!
When this job is finished,
I'll listen to your story!
Just give me directions right now!
Focus on navigating!
R-Really?
Then I'll try my best.
Turn right in 150 meters.
Yes, yes. Excellent.
That's more like it!
Turn left in 20 meters.
You are too close to the
car in front of you.
Hey, you're pretty good at this.
So turn right, turn left... What's next?
Kotatsu six kilometers behind.
What does your kotatsu
have to do with anything?!
You want me to turn around?!
You need to go check
if it's turned off?!
Why do you keep worrying
about your kotatsu?!
You are too far away from the kotatsu.
Current distance: 6,238 meters.
Who cares how far away the kotatsu is?!
Distance between our
hearts: 6,343 meters.
How does that even make sense?!
Where is your heart?!
So close...
And yet so far away.
You are so far away...
This navigation system
is a pain in the ass!
It's like you're straight out
of a Shinji Nojima serial!
I'm just kidding! You're
not a pain in the ass!
Thank you for the concern!
But don't worry, you
turned off the kotatsu!
Focus!
Do your job, okay?!
I'm sorry.
I can't stop worrying
about the kotatsu...
Are you sure? Are you really sure?
It's fine! Stop worrying.
I'm sorry.
I had a traumatic experience
involving a kotatsu.
Uh, could you just do your job?
Yes...
I was waiting for him that day...
Hey, what is this?!
You're like those couples who
get stuck in a traffic jam
and start watching shows
on their navigation system!
My boyfriend was so possessive that
he wouldn't let me go outside.
Boyfriend?!
Isn't that the mad
scientist who made you?!
And is this like a flashback
in a flashback?!
When I tried to go outside,
he would use d-doner kebab.
Domestic violence!
You were completely off!
And did he just rip off a wing?!
You had two earlier!
Back then, I had six wings.
Hell if I care!
And how come you can talk straight now!
I tried to convince myself that
he was acting out of love.
But there was one thing that worried me.
My mad boyfriend would always leave me and go away...
You're the one who's mad!
He went to Fukuoka a while back.
Last week, it was Hokkaido.
Today, he went to Nagoya.
Are these really business trips?
Or is he going to see other women?
Fukuoka, Hokkaido, and Nagoya?!
Aren't you from a different planet?!
I could only sit under a kotatsu and
watch reruns of Shinji
Nojima serials while
waiting for him to return.
What the hell?
Why does it have to be Shinji Nojima?!
Then I woke up.
I could smell something delicious.
It was a gift from Nagoya.
My boyfriend was really
on a business trip!
And he bought a present for me.
But then I realized that
it wasn't a present from Nagoya.
It was my wing that had been burned
by the heat from the kotatsu.
Why?!
And so, I was traumatized by
kotatsu, wings, and Shinji Nojima.
I-It's okay!
Everybody has to deal
with their own pain!
Wh-Who cares if you
don't have any wings?!
You don't need any wings!
I'll take you where you want to go!
Really?
Wow, the sky is so blue...
Next Episode: So in the Second Season of Prison Break,
They're Already Broken Out of Prison,
But the Name Works Once You Realize That Society is a Prison
Let me out!
I'm innocent!