Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Damn it! He's been awakened!
Let's go, Ichigo!
Okay!
What Spiritual Pressure!
He's been sealed away
for so long…
And yet he still possesses
this much Spiritual Pressure?!
You've awakened… Koga…
I've waited for this moment
for so long.
Now's the time for us
to complete our goal!
Mura…masa…
W-Why?!
About now,
Koga must be tied up in prison
feeling pretty humiliated.
It totally serves him right.
Yes, that's true.
He used to boast so
proudly of his power…
I wish I could see how dejected
he looks with my own eyes…
You are so mean.
You, too.
When I first heard of this plan,
I had my doubts about
whether it would work.
But he fell for it
hook, line and sinker.
It's over for him now.
Yes, it is!
What's wrong?
K…Koga!
W-Wait, Koga!
Pardon the interruption!
What is it?
Sir! Third Seat Kuchiki broke out
of the barrack jailhouse!
He killed the three Soul Reapers
involved in that incident.
Do you feel better now?
What's the matter?
No…when I think back,
it still makes my blood boil.
It's time for us to forget…
Those men are no longer around.
They're dead.
Let's use this opportunity
to forget our past karma
and live our lives looking forward.
Sir Ginrei…
Koga…
Do you know what I have to say?
Why did you do such a thing?
Why did you kill them?
Because they betrayed me.
But still…I believed that they felt
ashamed about betraying me…
But…
They were laughing.
Killing them…
Still didn't make
the empty feeling in my heart
of knowing that they tricked
and deceived me go away…
What am I…
supposed to do…now?
You've completely lost any chance
of proving your innocence.
If you had reflected
on your situation,
conducted yourself properly and
confined yourself to quarters
from the moment suspicion
was cast on you,
everything would have
been all right…
Confine myself? Why me?!
I didn't do anything!
You didn't do anything…
that is true.
But what about now?
You may have had good cause,
but you committed
a grave crime of
killing men who did
not draw their swords.
You will likely be put to death.
I am well aware of
your superior abilities.
However, you still
lack the heart
to make full use
of those abilities.
Your overconfidence
brought about this result.
Do not forget that you now bear
the title and responsibility
of our clan.
Ginrei…
I understand now.
You're the same.
You're just like them.
You act like you're on my side…
You befriend me…
put me off my guard…
But in your heart…
…you're just jealous of my power!
Koga!
Whisper…Muramasa!
Ginrei! You bastard!
Don't close your heart!
Undo that barrier!
Damn it!
That's all right…
I'll save killing you for last.
There are tons of people
I want to kill!
What's happening?!
Koga… Koga…
Koga…
Why is your soul
so agitated?
They're all enemies, anyway.
Everyone hates me.
I'll kill them before they kill me.
I'm doing what's
necessary to survive.
Let's forget about the past.
Can't you live your life
looking forward?
Why am I so hated?
Is it because I am powerful?
Koga! Let's create a new world.
I'll help you.
Is it this power that's
causing the harm…?
Is it my power…?
Koga?
Those people…
Everything…
Destroy…
Koga…
Your voice…
Whisper…Muramasa.
Muramasa, release!
I have news to report.
Koga's victims now exceed
several dozen as of yesterday.
Because of Koga's unique abilities,
selecting even veteran
squad members is meaningless
because their swords
get taken away…
There is one way.
The only way to take on
Koga's illusion-type Zanpakuto
is to understand his power
and close one's heart.
But in order to block
his attack in that state,
one must possess
considerable Spiritual Pressure
and an unyielding
mental fortitude.
Aside from myself, if there is
one other person who could,
on top of all that,
still cross swords with him,
we might have a chance…
Anyone?
In that case…
I will help you seal Koga away.
Koga?
Oh, it's you.
Why did you kill even innocent
people in the Rukon District?
Yeah…that's because…
I wanted to send a message
to all of the Soul Society.
A message? What for?
To show the foolishness of
ostracizing me from this world,
and to show how powerless the Soul
Reapers are to stop my power…
To do that, you indiscriminately
kill defenseless people?
Is that necessary to create
our vision of an ideal new world?
"Our"?
What do you mean "our"?!
Who're you kidding!
You consider yourself my equal?!
Koga?
You're my sword!
A sword should keep quiet
and do as it's told!
You're exhausted…
You should rest…
Shut up!
You're a sword—
don't give me orders!
What brings you two
senior citizens here?
Did you come to kneel down
before my power?
It would seem that's
not the reason…
Koga…
Wasn't your power for the purpose
of making your ideal come true?
Ideal?
There are no ideals in this world.
All that exists beyond ideals
is the despair of being unable
to make them come true.
But despair releases
my true power…
Despair is what
takes off my binding
and frees my heart
to do as it wishes.
Koga…you're mistaken.
Only those with power
create all order…
Even if that power is
dark black and ugly,
if that power wins, black becomes
the color of what is right!
Koga…
It's useless, Ginrei.
This fellow is possessed
by power—
he no longer hears
what you're saying.
Interesting…
I always wanted to cut down
the two of you one day!
Ginrei!
Are you going to fight me
with your heart sealed off again?!
You can't use all of
your strength that way!
Don't mock me!
Bakudo 4!
Hainawa!
What the—?!
I know your powers better than
anyone here in the Soul Society.
Dammit…
Whisper…
Muramasa!
What's the matter with you?!
Muramasa! Appear!
Release! Can't you hear me?!
Dammit!
Why won't you appear?!
I'm calling for you!
– Koga seems unable to use Muramasa.
– Muramasa!
Sir Genryusai, now!
Right.
Let's do it, Ginrei!
Right!
Good.
Shisokeppu!
Forgive me…
Muramasa!
Koga…
Koga… Why…?
Why did you do this to me?
What?
What in the world is going on?
Koga?
You didn't answer me…
When I was on the verge
of being sealed away,
I called for you…
You called…for me?
You refused to lend me a hand…
You say you…called me?
Your voice did not reach me…
It's the truth.
I waited so long
for you to call me…
And if I was called,
I would have come at any time
to assist you with
all the power within me…
That is how I felt…
But for so long,
your voice never called…
Eventually, I learned that
you had been sealed away…
That's why I've been
trying for so long…
to undo the seal…
It's meaningless if you're
not there when I need you!
I, a Soul Reaper,
gave birth to your power!
All you need to do
is to do as I say!
Weren't we of one spirit?
"One spirit"?
To me, you're just a sword…
Nothing more than a tool.
A mere tool shouldn't
be so conceited!
You call your own Zanpakuto
a tool and slay it…
You have no right to
call yourself a Soul Reaper.
Muramasa's objective was Koga,
but Koga stabbed him,
and then Byakuya appeared…
So…huh?
Next time,
Senbonzakura will explain it
so even a monkey
would understand.
You can confirm
your facts at that time.
Just as I'd expect from you,
Brother!
Thank you for being
so considerate.
I think he takes us for fools.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Byakuya.
Today, I'm going to
explain this to you.
The kenseikan is a headpiece
KENSEIKAN
that only high-ranking nobles
are permitted to wear.
You'll be wearing it someday,
as well.
Start thinking about
how you'll wear yours.
Yes, Grandfather.
If I might ask, Grandfather?
What is it?
Where do you wear your kenseikan,
Grandfather?