I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
It was Mabashi's Spiritual Pressure
that disappeared…
The enemy is pretty good…
Now then,
that person hiding over there.
Isn't it about time you came out?
Oh? How did you know?
I tried to copy you and
hide my Spiritual Pressure…
Even if you hide
your Spiritual Pressure,
anyone could find you
if you're that bloodthirsty.
Sorry…
I was searching for Ichinose…
Where is he?
Who knows? His Spiritual Pressure
disappeared long ago…
Do you suppose
one of your allies did it?
Hmm… What a waste…
It can't be helped, then.
I'll settle for you.
I'm going to make you pay
for embarrassing me.
Well, well… You underestimate me…
Well, fine…
It's my job…to erase Captains…
Baura.
Oh?
Boss, is he the next opponent?
That's right…
He's not like the small fries
you've been fighting until now.
He's a captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Okay. It seems like
I'll have fun today.
Is that the doll that you use?
My doll Baura.
What's so funny?
Sorry.
I was just thinking that the Bounts
are really interesting indeed.
Do you know
the source of your power?
It comes from Soul Society's
ancient technology.
What about it?
It was a technology that
was deemed dangerous
and sealed away because
of a single accident.
How regretful…
Even I don't have any complete data left.
But…
Here's a proposal.
Would you like to be
my research subjects?
What?!
To be honest, in the beginning,
I never cared about the Bounts, but…
I became interested when
I was looking at various data.
I wanted to do…
my own research.
It's all right. I'll try to make it
as painless as possible.
I'll even forget that you used me
to return that Quincy's power.
Unfortunately…
I refuse.
Our goal is the destruction
of Seireitei.
To do that,
I must remove those in our way.
Baura!
Okay.
My, my… Oh well…
Then…
I'm going to make you regret that!
That's nice Spiritual Pressure.
But it doesn't matter how strong
your Spiritual Pressure is.
I've received reports.
If I recall correctly…
You're a mole, aren't you?
You can only appear from
large surfaces like the ground or walls.
To try that on me in
the World of the Living is one thing,
but it's pointless here.
Tear him up.
Ashisogijizo.
Now then…
Come quickly.
I'm over here.
What is this?
I never heard about…this ability.
Don't underestimate me!
I've got you!
You barely dodged that…
Why you…!
Didn't you know…?
We Bounts have gotten stronger
by absorbing
large quantities of high-quality reishi
since coming to Soul Society.
The ground isn't the only thing
that’s Baura's space now.
This sky, which is filled with reishi,
is all Baura's space!
There's nowhere for you to hide.
You call yourself a captain,
but this is it…?
How boring…
This is…
The elevation of a Soul Reaper captain's
Spiritual Pressure…
Did someone fight a Bount?
That temporary fight amongst
Soul Reapers
was also the work of the Bounts…
Damn! Curse those Bounts!
Please hold up.
My, my…
How dare you do that to me!
Jeez…
How annoying!
Oh? You have an amusing body…
Shut up!
You're just an experiment subject!
Don't talk so big!
I'm going to make
you shut up, right now.
Baura!
Okay!
Don't think that
I'll fall for the same trick twice.
I would have brought Nemu
if I knew this was the case.
It would have saved me
a lot of trouble
if I had used her as a decoy…
He always hides himself in
an alternate space when he's moving…
But he always shows himself
when he attacks
and engulfs everything around him.
In that case…
This place is just right.
Come on. Come out.
Bount!
I found you, Bount!
When you appear from
an alternate space,
you have to swallow everything
in your way!
With this many obstacles
floating in the air,
I can sense your movements!
What?!
Tear him up.
Ashisogijizo!
It's over.
What?!
That's pretty good…
Humph! It seems that
it was a bit shallow.
Why you…
Fine…
If I've come this far,
I can finish you off easily afterwards.
Whoops, as an experiment subject,
I can't finish you off…
I've got to keep you
somewhat alive.
Will it go that well?
What?
This world is full of reishi.
It's a problem if you forget
that we Bounts are invincible here.
This power…
It's like the reishi subordination
of that Quincy.
We Bounts absorb reishi like this
to heal our wounds.
Unfortunately, it doesn't matter
how many times your attacks hit me.
Sooner or later,
you'll run out of spiritual power
and you'll be the one lying here
face down!
What's this?!
Who's the one who'll be lying
face down?
Ashisogijizo paralyzes the limbs
of whomever it cuts…
It only cuts off the signals
from the brain to move limbs.
Movement is the only thing
it takes.
Unlike anesthesia,
the pain doesn't go away at all.
Boss!
Don't move!
It seems that Ashisogijizo's power
is good against Bounts…
With this power,
it doesn't matter how much
you recover by absorbing reishi.
This is a new discovery.
Now then, we'll continue this
at the research facility.
Baura…
Boss!
It's useless to do anything.
Do it!
Okay.
What?!
He ran away!
But Ashisogijizo's effect won't wear off,
no matter how far apart we are.
Don't think that you can get away.
Boss, are you all right?
Don't worry about me.
I just absorbed
a large amount of reishi.
These wounds will soon heal.
But his zanpakuto's effect
is remaining…
Curse that Soul Reaper!
I can't disappear here…
Baura, counter attack!
Okay.
Just you watch, Soul Reaper!
Now then…
I wonder how long it'll take for him
to come after me
when he senses
my Spiritual Pressure…
I'm already here.
You were pretty slow.
I never thought…
you would come this quickly…
Hmm… That's a good expression.
I was going to finish this all at once
as soon as you appeared,
but I'm glad that I held back.
I was able to take
a good look at you.
How did you find my location?
My, my. Oh well…
I'll tell you if you insist…
I'd received a report that
when the lieutenant of
Squad 10 fought you…
She was able to track your whereabouts
using the Kakushitsuijaku.
In other words, as long as I have
your Spiritual Pressure data…
I can track you even if you hide
in an alternate space.
And Ichigo Kurosaki chased you
using a mod soul
which could sense
Bount Spiritual Pressure.
So I also developed something
like this.
It can't be…
That's right.
This sensor doesn't function
without the proper data.
I can't tell the locations
of all the Bounts, but…
your data has already been input.
It was very tough to receive information
from those who returned from
the World of the Living.
With that last battle,
I've made the final adjustments to
your Spiritual Pressure record.
Were you targeting me from
the beginning?
Do you think that it was
a coincidence
that you met me in Seireitei,
as wide as this place is?
Your body, which has aged
from absorbing souls,
makes for
a great experiment subject.
Curse you!
Now that's enough talk…
Let's go to my research room.
I'll be able to find out more things
about Bounts if I study you.
It's useless to run away.
Your Spiritual Pressure is
completely recorded in here.
I'm not the one who's cornered.
It's you!
Baura!
Okay.
This is…
Byakurai?!
This is the absorbed spiritual power
of the Soul Reapers
who attacked us before now!
What?!
I never thought that
it could move this fast!
Baura!
Okay!
What's this?
I sense a Bount!
Someone is fighting a Bount!
Where?
Umm…
Around that big building!
Shishinro, Repentance Cell, huh--?
All right.
Let's hurry!
We're just trading blows…
You Bount…
I can't wait for you to revive.
I'm going to finish this before
you inject yourself with that drug!
Go, Baura!
O-Okay…
Why you…
You're getting cocky for
an experiment subject!
I won't forgive you!
Bankai!
Wh-What's this?
Konjiki Ashisogijizo.
Konjiki Ashisogijizo turns
a deadly poison made from my blood
into mist and scatters it.
There's nowhere for you to run!
A poison…you say?
Baura! Suck in the poison!
Okay, Boss!
Baura! I'm going to give you
all my spiritual power!
Okay. I'm going to suck
everything in!
Don't get cocky!
I was going to keep you alive
and make you my experiment subject,
but that's enough!
You're finished here!
I won't die here!
I broke my tribe's laws
and sucked tens of thousands
of human souls…
I got this body as a result…
Despite that, I never stopped
trying to suck more souls
in order to increase my powers…
All for the sake of becoming
the leader of the Bounts!
Not Kariya!
I am most worthy of leading
the Bounts!
I wonder about that. Go!
Konjiki Ashisogijizo!
Die.
That's…
Konjiki Ashisogijizo…
Who's having such a flashy fight?
I thought I told you that
there's nowhere to hide.
Baura!
It seems like you had the ambition
to become the leader of the Bounts.
But it looks like
you won't be able to do it.
W-Wait! I'll give you
Bount information…
How pathetic…
I… I… I…
I'm no longer interested in you.
I…
Aww… The poison has already spread
throughout his system…
Oh well…
It seems like I wasted my time…
I've used up all the hojiku-zai
I had on hand.
I guess I'll return to the Department
of Research and Development.
How pathetic!
Isn't there anyone good
around here?
Damn! Get her!
Nieder!
Leave it to me!
The Quincy boy, huh?
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Ishida, sorry to interrupt you
while you're fighting,
but could you do something
about that uniform?
What are you talking about?!
This is the ancient Quincy uniform!
This fashion sense feels like
a breath of great history.
Don't you understand
how fabulous it is?!
I try to but…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
llustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Kira!
The Bounts have invaded the court,
haven't they?
Where should Squad 3 be positioned?
Oh. I forgot to contact you.
What?!
Matsumoto, really…
Oh well. Kira…Squad 3 is
to guard the Hakuto Gate…
Understood!
There aren't any other squads
you forgot, are there?
Of course not!
Come on, Boy!