Iron Town
Shifting to cleaning mode.
I will not stop until I have
eliminated all of the trash
in the Kabuki district.
It's cleaning time.
What's with them?!
They're like little demons!
Who are they?!
Why are these monsters
working for that old hag?!
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Snack Otose
You could say that Otose
has the power to attract such people.
We have no choice then.
Time to get serious.
Saigo!
Too bad, Bro.
You were trying to buy time
by fighting a bunch of chumps,
but that cat burglar of
yours won't be coming back.
She won't be able to steal Saigo's son.
Even if she manages to
make it to Teruhiko-kun,
Kada's people and my old
man will be waiting.
It's pretty much impossible for her
to make it back alive.
That's what you were trying to do...
There's no point in trying to
avoid a fight with Saigo-san.
Look what will happen
if you take too long.
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Otose-san's bar is going to burn down.
The building's on fire!
Oh, no!
We have to put it out!
You're leaving?
I believe that you barely have
enough fighters as it is.
You're pretty brutal
for a little shrimp.
I'm starting to like you.
But I'll need to separate your
head from your body first.
I've always liked you, Bro.
But you have to join my old man first.
Actually, you should just marry me.
That's the only way for you
to survive in this town.
You guys are all alone
with no coming to help.
All alone with no help?
I don't think so.
At least, there's one person
here who's willing to help.
Yeah, Gin-san?
You're...
...Tatsumi the firefighter!
Who are you?!
Trying to interfere?!
Die!
That's some weak iron.
You can't even scratch
these guys with that junk.
Want me to reforge that for you?
Te-Tetsuko!
Don't take us lightly!
Hey, now.
A lady doesn't like it
when you gang up on her.
Yes, a man should be hard-boiled, Camus
Kozenigata-san! Haji-san!
What's with that weird-looking bunch?!
Master Gengai!
Hey! There's a freak mixed in there!
Can't let this bar be shut down!
No more free drinks for me!
You have a running tab.
Why am I the only one who
gets the cold shoulder?!
The Members of Odd Jobs, you are not alone.
They have forged a bond during
their time in this town.
What?! Now we have an
army of male escorts!
The Kabuki district women
may cry once I'm gone.
But I will cry once you're gone.
How very naughty of you
to seduce a male escort.
Kyoshiro-san!
We won't let you carry the burden alone.
And here are a bunch of cabaret girls!
It's not very nice to decide the fate of
the Kabuki district on your own.
This town doesn't belong to any of you.
It belongs to us cabaret girls.
The Jirocho gang and tranny
gang can bring it on.
We'll show you how terrifying
the Kabuki district truly is.
We won't let you have your way here!
Those guys helped protect
the things we care about.
They know what it truly
means to be hard-boiled.
They're the hardest-boiled
bunch in Edo, Camus.
I'll never be able to pay you back.
But I also won't forget
what you've taught me.
Please watch us.
This time, we will protect the
things we care about ourselves...
Kabuki District 1st Street
Our Kabuki District...
Our precious friends, the
members of Odd Jobs...
We've lived together and
shared laughs in this filthy town.
In that case, we should suck it up and
protect this town together.
You are the ones who have become
enemies of the Kabuki district.
You're in our town.
E-Everyone...
What's with these people?!
Young lady, they
completely outnumber us!
Is that supposed to matter?
We're up against a bunch of amateurs!
Take them all out!
Yeah!
We can't let a bunch of
cabaret girls boss us around!
A bunch of cabaret girls, you said?
Get down on your knees.
I am the queen of the Kabuki district.
Idiot!
Are you trying to protect
this town or destroy it?!
Don't forget that you
have allies down here!
Straighten out your act or
I'll have to punish you!
If the town gets destroyed,
we can rebuild it.
This time, we can build
a sturdy iron town.
What are you talking about?
We already live in an iron town.
Gin-san, you guys go
settle this business!
We'll handle the small fry here!
You're the small fry!
That's the difference between you,
who takes things that others hold dear,
and them, who protect the
things that others hold dear.
You should know when a
battle is lost, Saigo-san.
Leave.
This battle is our...
...Gran's victory.
As long as Saigo-san and I are here,
your crowd doesn't stand a chance.
I won't let you go to my old man.
I said that you already lost.
You've really pissed them off.
Stay out of this, curly head!
I'm disappointed, Pako.
You're going to let a couple
of kids throw their lives away?
So be it.
I'd rather disappoint you
than disappoint them.
A couple of softies who
didn't want to fight
Saigo-san are supposed to put up a fight?
Looks like I'll need to rip your
head off to make you understand.
True, we were softies
who let you use us.
You tricked us, betrayed us,
but we'll be able to laugh
it off in a couple of days.
I'm used to having girls trick me.
But, no matter your reasons...
We can never forgive you for hurting...
...the Kabuki district's mother.
Don't underestimate Odd Jobs.
We won't let you hurt anyone else.
You won't have your way around here.
We aren't alone!
Now that the three members
of Odd Jobs are together,
you won't be taking
anything else from us!
It's time to show you the power...
...that has kept Odd Jobs safe.
It would be rude to go easy
on someone with such fierce eyes.
I understand.
Then I'll turn you into corpses first.
Where would you like me to
make some bright red flowers?
Your head?
Or your chest?
Or...
...Bro's heart?
There won't be any flowers.
Flowers aren't for samurai.
Flowers are meant for girls.
And trannies.
Huh...
That's strange...
How could I...
I can't let them reach my old man.
I'm gonna...
You used the back of your blade?
You're still softies.
You hit my chin so hard
that my head's spinning.
I won't be able to stand anytime soon.
Damn. Guess I can't stop you.
You're just as soft.
Yeah, I'm gonna talk
to myself for a bit.
Don't pay any attention.
We'll take care of your kid.
Rest easy and get some
beauty sleep or ugly sleep.
Then I'll also talk to myself for a bit.
Don't get yourselves killed.
I leave the Kabuki district,
our town, in your hands, Odd Jobs.
This town looks pretty meek
when there's nobody around.
Easier for your daughter to do her job.
The red light district will soon
be a playground for children.
Don't you mean it will be the
hunting ground for a certain vixen?
Are you here to keep an eye on me?
You think I would skip a sumo match
to come all the way out here
and waste my time on you?
I'm here for the vixen's head.
Hallelujah!
I'm next!
And then me!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Wouldn't you want to be sent
to heaven by Kyoshiro's rod?!
Uh, he's using a real blade!
They're literally going to heaven!
And what's going on?!
The others have been understanding
of our situation and have shown mercy,
but that guy won't stop
slaughtering trannies!
Stay back.
Agomi?!
I recognize his technique.
A special assassination technique
for slaying trannies.
Blade of the Male Escort!
That sounds familiar!
A thousand years ago,
during the great war between
male escort and tranny,
this legendary technique was born
during the Battle of Bootyloo.
I didn't realize that someone
had inherited the technique it.
This was the last place I expected
to run into the dreaded
foe of all trannies.
That stance, it can't be...!
You were too hasty.
Yes, I have inherited the
Kama-sen-ryu which counters
the Blade of the Male Escort!
I am Agomi, King of Fist!
Sorry, never heard of you.
Ago!
So you were willing to sever
this cursed chin of mine...
I have no chins in this life!
Yeah, you do!
You've got one long-ass chin there!
Oh, you're right.
He didn't cut it off?
Uh, could you pretend to be dead?
A male escort is only
allowed to penetrate women.
A toy?
Kyoshiro!
You were acting to keep
us from getting hurt!
I don't care if you use the sword
up here or the sword down there!
Penetrate me!
Penetrat--
What are you doing?
We're getting out of here.
Mama!
This fight is over.
We've lost.
Saigo-san...
I can't accept that.
My old man hasn't
conquered the world yet.
If you want to help
him conquer the world,
you shouldn't waste his men out here.
We don't need these useless chumps.
Go ahead and turn your
back on us if you wish.
I'll support my old man by
myself if that's what it takes.
I don't believe it.
He backstabbed his own relatives
for the sake of business.
The wife and daughter
you abandoned are here.
Doesn't matter what
people say about him...
This is the end.
We never want anything
to do with you again.
I see.
I assumed that it was
over a long time ago.
Doesn't matter if he
never looks at me...
I see...
So he's still making mischief.
How can you smile?
He abandoned us and started
doing terrible things
for the sake of a woman...
Before he left for the war,
he placed his hand here and promised...
...that he would surely return.
Pirako, he hasn't returned
from the war yet.
He's still fighting right now.
Medicine for Ingesting
But once he's finished, he'll return.
After all, the one thing
he knew how to do was
to keep his promises.
So don't hate him.
Once I'm gone,
there won't be anyone on his side.
We have his promise...
You will be the only one
who believes in him...
He promised...
You'll come back to me, won't you?
He promised to return...
Reinforcements from Kada?!
Take care of this.
I need to go to my old man.
Young lady!
So we were all played
by that damn vixen.
Mama!
Sa-Saigo-san...
Using a kid to set off
a war in this town
and manipulate the Four Devas
into wearing each other down
in order to take control of this town.
That should be the general
gist of your plan.
But it's too late.
Those pathetic monkeys are
being crushed as we speak.
Along with your daughter.
I doubt that they're
gonna roll over for you.
Well, this means I get a private
meeting with a beautiful lady.
We won't be having that.
Though I've prepared a little party.
Shinra?
Along with Yato and
Dakini in your troops,
it's clear that you're
not just some gambler.
My long battle with you ends here.
This town belongs to me now.
Or should I say...
It belongs to Kada,
captain of the 4th squad of
the space pirates Harusame?
You've finally revealed
your true colors, vixen?
Nonsense.
You already knew my identity.
If it weren't for you,
I would've taken over this town the way
Hosen took over Yoshiwara.
I know the reason
you were willing to sink so
low to protect this town.
You were protecting this
town from us Amanto.
I learned two things from the war.
First, at this rate, we'll
be swallowed by you Amanto.
Second, we are completely powerless.
Take care of her...
Take care of our town...
If you still want to protect
what's dear to you,
you'll have to change.
I gave up on being a human
so I could defeat you.
Kada, I can't say much
for any other town,
but this place won't go
down without a fight.
Your vaunted Four Devas have
perished, leaving you alone.
What can you possibly accomplish?
Have you been paying any
attention to this town?
Don't underestimate the Kabuki District.
Who are you people?!
Sorry to keep you waiting, dark dude.
I've been waiting for you, silver kid.
I'd like to return the favor,
but I guess the situation's changed.
You've got sharp eyes.
So while we were engaged
in a pointless fight,
they took control of this town.
Sa-Saigo-san...
Why?
Hostages are only useful alive.
I consider you a hostage
to use against Jirocho.
Besides, I've had enough.
I don't want to see any old ladies
or naughty kids bite the dust.
Our enemy is elsewhere...
Mama! Hang in there, Mama!
But it's too late when you realize it.
I can't believe it...
Saigo's spent.
The rest of us can barely fight.
We're finished!
The Amanto are gonna take
over our Kabuki District!
Good grief.
Could you stop whining?
And you call yourself
Kabuki District residents?
That voice is...
Bold and bullheaded,
adamant and adaptable.
Isn't that our creed?
O-O...
Otose!
Shinpachi, Kagura...
I'm leaving Saigo's kid to you.
We're running out of time.
Gin-chan...
We promised.
I'm trusting you to do as I ask,
so have some faith in me.
Gin-san...
We'll meet back up in
the Kabuki district.
I'm not sure why you're here,
but you're trying to allow
those kids to escape?
It's not like that.
They wouldn't be able to hold
themselves back against you people.
It's R-18 time.
I don't know the details,
but one thing's for sure.
I'm killing the old man and you, and we're all killing each other.
You got balls to talk like that to
the mighty Jirocho and
the Harusame, kid.
But it's easy to understand.
Count me in, kid.
I'm gonna slaughter you all.
We're all alone here
with no help in sight.
Just cut down anything that moves.
The last one standing is the winner.
Nice and simple, the way I like it.
You probably had bad grades.
Not as bad as yours.
What's so funny?!
Why are you laughing?!
Don't you realize the
situation you're in?!
You and your town are finished!
Damn old man!
Kid!
Don't die...
...until I kill you.
Next Episode
'Tis an Honor!