Time is up.
As stipulated, because Fullbring
was not detected within 15 minutes,
“Crazy Beast Mode” will be activated.
Please...don’t!
This is cruel…don’t…
W-What’s happening?
What do I do?
If I’m to manifest this Fullbring
thing using my Combat Pass…
How do I do it?
Your pride!
Think back, Ichigo!
Remember the time when you were
proud of your Soul Reaper powers!
The Combat Pass will respond to your heart!
Remember!
Ichigo!
When I…
was proud of my Soul Reaper powers?
There were…
Too many times to count!
This is...
Zangetsu’s...sword guard?!
Is that Ichigo’s...
Fullbring?!
That’s right.
Just as every battle you’ve
fought is etched into your soul,
it is etched into the soul
of the tool in your hand.
Each time you hold the
Combat Pass after a battle,
the Combat Pass etches the memory
of that battle into its soul.
That is the biggest
advantage to guys who have
fought countless battles
when they achieve Fullbring.
Even though you’ve lost your powers...
your Combat Pass still remembers.
Ichigo!
Crap…
Guess that wasn’t the way to use it.
The guard-shaped Spiritual Pressure
only comes out when I’m holding it…
It didn’t cut him.
So this guard doesn’t
have that kind of power...
I should’ve known...
You can’t cut somebody with just the guard.
In that case...
But...just as I thought, it
can be used just like a guard!
That sensation just now?
Nice...
I can tell your mind is becoming
sharper as the fight goes on.
Unlike a minute ago, when
you could do nothing at all,
a tiny light of hope has turned you
into a totally different fighter.
Is it from your experience, or from instinct?
I wonder…
Ichigo...
I can do this.
That sensation was definitely…
You idiot!
You’re going in too deep!
That sensation of Getsugatensho!
He...
He did it...
You did it, Ichigo!
With this...
With this, I might really...
be able to regain my Soul Reaper powers!
Hey!
I passed, right?
Let me out of here already.
Oh, fine already.
Not yet.
Giriko!
If that was truly Fullbring,
the terms of the timer
have been met and Mr. Pork
lying there should return to normal.
We must see that take place
before we release him.
See?! He’s back to normal!
Let me out of here!
Okay...all right, already!
I’ll let you out now!
You seem so happy...
What’re you doing?
Oh, boy...
How’s that?!
Sneezing on the object undoes my Dollhouse!
I got that without your explanation!
Look at me!
I’m soaked!
Need a towel?
What do you think?!
You knew this would happen but
kept quiet, didn’t you?!
I didn’t know how to make the
Spiritual Pressure subside,
but it did that by itself…
Is there a time limit to
the Spiritual Pressure?
What?
That can’t be!
Ichigo wouldn’t…
I can’t hear it anymore…
What was that?
That sounded like…Rukia’s voice!
What’s going on?
Her?
But she’s a girl…
Yes, you’re right.
She’s our next target to defeat.
I see…
You don’t have to do
anything, Shishigawara.
You can’t attack girls, can you?
That’s not so!
Kurosaki didn’t come
to school today either…
And Sado still hasn’t come back…
I’m worried.
The bread I left for Sado was gone,
so I guess he does come home once in a while.
I’ll make myself useful!
I will beat her to death no matter what
and prove useful to Mr. Tsukishima!
Hello!
I’m Shishigawara from
Miyashita High School!
Sorry!
Do you mind dying a little?
Making the first move is
what’s important in a fight!
Now turn around!
Hurry up and turn around!
The moment she turns around…
I’ll clobber her!
BULL’S-EYE
Knock out!
She’s hot!
Hey, c’mon, man…
What’s with that?! She’s too hot!
Is she really human?!
She’s so hot, she blew me away!
N-No, no, no!
My eyes must be playing tricks on me!
No way anybody can be so hot!
Maybe my senses are shot
because I haven’t looked
at women in a while!
Are…
Are you all right?
Take a better look…she isn’t all that.
I can’t!
Can’t! Can’t! Can't! I so can’t do it!
I can’t look her in the face!
I’m sorry, Mr. Tsukishima…
It looks like…
This is it for me.
No!
What am I thinking?!
I can’t give up like this!
Mr. Tsukishima showed me that
picture because he trusts me!
I can’t call myself a man
unless I finish this job!
Oh, he’s up.
Yo!
Say your prayers, woman!
I, Moe Shishigawara, am
here to take you down!
Down where?
She didn’t get that?
I didn’t know somebody
like her even existed!
Is she really human?!
Down as in, you know, kill!
It means I came to kill you!
Like your four-eyed friend!
Are you the one who attacked Ishida?
What’s with this chick…her
demeanors suddenly…
Answer me.
This is good…
I can fight with this tension in the air.
What’s the sense in
answering that question?
Didn’t you have your answer the
moment I mentioned “four-eyes”?!
You’re right…
Then tell me about your friends.
You’ve got hot looks, but
you ask stupid questions!
You’ll have to force that out of me!
Beat the crap out of me first!
Okay, that’s enough.
Mr. Tsukishima…
The one who attacked Ishida…
was me.
That ain’t right!
You kidnap me and brought me here,
and now that you’re done
with me, it’s “see ya”?!
What the hell’s with that?!
It’s just not right, you know!
What’re you getting at?
Money!
Give me fair pay for all the work I did!
Pay me, and I’ll keep my
mouth shut about what happened!
Right, kid?!
Huh?
Weren’t you grabbed and brought here
by this crazy girl just like me?!
I just don’t get what
kids are into nowadays!
I’m curious to see what kind
of parents she was raised by!
Anyway!
I’m not budging from
here until I get money…
Huh?
W-What?!
I’m not afraid of you!
I’m sorry!
I got carried away! Forgive me!
I’ll apologize, so don’t
put me back in that plushie!
So long as you understand.
Here! Take this cell phone!
What’s this for?
It’s for me to call you.
I’ll call if I need you for another job.
Make sure you arrive within fifteen minutes.
-What?!
-Gotta admit…they’re identical.
-Look young lady, don’t
go messing with adults…
Gimme a break!
Gimme a break, young lady!
Now then!
You can go home, too, Ichigo!
Huh?
I can?
I thought for sure I’d be
staying overnight to train….
What?!
Huh?!
As if I’d let a gross
creep like you sleep here!
Are you stupid?!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Look you…
She’s right.
Regardless, letting you
stay would be reckless.
Fullbring is the power to control
souls with your own flesh and blood.
It takes a far greater toll
on your body than you think.
Don’t push yourself too hard.
Once something goes wrong, your
whole body will shut down.
I see…
No need to rush…
We’ll call you as soon as your body heals.
You lived over a year without your power.
What’s a few more days, right?
The one who attacked Ishida…
was me.
Who…are you?
Shukuro Tsukishima.
Your…
Mr. Tsukishima!
It wasn’t necessary for you to show up!
I’ll take care of this one!
There’s no need to put
you through the trouble!
C’mon!
Come at me, woman!
Let me beat you to death!
Shishigawara…
What?!
Let’s go home.
What’re you talking about?!
As your apprentice, I can’t back away now!
I appreciate your looking out for me,
but your honor is more
important than my life…
Let me ask you something, Shishigawara…
Didn’t I say you didn’t
have to do anything?
Yes, sir…
Then…
Why are you here?
That’s because…I wanted to help you…
Oh no…
Now I lost track of how far I had read…
Darn…
Hey, Shishigawara…
There’s probably more again today…
What’re you talking about?
For a while now,
Inoue’s been bringing me leftover
bread from her part-time job…
Oh yeah… She has been worrying about you.
Let her know that you ate them.
She always leaves too much…
Tell you what.
Huh?
Stay here a second. I’ll bring them.
Take half home with you.
Huh? Uh…sure…
I knew it…
I feel bad that she does this everyday.
Ichigo!
What’s got you so freaked?
Something’s wrong with
Inoue’s Spiritual Pressure!
Something’s happening to Inoue!
Hey, Shishigawara…
Mind taking responsibility?
But!
What just happened?!
His bookmark turned into a sword?!
Is that a Zanpakuto?!
No.
This is a Fullbring.
My Fullbring, “Book of the End.”
Relax.
I have no intention of
doing anything to you yet.
For today, I’ll head on home right
after I punish this disobedient boy.
Oh?
You’re as kind-hearted
as I had heard you were.
You can’t bear seeing
even an enemy get hurt?
That’s not what this is.
If you’re the one who attacked Ishida,
I can’t allow you to get away.
Ichigo! There’s something else
that concerns me regarding Inoue.
What, there’s more?!
What the hell is happening to Inoue?!
With all that bread left unsold everyday,
how do you suppose her workplace
is managing financially?!
What?! This isn’t the time to…
Wait, now that you mention it…
Shoot… Not enough milk…
Shishigawara, mind going out to buy some?
Yes, sir!
I’m back!
I bought all sorts of things you might like!
Where’s my milk?
I’ll go get it, so watch this pot, okay?
Yes, sir!
Welcome back!
I watched the pot, just like you said!
From now on, you don’t have to do anything.