So here you are, Inoue.
Yoruichi!
Kisuke asked me to find you.
Mr. Urahara?
He wanted me to take you to
his training ground immediately.
That's so cute!
That girl's got
unbelievable fashion sense!
Shut up!
How long are you going to
keep making noise?!
M-M-M-M-Matsumoto?!
Where did you come from?!
The entrance...
The door's unlocked.
You're staying in
a pretty unsafe place.
That aside...
Have your tastes changed
since you came here?
This is something I got
from the owner of the house!
You wear clothes prepared
by the owner of the house?!
Of course!
I get a free bed and free meals.
I can't complain about
what to wear!
Really? I'd loudly complain
about the food and the clothes!
Hey... Who's the poor guy
she's staying with?
It's that girl, Orihime.
It's none of our business,
but I really feel sorry for her.
Hello... I'm home...
Ikkaku, Yumichika, how are...you?
Yahoo!
Is this a dream, or is this real?
It's the second coming
of the Breast Goddess!
You underestimate me...
I'm Keigo Asano!
The same technique
won't hit me twice...
Hey... He only pounced at you.
There's no need to go that far.
Oh! Sorry.
I kind of got carried away.
I'm home, darling!
Were you a good boy?!
Sorry... I went into the wrong room...
Hey!
No I didn't!
You made me do
something corny!
Who are you?!
Is everyone in this house
like this?
Things are going to get complicated,
- so do what you came to do and just leave.
- Hey! Don't ignore me!
- What in the world did you come here for?
- Hey, you! Get out of here!
Hello Inoue, long time no see!
Um...
Seriously... Lately, I've been
surrounded by two smelly guys,
so it really is cheery when
a woman is in the workplace!
Oh? So I'm not counted as a woman?
Oh, come now, Yoruichi.
I was talking about here
in this basement!
Because of you,
the shop upstairs is quite cheery!
What an interesting way to put it...
Come on. Inoue, sit right here!
Oh... Okay...
Sado... Renji...
They're loud as usual...
Urahara! He can't go on anymore!
I'm going to wrap up for today!
Sado!
Tessai! Ururu! Lirin!
Wake Sado up!
Leave it to me!
He'll recover as soon as I sprinkle
this magic water on him!
Sado, you're only slightly injured!
Stay conscious!
We're with you!
No problem...
W-Wait...
I can still do this!
Don't act too tough.
No problem...
It's a big problem!
"Enigmatic are the ways of Heaven."
Even things you think you can do
may lead to tragedy afterwards!
You must let us treat your body.
Hey! Nobody's listening to me.
You talk too much!
You bastard...
Ow ow ow ow ow...
Whoa... I'm surprised he hasn't died.
Give it your best!
Mr. Urahara... Umm...
What did you want to talk
to me about?
Earlier, Matsumoto of Squad 10
came here.
Huh?!
You know about the Ouken,
the royal key, don't you?
This is sudden and
kind of unexpected.
But whatever the case,
both Soul Society and we are preparing
for the upcoming battle in winter.
It'll be an all-out war.
More blood will probably
be shed than ever before.
And both Soul Society and we
will also need more power
than we have ever had before.
Yes...
It'll be all right. I'll stop Aizen.
I can still get stronger...
I can sense it.
I...
...want to become strong, too!
What's wrong?
Do you want to stop?
Not yet!
I thought so. Then I'll tell you...
Inoue...
I want you to sit this battle out.
Huh?
Tsubaki...
He still hasn't recovered since
he was destroyed in your battle
with the Arrancar, has he?
No...
I can't even find a trace of him.
He was smashed to pieces.
I don't even know how
to fix him.
Tsubaki is your only method
of attack.
Without him, I cannot allow you
to participate in combat.
It's the only logical thing to do.
Wait, Mr. Urahara!
Inoue is our friend!
She desperately fought in Soul Society
and against the Bounts!
Sado...
She says she wants to get stronger,
so we can't leave her out so easily!
That's an emotionally
charged argument.
Do you want Inoue to die?
No!
Inoue has more important abilities
than fighting...
She has defensive and
healing powers!
The Santenkesshun's defensive power
isn't that good.
It probably won't be of
much use in this battle.
And we have Squad 4 for healing.
This time, even Captain Unohana
and Lieutenant Kotetsu
will probably be on the front lines.
There are more than enough people
who can fill the space that
Inoue leaves behind.
But...
You're being stubborn...
I'm saying that a warrior
who's lost her powers
is just a burden on everyone else.
Mr. Urahara!
It's okay.
Inoue...
It's all right... Thank you, Sado...
Thank you very much, Mr. Urahara.
I'm glad you gave it to me straight.
Excuse me!
Inoue!
Wait...
Abarai...
Don't... Mr. Urahara is right...
Even though Squad 4 specializes
in medical treatment,
they're still Thirteen Court
Guard Squad members.
They're trained in combat.
But even though Inoue
has her abilities,
she's still an ordinary human.
Add her personality to that...
She was never meant for battle.
This might be a good time
to put it behind her.
Inoue...
She left.
Orihime...
Inoue?
What's wrong?
Why are you in a rush?
K-Kuchiki...
Huh?! H-Hey, what's wrong, Inoue?!
Inoue!
What?!
Urahara said that?
I can't forgive him.
No... It's all right...
I sort of calmed down
after talking to you.
This is for the best. I'm sure of it.
It's true, I'm not powerful enough...
It's not okay!
You've been fighting all this time!
Aren't you mad that
you were cut off so easily?!
I-I'm not mad...
Don't lie!
I'm not lying! I'm not mad!
But...
I'm just sad that
I can't fight with everyone!
But what I hate more
than being sad
is becoming a burden on everyone.
If I'm going to become a burden
on Kurosaki and everyone else,
I'd rather be sad.
Listen, Inoue...
It's not those without power
who are a burden in battle...
It's those who lack determination!
None of us have been a burden
in any of our battles.
Ichigo, Sado, Ishida,
everyone else, and you, Inoue...
Without even one of you...
I wouldn't be here right now.
There should be something
you can do
to prepare for the showdown.
Let's look for that together, Inoue.
Kuchiki...
Wha--?!
H-Hiyori?!
I'm taking you with me!
Hachi has business with you!
Hachi?
Wh-Who is she?!
Ow ow ow...
Hachi, this is what you wanted, right?!
Inoue?
All right, Ichigo!
Your break is over!
Wait a sec!
What do you want with Inoue?
I said that break-time is over!
You bastard!
I am Hachi, otherwise known as,
Hachigen Ushoda.
Pleased to meet you.
P-Pleased to meet you...
Hmm... Hmm...
U-Umm... What did you want
to see me about?
- Hmm...
- Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
You're pulling it off.
- Hmm...
- You're going to pull off my head!
Ow ow ow ow...
I thought so!
This hairpin is the source
of your power...
It's like a Zanpakuto!
Very unusual!
But it's cracked...
I've been wondering about that
ever since you came in earlier.
Yes... I can't fix it...
It's been smashed into pieces.
Shall I fix it?
R-Really?!
Of course!
All right! Thank you very much!
It's nothing...
All right... Let go of her head already.
I don't understand!
Why is Hachi suddenly fixing
that girl's weapon?
Who is that girl?
She just came out of nowhere.
I don't like her!
She's annoying!
- Quit your yapping!
- No, no, no, no!
- Yap! Yap! Yap!
- He's probably happy.
We don't really get to meet people
who have the same powers
that we do.
He probably feels like
his family has expanded.
Hachi...
As well as...
That's not good enough!
I see...
He was smashed into oblivion.
So he can't be fixed...
That's why you were left out.
Is that it?
Umm... It's not quite like that,
but I've already explained
this five times,
so that's good enough.
But that's odd...
From what I can see of
your Spiritual Pressure,
your power is very similar to mine.
If that's the case,
he should be able to return
to his original form
even if he was smashed to pieces.
Huh? What is it, woman?
Why do you look like that?
- All right! I'm so glad, Tsubaki!
- Whoa! What are you doing?!
- Thank goodness!
- Let me go!
Thank you, Hachi!
- I'm really glad, Tsubaki!
- Hey! Let go of me!
Orihime...
Yes?
I have fixed Tsubaki...
Now you can go back
to the battlefront.
But I also do not recommend
that you fight.
Since your power is like mine,
you are definitely not
meant for battle...
Especially against the Arrancars.
Even so, do you still want to fight?
Yes! I want to fight!
Then that's fine.
You still don't know everything
about your power.
You should have a way to fight.
Keep this in mind...
What's important is not
what things should be like,
but how you want them to be.
Okay!
Kuchiki!
- Kuchiki! Inside, it's actually...
- It doesn't matter...
Don't say anymore.
Huh?
Upon coming here,
I faintly sensed
Ichigo's Spiritual Pressure.
If he didn't say anything about it,
he probably had his reasons.
It's good enough that he's safe...
Let's go, Inoue.
Kurosaki...
I'm weak, and I always feel like
I'm looking back at you.
But right now, I'm going to go
forward without looking back.
When we meet again,
I'll be able to fight without
looking at your back.
Let's go, Kuchiki!
That you, Ulquiorra?
What do you want?
You're all better...
I'm glad I brought your arm back
just in case.
It's taking too long!
My arm's going to rot.
It would be easier if our bodies
automatically recovered,
just like your eye does!
Don't complain.
At least it's attached.
If your arm had been
entirely destroyed
like what happened to Grimmjow,
you would have been dropped
from the Espada.
That's true.
I'm finished treating your arm.
All right.
How is it?
Is there any difference in movement
or responses than before?
All right...
It's no good. If I were at my best,
she would have been blown
into pieces.
How silly...
Oh well...
It'll get better sooner or later.
I'll get my revenge on
that Soul Reaper when it does!
You have an interesting ability...woman.
Captain! Kuchiki has called
saying that
she's going to temporarily return
to Soul Society with a friend!
All right. Let's prepare for their welcome!
Yes! I've already mentioned it
to the squad
and suggested preparing
for a welcoming party!
Don't forget to cook the rice.
Yes!
Are you guys really that bored?
The Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today's lesson is on the techniques
that the Arrancars use!
GONZUI
Gonzui is used to devour
a large amount of souls!
PESQUISA
Pesquisa is used to
detect Spiritual Pressure!
SONIDO
Sonido is used to move at fast speeds!
CERO
Cero has powerful destructive power!
SONIDO
GONZUI
PESQUISA
CERO
Everyone, this is how you write them...
SONIDO
GONZUI
PESQUISA
CERO
They all look so difficult to write
that I can't remember them...
- Umm...
- Hey, Yammy...
- You shouldn't say that!
- Umm...