What the hell are you doing,
just waltzing up like that?
Actually... I want to ask a favor.
Huh?
I want you to...
Kill me... please.
Don't say disgusting shit like that!
I don't have time to screw around
with a crazy bitch like you!
If you can be bothered to say crap like that,
do something about this first!
If I open the door,
will you kill me?
Shut your damn mouth! Just do
something about this door right now!
Fine.
What's her deal?
You see, this... is my floor.
Huh?
Did you do that?
I used the key in the doctor's
pocket to turn on the elevator.
I get it! You're pretty smart, aren't ya?
You asked me to kill you earlier, right?
I did.
Well, I'm really dumb...
So you're gonna help me get out of here.
Once we get out, you might make
a better face for me, right?
When you do...
I'll kill you.
Really?
Sure, as long as you do your job right.
Okay.
And don't get all hyper.
Whenever I see someone who's
acting really happy...
I can't resist killing them.
But I guess I won't have to worry about that,
considering those dead eyes of yours.
What's your name?
Rachel Gardner.
I'm Zack.
Well, let's get outta this hellhole.
Right.
Was that guy on the last
floor a friend of yours?
Tch. Ignoring me, huh?
What about you?
Huh?
You called him by name.
Huh? Did I?
I don't even remember.
Let's go.
There's something in the water.
What? You think there's something in it?
Come on, let's get moving!
Do you know this building well?
Huh?
I don't know all the little details.
I only came here 'cause they told
me I could kill whoever I wanted.
It's probably the same for the
people on the other floors, too.
I see...
The hell is this?
Graves...
No wonder I smelled dirt.
What the hell?
It's filthy, and it's clinging to my feet...
Ugh, it's like, sticky!
Gross!
This is not my day, damn it!
What the hell are you lookin' at?
You wanna be in a grave that bad?
I already am.
Tch. Come on.
What's your fascination with graves, anyway?
Yo! Let's go!
You read it.
"The welcomed by the Holy Land.
The chosen by thee Lord, the Good Men,
the Beloved by the Angels, the Special Ones,
leave yourselves in the
magnificent glory of the Lord.
To the traitors,
here will be then prison forever."
I don't get it.
What's the point in putting graves here?
Hey, don't go off on your own!
What now?
You wanna get in that grave?
This looks like the only new one.
Yeah? So what?
There's a name on it.
"Rachel Gardner..."
And that unfinished grave...
Is that mine?
Tch. Is this here so I can die at any time?
This really pisses me off...
I'll crush it to dust.
You'll break your scythe.
Shut up! I know that!
Hey! Don't stand there staring at it forever.
I don't intend to die with you.
As soon as we find the exit, I'm gonna...
Huh?
There's a draft coming from there.
You think there's something inside?
Should I go in and look?
You're not thinking of running away, are you?
I won't run away.
You haven't killed me yet.
That crap again?
You really are creepy.
Okay, fine. Go ahead.
I'd like you to look for the exit out here.
What? Don't order me around.
It'll be more effective if we both search—
There ain't nothin' but graves around here!
There may be some trigger that we can't see.
You think I'd know a trigger if I saw one?
Right...
Huh?!
I'll check inside.
Also...
If you get caught in some trap
and die, you'd better tell me!
I can't tell you if I'm dead.
Hey...
You're still not done talking?!
If possible,
don't destroy my grave.
Whatever...
It won't open...
"Rachel..."
I've been curious about you for a long time.
I want to meet you,
but that guy is in the way.
You know something? I knew in
an instant that I liked you.
So I arranged something special.
A place just for you...
where you can rest in peace forever.
Rest... forever?
What's this?
How am I supposed to find a trigger?
There's nothing but gravestones.
Shit...
Someone had some serious
balls to make me a grave.
I wanna crush it.
Damn, it's hard!
There are calculations written at the bottom.
Added to the number of graves...
I sure showed you!
That'll teach you to be
so sturdy, for a rush job!
I know...
I'll crush them all.
What a racket.
Did he open it?
On to the next one, bitches!
Is someone here?
Watkin Becket...
"Place of death: B3."
"Cause of death:
blood loss from a bullet wound."
"Cut open on B6."
"Hanged on B5."
"Beaten to death on B4."
They're all people who
came to this building.
Here's my record.
Oh...
Take that, bitch!
She said not to destroy that one...
Laughter again.
I know what you really want.
I can make you fabulous...
Why's she so attached to
a stupid grave, anyway?
If possible,
don't destroy my grave.
This is just stupid.
Anyway, she said to look
for something, didn't she?
What's all this?
They pissed me off, so I destroyed them.
Well? Did you find anything?
There was something that looked
like a reference room inside.
I found this in there.
My profile.
The hell is that?
It's information about me.
That's useless.
There's nothing to gain from
knowing more about you.
Also...
Is this you?
"Isaac Foster.
Birth date unknown.
Entered an illegal orphanage as a child.
Later, the poor conditions
at the facility were exposed,
but from that point on,
Isaac Foster's whereabouts were unknown.
At the same time, in the facility—"
How did you feel after reading that?
Isaac Foster...
is me.
So how did you feel after reading that?
This is a piece of paper
with information about you on it.
No more or less than that.
You're not afraid of me?
No, I'm not.
I once knew someone else who
said the same thing as you...
Are you afraid of me?
No, I'm not!
I'm a fan of yours.
You were in the newspaper, you know?
I wanted to meet you!
I'm honored that I met you here.
You're so manly...
Hey, can we—
What the hell are you talking about?
And?
It amused me, so I gave her five
seconds to run instead of three.
If you're not afraid, why run?
I was lying, obviously!
I didn't want to be killed!
Well, I...
hate lies.
Does this story have anything to do with me?
If I run, will you kill me?
If I take the proper steps, will you kill me?
I forgot! You actually want me to kill you!
What's wrong?
Nothing!
So, were those papers all you found?
There seemed to be another room in the back,
but the door wouldn't open.
There must be some trigger that opens it.
Shit! Another trigger?
Also, I heard someone laughing.
Huh?
They said they know what I really want.
Is that so?
What's wrong?
I'm gonna have to destroy
that grave after all.
It's annoying the hell out of me.
Wait—
Your grave is not here.
You only get to die after I get out of here.
There's no trigger, damn it!
Hey! Don't just stand there! Do something!
I want you to look in there.
What?!
You're telling me to get in the water?
If you don't want to, you don't have to.
I never said I wouldn't.
Hey, are you really going to kill me?
I said I'd kill you once we get out of here!
If you just wanna die, then kill yourself!
Suicide is bad.
Huh? Why?
Because... God said so?
You're asking me?
I'm not sure why.
But...
If God says so, it must be true.
God, huh?
Then at least put some effort
into getting me to kill you.
What should I do?
Make a face that'll make me want to kill you.
You can get mad or cry
or something, can't you?
Do you just have no muscles
in your face, or what?
Just cry already!
Are you sure you're not already dead?
I'm alive. That's why I want you to kill me.
Okay. I get it, I get it.
Try smiling, then.
Smile? How?
Just smile, damn it!
Your eyes are dead.
What a useless waste of time that was.
Huh?
Don't move from that spot.
Stop ordering me around!
Move your own ass already!
This shit feels all cold and gross!
This wasn't here before...
There's nothing to be confused about.
You know my wish and yours
are a perfect fit, don't you?
Okay, that's long enough!
What's taking that little bitch so long?!
She didn't run away, did she?
Nah, probably not.
It's so hard to kill someone with
such a boring look on their face...
Of course, if her eyes hadn't
looked so dead earlier,
that face wouldn't have been too bad.
Huh?
You grave destroyer.
Tch...
Hello, Zack.