Takaoni!
Let's end this.
Ryusenka!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Let's do this, Stark.
He's coming!
I know that!
Slam!
Tengumaru!
Play...
Kinshara!
They're like flames!
There's no end to them!
You keep moving about!
I'm going to crush you!
Rose! Rose!
Can you hear me?!
What is it?
I figured it out!
They're not flames!
They're Cero!
They're dangerous when they
explode in close combat!
Damn it...
They're not Cero.
Regular Cero don't have the power to
mortally wound strong guys like you.
I split and rip my own soul into
pieces and make those pieces
follow and obey me like comrades
and I use them as weapons.
These wolf-shaped warheads
are both Stark and Lilinette.
That is the power of Espada Number 1,
Coyote Stark and Lilinette Gingerback.
Let's go...
It's game over.
If you run, I'll let you go.
Don't underestimate us.
I see...
I guess I have no choice.
I don't like the term
"finishing blow."
But here comes my
finishing blow.
What?
Stark!
What the hell...is this?!
What's that?!
Are you all right, Stark?!
Yeah, I'm fine.
No, you're not!
You got hit!
Shut up, Lilinette.
Don't act so tough!
You took quite a hit!
Don't you think it's about
time we get serious?
I'll show them!
You know we can't
overdo it, right?
I know that!
Stop being so picky!
The same goes for you.
What sort of technique is that?
Lurking in shadows is a pretty
ridiculous technique.
I'm surprised you were hiding
something like that.
Kageoni...
I wasn't trying to hide
it or anything.
It's just that "she" wasn't
in the mood for it.
This is why I don't like
playing with her.
My Katenkyokotsu has the power to
turn children's games into reality.
Katenkyokotsu decides
on the rules,
and everyone who enters
the domain of her
Spiritual Pressure is forced
to follow those rules.
Myself included.
In Takaoni, the person who
is on higher ground wins.
In Kageoni, the person who gets
his shadow stepped on loses.
The winner lives.
The loser dies.
She's a self-centered one.
Even though she's
my favorite sword,
it's quite draining always
doing what she wants.
Impressive!
You understand quickly!
Not sure if I can put
up a fight against him.
Takaoni...
I thought I told you.
In Takaoni, the person who
is on higher ground wins!
Whoa!
That's right, I forgot.
Those wolves are with you.
Are you all right, Stark?
Stay sharp!
Be quiet.
If I keep quiet, you
won't talk at all!
Shut up.
Say, are you talking with
that girl you were with?
So that means she still exists.
What of it?
If I recall,
you said you split your
soul into pieces,
make those pieces follow and obey you
and you use them as weapons, right?
Which is what those
wolves are...
You have good memory.
So if I take out those wolves, does it mean
the damage would go to you instead?
Who knows?
Or does it mean that
girl will disappear?
Who knows?
Oh come on, be a sport.
I gave you enough clues about
my powers, didn't I?
I never asked for any.
If I touch the ground,
he'll use that Kageoni.
But if I fight him in the sky,
he'll fight using Takaoni.
What a difficult opponent.
Hey, Stark.
What is it?
I have an idea.
Take his bait.
What are you saying?
You'll see.
Just do as I say!
Now what should we play next?
Calling a fight to the
death a game...
You've got some
pretty bad taste!
Takaoni!
Here he comes!
Sorry to do this!
I was waiting for that!
Kageoni...
Let's continue!
Let's do this, Stark!
Lilinette!
You idiot!
I'm still here!
What was that "tsk" for?!
You were worried about
me, weren't you?
I told you to keep quiet.
Takaoni!
What?!
Stark...
Bushogoma!
Lilinette!
Hey, Lilinette!
Lilinette...
That was a close one.
I didn't expect your wolves to be the
ones coming after my shadow.
For a second I thought
I was a goner.
But that same explosion helped
me understand your powers.
Your wolves can only drag the things
that they bite into their explosion.
In other words, they'd all explode and disappear
if there were objects surrounding me.
My Bushogoma was
perfect for that.
Now, then... It's finally
one on one.
I'm alone.
Iro Oni... Grey.
Why do I have to fight
someone this strong?!
I was always jealous
of weak guys.
Our mere presence taxed our comrades'
souls and made them disappear.
In our loneliness, we
split our soul into two.
I can't recall which one
of us was the original.
Maybe it was neither of us.
But that was the only way
we could escape solitude.
I was jealous of weak guys.
If I were weak, I could
remain in a group.
I want to become weak.
If that's not possible,
I want a comrade
as strong as I am.
Thanks to Lilinette, he's
moving a lot slower.
And my wounds are nothing
compared to his.
But something's not right...
Iro Oni... Grey.
When he cut me, it felt as if he went
deep enough to slice off my arm.
So why?!
My arm is grey...
He has no grey on his body.
What's wrong? It's your turn. Come
on, say the color you want to cut.
You won't be able to cut any color
aside from the one you announce.
Lilinette... I can still fight.
White!
Damn... You guessed correctly.
In Iro Oni, you are also prone to take damage
from the color you announced.
Also...
The more risky the color is to you,
the more damage you deal.
White is the color that you'd
take the most damage from.
I was planning to let you
in on the secret bit by bit.
But I didn't expect you to figure
out the rules in one shot.
You truly are difficult to fight!
That's my line.
Why do I have to fight
someone so strong?
Black!
Amazing...
Are you two responsible for
that mountain of Hollows?
No...
They just died on their own.
I see.
You seem strong.
I wonder...
I'm looking for comrades.
What a coincidence. So are we.
Are your comrades strong too?
Come if you want to find out.
Okay...
You seem like you won't die
from being in our presence.
Sorry, Lord Aizen.
It seems like I won't be able
to repay my debt to you.
I'm not alone.
I'm not alone anymore.
Do you...have a name?
Lilinette.
Do you have a name?
You were once me, after all.
Stark.
Stark...
What should we do now?
We can do anything.
Then where should we go?
Anywhere.
Let's be together.
Until the very end.
Good work.
Yep...
I'm glad you're safe.
You haven't changed at all.
I'm referring to your tendency to
not uphold the code of honor,
like interfering with another
person's battle.
Only amateurs would give up a victory
for the sake of their own code.
Us Captains can't afford
such a luxury.
Don't try to be good.
It doesn't matter who's
getting back at whom.
Once a war breaks out...
they're both at fault.
Smash...
Hagurotonbo!
Butcher her!
Kubikiriorochi!
Did we get her?
Not yet.
She's so persistent!
Bankai...
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!!
La Gota!
Cascada!
Ryusenka!
That's enough.
Gin.
Let's end this.
What?
Lord... Aizen?
I'm done with you.
It seems you aren't strong
enough to fight for me.
Gin, Kaname... Let's go.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
No world is without sacrifices.
Doesn't he realize it?
This sea of blood
covered in ashes.
We refer to this hell
as the world.
A ghost, clad in white garb, drifts
through Karakura Town.
That...would be you, right?
Except you're not floating.
Oh well... I'll perform
a Konso on you.
Now, of all times?!
Ishida!
Are you having problems with
a Hollow like this, Kurosaki?!
So that was you...