My melons!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
This is imprisonment!
A beating!
It's toy abuse!
Let me out of this jail!
Give me freedom!
Oh, shut up!
Stop whining!
They're going to think I'm
making a scene by myself again!
That's none of my business!
Why do I have to stay cooped up
in this crappy, cramped and
filthy room of yours?!
Life was good while you
were away in Hueco Mundo.
I could pick up girls, stalk them,
and do anything I wanted.
What did you say?
So you're the reason why people outside
are giving me dirty looks.
Unseasonal watermelons
are my favorites!
Let go of me!
My...my pretty melons!
You moron!
Melons...melons!
Didn't I tell you not to go out?!
Um... Excuse me.
My melons!
Yes?
Um... I heard that Karakura Mart
was somewhere around here.
Yeah, um...
Go back the way you came,
turn left where the roads cross,
and then go straight and you'll be right there!
Okay, I got it.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Aw man...
My pretty melons.
I told you not to show yourself!
If she sees you, it won't be a laughing matter!
Jeez...
A Hollow.
Get out.
Okay, look after things!
Right!
Behave yourself, you hear?
Yeah, yeah.
Not again.
Another weird sight.
Come on.
You can't expect me to behave myself at home
on such a fine day!
It's been a while since
I've felt the joy and excitement of youth!
Huh?
It's that voluptuous babe.
Darling!
Watch out!
Oh no!
Somebody...somebody! Help!
I'm sorry.
Because of me...
Forget it. It's no big deal.
And besides, this body doesn't belong to me,
so catching a cold is no big deal.
Huh?
No, nothing.
Just talking to myself.
By the way...
Weren't you asking directions earlier?
How did you end up there?
The truth is,
I see things that other people can't see.
Ken, I'm home!
Sorry, I lost my way, so I got back late!
I'll make lunch right away!
Here you go! Thanks for being patient!
What do you think? Is it good, Ken?
Yup.
Oh, guess what!
Ken, I just saw someone flying in a black kimono!
Someone in a black kimono?
Do you know who it is?
No, no!
Was that a ghost or something like that?
Yes.
I've been able to see things like that since I was a child.
But then...
Ken, after this, why don't we...
You know what?
What is it?
Let's end our relationship.
Huh?
I mean, you see people that others can't see,
and you talk to people who aren't there.
You're a great cook,
but you kind of give me the creeps.
I don't see ghosts because I want to.
And Ken told me he was leaving me
after he finished eating!
Isn't that mean?
Well yes, but I don't think before
or after he eats really matters.
You know?
I'm going to kill myself!
What?!
I can't go on living after breaking up with Ken.
Goodbye, Blond-boy.
Thank you for rescuing me.
Hey, wait!
There's nothing to gain by dying!
If you die, the Hollows will come after you,
and going to the Soul Society
isn't all that great either.
Look out!
Man, I don't see a Hollow anywhere.
Huh?
Rukia!
Oh, Ichigo.
Is something up?
Yeah. Look there!
Did a Hollow do that?
No. An ordinary Hollow would
only go after human souls.
So it's not a Hollow?
Wait. Let's not be hasty, Ichigo.
Recently...
There have been five identical incidents such as this one.
Five?!
Yes...
The Soul Society has been on
special alert for cases like this one.
The Spiritual Pressure of the Hollow believed to be responsible
for the incidents appears and disappears with each event,
making it extremely difficult to track it down.
But this body died very recently.
The victim's attacker couldn't have gone very far.
Right now, our priority is to
stop the next attack before it happens.
I want you to go on ahead and chase after the attacker!
What about you?
I'll follow you after I turn over this crime scene
to the others.
Now get going!
Got it!
Stupid Ken.
After all I did for you.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Ken!
Enjoy your dinner!
All right! I sure will!
That's right.
When I'm dead, I know you're going to regret it!
Do you want to die?
Then I will...
grant you
your wish.
What?
W-What're you talking about?
I will let you die.
So you can feel a Hollow's Spiritual Pressure?
What are you?
You're not human?
No. I'm just temporarily borrowing this body.
What are you afraid of?
I'm offering to grant your wish
of wanting to die.
B-But this is so sudden.
You know, I have to prepare myself for it.
What a silly thing to be concerned about
when you're about to die.
Relax, there's no need to be afraid.
The pain is only momentary.
Now open your mouth.
Huh? My mouth?
W-Why?
So I can do
this!
This Spiritual Pressure...
Could it be a Hollow?
No!
Now open your mouth wider!
I will leech on to you and then suck out your nutrients!
Just like I did to that dead man there!
The Great Kon
Shoot!
The Great Kon Kick!
What're you waiting for?!
Run for it!
R-Right!
The Hollow's Spiritual Pressure disappeared again?
Damn!
What the hell is going on?
We should be safe for now.
Um... What was that monster?
What was that?!
That's a Hollow.
Hollow?
Yeah.
A monster that attacks people
and sucks out their souls.
But back there, he said...
I don't really understand it myself,
but I think he's an unusual type
that uses humans as his host.
I see.
But why?
Huh?
Why'd you save me?
Why did you save me?!
Huh?
If you hadn't saved me,
I could have died right there!
Why couldn't you just leave me alone?!
Come on.
You can't be serious.
How can you say something like that?!
Don't talk about wanting to die so easily!
That guy who was killed back there...
I guarantee he didn't want to die that way!
Blond-boy?
You can tell, right?
I'm not an ordinary human being.
And to tell you the truth,
I was supposed to be disposed and killed off.
But even I'm still alive!
So don't talk like you want to die so easily!
But what should I do?
I'll protect you!
Huh?
I'm going to protect you, I promise.
And I want you to promise me that you won't die either!
Blond-boy...
Darling...
Hold it right there!
Who're you?
Ken...
Huh?
Haruko...
I'm sorry. I was wrong!
Huh?
I want to start over with you, after all!
Because your meals are really delicious!
Is it too late?
No! It's not too late!
It's not!
Ken!
Haruko!
I wish you happiness.
Well, guess that means things aren't going
to work out with that voluptuous babe.
Ah! Oh no!
Aw man...
Guess I'll go home and do the laundry.
Damn it!
Darling...
Did the Hollow make you its host?
Dar...ling...
Damn you, when did you enter her body?!
I just got a little lucky, you know?
After you knocked me down and left me there
I happened to run into that fatso.
Hey, Haruko...
Where did you go..?
Then that Ken guy I saw earlier, you...
She is such a stupid woman!
Without even realizing I was inside fatso,
she threw herself all over me!
Just as I thought,
this woman possesses considerable Spirit Energy.
I'll take my time sucking her Spirit Energy from her.
Is that...
so?!
Damn you!
I won't let you
have her!
I'll pound you out of her...
right now!
Blond-boy?
Are you all right, Darling?
Why?
I told you. I promised I'd protect you.
Damn you! How dare you!
Look out!
Oh no...
I suspected you weren't an ordinary human.
So, you were a Mod Soul.
I'll eat you first, then enjoy the other two.
Hey wait!
Just a minute!
Stop!
Getsuga...tensho!
Ichigo.
Jeez... You do such crazy things.
Hey, are you okay?
Blond-boy...
I was scared. So scared!
Ichigo, are you all right?
What is the meaning of this immoral scenery?!
Haruko...
I don't have any idea what's going on.
I'm begging you, Haruko.
Please come back to me!
No way!
I've decided to start a new love life with him!
Right?
W-What?!
Just a minute!
How did that happen?!
Remember, you said you'd protect me?
What?!
That wasn't me!
That bastard Kon must've said that!
How could you?
Did you trick me?!
T-Trick you?!
I've seen enough!
I trusted you!
No, it's not...
I'll hear your lame excuses
Hey, listen!
later when I have time!
Huh? Ken?
Um... Why are we in the park?
Beats me.
Oh Ken!
Sorry. I'm feeling hungry.
Shall we go, Ken?
Yeah.
When we get home, I'll cook lots of tasty dishes.
Okay.
What do you want to eat, Ken?
Everything you make is delicious, Haruko!
Just a minute!
Is it over?
Is this how it ends?!
My youth...
Give me back...my youth, damn it!
Damn it, you get to have all the fun!
There was nothing fun about it!
She's not your type, huh?
Say Ichigo, you never told us your taste in girls.
So what kind of girls do you like?
Well, if I fell in love, wouldn't that person be the one?
Aren't you a hopeless romantic!
Stop laughing at me!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Thirteen Court Guard Squads Rules of Cleaning!
THIRTEEN COURT GUARD SQUADS RULES OF CLEANING
RULE ONE
When moving heavy objects:
No Bankai!
RULE TWO
If an embarrassing object is found:
No Bankai!
RULE THREE
When reprimanding a lazy subordinate:
No Bankai!