Rachel...
Nothing suits a criminal better
than writhing in agony.
My head feels foggy.
I can't breathe.
If I die here...
What will happen then?
Yo.
It's too soon for you to die.
Zack...
We're getting out of here alive, right?
Don't you have that goal of yours?
Yeah.
The mechanism should be solved.
That wasn't there before.
There.
Huh?
A duct in the ceiling opened up.
But not even you can reach—
Can you move okay now?
Then get going!
What are you spacing out for?
Check to see if there's anything in there!
Okay.
Is that...
Find anything?
We have to hurry and open the door.
Damn it, is the poison getting to you?
Give it here!
Shit! Why won't it go in?!
Zack...
The card key...
...got bent.
I can't believe it!
This is so funny, I can't stop laughing!
We've come this far!
It might as well be open!
So open it!
Now, you know I can't do that!
Criminals have to obey the rules.
Right, Zack?
And now... time's up.
All right! The wait is over!
It's the moment you've all been waiting for!
Time for Cathy's special poison gas!
And now, you're going to die!
That bitch!
Zack...
Huh?
The promise we made can't be kept
if we don't get out of here, right?
Huh?! Why are you bringing that up now?
Answer me.
Me getting to the surface alive
is the minimum requirement!
Okay. I'll try.
Is there any way to "try" in this situation?!
I don't know if we'll survive.
Is that still okay?
I don't care. Do it!
If the gas is combustible, this should...
Shit!
You blew the damn thing clean off.
We showed that stupid bitch!
Get a load of this!
Hey, keep it together.
Was I useful to you?
Yeah.
If not for you, that bitch's
poison gas would've killed me.
I see.
Don't you go kicking the bucket here.
Right.
I'm okay.
You're alive after all that?
That's kind of surprising.
I commend you for that.
I opened the door for you
as a special service.
Yeah, no shit! We're out, aren't we?!
You condescending bitch!
Let's... keep moving.
Can't you go any faster?
You except me to keep walking at this pace?!
You can... go on ahead if you want.
I would if I could!
But you know I'll just end up
getting stuck if I'm on my own!
I'll try.
What are you planning to "try"?!
Try or not, when you're
gonna die, you're gonna die!
Maybe that's what you want,
but if you die, what happens to what I want?!
That's... true.
Then... I'll have to try even harder.
I know you're smart, but you're like a doll,
saying the same thing over and over.
What else should I do?
If you're human,
then think about that yourself!
I think... if you can wait a few minutes,
I'll be able to walk straight again.
You think so, huh?
The cameras won't see us here.
Get some rest.
Yeah.
Just like a pure white doll...
So damn boring!
And why am I getting so irritated?
Tch!
So damn boring.
The child just arrived this month,
but I noticed the stench and
realized they were already dead.
So bury it in the yard or whatever.
Is that really wise?
No one's gonna come here to see a bunch
of kids who were dumped here for pennies.
I'm sick of burying bodies.
Why is it all about you now?
Hey, I know. Get that brat to do it.
Nothing better to finish off
a brat than another brat.
Zack?
Huh?
Are you awake?
Are you ready to go now?
Uh-huh.
Then let's go!
I just had a dream that pissed
me off, thanks to you.
Well, well! And where have you two been?
Shut up!
Well, no matter.
Listen, I'll make the offer one last time...
Wouldn't you like to spend the
rest of your life in a cell?
I told you, I'm not gonna do that!
My, but you're no fun.
So you won't become tools
to be used for my entertainment?
Huh?
I hear you two made a rather silly promise.
One that only forces each of
your desires onto the other.
It appears as if you both
want the same thing,
but aren't you both just
deciding to be the other's tool?
I wonder which one of you is
really the tool here, though.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Goodness! You don't know?
But that's okay. I find idiots cute, too.
Well, please continue
to enjoy your punishment!
Damn her!
Zack?
All I did was step on 'em,
and look what happened.
You'd have to be even dumber than
me to choose to stay in a cell.
Let's go.
Don't worry about him.
He's dying anyway.
He's already dead.
Huh?
I see. Let's go.
Yeah.
Hi!
Welcome, and congratulations
on making it this far!
What's this? Looks like you're quite
taken with the dollhouse, Zack.
You bitch...
Zack, be a good boy, okay?
If you keep acting so violent,
you'll never get out of here!
I'm going to have one of you be the navigator,
while the other acts as the worker.
One of you will solve the riddle,
and the other will do as they say.
Easy, right?
Which way do we go?
I'll go this way. You can stay there.
All right, let's begin the game.
Your time is up the moment you die.
Start!
A math problem?
L is 27.
W is 12.
P is 266.
Hey, what do I do here?
Give me a minute.
P is for page, L is for line,
W is for word...
Page 266, line 27,
and the twelfth word is...
"Man."
"Living."
"Sofa."
Are you done yet?!
Put the man doll on the
sofa in the living room.
Tch!
My, what a distasteful movie!
What do you think, Zack?
Don't talk to me!
Aw, that's no fun...
Put the woman doll to the man doll's right.
Not his left. His right.
The right hand holds the knife, and
the left holds the fork. Remember?
Shut your damn mouth!
Zack! See, you can do it if you—
I said, don't talk to me!
Put the doll with the bandages
in front of the woman doll.
Zack, are you listening?
Huh?!
The doll with the bandages.
Put it in front of the woman doll.
My...
You're doing just as
you're told! Very good, Zack!
Give the black plastic
bag to the bandaged doll.
Zack, what's wrong?
You only need to do what you're told to.
That's not so difficult, is it, Zack?
You bitch!
Don't!
If you break it, you'll never
get out of here, Zack.
Put the bag in the bandaged doll's—
I know!
Give the shovel to the bandaged doll.
There's no thinking required.
Zack, do as I say.
Wh-What's that look in your eyes?
That's right.
That's all you need to do.
You're watching that movie again?
I just love seeing these carefree
morons get slaughtered.
So distasteful...
Shut up.
So what happened with that brat?
He didn't want to do it at first,
but when I ordered him to,
he did it without another word.
Even a monster like that can turn into
a good, useful tool if you let him live.
I see.
That's certainly convenient.
That thing's a tool.
Such a tool!
I'm...
Okay, that'll do!
See, Zack? You can do it if you try!
Just like a very convenient tool!
Shut up! I'm not a tool!
Zack...
Oh, no!
After all the work I put into making it...
But that's all right.
I don't need it anymore.
Go ahead and proceed to the next room.
Zack...
He's annoyed.
But all I did was pick the most
efficient way to solve the riddle.
How nice to finally meet you in person!
Hey, you sadistic bitch!
What do you want now?!
How could you speak that way
to a beautiful lady like me?
You never change.
What do we have to do next?
Give yourself a shot, and the door will open.
One contains vitamins,
and the other contains a very dangerous drug!
Huh?! So which one is the vitamins?
I'm not telling you. In fact, I forgot.
Inject every last drop,
and I'll open the door for you!
On that note, I wish you
the very best of luck!
Can you tell which one's bad?
Um...
I figured. I can't tell, either.
Should I give myself both of them?
Huh?!
You think you're gonna be okay if you do?!
I don't know.
Do you want to take them instead?
You know damn well I don't!
If you don't want to, then I will.
I don't know what'll happen, though.
And what's gonna happen if you die?!
The promise you made to me won't be kept.
Other than that, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Right, I forgot. You actually want to die.
It was dull of me to ask.
Dull...
That bitch was right.
You and I are both just like tools.
I don't know what I swore to God,
and maybe you'll be satisfied as
long as you get to die, but me...
Hey...
Can you even have a good look on
your face when you want to die?
Looking at that dead expression
of yours pisses me off!
The idea of being used as a tool
by a doll is boring as hell!
But now...
I'll let you use me just as you want.
Don't!
Let's go.
Zack...
Shit... My head is spinning.
Quit flashing through my mind like that!
Zack...
Are you okay?
I wanna kill you...
I wanna kill you! I wanna
kill you! I wanna kill you!
It's so bad, I feel like I'm gonna go crazy!
That's fine with me.
Oh, is that right?!
But... is it okay with you?
What?!
You haven't made it out of here yet.
And...
I still have the same dull face, don't I?
Are you trying to threaten me now?!
No.
You're the one who swore to God for me,
so it's your promise, too.
I won't give you orders right now.
I won't ask any favors.
I'm just asking you this...
Is it okay with you?
No matter how dull the look on your face is,
it's damn hard to hold myself back.
I mean, if I could hold back,
I wouldn't be in this
situation to begin with.
But even I can't stand lies.
You get what I mean, don't you?
Good girl.
So c'mon, I'm begging you...
Don't let me kill you just yet.