What the hell’s going on, damn it!
What’s happening that
I don’t know about?!
Isn’t there...
anything I can do?!
Here's some advice.
Act now while you can.
That's if you want to
protect your family.
You have reached Xcution.
This number is unregistered.
Are you a new member?
Please state your name.
Ichigo...Kurosaki...
Mr. Ichigo Kurosaki?
We were expecting your call.
Welcome to Xcution.
Please redial this number
followed by the digits “00800.”
Huh?
Next, please hang up your phone
before the second ring tone ends.
Your call will be placed
on your third try.
That was a pain in the ass.
Don’t say that.
If I didn’t do that, it’d
be a pain in the ass for me.
I need to talk to you.
I thought so.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t have called.
Kurosaki!
Know anything about Sado?
Your question is too broad.
Know what
about him?
About his condition!
Condition?
Did he catch a cold or something?
Oh…
Then you don’t know, either?
I thought I should tell him about
what happened to Ishida yesterday,
so I went to his class…
Seems Sado hasn’t been
coming to school recently.
I thought you might know
something about him, but…
I see...so you don’t know, either…
Maybe I’ll visit Sado at home
today with a get-well gift…
S-Say…
Would you like to join me, Kurosaki?
Sorry.
I have plans today.
Oh…Okay!
Of course! This was so sudden!
All right, I’ll go and let you
know tomorrow how Sado’s doing!
Yeah, thanks.
Something happened to Chad, too?
What the hell is going on?!
Today’s too soon.
How about tomorrow?
8 p.m. tomorrow.
Come to the front of the
dilapidated apartment
building located at 7-1
Seventh street in Chobara
District, Naruki City.
I’ll hear what you have to say there.
Relax.
I think I’ll be able to help you.
Sado!
Hey!
Sado! You there?!
Maybe he’s not home?
If we’re to assume that Uryu was
attacked by someone going
after humans like themselves,
then it means the next one to be
in danger is either you, or Sado…
No! No! I mustn’t think like that!
I pray that Sado will be back at
school tomorrow feeling better!
Here is some tasty bread!
Enjoy it and get well.
Seventh street…
7-1…
Dilapidated apartments…
This must be the place.
Hey.
Five minutes early…
Very punctual…
Not five minutes.
Three.
So, what did you want to talk about?
My friends were attacked.
So?
I want your help.
To find who did it?
I thought you don’t trust me.
You know about me and about my dad.
You’re no ordinary human.
Think so?
It’s not that I trust you…
But you’re the only guy…
You can ask? Is that it?
Fine.
Follow me.
Although I wish we could’ve
taken care of my request first.
You mean about my dad?
Don’t give me such a scary look.
There’s no need for you
to check on him anymore.
That was just a pretext
to draw your attention.
A pretext?
We’re here.
Slide the card here.
It’s big…
We knocked out five rooms on
each side and three
stories above and below.
One of our members is
a sort of wealthy…
Now then, before we
get to our main topic,
let me tell you our objective.
Your objective?
Yeah…
Our objective in approaching you.
It’s to restore your
Soul Reaper powers.
God, you’re unbelievable!
What kind of person sleeps
in a place like that!
You’re a grown man!
What are you, stupid?
For crying out loud!
You know what it’s like
having to go look for you?!
I never imagined you’d
be in a place like that!
Come to think of it, why did he
send me to find you, anyway?!
Ginjo should do it himself!
Right?!
Hey!
Why don’t you say something!
It’s your fault that
I’m so upset, you know!
Come on! You do think, don’t you?!
Damn you!
Oww!
What’s wrong?
I’m sure you’re not deaf.
Our objective is to restore
your Soul Reaper powers.
You heard right.
But…how?
How are you going to restore them?!
Why’re you doing this?!
For what purpose?!
Who the hell are you people?
Calm down.
I can’t answer your questions
if you ask them all at once.
Sit down.
The night is long.
I’ll explain nice and slow.
Want something to drink?
Why’re you looking at me like that?
I wouldn’t serve a minor alcohol.
You’re not a drinker, right?
You seem more straight-laced
than you look.
Anything you want.
We don’t have a menu, but
we have pretty much anything.
No thanks.
Okay, serve him some orange
juice or something.
Coming up.
We’re humans.
Of course, as you say, we are
not “ordinary” humans.
We’re humans born with
a certain special ability.
Special ability?
Showing you would be faster.
What I just did was draw out
the “soul” of the liquor
in the glass to “help” me drink it.
Our ability is drawing out
the “soul” in an object and
putting that object to use.
You have a puzzled look on your face.
Did you think that only
living things had souls?
Each and every object in
this world has a soul,
not just animals and plants.
It might be tiny,
but a telephone pole, a chair,
even a glass, possesses a soul.
Ever felt like you can
perform much better than
usual when using a tool you’re
comfortable working with?
That shows you understand
that tool’s “soul.”
An object’s soul is imbued
with the power to help its user.
We have the ability to draw that out,
give it a boost with our own soul,
and turn it into a greater power.
I can draw out the soul of asphalt
and augment its repulsive
force to jump higher…
With a liquid, as you just saw,
I can make it leap into my mouth
or make it support my feet
so that I can stand on water.
And, if it is an object I am
familiar and compatible with,
I can even change its form.
In my case,
it’s this necklace.
What’s happening?
Like so.
We call this ability “Fullbring.”
Fullbring?
I’m back!
Riruka.
You’re back earlier than I expected.
Did you find him?
I sure did!
Hey, that’s your sword glowing
over there, isn’t it?
What’s it doing out? Are you stupid?!
God, it’s so dark in here!
Add more lights right now!
I can’t see a thing!
I have no plans to add lights.
Put on some glasses…
I hate glasses!
But I hate contacts even more!
As soon as I put contacts
in they make my eyes dry!
‘Cuz I have big eyes!
Nobody asked...
Who is that?
Riruka Dokugamine.
She’s one of us.
What?!
Who’s there?!
I’ll introduce you later.
Now hurry up and bring him inside.
Don’t boss me around!
Hey, come on in!
What?!
Chad!
Ichigo…
What are you doing here?!
You haven’t even been
coming to school…
So why? What the hell is going on!
You bastard!
Calm down, Ichigo.
How can I be calm?!
Explain!
Depending on your answer, I…
Calm down.
Don’t make me say it a third time.
If you’ll hear me through,
you’ll understand.
Sit.
You too, Chad.
What?
You guys know each other?!
I wasn’t aware of that!
Did you know that, Ginjo?!
Don’t tell me I was the
only one kept in the dark?!
A drink for Chad, too.
Ignoring me?!
Wait!
Ichigo? You mean that’s
Ichigo Kurosaki there?!
Turn up the lights! I
can’t see his face!!
Later.
Why?!
Okay…
Now that everyone’s here, let’s
get down to the main topic…
All right, now I’m so pissed!
Show me your face!
He’s so hot!
Hey, are you okay?
I’m…
I’m not okay...
Ignore her.
Ichigo, let’s talk
about our main topic.
Uh, right…
Before you do that, Mr. Ginjo,
would you mind putting the sword away?
Good idea.
Be sure to pay for the
floor tiles later.
Good idea…
Do you understand our power now
that you’ve seen it
with your own eyes?
Yeah…
Good.
Now we can move on.
Do you know why a Hollow
has a hole in its chest?
What’re you talking about?
The pain of not being
saved by a Soul Reaper
tears out its heart and leaves a hole…
But where does that heart go?
The lost heart becomes its mask.
Not just its mask.
A Hollow’s unique appearance
and unique powers
are all created from the
heart that was torn out.
All of our parents were attacked
by Hollows before we were born.
Vestiges of Hollow powers were left
behind in the mothers
who were attacked...
The power inside of us when we were born
was more like that of a Hollow
rather than of a Soul Reaper.
We found our power loathsome...
Ichigo, you once possessed
Hollow powers yourself.
You must understand how we feel.
We want to rid ourselves
of this loathsome power...
Over the course of many years,
we gradually gathered
others with like powers.
And that led us to a discovery.
With our exact opposite...
That is, someone who possesses
both Soul Reaper and human powers,
we can exchange powers.
Are you saying...
There was someone…
One other person who, like you,
was born of a Soul Reaper
and a human being.
By yielding our powers to that person,
a number of our members in the past
were able to return to
being ordinary humans.
Do you understand?
For us to return to
being ordinary humans,
it is necessary for you to regain
your Soul Reaper powers...
That’s not the answer I want to hear.
What?
I want to know what’s happening
to me and my friends.
Whether I regain my Soul
Reaper powers or not...
is beside the point.
So you’re saying you don’t
want your Soul Reaper powers?
Crap, I left something
at Ginjo’s place.
I better call him…
You have reached Xcution.
Yes, hi, I left something at…
Mr. Ichigo Kurosaki?
Yeah, I left something…
“00800.”
I have to do this over again?!
Xcution Dictionary!
Today, I’ll introduce our members.
Giriko Kutsuzawa
Giriko Kutsuzawa!
He pisses me off sometimes because
I can’t tell what he’s thinking!
Jackie Tristan
Jackie Tristan!
The way she dresses to flaunt her
figure pisses me off big time!
Yukio
Yukio!
The way this kid talks back
at me really pisses me off!
Riruka Dokugamine
And...
Riruka Dokugamine...
A troublesome woman who can’t
speak her honest feelings.
God, you piss me off!