Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Wow! A frog, a frog!
That hurts!
Why did you do that
out of the blue?!
I should ask you the same thing.
We just got here, and already
you're going after frogs?
Get serious!
Okay, I got it!
I was just looking at them!
Listen.
I brought you two with me
to the World of the Living
so we can quickly capture
those Sword Beasts.
Stop fooling around.
Let's go.
Yeah, I know.
What's wrong, Snake?
We're splitting up to
look for them, right?
We can't split up if
you don't remove this.
You won't fool around, will you?
I won't. I absolutely won't.
It's near by!
Let's go!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Roar…
Not good enough!
The same goes for you!
Damn it!
You're not getting away!
He's fast!
Snake is in that direction.
He's finished!
Damn it!
Snake! There he goes!
Hey!
Look at this, Monkey!
I caught a big fish…
Huh?
Out of the way!
Damn it.
What are you doing, snake?!
No matter. He's injured.
He can't have gone far.
Honestly…
This always happens
when I remove your chain.
You know what to
expect afterwards, right?
Anyway, let's go after him.
Yes.
What's her problem?
It's not often
I get to move on my own.
I can have a little fun, can't I?
Is he injured?!
In that case,
I can handle him by myself!
Hey!
He found me.
Why don't you give up?
I'm finally able to be on my own.
I'm not going to give that up!
On your own?
Is it really that great?
That's right.
Being on your own
is great, boy.
You get to roam freely
at your own will.
A miracle we could usually
not have experienced.
A miracle?
That's right.
Come on, spare me.
If you do, you can also
become your own man.
If you capture me,
you'll be restrained again!
You know what to
expect afterwards, right?
Wait!
Damn it.
He got away again.
Why are you just
standing there?!
Well… Umm…
You didn't let him go, did you?
Sh-Shut up!
I didn't let him escape!
I have no choice.
I'm sorry, Snake.
Wait a second!
I don't want to be
chained up all the time!
But you're clearly being
a hindrance, Snake.
You're calling me a hindrance?!
Do you really want to
finish this mission
and become a regular
Zanpakuto that badly?!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm finally able to be on my own.
I'm not going to give that up!
I'm finally able to
move around on my own!
I don't want to be
connected to you again!
You bastard!
Stop.
Not now.
I can't stick with them!
I'm my own man!
My own?
Being on my own means…
That's right!
I can do anything I want!
All right! What's the first thing
I want to do?
I've always wanted to
eat all I wanted
without anyone
getting mad at me!
I'm digging in!
Wait one second!
What do you want?
Are you kidding me?!
You can't eat that without paying!
Huh?
What's wrong with
eating what I want?
I'll pummel you if you interfere!
Excuse me!
There's a kid who's trying to
eat without paying!
You idiot!
Don't draw attention to me!
I can't have Monkey and Renji
find out about this!
What's wrong?
A strange kid is
trying to steal rice balls…
There's no one there.
Huh?
Jeez…
What's that kid's problem?
Being your own man is great!
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want!
I can't do this when
I'm with Monkey!
Excuse me.
I'd like this chicken breast
and a pack of eggs.
Okay.
Chicken breast and eggs.
– Here you go.
– Hey!
– Thank you.
– Give me this chicken leg and eggs!
Thank you very much.
And what would you like to order?
– Hey! Old man!
– Let's see, I'll have
– I want this chicken leg and eggs!
– fifteen chicken wings for tonight.
– You got it, pretty lady!
– Hey, old lady!
I was here first!
– Why are you cutting in line?
– Oh, you're so flattering!
All right, you can add
those breast meats there too.
Okay!
Can't they see me?
Then…
How could that kid see me?
Is that so?
This soft serve is
on the firmer side.
The soft serve is hard.
– What is that?
– Doesn't it look delicious?
I don't know what it is,
but it all looks delicious.
What's wrong, Karin?
Huh? Well, it's that kid
from the convenience store…
Huh? A kid?
Yeah, this strangely dressed kid.
Strangely dressed?
Hmm… There isn't anyone.
Oh, I get it.
Only I can see him.
Hey!
That kid from earlier!
You're a kid too!
Shut up! I'm not a kid!
Hey, who are you talking to?
A strangely-dressed kid.
Who're you calling
strangely dressed?!
And you're a kid too!
Why hello,
strangely-dressed person.
Hey! Over here!
Are you hungry?
You're drooling.
I-I'm not drooling!
Anyway,
that's none of your business!
Oh yeah? Then never mind.
Let's go, Yuzu.
Okay.
What's the deal with that kid?!
L-Like I'd ever eat that!
I'll never eat it!
I don't need that kid
to give me things!
Hey!
What is it?
Well… Umm… Uhh…
Do you want more rice balls?
N-No way!
Who'd want those?!
Besides, I haven't eaten it!
I'm amazed you can
tell such an obvious lie.
Hey, about
the strangely-dressed person…
Maybe he's still hungry?
What?
Do ghosts get hungry too?
I'm not a ghost!
I'm a Zanpakuto!
Zanpakuto?
Okay…
Hey, how about we do this?
Let's invite the strangely-dressed
person to our house!
What?!
What's wrong?
Are you that worried
about Snake?
That's not it.
Then what?
Acting like a Sword Beast…
How pathetic.
You're not very honest with
your feelings, are you?
Renji!
Ichigo!
I thought it was
your Spiritual Pressure.
What's going on?
Oh. You probably heard about it.
We're here to capture
those Sword Beasts.
Oh, Zabimaru's with you?
Huh?
Wasn't there also a kid?
He ran off.
He's probably
somewhere in the area.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's hot, so drink it slowly.
Hey, over here!
Dad and Brother Ichi
aren't here right now,
but if they come back,
I want you to hide somewhere.
I'm sure that Brother Ichi
can see you.
Who's Brother Ichi?
Our older brother.
Do you always hang
around other people?
So what if we do?
It's so lame.
I'm my own man.
I can do anything
when I'm on my own!
Yet you couldn't
get anything to eat.
Besides, there's nothing cool
about being on your own.
What?!
You get to be your own man!
Of course it's cool!
Where are
your mother and father?
I don't have any.
I don't have any!
I told you, I'm a Zanpakuto!
I don't really understand.
Here! This is our brother's flan,
but you can have it.
You're hungry, right?
I keep telling you, I'm over here!
Why do you think
I'm over there?!
I-It's delicious!
I've never had anything so good!
By the way, what is your name?
It's Zabimaru. What's yours?
Karin.
This is…
I'm Yuzu.
Karin and Yuzu, huh?
All right!
So what shall we play?!
I said, I'm over here!
I can't do this!
What? You can't?
Then…
I don't get it at all!
I guess ghosts can't play games.
I told you, I'm not a ghost!
Did you know?
Cooking in a rice cooker
is really popular now!
I have a soft spot
for popular things,
so I was quick to pick this up!
– We're going to make Dongpo pork
– Is he enjoying it?
– with a rice cooker!
– Seems like it.
– You may think you're cooking rice,
– We should have watched TV
– but you're actually
– from the beginning.
– making Dogpo pork!
– Yeah…
The finished Dongpo pork
– comes out round!
– Amazing…
It's supposed to have corners!
Hey…
How does this thing work?
I'm home!
What's going on?
Are they both sleeping?
I can't eat anymore.
Hey!
Huh?
Why are you in my house?!
And who are you?
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki!
The Substitute Soul Reaper!
Substitute Soul Reaper?
I don't know why
you're in my house,
but Renji and the others
are worried about you.
How do you know about Renji?!
You're Renji's Zanpakuto, right?
Aren't you supposed
to go back to him?!
Shut up!
That's none of your business!
What's wrong?
How dare you bring me
to this place!
This isn't funny at all!
Hey!
Wait!
Karin!
Damn it!
Everyone's ganging up on me.
Hey…
You!
I see you're still on your own.
Well?
Are you enjoying your freedom?
Thanks to you,
I was able to buy the time
I needed to heal my wounds.
All that's left is to take
all of you down one by one!
So that's what your plan was!
I can take you on by myself!
Zabimaru?!
Roar!
Where do you think
you're looking at?!
Not bad.
But…
Don't underestimate me!
What's this?!
I told you!
I can take you on by myself!
Damn it…
Zabimaru!
That kid!
Karin!
Don't worry.
That was just to scare you.
But if you don't stop attacking,
she's done for.
Damn it…
You fool!
In the end, you got to experience
the freedom of being on your own.
You should thank me!
You sure are a stubborn kid.
But I won't give up
my freedom to anyone!
I don't need some
stupid master or friends!
I feel sorry for you.
It's pretty nice being with people.
Don't make me laugh!
Die!
Good job on keeping him busy!
Now leave the rest to us!
Right?
It took some time,
but it seems letting you go out
on your own did pay off.
Right, Snake?
Karin!
You?
She's all right.
She'll wake up eventually.
Thanks.
Are you going?
Listen.
Don't tell Karin or Yuzu
about me.
Huh?
Promise me.
What's wrong?
Where's Zabimaru?
You're finally up.
Brother Ichi, where's Zabimaru?
What are you talking about?
No.
It's nothing.
Are you all right with that?
Yeah, I'm fine!
I'm just a Zanpakuto.
Besides, Monkey would
be sad if I'm not around!
What are you saying?!
Let's go home.
Yuzu, do you know what happened
to the flan I left in the fridge?
Huh? W-Well…
Oh, Dad ate it.
What?! I'm going to pound
that moustachio!
K-Karin?!
It's no big deal.
Besides, Dad was begging for
some family time, remember?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
The three of us are best together!
We'll always be together!
– Yeah!
I want to go to the bathroom.
– I'm going too!
Give me a break!