Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Ichigo!
Hey Ichigo! Answer! Hey!
Someone's coming!
Three…maybe more.
Let's retreat for now.
We can't let them find us.
Yes!
That's…
Lieutenant Abarai!
Are you all right?! Sir!
It can't be… Abarai can't have lost.
His opponent seems to
have gotten away.
Shall we give chase?
No, first we must get Abarai treated.
Get a stretcher.
We're taking him back
to the barracks.
Healing power?
Without using any medicine?
No, it's different with us.
With other Soul Reapers,
their spiritual power is mostly for combat.
But those of us in Squad 4
have healing power as well.
Although…
that's about all we can do.
I see… And…?
How is Ichigo?
It's very bad.
He took direct hits from
a Zanpaku-to of a Lieutenant…
It's to be expected.
Normally, he'd have died instantly.
He has an unbelievable will to live.
I'll heal him without fail.
Please give me some time.
I'll heal him in one night.
That's…!
When I found him,
he was already in this condition.
If only I'd found him sooner
and assisted his fight.
Don't blame yourself, Kira.
In any case,
I'll contact Squad 4.
I'll ask for emergency relief.
There's no need.
Captain Kuchiki!
Put him in prison.
B-But… Abarai fought Ryoka by himself.
And yet…
No excuses.
If he entered a fight alone,
defeat is absolutely forbidden.
I have no use for a fool who
did not understand that.
He is an eyesore.
Take him away.
P-Please wait! How can you say…
– Lieutenant Abarai…
– Stop!
Kira!
My deepest apologies!
My deepest apologies.
Hinamori, let's follow his orders,
and take Abarai to prison.
But…!
Oh, so scary.
Captain Ichimaru!
Why'd he have to talk like that…huh?
He's as scary as ever…
the Captain of Squad 6.
Well, don't worry.
I'll call Squad 4.
Really?
Of course. Come with me, Izuru.
Yes sir!
Thank you very much.
Wow, Abarai got messed up
pretty good.
Hitsugaya!
Hey, hey… I'm a Captain, too.
And you're gonna address me
like that?
Never mind that!
How come all you Captains
creep around so silently?!
And why are you
here anyway, Hitsugaya?!
Yes…why are you here?
Without your Lieutenant?
I came to warn you.
Warn?
Be careful of Squad 3.
Squad 3? You mean, Kira?
I mean Ichimaru.
But I'm not sure about Kira, either.
The alarm sounds quite
conveniently these days.
I don't understand…
just what you mean.
And you think you
can get away with that?
You should not underestimate me.
Anyway, it won't hurt to be careful.
Especially…
The situation…is critical.
This means that we are
short one Lieutenant
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
We can no longer leave this
to the lower-ranked members.
Therefore, in view of the situation,
I will not discipline…
Ichimaru for his independent actions earlier.
Thank you very much.
Furthermore, I will allow senior officers,
including Lieutenants,
to carry their Zanpaku-to at all times
as well as allow full release of their
Zanpaku-to in the Court, as in wartime.
Carry the Zanpaku-to all the time, huh?
Full release as in wartime, huh?
I con’t be happier.
If someone hadn't allowed
Ryoka to escape,
we wouldn't be talking about this now.
C'mon, stop that talk.
Yes, 'cuz he'll be my prey from now.
Men…
This is all-out war.
Oh, you're awake, Ichigo.
Hanataro…I…
Please don't move.
Your wounds haven't closed yet.
Wounds?
Oh right…I fought Renji…
Ichigo!
Thanks, Hanataro. I'll be fine now.
What are you saying?
You can't get up!
Chad and the others
don't know where Rukia is.
I must go and…
Ichigo! You can't!
You see? You're not recovered yet!
If you go out in your condition,
you're certain to die!
Ichigo!
If I can knock him out like that,
how can he be all right?
Sleep until you're healed, idiot!
Ganju! Oh no…
he's got another wound now.
You're so rough, Ganju.
Shut up! I stopped him, didn't I?!
Don't complain about how I did it.
But…
I didn't think that the slash across
his left shoulder and chest
would be this shallow.
I thought it would definitely
be a fatal wound…
Was it because of…
that mask inside his clothes?
To be able to stop
Lieutenant Abarai's slash…
I wonder what it is? And…
This mask looks too much
like a Hollow.
Doesn't it, Ichigo?
Excuse me…
Huh?
Can you tell me
what's going on outside?
Just a little is fine…
We don't know
the details either.
But we've heard that
Lieutenant Abarai was taken down.
Huh?! Renji?
I'm done treating Lieutenant Abarai's
wounds for today.
Thank you very much.
Abarai…
Why did you attack the Ryoka alone?
Does it have anything to do
with Rukia?
Owwee! You!
You don't have to get so serious!
We can't afford to get
hurt practicing, you know!
Stupid! Unless we're serious,
practicing is useless.
You just didn't pay attention.
Then I'll be your opponent, next.
Kira…!
It's no fun beating a girl, is it?
What are you saying, Kira?!
Are you making fun of women?
Oh, no…nothing like that!
Quit acting so embarrassed!
Well, I wasn't thinking of
you as an opponent,
but at least I won't be bored.
I'll make you eat your words.
You're good, Abarai!
So are you! You've improved, Kira!
Huh? Kira, just a minute.
Rukia!
Abarai!
Abarai…
Lieutenant Hinamori! Special wartime
orders were just announced.
Special wartime orders?
– Special wartime orders!
Hurry! Let's go!
First: All senior officers
including Lieutenants
will be permitted to
wear their swords at all times.
Second: They will be permitted to
release their Zanpaku-to as in wartime.
Those are the orders from
Squad 1 Captain and Captain General of
the 13 Court Guard Squads
Shigekuni Genryusai Yamamoto.
Understood.
Wartime orders.
Permission to wear swords…
Why did it come to this?
They don't have to let us carry Zanpaku-to.
Peace is all that I want.
And…Hitsugaya's warning…
I'm worried.
Be careful of Squad 3…
Especially…
Captain Aizen…
What's the matter?
Is something wrong, Hinamori?
I'm sorry…
What is it at this hour?
Dawn is about to break.
I know full well that
this is very rude…
but may I have a quick word?
I promise not to make any blunders.
So please…
Do you think I would turn you
away simply for rudeness?
N-No…
Do I seem so heartless these days?
N-No…not at all!
Then come inside.
Today was a very difficult day.
Talk to your heart's content.
Owweee…
Are you awake, Ichigo?
Damn that Ganju!
You remembered?
Naturally! That guy…
laying his hand on
an injured man!
But I'm glad Ganju was able to
stop you earlier.
Otherwise, you would have
started to bleed again.
I know… I gotta cool my head, huh?
It's better if you lie down for a bit longer.
No one will come after you here.
So rest assured.
I wonder what happened to him…
that Renji?
Huh? Oh…
I'm not really sure of the details…
But he would normally be sent
to emergency relief.
I see.
Yes.
What's the matter?
Didn't you have something to talk about?
Err, yes… I…
How is Abarai's condition?
Oh… his life isn't in danger.
I'm glad.
Don't worry about the
captains' meeting.
Captain Kuchiki asked that
Abarai be discharged,
but there were objections
and so he backed off.
Once his wounds heal,
he'll be able to return
to his squad.
By chance, were you the
one who objected, Captain Aizen?
Not only me. He's an excellent officer
and liked by everyone.
There's not one person in
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
who would rejoice at his dismissal.
Yes!
Captain Aizen…
Yes?
I won't disturb you…
So may I sit here and watch you?
Or is it an imposition?
No, I don't mind.
Stay as long as you like.
Yes!
Darn!
I'm sorry! I…I fell asleep!
Huh?
Oh no! Look at the time!
Geez, I wish the Captain
would've waken me up.
I wonder if I'll make it
to the meeting on time…?
I'll take a shortcut…!
There, I think I made it…
What was that scream?
It came from the Eastern Wall!
That was Hinamori's voice…
Hinamori!
Hinamori! What's wrong? Hinamori!
Whaa--?! I-It can't be…!
Captain Aizen!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Thank you, Hanataro.
I'm fully recovered.
It's about the only thing I can do.
As long as we have Hanataro,
you're fine.
So Ichigo, go and get all cut up.
Absolutely not!
– Go for it! Just go!
– No thanks!
Just get cut up!