What?!
Are you ready to die now?
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
nando demo umarekawaru no
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Cascada.
Ryusenka!
I hold within me the resolve of those
who sacrificed their lives.
I know that...
I suffered a great deal
of damage, but...
You probably can't fight at full
strength with those injuries.
And that's exactly why I will...
Such a waste of effort.
What is this?
My Hyorinmaru is the strongest
ice-snow type Zanpakuto...
All water is my weapon.
All the heavens are
under my control.
Cero...
Not bad!
You too.
I must say, it's so much bigger
and faster than the Cero
of other Espada I'd heard about.
It's virtually impossible to
avoid getting hit by that.
Is that so?
But you know, I took the trouble
of showing you my Cero...
You could at least show me a bit
of what you've got, Captain.
Don't flitter around so much, especially
with that flashy outfit of yours.
It's making you look silly.
Cero.
He fired without a gesture?!
I said stop dodging...
What the hell?
What just happened?
What is this?
It's called Tenso Jyurin,
Weather Manipulation...
Though it's one of the basic
abilities of Hyorinmaru,
at the same time,
it is the most powerful.
My powers are not yet mature.
I realize that better
than anyone.
That is why I didn't want to use
this power in a Bankai state.
Or rather, I couldn't.
I did not have confidence...that
I could fully control it.
But thanks to the fact that the ice flowers
in the back have largely scattered,
it would seem that those
fears were needless.
Let me ask your name, Espada.
I am Espada Number 3,
Tier Halibel.
Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
Here goes.
What?!
This Spiritual Pressure, it's...
It's Captain Hitsugaya's...
Get lost, Kira.
Out of my sight and
even farther.
If you're within ten miles of me...
I can't guarantee I won't
kill you by mistake!
Hyoten Hyakkaso!
Cascada!
Hirvi-
What is this?!
Hyoten Hyakkaso.
Anything that comes in
contact with that snow
freezes instantaneously into
a flower-like shape.
By the time the flowers blossom
in the hundreds...
your life will have faded.
Sorry about that...
I can't let you avenge
your subordinates.
Toshiro...
He did it!
Yes!
Quickly, Kira! Return
to healing the others!
Yes, sir!
And now, there are
two Espada left.
Whatever it takes, we must at
least get rid of the Espada
before those three
enter the battle!
Hmph, Halibel...
Losing to such a lowly opponent.
What a disgrace.
What destructive force!
What's with that old man?
He not only has outrageous power,
but he even has the speed to
dodge your attack, Captain.
I'd be no match against him.
Don't worry, Omaeda.
Huh? What?
I'm not expecting anything
from you.
Stay there and watch.
No, don't say such things! I'm
quite capable of fighting, too!
That said, I have utterly
no confidence!
What was that just now?
I guess I'll test it...
Go Captain!
It happened again!
When I get within
striking distance,
the speed of my kick suddenly
slows down!
Damn!
Captain!
Don't get flustered.
"Don't get flustered"?
But I can't help it!
Shut up. I'm fine.
Keep that hot and sticky
face away from me.
Although...
It's not as though my
movements are slowed
because my Spiritual Pressure
is being suppressed.
My movements themselves
are slowing down!
Is he controlling gravity?
Or does he have the ability to directly influence
my muscles or my motor coordination?!
Can't figure it out?
You must be bewildered because you
can't decide the nature of my power.
Remember I said that each Espada
signifies an aspect of death?
It is each Espada's beliefs,
their reason for existence,
and at times it relates
to their abilities.
The aspect of death
I signify is "aging."
Aging, means "time."
The largest and most absolute power of death
that stands in the way of all things that exist.
See?
When did he...?!
If I touch you with
intent like this,
that alone is enough to cause
your bones to age.
It's broken!
That can't be!
You can't comprehend it.
That's how death is.
And from here on, until
this battle ends,
your mind will be unable to comprehend
anything that is about to occur.
What?!
Are you ready to die now?
Impudence!
Don't think the captain is your
only opponent, bastard!
Such brave words from
a lieutenant...
But they don't sound
very convincing.
Shut up!
Damn right! I can't
take you head on!
Captain! Let me take care
of your backside support!
Fool.
Huh?
I know what you're thinking.
You figure that if you manage to
take a position outside his range,
you'll be in no danger.
You lack the strength. Not only that, you'll leave
me open to being attacked from behind.
H-H-How could you even
say such a thing?!
I'll do it! I'll show you!
After all, I'm the lieutenant
of Squad 2!
I see...
Then I have a plan.
Plan?
If I recall...
If I touch you with
intent like this,
that alone is enough to
cause your bones to age.
That's what he said.
Then if we attack him in a manner where
he can't touch us or fix his aim,
we may have a chance
of winning.
Omaeda...
Wh-What is it?!
Listen up. I want you on my six.
But make certain not
to get in my way.
I know that!
Are you done with your
strategy meeting?
Can you make it
entertaining this time?
Go!
Above, eh?
I won't let you touch
me that easily!
Behind me... No, that's a trick...
You're below!
Did you think I
wouldn't figure out
that you're using your second-in-command
as a decoy so you,
Captain, could aim for
a finishing blow?!
You fool!
How pathetic.
You boldly used your second-in-command
to deliver the final attack.
I see... That was
quite a fine idea.
However...
It seems he wasn't quite
ready to go all the way.
If he had been willing to die trying,
he might have had a chance.
F-Forgive me, Captain!
I was a fool to expect
anything from you.
Go. Run with everything
you've got.
Is that it for you, Captain?
You fool! Don't be so reckless!
A-Are you all right, Captain?
You didn't escape?
Are you crazy?
I'm lieutenant of Squad 2!
Even if you tell me to run, it's
my duty to assist you Captain!
In any case, stop looking
so hot and sticky.
It's an annoyance when we're
fighting close together.
M-My face has nothing
to do with this!
So you came inside my range...
It would seem both of you
are prepared to die.
Then it's about time...
I put an end to this circus.
Rot...
Arrogante.
Wh-What?
What is that form?!
His footstep is rotting and crumbling
away the rooftop!
I told you earlier...
I signify aging.
All things near me
age...and die off.
B-Bastard! What's
he up to now?!
What are you doing?!
Run, Omaeda!
Damn it!
You fool!
You're no match for him!
What?
Neither are you, Captain.
Suffer the Dying Breath...
Respira.
Omaeda!
Cut off my arm!
Captain...
Hurry!
Do you want me to get killed?!
Omaeda!
Damn it!
How amusing...
It seems even Soul Reapers
are afraid of death.
Barragan, was it?
I'm told subcutaneous fat
decreases with age.
Yes, and?
Can you age my subordinate's
subcutaneous fat?
Uh... Captain?
I can guarantee him
a 20kg weight loss.
No!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Captain Hitsugaya's Hyoten
Hyakkaso was awesome.
Brrr... It's freezing...
Whew... It's nice and cozy in here
thanks to a certain Head Captain
surrounding us with flames.
Lord Aizen, your tea is ready.
Oh, mind pouring
me a cup, too?
DAMN YOU... TOSHIRO HITSUGAYA