Yes...
This is inexcusable, isn't it, Hogyoku?
This is the Final...
Getsugatensho.
Impossible!
He caught it?!
Why so surprised?
Does it scare you?
That something you can't comprehend
happened right before your eyes?
Hado Number 90: Kurohitsugi!
Now that I transcend both
Hollows and Soul Reapers,
this is Kurohitsugi with a full incantation!
You don't seem to realize, do you?
My power is greater than the
power you have right now.
What an odd feeling.
When I backed away from
you in our last battle,
you asked me why.
But now you're doing the exact same thing.
So let me ask you the same question.
Why did you back away just now?
I see.
You're pleased that you stopped my sword?
Are you pleased that you overcame my Kido?
Are you pleased that you
put a scar on my body?
Don't be so full of yourself, human!
Yes...
This is inexcusable, isn't it, Hogyoku?
That I
let a human get the better of me.
Ichigo...
I see.
You took my attack with so little damage.
However, that left arm of
yours is no longer usable.
Can you hear me, Ichigo Kurosaki?
Indeed, for a moment,
you broke the boundary between Hollows and
Soul Reapers to become a transcendent being.
But that power is no more!
Not a trace of it remains!
You're not even worth trying
to understand any more.
I, a true transcendent being, will kill you.
By killing you,
I will completely break free from both
insignificant Soul Reapers and Hollows alike.
It's over!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Over, you say?
Is this all you've got?
Let's end this already, Aizen.
I've grown sick...of your
arguments.
I'll show you.
This is the Final...
Getsugatensho!
What is...
that form?!
You still refuse to stay down,
Ichigo?
I told you I wouldn't go down.
Not until you tell me what
the Final Getsugatensho is.
I said I have no intention of telling you!
What is this?
If he were serious about defeating me,
he could've done it at the very start.
There was that great a difference
between our powers.
If he had no serious
intention of telling me,
he should stop fighting
and keep himself hidden.
It would have been easy
for him to just do that.
What is this?
Why is it that I only sense sadness
flowing from his blade?
You've realized it.
The only way to acquire the
Final Getsugatensho is to accept my blade.
There's... no pain.
Of course not.
I, Tensa Zangetsu, am originally you.
If you accept me,
there can be no pain when I run you through.
Why...are you crying?
Ichigo.
Do you recall what I said
when we started this fight?
Don't misunderstand, Ichigo.
What you want to protect
is not what I want to protect.
I do.
What I wanted to protect was...
you, Ichigo.
What do you mean?
The answer
will be conveyed directly through this blade,
along with the technique's secret.
Ichigo...
If you use this technique, you will...
The Final Getsugatensho is...
me...
becoming Getsuga itself.
The Final Getsugatensho...
If I use this technique,
I will lose all of my Soul Reaper powers.
That's what "final" means.
I still can't sense his power.
I have evolved into a being far
beyond that of a Soul Reaper.
Just as two-dimensional beings
can never interact with
three-dimensional beings,
no Soul Reaper or human could
detect my Spiritual Pressure
unless I deliberately brought down my
powers to their level of awareness.
Could it...possibly be that he...
is at an even higher level than myself?
Absurd!
That couldn't possibly be!
A mere human cannot surpass me!
That can't be!
Mugetsu.
If you use this technique,
you will lose all of your Soul Reaper powers.
Farewell, Ichigo.
He is still able to regenerate?
Crap...
My Soul Reaper powers...
are disappearing.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
You lose.
Observe.
My Zanpakuto is fading away.
You should know what that means.
The Hogyoku has determined
that I have no need for a Zanpakuto!
Like you, I have become one
with the Zanpakuto and its powers.
In fact, you no longer have that power,
while I will reach a level
far beyond that of yours!
It's over!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
What is this?!
Kido?!
But when was I attacked?!
Seems it's finally taking effect.
Mr. Urahara!
Kisuke Urahara, is this your doing?!
Yes.
Before you were able to
completely transformed,
when you were most vulnerable,
I planted that Kido into another Kido
and shot it into your body.
It's a seal.
I figured that once you
fused with the Hogyoku,
killing you would be nearly impossible.
So I invented a new Kido to seal you off.
Is that so? I hate to disappoint you.
See!
At this moment, I am about
to evolve even further.
You can't seal me off...
with this level of Kido!
What?!
What's happening?
It is the Hogyoku's will.
The reason the seal that I shot
into your body is only taking effect now
is because your powers have weakened.
It was thanks to Kurosaki.
It was able to take effect
because he fought this hard
and pushed you to your limit.
The Hogyoku is saying that it does
not recognize you as its master.
That's absurd.
That can't be.
There's no way!
Kisuke Urahara!
I despise you!
With your great intellect,
why won't you take action?!
Why do you subjugate yourself to that thing?!
That thing?
You mean the Soul King?
I understand now.
You saw, didn't you?
Without the existence of the Soul King,
Soul Society would split apart.
The Soul King is the keystone.
Without the keystone in place,
it would fall apart easily.
That's how the world is.
That's an argument a loser would make!
A victor must always speak
of how the world
should be rather than how the world is!
I...
Ichigo.
It's over, isn't it, Ichigo?
Say, Mr. Urahara.
The training in the Precipice World has made
me a little bit older than my friends, right?
I suppose you could say that.
Yeah?
It's not a bad feeling
being older than the others.
To put it another way,
it also means you're an old
man compared to the others.
What?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers...
You there.
Wake up.
You'll catch a cold
sleeping in such a place.
We work for a heavenly place called the
Department of Research and Development.
I'm up!
A stranger with great boobs...
I mean, beauty!
Now, blam!
And an extra blam!
Heh... You fell for it.
Using their devious plot,
the Department of Research and Development
has now taken me prisoner.
What will happen to me now?!
WILL NOT CONTINUE
What?!