It’s cold.
Oh that’s right…
I fell asleep yesterday after that.
Ichigo’s not here, so maybe I’ll
go back to sleep in his bed.
She’s gone!
Gone!
Gone! Gone! Gone!
Gone! Gone! Gone! Gone!
She’s gone!
Where’d she go?!
The typical winter pressure
system will make way
for mostly sunny forecasts
today in the Pacific region.
Temperatures will be at
average highs in most areas.
What the hell are you doing?!
What’re you doing up?!
No one saw you, I hope!
Listen…
I brought you here without
telling any of the people here!
Don’t take one step
outside this room, okay?
Think what would happen
if they found out
I brought a young girl here!
They’ll think I’m a
pervert and kick me out!
They’d do that to me!
Is something wrong, Brother?
PERVERT
My name’s Kon.
You probably don’t remember
but I helped you yesterday.
What’s your name?
Where are you from?
I won’t tell you.
Huh?
I said I won’t tell you!
Go away! Pervert!
Who’re you calling a pervert?!
Don’t come near me, pervert!
Keep your hands off me, pervert!
What’s the matter with everyone?
Were they brainwashed by someone?
No, it didn’t seem that way.
Ichigo… Ichigo…
Rukia…
Hey, would you like something to eat?
Is there something you’d like?
Can’t you hear me, stupid?!
Oww…!!
Where…
Where is this place, stupid?
What’s with the “stupid”?
You’re at my place in Karakura Town.
Well, it’s sorta my place.
Karakura Town…
So, where are you from?
How many times do I need
to say to make it clear?
You don’t need to know.
Are you not only a pervert,
but an idiot as well?
Shut up!
I’m not stupid, or a pervert!
I not only helped you, I even
looked after you, yet…
Brother.
You’ve been making
way too much noise.
Is something the matter?
I’m coming in…
Wait…Wait just a second!
What’s the matter?
N-Nothing!
Doing my vocal exercises.
I’m leaving for school.
You’d better hurry too,
or you’ll be late.
R-Right!
She almost found out.
Perverted freak.
I didn’t…mean to…
Perverted freak!
I told you, I didn’t
mean to do anything!
First of all, I’m not interested
in little kids like you!
If you’re not interested,
why’d you help me?
I don’t recall asking for your help.
Stupid perverted freak!
What an unlikable brat.
I can’t imagine Ichigo
could possibly be
involved in this incident.
Yes, me neither.
But then how do you
explain that evidence?
What is the important item?
We found it near the area where we were
supposed to rendezvous with
Captain Kurotsuchi’s group.
I don’t know what connection
it might have to the incident.
This is…
But I believe it warrants
investigation.
A Substitute Soul Reaper Combat Pass?
That is definitely the one I gave him.
It’s unthinkable that anyone
other than Ichigo would have it.
You’re right.
But I believe…
What’s happening?
Reporting!
Substitute Soul Reaper Ichigo Kurosaki,
who was detained as a material
witness in the case
involving the disappearance of Soul
Reapers in the Precipice World,
has disappeared from jail!
Why do I have to run?!
We’re heading to Hakuto Gate
to get us out of the Seireitei!
If I give them a good explanation,
they’ll understand.
Is doing something like
this a good idea?
It’s not…normally.
But don’t you think
something’s wrong?
What did I do, anyway?
I don’t know, either.
I did some checking.
It appears a time gap
has formed between
the Soul Society and the
World of the Living.
Renji!
Ikkaku!
Damn!
Sorry, Ichigo.
You’ll have to return
to jail quietly.
You guys too?
I apologize.
Our person in charge of the Precipice
World is out doing a survey.
That can’t be helped.
We’ve been in a constant
state of emergency.
Oh, here it is.
We did indeed record
Spiritual Pressure in
the Precipice World during the morning.
Would you like me to compare it to
Ichigo Kurosaki’s Spiritual Pressure?
No, that won’t be necessary.
I’ve no doubt that the
Spiritual Pressure was his.
Did you find out anything?
Oh, Captain Kuchiki. Thank
you for all your hard work.
What do you think you’re doing in the
middle of an emergency deployment?
As you can see…
How about you, Captain Kuchiki?
They‘ll do fine without me.
That’s nice to hear.
Forgive me if I offended you.
Well, guess I’ll go
deploy my men too.
Wait, Isane.
It’s this way, Captain Unohana.
The Senkaimon?
When we came through,
there was a slight variance
in the Spiritual Pressure.
Wait!
Are you sensing something?
No.
I believe I need more time.
Let’s go back.
Yes, ma’am.
We have no intention of killing you
as long as you quietly
turn yourselves in.
Though, I don’t think
that’ll happen.
Tell us one thing, Renji.
Why is Ichigo a suspect?
Your Combat Pass.
My Combat Pass?
Yeah.
It was presented as evidence.
Now that you mention it…
My Combat Pass!
I lost it when the Cleaner attacked
us in the Precipice World.
We found that
your Combat Pass was there
in the Precipice World several days ago
at about the very same time that
Captain Kurotsuchi and
the others disappeared.
What do you mean “several
days ago”?!
We passed through the
Precipice World yesterday,
shortly after noon.
And are you accusing me
of eliminating Captain
Kurotsuchi and the others?
I’m no magician, you know.
Wait, Ichigo.
I’m beginning to understand.
Understand what?
The question of why your Combat Pass
was presented as evidence
even before we left the
World of the Living
is definitely a mystery.
But one thing is clear.
Whoever is responsible
for trying to frame you
is the mastermind behind this incident.
So you’re saying that guy
is manipulating everyone?
I don’t really understand
what’s going on,
but we’re not doing
this because we want to.
But if your resistance
means we can fight again,
that’s just fine with me!
You haven’t lost your
Spirit Energy yet, right?
Before your Spirit Energy is gone,
Let’s have one last fierce fight!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Why’re you doing this, Renji?!
Do you really believe Ichigo
could cause this incident?!
I don’t!
Then why?!
I can’t help myself!
I’m not doing this because I want to!
When…did he become this powerful?
If you’re going to stop us,
you’ll have to fight us!
Rukia!
Stop it, Renji!
Ikkaku!
I have no reason to fight you!
The same goes for me,
but I don’t need a reason
to fight a strong opponent!
Ichigo!
What's the matter?
If you don’t fight back, I can’t
guarantee you’ll keep your life.
Even if you’re the opponent.
He’s not bluffing!
Renji! Why?!
What happened to you?!
Are you guys really under
someone’s control?!
You leave me no choice!
Bankai!
You’re finally going to fight?
Damn it.
Bakudo 73: Tozansho!
What?!
Yoruichi!
Ichigo… Kuchiki…
Let's go.
You saved us, Yoruichi.
We can’t stay here long.
Yeah.
But something’s wrong with them.
I agree.
The look in Renji’s eyes was
dead serious about killing us.
Well, that can’t be helped.
That wasn’t the real Abarai
or the real Madarame.
I see.
What?!
Not real? What do you mean?!
What? Were you fighting without
having realized that?
But…their Spiritual Pressure was
the same as it always was, and…
He’s right.
But they seemed to be much
more powerful than I recall.
Is that so?
Well, they are very
well made, after all.
Well made?
Soul Reapers require a
vessel for their Konpaku
in order to function in
the World of the Living.
In other words, a gigai.
At the same time, bodies that serve as
vessels for a Konpaku exist
in the Soul Society, as well.
In other words, the Soul Society
versions of a gigai, so to speak.
Is that easier to understand?
A Reigai.
REIGAI
Rei…gai?
The Abarai and Madarame you saw earlier
are fakes created by placing
a near-perfect Konpaku
inside near-perfect Reigai.
Although fakes,
they’ve been created so that their
memories, personalities, and thoughts,
nearly everything, are almost
perfect copies of the real thing.
What’s more, I have absolutely
no idea how many Reigai
have currently infiltrated the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
But, I don’t get it.
Wouldn’t those so-called Reigai
be unnecessary in the Soul Society,
where the Konpaku itself
becomes the body?
That’s probably true for
ordinary Soul Reapers.
However, there are those for
whom they are a necessity.
And they are?!
Reigai are indispensable for
development of, and experiments on,
the Soul Candies in the Soul Society.
Then…
The Department of Research
and Development…
It’s probably certain that someone
in Squad 12 is secretly involved.
Ichigo?
Ichigo! Where did he go?!
Probably to Squad 12.
I’ll do something to
throw off security.
Rukia, you rendezvous with
Ichigo to gather information.
Ichigo!
Where are you going?!
I’m storming into Squad 12!
Fool!
You’re not going to
succeed by storming into
the main compound without a plan!
We’ll secretly sneak into Squad 12
and gather as much
information as possible!
All right.
North!
They’re headed for Kokuryo Gate!
Department of Research and Development
Sure is boring.
At least it’s better than getting
some weird additional assignment!
Shut up.
What do you want?
Who is it?
Sorry about that.
What happened to secretly sneaking in?
Is it okay to use such
an obvious Bakudo?
This is no time to debate that!
So what now?
Checking the records of past movement
through the Precipice World.
There should be someone in here that
holds a clue to what’s happening.
Hold on a second.
What is it?
Can you go back a few windows?
That’s…
So it’s that girl?
Gone missing in the
World of the Living;
later found in Karakura Town.
If she refuses capture, elimination…
is authorized?!
Will you get that, Brother?
Okay.
You…
Who are you people?
You are Ichigo Kurosaki’s
Soul Candy, are you not?
You’re very well-informed.
Huh? Aren’t you…
We are from the Seireitei.
We understand that a Soul Reaper
named Nozomi Kujo is here.
We’ve come to take her with us.
Nozomi Kujo?
Take her with you?
Oh, you mean that kid?!
You mean she’s a Soul Reaper?
Hadn’t you heard from either
Substitute Soul Reaper Ichigo
Kurosaki or Rukia Kuchiki?
N-No…I hadn’t heard.
That’s odd.
We were under the
impression that you had.
No, no!
I’ll gift-wrap her and give her to
you if you’ll take her with you!
So…
Where is she now?
Up…stairs…
I’ll bring her down!
It’ll be a relief!
Hold on a bit!
Hey!
There’re some people here from
the Soul Society to pick you up!
What’re you doing?!
Huh?!
H-Hey!
Wait!
She’s making a run for it!
This is bad!
Bad! Bad!
Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad!
What’s with those guys?
This is really bad, isn’t it?!
Hado 58:
Tenran!
Damn!
Hey, are you all right?
You struggled for nothing.
Don’t think you can escape us.
Forgive us.
It’s all right.
Get rid of him.
He is, after all,  a
mere Modified Konpaku…
a Mod Soul.
I’ll be going back first.
Hold on a minute.
Forcing down a girl against her will?
I wouldn’t call that a nice habit.
How do you plan to throw
them off, Yoruichi?
Are you curious to know?
Well, yeah. I hope it’s
not a risky plan.
I suppose you could
call it a risky game.
You don’t mean…
One piece of clothing off!
And another one comes off!
Please, not that!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey! Kon here!
In this installment, I’ll
be interviewing Nozomi!
Hey, Nozomi!
What do you want, pervert?
Who’re you calling a pervert?!
I’m not a pervert!
I’ll show you proof!
Pervert!
No, I was just…
All I did was help you
after you had collapsed.
I’m not a pervert!
KON’S PERSONAL COLLECTION!
SEXY DYNAMITE!
It must be in a guy’s
nature, you know?