Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Excuse me…
Yes, what is it?
Sweet…flowers…?
By the time you read this letter,
I doubt that I’ll be alive.
So to you, my most trusted one,
I’ll write everything that
I have uncovered.
When I first read
the captain’s letter,
I couldn’t believe my eyes.
I couldn’t believe it.
But it is true…
I’ll believe the captain.
Captain Aizen…
The one who killed you is…
Eat.
If you can faint from hunger…
you have it, too, right?
The power…
You, too?
Yeah, me, too.
I’m Gin Ichimaru.
Pleased to meet you.
Gin… What a strange name…
You awake, Matsumoto?
Captain…
What’re you doing in
my room?
Idiot!
The office isn’t your room!
If you’re awake, take over.
I’m beat!
That’s because you went and took
all the paperwork for Squad 5’s takeover.
Quiet. You finish up.
Is this all?
There was so much more…
Quiet, I said!
I’ve been asleep a long time,
haven’t I…?
Never mind.
Your classmate is fighting
with your junior.
It must be rough on you.
My classmate, huh…
Captain…?
Do you really suspect Gin…
Captain Ichimaru was the one who…
Excuse me, sir!
I am Kokichiro Takezoe,
Squad 10, 7th Seat!
Are Captain Hitsugaya and
Lieutenant Matsumoto here?
What is it? Come in!
Sir!
Pardon me!
Reporting!
An urgent message from
the guard stations.
Lieutenant Abarai, Lieutenant Hinamori,
and Lieutenant Kira…
have vanished from their cells!
Forgive me, sir!
When Lieutenant Hinamori called,
and I turned around,
I saw a blinding white light,
and I awoke in this state…
I have…no excuse for it, sir!
Hakufuku…
Hakufuku…?
Hinamori is a master
of the Kido.
If we truly wished to restrain her,
we should have sealed
her Spiritual Pressure.
But that wasn’t done because
no one expected her to go this far.
It’s not like she was under
a death sentence.
Why…?
There’s only one reason…
Matsumoto…
Yes?
Go back without me.
I’m going to save Hinamori!
Hinamori, don’t do anything rash!
He now maintains his stance,
even when his sword breaks.
Hurry, Ichigo, the deadline is near…!
Fifty-one.
This time, for sure!
Keep your eyes on the enemy.
That’s fifty-two.
Dammit. I almost had him…
Ichigo…
At the moment of impact,
he adjusted to the enemy’s speed
and deflected the blade.
Then, without slowing down,
he shifted instantaneously
to counterattack.
Clearly, he no longer relies on
the power of Zangetsu, his weapon…!
He’s absorbing it…
With fearsome speed…
At a fearsome level…
Urahara, you were right.
The boy is truly…
Oh? Boss,
have you caught a cold?
No, some pretty girl is
probably talking about me.
Wow, that’s such a cliché.
You said something?
No…! That will never do!
I have a good remedy for colds.
Remedy?
This expired two years ago!
It’s nicely aged.
That’s not right!
Say “Aah…”
Haah? N-No! Stop! Stop it!
Drink, drink.
Hah? Ah?!
Damn! Not yet!
I gotta…I gotta save Rukia!
Why does Rukia Kuchiki
have to be executed?
Why do they keep
moving up the date?
As I was investigating,
I came upon the truth.
I want you to know it.
In my place…
Captain Aizen…
He’s been fighting
for over five minutes
with this single sword…
But it’s nearing the end…
Here goes!
Wha…?
Huh?
Lay down your sword, Ichigo.
The first day is over.
This way, sir.
This is…!
I couldn’t tell it was night, already.
You can’t tell time here,
so you sure get disoriented.
Wh-What’s with this hot spring?!
My scar’s healing like crazy!
Huh?
Awesome! Just awesome!
Would it work if I drank it?!
Ichigo…
How’s the bath?
[Great! The water’s great]
Yeah? That’s good.
Then I’ll join you…
A-Are you nuts?!
What’re you doing?!
Aw, what’s wrong?
Plenty’s wrong!
And why do you take off
your pants first?!
You always react exactly
as expected.
You’re so naïve.
Sh-Shut up!
You makin’ fun of me?!
Agh! Don’t come in! N-No!
There’s no problem now,
is there?
What? Are you a little disappointed?
Be honest.
Eh?
You creep!
I’m gonna drown you!
Hey, Yoruichi…
What?
I’ve been thinking…
This place looks a lot
like that place…
The Training Ground
under Urahara’s Shop.
I suppose so.
That place was modeled
after this one.
Really?
Yeah.
When Kisuke and I were kids,
we secretly built it as
our secret play ground.
Secretly…?
This hu-ge space…secretly?
It’s an old story.
When we were kids,
we played here almost every day…
After he joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
and I joined the Stealth Force,
we honed our skills here.
W-Wait a minute, Yoruichi!
Yow!
Why sit cross-legged?!
Don’t sit like that!
Heh. I never get tired
of that reaction.
Just tell me more about
the old guy!
So he was a Soul Reaper, after all?
Yep.
I thought it was strange.
He knew so much about Soul Society
and he had a zanpaku-to.
Tell me, Yoruichi.
Who is he, anyway?
He’s the former captain of Squad 12
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
He even founded and served
as the first chief of the Department
of Research and Development.
For real?!
Didn’t know he was that important!
I thought so…
What?! Are you trying to kill me?!
I have a good stomach medicine
that works wonderfully.
Please wait!
You are trying to kill me!
I’ll dig it out from the back yard!
What the heck are they doing?
So you’re together,
as I suspected.
Captain Hitsugaya…!
Just as I thought.
Only Kira’s cell was unlocked
from the outside.
If you wanted it to be a secret,
weren’t you a little careless?
…Ichimaru?
Well, that’s a funny thing to say.
I did it on purpose,
so you’d know.
It’s a good thing
I got here before Hinamori.
Before she gets here,
I’ll kill you!
Hinamori!
At last…I’ve found you.
So you were here…
No, Hinamori!
You’re no match for him!
I’ll handle this. Stay back!
Hinamori…?
To avenge…Captain Aizen!
Why did you kill the Captain…?!
I know everything…
from this letter left
by the captain.
Hinamori, the true purpose
for this execution
is not to kill Rukia Kuchiki.
This execution was contrived
in order to steal a certain object.
Its true objective is…
The Sokyoku.
The Sokyoku’s seal is
broken only for an execution.
In its blade lies the destructive power
of a million zanpaku-tô.
It also possesses
the defensive ability
to block equally powerful
zanpaku-to, as well.
Moreover, when a Soul Reaper
is crucified and stabbed with Sokyoku,
its power grows dozens
of times over.
The one who plotted this execution
plans to use this power
to destroy not only the Seireitei,
but Soul Society itself.
And the name of this vile person is…
Toshiro…Hitsugaya…
Wha--!
The letter goes on to say…
I’ve called him out to
the Sacred Eastern Wall tonight.
I must stop his plan somehow.
“I’m resolved to fight him
if he won’t desist.
But if I should die…
Hinamori, won’t you carry out
my wishes and avenge him?
This is my final request…
not as the captain of Squad 5…
but as a man.
I ask this…of you…!”
Hinamori…
You fool! Think carefully!
If he dies, he wants you
to fight instead?!
Do you think
Aizen would say that?!
The Aizen I know was
never stupid enough
to face unbeatable odds alone.
And he was no coward that makes
his men bail him out either!
But…But that’s what the letter said!
In Captain Aizen’s handwriting!
I didn’t want to believe it, either!
But that’s what
Captain Aizen said!
I…I…
I don’t know…
what to do anymore…Shiro-chan…
Hinamori…
Rats.
No good. She’s too upset
to think rationally.
But Aizen would never write
a letter like that.
Somebody must’ve forged it!
So that Hinamori and
I would kill each other!
I see. This, too…?
Was this all your doing, too?!
Ichimaru?!
Hinamori…!
Oh, my. That was cruel,
Squad 10 Captain.
The girl was hurt and so desperate.
Why hit her so hard?
Ichimaru…
The warning certainly came…
at a convenient time for you.
What are you after?
I’ll never forget what you
said back then.
You’re always the same.
You should stop and listen to
the last alarm, at least.
Soon you won’t be able to anymore.
So Aizen wasn’t enough for you…
You even had to hurt
Hinamori this bad…!
To make her grip her sword
so hard that her hands bled…!
Whatever are you talking about?
I told you…
If you ever made Hinamori bleed,
I’d kill you!
That will never do.
Draw your sword in a place like this
and I’ll be forced to stop you.
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Boss, this time for sure,
I have a safe,
nutritional supplement.
Uh, no… I’m all right now.
It’s the latest Chinese medicine
advertised in the evening paper.
I wouldn’t trust that…
It works on a variety of ailments!