Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Why do you have to keep fighting so?
What’s your purpose?
Why did you come here?
My purpose is to save Rukia Kuchiki!
Rukia?
Wasn’t it just this spring that
she went missing in the human world?
That’s too short.
It’s a shallow friendship.
I would hardly think
that’s worth risking your life for.
It’s true I know nothing about her…
And that it may fall short of
being worthy of risking my life.
However, Ichigo wants to save her!
So that’s enough!
I don’t need any other reason
to risk my life!
Oh boy, what a problem.
Well, if you’re that determined,
then it would be insulting
to ask you to go away.
I guess it can’t be helped.
Then, I guess I’ll have to take your life!
I’m sorry…
What does the Ritei-tai want with me?
If they wish to give me orders,
the Hell Butterfly should have sufficed.
Yes… However,
it's because this message is signed
by both Head Captain Yamamoto
and Captain Hitsugaya of Squad Ten.
Signed by both captains?
Is it a top priority order?
Is that all you can do, run?
Calm down… Calm down…
I can get him.
There’s no way I can’t!
I’ll let you take the first swing.
You can cut me up anywhere you want.
So, come on.
You can go for my neck,
my gut, my eyeball…
If you want,
you can even kill me with this attack.
Stop quivering! Come!
No way… I know I swung down
with all my might.
Why is it that…
there’s not even a scratch on him?
my hand’s split instead?
This…
What?
Hey… Is that it?
Damn! I’m not scared!
Don’t run around so much.
I don’t like
playing tag with weaklings.
Damn!
Damn…! Why…?
I hit him…
But I couldn’t cut him!
Does it mean there’s such
a great difference in power between us?
Dammit!
No… Calm down…
I’ve got to calm down.
There’s no reason for me
NOT to be able to cut him.
I’m just overwhelmed
by his Spiritual Pressure.
That’s the problem!
If I calm down and sharpen
my Spiritual Pressure…
there’s no reason I can’t cut him!
Even Old Man Zangetsu said it…
Calm down…calm down…
Calm down… calm down… calm down...
Rid yourself of fear… Look to the fore…
I can win… I can win…
Retreat and you will age…
Hesitate and you will die!
I can win…
I can win!
I’ll get him!
Chad’s Spiritual Pressure…is gone!
No…
It can’t be…
Chad has lost?
Is he dead? No way!
That can’t be!
Chad can’t have lost…
It’s impossible!
Who’d have thought his final attack
would be this powerful?
If I’d taken a direct hit,
it could have been really bad for me.
It’s amazing for any human to
even get into Seireitei,
but to think he could fight this hard…
Captain Kyoraku!
We have a message!
What is it?
It's not like you to be out of breath.
Come to think of it,
one of the boys from Ritei-tai was here,
wasn’t he?
What did he want?
Captain Aizen has…
passed away…
Wha--?!
The cause of death was removal
of his Saketsu Chain and Hakusui,
and destruction of his heart.
It wasn’t an accidental death.
He was murdered.
The murderer is unknown.
It is a top-priority message
signed by both Head Captain Yamamoto
and Captain Hitsugaya,
so I don’t believe there is any mistake.
I see.
Shosuke was…
Well, anyway…
Shall we go and see him?
Yes, sir.
Chad… Chad…
Chad!
Is something wrong, Captain Kyoraku?
This Ryoka isn’t dead, is he?
Shall I deliver the final blow?
Chad!
Leave him be.
Girls shouldn’t
do things like that.
But…
the person who killed Captain Aizen
was probably one of the Ryoka!
Hmm… Perhaps.
But then again, maybe not.
Huh?
No…I’m just talking about possibilities.
Anyway, there’s no need to be
in such a hurry to kill him.
Let’s call the rescue squad
and have him put into a cell somewhere.
If there’s the possibility that
one of them is the killer,
all the more reason to keep him alive.
You understand, don’t you?
Yes, sir.
I will make the arrangements at once.
I apologize for trying to meddle.
Things seem to have gotten
quite out of hand.
Chad!
He’s alive!
It’s faint…
but his Spiritual Pressure is still there!
That’s right. What am I hesitating for?
I…
If I lose here…
Chad…and Inoue…
and Ishida…and Ganju…
and Hanataro…
and Yoruichi…
All the people who have
lent me their strength…
They’ll all die!
I haven’t got any time…
to be afraid!
So, finally you show yourself.
Are you prepared to die?
Or, have you just given up?
Both of those…
are wrong!
Wait for me…Chad!
I’ll beat this guy…
and I swear…
I swear…
I will…save you!
Sorry…
I don’t feel like dying yet.
If I die,
everything on my shoulders
will be destroyed.
I can cut him…
I can!
Now I know I can fight him.
I know…
I can defeat him!
What’s this?
You can do it if you try!
Don’t let your guard down yet.
Stay…sharpened like that…
This is where the fun begins.
Right…
Ichigo Kurosaki…?
Kenny seems so happy…
Sosuke Aizen, Captain of Squad Five,
has passed away.
When he was lowered from the wall,
he was no longer breathing.
Is there any possibility of a gigai?
Yes.
I investigated every possibility,
including the chance that
someone had used a gigai
to deceive others’ eyes.
But it only served to confirm
the truth of his death.
After this wartime chaos is resolved,
a new captain of Squad Five will
be selected
by the Central 46 and Squad leaders.
Squad Seven Captain Komamura…
Squad Nine Captain Tosen…
Would you two please return
to command your squads?
I too…shall visit the front lines soon.
Thank you for your efforts,
Captain Tosen…
Captain Komamura…
How was he?
I see…
What did Captain Unohana say?
Just that Captain Aizen had passed away.
In order to inquire into the truth
behind Captain Aizen’s death,
it seems the quickest route lies
in ending this fighting.
Then…that means…
Yes. I will join the fight.
Nothing would be better
than to avoid fighting,
but it seems things aren’t
going to go so smoothly.
Fighting…
If not for fighting,
people would not be mislead
by ugly emotions
and neither would ugly tragedies occur.
Finally, it is time for
Captain Tosen’s “suzumushi” to cry out.
I detest fighting…
from the bottom of my heart.
That’s good… Good reaction!
Your concentration is improving!
Unlike earlier,
you can actually hear my bells ringing!
I wear the bells and my eye patch
just so I can get greater enjoyment
out of my battles.
There’s no reason for me to wear them
if you don’t take advantage of them.
Damn!
You take me for a fool?!
And that’s why you won’t release
your Zanpaku-to, either?
Do you realize?
My sword can cut you now.
If you let your guard down and --
My Zanpaku-to doesn’t have a name.
My sword is out in the open.
It has never had a sealed form.
This is the true form of my Zanpaku-to.
Is that so? Well, that’s a relief to hear.
So that means your sword won’t get
any more powerful than it is now.
In that case…
“In that case,” what?
“I’ll be able to win soon.”
Is that what you thought?
You’re the one taking me for a fool.
The reason I don’t seal
my Zanpaku-to is that…
my Spiritual Pressure is so huge
that I can’t seal it,
even if I use all my might.
So, when I fight, I make it a habit to
hold back when I swing my sword.
Do you see why?
If I didn’t do that,
my enemies are so weak that
I wouldn’t have enough time
to enjoy the battle!
I told you not to let up, didn’t I?
On your Spiritual Pressure.
Loosening up just because
you found a chance or two of victory…
What a boring ending.
And it had been a long time…
since I came up against someone
who could have killed me,
or could hear my bells during battle.
Is this the end?
No fun at all…
Damn!
Damn! Damn! Damn! Damn!
I don’t want to die!
Don’t want to die! Don’t want to die!
How can I die in a place like this?!
I can’t…
afford to…
die yet!
Move…! Move, body!
Stop, blood!
Let me…
fight one more time!
I…
I have to…
save Rukia!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Did you see that, Ichigo?!
This is the strength of our Captain!
This isn't over yet!
I'm going to turn things around now!
Oh? How?
T-That is… Right?
I'm looking forward to it, too.
Kenny, looks so happy!
I'll do my best!