[end flashback]
[flashback begins]
Pleased to meet you.
[end flashback]
[begin flashback]
Living peacefully without avenging the dead
is evil!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Stop! Tosen!
Is that how far you've fallen?!
Tosen!
Hisagi!
What...is...this power?!
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
Tosen!
I will do whatever it takes...
to open your eyes!
How foolish.
You've seen my power,
and yet you still think you can defeat me with the likes of a Bankai.
"The likes of a Bankai"?
That sounds like something an Espada would say.
Don't compare me to the Espada.
I have surpassed all of them.
And, you Soul Reapers as well.
Have you forgotten your days as a Soul Reaper?
A Soul Reaper?
Becoming a Soul Reaper...
is not what I sought after.
Tosen...
When? When did you choose this path?!
Are you all right?!
Sorry.
I didn't think that anyone was there.
I'm over here.
Huh?!
That's odd.
I mean, I'm sorry. I didn't think you were over there.
I'm Kaname Tosen. Pleased to meet you.
You really are good at hiding your presence.
You're big too.
I may not be able to see,
but I've never been unable to sense someone's presence.
Oh, sorry. It's a force of habit.
Komamura? Is that you, Komamura?!
I see...
You've joined the Thirteen Court Guard Squads too!
Would you like to join my squad?
I have a wonderful superior!
I'm sure you'll like him too.
So you're Komamura?
Tosen has told me all about you.
I am Sosuke Aizen, Squad 5 Lieutenant.
Why did you
become a Soul Reaper, Komamura?
To repay a debt of gratitude toward the one who saved my life.
A debt of gratitude, huh? That sounds like something you'd do.
What's your reason, Tosen?
Me?
Mine is...
Here I come!
You finally drew your sword.
You sure like to take your time.
Are you scared?
It's no use trying to ignore me.
No matter how strong you are you must still have your doubts.
You said it yourself a hundred years ago.
I never opened up to you,
I never gave you any information,
and I never tried to get too close to you.
That's why
you don't know what my zanpakuto's power is.
Do you think I can't do anything unless I know its power?
Who knows?
But I already know that your zanpakuto
controls your opponent's senses.
Are you saying that's my disadvantage?
No, I'm not.
Let me tell you this, Aizen.
If you think your Kyokasuigetsu is the only zanpakuto that
can completely control a person's senses, you're gravely mistaken.
Collapse...
Sakanade!
How naive.
I already know your Bankai's powers.
Its destructive power certainly is exceptional.
He hasn't taken much damage.
He stopped it with his zanpakuto.
You said that I could not defeat you with the likes of a Bankai, right?
What about that?
But the difference in power between you and Tengen Myo-oh
is like that of an infant and an adult.
Give it up.
An infant and an adult, huh?
When your arrogance goes that far, it's almost pitiful.
Very well then, Komamura.
I shall bring that arrogance of yours to the ground.
His speed boosted in an instant!
Where are you looking?
Myo-oh!
You and that thing
are linked with the same movements.
And if you damage the giant, you'll be harmed as well.
What an inconvenient Bankai, Komamura.
As one who has seen your Bankai several times,
it's easy for me to target its weakness.
Because of its immense destructive power,
you never believed that an enemy couldn't be beaten
in a single blow, let alone counterattack.
Even if I don't target your vital spots,
if I continue to damage your limbs,
sooner or later, you will not be able to move.
The same goes for you too.
The same?
Don't put me on the same level as you!
Instant Regeneration!
You've really
given up being a Soul Reaper, haven't you, Tosen?
Given our current situation,
you sound like a sore loser, Komamura.
I recall you said my power was that of corruption.
You said that tricking my friends and subordinates
to gain power was corrupt.
Then I ask you this.
If someone who joined an organization for revenge
were to forget his purpose and live
peacefully while working for that organization,
wouldn't that be corruption as well?
To my unseeing eyes, that appears far more corrupted.
Tosen...
Was your reason for becoming a Soul Reaper...
Revenge.
I love the night sky, Kaname.
Because the night sky is similar to the world.
It's engulfed in darkness, and has many small lights.
But there are clouds that try to shroud them.
Kaname,
I want to become someone who removes those clouds.
I want to remove the clouds
so not a single light is lost, Kaname.
I'm going to get married, Kaname.
He's a Soul Reaper.
Also, I got a notice of acceptance yesterday at the Academy.
I'm going to be a Soul Reaper.
I'm going to be a Soul Reaper and fight Hollows.
I'm going to create peace.
I wanted you to hear it first, Kaname.
Congratulations.
Let me know if there's anything I can help you with.
Thank you.
But I want you to remain just the way you are.
And I want you to listen
to my stories when I come back from missions.
She said that it was a promise.
She sounded as if she was smiling.
That was the last I heard of her.
She never came back.
The man who killed her was her husband.
He killed a colleague over a petty disagreement.
When she scolded him for it, he killed her too.
She wished for world peace more than anyone.
She had a stronger sense of justice than anyone.
Because of that, she had chosen to fight.
But she couldn't even do that.
What was lacking?
Is a belief in justice not enough to attain world peace?
In that case, I want power.
I want the power to grant peace.
If justice is not enough, I will become justice itself.
And then...
I will wipe out the evil of the world like clouds.
I will put my sense of justice at stake.
Revenge, huh?
That's right.
You sound surprised, Komamura.
You've become reliant on your seeing eyes
and have become too lazy to see the truth.
Your eyes cannot see a single truth that I can see!
Too slow!
What's wrong, Komamura?
Have you lost the will to fight back?
Then let me ask you this...
Didn't you ever think it was strange?
Someone joining the organization that killed his most precious friend.
Why didn't you think that was strange?!
I thought it was out of a sense of justice.
I believed that it was to fulfill
the desire for justice that your fallen friend
had been unable to achieve.
You're right...
It was for justice!
In that case...
In that case, what is justice?!
Is it to forgive the man who killed my beloved friend?!
That is certainly virtuous!
It's admirable!
Sickeningly so!
But even if something is virtuous, is it justice?!
No!
Living peacefully without avenging the dead
is evil!
I understand.
It seems that I misunderstood your feelings.
If those are your true feelings,
you and I will never see eye to eye.
So are you going to kill me because of that?
Is that justice?
How absurd.
That's right. It's justice.
If our beliefs are incompatible,
there's no point in trying to reason with you.
I must kill you for the sake of the Soul Society.
I don't want to kill you.
I'm glad that I heard your true feelings.
I've already forgiven you.
Forgiven me,
you say?
You talk as if you're God, Komamura.
When did I ever ask for your forgiveness?!
If you want to kill me, then do it!
That is...
if you can still say the same thing
Suzumushi Hyakushiki...
Grillado Grillo!
I can see...
I can see!
I can see, Komamura!
I can see, I can see, I can see, I can see!
So this is the sky!
So this is blood!
So this is the world!
And...
So this is you...
Komamura.
You are much uglier
than I imagined.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
My song will reach the person you want to be.
kimi ga omou kimi e
All people, every one of them, are evil.
In order to make themselves believe that they're good,
they need to convince themselves that someone else is more evil.
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today, we'll be talking about Kaname Tosen.
Kaname's sword release is Grillado Grillo.
But you know, I don't really want him
coming around here in that form.
Damn, he came!
You shouldn't judge others by their looks.
Ah... That's a nice sound.
On a side note,
if I make this sound, my friends who make the same sound show up.
Huh?
Whoa...