Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities arebased
on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
I'd better hurry and
help the others.
Your back is totally unguarded.
You're finished…
What was that?
That's…
This Spiritual Pressure…
That's right.
You remember it, don't you?
It belongs to the leader
of our Squad 11…
Captain Kenpachi Zaraki.
Kenpachi!
Looks like you guys are doing this
in bits and pieces, Ichigo.
What a way to finally show up.
Not only are you late, but to make
this big a spectacle of it…
Shut up.
I rushed to get here before
you guys finished things up.
So what if I made a mess?
So…
I hope you left my play buddy
for me, like you were supposed to…
Okay then,
I'll go and do as I please.
You're in my way…
I don't like it…
Hey.
You're trying to kill me
with this dull thing?
I don't have time to be bothered
with someone of your level.
How can this be?!
In…credible…
It instantly turned back
into a sword…
That's the outcome
of a Zanpakuto
slain by someone
other than its wielder.
The relationship between
a Zanpakuto and a Soul Reaper
is one of communication,
synergy, and subjugation.
However, when a third party
becomes involved,
that relationship
can no longer be.
Let that be a lesson
to all of you as well.
You sure talk big…
Next!
Just what I expected from
the captain of Squad 11,
the combat unit.
He snapped a Zanpakuto
just like that…
But his Spiritual Pressure
is rough and too ugly.
It doesn't appeal to me…
Don't you feel the same way?
What do you mean?
I'm afraid you and I
are very much alike.
Very much alike?
That's right.
We both live according
to our sense of aesthetics.
Beauty above all…
But you were in the wrong place.
I mean,
you're among those
slow-witted, boorish,
hot-blooded people.
If you unleashed your true power,
they'd only make fun of you.
You can't be worrying
about aesthetics, right?
Being unable to expose
your own technique
to Kenpachi Zaraki and
Ikkaku Madarame…
In time, that in itself,
became an aesthetic to you…
It can't be helped.
A halfhearted narcissist is always
concerned about how people see him.
What is it you're trying to say?
I'm saying that someone like you,
who won't accept his own powers
for fear of how people will see him
can never win against someone like
me who believes in his own powers.
You really do talk a lot.
I don't want to hear
that from you.
Now…shall we end it
about now?
See you…Master.
Kenpachi Zaraki, eh?
Indeed…with that kind
of Spiritual Pressure,
I can understand how he took care
of Wabisuke with a single blow…
Maybe it was simply because
Wabisuke was an idiot—
attacking carelessly
the way he did.
Zaraki.
Where were you
hiding until now?
Hiding?
I don't like how that sounds…
Okay! Then I'll explain!
Ken went to get rid
of some Hollows
that appeared in the outskirts
of the Rukon District.
When he got word, he tried to
hurry back, but along the way,
he became totally lost and
ended up being this late!
Don't blabber
unnecessary things, Yachiru!
But it's the truth!
We even passed
right by the sweets shop
we found along the way,
up on the ridge!
That's why I said
we'd go there next time!
Promise?!
What is this lack of tension?
I'm going on a little rampage.
Get down.
Okay!
Now then…
Who among you here
is the strongest?
Looks like we have
a troublemaker…
It appears so.
Leave this to me.
What?
You go.
Bankai.
So impudent!
A lowly Zapakuto
shouldn't get cocky!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
So this is Kenpachi Zaraki!
It's impressive no matter
how many times I've seen it!
Captain Zaraki!
What?!
W-What power!
Can't withstand…
the Spiritual Pressure!
You're in the way.
Seems like it's begun.
For that much Spiritual Pressure
to reach this far…
That man really is exceptional.
But…
You'll only be able to
feel his Spiritual Pressure
for only a few moments more…
I like that expression.
Everyone is frightened
and pained in death.
I hope you die beautifully.
I've decided.
Decided…you say?
That's right…
What did you decide?
Are you about to
tell me that you've
decided to accept
death gracefully?
It's a little late for that.
Wrong.
That's not what I decided.
I decided to defeat you.
Oh?
It's indeed true that
I was concerned about
what the other captains
and Ikkaku might think.
Right?
That was simply because you were
so concerned with others' views
that it confused
your position on aesthetics.
Wrong.
I would rather die than have people see
the release of Ruriirokujaku.
But that's not all there is to it!
This can't be!
The greater
the Spiritual Pressure,
the faster the flowers grow and
the closer you should be to death!
I know!
But…
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
You released a considerable
amount of Spiritual Pressure
in order to cull out the others.
I suppose it had to have been
taxing on your body, as well…
That doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter?
That's right.
I never had any
intention from the start
of taking on the small fry…
I am forever a member of
the strongest fighting squad among
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
I'm a member of Squad 11!
Whatever happens to my body,
I will do whatever
it takes to fight you…
The captain and I will stake
our pride to continue fighting…
And if I should fall trying, then…
– laugh at me!
Where's Ichigo?
Looks like he was blown away
like the rest of us…
We can't have any more people
who will stand in Byakuya's way!
Not a single one of you guys
know when to give up!
T-Tenken!
I'm ashamed to say,
I can't get up.
Would you mind
lending me a hand?
Are you trying to
destroy me, too?!
Scattering so much
Spiritual Pressure around…
Can't that guy fight a quiet battle?
You're good.
A surprise attack?
Nice tactic.
With such bad footing,
I can't keep up with
her movements.
This no time for me to be
fighting a quiet battle, either…
Running away?
I'm changing location.
Follow me!
How shall we do this?
Shall I attack first?
Or…do you want to
come at me first?
I don't have time to be
facing off against you.
Is that so?
In that case, I'll attack first!
Let's have fun!
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Scatter…
That's not working.
Don't disappoint me too much!
Did you think I couldn't see
through your Flash Step?
Did you think you could
capture me with your speed?
How fun…
Looks like your speed is
only good for running away!
Laughable.
Do you see now?
You cannot capture me…
Is that so?
Caught you!
Is that all the attack
you can muster?!
How the combat squad,
Squad 11, has fallen!
Damn!
I used up a considerable
amount
of Spiritual Pressure to
escape from those vines!
I know…
Your Spiritual Pressure
has gotten weaker.
You shouldn't do rash things.
You talk too much!
Just as I expected of you…
You dodged at
the very last moment.
You… Why're you doing all this?
Because I thought
that unless I did,
you wouldn't give me
your best…
I see…
Scatter…
Impressive…
I'm unable to even
do a Shikai…
Even if I continue to run,
there's nothing more I can do…
I never thought I'd suffer because
I couldn't use Ruriirokujaku.
Looks like you're out of options.
If you don't mind, shall I let you
use the power of my Ruriirokujaku?
That would be fair, wouldn't it?
No thanks.
I thought so.
Then would it be fair
if I didn't use it either?
Yes…would you do that for me?
If you don't use that power—
despite all that talk about
aesthetics and all that—
it means that you
lack confidence…
In the power of your
Kido techniques.
Now you've said it.
All right. I'll do as you say.
I'll fight to the end using
my sense of aesthetics.
Unfortunately for you, I can use
the techniques any number of times.
Tear in Frenzy…
You told me earlier…
To laugh at you if
pride brings you
back to your feet
but you still fall.
Well, I intend to laugh
to the fullest.
Bakudo 4!
Hainawa!
What?! You're using Bakudo?!
This ends it.
I got lucky since you, like me,
are stubborn and overconfident.
If you had fought a normal fight,
I would've had
no chance of winning.
True, we are so alike
it's almost repulsive.
I'd rather die than have you reveal
the release of Ruriirokujaku.
But that's not all there is to it.
If you won't release Ruriirokujaku,
then I will make sure that I win…
That is my aesthetic.
Don't concern yourself
with me any further…
Otherwise, next time I'll be
forced to take your life…
Take my life, you say?
Fine! Go ahead and try!
I've always wanted
to have a swordfight
to the death with you!
You're finally on board!
Come at me with that spirit…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
I see.
Then you leave me no choice.
Kenpachi's Zanpakuto
doesn't manifest!
Of course not!
If it manifested,
Soul Society would be destroyed
without the story arc
moving forward!
So it's one of those
backstage circumstances?
Exactly.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Suzumebachi has gone
somewhere as well…
Who the heck are we
supposed to fight now?
On the other hand, I don't
feel like fighting those guys…
Tenken!
Would you mind burying me
back into the rubble?
I'm going to lay low
and wait for an enemy!
Okay, this is perfect!
Hey!