It won’t be long now.
Looks like this is the place.
That you, Zaraki?
Yeah.
Looks like we’re the only two left.
Guess it’s not that bad.
We don’t know if the
others were defeated yet.
What are you laughing about?
We wiped out most of
your invasion force.
We’ll crush your plans right here!
But tell us something
first, Kageroza Inaba.
Who the hell are you?!
He doesn’t want to answer.
Well, it doesn’t matter.
I only want to know one thing.
Are you strong, or not?
How disappointing.
You still haven’t realized
you have no chance at victory?
Well?
I still can’t get a
reading on Kurosaki.
Does that mean he died?
No, I can’t say at this point.
C-Come on, he’s okay!
That bastard Ichigo wouldn’t die!
Knowing him, he’ll probably
just plop right back here!
Right?!
It’s okay, Kon.
Huh?
You’re trying to be strong,
but you’re way too obvious!
You’re worried the
most out of all of us!
Shut up!
Me being obvious about worrying?
No way!
You bastard!
Kurosaki made it to the Soul Society,
Stop that!
then suddenly disappeared
in the Precipice World.
What is Kageroza’s power?
We know all too little about that man.
But she
knows something about Kageroza.
Perhaps more importantly,
she might even think like him.
When I have retrieved Nozomi,
I will be able to show
you my true power.
What did Kageroza mean by that?
What secret does this girl hold?
Go mad, Raiku!
What’s with this guy?
I don’t sense any Spiritual
Pressure from his Shikai.
Until we actually cross swords,
we won’t know how strong he is.
I don’t know how you’re
hiding your Spiritual Pressure,
but try to make this fun, okay?!
Wait, Zaraki!
Rushing in like that!
Hyoryusenbi!
Sorry, but I’m not going
to let you do this alone!
Whatever!
If I kill him first, it’s over!
What’s the matter, scientist?
You didn’t show up
just so we could kill you, did you?!
I’m still alive?
What?!
Goodbye…Ichigo Kurosaki.
Is this…the Precipice World?
Damn it, I’m losing consciousness.
Who are you?
Hey scientist…
That was daring of you to take
on the two of us by yourself,
but I don’t think you’ve
got what it takes!
You’re taking the
fun out of this, pal.
I don’t know if this
is your true strength,
but if you’ve got no intention
of taking this seriously,
I’ll kill you right now
and be done with it!
Zaraki, wait!
He’s waiting for something!
Guncho Tsurara!
I see.
You were evading us in order
to use that technique just now!
I remember now.
You’re a Precipice World specialist.
You create portals that shouldn’t
exist and seal your opponents
in the Precipice World that lies beyond.
That is the power of your Zanpakuto.
The ability to manipulate space.
Man, I thought you had
some awesome power,
but it’s just some cheap trick.
How boring!
Now that we know,
that technique won’t work on us again!
Huh?
So predictable!
He’s the decoy?
Hyoryusenbi!
Looks like you do have some skills!
You took the words right out of
my mouth, Captain Hitsugaya.
What’re you trying to say?!
You thought I would make the
Precipice World appear again,
so you switched to attacking from
a distance instantaneously.
Is that a compliment?
Or are you making fun of me?
I’ll let you figure that out.
Yes, I manipulate space.
As you said, that is the extent of
my zanpakuto’s capabilities.
No matter how you
change your attacks,
they mean nothing if
they do not reach me.
Yeah.
I suppose not.
Guncho Tsurara!
Huh?!
Who said anything about killing
you from a distance?!
It’s all about setting the table
for this one strike!
What a coincidence.
I was setting the table as well.
For this!
What?!
What just happened?
That was definitely my
own Guncho Tsurara.
Manipulation of space…
That was how you
described my powers.
You were certainly correct.
But you made one grievous error.
My abilities are not
merely limited to
manipulating a small world
like the Precipice World.
You might say I can
manipulate all space.
What?!
My Zanpakuto, Raiku, uses space itself.
It records space and recreates it.
Earlier, I made it recreate the
Precipice World back there,
but I also had it record
a new space as it watched your attack.
Do you understand now?
No, I don’t.
Still sounds like a magic trick.
If you can’t fight without
using cheap tricks,
then I have no more use for you!
You’re an eyesore!
Get the hell out of here!
Quit messing around!
That was…
That’s right. Your own attack.
You can even recreate
a Zanpakuto attack?
What will you do now?
It’ll make no difference.
There!
Oh?
I see now…how you use your Zanpakuto.
You twirl it to the
right to record space.
To recreate space,
you twirl it to the left.
If I prevent you from twirling
it to the right to record,
you’re powerless!
I’ve got you!
I can recreate the last recorded space
not just once, but as
many times as I wish.
So this is where you were, Kageroza!
Well, well, if it isn’t
Captain Soi Fon.
I never thought you’d make
it out of that barrier.
I’ll give you credit for deciding
to seal me in there first.
Naturally…
With you out of the way,
I have free reign over
the Punishment Force.
You sure went through a lot of trouble.
Yoruichi Shihoin…
So you’re Kageroza Inaba?
You’ve finally shown yourself.
I was wondering why I
couldn’t spot you.
So that’s how it is.
It was hard work rescuing
Soi Fon and the others
without you realizing it.
I apologize for putting you
through all that trouble.
But it had to be done
in order to bring everything
under my control.
You truly believe that you’re
capable of such a feat?
How silly of you.
Are you saying it is
beyond my capability?
Am I wrong?
Don’t underestimate my
powers, Yoruichi Shihoin.
I do not appreciate being overrated,
but I despise being
underestimated as well.
In that case, you shouldn’t
underestimate your adversaries either.
The two of you too?
Kuchiki…
You’re alive?
You still won’t give up?
There is only one head
of the Kuchiki clan.
There is no need for two.
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Bankai, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
I have witnessed the pride
that you…that Reigai have.
As I said…
The Kuchiki Clan does
not need two heads.
We will stake our pride
to bury your ambitions.
That’s all there is to it.
There is nowhere for you to escape!
Give it up, Kageroza.
What’s so funny?
Do you think you have me
cornered with so few of you?
I commend you originals for fighting
so well against my invasion force.
You did better than I
originally anticipated.
But it won’t be enough to defeat me.
Your madness ends here!
What is it?!
I’m picking up a reading of
Kurosaki’s Spiritual Pressure!
Really?!
Where is Ichigo?!
-Are you ready, Abarai?
-Hey, come on! Please tell me!
-Ready!
All right, let’s go!
You too, Nozomi!
So that’s what he meant.
By the numbers, we’re equal.
But because they’re not injured,
they have the advantage.
Who cares?!
It’s finally getting interesting!
This is the finale.
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Now’s your chance! Go!
- Shunko!
Not so fast!
What the—?!
Sennen Hyoro!
Shunko from his Zanpakuto?!
He says he can copy whatever we do!
Can you stop that counterattack?
We can! Soi Fon!
Right!
-We’re ending this!
It’s no use!
We’ll cancel his Kido…
By spinning in reverse!
- Hankisosai!
Why bother fighting us?
Your master is already…
That was fine teamwork.
But as I told you a long time ago…
You had no chance at victory.
Do you understand now?
What?!
What’s the matter, loser?
Y-You…
Surely you didn’t fail to realize
that I had changed places
with the fake one a long
time ago, did you?
Kageroza Inaba…
Why didn’t you create a
Reigai of Lady Yoruichi?!
Well, when she passed
through the Senkaimon...
Meow!
As you can see, she took
the form of a cat,
so I could only create a cat Reigai.
Lady Yoruichi!
Meow!
Oh, bother…