If you're going to muster the last of
your strength, use it to leave here.
Shut up!
Any human who loses this
much blood is gonna die!
What's the point in getting
out if she's dead?!
Rachel Gardner is still alive.
If you get out right now, you can save her.
What are you talking about?
Go, and you will see.
Now, go quickly, Zack!
I'm telling you to go!
Zack...
Zack!
Who could have guessed that
it would end this way?
Father...
Why?
I admit that I was self-serving.
Yes, that's right. Even though
I was working for you...
But I... Nothing I did was wrong!
What I did for my own happiness,
and to stop anyone who violated
the rules of this building,
should have been beneficial to you, too!
It is true that I got to see something
of profound interest, thanks to you.
I believed Zack was a being
that possessed invisible wings,
but now those wings have become
entirely imperceptible to me.
Invisible wings?
Did you actually think he was an angel?
I did.
Precisely because he was so pure that he
thought of only one thing: killing people.
But then Zack learned to wield his
blade for someone else's benefit.
As a result of this, his blade broke,
and he fell from the ranks
of angels, becoming a human.
No, perhaps it is more accurate
to say he was always human.
What's more, the one who showed this to me
was Rachel Gardner, the one
I had denounced as a witch.
It was a transformation
both dizzying and striking,
for a girl who was once so self-serving
and rife with contradiction.
Looking back now, I see that the one who
tried to take Zack's humanity from him was me.
Then why... why did you shoot me?!
It was my own vain attempt at
atoning for what I've done.
My observation and
experimentation are over now,
as is my duty to stand
in the position of God.
After all this, what are you..
You brought that girl to this place,
but although you were meant to steal
her soul, you sought to give her one.
You tried to become her God, did you not?
But, Danny, you are no God.
You must have known that.
But if I hadn't done that, I'd have nothing!
When I first looked into Rachel's eyes,
they were the eyes of
someone who'd lost all hope...
...and would never love anyone.
I wanted to give my love
to those eyes for eternity.
She gave new meaning...
...to the life I thought I had lost!
That gave me the power to do anything!
But I can't love her eyes any longer.
If she isn't all alone anymore,
there's no one left who'll accept
the ugly thing that I am.
By continuing to offer her your love, then,
you hoped that she would
one day love you in return.
Danny, both you and I are
mere humans, after all.
I'm... human?
There was never anyone
here who wasn't human.
It is humans who create God,
as well as angels and people.
That may have been true for
Rachel Gardner, too.
And the ones who attack
and destroy all that...
...are those same people.
Father...
What have you seen in the
people you've known here?
Indeed...
Unfortunately, very little
has significantly changed.
They were ugly, blind in
their devotion, and...
...so beautiful.
That is all.
And Danny, I feel the same is true of you.
You have been here longer than any other,
yet I didn't realize it until now.
Forgive me.
It's already the end for me.
Hearing you say I'm beautiful
doesn't help much now, you know?
Mother...
Hang in there. We're almost outside.
Don't you die on me!
Hey. We're outside.
He said I could save you once we got out.
What did he mean?
What am I supposed to do?
Hey! Wake up! Come on, Ray!
Wake up!
I'm begging you...
Open your eyes!
Ray!
That priest... This is what
he meant by saving her?
You there! Release the girl!
Don't bother resisting!
Release the girl, put your hands behind
your head, and get on your knees!
Ray, don't forget. I promised you...
...that I would kill you.
The girl recovered from the burning building
was found to be Rachel Gardner, the daughter
of the murdered Mr. and Mrs. Gardner,
who went missing while their
case was being investigated.
Isaac Foster, the man arrested on
suspicion of blowing up the building,
is believed to be behind several past crimes.
Has Isaac Foster confessed?
He's not the one who blew up the building.
He's also denied kidnapping
the girl who was with him
as well as killing her parents.
Has he also denied involvement in other crimes?
Actually, he admitted guilt to
those with shocking honesty.
"I don't lie," he said.
Are you sure you can believe him?
Personally, I don't think he's lying.
Oh...
Nah, that's a dumb idea. Forget it.
He's a twisted killer. No doubt about that.
Have you found out how he's connected to the girl?
The only answer he gives us
about her is, "I don't know."
Come to think of it,
he actually asked us about her.
He asked if she was alive.
So we told him she was,
but all he said was, "Okay."
What was your first impression of Rachel Gardner?
I thought she was a beautiful girl.
Her expression was very desolate, though.
I guess I can't blame her for that.
Has she told you anything pertaining to this case?
No, I've asked, but she denies
knowledge of everything.
What sort of counseling are you giving her?
My top priority is to help
her regain her peace of mind.
She gives very little in
the way of facial cues,
and she seems incapable of
expressing her emotions.
And... all she wants to know
about is that murderer.
Could it be that she can't get
the murderer out of her mind?
I do think that's the case.
That's why I've made an effort to keep
all information about him away from her.
I've cut her off from the
things that she fears.
I hope she'll make a speedy recovery.
I'll keep working with her emotions,
patiently and persistently.
Good morning, Rachel.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Your counseling for today
will be in the evening.
It's a gorgeous day.
After breakfast, why don't
we take a nice walk outside?
Okay.
Places like this are so relaxing, aren't they?
Yes.
Rachel, could you wait here for a moment?
The suspect in these serial
murders and kidnappings,
Isaac Foster...
Has anything made you feel uneasy?
No, not really.
Then have you been sleeping well?
Yes.
I see.
Let's call it a day, then.
I'm sorry we started so late.
My session with another patient ran long.
I'll walk you to your room.
I can go by myself.
I can't let you do that.
I'm sorry.
My, the sky looks so pretty.
It's a beautiful night.
A beautiful night?
Yes.
The best thing to do on a night like
this is get into bed and sleep.
You'll have sweet dreams.
Come, let's go.
Rachel, could it be that you're afraid?
You've gotten much better
since you came here.
You're nothing like who you were
when you kept asking about
that murderer you were with.
So... to put you at ease, I'll tell you this.
I'm not supposed to, but...
That murderer...
...was sentenced to death.
He... was?
Yes. I'm sure you're surprised,
but I believe this will
help you sleep in peace.
Yes.
Now, let's go.
Go straight to bed and sleep, okay?
The truth was that I hadn't
slept well the whole time.
I just couldn't calm myself down.
I was sure I wouldn't
sleep that night, either.
But... there was nothing left
to do but close my eyes.
Damn...
There's that boring look on your face again.
Zack... How...
Huh? How what?
I mean, weren't you in prison?
Yeah, well... obviously, I left.
But...
That day...
I told you I'd carry our promise with me.
Yeah, so what?
Who said you could go and
take it for yourself, anyway?
Then...
You still... want to kill me?
You know me. When I want something,
I don't let it get away.
So hurry up.
I don't have much time.
Or did you already forget?
No, Zack. I didn't forget.
I could never forget!
After all, we promised!
You and I promised each other!
That's right! So come on, Ray!
Yeah!
Hey, Zack...
Please...
...kill me.
If that's what you want,
stop crying and smile.