Shusuke Amagai is named
the new captain of Squad 3,
which had been without a commander
since Aizen’s rebellion.
Kira organizes
a welcoming party
to help members of Squad 3
get to know their new captain,
who they are still unsure of.
But Amagai, who cannot handle liquor,
gets drunk and faints.
In this inopportune moment,
an alert goes off stating that Menos
have infiltrated the Precipice World
and the squad is
ordered into action.
Kira and the squad leave Amagai
behind and go to attack.
But the Restrictive Current,
which should have been quarantined,
is released and
the men are in peril.
Just then, Amagai, who was
supposed to be in a drunken stupor,
appears and saves his men
with his amazing power.
It will be a while until dawn.
The things I arranged for
haven’t arrived yet.
We will have to wait here
for the time being.
I’m hungry.
That’s the last of it.
All right.
One, two…
Ichigo!
Oh yeah?
Mornin—
What?!
Damned old man…
He always gives me
a headache in the morning.
You mustn’t speak of
your father in that manner.
Shut up!
Say Ichigo,
did you know that Ms. Hosaka,
the neighbor behind us, moved out?
Yeah, I saw them earlier.
She suddenly came
to say goodbye yesterday,
and seemed to be in a real hurry.
I wonder what happened?
Maybe she got sick
of our old man’s behavior.
Absolutely not!
She constantly praised me for always
seeing eye-to-eye with my children!
Meaning you’re
stupid and childish.
What?!
Since when did you
become such a jerk?!
It saddens me.
The glass that was stuck in my butt
just went up deeper!
– Thanks for breakfast.
– Are you all right?
Let’s go, Rukia!
Ichigo!
Why’d you move aside?
Sorry. Blame my dad.
Usually, you’d go
for a lariat like this.
Why you, Chad?
Are you all right?
Well, if you’re apologizing,
I’ll forgive you.
Huh?!
Don’t leave me!
Ichigo!
Sorry.
Hey, Tatsuki!
You look like a tattered rag.
Rag?
That’s Tattered.
'Morning, Kurosaki! Tatsuki!
Yo!
Why’s everyone
huddled together?
Art homework.
I think I’ve gotten better.
Ta-da!
A tyrannosaurus doing yoga!
The theme was “Healing.”
Oh, that is so avant garde!
I want to kiss it.
Is that all you think about?!
What did you draw, Rukia?
This!
What is it?!
Oh, it’s Chappy doing yoga!
That’s so cute!
Yours is even better, Orihime.
Thank you! Actually…
Kuchiki!
Don’t worry.
It’s the usual thing.
Ichigo!
I guess I have no choice.
We’ll be right back!
What’s going on?
Who knows?
What is this?!
What’s wrong?
The number of Hollows
is steadily growing!
Thirty…no, fifty!
What?! What’s going on?
I don’t know!
Anyway, we’ll split up
and deal with them!
I’m hungry.
I did discover what they call
a “convenience store,”
which I had heard about.
Really?
Let me have something
to eat then.
Yes…however…
Well, come now!
I will not be picky. Hurry!
The gigai still haven’t arrived.
Shopping is not possible!
What?!
Please forgive me.
I’ve contacted the dealer.
It won’t be long.
No! I cannot wait any longer!
You must not!
This headgear is to
suppress your Spiritual Pressure!
If your presence in
the World of the Living is discovered,
it will be disastrous.
But…
Just bear it a bit longer.
The gigai I’ve arranged for have
a Spiritual Pressure masking function.
But that aside…
Enryu is preparing
valuable tests right now.
From here on,
you must not leave my side.
Ruri—
That Kenryu is so picky!
I’ll just have to find something
to eat on my own.
What’s that?
Damn it!
How many are there anyway?!
Hey, you!
Over here!
You! Are you a Soul Reaper
from this town?
A soul?
You’ll be eaten if you keep
wandering around here.
I’m the one who wants to eat.
Eat? You?
Oh never mind that.
I…
Hey!
Oww!
That’s why this headgear is…
Where are you from?
What are you doing?
You have my permission.
Huh?
Give me your hand!
Oh…here.
Perfect timing.
Bring me something to eat.
Hey! Did you hear me?
Stay back!
I’m said I’m hungry!
Huh?
It can’t be helped. Just find her!
It’ll be terrible if anything happens
to Lady Rurichiyo! Also…
You collected way too many!
I told you I’m hungry!
Don’t you understand?
And this is no time for that!
I’m hungry! Hungry!
Hungry! Hungry!
Hey! Stop it!
Let go of me!
Lady Rurichiyo!
Hey!
Take care of the rest.
Huh?!
Kenryu! He’s been eaten!
That Soul Reaper!
Yes. It is his duty to protect you,
Lady Rurichiyo!
We must get you to safety first!
But…
Bankai!
Tensa Zangetsu.
Who is that, Kenryu?
Ma’am.
He is Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You’re in my way!
Ichigo!
That you, Rukia?!
What are you thinking?
Using your Bankai?!
Don’t raise your Spiritual Pressure
so recklessly!
But those guys…
Huh?
What’s the matter?
No… Two weird Soul Reapers
and a kid…
Where’d they go?!
Let’s take care of
these guys first.
What a bother!
Kurosaki!
You guys?!
Cripes… You still can’t control
your Spiritual Pressure?!
We have to get back quickly.
The second period will begin.
Thanks.
Those arrows are perfect for
dealing with large numbers.
Almost like pesticides.
How rude of you.
I didn’t come here to hear that.
There was Spiritual Pressure from
a Soul Reaper that I didn’t recognize.
Yeah… I saw them.
Although it was just briefly.
It seems they used bait
to lure those Hollows.
Bait?
Huh? Like the one
you used before?
The composition is probably different,
but the potency is the same.
Do you know where they went?
No, they’ve disappeared.
What were they up to anyway?
Huh? A princess?!
Ichigo said she spoke like one.
Right?
Yeah.
A princess…
But, the things she said
weren’t princess-like.
She kept talking about being hungry
and pounced on me.
Sounds like she was
messing with you.
A princess who’d
make sport of Kurosaki?
Oh! Did she wear a revealing
black leather outfit
with spiky patent leather boots
with lots of weapons
and say something like,
“So who’s really hungry? Me!”
Or something like that?
Inoue, that doesn’t sound like
a princess, but more like a queen.
Doesn’t matter.
But say, Rukia,
what’re you doing there?
Yeah…
I’m researching those two Soul Reapers
and the princess you saw, but…
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Enough already. Give it up!
All that beeping is so irritating!
You be quiet!
For a Soul Reaper to come
to the World of the Living,
he must pass through the Senkaimon.
And there should be a
record of all passages,
which I can access.
Jeez! This manual is
so hard to read!
Sis! Just leave that to me.
I’m known as
the “world’s top manual reader”!
What the hell is that?
Shut up!
I also was created by the Department
of Research and Development.
Don’t take me lightly!
Okay, try it.
Really?
Oh then, here I come!
I’m in heaven.
Hey…
Well?
Oh, yes. Right away.
Oh… I don’t understand it.
Oh, Ichigo!
Huh?! Now what?
Move-in!
If you’re talking about next door,
they were done this morning.
No!
It’s a gigai!
What?!
That guy!
Hey, Ichigo!
Please put all the furniture
in the living room.
I’ll arrange it later.
Hey!
Hey you!
What? Oh, if it isn’t
the low-life from earlier.
What do you want?
Don’t give me that!
Who the hell are you guys?
I’m not obligated to answer a question
from someone like you.
What?! You’re the one who
lured all those Hollows here!
Don’t know anything about it.
Do you have any proof
that we brought them here?
Don’t kid around!
Ichigo!
It is you, after all, Ichigo!
Forget the formalities.
I know you came to offer your greetings.
She’s the “princess”?
Yeah…
Hey you!
How do you know my name?!
– We did some checking, you know.
– Enryu, what are you doing?!
What?!
Insolent fellow!
Isn’t it obvious that there is a world
of difference between you and us?!
– If I have need of you, I shall contact you.
– Move, you’re in the way!
Lady Rurichiyo,
it will be dark soon.
Hollows like those from
earlier today may appear.
Please return to the mansion now.
I see. I guess it can’t be helped.
Ichigo, I will see you again!
Her name should be Byakuya!
My brother is nothing like her!
Hey! I’m not done talking to you!
Hey you!
Put up a barrier, did you?!
Come on out! Hey!
– Damn him!
– Don’t exhaust yourself.
We don’t know who he is,
but his Bakudo is impressive.
I’m going out.
Sis, please wait!
Don’t leave me!
We’re outside, pipe down!
We are very sorry, but…
that is a trade secret.
I cannot answer you.
There’s no other explanation!
That was definitely
a gigai from your place!
As I said, that is a trade secret!
I cannot answer you.
Please…
If we can’t tell you, we can’t.
We’re the ones who’ll
get scolded by the boss.
Where’s Urahara then?
I’m not sure.
But he hasn’t been back
for the past few days.
I’ll tell him you came.
Let’s go, Ururu.
Oh, Jinta.
Hey Ichigo!
They’re done moving in!
What? Aren’t you going?
Nah.
What?! It’s only them right now.
If you change into
a Soul Reaper,
you can break down a barrier
like that, can’t you?
It’s all right.
What?! How boring.
I was keeping watch all this time!
What? You got a bellyache
or something?
Ichigo! Dinnertime!
Hey!
Pipe down! I said it’s all right.
Aw man,
was all this worrying for nothing?!
Oh, it’s dark.
Lady Rurichiyo… Lady Ru…
She’s asleep.
Don’t cry just because you were
too late with her meal.
Don’t worry about it.
You also saw it today,
didn’t you?
Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
His skill and power is genuine.
I’m sure he can go
up against them.
Coming to the World of the Living
was the best choice, after all.
What?! The princess
moved in next door?!
You saw her too,
didn’t you, Kuchiki?
Yes. She had bodyguards,
so I couldn’t get close to her.
Oh… She has bodyguards too!
She’s the real McCoy!
So did you find out anything?
Nope. They put up a barrier
and haven’t come out at all.
And you’re just sitting here,
doing nothing?
Ishida? You’re here!
You amaze me.
It doesn’t matter.
They seem to be the ones
with business.
I just know they’re gonna
come meddling soon.
Okay, take your seats, guys.
All present today too. Good.
All right. I have a great
announcement for you all.
Let me introduce
the new transfer students.
And get this…
We have three of them!
Come in, please!
Here they come!
What?!
It’s a girl!
She’s cute!
She’s so small!
He’s huge!
What is that?
A giant?!
That girl has to be in grade school!
Two adults and a child!
I am Kenryu.
This man on my left is Enryu.
And this person here is…
I am Rurichiyo Kasumiohji!
Pleased to make
your acquaintance!
– Huh?!
Was it also Urahara's Shop that sent
those guys next door to my house?
That is a trade secret.
Who arranged the school transfer?
And why is Rurichiyo’s uniform
so loose on her?
Blame that on the boss's taste.
He has pretty hardcore taste,
doesn’t he?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Right!
MEN'S SOUL REAPER
ASSOCIATION
PRESIDENT: TETSUZAEMON IBA
VICE PRESIDENT: YASOCHIKA IEMURA
DIRECTOR: MARECHIYO OMAEDA
DIRECTOR: IZURU KIRA
DIRECTOR: SHUHEI HISAGI
XX: HARUNOBU OGIDO
DIRECTOR: JUSHIRO UKITAKE
And today…
Please bring all of that
into this room.
Huh?!
We’re going to be using
this room for storage.
Please find another room.
But…
What is your answer?
Okay.
Good.