Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
I've come to inform you!
We have confirmed strange movements
in Kusajishi!
Strange movements?
Someone has gathered
a large number of thugs
to cut the trees in Kusajishi Forest.
Captain!
Is it the work of the Bounts?
On the surface,
it looks like a bookie
of one of Kusajishi's countless
gambling houses is behind it, but…
Is there someone else pulling
the strings?
Yes! I also have information
concerning that!
What should we do?
This is the clue we've been waiting for.
We'll probably need to investigate.
Then have someone do a search…
No, Matsumoto--!
We're going to Abarai's place!
Renji's place?
Abarai has had the most contact
with the Bounts…
I want him to come with us.
I've received a report from
the reconnaissance guy.
So what are Kariya's movements?
Yeah… They've gathered an impressive
amount of people in a short time…
It seems that they're gathering
ruffians from throughout Kusajishi…
They're pretty tough,
but they don't have spiritual power.
They can't win against Soul Reapers
even if they gather in large numbers.
But there's no way that
they'd fight seriously
against Rukon District residents,
would they?
It's a huge burden to fight while
continually holding back!
I see… Indeed…
The Bounts are few
in number to begin with…
They're going to think of more
than one way to fight Seireitei.
So what are you going to do?
We're going to stop them!
They're a disorderly crowd
to begin with.
We're going to make it easier
for the Soul Reapers
to fight them by breaking up
the crowd!
This is the part I have to
consult you about, Brother!
When did I become your brother?!
Think nothing of it!
At any rate, we don't have time!
Could you gather as many
of your allies as you can?
Ganju, why are you so passionate
about this?
A friend of mine is working like mad
to do something about the Bounts…
I want to help him!
A friend?
Ganju, could you mean Kurosaki?
Ah, the beautiful power of friendship!
No one is ever really alone!
Helping each other is more important
than anything!
Shut up!
Oh my!
At any rate, he had a terrible time
with the Bounts!
I don't want to let him die!
Tales of friendship, huh?!
I'm amazed you can say that
without feeling a bit embarrassed!
Well, fine…
I never liked that bookie…
I, Daiji Hirasako, the Bull of Kusajishi,
will help you!
So, the Bull of Kusajishi
wasn't your real name…
Why do you need to go by that name?
Because it's cool!
Yeah!
They’re so alike…
Hey! Conboy! Max! Lady!
Yes!
Gather up some sturdy guys!
We've gotten quite good at repairs…
Ryoka invasions have
become more frequent.
Everyone's probably become
more skilled…
But nothing is resolved,
even if we finish repairs…
Who in the world destroyed it,
and for what purpose?
Do you suppose it could
be a diversion?
A diversion?
The Bounts probably created
a diversion upon coming here…
But there's no point to it if it's repaired…
Jeez. You sure are naive…
This kind of distraction also
causes mental shocks…
Right now, Seireitei is
in complete chaos…
Everyone must have become lazy
to allow invaders into Seireitei so easily…
Wait…
Diversion?
What's wrong?
Did you figure something out?
It can't be…!
No…
I just remembered something important
I have to do! Excuse me!
A-An exploding egg…
What kind of dream did you have?!
You sleep too long.
It looks like you've finally awakened.
Now let's eat.
Rantao…
Umm… I'd like to continue where
we left off yesterday.
Sorry about yesterday.
I fell asleep half way…
Umm…about your face…
My face?
We met a Bount
in the World of the Living
who had a face that looked
very much like…
No, exactly like yours…
Yoshino Soma…
That was the Bount’s name.
What's the meaning of this?
That's right. That's also what
I've been wondering…
The Bount called Yoshino
is probably a copy of me.
Co…?
A copy?!
In the experiment
to create immortal souls
that produced the Bounts…
We didn't use normal souls…
They're not normal souls?
We created artificial souls that
were based on our own,
and experimented on them…
Artificial souls?
The experiment for eternal life…
Even though it was
mathematically possible,
still there was a moral problem
using human souls.
So we created artificial souls
based on our own souls.
Then…
The artificial souls went through
a sudden mutation
in the accident during
the experiment…
and were incorporated within
the cycle of rebirth…
That's what the Bounts are.
That's right…
We created artificial souls based
on Soul Reaper souls.
It's expected that
they have incredible power.
I see…
So the Bounts can use Dolls
like Soul Reapers use
their zanpakuto, right?
Yes… Afterwards, artificial
soul research grew
and the gikongan and mod soul
technology was developed.
Then…
The Bounts are like
my distant relatives.
I see… Lirin and the others are able
to have Bount sensor abilities
because they're based on
the same technology…
I thought that since they dived
through the cycle of rebirth,
the features of the Soul Reapers
they were based on
would not directly
surface themselves, but…
This Bount called Yoshino
resembled me, huh?
Yes…
So what happened to that Bount?
Kariya killed her…
At any rate, we have to stop
the Bounts as soon as possible.
Kenny…
Are you going to meet Maki?
Yeah… The captain of Squad 10
has been able to track them…
I'm going, too!
I also want to see Maki!
Gentlemen! Take a rest and
listen to me for a moment!
First, I want to pay tribute
to your courage!
This is your fight!
You were controlled and
discriminated against,
even though you are also
from the Soul Society.
Today, you will be released!
You are free!
We shall now commence
an attack on Seireitei!
In order to do that…
we need your help!
I wish you the best of luck!
I thought so…
What is the matter, Master Mayuri?
The one who snuck into Seireitei
and did the destruction was…
Maki Ichinose.
Take a look at this, Nemu!
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Lately, there haven't been
Soul Reapers passing through, but…
the Senkaimon has been opening
and closing frequently.
This is that record…
Ichinose has been coming
in and out.
The gate will open and close
when he's passing through
the Senkaimon even if he's invisible.
And no matter how skillfully
he hid himself…
he wasn't able to completely erase
his Spiritual Pressure as he passed.
Of course, this was something
only I was able to notice.
He's been breaking into the database…
and making alterations
and hiding information.
But that won't work on me.
Maki Ichinose's Nijigasumi
has an ability
to use light refraction
to make him invisible.
And the Bounts have
a special technique
to hide their Spiritual Pressure…
If he had that technique,
there is no way that
he wouldn't use it.
This means that Ichinose
made himself invisible…
and was coming into Seireitei
and creating diversions.
There may have been
other times when
he broke into the database
and made alterations…
I'm going to make a search
with this pattern in mind.
I thought so.
I never thought that
he could break in this often
without anyone noticing…
What?!
What's wrong?
This is…
It can't be… It can't be!
Take a look at this!
This is…
This is the data we retrieved
after it was erased!
Yes, Master Mayuri.
I looked at this and thought of…
drawing the Bounts to Soul Society
by using the Quincy power, but…
Was it Ichinose…
who showed me this data?!
They were using me!
They had the Quincy use
his bow to go to Soul Society!
How dare they…those Bounts!
I've found their location.
They're gathering deep
in Kusajishi Forest.
According to our information,
they've gathered an
incredible number of thugs…
Though thanks to that,
the area around Kusajishi is said
to have become pretty quiet.
So…what should we do?
Since we've come this far,
we've got to go.
The thugs are still residents
of Rukon District.
Try not to harm them if
you encounter them.
Roger.
Renji… Is your zanpakuto all right?
Huh?
You used Higazekko in
the World of the Living, didn't you?
Your zanpakuto hasn't recovered, has it?
It's all right! I don't have to use
my shikai on the likes of thugs…
But what'll you do if Bounts come out?
Well…
Well, when that happens,
you can run to Seireitei
as a messenger.
How mean…
Let's go!
Are you going?
Yeah… Inoue's Shunshunrikka
just informed me that…
the Bounts are doing something
in the Kusajishi Forest.
We've got to go.
Rantao, what about you?
This shouldn't be the only thing
that the Bounts are doing.
I have something
I have to prepare just in case…
All right…
Let's meet again afterwards.
Yeah…
Oh yeah!
Hm?
I have one more thing
I had to ask you.
What is it?
Rantao…
You know about
Ishida's artifact, don't you?
How long will it hold up, in actuality?
I don't know…
It may become useless today…
It may be tomorrow…
If it goes off accidentally…
it may blow away everything within
a radius of several thousand meters.
Well, there's no reason to
get scared at this point.
I've just got to do what I can!
Hey!
Be careful…
The preparations for a surprise attack
on Seireitei are on schedule.
Good work.
Master Kariya.
What is it, Ichinose?
It seems that several Soul Reapers
are approaching this location.
There's also a captain…
I'm thinking of remaining here
to deal with them.
If we deal with the Soul Reapers now,
things will be easier later.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes! Anything for you.
Captain!
It seems there's no mistake.
The Bounts are beyond here.
But it sure is strange…
There are much fewer people
here than I thought.
What should we do?
At any rate, let's split up
and move on! Be careful!
Right!
I found one…
Who are you?
Maki Ichinose.
Are you the Soul Reaper
who's helping the Bounts?
I am no longer a Soul Reaper…
I am a comrade of
the great Master Kariya!
Where are the Bounts?!
I don't need to answer you.
Then I'll force an answer out of you!
Come on!
Why do you help the Bounts
when you have this much skill?
I saw that Master Kariya's goal
as justice.
What?
There is no longer any justice
in Soul Society.
Master Kariya will purge you!
You bastard!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Why, it's Toshiro!
It's Captain Hitsugaya!
What's going on in this forest?!
Matsumoto! Abarai!
There really are too few thugs
gathered in the forest.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Oh! Kurosaki!
Why are you here?
Right now, Ganju and the others are…
You're not good enough!
At any rate, don't let any
of them get away!
We came with Ganju and the others to…
stop the people
gathering in the forest…
For some reason,
there seems to be only a few people!
What's the meaning of this?!
What's wrong, Chad?
There's a guy who can
control space just like Noba…
That old man!
It's too late!
Master Kariya and the main force
have already headed to Seireitei!
Are you a Ryoka?
So what if I am?!
Hm?
Who are you?
A Bount… Go Koga…
Sorry, but could you let me in?
I can't let you pass!
Then I'll have to force my way in…
Zeig dih, Dalk!
An army, which was believed to
be gathering in Rukon District 79…
has appeared at Hakuto Gate
and Kokuryo Gate.
Hurry to your defense positions.
I repeat…
An army, which was believed to…
Pry it open!
Now… next is Kokuryo Gate…
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Tadah!
Kenny finally has a part
in the next episode!
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
Now then, shall we do this, Ichigo?
Come at me for real with your Bankai.
No! No! I'm not your opponent!
That way! That way!
Don't be so tense.
It doesn't matter who I fight.
No, it’s not!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Now, here are everyone’s presents
from the World of the Living!
A Nekoichi.
Snacks. A pennant.
A bear. A shield. And…
What is this?!
A swimsuit!
Why is it all stringy?
To be honest…I bought it at
Captain Kyoraku's request!
He said, “Buy some sexy clothes
for Nanao…”
It was a rare opportunity,
so I got a swimsuit!
Put it on.
Absolutely not!
Tune in next week!