Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Former Squad 5 Captain, Sosuke Aizen,
Former Squad 3 Captain, Gin Ichimaru…
and former Squad 9 Captain,
Kaname Tosen…
The whereabouts of these three
are still unknown.
Fortunately, according to the report
from the Department of Research
& Development,
The Hogyoku in Aizen’s possession
requires much preparation
and a good amount of time
to utilize it.
Therefore, in my judgment,
it will be quite a while
before it can be misused.
However, those three still
pose a great threat
to the Soul Society and
to the World of the Living.
I have therefore organized
an Investigation Force,
and mobilized them.
That is all for today.
You are dismissed.
So, they’ve organized
an Investigation Force.
Well, he calls them
an Investigation Force,
but they’re just assassins, right?
Aizen’s in big trouble.
But I guess he asked for it.
By the way, that Renji…
I hear he’s been assigned
to the town where
that Ryoka boy comes from.
Yeah… Seems he’s been keeping busy.
Oh…?
What?
Well…
it’s just that I heard
some disturbing rumors
about that the other day.
What…?!
Inoue!
Damn… We searched all night
and got nowhere.
Yeah… I don’t sense Inoue’s
Spiritual Pressure anywhere.
If only we knew
what that thing was…
It sort of looked like
the Gate of Hell.
The Gate of Hell?
Don’t you know what it is?
I do.
I saw it once before.
Well, there’s no way
Hell would make off
with a living human being.
Hey, Renji…
Why are you here at school?
Stupid! I’m in charge of this town.
If something strange happens,
it’s my duty to do something, right?
Renji, the point of your argument
is slightly off.
You were asked what
you were doing here at school.
Where am I off, huh?!
As I said, the question was…
Stop it!
This isn’t getting us anywhere!
What bothers me most
is what happened earlier…
Hey, Tatsuki…
Isn’t Inoue here?
Huh? Inoue…?
Who’s that? A new student?
What are you talking about?
Orihime…Inoue!
What the heck
are you talking about?
There’s no one here
by that name.
Huh…?!
Their memory of Inoue
has been erased.
It’s like when
Rukia disappeared.
I get it!
What is it?
Someone went to the trouble
of using the “Memory Replacement.”
That means they’re taking
our actions seriously.
Inoue hasn’t simply disappeared.
Someone’s behind this.
Okay! Then let’s go and
check out her apartment again.
We might be able
to find some clues.
That’s right.
Come on. Let’s go.
Yeah…
Hey! Just a minute!
What about your classes?
This is no time to be worrying
about that!
It won’t open.
Then let me…
You’re going to break down
the door?!
We have no choice.
Let me handle this…
Hey…isn’t that illegal?
There’s no other way, is there?
I suppose it might be better
than breaking down the door.
But listen…
Will you make sure
no one sees me from the road?
Ishida, you’re really good
at detailed jobs like this.
Quit making me sound worthless.
Hey! What’s it like in there?
Huh?!
Damn, there isn’t anything good…
Hey, what are you eating?
I didn’t get much
to eat last night.
I’m starving.
Hey! Look at this!
There are two cups…
What, and no cookies?
Do you have to keep
talking about food?
I’m hungry!
It hurts my stomach when you yell.
But you just ate!
That wasn’t enough!
Shut up! What in the world
are you guys doing?!
This means…
the being that possessed the Spiritual
Pressure we sensed late last night
was invited into this room
by Inoue.
It really was a strange
Spiritual Pressure.
I guess that means Inoue
knew who it was.
Who could it be?
Who’s cell phone is that?
It’s my Soul Pager.
A Hollow?
No, it’s not. It’s a call…
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hey, you guys!
You’re crowding me!
I’ve got your friend.
She’s with me now.
A child?
Who are you?
Hm… What should I do?
Should I tell you?
Why’d you kidnap Inoue?
Why?!
Calm down, Kurosaki!
Uh…yeah…
You shouldn’t go into people’s houses
without permission, you know.
Maybe I’ll call the police…
Were we being watched?
There’s no one around.
Do you want to see your friend?
Sure I want to see her.
Bring her back, you!
Why don’t we play a game?
Game?
Yes. If you boys win,
I might return your friend.
You…! You think you’re funny…
Don’t let her get to you! Calm down.
So what do we do?
Come to the park at 2-chome
within three minutes.
If you’re even one second late,
there’s no telling what
will happen to your friend.
So long!
Within three minutes?
What do we do?
I don’t know what’s what,
but we have no choice
but to go there.
Damn! You’d better be safe, Inoue!
Renji, don’t you have
any idea who it is?
She called you on
your Soul Pager.
I have no idea.
This was just supplied to me.
Anybody could find out
the number.
We haven’t got much time.
Let’s hurry.
Okay!
Huh?!
Looks like you got a little faster
in the short time
we didn’t see each other.
You just got slower.
What?!
Can you keep up?
Of course!
I won’t lose to you!
Kurosaki! Kurosaki!
People will think you’re strange!
Stop it! You look weird!
We made it.
Hey, there’s no one here.
That’s strange…
Hey! We got here in three minutes!
Show yourself!
Hello?
The first hurdle… You passed!
Huh? The first hurdle?!
Next…
Just a minute!
We got here in time!
Give Inoue back!
No, no! This is a game!
It’s no fun if it ends so quickly.
Damn kid…!
Get to the supermarket in
the 3-chome shopping arcade…
within three minutes!
W-Wait! That’s a crazy distance!
Then, maybe your friend will die…
Let’s hurry!
We’ll make it!
There it is!
Hello?
Sorry. Get outta the way, will you?
The 2nd hurdle, you lose.
Wait! We made it in time!
Someone else answered the phone,
so you lose!
Was that in the rules?
You didn’t tell us!
Too bad…
I guess your friend’s gonna die.
So long!
Hey! Hold on!
Hello?
Hey! Hey!
Hello…!
Inoue…
What do we do…?
What do we do?
What do we do? Damn it!
Calm down, Kurosaki!
That’s right. There’s no use
in your getting excited.
We lost our lead!
Hello?!
Fooled you! Shall we go
to your third hurdle?
Listen, you…
Making fools of us…!
Kurosaki, Inoue’s safety comes first!
Hey, is Inoue all right?
Let me hear her voice!
I’ll let you hear her voice
if you pass the third hurdle.
Okay. Hurry up and tell me what it is.
Where now?!
This time…
What?!
Oh!
Huh?
Urahara's Shop
Yikes! What are you guys doing?!
Hey, your phone!
Where’s your phone?!
Hurry up and tell us!
Welcome…
Kurosaki, what are you all
so excited about?
Our phone is inside…
Sorry! We’re going in.
Pardon us!
What’s the big hurry, anyway?
Are you hungry, or what?
Mr. Freeloader, it’s not time
for lunch yet.
Hello?
Wow! You made it!
Hey! How did you know
this number?
Where are you calling from?
Can’t you tell where it's coming from?
I can't tell you that!
Since you passed the 3rd hurdle…
You mean, trace the call?
Only the police can do that.
Maybe I'll give you a bonus!
Shall I make a recording of the call?
Eight o’clock tonight…
try going back to her apartment.
You may find her there.
Why tonight?
Bring her back now! Now!
Now, now…
Don’t get so excited.
Hey! At least let me hear her voice!
Tonight. See ya!
Hey! Don’t hang up!
Hello? Hello!
How noisy!
What in the world’s going on?
Yoruichi…!
Now, now. Don’t get so excited.
Hey! At least let me hear her voice!
Tonight. See ya!
It sounds like a kidnapping,
doesn’t it?
It is a kidnapping!
I doubt anyone
who would do this
would just hand Inoue over.
It’s some sort of trap.
Judging from the fact
that she called this shop,
I’d say she’s not
an ordinary person.
Then…a Soul Reaper?
Not necessarily.
There just isn’t enough information
to be sure.
What do you think?
The same as Yoruichi.
There’s too little to go on.
Isn’t there any way you can check,
Mr. Urahara?
I guess I’ll have to try.
However, this is the first case
like this for me,
so don’t expect too much.
Okay. Thanks.
8:00 tonight…
Are you going?
Of course!
We can’t leave Inoue to them.
I guess not.
8:00 PM?
Huh? Are you going too, Jinta?
No. It's just,
if they’re going at 8:00,
our freeloader won’t
need dinner tonight.
What…?!
Renji…
Pitiful…
Yeah…
Anything going on inside?
No. Nothing yet.
Ishida, you didn’t bring your cape?
Well, uh,
I sent it to the cleaners.
You send it to the cleaners?
That thing?
Why not? It’s 8:00.
What’s that?!
That’s Inoue’s apartment!
Damn! It’s locked again!
Okay, I’ll open it…
There’s no time for that!
Chad! Break it down!
Okay.
Kurosaki…?
Inoue…?!
Did she really bring you back to us?
What’s going on?
Are you all right?
Huh? What do you mean?
You were kidnapped last night.
What? Me? No way!
You don’t remember anything?
Think hard, Inoue.
What’s the last thing
that happened?
What…? Let’s see, today…
It’s a new semester,
so I went back to school…
met up with everyone…
I ate shaved ice with Tatsuki
and got a headache…
Then I went home
and after eating dinner,
went right to bed, I think…
The new semester started yesterday.
Huh?
They got to her and
erased her memory.
Well, anyway, I’m glad you’re okay.
But we can’t breathe easily yet.
That’s right.
Let’s keep an eye out for a while.
Try going back to her apartment.
You may find her there.
Now, now…
Don’t get so excited.
Hmm…
Did you find something?
No. I sent it through
the voice analyzer, but…
this voice has no Reimon,
Spirit Crest.
No Reimon, Spirit Crest?
That would be equivalent to
a voice print in a human.
Could it be broken?
Boss…
Huh? What is it?
Look there.
Hmm… I’ve never seen
a cloud like that.
Is it Menos…?
No. It differs somewhat.
What in the world…?
Nothing’s happening.
Shall I make some tea?
Wait…
Something’s coming!
Here it comes!
Inoue! It’s not safe near
the windows!
The door won’t open!
Inoue!
I-Inoue…
L-Let go of me!
Inoue! What are you doing?!
What could it be?
You… You’re not Inoue!
Who are you?!
Damn it!
What’s the matter, Chad?
Never mind! Just shake her off!
Chad!
Damn you!
Don’t use your zanpakuto.
They may just be
using her body!
Wh-What the…?!
Who are you?!
You’re not the one who called us!
Or course, not!
It would be weird if I had
a voice like that, wouldn’t it?
My name is Kurodo.
And here’s someone else…
Come on out, Noba!
Glad to meet you.
Renji!
I’ve got another one!
Chad!
It’s that kid! Where are you?!
I’m over here!
Good evening!
You’re the one who
phoned us, aren’t you?
I am! My name is Lirin.
Nice to meet you!
Why are you doing this?
It’s a game! A game!
She has some nerve…!
It’s hard fighting a kid…
I’ll take the guy on the left.
I’ll take the guy with the hat!
Ishida! You take care of the kid!
It’s no good, I told you!
See you later!
Damn!
What’s going on?!
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
There’s something wrong
with my gigai, I tell you.
I just can’t get out of it quickly.
Then, shall I lend you
my Soul Candy?
Oh! Thanks! That’d be great!
Let’s see, yours was…
Yo, did you want something from me?
I changed my mind.
I think I might get stupid…
Just one second!
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers…
Golden!
Don’t make a sound…
Owww!
Too easy…
Tune in again!