Shoyo is also watching
as the student he sacrificed
his life to protect
falls apart without protecting a thing.
Don't you leave...
Don't you leave!
Gintoki!
Excuse me.
What are you doing here
so late at night?
Excuse me, could you please
show me your license?
Please hurry, My Lord.
What's the matter, Oboro?
I was hoping to watch those
rebels meet their demise.
The crows are astir.
It appears that there's
been a shift in the wind.
What are you talking about?
Those rebels are already...
Good evening.
This is the police.
What are you people doing?
If you screw up...
We'll lose our heads!
Y-You guys...
Pinky Swear
I-Impossible!
Why are the Mimawarigumi
inside the palace?!
What's going on here?!
You serve the Bakufu!
You're police officers, yet you assist
the rebels, you traitorous scum?!
Assist the rebels?
Don't make false accusations.
There was an order to execute
those criminals in the morning.
If you're trying to dispatch
them before the sun is up,
you would be the ones
defying the government.
Our lord ordered us to guard
the criminals until the
execution takes place.
In other words, it is our duty
to protect them until morning.
K-Kondo-san...
You rural samurai don't get to talk!
Have you forgotten who let you
country bumpkins keep your swords?!
And now you're biting the
hand that feeds you!
You're lower than rebel
scum, you animals!
I'm fine with being an animal.
Beats being a dog that wags
its tail at fat pigs.
When a fat pig is lying
on the ground before you,
it gets eaten by
the wolves.
Don't call me a pig,
you punk Chihuahua!
I wasn't talking about you, Miss Piggy!
It was about me!
Were you the ones who let the
Mimawarigumi inside the palace?!
Has Sasaki joined forces with the
Shinsengumi to start a coup d'etat?!
Who joined forces with who
to start a what d'etat?
Why don't you repeat that?
Have you...
Eh? I couldn't hear you. What was that?
...and the Mimawarigumi...
I said that I can't hear you! Yell it out!
...joined forces?
Can't hear a thing! And I'm
not interested in hearing you!
You make me want to throw up!
Who would join forces
with those losers?!
Calm down, Toshi.
Okay, Kondo-san.
We've got them inside the palace.
Let's torch 'em with Sadasada!
Wait! That wasn't part of the plan!
Hell, you're sounding
like one of the Joi now!
Forget it! Kill 'em all!
Oh, it appears that
they've gotten started.
As you can see, the palace has
been surrounded by us elites.
I told them to drop their weapons
and surrender, but I was lying.
I've always wanted to say that.
Please don't drop your weapons.
It would look bad if the cops
were to slaughter a
bunch of unarmed people.
Y-You bastard...
You're late.
I'm so sorry, Nobume-san.
Thank you for carrying out your
mission alone while I was gone.
Here's a donut for you.
You see, being an elite, I was
able to avoid a lethal blow,
but it took a while to remove
the poison from my body.
Well, it was still easier than
removing a curry udon stain.
And it appears that you took good
care of our Nobume, Sakata-san.
I owe you now.
They only got in my way.
You can't blame them.
Nobume-san, they're ordinary
people, unlike us elites.
But it appears that he won't be
of any more use at this point.
That's bullshit.
The elite must be really
special to need help
from the ordinary to make it back here.
It wasn't by choice.
A certain person requested
that we work together.
And we are simply using each
other to ensure our survival.
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Oh, excuse me.
That's probably too difficult for
you ordinary folk to understand.
Essentially, it's like Nobita and
Gian in the Doraemon movies.
Two rivals who will use each other
to achieve the same purpose
when faced with a crisis.
Doraemon isn't such a dark story.
In other words...
Sakata-san, you are useless trash now.
Now that I've disposed of that
garbage, let's clean this place up.
Bastard!
Gintoki!
Hang in there!
Hey, Ginto—
Gintoki, you...
What is this?
It's a form of acupuncture.
His body will still feel numb for a while,
but at least he'll be able to move.
I also injected some serum into him.
The elite never miss a step.
Consider my debt paid.
Now, go back to the
other ordinary people.
If you stick around, you'll end up
being taken out with the trash.
Don't make me laugh.
You're not giving me any interest
after taking this long to get here?!
Begging for more again?
What do you want?
Sadasada's head.
Good grief.
That's a lot of interest.
Nah, his head's worth nothing.
I have an order for the Mimawarigumi.
All elites will begin supporting
that ordinary man.
On our pride as elites, we must not
allow a single person to go upstairs.
You won't listen if I tell you that
your body can't take any more.
Then I'm coming with you.
I won't let you break our promise.
That goes for you and Maizo.
Time for the last stage.
I won't let you hog the glory.
The last bite of a donut
is always the best.
What's going on here?
The Shinsengumi and Mimawarigumi,
the two largest police forces
in Edo, have joined forces.
I was told that they were rivals.
It would seem that someone
has brought them together.
The ship will be here soon.
You should escape, for your own safety.
My Lord.
Are they serious about
taking over this country?
In that case, I must respond.
Summon every remaining police
force to the palace.
We'll crush them with all of our might.
Wh-What's happening?!
B-Big trouble!
There are armies attacking
the north and south gates!
Impossible! Who are they?!
Listen up!
Clear me a path in three seconds
or else I blow down the gates.
One.
What happened to two and three?!
Couldn't tell you.
A man only needs the number
one to get through life.
Th-The entire police force?!
Impossible!
The police are rebelling?!
That's absolutely absurd!
This is no uprising!
Nobody's capable of bringing
all these men together!
There's one person who can do that.
One person capable of ordering
the police, or anyone, around.
You still don't understand
what this is, Lord Sadasada?
You are the traitor who has betrayed
this country.
Shigeshige... So you're behind this.
My Lord! What are you doing here?!
Lower your weapons.
We've wasted too much time fighting.
You men are valuable soldiers
who defend this country.
I will not allow you to
throw your lives away.
B-But, My Lord...
We have orders from Sadasada-sama.
Were you not listening?
I told you to drop your weapons.
Will you clear a path for me?
My Lord?!
You mustn't!
They're rebel scum who
wronged our country!
It's dangerous to approach them!
Sh-Shogun-sama...
My shortcomings have caused
you so much suffering.
Let me offer you my gratitude.
Thank you for defending
my loyal retainer.
If it weren't for you, I would have...
We would have allowed the beloved
man who raised us to die.
Grampy!
Y-Your Highness...
Grampy, I'm sorry.
I was by your side,
yet I never realized your pain.
You've devoted your life to
serving the shogun family,
yet we've only made you suffer for it.
Grampy, is it too late to
fulfill your promise?
Shigeshige-sama...
Soyo, take care of Grampy.
Yes, Brother.
Clear a path.
I need to talk to my uncle.
The man who raised them?
Oboro, what is he talking about?
Who was the one who turned a helpless,
fatherless boy into the shogun?
Who was the one who kept
you and this nation safe
while being accused of
selling out this country?!
It was me!
I, Tokugawa Sadasada, am
the father of this nation!
My rule has kept this nation safe.
Despite all that, you now
choose to turn on me?!
They say that a doll will gain
a heart if enough time passes,
though it seems that this doll
was given a stubborn soul.
He's realized that you were protecting
yourself, not this nation.
If you continue to
cling to this country,
your position may not
be the only thing lost.
You may lose your life.
Please join me in seeking
help from the Tendoshu.
Are you telling me to abandon
what's taken me half
my life to build up?!
To run off to the Tendoshu and
allow these traitors to live?!
Considering the contributions
you have made,
they will surely assist
in restoring you to power.
Nonsense.
They consider both myself
and Shigeshige...
No, they consider this entire planet
to be nothing more than a tool.
Isn't that right, messenger
of the heavens,
Yatagarasu?
The Tendoshu sent you to ensure that
I would be an expendable tool.
If I am the traitor who
sold out this country,
you Naraku are the crows
who feed on its carcass.
That ship is here to help?
Don't make me laugh!
Once I meet with the Tendoshu,
I'll never return to Earth.
We are ready to take
you wherever you wish.
Our mission is to assist
you in any way possible.
You'll take me wherever I wish?
In that case,
let's go to Yoshiwara!
The place where my rule began.
The cursed land where I was betrayed.
I want you to prove your
loyalty to me in that place.
Prove our loyalty? How?
Kill Suzuran.
That betrayal was where this all began.
So Maizo and Suzuran...
I will completely shatter your promise
and end this once and for all.
I will punish every person
who dared to betray me.
If that is what you wish.
I will follow shortly.
Set sail for Yoshiwara.
Yoshiwara?
I don't think so.
This ship won't take you to paradise...
It's headed straight to hell, bastard.
You bastard...
Did he pull it off?
Gi—
Gin-san!
You refuse to die.
I didn't expect you to drag that
beaten body back before me again.
You continue to fight?
You continue to howl?
If you would close your eyes, you
would not suffer any more loss.
Yet you return to the
battlefield again,
White Yaksha.
It's too late now.
No matter how much you struggle,
none of it will come back to you.
Not this country, not your
friends, not Shoyo...
Th-The Tendoshu!
Did they come here after
hearing about the revolt?!
I-It's over...
You're all finished!
You are nothing more than a ghost
who roams the battlefield in
search of that which was lost.
This is not where you belong.
You will be consumed by the flames
of revenge and sent back to hell,
demon!
He's trying to prevent me
from using poison needles?
He learned my technique just
by experiencing it once?
Sent back to hell?
You must be dreaming.
You and I are already
on a date in hell.
Do you believe you can use
my own technique against me?
My assassination techniques aren't meant
to attack enemy pressure points.
They're meant for controlling my own
pressure points to maximize my strength.
I can easily remove any
poison from my body.
O-Oboro...
That's enough.
Hell's too good for that guy,
but it seems appropriate
for him to be judged
by the laws he created.
What?!
I don't need needles to attack
your pressure points!
It's over, White Yaksha!
It's not over.
I haven't lost.
My body can still move.
My hand can still reach.
Gintoki,
look after things for me.
Don't worry. It's no big deal.
I'll be back very soon.
So until then, please protect our friends,
protect everyone, for me.
Promise me that.
Yeah.
It's a promise.
Sensei!
Go back to hell, White Yaksha!
Sorry, I have a prior engagement.
I already made reservations,
so you'll have to wait in hell for me.
Say hello to Sensei for me.
You bastard!
Promises shouldn't be made lightly.
Uh, so when in summer is
the movie coming out?
Summer's a long time.
Stupid, summer is the period
when TUBE is active.
So the movie can only be released
when Maeda's feeling up to it.
Hell no!
Unsetting Moon
The Courtesan of a Nation arc
ends next episode.
Will the promises that were made
be fulfilled...?