Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Well, if you'll let me
eat you, I'll tell you.
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh, all creation,
flap of wings...
the one who carries
the title of human!
In the name of truth
and temperance,
dig your claws into
the wall of sinless dreams!
Destruction Spell 33...
Pale Fire Crash!
Good, at least this much of
my powers are back... Huh?
Ridiculous! It didn't even scratch him!
Hah! I know that trick!
It's a Soul Reaper spell, right?
But yours is so weak.
I felt nothing.
Dammit!
As I thought, my Kido hasn't recovered
enough to use a spell of that level.
How many years has it been…
since I last saw Karin cry…?
Until our mom died,
Karin was a crybaby, just like Yuzu.
After she died, Yuzu, who was
the clever and responsible one,
tried to fill in for our mom, and began
to take over the housekeeping.
Karin, who wasn't good
at much of anything,
stopped crying altogether so
as not to worry the rest of us.
Even when she lost
a fight with an upperclassman,
or when she hit a ball through
the window
of the principal's office and
was reprimanded,
or when she broke
her leg while hiking,
she never cried once.
Karin…leave this to me.
Are you really a Soul Reaper?
Why don't you take off that human form?
Huh?!!
Oh…did I…get him?
Huh…? He hit a Hollow…?
Can he see spirits…?
No…maybe not…
What's this…
he just happened to hit me…?
I thought he could see me-
There… I got 'im…
I-Impossible…
He shouldn't be seeing the Hollow,
much less hearing his voice…
He's calmly facing down an enemy
he cannot even sense…
Doesn't he have any fear…?
Damn…
Bet you can't touch me here!
What are you going to do,
you good-for-nothing Soul Reaper?
Don't just stand there!
Get away! He's up in the air!
Transfer student… You can see ghosts?
Never mind about that!
In any case, at that distance…
– Where is he?
– What?
He's flying isn't he?
In which direction?
What good would knowing that do?
I'd do this…
Now, what shall I do…?
Shall I do a hit-and-run and
snatch him like a falcon?
What is this…?!
Now…where is he…?
Right there!
Swing down right there!
Now, give up.
Someone's on his way
to finish you off.
What's so funny?
No wonder you Soul Reapers,
the whole bunch of you, are always…
getting beaten by us!
Looks like the shoe's
on the other foot.
You Soul Reapers take us too lightly.
That's why you end up like this.
Now…who shall I start eating…?
I think I'll save the guy for last.
What…?!
T-This is crazy!
You think you can solve all
your problems with muscle?
You muscle-headed idiot?!
Ugh…This one's got such
sharp instincts…!
This way, Chad! Kick the air above me!
Damn!!
No! Not there! Up above!
In the sky?!
I have an idea!
Transfer student…
Will this really work?
Yes. We'll utilize your strength
and my brains.
What can I say…?
This don't seem smart at all.
I don't have to take that from you!
Let's go! In the direction of the tiger!
Which way is the tiger?
Humph! Left!
Left…
You fool! That's too high!
Okay, here we go.
If I'm this far up in the air,
no electric pole will reach me.
Fire!!
Give up!
O-Okay…! I-I give up…!
Just kidding!
W-What happened?
S-Sorry about that.
He caught me by surprise.
Damn…! What in the world
are these… leeches?!
Exactly!
They won't come off easily…
Besides,
they're my targets!
Transfer student…!?
W-What happened?
Are you surprised?!
Those leeches are small bombs.
They respond to sounds from my tongue,
and explode!
Your guard was wide open.
You wanna take me on, you lummox?
But you…
Oh!
I get it… He ran off a while ago to gain
some time to bring this here…?!
I'm sorry, Mister…
He caught me…
Shibata…
Looks like you understand now, big boy.
Now, it's time for us to play, Soul Reaper!
Now run! Let me enjoy hunting you down!
Don't move from here, Chad…
If you take even a step,
he plans to blow up that birdcage.
Transfer student, what about you?
You needn't worry about me!
I gave my word…
not to foul up!
Your word?
This is getting fun…!
You're covered with them!
How nice…to see you covered in blood.
You're so pretty…!
I can hardly…wait!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
How long do you intend
to keep running?
You can turn around
and attack me, if you like!
Well?! Soul Reaper!
Huh? What is it…?
Have you given up already?
That's no fun.
Come on, run, will you?
I haven't given up…
I have no need to run anymore.
What…?
You said that I could
attack you, didn't you?
In that case,
I will take you at your word.
Right…Ichigo…?
What do you mean,
"Right, Ichigo"?
Didn't you promise to not worry me
by fouling up?
Fool! That's a line for someone who's
even a little bit worried, to say.
I guess you're right.
Damn you…!
How long do you intend to
sit on my head!!
Ichigo Kurosaki, 15 years old!
Currently a surrogate Soul Reaper!
If you want to chase someone,
aren't you running after
the wrong person?
Surrogate Soul Reaper…?
Damn!
If that's so…I should have…
gone after you from the start!
Ichigo!
You slowpoke!
You look the tastiest…
I see. So you used those bombs
to pin Chad down
so you could enjoy attacking a girl?
You're nothing but a stinking pig!!
But now you're gonna be eaten
by that stinking pig.
I-Ichigo?!
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Chad! Perfect timing.
Go and hide him and
the parakeet somewhere safe.
Transfer student… What is this…?
Don't worry. He's now…
in the middle of a battle!
Good move.
But remember, the leeches,
that flowed out of their bodies…
are also bombs!
There's something
I want to ask you.
Are you the one who
killed the parents…
of the kid inside the parakeet?
What?
He said it's all my fault.
Because of me, the man
and the girl got hurt.
Shibata…
It's all because I wanted to bring
my mom back to life.
I'm sorry…
I want my mom to come
back to life.
But...
Wait!
Did someone tell you…
that he would bring
your mother back to life?
Did someone tell you
there was a way to do that?
That's right.
I'm the one who killed
that kid's mother – while I was still alive.
At the time, I was a serial killer.
It was all over TV –
I was famous.
That kid's mother was my last victim.
It was so much fun…
She ran as hard as she could.
She barely had any breath left,
but she still tried to protect her kid.
It was such a thrill.
But that's where it went wrong.
I chased her out onto her veranda…
That kid!
He grabbed my shoe laces…
Who woulda thought I'd get killed
by a slip up like that…?
I decided to pay that kid back.
I put the soul of the boy, who survived,
into the parakeet, and I told him this:
Three months! If you can
run around in that form for that long,
I would bring his mother back to life.
Bring her back to life…?
Fool! Of course, I couldn't do that –
bring a dead person back to life!
But that kid believed me.
He ran as hard as he could.
What's fun about this
penalty game is that
I could kill off any and everyone
who tried to protect the kid.
And each time, the kid would whine
and beg to quit.
He didn't like it, he said.
That's when I used my clincher…
"Your mother is waiting for
you to save her!"
Hearing that, he would
always regain his will.
He'd cry, "Mom…! Mom…!"
What are you sympathizing
with him for?!
You dropped your guard!
This is the end for you!!
You can have this bomb back.
What's wrong?
You're going to set it off, aren't you?
Come on and click your tongue!
Aren't you going to
click your tongue?
In that case…
I'll take your tongue!
Ah, my tongue!
Get lost…!
Wha..?!
It is Hell…
The Zanpaku-to can only wash away
sins committed after death.
For Hollows that committed major sins
before their death…
the Gates of the Netherworld will open!
So…he's gone to hell…?
Well…?
It's unfortunate, but…
his chain of fate has been severed;
there's no sign of it.
There's no way I can return him
to his body.
No…
Shibata…
Don't worry!
Soul Society isn't a scary place!
You'll never get hungry,
and your body will feel light.
You'll probably find it
a better place than this!
Oh…? You can say that…
when you're just a hanger-on…?
But, that might be true.
At least, if you go over,
you'll be able to see your mom.
Oh!
You can't bring her
back to life,
but now, you can go to her.
Ichigo…
Mister…
Thank you for everything…
You ran around with me in your arms,
so I didn't get hurt at all…
Yes… You're safe…
Well, I'll be going, then.
Thank you very much.
Yuichi…
When I die and pass over...
would it be okay if I carried you
and ran around again?
Yes!
Now, then…
Shall we get on with the Konso?
Thank you…Ichigo…
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Pardon me for the last time.
I'm Kisuke Urahara,
owner of the Urahara Store.
I'm going to do my best to bring you
the preview this time.
The Urahara Store
got its start when I…
What are you talking about?!
I told you we don't have
much time, didn't I?!