Ichigo and his group had been
defeated by the formidable Espada
when the captains of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads arrived.
Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto
had ordered them
to go to Hueco Mundo.
Captain of Squad 11,
Kenpachi Zaraki,
came to Ichigo's aid and
engaged in a fierce battle
with Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora Gilga.
After his eyepatch was cut off,
Kenpachi unleashed his power.
In response,
Nnoitora did his sword release
and took on
his Resurrección form.
With six arms, Nnoitora repeatedly
lashed out at Kenpachi,
and seriously wounded him.
But no matter how much
blood he lost,
Kenpachi laughed,
reveling in his joy of fighting.
Unnerved by
Kenpachi's eerie laugh,
Nnoitora lost patience and
attacked even harder.
With deep wounds
that bled profusely,
Kenpachi was
unable to counter.
Then he senses
his impending death.
And finally,
Kenpachi made his move.
You're an eyesore!
Just hurry up and die!
Kenpachi!
At this rate…
I will really die, huh?
Kenny…
Cripes… I have no choice.
It's been awhile, but I guess…
I'll try some Kendo.
Did you know?
They say the sword is mightier
when swung with both hands
rather than one.
Huh?
Isn't that…pretty obvious?!
Nope, it's not.
Has he given up?
He's just standing there like that!
I'm the strongest!
I am the strongest!
W-Wait! I give up!
I-It's my loss.
What? You want to say something?
What's wrong with
killing the loser?
"Even though it's
a fellow Arrancar," you say?
Of course. Isn't it obvious?
It's because we're both
Arrancars that I killed him.
Listen up…
If you intend to follow me,
then remember this.
Pity won't save a comrade.
I'm…
I'm saying I don't
want to fight you.
I can't see any purpose
in fighting you.
Sure, there's a purpose.
Fighting itself is my purpose.
I don't understand.
Why are you so desperate to fight?
Because I want to die.
I want to die in battle.
That's why I get strong.
If I'm strong, people will
come to me looking for a fight.
And I'll be able to live
and breathe fighting.
That's an addiction.
You're right.
Even the best drink tastes
like water compared to a fight.
In our existence,
there's no such thing as salvation.
That doesn't change,
whether Aizen is here or not.
If I'm grateful to him at all,
it's for making me more powerful.
Thanks to him, I've been able to
experience higher levels of battle.
I will become strong.
Stronger than anyone else.
If I'm going to fight
the strongest foe,
there can't be anyone else
stronger than myself.
I'm gonna crush them…
with whatever method necessary.
I'll be cut, and breathe
my last before I fall.
That's how I want to die.
That was a blast, Nnoitora.
Kenpachi…
Kenpachi?
H-Hey, are you crazy?
You…
Kurosaki!
What're you doing?!
Pick up…your sword.
After you pick it up,
take the women and go home.
Your job is done.
We'll take over from here.
W-What're you saying?!
I've come this far! I'm also…
What are you?
You're a Substitute Soul Reaper.
Your job is to protect that town.
Isn't that so?
You rescued that woman.
You should be satisfied.
If you understand, go home.
Besides, you've already had
your share of fighting.
Woman!
Y-Yes!
Heal my wounds!
Sorry…
I don't usually enjoy doing
troublesome stuff like this, but…
Let me borrow her for a bit.
They disappeared.
Welcome back…
Orihime.
What's the matter?
You look awfully troubled.
Smile.
Everyone will be sad
if the sun doesn't shine.
Smile and wait here for a while.
That is all you need to do.
Just until…
we erase Karakura Town.
Erase…Karakura Town?
Yes.
I will destroy Karakura Town
to create the Ouken.
Kaname…
Yes, sir.
The Tenteikura.
Bakudo Number 77…
Tenteikura.
Can you hear me,
my guest of intruders?
That voice…
Aizen!
They are using the Tenteikura.
I commend you for defeating
the Espada thus far.
And I shall reward you
by telling you this.
We will proceed with our invasion
of the World of the Living.
What?!
It can't be!
I thought there would
be no invasion
until Inoue awakens
the Hogyoku?!
Where is Inoue now?!
Orihime Inoue will be
kept in the Fifth Tower.
If you wish to rescue her,
come and get her.
She is no longer of use to me.
What?!
Did he say, no longer of use?!
Her powers are amazing.
Her power to reject
all forms of phenomenon exceeds all
bounds of human potential.
The higher-ups of
the Soul Society
understood the importance
of that power.
That is why her capture
would be a threat to them,
and they took steps, not to
protect the World of the Living,
but the Soul Society itself.
We now know that the Arrancar
are ready for battle.
All the members of
the Hitsugaya advance troop
are to return immediately
and defend the Soul Society.
And her presence was
enough to become
the bait to lure in
the Soul Society's potential
new military strength.
The Ryoka, which included
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
Damn it.
Furthermore, I succeeded in
imprisoning the four captains
who came to assist them
here in Hueco Mundo.
The four Garganta that we
passed through to get here…
have all been sealed!
What?!
Can't we open it up
from this side?!
Not possible.
The only one who knows how
the Garganta works at this time
is Kisuke Urahara.
As long as there's
no way to contact him,
opening it up again
is impossible.
As much as I hate to admit it.
The magnificence of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
lies in the thirteen captains
all possessing the power
to stand as a military strength
all on their own.
But now, three have defected
and four are imprisoned.
It can be said that the military
power of the Soul Society
has literally been cut in half.
It will be so easy.
We will destroy Karakura Town,
create the Ouken,
and overthrow the Soul Society.
I shall take you on, leisurely,
after all this is done.
Destroy…Karakura Town?!
Hold it, Ichigo.
Where are you going?
What do you think you can do now?
Then what do you suggest?!
Karakura Town is in danger!
You expect me to sit and
wait for that to happen?!
Didn't I tell you?
The Old Man gave Kisuke Urahara
a set of orders to carry out
once he knew the final battle
was gonna come in the winter.
The first order was to send
the captains to Hueco Mundo.
The second order was
to get every officer…
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
that is at captain-level
ready for battle in Karakura Town.
The second order was
to get every officer
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
that is at captain-level
ready for battle in Karakura Town.
Then the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads are…
Yes, they should have
arrived by now.
That's crazy!
To fight in Karakura Town…
The power of all
the captains fighting there…
What would happen
to Karakura Town?!
It will be totally leveled
to the ground.
Remember,
he said "ready for battle."
That was his order.
Just increasing the number
of captain-level men
does not signify being
ready for battle.
He meant "Tenkaiketchu."
It means to reconstruct Karakura Town
to make fighting possible there.
In order to do that,
Kisuke Urahara constructed
a device called "Tenkeiketchu,"
connecting four pillars to
form a giant Senkaimon
with a radius of one Spirit Mile.
And he placed it around
the four corners of Karakura Town.
At the same time,
he asked my Dept. of Research and Development
to construct an elaborate
replica of Karakura Town
in the outskirts of
the Rukon District.
Now, what a headache that was.
But we pulled it off.
The Tenkaiketchu differs
from a Senkaimon
in that it can switch
what it encircles
with something in
the Soul Society.
In other words,
by utilizing this,
we were able to transfer
the real Karakura Town
directly into the outskirts
of the Rukon District.
What about…the residents?
We put them to sleep
and sent them all
to the Soul Society
along with the town.
What you see out there now is
merely a replica of Karakura Town
that's completely devoid of people.
Even if the captains do battle,
even if the town is destroyed…
It won't matter at all.
It seems we made it in time.
Made it in time?
Now why would you say that?
I'm well aware that what lies there
is not Karakura Town.
But that means nothing to me.
Stark, Barragan, Halibel…come.
If Karakura Town is
in the Soul Society,
we'll just kill you here
and create the Ouken
in the Soul Society.
That's all there is to it.
Until then…
I will leave
Las Noches to you…
Ulquiorra.
Yes, sir.
Kenpachi…
You said earlier
that protecting Karakura Town
was my job, didn't you?
You're wrong.
My job…is to protect my friends.
Come…
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Kurosaki, I got an invitation to
Rurichiyo's kemari festival!
What? Weren't we
gonna talk about
the Soul Reapers' past
in the next episode?
That can wait until
after the tournament!
We've gotten such little
screen time as it is.
Let's savor it!
Ishida, don't make it
sound so pitiful.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Okay, look this way!
In order to look sexy, you have to
open up your collar this much!
This is…too embarrassing…
Oh, this is nothing!
COURSE ON HOW TO LOOK SEXY
IN YOUR SOUL REAPER UNIFORM
Okay, you too, everyone.
What are you doing?!