What's wrong?
You can't cut me from that distance.
The fact that you're
waiting there means that
coming any closer puts
you within my range.
I need to think of a plan.
Did my actions seem meaningful to you?
What about this?
I believe I shouldn’t view
them as meaningless acts.
Scatter…
Senbonzakura…
It seems like you've got guts!
Wait…
I haven’t lost yet!
Stop, idiot.
Why die in a pointless battle like this?
It's…It's not pointless!
I’m ready to throw my life
away for Mr. Tsukishima!
Is this Tsukishima guy really
worth risking your life for?
Of course!
Mr. Tsukishima is super strong!
I would die for him!
That's not what I meant.
I'm asking you whether
he would die for you!
What does that matter?!
He may not die for me, but
I’ll die for him anytime!
You idiot!
If you're going to risk your life,
it should be on equal terms!
It doesn’t matter if he’s
your boss or subordinate.
Only die for somebody
who’ll die for you!
Throwing your life away so easily
is something a kid would do!
I’ll ask you again.
If you’re to die here right now,
will your boss risk his
life to avenge you?
Aren’t you going to share
it with Shishigawara?
It’s not nice to leave him out.
I thought it’d be troublesome
to increase his power.
When this fight’s over, kill him.
I thought he had an interesting
ability, though.
If you’re still willing
to die for him, come at me.
I'll kill you with everything
I've got so you have no regrets.
Do you understand now?
You cannot cut me or
even get close to me.
Oh, right there.
What is this?
A trap I set.
When did you set this up?
A long time ago.
Does that mean you’ve been
in this dimension many times?
You know about my powers, right?
I see you've figured it out.
My “Book of the End” inserts my
existence into my target’s past.
When I cut the ground back there,
it made it so I’ve been here before.
So your power works on
inanimate objects, too.
I don't remember ever saying it didn't.
And I just inserted myself into
your sword’s past as well.
Your blade will never hit me again.
I've seen your sword and
all of your techniques
so many times that they bore me.
A moment of hesitation sealed your fate.
You wondered if I knew about
your Senbonzakura’s…
“safe zone.”
Due to Senbonzakura’s unique
attack method, there is…
an area where the blades can never
enter in order to protect its user.
The area encompasses an 85
cm radius from its user.
Once inside, you cannot be injured.
That is the safe zone.
The safe zone even exists in its
Bankai, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
It is probably the only
weakness of Senbonzakura's
invulnerable offensive and
defensive capabilities.
When fighting against your
Senbonzakura, one must advance,
not retreat.
But without that knowledge,
taking that action is
psychologically near impossible.
That is why you have
not mentioned this fact
to anybody, with the exception
of a very few close relatives.
So you’re saying
you uncovered Senbonzakura’s weakness
by facing it countless times?
Then tell me, whom did you hear
the term "safe zone" from?
From you.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
I cut you just now.
Now come get me, Byakuya.
None of the techniques you’ve
developed will work on me.
That's because I helped you
develop those techniques.
I guess that means Senkei and Gokei
won't work on you.
Not even Hakuteiken.
It's no good. I can't cut it!
I'm not sure what kind of animal it is,
but I could never cut it!
I just can’t!
What's this?
I thought you couldn't cut cute things.
You fool!
Dressers aren't cute at all!
Oh yeah?
I guess we have different tastes.
I should have filled that
stuffed animal with rocks!
You finally came out of hiding, huh?
Are you relieved that you
can finally kill me?
A Soul Reaper's duty
is to protect humans.
I have no intention of killing you.
Huh?!
That's not what I was asking!
Read between the lines, will you?
You think you could kill
me in a fight, don't you?!
Well here’s what I think!
You’re full of yourself!
Dodging it like it's nothing, huh?
Cocky little bastard!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
No matter how much you
increase its power,
you are no match for me.
Give up.
Let's end this.
Think of me however you want.
But I have no intention of
killing an ordinary human.
A Fullbringer isn’t
an ordinary human!
Addiction Shot!
What is this?
Rukia Kuchiki!
I permit you!
What?
Why am I a stuffed animal?!
Oh, how cute!
But you can't hold your
Zanpakuto looking like that!
Come back here, Tiny Devil!
Who are you calling a
Tiny Devil, you fool!
This is a rabbit stuffed animal!
At least call me Tiny Bunny!
It’s not a rabbit, it’s a devil!
Can’t you tell by looking at the tail?
What are you, stupid?!
And don't you think you're
pathetic for not being able
to keep up with a stuffed animal?!
I can use my Flash Step!
I see!
When I think about it, I'm only
trapped in a stuffed animal.
I haven't lost my Spirit Energy!
What?!
Hado Number 33:
Sokatsui!
It…
It exploded inside of me…
What?
I don't know what just happened,
but you sure are stupid!
You don't mind if we
finish this, do you?
Now you understand that
Fullbringers aren't
ordinary humans, right?
You seem to care a lot about proving
that you're not ordinary humans.
Is not being normal
that important to you?
Of course.
We were able to meet Tsukishima
because we weren't normal.
Ginjo saved us because
we weren't normal.
When asked what rule every animal
and human in the world has to obey,
most people would say
"survival of the fittest."
There are clear differences
between the strong and the weak.
But it's not as simple
as kill or be killed.
You know what true survival
of the fittest is, don't you?
So let me tell you a story…
About how our…
survival of the fittest works.
Let go, Riruka!
No! It's mine!
Why don't you let go, Gina?!
Don't be like that! Are you stupid?
Mom!
Riruka took my doll!
I found out I had an ability
that no one else had when
I was five years old.
When I was six years
old, I was invincible.
When I was seven years old,
there was someone I liked.
He was a young man who moved
into our neighborhood.
He used coarse language,
but he had a kind voice.
If he saw someone in trouble,
he would run over to help them.
I hid him away without a second thought.
Everyday, I'd bring him sweets
and we'd eat together.
I was so excited because I thought
he was going to become mine.
But that never happened.
Ever since I hid him in my treasure box,
he'd become more and more afraid of me.
I couldn't bear to see the way
he looked at me any longer,
so I let him go.
I didn't even stop to think
what would happen if he
told anyone about my power.
The term "Survival of the
Fittest" is just an illusion.
The weak believe that they can become
the predators if they work hard.
But they don't get eaten
because they're weak.
They get eaten because
they are the minority.
It’s always the incompetent
and loud majorities who
become the predators.
You and everyone else know this,
but you choose to ignore it.
Separated, we were the prey.
One who couldn't see the
value of her ability
because she couldn't
protect her family.
One whose mind and the way he used
his power were twisted
from being neglected.
One whose power convinced him
that he was the voice of God.
Someone who became alone
because she used her power foolishly.
When Ginjo appeared
before us, he said…
Are you just going to die quietly
just because there are only a few of you?
That's absurd!
Look at history!
Whether it is royalty or warriors,
it was the minority
that controlled things!
You haven't done anything wrong.
The world is just too
lenient towards idiots.
Let's change all that.
It's our turn to eat them.
We…
Somenomai… Tsukishiro!
Damn it!
I'll be honest with you.
I can understand where
you’re coming from.
However…
I will not make that an excuse of
having to abandon my friends!
Friends?
Why don’t you just say that it’s
the majority that matters to you!
Don't make a fuss.
If I use Tsukishiro one more time,
your entire body will be frozen.
That's what I mean when I say
you're full of yourself!
What?!
How did I get out of
the stuffed animal?!
I’m really sorry.
I didn’t want to use this
power to end our fight, but...
Damn it…
Where did she disappear to?
It broke.
You made a wise decision
to undo your Shikai
after learning that I’ve
uncovered your safe zone.
And your sword skills have
improved considerably.
But now that your sword is broken,
you will have to fight
using Shikai again.
What's wrong?
Are you unable to use Shikai
now that it's broken?
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi…
You're going straight into Bankai, huh?
But…
Whether you're in Shikai or Bankai,
so long as I enter your safe zone…
you're powerless.
There are blades in the safe zone?!
You revealed your weakness too soon.
My weakness?
The fact that you figured
out my safe zone
means I can anticipate
where your coming at
If I set up my blades from
within the safe zone,
it can cut you.
How odd.
I don't remember you
doing such training.
Things I've trained to do
won't work on you, right?
I get it now.
It was just a desperate maneuver.
Trying to cut me with
that is ridiculous.
You can make Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi move twice
as fast if you control it
with your hands, right?
It feels like it's moving
even faster than that.
But you do realize it, don’t you?
The more you train
yourself to be faster,
the narrower your safe zone
becomes. It’s suicidal.
The safe zone is meant to give you
minimal response time to
dodge your own blades
in the event you lose control.
When you increase the
speed of your blades
and narrow your safe zone,
if I just disrupt your timing a little,
you won't be able to dodge them.
Well?
Do you understand?
You can't defeat me no
matter what you do.
You're using Kido now?
Before you fall into despair,
I'll tell you something.
I know how to cancel out all of
the Kido techniques you use.
Come on. Why don't you
try one out on me?
I see…
You grabbed some of your blades…
I never knew you could fight like that.
I used to think that battle was something
you trained for and went
into fully prepared.
But today, for the first
time during our battle,
I experienced the ecstasy of
being in the moment
between life and death.
Thank you.
I enjoyed our battle.
If what’s hidden inside
your Combat Pass
is nothing but a horrible truth…
Then I will cover your eyes
and ears to prevent you from learning it.
The Complete Quincy.
Honestly… Going off
on his own like that…
He hasn't changed at all.
Sir, we have an emergency patient!
Understood. I’m on my way.
Do as you please…