Other than being able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
In order to prevent Aizen
from wiping out
Karakura Town,
an Enriched Spirit Zone,
the Soul Reapers moved
Karakura Town
to safety in
the Rukon district
and took up positions in
a replica of Karakura Town
that they had placed in
the World of the Living.
Upon Genryusai's order,
each of the Soul Reapers faced off
against the Espada and Flacciones.
Soi Fon,
captain of Squad 2,
faced off against
Barragan's Flaccion, Ggio.
Soi Fon engaged in
a mid-air battle with Ggio
in his released form,
Tigre Estoque,
but Ggio's increased speed
and strength of attack
gradually began to run her down.
Meanwhile, Omaeda,
who faced off against another
of Barragan's Flacciones Nirgge,
also struggled against Nirgge's
released form, Mamut.
Omaeda could only
run away from Nirgge,
who swung his trunk
and chased Omaeda
with speed that did not
match his body.
It appeared Nirgge's attacks had
finally caught up with Omaeda, but…
How did you?!
Who do you think I am?
What?
I am lieutenant of Squad 2,
and concurrently the leader of
the Stealth Force Second Unit,
"Patrol Troops," Marechiyo Omaeda!
That's the "Stealth Force."
There's no way I'd be slow.
Smash 'em,
Gegetsuburi!
All right!
You fool! I won! Serves you right!
Talk smack to me, will you?!
Look at you now, pauper!
Hopping like a bunny with
that huge body of yours!
You've got no substance!
You've got a face like
a vacuum cleaner, you bastard!
Shall I tear off this
funny nose of yours?!
Oh?
I see. So it was all an act, huh?
Uh, no, I'm sorry!
C'mon…
I said wait.
Oh… Ow ow ow!
My nose is still here, right?
What?! What just happened?!
What the…
C-Captain?!
C-C-C-C-C-Captain!
Are you all right, Captain?!
I mean, what's gotten in to you,
Captain?!
You look like you're in
serious trouble, Captain!
Shut up!
Don't make a fuss over
something so minor.
You're stifling me.
But…Captain?!
Turning your back to an enemy
during battle is inexcusable,
even if your superior is down.
But what subordinate wouldn't rush
to their fallen superior's side?!
Besides…
That guy has
overwhelming strength
to be able to put this much
pressure on Captain.
We have to fight him together,
Captain!
Is that compassion
for your superior?
Or is it loyalty?
That's not it at all!
It's just that…
Just what?
I don't ordinarily even feel like
dealing with your arrogance,
but don't forget that sometimes
it leads to insulting me!
Move. You're in my way!
Have you completed your farewells
with your second in command?
Why would I have to do that?
Because you're going to die.
Isn't it obvious?
Even if I should die, I have
no need to tell him farewell.
Glad to hear that.
What's the big idea of
treating me like a nuisance
when I'm just concerned about her!
No matter how you look at it,
that was mean!
She landed on her butt.
She hasn't got any leeway!
Damn, she really pisses me off!
That bastard's impressive…
He's keeping up with
Captain's moves!
In fact, he's evenly matched
against the Captain!
Wait…
Can you really call that even?!
Isn't it nice that
our weapons are similar!
You can fight using familiar
fighting techniques!
You can make full use
of all your strength!
In other words…
Even if you use all your strength,
this is the best you can do!
I knew it.
Captain is getting pushed back.
Is she putting on an act?!
No, even if she were
putting on an act,
that prideful captain who
shoved away my offer to help
would never pretend to be losing.
Should I go to assist, after all?
No, if she says something
like she did the last time,
even my natural reaction would be
"don't monkey with me!"
That's right,
see if I go to assist!
I don't care what happens to her!
Is that so?
Oh, damn right!
Don't forget about me!
Worried about your subordinate,
after all?
If I have to worry about
my subordinates each time,
there'd be no end.
I wonder.
But it looks like there
won't be anything
about your subordinate
to worry about.
Why is that?
I doubt your second will be alive.
What do I care?
It's his fault for being weak.
He gets what he deserves.
You are quite a cold captain.
Maybe I overdid it.
I should've held back a bit.
That fatso was
a real wise ass and annoying,
but it's not fun
if it ends like this.
Well now, you have nothing more
to worry about, right?
I think I'll settle this now.
Worry, you say?
Sorry, but I hold no such feelings
toward my subordinates.
And besides…
Oh that hurt.
Damn you!
I wonder why it is.
I don't really know why myself,
but my body's been sturdy
since the time I was a kid.
Maybe it's because rich people
are built differently than
the average joe, after all.
I'll fix that wise-ass
mouth of yours
so it'll never speak again!
I'm not falling for
the same thing twice!
Smash 'em, Gegetsuburi!
Here goes!
C'mon, c'mon!
What happened to
the fight you had earlier?
Are you afraid of my strength?!
I'm doing well!
Did you see that, Captain?!
What's she doing?
She'll get killed!
Oh no!
No fair, you bastard!
One more time!
Looks like our roles have switched,
captain of Squad 2.
It seems your second in command's
battle will be settled soon.
It's about time we settle
this side, as well.
Now you know.
Damn it!
It's useless.
You can't run away anymore.
It looks like your boss's fight
will end first, though.
That's not my concern.
She's in quite a peril over there…
Do I go to help her…
No…But…
If I don't do something
about this guy first,
he'll attack me from behind!
I can't do anything unless
I get this trunk off of me…
A Cero?
Here I go!
I wonder what'll happen if you
get hit at pointblank range.
Come to think of it,
I told you my name,
but I didn't have the time
to ask for yours.
Not that it really matters, though.
See you, captain of Squad 2.
What is this? You're in the way.
How'd you appear all of a sudden?
Gotcha!
Didn't Nirgge kill you?
Nirgge? Oh, you mean
that elephant bastard?
I can use this force against him…
Idiot! I used the strength
of your pull!
Captain!
That's how it happened!
Anyway, I did it, Captain!
I got him!
Now, Captain!
This is your chance!
Got me?!
Who are you saying that to?
Blow away.
Who told you to come
and rescue me?
Didn't I tell you earlier?
Your arrogance can sometimes
be an insult to me.
But…
I wanted to observe the strength
of an Arrancar's Resurreccion.
In preparation for the next battle
against the Espada.
Well, never mind.
I've seen enough of his limits.
Y-You-You don't have to
put it like that!
I came to rescue you, Captain,
because I thought you were
going to be killed!
But what's with that?!
"Who told you to come
and rescue me?"
That's so mean!
You said it like I did something
I shouldn't have!
Miser! Ogre! Meany! Wicked!
Lend me your ear, Omaeda.
What is it?
You moron.
My guess is that you were
worried that if I was killed,
you would be next,
that's why you came to help.
Well? Am I correct?
I…never…
Besides,
let's say I was killed.
Have I ever taught you
to come to my rescue?
I thought I taught you,
if a fellow squad member is killed,
think of it as a good opportunity.
Don't get in-between.
Stab the opponent from the back.
If there is that big
a difference in ability
between you and the enemy
that you can't even do that,
then let your fellow
squad member be killed.
That's the way of
the Stealth Force!
See?
Your enemy is still alive and well.
Hurry and get going.
That's harsh!
You don't have to treat me
like a nuisance!
Never mind and go.
And…
defeat him quickly.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Arrancar…
I'll show you
what you mocked as the "best"
a Stealth Force fight could be.
A real assassination…
What?!
That bastard!
He's seriously lost it.
I can't get close to him like this!
Unforgivable!
I'm never going to forgive you!
That was an anticlimactic ending!
You're mine now!
Sorry.
Where are you?!
I learned something earlier.
I thought I taught you,
if a fellow squad member is killed,
think of it as a good opportunity.
Don't get in-between.
Stab the opponent from the back.
It's not only when
a fellow squad member goes down.
One's own crisis can be
an opportunity, as well.
You bastard…
You mean you went down on purpose?
It's over!
You're going to show me
a real assassination, you say?
Amusing.
Wait. I take back what I just said.
What?
Someone of your low level
might not be able to see it.
Don't…Don't mock me!
W-What was that?
Look you!
I'm going to show you
what true strength is!
Behold!
This is Tigre Estoque's
actual battle form!
Tigre Estoque Sable!
Sorry.
I said my Suzumebachi
kills in two stings,
but you probably felt
only one, didn't you?
Damn it.
All right!
You did it! Way to go, Captain!
But I don't get it.
So Suzumebachi is
effective even if it
doesn't sting twice
in the same place?
It did.
Huh?
I gave him two strikes to the same
location in his right lung,
once from the chest,
and once from the back.
I went for the organs instead of
the wound from the very start.
Never mind that.
Don't talk too much, Omaeda.
A new opponent.
Don't give out anything that
might put us in jeopardy.
Right.
And follow me so
you don't get in the way.
Right!
That Mamut what's-his-name
wasn't much of an opponent.
Wrong! My name is Nirgge Parduoc.
Mamut,
written "giant elephant soldier,"
is my Resurreccion form!
It doesn't matter.
You're already dead.
Oh shut up!
Today's Zanpakuto is
Renji Abarai's Zabimaru.
Roar, Zabimaru!
When Zabimaru is released
it can extend and retract
via its segments, allowing it to
destroy even enemies at a distance.
It is a frightening weapon.
When it takes form,
it is a baboon's body
with a snake for a tail,
each with its own personality.
Renji is fond of saying
that the two
often complain
to him together.
You'll have some,
won't you, Rukia?
Now I understand why
you get a lot of complaints.