Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
You're pretty good!
But I don't have the time to
be fighting with you!
You fell for it!
Good bye.
You idiot…!
Y-You…!
Hado 33! Sotatsui!
You're too slow!
Kuchiki!
I'm all right.
Thank goodness…
Is that it?
You're not a problem at all…
An Eishohaki Kido
isn't good enough…
But a spirit chant will take too long
against her speed.
Then leave this to me!
Kurodo.
What do you plan to do?
This is what I'll do!
What?!
I borrowed Renji's form.
I'll distract her.
Do a spirit chant in the meanwhile!
Oh my… You plan to challenge me
with a sword?
How amusing…
Did he transform?
It doesn't matter…
We'll just defeat him!
Now here I go!
Kurodo!
It's all right.
Kurodo can also copy the fighting ability
of the people he copies!
Kuchiki, do it now!
All right!
I'm not finished yet!
This isn't child's play!
Cut it out!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh,
Come on, come on, come on.
all creation, flap of wings.
The one who carries the title of human!
Tsubaki! Koten Zanshun!
I reject!
In the name of truth and temperance…
It's useless, useless, useless!
Dig your claws into the wall
of sinless dreams!
Hado 33! Sotatsui!
Impossible! We had her… But…
Oh my god!
Close.
Too bad!
Kurodo!
You bastard!
Now then…
What are you going to do next?
I can't move…
It seems I'm fated to witness
the death of young ones.
It saddens me to see lads with
bright futures ahead of them…
die before my eyes.
Old man…
I don't want to die…
I'm not ready to die!
Kariya.
It's been a while, Cloud…
No, do you have a different name now?
What do you want?
I want to entrust this young man to you.
I want you to teach him how
to live as a Bount.
Sorry, but I don't
have any intention to.
A Bount lives by training himself in secret
and believing only in his own strength.
I don't plan on conspiring with anyone.
I want to entrust him to you
because you believe that…
It seems you didn't understand
what I said…
I told you that I refuse.
I'm asking a favor of you.
You've lived through
a mind-numbingly endless time.
That's why I want to entrust him to you.
He's the seed of hope for us Bounts…
Despite that, what if I refuse?
We will lose an important friend…
I'm sure you'll accept.
His name is Cain.
That's all he has.
Indeed. He doesn't even seem
to have a bit of respect…
You have a lot of time.
I want you to
take your time to train him…
Make him into a person with
your hands.
What's that?
It's a Book of Doll Summoning.
I was finally able to write it.
It would be nice if it allows even
one of our comrades
who doesn't have a doll
to be able to obtain a bright light.
Glory to our tribe.
Are you going?
I'm of the same opinion as you.
There's no way that
I'll join a fellow Bount!
Farewell!
Screw you!
If you want to go, then go.
I won't stop you. But…
If that's all the power you have,
then you won’t live very long.
Damn you…
Now if you understand,
help me with my work!
Old man, take a look at this.
Oh?
This is pretty nicely made.
How about this much?
Thank you…
This will be enough, won't it?
Of course!
Take this.
This is for me?
It's going to get cold
this time of the year.
You can't train if you're frozen.
Say, Old Man.
What is it?
Thank you!
It might have been good
for me to meet you…
Until I met you I was living in a way
I don't even want to remember.
I even thought…
that you were a joke.
Be proud that you
were born a Bount.
Pride…
Oh! Wait for me!
Oh?
That's a pretty nice coat.
This is for your own good.
Leave all your belongings here!
Who the hell are you!
Stop!
They're not people you want
to waste your time on.
I see…
That's great!
Y-You bastard!
Wh-What's with this guy…?!
Let's go.
But…
We're leaving.
As I expected…
They followed us…
We thought that you were acting big.
You're the forest monsters, aren't you?!
Monsters should stay in the forest!
Get them!
It can't be helped…
Zeig Dih.
Dalk!
Did you call?
I'll leave this to you.
Roger!
It's been a while,
so I'll give it my best!
It's a monster!
Amazing… So this is your doll…
You're still all by yourself aren't you?
One day you'll have one as well.
You're not a stray dog.
You're a chosen human. A Bount.
A chosen human…
A Bount…
Cain, just leave it at that for today.
But I can still do more!
Cain…
What do you want to do once
you become strong?
What do I want to do?
Yeah…
I want to catch up to you.
And if it's possible,
I want to live with you…
Since coming here…
I train my body, make meals,
wash clothes…
Well, cleaning is a pain, but…
I was thinking that things
like that aren't that bad…
It feels like I'm living…
I see…
Yeah…
It might be about time you
had a doll of your own…
A doll?!
The steps to gain a doll are written here.
It's a Book of Doll Summoning
that Kariya finally put together.
A Book of Doll Summoning…
A doll will become someone who
understands you if you raise it properly.
But…
I'll give the summoning steps.
Don't do things on your own!
Okay…
It was too early for him,
everything was…
I'm the one…who killed him…
Schwefel, phosphor, kohlenstoff,
wasser, fett, magnesium, kalk…
Zauberspruch für die ladung.
Oh great power…
I, with my tribe that has eternal life,
wish for a way to personify your power…
Awaken and give your birth cry
within the crimson fire.
If you do, I shall give you my life
as a token of your heart's integrity.
Right now, our hearts stretch across
different worlds
and welcome the time we become one.
Zeig!
Mein doll!
Cain!
Old Man…
I've finally got a doll!
Take a look at her…
Look at how small and beautiful she is…
Just watch.
I'm going to make her follow orders!
Stop, Cain!
With your power, you still can't…
It's all right! I can do it!
If I talk to her kindly like this…
I'm sure she will…
Say… Do something! Just like Dalk!
I'm tired… I still want to sleep…
Don't say that… Please.
Lend me your power.
Okay? Please…
Then…show me your power.
I won't do anything for you
if you don't!
Huh? My power?
Yeah!
W-What should I do?
Then I'll test you…
Oh no!
Cain, get away from her…
Cain!
Old Man…
I don't want to die…
I'm not ready to die!
Cain!
Cain! Cain!
Forgive me… I lost the life
of an important comrade…
I…
I wanted to show this
to Cain as well…
The dawn break…
Yeah.
Let's live together.
This sadness is too painful for us
to bear while living in isolation…
We should live together…
Yeah…
Since that day…
Kariya became our leader to me…
Oh my, how persistent.
You…
What do you plan to do?
The thing that Kariya wants is…
a clean world ruled by Bounts.
He wants to create a new world!
What?!
When a Bount is powered up
by sucking the souls of living humans…
Their Dolls gain even more power
by a multiplier effect.
And soon, we will rule the world…!
No way…!
I won't let you
use Keigo's life for that purpose!
It's useless.
Realize that you can’t beat us, boy.
I won't!
Those eyes are dangerous…
Power without ideals is dangerous.
Please understand, boy…
Damn it! I won't let Keigo die!
It seems evident that
I was born under a star,
destined to witness
the death of young ones
with bright futures ahead of them…
Farewell, boy.
Oh my. Is it all right to do it?
Yeah…
Who is it?
So…you're a Bount.
Thirteen Court Guards
Third Company Lieutenant…
Izuru Kira!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Inoue, we're going to
cooperate in this battle.
This is the first time
we're working together, isn't it?
Huh? If that's the case…
does this mean you're the groom
and I'm the bride?
No, in this case,
I'm the groom and you're the bride?
Oh! Could it be that
we're both the groom?!
I don't know what you're talking about…
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
If you say the world lacks justice,
then I shall become justice itself.
Then I will erase the world's evil
like clouds.
I risk all of my justice.
Cry, Suzumushi!
Aren't bell bugs amazing?
They sure are…
Tune in next week!