Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
The appearance of my next target.
Kurosaki!
Look!
Wha--?!
Zabimaru!
Hado 4!
Byakurai!
Kuchiki!
Sister!
Roar! Haineko!
This doll uses the shadows that are
produced by the eyes as a gateway!
You!
Abarai! Kurosaki!
Go on ahead of us!
Renji!
All right.
Yumichika!
Renji, it's coming!
Damn!
This is the real Gesell!
Yumichika!
What the--?!
He's huge…
This guy…
Now which should I crush first?
Before that,
I should return this to you.
Stop!
Are you all right?!
Yumichika!
To think I let him…
do this to me. It seems that
things have become quite ugly.
It's Zaraki Squad's style
to lose only when you die.
I can't face my Captain
and the others like this.
Oh? You're still breathing…
Soul Reapers are pretty persistent,
aren't they?
You bastard… Where are you hiding?!
Come out!
Damn! If he won't come out, then we'll
defeat his doll and drag him out!
Ichigo!
Could you leave this to me?
Teamwork isn't so bad…
Urahara taught me that
direct attacks aren't the only means
of fighting, and I understand that.
But… I've been thinking that lately,
I've become used to those situations and
I've been letting my guard down.
What are you talking about?
I remembered…
The way we do things,
fights are one-on-one.
We lose when we die.
If I'm going to die,
I'm going to go all out!
Renji…
I couldn't save a single child.
At that time, I might have thought
that someone would come to save me.
URAHARA'S SHOP
But…
I only put that kid in danger.
It seems that I've become soft ever
since I've come to the World of the Living.
If I don't show more spirit right now,
I can't return to Soul Society!
Besides, there are still
more Bounts after this.
You should save your stamina!
Renji… You…
An active Lieutenant is paving the way
for you! Don't complain!
All right.
I'm your opponent!
You're going to fight Gesell
by yourself?
It's reckless… Gesell, crush him!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Renji! Look out!
Zabimaru!
My Spiritual Pressure is holding
Zabimaru's blade segments together.
I can separate or join them at will!
It won't break with that kind
of attack!
That's pretty amazing…
But it's not beautiful.
I'm going to finish this all at once!
Oh, well…
What's this?!
Fighting your way doesn't
seem like a good idea.
Renji!
Stop!
What?!
It's Zaraki Squad's style to
fight one-on-one!
He's not a part of Eleventh Squad!
He's a former member
of Eleventh Squad.
Anyone who joins Zaraki Squad
never forgets that, even if they leave.
But--!
Ichigo!
Just shut up and watch!
I'm going to turn this around!
Renji…
Oh? How?
You don't have
any options left.
Th-This is…
Master Kariya!
It seems that a Soul Reaper
has appeared before the Quincy!
So they've arrived…
What should we do?
The situation has changed.
Ugaki, finish this at once!
I understand.
So you've come out.
That fighting spirit is
quite impressive!
I never expected you to confront me,
knowing that you'll die. How foolish.
It's easy for me to finish you off.
Fine.
I will respect your feelings and crumble
your snake with Gesell's power.
This is the end!
Go! Gesell!
Higazekko!!
Gesell, what's wrong?!
Damn! I've got to retreat…!
What's that?!
There! He's controlling the doll
from there!
Th-This is impossible… Why?!
Ugaki, good work.
What?!
Farewell.
That's impossible!
Master Kariya! Wait, please!
Gesell has gone out of control!
Kariya! You won't get away with this!
I fought perfectly!
But you…
Stop, Gesell!
It's me! Don't come near me!
Renji!
You go on ahead!
I'll take care of Abarai!
Wha--? What are you talking about?!
Seems like I am indebted to Abarai.
Go quickly!
Hey!
Renji! Yumichika!
Damn it!
Are you the only one that survived?
You bastard…
How many Bounts do you have to
destroy to make yourself feel better?
We're a valuable tribe…
that's few in numbers as it is.
What did you say?!
I would have preferred if you were
buried along with Gesell.
What?!
Well, that's fine.
It seems it'll take a little longer
to get what I seek.
Th-This is impossible… Why?!
You bastard… Did you intentionally
collapse the area around him?!
Who knows?
The foundation loosened due to
that redheaded Soul Reaper's attack.
Whatever the case,
the wall fell on its own.
What do you mean, "valuable tribe"?!
You used one of your allies
as a pawn to slow us down!
I didn't plan to.
It's just that things are going
slightly faster than planned.
We have to prepare to
leave the World of the Living.
Leave the World of the Living?!
Do you really plan on connecting
the World of the Living with Hueco Mundo?!
Could it be that you're planning…
the same thing as Aizen?!
I'll be fine by myself.
Begin preparations.
Andere welt eins schritt sende porte,
tauch dich sofort auf!
What's that?!
It's our Senkaimon.
What?!
You know, don't you?
Powerful Bounts who have absorbed
a large number of souls can…
manipulate space.
I'll take the controls.
Please do.
I really should have
finished you off myself.
What?
Now let's begin.
I, too, want to test my own power.
Fine!
I'm going to crush you
along with that gate!
What?!
What's going on? I thought I hit him.
How can he block Zangetsu unarmed?!
Mabashi.
Huh?
If you have the time to get drunk
off living souls,
take a good look at that battle.
That is the essence of a Bount
who has gained power!
Is that it?
I can't even test my powers
at that level.
What about your Bankai?
What?
I know everything.
You're the only one who can
use your Bankai in the World of the Living
without strength restrictions.
That's why I said you would make
a good target to test my powers against.
Take your zanpakuto!
Damn…
Looks like this is it.
That's not…
True!
I know. It'll be a pity for you to die
without knowing anything.
So I'll tell you what our true goal is.
What?!
Kariya?!
There's nothing to worry about.
I don't remember hiding it
to begin with.
Connecting the World of the Living
with Hueco Mundo…
That's an explanation that Yoshino and
Soul Society thought up on their own.
What good would that do?
We're not headed to Hueco Mundo.
We're headed to Soul Society!
Wh-What--?!
This is revenge.
We're going to Soul Society,
where the Bounts were created!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Is it true that the Bounts plan
to go to Soul Society?
That's what that bastard, Kariya, says.
Then we've got to go back.
Aww… I haven't even gone
shopping or sight seeing yet!
Ichigo, tell me some interesting places
I can go to quickly.
Miss Rangiku will be leaving now,
show her the way out!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden After These Messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Woosh--!
Jeez…
It's fine since I don't have to
do much right now, but…
Where has Hana wandered off to?
Come to think of it,
what did I come here to do?
Is that what you like?
Huh?
H-H-Hold on a second, Store Manager!
Oh, no… I can't do this.
Tune in again!