Under orders from
Genryusai Yamamoto,
the captains of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads
come to rescue Ichigo
and the others,
who had fallen to
the powerful foes, the Espada.
Each of the captains who
came to Hueco Mundo
throw themselves into
the battle against the Espada.
Mayuri appears before
Ishida and Renji.
Despite having Nemu
taken hostage,
Mayuri swallows Szayalaporro
using Konjiki Ashisogijizo.
He thinks he has
defeated Szayelaporro,
but Szayelaporro is still alive.
He succeeds in reviving himself
by invading the body
of his captive, Nemu,
and sucking out her Reishi.
How interesting.
How nice.
Such an amusing power.
It arouses my curiosity.
And?
Is that all?
It seems…
you have no other
hidden power.
Well then, you can be
my test subject for a new drug I've developed.
You don't have to be on guard.
That drug has been
administered already.
His speech just now…
Szayelaporro, who had come back
to life through Nemu's body,
has been drugged without
his knowing.
The drug is a Superhuman Potion,
heightening the senses
to the extreme,
making instantaneous movements
appear as though they have stopped.
tNow then…
Does this sword look like
it has stopped?
Right now, one second seems
like a hundred years to you.
In other words,
as this sword gets closer to you,
with your superhuman sensitivity,
the movement looks very slow,
like it's going to take
several hundred years.
And while your senses are
heightened to superhuman levels,
your non-superhuman body
falls heavily behind.
In other words,
the body cannot keep up with
the movements caught by
the exponentially sharpened senses.
Even if you try to stop it
with your hands,
it will take several hundred years
before you can feel this blade
pierce through your hand.
But, no need to panic.
Take your time to thoroughly enjoy
the sensation of your heart
being pierced by my blade
until your dripping fluids
turn into sand.
And so, I bid you adieu until
a hundred years from now.
So long…
How many years, how many decades,
has it been since then?
No, it's been longer.
At any rate, an immense amount
of time has passed.
When on earth…
When will this sword…
pierce my heart?!
Hurry.
Hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry, hurry…
Hurry up and kill me!
The perfect being, is it?
In this world,
nothing perfect exists.
Though it's so cliché.
It is the truth.
Which is precisely
why ordinary men
are infatuated with perfection
and pursue it.
But I ask…
What is the meaning of
being "perfect"?
Nothing.
Not one thing.
I despise "perfection."
If something is perfect
there is nothing above it.
There is no room for imagination.
No space for
intelligence or ability.
Do you understand?
To men of science like us,
perfection is…hopelessness.
Be more wonderful than anything
that existed before you,
but never perfect.
Scientists must be creatures
who always agonize over
these conflicting concepts,
and search for joy in that.
In other words,
the instant you said
a crazy word like "perfect,"
you had already lost to me.
That is, of course,
if you are indeed a scientist.
H-Hey…
Is that okay?
Your Zanpakuto is broken.
It's not broken.
I broke it.
You broke it?!
As long as the hilt remains,
it can be remade.
Breaking once is fitting punishment
for a sword that disobeyed me.
Nemu! Come here!
Nemu!
Good grief…
She sure is a handful.
What are you…planning to do?
– She recovered!
H-How?! Where in your movements
did you cure her?!
What?
You can't even understand something
that obvious and easy, scum?
There's no way we could!
Just now, you did something that
you couldn't show the audience!
Something I can't
show the audience?
That couldn't be.
You people were watching with
your minds in the gutter.
Well, never mind.
Explaining my techniques
to ordinary people
is just a waste of time.
That was a blatant dodge.
Ishida! Are you all right?!
Don't get too excited!
What?!
What do you mean, "excited"?!
I was simply speaking along
the lines of good public decency!
I'm stunned that you talk about me
like a wicked pervert!
You're mistaken!
What I wanted to say is that
even if the poison is gone,
our organs are still crushed,
so we have to be careful.
The way you said
it was misleading!
Calm down…
Nobody thinks of you as
a four-eyed pervert.
Who are you calling
a four-eyed pervert?!
Man, you guys are
so stupid and arrogant.
You're really messing up
my seasoned reasoning skills.
Nemu, dig up this place again.
Yes, Master Mayuri.
– Ta-da!
– Two out of the
– Three Great Desert Brothers!
– Three Brothers of the Burning Sands
– Back in business once again!
– are back in business!
This time,
we've come back in style!
Wait, wait, wait. Calm down!
We've met once before!
Remember?!
We're on your side!
– On…your…side!
You're in the way.
While you're at it,
dig them up too.
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Wait!
Okay, okay!
We get it!
I can't blame you guys for
not knowing who we are
since we arrived in
the middle of everything!
All right, we'll kindly explain
once more.
Let's do that!
I know who you are.
You should be dead, right?
That's cruel!
It's true, but it's not!
That's right!
Whoa! Whoa! Watch it!
Watch it! Whoa!
Oh, hey!
All right, goodbye everybody!
What's this door?!
Why is this the only place intact
after everything has collapsed?
That's obvious.
When a scientist builds
his own laboratory,
he builds one place more sturdy
and secure than any other.
That place…
is neither the room where
his costly equipment for
his experiments is located,
nor is it the archive
where he keeps the papers
he wrote through the night.
The thing we do not want destroyed
more than anything else
is the storeroom where
we keep the research materials
that we went crawling to
the ends of the world to obtain.
This is…
You see?
Did he get him?!
Don't make me keep
repeating myself!
My Hierro is the hardest in
a long line of Espada!
There's no way
a Soul Reaper's blade
could cut through it!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
What're you going to do to me?!
– What, you ask?
– Let go!
– Isn't that obvious?
I'm going to fix you!
REBUILD
You're making a mistake!
That's not "healing,"
that's "rebuilding"!
I knew it!
Crap! Let me go!
Your squawking is annoying.
You really are
a lily-livered fellow.
Come on, give it some thought.
I'm saying I'm willing to
heal your wounds for free.
It's only reasonable to say
a word of gratitude
regardless of how your looks
or appearance end up as a result.
I'll do no such thing!
You mean you were planning
to go as far as
to change how I look?
Please don't move.
Too close, too close, it's too close!
What is?
Oh! Very good, Nemu!
Suffocate him just like that!
It's okay if he goes
into cardiac arrest!
This will make it a little easier.
Captain Kurotsuchi…
What is it?
Please start by healing me first!
Why?
I want to fight as soon as I can.
There are Espada where
the others are as well.
I need to rush there
and assist them.
There's no need.
Huh?
The only one who's dragging
on the fight is Zaraki,
who went to
Ichigo Kurosaki's location.
There's no need
to help such a riff-raff.
And I'm sure you're aware.
Stepping into a battle zone is like
raw meat thrown before beasts.
If you get in their way,
you'll be eaten as well.
Death by being eaten by beasts
is about as stupid
a way to die as there is.
Don't you think?
You dodged.
Dodging means you felt threatened.
Am I wrong?
It would seem that even
though you said
"a Soul Reaper's sword
can't cut me,"
there are areas that can be cut.
Stop your nonsense!
Dodging an attack is
a fighting instinct!
It's a natural reflex to
defeat the enemy!
There is no place you can cut!
Your sword cannot cut me!
That's all there is to it!
There are many types of people
in the Soul Society.
I've come across annoying guys
like you who say,
"your sword can't cut me"
on several occasions.
But…
I still haven't met someone
whose eyes and throat can't be cut!
How many times are you
going to make me say it
until you're satisfied?
You can't cut me!
Kenpachi!
You can't understand it, can you?
It's impossible for someone
who's had his head run
through to not be dead.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
You're exactly right.
Bastard!
That's where his…
No one survives when
their head's been run through.
But, I am alive.
You get it, Soul Reaper?
Your sword hasn't run
through my head.
It simply passed through my head.
Do you understand?
That was the limit of
what you could do,
Soul Reaper.
We have to rush to
Master Nel's side!
But I hear there's a beast there.
A beast, you say?!
A spikey-haired beast
covered with scars
that has a frightening gaze?
He's our ally.
Is he really our ally?
I'm not confident about it.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
A facility for Reishi experiments?
Dept. of R & D
Reishi Experiment Facility
Construction Site
We apologize for
the trouble being caused.
It's the one Captain Kurotsuchi
was talking about.
It sure is huge.
If an accident ever happened,
the Seireitei would be blown away.
What an ominous thing to say.
Iba?
Yo!
What are you doing here?
You idiot!
I've come to take back
the Men's Soul Reaper Association
fund that this building
took away from us with my own hands, of course!
I don't think you call
that "getting it back."