Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who
keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Aizen, who had taken the Hogyoku
from Soul Society,
has finally made his move.
And the battle between
the Arrancars and the Soul Reapers
has finally begun to
manifest itself.
Dance...
Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai...
Tsukishiro!
Which one?
I'm asking which is the stronger one?!
Snip!
Tijereta!
Hitsugaya, Renji and Rangiku find
themselves in a tough situation
against the formidable power
of the Arrancars.
And Rukia is seriously injured
before Ichigo's eyes.
You bastard!
Bankai!
Hitsugaya and Renji throw everything
they have at their foes,
but they are powerless
against the Arrancars,
who have released
their zanpakuto.
Squad 10 Lieutenant,
Rangiku Matsumoto!
Your "Gentei Kaijo"
permission request...
has been granted.
Thank you!
Captain!
Renji!
We've been granted
a Gentei Kaijo!
It's finally come!
I've been waiting for that!
What's this?
Gentei Kaijo!
Gentei...Kaijo?
What is...that?
Gentei Kaijo.
We captains and lieutenants of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads...
In order to avoid
unnecessary influences
upon the spirits in
the World of the Living...
When we come to
the World of the Living,
we have Spirit Seals shaped
after our squad emblems
placed on our bodies which
drastically limit our Spiritual Pressure.
The limit ratio is 80%.
In other words...
Now...
...we're five times stronger!
Too slow!
When you first came here,
you moved with amazing speed.
Well, come at me with that speed!
What's that technique called?
It's called Sonido!
I see! Ours is called Flash Step.
It's over!
Shawlong Qufang!
Growl! Haineko!
Ryusenka!
Hikotsu Taiho!
Retreat! Retreat for now!
As if we'll let you get away.
Captain! Captain!
Orihime!
Orihime! Come quickly! Please!
Dammit! That was bad...
Thanks to the Gentei Kaijo,
that guy got agitated,
so I was able to find an opening.
Even if we had fought with a full release
from the beginning,
who knows if we would've won.
Are all Arrancars strong like them?
If that's the case...
It's bad... Ichigo!
He's slow!
What's that idiot doing?!
I'll crush his balls when
he gets back!
I'm back.
Too slow!
Keigo, you went to get juice
from a vending machine.
How long does it...?!
Huh?
Umm...Sis...
Err...Umm... Actually...
When I went to buy the juice,
this man was lying on the road.
And so I couldn't buy juice.
And anyway, he'll be staying
at our house for a while.
Oh! But if you absolutely forbid it, then...
Then of course,
then I'll tell him that we can't...
Wh-Why you!
Good job, Keigo!
I'm sorry!
Huh?!
What? You're letting them stay here?
Okay! Okay! Absolutely okay.
Okay?! Are you...
Huh?
Err... No, Sis...
I mean, don't we have to get
Mom and Dad's permission?
You can't just decide by yourself.
Hello! I'm Keigo's older sister, Mizuho.
Hear me out!
Shut up, will you?!
Any complaints?
You brought him here!
But...
But I figured that if you
bluntly turned him down,
we wouldn't have to put them up.
And that's why I introduced him to you
with such frail hope, you see?!
Oh, I see.
Too bad. It's fine with me.
But why is it okay?!
He's a complete stranger!
It's dangerous!
Think it over more carefully!
It's all right.
I am the older sister who
kindly accommodates
the total stranger whom
my young brother brings home
without asking any questions.
That's the kind of sister
I want to become.
Shut up!
I don't care what kind of sister
you want to be in the future!
Or rather,
I love men with buzz cuts.
That's totally the only
obvious reason!
For that matter, he doesn't have
a buzz cut. He's bald!
Huh?!
I'm not bald either.
Yes...you're right. I'm sorry.
Dammit!
What...is this guy?!
Sheesh... You call this your Bankai?
Don't disappoint me,
will ya, Soul Reaper!
You used your Bankai
and the only thing that improved
was your speed?
Huh?!
Getsugatensho!
What was that trick just now?
Ulquiorra didn't say anything
about that in his report, Soul Reaper!
So maybe I won't disappoint you,
huh, Arrancar?!
Now we're talking, Soul Reaper.
Finally...you're worth killing!
Ichigo...! What are you laughing at?
You're sure taking your time. Huh?
Hold it. I'm almost there.
Humph...
what can you do alone?
Dammit!
His wounds aren't that deep!
He got hit with
my Getsugatensho head on,
and that's all the damage
he gets?
The Black Getsugatensho
is originally his technique.
If I use it, he'll manifest himself
more quickly.
I can only make two or three shots
while under my control.
What'll I do?!
Hey, how long are you gonna
stand there, Soul Reaper?!
Ichigo...
Now it's my turn!
Put down your sword... Grimmjow.
Tosen!
Tosen?! The captain who
disappeared with Aizen?!
Why are you here?!
Why...you ask?
You really don't understand?
Infiltrating the World of the Living
on your own...
Mobilizing five Arrancars
without permission.
And losing.
All are against orders.
You understand, don't you?
Lord Aizen is quite upset...Grimmjow.
Let's go.
Your punishment awaits
in Hueco Mundo.
Sheesh! All right!
Wait!
Where're you going?!
Shut up! I'm going home...
to Hueco Mundo.
No way!
You came and attacked!
And now you're leaving?!
Don't be ridiculous!
Come down!
Our match isn't over!
Shut up!
The one who's life was spared
because of this was yours,
Soul Reaper!
I can tell just from your current state.
That earlier technique
also damages you as well.
You probably had another
two or three shots left, right?
But even if you were able
to use it infinitely...
you wouldn't beat me
in my released state!
Released state?
Don't forget my name!
And pray that you never
hear it again!
Grimmjow Jeagerjaques!
The next time you hear my name
will mean your end, Soul Reaper!
Have the Arrancars returned
to Hueco Mundo?
Did you win?
I lost.
You fool...
The fact that you're alive
means it's a win.
Don't lie...
If you were me you wouldn't say that.
I haven't been able
to protect anyone.
I haven't even been able to bring
down the one who hurt my friends.
I lost...
Grimmjow...
K-Kisuke... Kisuke...
It's okay, Ururu.
Welcome back...
Grimmjow.
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
It seems the Arrancars use
some sort of nerve radar
called Pesquisa
to search out Spiritual Pressure.
Ichigo, if you had something
like that,
you'd be able to find our hide-out.
Shut up! Just wait!
I'll find you in no time!
We'll prepare a welcome party
and wait for you!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Golden!
Don't come near me, you-
It's useless, I tell you!
No matter how much you swing,
it'll only make our wounds heal!
Huh?
Let me explain.
Each time Hisagomaru heals
a wound,
a red gauge fills up and
when it is completely full,
it changes automatically
into the "Vermillion Hisagomaru"
and spits out the injuries
it has absorbed.
It has an amazing attack power!
Chance!