Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What about Kurosaki?
Can he be saved?!
I don't know…
But since we can't get near it,
we'll have to leave
the rest to Ichigo himself.
But…
Ichigo!
Kurosaki…
Where am I?
Is that you, Ichigo Kurosaki?
Imagine meeting you here…
How did you get here?
How should I know?!
What is this place?
Can't you tell?
Just as your Zanpakuto has
a home in the world of your mind,
I too, had a home…
Then this place is…
But he…
I don't understand it, myself…
Why am I in this place?
Did my reunion with
Koga summon me here?
Or is this simply not real…
Either way, this place will
likely come apart soon.
But more than that,
I am grateful to the destiny
that connects you and me…
To this destiny given to me
to settle our battle.
Why?!
You should no longer
have any reason to fight!
You don't get it!
Your power will nourish me.
That being the case,
I will not give up the fight.
That's all there is!
I won't fall for that!
You're not using
that attack on me!
I've seen through your move!
What?!
It's useless.
Flailing your sword around won't
allow you to escape my power.
Dammit… Why?
Looks like it's over for you.
What happened?!
It suddenly loosened…
Getsugatensho!
I figured it out!
It isn't that your technique
is invisible.
By reflecting your technique
in a mirror or on water,
you make your enemy think
there is an invisible power there.
But…
It seems the real power is
in the reflected image.
In that case…
If it doesn't reflect
on the water's surface,
you can't use your technique!
You're mine!
Indeed, I can't seem to
utilize my power
to its fullest extent right here.
But that is not
the only ability I possess.
From the moment
you and I faced each other,
you were caught in my technique.
Damn…
How do I beat this guy?
Ichigo…
Feel it…
Zangetsu!
His power of suggestion
does not work on me.
I will become your eyes.
But it is impossible for this
to work without you and I—
Zanpakuto and Master—
are truly connected to one another.
I got it, old man.
You're coming at me again?
Here we go.
How is he?!
Getsuga…
…tensho!
That's right…
You have Zangetsu by your side…
I understand now what
the old man was saying…
What?!
Recognizing and accepting
each other's existence.
That's how the relationship between
Zanpakuto and
Soul Reapers should be.
You must know that, too.
What would you know?!
Isn't it about time
you get it, already?!
Ichigo… We're at the limit.
There is a maelstrom here
of deep-seated grudges
belonging to the Hollows that
he kept consuming for many years.
They are about to crush him
at any time now.
We don't have time, Ichigo.
Yeah.
His voice never reached me…
Muramasa!
Ichigo, get out of here…
If you remain here,
you'll never be able to go back…
Muramasa…
why must you go this far to…
It's none of your business!
He said he didn't need you…
So why?
Koga's abilities are worthy
of ruling the Soul Society…
I was proud of that.
He possesses that much ability!
I can still fight!
So what?!
Didn't you say you were
going to free the Zanpakuto?!
So now you bring that up?
That was bullshit to trick you!
Is that really true?!
You even said you
killed your master!
Wasn't the truth that your master
wasn't paying
any attention to you?!
You realized that,
but still continued to exist for
the purpose of undoing Koga's seal.
Wasn't that because
you wanted to
communicate with Koga
more than anyone?!
It was a pipe dream…
It wouldn't have lasted long…
Hey!
Ichigo… We won't be able to
make it in time.
If he becomes a Hollow,
pockets of reishi in the World of
the Living would become unbalanced,
and Karakura Town
could be destroyed.
He won't become a Hollow…
Muramasa…
I intend to be together with
my Zanpakuto, Zangetsu, to the very end.
Not only me!
My friends, and even
the captains, as well…
To a Soul Reaper
and Zanpakuto,
each is irreplaceable and
special to the other!
You knew that better than anyone.
Why have you been doing things
that trampled on that pride?!
You have no right to tell me that!
That is the true nature
of my power!
Holding someone down by force isn't
the only way to use a Zanpakuto.
There's no need to accommodate
everything a Soul Reaper does!
Looks like my time is up.
Ichigo…
Yeah… Here I go!
Hyorinmaru!
Captain!
That was the last one!
Yeah…
What's going on?
What?!
Muramasa…
Muramasa!
How ironic…
It's your voice that
reaches my soul?
What happened?
I don't know the reason,
but the Hollows'
Spiritual Pressure is gone.
Then Karakura Town is saved?
Kurosaki?!
What?
That's definitely Kurosaki's
Spiritual Pressure!
Is this what you call
a sharing of the soul?
Yes…
I wound up making quite
a mess of Koga didn't I?
It happens to all of us.
If you made a mistake, just fix it.
I'm sure… someday…
Ichigo…
Is everyone all right?
They're all safe.
Is Muramasa gone?
He kept his pride as a Zanpakuto
until the very end.
Brother…
Byakuya…
Rain?
What's this?
It feels strange, somehow…
I want to go back.
You're back.
Welcome back…
We're going back.
Huh?
Captain…
Yeah… They sure put us
through a lot of trouble…
Ichigo Kurosaki…
This is the second time
I'm thanking you.
Thank you for your help.
Sure…
Uh-oh, I'd better get back
to Las Noches quickly!
Huh? Sure is quiet around here.
What's going on?
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Looks like no one told you
anything again.
Ulquiorra?!
Oh no, not this again!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
What're you relaxing for,
Ulquiorra?!
Aren't we returning to the Arrancar
story arc starting next episode?
You're such a fool, Ichigo.
That's right, Ichigo!
The producers are shifting
the story line for a bit longer!
See! This is the script
for the next episode!
Why am I always late
to be informed?!
You have only
a few scenes again,
so they were going to
let you know later!
Again?
But I'm the main character!
Everyone out there, you'll need
to wait a little longer.