An unknown enemy attacks
Rurichiyo Kasumiohji,
who is from the Soul Society and
has transferred to Ichigo’s school.
Ichigo tries to
identify the enemy
but the assassin, in defeat,
commits suicide at the scene.
Rurichiyo is in fact the princess
of the Kasumiohji Clan
who got caught up
in an inheritance dispute
and escaped to
the World of the Living.
Ichigo is forced to accept
the role of bodyguard for Rurichiyo.
Today was another fun day.
Yes, Lady Rurichiyo.
Though it’s annoying for us.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You sometimes have a problem
with your choice of words
in relation to the princess.
Please be careful.
Huh? As far as I’m concerned,
this one is…
What’s with you?!
Get out of my way!
Come on, stop it!
– Hey, do something!
– It is because you did not respond quickly.
All right! I get it already!
Cripes…
Yesterday you get down
on your knees to beg me,
and now this is the attitude I get?
What do you mean,
"down on your knees"?
Did Kenryu and Enryu
ask you to do something?
Huh?
Lady Rurichiyo is not aware
that she is being targeted.
And we don’t want her to know.
Hence, we want her to remain
totally unaware of the real situation.
Uh, well…
Just some tips on how to get along
with the community in this world.
Right?
Yes.
Last night Ichigo Kurosaki
was teaching us the social customs
regarding the World of the Living.
Yes.
Huh? Princess?!
Ichigo!
What is this?
Princess,
this is a vending machine.
What does it do?
It…
Here.
Try a sip.
Princess!
Don’t worry.
It is orange!
It tastes like orange!
Drinks are sold in this machine.
Hey, Ichigo!
In this world, there are a lot of interesting
items here that I don’t know about!
So, do not hesitate to
teach me much, much more!
Is that the attitude to have when
asking someone for something?
O-Okay!
I’ll explain a little
at a time to Rurichiyo.
Address her as Lady Rurichiyo!
Too close.
It’s okay, Kenryu.
I have a huge heart,
therefore I shall forgive
Ichigo for his indiscretion.
How generous of you, Princess!
I, Kenryu, admire you!
You overreact, Kenryu!
Madam Rurichiyo!
Shall we see a few more
interesting items from this world?
Where might that be?
I’m sure you will have fun!
Here.
A job well done!
Madam Rurichiyo!
Next, let’s all do that together!
See how happy
the princess looks?
I’m glad we brought her
to this world.
Don’t cry.
You guys…
Have you thought about
what you’re going to do next?
There’s no need for you
to point out the obvious.
Well, you better
hurry up and decide.
We don’t know when those weirdos
will come around again.
Miss Kuchiki, I had never been
to such a fun place!
I’m glad to hear that.
Okay, I’ll take you home.
That’s all right.
I can get home by myself.
But…
I tell you…
Those two worry too much.
Going on by themselves
to inspect the house
before even
allowing me to go in.
It is so stifling.
It can’t be helped.
Brother!
Hey, Yuzu! I’m home!
Welcome home!
You’re late tonight.
Oh? Is that the person who
moved in behind our house?
My name is Rurichiyo Kasumiohji.
Good evening,
I’m Yuzu Kurosaki.
Oh, you are
a high school student?
I thought so.
What is a high school?
Come on, Rurichiyo.
Let’s go!
Hey, Brother!
Since we’re neighbors,
why don’t you invite her for dinner?
What?
Delicious!
Really?!
Yes, very delicious.
The tastes of the World of the Living
are quite good!
World of the Living?
Really Yuzu, your cooking
is always delicious!
Aristocratic meals are nothing
but manners and they are so boring.
Don’t you agree Miss Kuchiki?
Aristocratic?!
Never mind the details, Yuzu.
Huh? But…
She’s a little different, this one.
Rurichiyo, what’s wrong?
I don’t like this.
Oh, you don’t like carrots?
I’m sorry.
What are you saying?
Farmers work very, very hard
to grow these vegetables.
Eat them all.
Farmers grow these?
Yeah… Just growing one of
these vegetables is a lot of work.
Eating them with curry
is very delicious!
D-Don’t worry about it.
Don’t spoil her!
Wait!
Just who are you people?!
Pardon us, so late at night.
You guys…
Ichigo Kurosaki!
How dare you force Lady Rurichiyo
to eat carrots!
Huh?
I can’t even remember how many
stewards have been heavily punished
in the past for serving carrots.
Well, in this case,
you didn’t know, so…
As for members of the Kurosaki family,
we will make a special exception.
What?! Me?
Listen!
You guys spoil her like that,
and she’ll become
more ignorant of the world!
It is none of your business!
Keep your mouth shut!
Ichigo!
You ask a favor of someone and
that’s the language I get from you?!
Favor?
What’s this about, Kenryu?
With a princess
as noble as yourself,
we believed we were
a little short-handed.
Are you…
hiding something from me?
N-No.
Kenryu! Enryu!
Why can’t you tell me the truth?!
Princess…
If Mother and Father were here…
I’m sure they would have
told me about farmers!
Until now, I never cared to
think of how foods were prepared!
I’m not an idiot.
I understand what you were
saying earlier, Ichigo.
But, Princess…
That’s enough!
You two are always
hiding something from me!
I do not believe you!
I hate you guys, Kenryu!
Rurichiyo!
Yuzu!
She hates us.
The princess hates us.
I tell you, those guys.
Why act like it’s
none of your business, Ichigo?
Half of this is because of you.
All right, already.
Hey, pull yourself together!
I’m at fault, too.
I’ll apologize with you, okay?
Ichigo!
Yuzu! Karin!
Rurichiyo really ran away!
Hey!
Come on, she’s right here.
No, that’s just her gigai.
Lady Rurichiyo! Where are you?
Where are you?!
It seems she turned
back into a soul.
This is bad.
If she gets attacked
by an assassin…
Either way, let’s split up
and search for her!
Okay.
Kenryu, that idiot.
Enryu, that…
Ouch…
Rurichiyo?
It is you, Rurichiyo!
What are you doing here?
You are…
Oh yes, you are Orihime!
That’s correct! It’s Orihime.
Orihime Inoue.
I wouldn’t forget.
Your name, “Hime,”
implies that you are also
a princess from a noble family,
does it not?
The “hime” is just in my name.
You are a “hime”
but not a princess?
The World of the Living
is strange.
Hey, Rurichiyo…
Why are you by yourself?
Where are Mr. Kenryu
and Mr. Enryu?
I do not know such people.
Did something happen?
It is true that I never ate carrots,
and usually left them.
But, I could eat them if I tried to.
And yet, those two were always
hiding something from me.
Mr. Kenryu and Mr. Enryu care
deeply for you, don’t they Rurichiyo?
You are so important, so they didn’t
want to make you worry about anything.
It does not seem that way.
Kenryu and Enryu are
only treating me as a child.
Hey, Rurichiyo…
When you’re cared for too much,
you begin to take it for granted.
You only end up regretting it if
you realize that once they’re gone.
Orihime…
See? That’s why you
have to understand.
I said some terrible things
to those two.
I do not believe you!
I hate you guys, Kenryu!
Will they forgive me?
It will be okay!
Let’s go home!
Okay!
My hat!
Look out!
Who are you?!
Are you committing
this act of violence,
knowing that I am
Rurichiyo Kasumiohji?!
Orihime!
It’s okay!
Huh?
What?!
W-What is this?
This way!
We’re blocked in!
That can’t be.
Why?! Why is he after me?
To do this kind of thing…
Santenkesshun!
Is this because I came to
the World of the Living in secret?
Or am I being punished for
causing trouble to so many people?
No!
Rurichiyo, you haven’t
done anything wrong!
Then why?
I…can’t hold it any longer.
I don’t like this.
I don’t like this!
Kenryu! Enryu!
Princess!
Are you all right, Princess?
Kenryu! You came for me!
Enryu, too.
Forgive me. I was wrong.
Rurichiyo!
Kurosaki! Kuchiki!
You’re late, Kurosaki!
What happened?
That!
He’s…
He’s with that guy
from the other day!
Be on your guard!
Okay!
Be careful, Ichigo!
He might use some
tricky technique.
Got it!
What?!
H-Hey, Rukia!
What’s going on here?!
It appears to be a technique that
converts a bladed attack into walls.
I’m stuck!
Damn!
Oh no!
Rurichiyo!
I-Ichigo!
Please leave this enemy to me!
Kenryu!
Bloom in glory…
Benishidare!
Oh, how pretty!
What are you
playing around with?!
I’m not playing around!
Look!
Huh?!
My Benishidare’s pollen will sprout
flowers onto any weapon it touches,
rendering them useless!
Don’t you have something better?
That’s amazing!
Don’t get impressed by that.
Now’s your chance,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Right!
Getsugatensho!
Pale Fire Crash!
H-Hey!
All right you, let’s find out
who put you up to this.
Why the hell are you all held up?!
What happened to your flowers?
You’re the one that
blew away the pollen!
My Benishidare’s pollen only works
in the area where it floats!
Useless.
But I’m prepared for this situation.
Yes! He’s blinded!
Now’s our chance!
You take care of the rest!
Are they serious
about that technique?
You’ve got it all wrong!
Let me show you
how to shoot an attack.
Getsugatensho!
That’s far enough!
Now, you will spill it!
On whose orders are you here
to kill Lady Rurichiyo?
What?!
Rukia!
Damn! Again?
This is how they work.
It looks like it’s all over.
Yes. A fabulous
Substitute Soul Reaper he is!
But… Who was that anyway?
Just a common night thief.
Princess, you have nothing
to worry about.
I’m telling you,
don’t treat me like a child.
Rurichiyo!
Sir Kenryu, are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
Ichigo Kurosaki,
even you did good!
I shall give you my thanks!
You don’t look like
you’re grateful at all.
Are you okay, Rurichiyo?
Yes, I’m fine.
That’s because Kenryu and Enryu
protected me!
Princess…
Let’s go home and
continue our meal.
Yes, but…
Don’t worry!
I won’t leave my carrots!
If I do…
I can’t face those who raised me!
Princess!
Princess, please don’t
wander off like that again.
– I was… I was…
– I know…
– Hey!
– I know now,
– Hurry up,
– so don’t make such a shamed face.
or we’re going to leave you behind.
Hey, wait Ichigo!
Enryu! Will you
cut it out already?!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
What is it,
so early in the morning?
W-What are you doing?!
That doesn’t matter!
Lady Rurichiyo has
disappeared again!
So your family makes curry
with carrots in it, Kurosaki?
Huh?
My curry only has
normal ingredients.
Aroid potatoes,
elephant yam and sweet beans.
That’s normal?
It was delicious, Inoue.
You had some?!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Yeah!
MEN'S SOUL REAPER ASSOCIATION
MEN’S LAVATORY
Don’t you have
anything more manly?
My version has manliness built in.
Color is silver and it extends
to three meters when on the phone.
Rejected!
How about this? Let us shift our focus
away from manliness a bit.
Please do focus on
the manliness part!
I guess I’ll have to show you all
what real manliness means!
There you are.
Look!
– Yeah!
I have something to report.
The Women's Soul Reaper Association
has cut the men’s budget completely.
– What?!