The End
Let the girl go!
Kurosaki!
Scatter Senbonzakura.
Who are you?!
Go, go, Kenny!
So, how do I look?
Scene 28, action!
We're going to do a movie!
What?
What did you say you're
going to do?
It's almost New Year's
movie season!
Although the great
Heisei recession,
the so-called "lost decade" of
the 90's, had come and gone,
various financial crises occurred
just as people thought
that things were finally
starting to look up.
As people tightened their
wallets from spending,
people sought low-cost
entertainment and began
flocking to movie theaters
on their long vacations
and spent their money there!
It behooves us not to get
left behind by that trend!
Are the Thirteen Court Guard
Squads that short on funds?
From what I heard,
there apparently were
considerable expenditures
to repair the damage to Seireitei
caused by repeated emergencies.
That's because nobody thinks
about the damage
to their surroundings
when they fight.
And so we have decided
to hold a
"Seireitei International
Film Festival,"
celebrating the release
of Bleach Movie 4!
The release of Bleach Movie 4?
What the hell is she talking about?
Don't think too hard.
Let's make an awesome movie
and wow everyone.
Yes, let's do our best,
Renji, Ichigo!
Huh? Why am I included?
What's with all this enthusiasm?
And where did all this equipment
come from anyway?
Make way!
Seireitei International
Film Festival
Co-sponsored
by Urahara's Shop
So it's from him, eh?
Isn't he supposed to be
banned from Seireitei?
Kurosaki.
Unohana...and Komamura?
Good afternoon.
Are you guys filming too?
Yes. Squads 4 and 7 are working
together to make a movie.
Oh? What's it about?
It's a moving drama about
animals saving human lives
in a world where disasters
have destroyed civilization.
Animals? You don't mean...
What are you looking at?
Is there a problem?
Uh, no... How should I say this?
You don't quite fit the image.
I see...
Actually, I thought the costume
wasn't as well-made as
it could have been.
Captain! Please don't say that!
It's because my acting
isn't good enough.
Forgive me for hindering
the production!
No, that's not it.
All right Tetsuzaemon, then I shall
teach you how to act better!
Yes, sir! Woof!
Ready? Shake!
Perhaps we should ask Squad
12 for some help.
Captain, should I do that
with my right hand, or left?
Captain Kurotsuchi did
say he was preparing
Hmm... Let's try
it with the right.
Shake!
Woof!
full-body costumes for
his special effects film.
Too slow!
Urr... Let me try
it again, woof!
Shake!
A special effects film
by Squad 12?
Too soon!
We need to get
our timing right!
You sure they're using
full-body costumes?
Right!
This time we'll try
with the left hand.
Kurosaki.
Okay, woof!
Are you free right now?
Shake!
Woof!
Yeah, I suppose.
That's good!
Then would you mind playing
a part in our movie?
We're short on actors and
could use your help.
What? I don't think I...
We're short on actors and
could use your help.
O-Okay...
It looks very good on you.
Um... Isn't this a...
All right, we'll be doing scene 15,
the fight scene between the main
character and the human
who was turned into a dog-man
by the curse of the dead dog!
What kind of scene is that?
What? That you, Ichigo?
K-Kenpachi! What are
you doing here?!
We're making a movie!
We in Squad 11 are making a blockbuster
movie starring our captain!
It's an action flick where the
captain cuts down anything
and everything, including people,
poles, and even worms.
And what's more, it's a documentary
where nothing is faked.
Awesome, huh?
Will that work as a movie?
Ichigo! Just the man I needed.
I had the urge to cut down
someone tough!
So fight me for a while!
No thanks!
What?
You saying you can't fight me?
Uh, no, well...
Captain Zaraki.
Kurosaki is currently occupied
with our film.
Please don't go along with your
plans without our consent.
What?
Unohana...
Ichigo, we'll fight later.
Let's go guys!
Yes, Sir!
Gladly!
Go, go, Kenny!
Now then, let's get
back to filming.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Thank goodness that's
finally over.
Is that you, Ichigo?
Ukitake! Kyoraku!
Hey, what's wrong?
You look beat.
Well, that's because
Unohana insisted
I participate in the filming
of Squad 4's movie.
That must've been rough.
Aren't you guys making a movie?
Well... I was all for it,
and even submitted a proposal,
but Nanao here...
I will not approve of any
films rated "adults only"
from the very beginning!
Just what kind of movie were
you planning to make?
I'm being filmed right now.
Sentaro and Kiyone are making
a documentary film
about me living life to the fullest.
They say it's to leave behind
for future generations.
What can I say?
Ukitake, are you all right?!
I just felt a bit dizzy.
Ichigo!
So this is where you were.
Quit wandering around, will you?
We were ready to start
filming ages ago.
Oh, sorry.
Well, take care, Ukitake.
Yeah, thanks.
Looking forward to your
finished product.
You're late, Ichigo!
Rukia?! What's with the outfit?
So, how do I look?
Rukia is the star of our movie.
Star?
Just what sort of movie are you
planning to make with her?
It's called "Battle Maid Cop!
Protect the Soul Society
from Space Invaders!"
I am Rukia, the Maid Cop.
Pleased to meet you, Master.
So why the hell is she
dressed as a maid?!
We incorporated the latest trend.
We can't attract moviegoers
if we don't
incorporate the latest
trends, you know.
Just so you know,
we asked Rangiku to play
the role of the Maid Cop's rival,
the lovely criminal
from outer space.
Yoo-hoo! How do I look?
And your role will be the
mysterious High School Soul Reaper
who comes to Rukia's rescue.
That's no different from real life.
And these are the members
of the Abarai Gang.
What exactly are we
doing, Kurosaki?
I came because they asked
me to come if I was free.
Muh...
Inoue will play the role of the human
under Rangiku's control.
Chad, you'll be our gofer.
And I'll be in charge of the
costume design, of course.
No wonder the maid and alien
are both wearing capes.
Ishida, you'll also be
our cameraman.
Oops! I almost forgot someone
very important.
Captain Kuchiki.
Byakuya?!
The captain will be in charge
of visual effects using kido.
The Seireitei's honor hangs on
the Film Festival's success.
Therefore it is mandatory for all captains
to participate in this event.
Okay! Let's begin before
it gets dark!
Scene 62!
In this scene, Ichigo rescues Rukia,
who is about to be executed
by Chad and Inoue
who are under Rangiku's control!
Let's do it!
Wow! I get a scene
right from the start.
Mu...
Wasn't I supposed
to be the gofer?
Don't worry about the details.
Wait, you're the director?!
Listen up! Here's how it goes.
Rukia is captured after falling
for Rangiku's trap.
And Ichigo can't do anything
since Inoue and Chad
are under Rangiku's control.
Meaning you're in a
desperate situation!
And?
You rescue Rukia. That's all.
How?
Figure that out yourself!
Are you serious?
Places, everyone!
Captain! I'll leave the visual
effects up to you!
Please make it look dramatic.
Got it.
Action!
That is cowardly, space
criminal Rangiku!
That is the whimpering of a loser!
If you're frustrated, try getting
yourself out of this situation.
This will not make me lose heart.
I am sure my friends will come
to rescue me at any moment.
It'll be over for you by then!
Finish her!
Okay!
We're sorry, Kuchiki.
We don't want to do this,
but right now, she has
us under her control.
Inoue, that's not what
you're supposed
to say while under control.
Oh dear heavens!
I am in a pinch!
What will happen to the
fate of the Maid Cop?!
Hold it right there!
Who are you?!
Let the girl go!
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, the High School
Soul Reaper will take you on!
Hey, for someone who was reluctant,
you're really into this.
Shut up!
Say that after you see
the situation you're in.
I have hostages, you know.
Can you harm people
from this planet?
Kurosaki, I'm so sorry.
She has us under her control.
Muh...
You're playing dirty!
Say what you will!
Now, kill this guy!
What should we do
in this situation?
Never mind! Just attack!
Ichigo, you dodge!
Man, your directions
are so general.
Muh...
Okay.
El Directo!
That won't work on me!
It needs to look more
exciting than that.
Captain Kuchiki, please do your thing!
Got it.
Inoue! Put your hands out in
front and take your stance!
Huh? Me?
Just a pose will do!
All right then.
Hado Number 33: Sokatsui!
That was close.
Hado Number 4: Byakurai!
Why is your aim so accurate?!
You're not the one I'm fighting!
Chad! What're you waiting
for?! Continue attacking!
Mu...
El Directo!
Scatter Senbonzakura.
Oh no, Ichigo!
How could you do such
a thing to him!
I won't hold back even if you
are people of this planet!
Inoue! Chad! Now drop
to the ground!
Oh no, she got me!
Muh!
Such impertinence!
Ah well...
I'll let it go for today. Farewell!
Kurosaki... Thanks to
your sacrifice, I live.
Thank you...and farewell forever.
Don't go killing me off!
Oh my gosh! You're alive!
Of course I am!
Point!
Let us continue to protect the
peace on this planet together.
Cut!
OK!
Are you all right, Kurosaki?
I'm not all right.
I thought I was going to die.
Kuchiki!
Huh?
What's the matter, Ishida?
I forgot to put this patch
on Kuchiki's costume!
What? Who cares?
We have no choice.
We'll fix the costumes
and do it again!
Everyone! I want you to do
it again just like we just did!
What?!
This is going to be our
next filming location.
Sokyoku Hill?
Yeah. No camera has ever
entered this sacred place.
That's why there's value
in filming here!
Are we pulling off the "Produced with full
cooperation from the famous" tactic?
Yeah.
So what do you think, Ichigo?
Doesn't it make you excited?!
What's the matter, Ichigo?
There's something wrong
about this whole film.
What do you mean?
I mean, why am I the only one
who's getting beaten up?!
The explosions are
too powerful,
the attacks are precise,
and I get shoved down from crazy
places without warning!
You did some great acting in
every one of those scenes!
I wasn't acting!
And besides, I don't
have a clue as to
what the story of this
film is to begin with!
Who cares?
We're going to cut and paste during
the editing stage anyway!
When it comes down to it,
we can just erase the sound
and dub over it,
and we can do anything we
want with CG and music.
I knew it! You're not putting
any thought into this!
I think that's fine.
Focusing too much on the script
could cause problems.
Take Shuhei's group
for example.
They still haven't finished
the script yet,
and now they are way
behind schedule.
Hinamori is so
pissed off.
You don't want to
end up like them.
Wow, that sounds rough.
When the script is late, it's the
crew on the scene that suffers.
Muh!
That's not my concern!
Byakuya! Your aim
is too accurate!
Do you have a grudge against me,
or something?
Not at all. It's just that...
I decided it was necessary
in the pursuit of reality.
How noble of you, Brother!
We're letting our names
be credited in this film.
By the Kuchiki Clan's honor, I cannot
allow any mistakes to be made.
Aargh! Forget it!
I'm quitting!
What?
But Kurosaki, we've come
this far into the filming.
Sorry Inoue, I can't
do this anymore.
What'd you do that for?!
What're you afraid of?!
So you got beat up
during filming.
You're letting yourself get discouraged
by something so trivial?
You're not confident about
looking good on camera?
Or are you afraid of getting beaten
up in the pursuit of reality?
If you don't have confidence
in your acting,
make up for it with passion.
If you're not confident about
making it look real,
think up some way to fake it.
If you're afraid of the schedule
pressing down on you,
do all your scenes in one take.
Even if no one else
believes in you,
hold your head up high and
shout out your lines!
That's the man I know
you as, Ichigo!
You talk too much!
Okay! Let's start filming again!
Is everyone ready?
Yeah!
What are you people doing here?
Crap! They found us!
Huh? What do you mean, Renji?
Never mind. Pack it up everybody!
Hey, you didn't get a
permit to film here?!
Of course not!
What?!
I thought it would be easier
to just do a guerrilla filming
than go through the hassle
of getting permission.
Intruders! Get them!
We're surrounded!
No!
Roar! Zabimaru!
This way! Hurry!
Hey! Wait, Renji!
Kurosaki! Hurry! Hurry!
Don't let them get away!
What is this place?
How would I know?!
Hey, it's a dead end!
No choice.
Bankai! Hihio Zabimaru!
All right! Just as I planned it!
That's going too far.
Damn! They headed us off.
How is this "just as
you planned it"?!
They're coming from behind too!
Captain...
By the Kuchiki Clan's honor,
I won't allow myself to
be captured here.
Your honor disappeared the moment
you got involved with this film.
Wait, Byakuya! What're
you going to do?!
Bankai... Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Run!
He did it!
And so peace returns to the
Soul Society thanks to the
Written by: Renji Abarai
efforts of young Ichigo Kurosaki,
who blew himself up.
Maid Cop: Rukia Kuchiki
Lovely Criminal: Rangiku Matsumoto
Finally, we'd like to add that
this story is a work of fiction
and is not associated with
any actual location.
Special Effects: Byakuya Kuchiki
Camera: Uryu Ishida
Gofer: Yasutora Sado
Thank you for your
support everyone.
Directed by: Renji Abarai
Okay! It looks great!
I'm calling it "Close Call
for the Soul Society!"
The Film Festival Grand
Prix is as good as mine!
I knew I shouldn't have done this!
There's a grand prix for
this film festival, right?
It's been cancelled.
Why?!
The Seireitei was destroyed
during filming.
Therefore, the grand prix money
was used for the repairs instead.
But that was all your fault.
The Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
We're making a movie too!
How stupid! Count me out!
Oh? And here I was going to
make you the star, Hiyori.
If that's the case, then
I might consider it.
What the hell is this?!
I'm calling it
"Great Monster Hiyora"!
You damn baldy!