The new Gintama anime has been running for half a year.
It's already been half a year? We've finally made it through half a year?
The world may change around us, but
we're still rolling along here.
Kodokan Dojo
S-Sis...
I-I...
I got myself a g-girlfriend!
What? A girlfriend?
I'm in a relationship with a girl.
R-Really?
I-I see...
In that case, congratulations, Shin-chan.
You approve of our relationship?!
I was up all night,
worrying about telling you.
A-Actually, I brought her here
so I could introduce you.
Huh?
Will you meet her?
I'll tell her to come in!
Wait! She's here?
Isn't it a little early for this?
Don't worry. She's not that
fussy about that stuff.
Come in, Momo-san.
Sis!
This is my girlfriend, Momo-san!
Hello.
Love Is Neither Plus Nor Minus
Right now, Edo is obsessed
with the new game Love Choris.
In this dating sim,
the game is linked to the real world
as events progress in real time.
When you start the game in the
morning, she says good morning.
Good morning.
At night, she says good evening,
and this is only the beginning.
Good evening.
This game is made so well that
Edo is filled with boyfriends
who can't bear to
spend a minute away from their little lovers.
Huh, that's not good.
If you waste all your time because
you can't distinguish
between game and reality,
you'll never get a real girlfriend.
Isn't that right, Momo-san?
I wish we could share some
of our happiness with them.
Here you are.
It seems that I'm not wanted
here, so I'll be making my exit.
Hey, where are you going?!
And I ask you where your brother has gone?
He's trapped in some dimension
between game and reality.
He showed up with that thing and said that
he wanted to introduce me to his girlfriend,
and he's been like this ever since.
It's okay.
When Sadaharu is in heat, he
keeps humping stuffed animals.
After a while, he'll stop.
That won't work! Shin-chan
is in heat all year round!
You girls don't think much
of Shinpachi-kun, do you?
Are dating sims supposed
to turn men into that?
I wouldn't know.
You see, Otae-san,
dating sims are games where the
goal is to score with the many beautiful girls who show up.
Why is this guy showing himself
like nothing is wrong?
Why is he acting like he's
been up there the whole time?
In other words, this is
the only way to enjoy love
for men who have no luck with women.
You would know, wouldn't you?
In other words, the worse
a guy does with girls,
the more likely he is to
get hooked on dating sims.
So a super S-class cherry boy like
Shinpachi-kun will stand no chance.
A super S-class stalker shouldn't be talking.
This game was able to completely
hook a veteran date simmer like me.
It is difficult to describe the
destructive powers of this game.
That's what my girlfriend Sayaka-chan said.
I'm Sayaka.
Those destructive powers did a number on you.
Th-This can't be!
Does that mean Shin-chan might
never return from the dark side?!
Sayaka-chan!
Did you try to make contact?
Yes, I was looking for a chance
to take the game away from him...
What are you doing?
Please don't touch Momo-san!
He's so mentally unstable that he
thinks the game is his girlfriend.
If you want to reach out to him,
you must join him in his little world!
How do we do that?
That should be obvious.
Welcome to the world of Love Choris.
Name
Birthday
Blood Type
Please begin by inputting your name
as the name of the main character.
Gintoki Sakata.
Hey! Why do I have to play this crap?!
To bring Shinpachi-kun
back to the real world.
Don't give me that crap!
That'll take too long!
How am I supposed to get
hooked on a kiddie game?!
It doesn't matter if you
get hooked on the game.
You just need to be in
the same world as he is.
Why don't you go talk to Shinpachi?
You think Shinpachi-kun
is going to listen to me?
First, you need to choose
one of the three heroines.
Love Choris is a game where
you win over one of the
heroines and engage in a
real-time relationship that
is amazingly realistic.
The first heroine is Sayaka Otakai-chan.
She is the captain of the railway
club that you're also in.
An excellent student and athlete
who's also Isao Kondo-kun's girlfriend.
Why are you part of her description?
I sure like you.
You just happened to choose
her as your heroine.
The second heroine is Momo Anigasaki-san.
She's one year older than the main character
and the helpful older sister type.
Shinpachi-kun chose her as his heroine.
Why did he choose an older sister character?
That's pretty disgusting.
You don't want to choose
the same heroine or people will get jealous.
Which means you're left
with the third character.
Pinko Shiramizu.
Wait a sec!
This character is noticeably
different from the others!
Pinko-chan is the owner
of a Chinese restaurant
that the main character frequents.
She's a widow who lost her
husband, Takuzo, a while back.
This is obviously Pinko!
It's like she's from a
totally different world!
Give me Sayaka-chan or Momo-san!
Hmm, but they will be very difficult.
Doesn't matter.
It feels better when you finally land them!
No, that's not what I mean.
To choose a heroine,
you have to shoot down the one you want.
Why is it a shooting game?!
And it takes a long time before
Sayaka-chan or Momo-chan show up.
The hell, it's like I'm
Making It Through Pinko!
Oh, now you've done it.
You're stuck on Pinko-chan's route now.
There is no other route, is there?
How did you guys get normal heroines?!
Forget it! Let's just get this over with!
I'll just win over Pinko!
But first...
You have to decide what you
want Pinko-chan to call you.
I don't give a damn!
It's more fun if you have her call you by that.
If she wasn't Pinko, maybe!
Forget it! Gintoki will do!
This is good enough!
Takuzo.
She's completely ignoring me?!
She didn't even say my name!
She's still stuck on Takuzo!
But you can choose between the pronunciations
Takuzo, Takuzo‘!, and Takuzo“!
They're all the same!
The ones on the right are Takuzo.
The ones on the left are Takuzo“!.
Another choice that
involves a shooting game?!
They're all Takuzo!
Can I just start this game already?!
Okay! I can finally begin!
Right, your next choice is about the
catchphrase for Pinko-chan's
child, Enari-kun.
How do you want him to pronounce,
"That's not helping, okay?"
Enough is enough already!
You're going to become his new father.
It's important to build a strong
relationship with her son.
Sengoku BABASAN
That's not helping, okay?
The right castle is "That's
not helping, okay?"
That's not helping, otay?
The left castle is "That's
not helping, otay?"
Proceed
Secure Weapons
Secure Provisions
There's no way I have to
play a simulation game.
I'm not wasting my time on this shit!
Man, you don't know how to treat a lady.
If you turn off the power without saving,
your relationship will suffer.
Huh?
For example, my game shut down abruptly when
Otae-san laid the smack down.
When I restart the game...
Geez...
You just turned off the game again.
What was that for?
Huh? What is this? What is this?
I told you to be gentle.
What's with her? She's throwing a fit.
Sorry! Forgive me!
You want me to forgive you?
Then you have to kiss me ten times.
I'm not jealous or anything.
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
I love you, Isao-kun!
And I love you, Sayaka-chan!
Do you understand the capabilities
of Love Choris now?
They're breathing on the
other side of the screen.
B-But they're 2D.
You should look at yourself in the
mirror. I guarantee you'll cry.
Don't be so stubborn.
Apologize and patch up your relationship.
I-It's not worth it.
I mean, my girlfriend is Pinko.
The girls change according
to the player's preference.
That's the best thing about Love Choris.
She might be Pinko now,
but eventually, she may turn
into the girl of your dreams.
No, no, no. We're talking 2D here.
Well, I guess...
If you really insist, I
might give it another shot.
So, what do I do after I turn it on?
Didn't you see what happened in my case?
My girlfriend gave me the cold shoulder
because I suddenly turned off the game.
You need to do some sucking up.
That was just despicable how
you turned off the game.
You're right.
She's so mad that she won't even look at me.
That's amazing.
It's all your fault... All your fault...
Her Enari is cold and stiff now.
Hey!
Cold shoulder?! More like cold Enari!
I can't fix this now!
It looks like you were too violent
when you turned off the game.
Just apologize.
Uh, an apology isn't going to help!
You want me to forgive you?
I-I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
I didn't mean any harm!
Then recite the Heart
Sutra one hundred times!
No!
Why is my Love Choris so different?!
This isn't a dating sim!
This is Resident Evil!
Her son died.
You should wait until she's
gotten over the loss.
Uh, doesn't this game move in real time?!
I can't wait two years!
Well, in any case,
keep working on winning
the heart of Pinko-chan.
Do your best to turn her
into your ideal girlfriend.
Isn't this enough already?
I should be able to communicate
with Shinpachi now.
You really think that this
will be enough to save
Shinpachi-kun from the world of Love Choris?
Love Choris
The My Wife World Tournament
You should enter this tournament!
Th-This is...
The My Wife World Tournament?
Love Choris players from all over the country
will gather to determine
whose girlfriend is the best!
You must defeat Shinpachi-kun
in this tournament.
That is the only way to bring him
out of his dream and back to the real world.
You must shatter his fantasy...
...by using your own fantasy!
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Wake up!
It's morning!
How long are you going to sleep?
Why are you so loud every morning?
I get to decide when I'm going to wake up.
It must be nice to wake up
and go to sleep every day.
But my son...
...will never wake up again!
No more! I've had enough!
Listen to me.
You must keep Love Choris
by your side at all times,
including when you're eating and sleeping.
This will help strengthen your bond.
I did what he said.
It's already the day of the tournament,
but there hasn't been any improvement.
Enari is decomposing in real time!
And this woman is cursing me 24/7.
I wish you would suffer
the same fate as my son.
How is this a dating sim?!
No more!
Kagura's starting to look at me with disgust.
Screw Shinpachi and this tournament!
I feel the same way.
Why would I fall in love with the man
who killed my son?
Honestly, this isn't funny.
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
Gin-chan, Shinpachi wanted
to take the day off.
Oh, really.
What's going on, anyway?
Aren't you also playing that dating sim, Gin-chan?
Uh huh.
Is it really that good?
Well, I'm a grown-up now,
so I can't really say.
Yeah, it's like not like they're jumping
out of the screen or anything.
I don't get it.
Yeah...
I don't get it either.
This is why men are called herbivores and
considered weaker than women now.
I know. Me and my sweet
tooth don't get it either.
Sadaharu, pipe down.
This is how he acts when
there are strangers here.
Stop that, Sadaharu!
Gin-chan, Sadaharu won't stop barking.
Ah, Gin-chan!
What the hell...
What the hell is going on?!
Everywhere I go! Everywhere I go!
Pinko and Enari are there!
It's like I'm really Making
It Through with Pinko!
Damn, what's wrong with me?
Hey, Odd Jobs!
Gorilla!
What are you doing here?
The tournament is today.
Want a ride?
S-Sorry, I appreciate this.
What's wrong? Why are you so flustered?
Well, there's something
crazy chasing me around.
Something crazy?
Oh, no! I'm so scared, Isao-kun!
Everything's okay, Sayaka-chan.
Hey! What is this?!
Hey!
Why is your girlfriend out
in the real world, too?!
It appears that you can finally see them.
I can finally see them?!
Don't tell me that...
Of course, I can see Sayaka-chan.
And I can also see your
girlfriend, Pinko-chan.
I knew you could make it to this stage.
Other people may think that
we're just playing a game,
I love you, Isao-kun!
but this world where we can
see the manifestations of our girlfriends...
A world only accessible to those
who have mastered Love Choris...
The dimension between game and reality...
Love Choris Hole!
We're just insane!
Love Choris Hole?!
All this means is that
we've spent so much time
playing games that we're hallucinating!
You're finally on the same
level as Shinpachi-kun.
That's a bad thing!
This ain't funny!
This is no longer about saving Shinpachi!
Hey, let me out at the hospital!
It's true that from the
perspective of the real world,
we have lost our minds.
But where are we heading?
Yes, to an otherworldly
battlefield of warriors who are
trapped in their fantasies.
Love Choris
The My Wife World Tournament
There, fantasy becomes reality!
This is one creepy tournament!
They're all in the Love Choris
Hole like nothing's wrong!
They've all been hit by a Dazzle spell!
A person who hasn't reached the Love Choris Hole
is like a Soul Reaper in the Soul
Society who can't Bankai.
It's supposed to be cool?!
In the real world, these people
would be considered total failures!
These people have reached a high level.
They have completed their ideal girlfriends.
But your girlfriend is also standing out.
And not in a good way!
There's no way I can win!
That's not helping, okay?
Of course not.
Because you're dead.
Could you please shut up?
You're scaring me.
However, she's gradually approaching
your ideal girlfriend.
Watch your back.
I'm gonna avenge Enari.
You sure about that?
I see. This would be that
new yandere fad, right?
Hell no!
All I see is a psycho old lady
and a decomposing Enari-kun!
Hey, I'll trade the decomposing
Enari for your Sayaka-chan.
No, I like, want Isao-kun.
I know, right?
Why is this bitch so cute?
Your boyfriend was a
yandere in the real world!
Couldn't keep a lid on his load!
Hey! Don't say that stuff to Sayaka-chan!
Hey, now. They're starting a fight.
Stop this.
This is not a place for being
jealous of someone else's love.
It's a place to be proud of your own love.
You're...
Is it...
Kyubei...
Who the hell are you?!
It's Pinko!
A Pinko who's based off Kyubei!
Lady!
Ayu-tan!
Where did you go?
You're the one who let go of
my hand, and then I got lost!
Wh-Wh-Wha-
What are you people doing here?!
Yeah, that's what I was about to ask.
And so...
Is that supposed to be Kyubei-kun?
No way! Absolutely not!
Uh, it's Kyubei.
You obviously failed,
but you clearly based this
sad monster off of Kyubei.
You're wrong, I say!
I do not have any improper
feelings for the Lady!
Yeah!
I'm not Ayu-tan's girlfriend.
I'm Ayu-tan's mama.
Oh, really...
Hey! Stop talking!
Usually, you're the one looking after Kyubei,
but you actually wanted her to baby you.
You're wrong!
I was playing the game, and
this just kind of happened.
Okay, time to change your diapers.
What kind of playing are
we taking about here?
This tournament is messed up.
People's fetishes are on display.
And what do other people think about me?
Hey, let's trade girlfriends.
No, I, like, want Isao-kun.
I know, right?
Cut that out, stupid girl!
That little act isn't cute!
Do it again.
Say, I, like, want Gintoki-kun.
I promise to, like, avenge Enari.
I wasn't talking to you!
That's not, like, helping, okay?
I wasn't talking to you either!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna beat you down!
Hey, Odd Jobs!
Was there a heroine like that in this game?
Huh? Isn't that Sa-chan?
Looks like her.
Did someone want her as a girlfriend?
No, nobody would like that sick girl.
But look, there's her boyfriend.
Where did you go, Pin-san?
Geez, you're not supposed to leave my side.
Who the hell is this Pin-san?!
Why did you turn Pinko into this?!
Isn't this a tournament for
showing off girlfriends!
Hmm? I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I'm the ideal girlfriend from Pin-san's game.
I don't know anything else.
What's this game called?
How to make annoying girls?
AKA Annoying Girl?
Could you stop that?
My boyfriend is Pin-san.
It's too late for you to be jealous.
It's your turn to suffer the way I did
when the one I loved had
been stolen by Pinko!
Why is she here?
She's creating fantasy on top of fantasy.
Let's see if your Pinko or my Pinko wins.
Sit tighty-whitey!
Wait, that's not what
this tournament is about!
What's wrong here?
Only freaks are using Pinko!
Let's trade girlfriends.
No!
I, like, want Isao-kun.
I know, right?
Just suck it up and win with your Pinko-chan.
Sayaka-chan will always be mine.
Even after death.
Oh, there you are.
Finally found you.
Sogo, why are you here?
Huh? Kondo-san and the chief.
Are you also participating
in this tournament?
Huh? So are you?
Of course.
Don't you see my Sayaka-chan here?
Welcome back, master.
How did it feel to serve
a man you can't stand?
It was very painful.
But when I realized that I was
being my master's loyal slave,
I began to feel happy deep down.
Heh, bitch.
Please don't send me away again, master.
Well, we'll see.
Sakata-kun.
I'm not gonna trade girlfriends with you.
Please!
Can you at least give me Enari-kun?!
No.
What happened to your catchphrase?!
Wh-Who is that?!
Why is it so bright?!
I-It's a goddess!
Who is her boyfriend?!
How was he able to raise that girlfriend?!
Sh-Shinpachi?!
The day has come!
We will choose the best of the best from the
ideal girlfriends everyone has
painstakingly raised!
The Love Choris My Wife
World Tournament begins now!
Can my puny fantasy defeat his massive one?!
To be continued.
Next Episode: Making It Through Love
Next time:
Making It Through Love.
The My Wife World Tournament finally begins.
Who feels the greatest love for his girlfriend?
Gintoki is faced by difficult opponents in a battle
of fantasies. Will he be able to wake up Shinpachi?!
-