Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Good evening.
My name is Lirin.
Pleased to meet you!
Why are you doing this?!
It's a game, a game!
Damn you!
That won't do anything…
Well, see ya later!
Damn.
What's going on?!
Urahara's Shop
– Wait a second! Hey!
– Hey!
Why'd you do that all
of a sudden?!
Urahara!
Could I leave my body
with you for a while?
That’s all right.
But what happened?
Chad was kidnapped too.
The enemy is attacking us
one by one.
It's too dangerous to leave
my body laying around unoccupied.
What am I going to do?!
Come with me.
Oh?! So you're finally acknowledging
my abilities, huh?!
You should have told me earlier
if that's the case!
Well, I understand the situation.
I'll take responsibility for your body.
Damn! What’s with those guys?!
It was incredibly hard
to fight them--!
It means that there's more to fighting
than charging at your enemies.
Could it be that Aizen is involved?
Who knows…
Urahara, did you find out anything?
I analyzed
the telephone conversation…
but there wasn't a Riemon,
which is the spirit equivalent
of a voiceprint.
What does that mean?
Who knows…
At any rate, it probably means
that they're not humans
or Soul Reapers…
The Spiritual Pressure of those
three are definitely a little strange.
You can tell?
Your ability to sense Spiritual Pressure
is as poor as always…
Shut up!
If the enemies' powers
are derived from Kido,
it will be difficult to directly
attack them with zanpakuto.
So does that mean
that I can't damage them
with Zangetsu's Getsugatensho?
In theory, yes, but…
Kurosaki, can you control
the power of that technique?
It has enough power to match
Captain Kuchiki's Senbonzakura.
Even if we do defeat the enemy,
we'll suffer too much
collateral damage.
What about you?!
If you use Bankai,
you can do Kido-type attacks,
can't you?
I'm not confident that I can
control my Zabimaru in Bankai.
Those in the ranks of lieutenant
and higher, like me…
are allowed only limited powers
while in the World of the Living.
In that case…
Ishida, you're the only one
we can rely on.
Hit them with your
Quincy's power!
Y-You don't have to
tell me that!
The enemy targeted
Miss Inoue and Master Sado first
because they were easier
to take out.
Everything is going exactly
as they planned…
Thank you for your patronage.
This is Urahara's Shop.
Where's Big Brother?
It's me.
Let's continue our game
at the Karakura Museum!
Come with everyone!
Hey, wait! Hey!
What happened to
Chad and Inoue?!
Are they safe--?!
Hey!
It seems they're
at the museum.
Again--?
All right!
This time, I'm with you!
Put your minds at ease
and follow me!
Hey…
What's the meaning of this?!
Shut up!
I told you,
we don't know where this enemy
is going to come from,
so keep watch behind us!
But did you have to modify me
into a backpack?!
Don't pull. That hurts!
I wouldn't mind if
it was Inoue's back,
but why do I have to be
on this guy's back?!
Well, if I knew
I was going to carry you,
I wouldn't have modified you!
It can't be helped…
Renji and I have become
Soul Reapers,
so people can't see us--!
I would have preferred
Inoue's back…
Ishida… If something happens,
you can throw him away and run!
What was that?!
I can't do that.
I have important tools
inside him.
Tools?
Ooh…
Wh-Wha--…
What the hell is this?!
I took out some of the stuffing
in your stomach
and modified you
so I can stuff things in there.
Ah… Nicely done.
I think he'd sell if
you made lots of him.
Damn you…
I'll sue you for infringement
of stuffed animal rights!
Just in case, should someone
keep watch outside?
No, they have hostages.
There's no point in doing that.
Special Exhibit for Ichigo Kurosaki
and the Others.
Welcome.
I've accepted your invitation!
Come out!
Hide and go seek.
You guys are it!
What?
What's the meaning of this?!
If you find us,
we'll return your friends.
All right. We'll find you.
Also, leave your weapons here!
What?!
You don't know
what'll happen to your friends.
Threatening us, huh?!
Put them in that case!
Zabi- “maru” (“circle”)
They’re screwing with us!
I think a circle is fine.
Shut up!
Zan-“ketsu” (“butt”)
I'll pummel them!
You two, don't fall for
their cheap shots!
– Shut up!
It's no good…
Everything's going
just the way she wants.
What's this?
What's wrong?
Don't you feel something?
Hmm? Not really…
But I've been feeling
strange Spiritual Pressure
since we've been here.
I see…
Kon, tell me if anything out of
the ordinary happens behind us!
Leave it to me!
What's with this place?
It seems like the same room
goes on forever.
Was this building ever this big?
We're over here…
Over here… Over here…
Over here.
Which way?
The way to get out of
a labyrinth is
to advance with your hand
against the same wall.
Let's go right.
There doesn't appear to
be anything especially strange.
That's odd.
We kept going right.
So this room should be
the room next to the hall
from where we entered.
But instead there's another entrance
to the right.
It's the same room…
What's going on?
At any rate, let's head back.
What's wrong?
The entrance is gone!
What?!
Kon! I told you to keep watch!
Shut up!
I was watching,
but there wasn't anything
out of the ordinary!
That's no good.
At this rate,
you'll never clear this!
Damn!
At this rate,
I'll break down this wall!
Stop!
There's no point in doing that.
Judging by what they said,
this is a game
in which we have to solve
a puzzle or something.
A puzzle?
Yes… There should be
some sort of hint…
It's as the boy
with the glasses says!
They're making fun of us!
We shouldn't indulge them.
They're just stalling us
by doing that.
They’re such a pain
in the neck!
They're using a fighting style
that restrains our power
and keeps it to a minimum…
while making the best use
of their power.
We're going to lose if
we don't do this calmly.
All right.
Wait just a second!
– Huh?
Ah… That tickles…
Let's use this room as
the basis of our investigation.
This role again, huh?
No, this is an important job
that only you can do.
We're counting on you.
Oh well…
If you put it that way,
I guess I have no choice!
Be thankful to me!
What a simple guy…
At any rate,
let's go straight forward.
What's that room?
Let's check it out.
There's something here!
It's…a display case?
Ichigo Kurosaki
Wh-What?!
Renji Abarai
Over here, too!
There's one for Ishida as well…
What's wrong?!
Inoue!
Hey!
Chad!
Kurosaki! Abarai!
What's this?!
Hey, this doesn't look good!
I can't raise…my arm…
M-My body…
This is bad…
Da…mn…!
Hey!
Wake up!
Ichigo--!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up--!
That…hurts, you bastard!
My stuffing…is coming out…
My stuffing…
That's it!
Ishida!
Hey! Renji!
It's dangerous here!
Hurry! Let's go back to
the previous room!
This way! Follow me!
Damn!
I was surprised that you suddenly
passed out and collapsed!
Be thankful to me!
Did that mist have
hallucinogenic effects, or something?
Be careful.
Damn them!
It seems safe here.
Renji!
Stop!
That was close…
The floor suddenly disappeared…
Too bad…
Damn!
This is really strange.
This kind of infinite loop
is impossible
even considering the size
of this building.
Even so…
Hey! Come over here!
This is the pole we tied
that line of yarn to earlier!
Could it be?
Ishida, put Kon down.
Y-Yeah…
Kon, don't let go!
Huh? What?
It's a möbius strip!
They've twisted space to
connect this labyrinth!
So that's why we were
going around the same place…
Is it possible for them
to do that?!
That's the only thing
I can assume.
Anyway, right now,
we have to solve this game.
Drawing out the path
we've taken…
It's like this…
There were traps in this
and this room…
If we go to the room ahead of us,
there'll definitely be
a trap in it.
But if we move in an L shape,
we won't come across any traps…
That's it!
That's the secret of this labyrinth!
All right!
Now we can get past this!
Yeah!
That would be great, but…
Damn--!
We must have missed…
something.
How many things
do you have stuffed in me?
What's going on?
I haven't heard those guys' voices
for a while…
Shut up. Use your head a little!
It's amazing you worked
as a lieutenant
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
What did you say?!
Stop, both of you!
Besides, you're in charge
of this town.
If you did your job,
none of this would
have happened!
Be thankful that a lieutenant
took his time to come!
They're fighting!
Hey! Cut it out and
show yourselves!
Understand that it's pointless
unless we solve this puzzle.
You don't know
how to do it either!
What did you say?!
Stop! Everyone's just tired
and annoyed!
Calm down!
Shut up!
Ichigo, I'm going to do this
by myself!
Yeah, you do that!
I don't want to work
with you anymore!
Oh come on…
A split among friends--!
– I wasn't this guy's friend to begin with!
Really…!
What's this?
The space…is twisting?
What's wrong?
By this order, there's a trap
in that room, isn't there?
Advancing in
an L-shaped route…
space loops…
and traps that block us…
When that gate mysteriously
appeared…
When Inoue and Chad
disappeared…
And ever since
we've entered this building,
this Spiritual Pressure I feel is…
I see!
Kurosaki!
Abarai!
I know the secret!
What did you say?!
Really?!
Listen closely…
Could it really be so simple?
Is that really all right?
Yeah. Leave it to me.
Also, Kurosaki, lend me
your Substitute Combat Pass.
What are you going
to use it for?
It's just in case…
Here I go!
Ishida!
I knew it!
Correct!
This is…
How did you figure out
the secret?
We had the hint for a while.
I figured it out once I drew it.
This is a child's game.
There are nine rooms placed
in a 3 x 3 format.
You just made them loop infinitely.
If we were to go three spaces
forward or horizontally,
we would win.
So whenever we were close
to getting to three spaces,
you'd create trouble for us.
Your traps were all illusions.
There was no way
you could set up real traps
to match our movements.
With illusions,
you could lead us any way
you liked.
We discovered the way
that the traps were set
and avoided them.
But that was a psychological trick.
Our friends were kidnapped
and we became extra cautious.
So we moved as a group.
You never expected that
we'd suddenly go
in separate directions and…
by chance,
take up three spaces.
You probably started to worry
when Kurosaki and Abarai
went more than nine spaces
apart from each other.
That's when the twist
in space appeared.
Well, finding that was
a coincidence.
At any rate, we just had to pass
through the rooms with traps…
and connect three spaces.
Correct…
But…
Ishida!
Even if you solve the puzzle,
the game won't end
until you catch us!
It's finished!
I thought so,
you really are mod-souls.
Oh… How did you know?
I noticed that the small traces
of your Spiritual Pressure
that I felt when
I entered the Museum,
matched that of
Kurosaki's stuffed animal.
I was carrying
this embarrassing backpack…
So I got to learn about the characteristics
of a mod-soul's Spiritual Pressure.
Don't call me embarrassing!
Renji, did you notice?
No…
The one who appeared
from nowhere
used his power to control space.
Are you the one who showed us
those illusionary traps?
Tell us what you plan to do!
Wait!
Inoue! Chad!
Kurosaki!
Why?
I don't know. We were just
suddenly thrown out here…
What?!
Are you trying to use
that gate again?
No, that's not it.
You won at playing
hide-and-seek,
so we just gave
your friends back.
I'll give these back, too.
Where are you going?!
Well then…
I'm going to start the next game!
School is about to begin!
Students should go to school!
School?!
If you don't go quickly,
your friends will continue to disappear!
What?!
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Now that we know that
our enemies are mod-souls,
we can set up a plan.
You shouldn't group us
with a certain idiot we know.
Who are you calling an idiot?
You do know that
she's only referring to you
because you reacted, right?
Yeah.
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
– The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers…
– Golden!
The Female Soul Reaper Association…
It's…
An official association
of Soul Society…
which was created to elevate
the status of Female Soul Reapers.
The matters they decide on,
even affect the management
of Central 46.
It is a powerful underground organization.
Everyone!
Thank you for waiting.
Vice-Chairwoman: Nanao Ise
Our chairwoman has arrived.
Go right ahead, Chairwoman.
Chairman: Yachiru Kusajishi
What shall we play today?
Tune in again!