Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
The last specimen I had
was a grubby old man.
He kept calling his apprentice’s or
grandson’s name the whole time.
It was so creepy…
Do you want to see his picture?
It’s after the experiments were done
so his original form wasn’t maintained.
What was the name of his apprentice?
Goodness…
It seems once my experiments
are concluded, I lose all interest.
What’s that?!
The name of his apprentice…
Do you want me to tell you?
The name of his apprentice is…
Uryu… Uryu Ishida!
This person is Soken Ishida.
He was my teacher.
As well as my grandfather!
Oh… And?
By the pride of the Quincy…
I will kill you!
Oh…
Even though I immobilized your limbs
with the Ashisogi Jizo,
you managed to stand up…
I know why… It is…
Ransotengai!
Countless threads of spirit particles
bundle together
and connect with immobilized parts
to forcibly move them,
like the strings of a puppet!
Originally, elderly Quincies,
in order to continue fighting Hollows,
developed this technique.
Whether their tendons were cut,
or their bones were crushed,
it meant nothing with this technique.
It exists so that one can fight
until one’s body falls to bits.
The Quincies’ ultimately
superior battle technique…
I had thought it was a lost art.
In fact, of the 2,661 subjects
I have researched,
no one could use even
a hint of that technique.
And for you to use it
at such a young age…
A genius, one could say.
Genius? You shouldn't refer to it
by such a commonplace term.
What?!
My Ransotengai is neither
an ordinary defense technique
nor a way to prolong my life.
Until I avenge my master,
even if I’m reduced to a corpse,
it is the expression of my will to fight!
Let me retract the term “genius.”
You’re just a greenhorn little brat.
Uryu…
I heard you went to
your grandfather’s place again.
How many times have I told you;
stop going there.
B-But--
Don’t make excuses!
I’ve told you time and again.
It’s pointless to save the dead.
Father--!
That’s the Soul Reaper’s job.
You only need to study
how to save the living.
I have no interest.
You have no talent.
The Quincies will end with
your grandfather’s generation.
Do you understand?
Father… Why do you hate
the Quincies so much?
Because they don’t make any money.
Hmm… There is truth
in what he says.
These days, you can’t put food
on the table by being just a Quincy.
With a family to support,
that’s a big problem.
But still…
Hmm… What he says is right.
B-But… I can see them!
The Hollows, and the people
being attacked by them…
The Soul Reapers can’t handle them all.
I’ve seen it with my own eyes!
I’m sure Dad can see it too.
So how…
how can he say those things?
– Master…
– Hmm?
I want to become strong!
I want to become a strong Quincy
and protect everyone from the Hollows.
If I do that, then I’m sure Father
will acknowledge the Quincies…
Thank you, Uryu, my boy…
Pretty good.
Maybe I could be interested in you…
I won’t kill you.
I’ll take you back alive.
And have you be
my research subject.
But Uryu…
Try to understand your father too.
If you wish to protect changes,
then your sense of justice
changes as well.
It is like that.
What Father wants to protect?
What is that? Money?
There will come a time
when you understand.
And by that time,
you should understand what it is
that you truly wish to protect.
For that time,
I shall leave this with you.
This is…?
This is the Sanreishuto.
It is a glove with the power
to disperse spiritual particles
at a high level.
If you put this on and create a bow,
and are able to maintain it
for seven days and seven nights,
you will become infinitely closer
to the pinnacle of the Quincy powers.
However, once you go there, Uryu…
you must never remove this glove.
For if you do, at that moment,
your ability to draw in spirit energy
will have surpassed the limits of a Quincy.
Too strong of a flame,
and you will burn yourself.
If you remove the glove,
for a moment you will
gain enormous powers, however…
you will surely lose all
your Quincy powers as well.
Well, shall we go now?
To my laboratory.
I wouldn’t want to kill you
before that.
One day, you’ll understand
your father’s feelings
and when you find that
which you truly wish to protect,
at that time, if you still wish
to follow the ways of the Quincy…
You will surely come upon
an unavoidable battle.
And a time may come when
you must thrust yourself
into a battle far beyond
your abilities.
When that time comes,
use this Sanreishuto.
However, I will say it again,
once you put this on,
you must never take it off.
I know of many ways to take you
with me without killing you.
That is, if you don’t mind
experiencing some hellish pain.
Shall I demonstrate
one of those methods now?
There is a limit to the Ransotengai.
I cannot hold out forever.
I’m sorry… Master…
I still don’t understand
my father’s feelings.
And I probably don’t understand
what I truly want to protect.
But that which cannot be forgiven…
I think I do know that one.
I’m sorry… Master…
I…just once more…
I must disobey you!
Wh-What? What is that?!
Wh-What is with that attire?
What is with that Spiritual Pressure?
I’ve never known such a thing!
That…!
He’s absorbing the structures nearby?
All the structures in the Soul Society
are constructed entirely of spirit particles.
He’s managing to break those bonds
and is forcibly absorbing
the spirit particles.
In other words,
the subjugation of the spirit particles!
You’re exceeding the limits
allowed to humans, you brat!
He’s fast! But if this is all…
Weep and beg for forgiveness.
And never appear in front of me again.
If you do that, I may let you go.
If you refuse,
the next attack will be three times that!
Don’t get carried away, you brat!
A mere Quincy, toying with me…
Fine.
Then I shall respond with
appropriate force!
Bankai!
What’s that? Ban…?
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
No way! That zanpaku-to
was already released!
Didn’t you know zanpaku-to
have two stages of release?
What?!
Ashisogi Jizo is the first stage
of my zanpaku-to, the Shikai.
And this Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo
is the second stage.
In other words, the Bankai.
The deadly poison that
this thing spews will kill off all of you!
It’s regrettable that
I can’t do research
on an excellent specimen
such as you.
Go!
Sir…Mayuri…
Damn it…
You…Quincy lowlife!
The ability to liquefy
whatever it cuts…
That was close, Quincy.
One’s last ace in the hole should
only be used after much consideration.
In case he needed to escape,
he left himself that ability! Damn it!
It’s useless.
Although I cannot make
any attacks in this form,
I cannot be attacked
in any way either.
For a few days,
I cannot change back from this form,
but during that time I’ll return to
the Bureau and tend to my wounds…
Farewell… Quincy…
It was a bit cumbersome, however,
I will live and you will die.
That outcome will not change.
Damn it!
The poison… At this rate…
Q-Quincy…
Behind the Lieutenant’s emblem
on my left arm…
I have the antidote…
Wouldn’t you be more comfortable
lying down?
No… This is fine.
Yes, behind it there…
You first.
No, I’m all right.
My body is made of the
same substance as Sir Mayuri’s body.
This toxin will not kill me.
Are you thinking this may be a trap?
If so, please bring it up to my mouth.
I will drink to show you.
No.
There’s no reason
to entrap someone
who would have been poisoned
to death anyway.
Thank you very much.
Had you aimed for the head,
you could have killed Sir Mayuri.
But you did not…
It was a fluke.
I had fired intending to kill him.
But you refrained from
killing Sir Mayuri.
That antidote is
a token of my appreciation.
I don’t get it.
How could you feel that way
about someone like that?
I do not understand it either.
But, when I realized
that he was still alive,
I was somewhat relieved.
Well if you’ve drunk it,
please go!
I will be all right.
Soon the troops will arrive.
Thank you…for the antidote.
Good bye.
It hurts… My body feels heavy…
My legs…
I can’t raise my arm either…
Damn… I guess the end is nearing
for my time as a Quincy.
Orihime… I…
I’m sure she’s doing fine.
I’m sure that guy from
Squad Eleven would lead her here.
Ichigo… Chad… Yoruichi… Ganju…
I wonder how they are.
I have to believe that
they will arrive here.
That’s right! If I’m the first one here,
I could rescue Rukia myself.
I bet Ichigo wants to save her himself.
If I did that, he’d be ticked off.
I bear no ill feelings.
However, for the sake of our peace,
I must eliminate you.
Cry, Suzumushi!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Oh goodness, once I've taken this form,
I can't get back to normal for a while.
Never mind eating,
I can't even take a shower.
I wonder if I had
a big enough container--!
Hey! Don't pour water on me!
You're diluting me!
It's more inconvenient
than I imagined.