Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
Soul Reapers and Arrancars
faced off against each other
throughout Karakura Town.
Rangiku Matsumoto squared off
against Halibel's Fracciones,
Apache, Mila Rose and Sun-Sun.
Rangiku targets the discord
between the three Fracciones
and attempts to take them
all at once by using Haineko,
but the disadvantage of
fighting three versus one
gradually pushes her into a pinch.
However,
an unexpected helper appears.
I just told you, it's no contest!
That won't work on me!
You're no competition
even against just me!
W-What?!
Y-You're!
Hinamori!
You appear to be a lieutenant, but…
Two lieutenants aren't much
different than three against one.
See you! Holstein!
What…the hell is this?!
Snap, Tobiume.
Are you all right, Hinamori?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It was the first time I used
that combination of techniques, so…
Incredible.
To be able to combine several
of these Kido in her own way.
Thrust upwards, Cierva!
Eat Apart, Leona!
Strangle to Death, Anaconda.
Take that, and that,
and that, and that,
and that, and that…
What's the matter?
That child…Lilinette, was it?
Are you okay with that?
And that, and that,
and that, and that…
Why don't you say something
to make her stop?
She wouldn't listen, anyway.
Shouldn't you be worried about
yourself instead of the others?
Man…
You are so right.
Bakudo 8: Seki!
No way.
In my time,
I've seen hundreds of Cero.
That's why I'm going to tell you…
your Cero is immature.
It's not even at
the level of Menos.
As you just saw, I can knock it
down with my bare hands.
I won't hold it against you.
Go on home.
It's unbearable to
fight you anymore!
I didn't think we could defeat them
with that, but…
They're practically unscarred.
When they do Resurreccion,
their injuries heal.
That's how they are!
I'm sorry, Rangiku.
Mila Rose! Sun-Sun!
Let's finish this!
Let's take care of
this silly battle and…
What good is it going to do to
get even more angry with them?
We'll use "that" to take care
of them in one swoop.
Guess we have no choice.
To think we have to take "that"
out on the likes of them.
Quimera Parco.
What?
What…is that?!
Quimera Parco.
It's our pet,
created from the left arms
of the three of us
in our released form.
Its name is Ayon.
What?
What is this chill?
It's like I'm peering into a deep pit
whose bottom I cannot see.
Just what I would
expect of Captain-class.
If you continue to act like
you still have leeway,
you'll get hurt, you know!
You won't get away next time!
Haineko!
Oh, I forgot to warn you.
Ayon is deadly, so be careful.
Rangiku!
Matsumoto…
Bakudo 37: Tsuriboshi!
Hang on, Rangiku!
I'll heal you right away!
From below the ribs
to her intestines.
She can't breathe
with these injuries.
I have to hurry!
All the bones in my entire body
are broken.
Both Rangiku and myself,
taken out by a single strike.
This is crazy.
There's no way we can
win against this thing.
Bakudo 37: Tsuriboshi!
Kira…
Hisagi…
Good job on holding down the fort.
Rest a while, Hinamori.
We'll take care of this thing.
Huh?!
Who are those guys?!
Their friends, probably.
I saw them coming from
the direction of the pillars.
If you saw them coming,
why didn't you stop them, you!
Oh, weren't you in a better
position to see them coming?
Or are your eyes just
useless peepholes?
What did you say?!
Stop it, you two!
We're in the middle of a battle!
Concentrate!
Help is coming
one after another.
These guys sure like
butting into other's battles.
Ayon!
Don't give them time to butt in!
Kill them quickly!
Ayon!
He's ignoring us, damn it.
Stop it, stupid.
There's no way Ayon
can hear what we say.
He's got to have eardrums
on him somewhere. Well?!
I wouldn't know.
I've never seen him
react to what we say.
But never mind that.
Would you mind
not seeking my agreement?
It's annoying.
Ayon probably gets his
unfriendly side from you, I'll bet!
He gets his face from you.
Those ugly horns
are exactly like yours!
You! I'll start by killing
you before the Soul Reapers!
Cut it out!
It doesn't matter who
Ayon looks like!
That's cuz his ugly looks,
that most resemble you,
make you want to look away.
What?!
What the heck are
those three over there doing?
Kira, don't pay them any mind.
Right.
I'm going to
kill you someday!
That's enough!
I knew it was a bad idea
to bring him out.
He's a creepy one.
Kira,
I'll handle this guy.
You take care of
Hinamori and Rangiku.
You sure you want to
handle that thing alone?
Who said I'll fight alone?!
After you've done
emergency first-aid,
hide them using Kido and then
come back here to assist me!
Rangiku, especially, needs help
quickly or she might die.
I'm counting on you,
former Squad 4 member.
When are you referring to?
Let's go.
Yes, let's do it.
Hey!
What're you standing around
in a daze for, Ayon!
They took that Holstein with them!
Bakudo 73…
Tozansho.
Hang on a bit longer, Hinamori!
I'll heal you soon!
No…I'm all right.
Hurry and help Rangiku…
Hinamori is in pretty
bad shape herself.
She's either got a rib
stuck in her lungs,
or heaven forbid,
one of her lungs has collapsed.
But…
This one's in even
worse shape.
Please…
I hope my skills haven't dulled.
This thing is
a complete unknown.
I'll keep my distance
and watch what it does.
Hado 11…
Tsuzuriraiden.
Did it have an effect?!
My, my, that was pretty good.
He seems stronger than
that Holstein and the other one.
They're all the same.
Judging by that attack…
It was effective!
I can do this!
So this thing's
weakness is Kido!
You see?
Damn monster!
He broke free with ease.
Could've done it anytime, is that
what you're trying to tell me?
Oh no…
Hisagi!
Right now, treating Matsumoto
is the priority.
Why you…
What?
It hasn't reacted to me yet!
Will I make it?!
Iba!
Is it over now? That was fast.
I thought they'd put up
more of a fight than that.
How disappointing.
Ayon is too strong.
Serves those Soul Reapers right!
Ayon! Get on with
finishing off the rest!
It's coming!
Damn it.
I'm so close to finishing.
Just a little more.
Hurry.
Good grief.
Making the Head Captain
come out to the front line…
Such hopeless squad members.
Let's go!
Our battle has just begun!
That's right,
our battle has just begun!
That phrase sounds almost
as if we're getting cancelled.
Focus!
Our battle has just begun!
Not you, too, Head Captain…
In today's segment,
we introduce you to
Izuru Kira's Zanpakuto, Wabisuke.
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Wabisuke has the ability to double
the weight of anything it slashes.
The enemy ultimately becomes
unable to bear his own weight
and ends up in a position
like a criminal bowing down
as he apologizes
for his crimes.
You might say it makes Kira
both judge and executioner.
I can really understand
why you'd
turn to alcohol to
drown your sorrows.
I'm fine. I'm fine!