chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Welcome back...
Orihime.
What's the matter?
You look awfully troubled.
Smile.
Everyone will be sad
if the sun doesn't shine.
Smile and wait here for a while...
That is all you need to do.
Just until
we erase Karakura Town.
Erase...Karakura Town...?
Yes.
I will destroy Karakura Town
to create the Ouken.
Aizen, who planned
to create the Ouken
in Karakura Town,
an Enriched Spirit Zone,
left his castle in the hands of
Espada Number 5 Ulquiorra
and invaded Karakura Town
with Gin and Tosen.
In order to rescue
Orihime Inoue,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
went into Hueco Mundo.
They, together with the four captains
who arrived as reinforcements:
Byakuya, Kenpachi,
Mayuri and Unohana,
found themselves left
behind in Hueco Mundo
because of Aizen's trickery.
By then, however, Soul Society had
already swapped Karakura Town
with a replica using Tenkaikecchu
and turned it into a battle-ready zone.
All of the captain-class members,
led by Genryusai Yamamoto,
gathered here to engage Aizen.
70M ABOVE
KARAKURA TOWN
It seems we made it in time.
Made it in time?
Now why would you say that?
I'm well aware that what lies there
is not Karakura Town.
But that means nothing to me.
Stark, Barragan, Halibel...come.
If Karakura Town is
in the Soul Society,
we'll just kill you here and create
the Ouken in the Soul Society.
That's all there is to it.
All things in the universe
turn to ashes.
Ryujinjakka.
Jokakuenjo...
Aizen and the others won't be able to
get past this wall of flames for a while.
Now then...
Shall we crush them
at our leisure?
Geez...that's hot, hot...
Head Captain sure
went overboard.
What'll we do now,
Captain Aizen?
Nothing.
This battle will end without the need
for us to get our hands dirty.
That's all it means.
Everyone!
Put your entire spirit on the line
and crush them here!
Even if your flesh
is torn from you,
use pieces of your bone
to form an iron-clad wall!!
We mustn't let them step even
one foot into the Soul Society!
Attack!!!
You! You! You!
I'm not falling for that!!
You're no competition
even against just me!!
Wh-What?!
Y-You're...!
Hinamori...!!
Strike Above, Cierva!!
Eat Apart, Leona!!
Strangle to Death, Anaconda.
Quimera Parca!
Using a part of
their own bodies,
Halibel's Fraccioines:
Apache, Sun-Sun and Mila Rose
created Quimera Parca "Ayon"
and inflicted critical, nearly fatal,
injuries on Rangiku and Hinamori.
Ayon then incapacitated Hisagi and Iba,
who had come to help,
and extended its evil hands
to threaten Kira,
who was administering
emergency first-aid to the others.
However, just then...
Making the Head Captain
come out to the front...
Such hopeless
squad members.
Head Captain...
Yamamoto...!!
Captain...was that...
Don't lose your cool.
That was the Head Captain.
What?!
The Head Captain
himself, fighting?
Omaeda...
Your face, please.
Huh? What is it?
Captain...I, Omaeda,
won't fall for the same trick...!
We've come here to fight.
Even the Head Captain
is no exception.
Don't be so stupid.
That's...mean...
Hmm...
It would seem...
I didn't punish it enough.
What happened...?
You didn't reach me.
What?!
A monster whose thoughts are
only filled with killing people...
Pitiful.
Ryujinjakka, Hitotsume...
Nadegiri...!
What...?!
I admire the spirit of
challenging me with one arm.
Dammit...
In consideration of your spirit,
I'll let you get off with just burns.
What?!
What is that?
Apache...Sun-Sun...
Mila Rose...
You fought well...
With your level of strength...
And you're still number three...?
With my level?
I don't recall showing you...
the extent of my strength...
Bankai!!!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!!!
You fellows...are strong.
Why thank you.
I wanted to keep dodging and
wait until the battle ended...
But that's not going
to be possible.
I'm happy to hear that...
My guess is that among
the three of you,
that girl there is
number three in ranking...
Am I correct?
Personally, it would be nice if
that old gramps is number one
and you're number two.
I see.
Sorry to disappoint...
But I'm number one.
I knew it...
Too bad...
When someone like you is number one...
it makes it difficult you know.
AT THE SAME TIME
HUECO MUNDO,
THE FIFTH TOWER
Are you afraid?
Lord Aizen has considered
you unnecessary.
There is nothing to
protect you anymore.
It's over.
You will die here, all alone,
with no contact with anyone.
I'm asking if you are afraid.
I am not afraid.
Because everyone came
to rescue me...
My heart is...
with theirs...
This is absurd.
Your fate and that of
your friends are already set.
Even if your friends came,
it won't overturn the fact
that all of you will die...
Sharing feelings with those
who are about to die...
That is how you humans
comfort yourselves.
It is one of your instincts to help you
escape from fear and hopelessness.
Sharing feelings doesn't
exist in the real world.
It is nothing more than a meaningless
illusion you humans have.
You may be right...
Perhaps it is impossible to feel
exactly the same emotions.
But by cherishing each other,
our hearts can be that much closer.
Don't die!
Don't die, Kurosaki!
You don't have to win!
You don't have to keep trying!
Just don't hurt yourself
any further!!
That's what it must mean
to "be of one heart."
What is "heart"?
If I rip open your chest,
will I see it inside?
If I split your skull,
Kurosaki...
Step away from Inoue.
I was about to.
My duty is to protect Las Noches
until Lord Aizen returns.
I've received no orders
to take the woman's life.
Until those orders come,
I will let this woman live.
However...
You are a different matter.
Killing you is synonymous
with protecting Las Noches.
I shall eliminate you
with my sword.
That was unexpected.
I didn't think you would
draw your sword first.
I came here thinking that I'd have to
start by making you draw your sword.
Can I take it you consider me
an equal opponent?
At the very least,
I consider you worthy of destroying.
That's good enough for me.
Kurosaki...
I finally remember what happened
to the story up till now.
So you're saying
you have forgotten?
Huh? Oh, the guy
I was fighting against!
Kurosaki Ichigo...
What is it,
"guy I was fighting against?"
Say my full name.
Oh come on now,
"guy I was fighting against!"
Ta-da!
Today, I'll tell you about
the important roles I played
in Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
up until now.
Did you have
any important roles?
In Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers,
I was sent off by teary-eyed lovelies.
In the Complete Quincy,
I made those old daddies my retainers.
And in Arrancar Encyclopedia,
I pounded my fateful enemy into a pulp!
You can look forward
to more important roles!
THEY ARE ALL LIES
Is that right...?