I took him out!
I took out the shogun!
C-Calm down, Gintoki!
He's just unconscious!
We need to get him help, quick!
Found Whitey and Blondie.
That's not a can!
It'll be faster to cut him up.
Your way of moving faster is too fast!
Excuse me, Shogun-sama.
The former shogun,
Sadasada-sama is here.
Are you available?
Is he available?
That's what I want to know!
This is a disaster! What the hell
do we do about this?!
We finally found the former shogun,
but the current shogun is flying away!
Butterflying away in the River Styx.
At this rate, we'll be
butterflying away with him,
Calm down!
so before that, let's start running away!
Hey, where are you going?
Get back here.
Are you gonna give up
on this perfect chance?
Is something wrong?
Shigeshige-san is my nephew.
I don't need his permission to visit.
I'm coming in, Shigeshige-san.
H-Hold on!
What is the meaning of this?
O-Oh no!
We said to wait!
Shogun-sama is busy right now.
Hello, we're Delivery
Yoshiwara's Nobume...
...and Tsu-ki. It's a pleasure.
Inside the Palace!!
Found the princess.
Shot Grampy.
Sorry, but I already found everyone.
Forgive me for being an elite.
My apologies, Sasaki-dono!
We were just...
It's fine.
But watch where you hide.
I almost mistook you for
a villain and shot you.
Almost? You nearly shot me to death!
Rotten-dono, if you agree
to take responsibility when
I accidentally kill the princess,
we can play another round.
We'll stop! We're going to stop!
I'm so very sorry!
A wise decision.
I would expect as much
from Rotten Maizo-dono,
advisor to the former shogun.
I've heard that you gave up your
left arm to show your loyalty.
Grampy, you served Sadasada-sama?
I-It was a long time ago.
It was a tempestuous age of
political purges within the palace,
and Rotten-dono played a pivotal
role in keeping his master safe.
Sadasada-sama's elevation to shogun
was thanks to Rotten-dono's hard work
since the other candidates
were all sent to heaven.
Yes, by "heaven," I mean Yoshiwara.
What do you...
Sasaki-dono, could you escort
these visitors outside?
Come with me, Your Highness.
Wait, Grampy!
Kagura-chan!
Soyo-chan!
Here you are, Shogun-sama.
Come on, Shogun-sama.
You're spilling everything.
You're so hopeless.
There's no way!
Not a chance in hell!
There's no way we can fool him!
Why are we bothering with this act?
His eyes are rolled back!
The former shogun's eyes
are also rolled back!
Say something! Say something, now!
I'm not a ventriloquist!
Still beats staying quiet! Hurry up!
Y-Yeah, you gave me a scare
since you walked in without
any warning, Uncle!
Give me a break!
I look like a fool now!
Why are you being so casual?!
Act more serious, like the shogun would!
Bring Genda Tessho-san here, then!
I don't know how to
play a serious shogun!
My apologies, Dearest Uncle.
She can mimic voices?
I have humiliated myself shogun.
Huh, shogun?
I'm so embarrassed shogun.
Hey! Why do you end every
sentence with shogun?!
Please forget what you saw shogun.
You're sounding like Korosuke now!
Who are you trying to imitate?!
Oh, that's odd.
The shogun is talking faster than
his mouth can move shogun.
Nobody asked for an
Ikkoku-dou impression!
No, I should be the one apologizing.
You seemed to frown upon such behavior.
I did some crazy things when I was young,
though nothing as bold as this.
What does he think was going on here?!
But I'm shocked that the Mimawarigumi
would allow visitors inside.
It seems that they aren't
here to protect us.
Look at that.
Huh? Er, can I sit here?
Can I just stare at his
receding hairline from here?
Of course not!
Stand up! Get over there!
They claim to be training, but
that's no more than an excuse.
They're monitoring us.
You know that the current Bakufu
Hey, be careful!
is split between our faction,
which backs you,
and the faction that
wants to make one of
the young Hitotsubashis Shogun, yes?
The recent assassination victims
have all been members of
the Hitotsubashi faction.
That is why they suspect us.
The Mimawarigumi have strong ties
to the Hitotsubashi faction.
They may attempt to make
false accusations.
Try not to do anything that would
attract their attention.
Shogun-sama, give me back my underwear!
This doesn't seem right.
Any naughty underwear around shogun?
Ugh, this stinks!
Shigeshige-san...
Was your hair always so bushy?
Oh, this hair was on her underwear.
I don't remember that bushy object
being in this room before.
Oh, this hair was always here shogun.
Honestly, I can't tell if you're
being resilient or foolish.
Wait, it worked?
But try to control yourself.
I've seen many people ruin
their lives because of women.
Yes, beware of courtesans.
My Lord.
Please forgive my interruption.
But there is something I must ask.
Do you remember the courtesan Suzuran?
No, it doesn't matter if
you don't remember her.
I just... I just...
I see.
So you want to know the
connection between
that courtesan and Sadasada-sama.
It sounded like you knew something.
Let me offer you some advice.
Give me your e-mail
addresses and leave.
We don't have any!
Become my e-mail buddies and leave.
We'd rather stay strangers!
The courtesan who bewitched
and toppled our very country...
Stay out of this, unless you
want to get yourself destroyed.
I see...
So Suzuran is still alive.
You're right.
Lady Suzuran was Sadasada-sama's
companion when he was young.
However, he wasn't the one
who fell for her charms.
At the time, Yoshiwara was a place for
high-ranking officials
to meet and socialize,
and every man who visited
was entranced by her.
Suzuran...
How could I forget her?
I could never forget.
Those eyes shining with kindness...
The graceful way she moved...
Her silky hair...
Glossy lips...
Supple skin...
And...
...those blood-stained hands.
I'd love to suck them off again.
He was using her.
Using her as a tool to
topple this country.
And after becoming shogun,
he prepared a puppet to succeed him,
so his influence in the
palace would not wane.
What about that promise?!
Do you really think that man
would grant freedom to a tool
who knew his secrets?
If he ever made such a
promise, he was lying.
It was nothing more than a
curse to maintain control
over his tool.
That cunning old man is not
someone you can handle.
You should go home and let
the elites deal with this.
Yoshiwara was only the beginning.
This place has become
his hunting ground.
Who knows what might happen to you...
I just got a curry udon
stain out the other day.
See? I told you that you
were asking for trouble...
Sa-Sasaki-san!
Yes, I've found some more tools to use.
Apprehend them.
These criminals are guilty of
murdering Bakufu officials
as well as the leader
of those snooping dogs.
Sasaki was taken down.
Well, his life was forfeit once he
let murderers inside the palace.
The Mimawarigumi have been
removed from palace security.
It won't be long before they disband.
And we've been selected
to take their place.
But something about this stinks.
Stinks?! What does?!
I hear the alleged criminals in the serial
Bakufu murders were apprehended,
and they'll be executed
tomorrow morning
without conducting any investigation.
It sounds like they're trying
to cover something up.
Oh, whew.
I thought he could smell my gas.
Kondo-san?
R-Right!
Something's not right.
Let's clean up these murderers.
Oh! Kondo-kun! Hijikata-kun!
Fancy meeting you here!
Perfect timing!
I need to talk to you.
I'm gonna kill you, you rotten cops!
Don't ignore me! Hear me out!
It's hopeless. That's some stubborn
filth they're covered in.
That won't ever clean off.
Everyone! That gorilla pooped a
little when he farted earlier!
How do you know that?!
It's no use, boss.
You picked the wrong enemy this time.
Nobody's going to lend
an ear to your pleas.
Then rip off your ear
and lend it to us!
Sorry, my ears have a prior engagement.
Then give me an ear of corn!
Oh? I see a familiar face in there.
That's odd. Why is there an
elite locked up with the scum?
What will happen to the Mimawarigumi
if I tell the shogun?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry, you guys are
already finished, regardless.
Hand over a Pon De Ring!
That's what you want?!
You're ripping me apart!
Give me my dinner!
We really picked the wrong
opponent this time.
Sasaki-san said that the palace was
Sadasada's hunting ground now.
And Sasaki-san was also...
He's alive.
Isaburo is alive.
So it turns out you were right, Gintoki.
I was the one blinded by a false dream.
Suzuran was waiting for a
man that doesn't exist.
She must have known
that refusing Sadasada
would mean her death.
That the promise was meant
to chain her to Yoshiwara.
Suzuran wasn't waiting for anyone.
She had no choice but
to cling to her dreams.
Shigeshige-sama!
Please reconsider!
Those people are Princess
Soyo's friends!
If you must punish someone,
please slice off my ass instead!
Calm down, Grampy.
My uncle was the one
who saw what happened.
I know nothing.
But you're the only
one who can stop him!
There's no need to worry.
They are murderers.
Or are you saying that I'm lying?
B-By no means...
Get some rest, Shigeshige-san.
This old man will take care
of everything for you.
Lord Sadasada?!
Is that true?!
I don't know if it's true,
but that's their story.
Toshi!
So what?
Our job is to defend Edo.
It's not our problem if those pigs
want to feed on one another.
But if we ignore what's happening,
we'll be no better than them!
Don't forget that those
pigs are the only reason
we country boys get to play samurai.
I'm not interested in being a bogus
samurai that doesn't follow a code!
We have to play bogus samurai
if we want to defend anything!
Don't you realize that this is what
we're supposed to be defending!
Hey! Hold on!
What are you two doing?!
Shut up!
I can't get any sleep, you bastards!
Soyo-chan!
Is she going to save us while
those fools are fighting?
Um, I was having trouble
falling asleep all by myself.
Can I sleep out here?
I'd gotten used to Nobume-san
sleeping with me,
so I was too scared to fall asleep.
Uh, we're the ones who should
be too scared to fall asleep.
I'm a little nervous since this
is almost like a sleepover.
Uh, we're the ones who
should be nervous.
We're going to be executed tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Grampy will prove your innocence.
If you still can't fall asleep...
I know!
I can tell you some bedtime stories
that Grampy told me when I was little.
They're so boring that you'll
fall asleep in no time.
Um...
Long, long ago...
How boring do you expect it to be?!
That's rude!
Long, long ago, there was
a lord and his retainer.
The lord's wife was the most
beautiful princess in the land,
and she cared about him very much.
But the lord used the
princess's feelings,
threw her in prison, and forced
her to do terrible things.
The princess could only cry
in her prison every night.
The retainer felt sorry for the princess
and often came to wipe her tears.
Yes, for he had fallen in
love with the princess.
However...
Dispose of Suzuran.
The retainer would be
killed if he didn't obey.
But he couldn't bring himself
to kill the woman he loved.
Instead, they made a promise.
They would escape together.
"I will take you with me on the
night of the next full moon."
And then they exchanged a pinky swear.
But he never returned,
for the lord already knew about them.
How long will Suzuran wait for you,
a man who's long forgotten his promise?
The woman will wait for
the rest of her life
for a man who will never come,
while the man will live
the rest of his life
with the pain of breaking his promise.
A beautiful story, yes?
If the retainer were to go see the
princess, she would be killed.
Their promise was transformed
into a chain heavier than death.
So he swore to himself.
It didn't matter how many
full moons came and went.
It didn't matter if they
were covered in wrinkles.
It didn't matter if the
princess forgot about him.
He would live until the day he met her.
And so, he continues to live by
crawling on his three limbs.
Maizo, I heard something
fascinating that
I wanted to pass on to you.
Suzuran is still living in Yoshiwara.
But she won't survive much longer.
Do you wish to see her?
How many full moons have come and gone?
I suppose it's time to forgive you.
I'll let you go see her.
Take responsibility for inviting
those criminals into the palace.
Disembowel yourself.
Suzuran will be waiting
for you in hell.
And the princess and retainer were...
Stop.
We've heard enough, Your Highness.
You weren't able to fall asleep?
No.
We already know the rest of the story.
Can you open the door
now, Your Highness?
Huh? How?
Over there.
They were tossed in when you entered.
What are you waiting for?
Come out here. It's time
for your execution.
Put on your execution clothes.
Boss, don't forget you
have an appointment
with the executioner's block.
Make sure you come back
with your head attached
since we'll need to chop it off.
Try to commit a crime that's
worthy of this punishment.
What crime will you be guilty of?
The crime of
ripping off a lord's
topknot down there.
This may be the last
time we send him off.
The same goes for you.
Now that you've sided with
us, there's no turning back.
Don't worry about that.
If you cause an uproar, that old man
will start to show his true colors.
Once there's no one left to
interfere, we'll grill him good.
So you can go die in peace.
Or do you want me to dispatch you now,
murderer?
Remember this.
You have no allies in this palace.
If you aren't prepared to take over
this country, you'll all die.
The only difference is that
you'll be eliminated by
that old man instead of me.
If you want to join in the
battle for this nation,
forget about anything
being black or white.
What's going on?
Are there more bandits about?
Zura would love to see this.
Who would have thought we'd be trying
to seize this country for
the sake of an old woman?
This makes us wanted criminals.
Sis won't be happy.
Don't worry, sister lover.
If there's no place for us
on Earth, we'll go to space.
Odd Jobs in space?
That doesn't sound too bad.
The independent city Yoshiwara
will keep you safe.
Odd Jobs in Yoshiwara?
No, there's a gay bar
that's understaffed.
That means we'll be seizing your
balls after you seize this country.
Ow!
Why did you hit me?!
Were you the one who
brought her with us?
Were you the one who taught
her those dirty jokes?
It's your fault for telling dirty
jokes to innocent little girls!
Girls our age absorb
everything like sponges!
A sponge?! You're more like a
dirty rag soaked in milk!
Shut up, toilet paper!
I at least deserve to be called a rag!
A rag used to wipe asses!
Are you sure about this?
You'll be sacrificing
everything for Yoshiwara.
It's too late.
I already made a promise.
I see.
In that case...
Promise me this.
We will all return alive.
It's a promise.
To be continued...
I'm starting to feel the pressure.
There was the One Piece film
at the end of the year.
Then you've got Hunter x Hunter and
Dragon Ball films in spring, and us in summer.
We should ask TV Tokyo to show our
movie with the Pokemon movie.
That's it!
That's it, my ass!
Five Fingers
The Bakufu army stands in the way.
Overwhelming manpower!! Firepower!!
to seize this country!!
Our five heroes have made a promise