Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Ishida has lost his powers,
so he separated himself from us.
He was saved by a female Bount,
Yoshino Soma.
Yoshino was trying to
stop Kariya's ambition.
But the hands of evil crept before them.
Yoshino calls on Goethe to fight, but
cannot match the power of Koga's Dalk.
Koga had increased his power
by absorbing living souls.
Yoshino and Ishida end up
being captured.
Meanwhile, we snuck into
the enemy's mansion in search of Ishida.
But our actions were all anticipated
and we were led to a hall
where the Bounts were gathered.
I stayed behind to battle.
Rukia and the others escaped
and searched for Ishida,
but they were attacked by
Maki Ichinose, a Soul Reaper.
I struggled in battle with
Udagawa's doll, Friede,
and his absolute field,
but I used my Getsugatensho to
escape danger and even the odds.
But at that moment, Udagawa suddenly
stole Kariya's crest and revolted.
Kariya--!
What?
A Soul Reaper?
Don't interfere!
What's this?
It's over.
Hey!
Why in the world is
a Soul Reaper here?
You're going to die.
There's no need for you to know.
I have to beat it out of you, huh?!
Here I go!
Kurodo!
Noba!
They took an attack from
a skilled Soul Reaper.
They should have taken
a lot of damage…
What'll we do?
What if they were to die like this?!
If Noba and Kurodo aren't around…
I'll be all alone!
Come on, wake up!
Open your eyes! Noba!
Kurodo?!
Kurodo!
–Hey, Kurodo!
–I wonder if I can
–circulate the ki to heal
–Wake up!
–in my current state…
–I won't call you stupid anymore!
Wake up! Kurodo!
No!
Kurodo!
Stop it.
But…
Hey… Stop pretending to
be unconscious already…
Huh?
Good morning!
What about Noba?
Kurodo!
Well, we were like dying swans,
but we couldn't leave you alone
after hearing your voice.
We came back right before
reaching the River Styx…
Owowowow…my chronic cramps…
Idiot!
You sure have your share
of troubles with them…
Here I go!
It's useless to try to escape!
You cannot see my sword,
no matter how you struggle!
Don't underestimate me!
Is it just instinct?
You shouldn't be seeing
my Nijigasumi's attacks…
But you're reflexively dodging it…
That's interesting.
Heh! That's the power of
your zanpakuto, huh?
In that case…
In that case?
I’ll just keep attacking!
Things won't go quite so smoothly!
Where are you?!
Now have a taste…
of my true power!
Flash and burst, Nijigasumi!
When my Nijigasumi shines,
its light will shine through everything.
There are no longer any shadows
to hide in.
You shaped highly-dense
Spiritual Pressure into a blade
and threw it.
You used that power to cause
an explosion under your feet to escape…
But it seems to have put
a huge strain on you…
Shut up!
Wait.
Master Kariya…
I'll do this.
You don't have to
do something like this.
I'm interested in his soul…
As you wish…
Hey, you!
What are you talking about?!
Sorry to keep you waiting…
Now live with us…
Forever.
No thanks.
I won't be eaten!
Master Kariya…
You charmed me with that strength.
Your power hasn't changed
since I met you…
Why?!
Unfortunately, it's acceptable.
A single combat match under
the attendance of
over two hundred squad members
to show supremacy.
It’s one way to succeed a position
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squad.
He accepted that man's challenge.
We're not allowed to stop him.
But Soul Society needs
a will like that of our captain’s…
That's what I have believed in…
I have the same feelings.
Soul Society is supposed to wish
for the peace of souls.
How could a law like this exist?
That man, Kenpachi Zaraki,
is especially dangerous.
His sword is madness itself…
Captain!
Wait!
Zaraki…you… How dare you
do this to the captain!
I won't accept it!
Please stop, Ichinose!
Let me go!
At that moment, the captain
I respected was taken from me.
Is it all right for a battle
to be so meaningless,
a battle between those
who only seek strength?
I couldn't stop trembling
with anger.
But in the end, everyone stopped me
from attacking him there…
And…
Soon, Zaraki officially became
captain of Squad 11.
Huh? A one on one fight?
Forget it…
I am officially challenging you
to a fight…
How could you?
You're different from me.
You can become captain
by taking the captain's exam…
I don't intend to hold
a grudge against you.
But I cannot leave
my late captain unavenged.
Humph. So that's it…
What a pain…
You can’t cut me.
What?!
Do it right now if you want to!
If you can give me even a scratch,
I'll consider it!
What's wrong? Come on!
Flash and burst, Nijigasumi!
I told you… You can't cut me…
Why--? Why are you like that?
You're like ivy… You can't live…
unless you're clinging on to trees…
Because you're ivy…
Learn to plant some roots
to stand on your own…
I didn't care about anything…
I died at that moment…
That's what I thought…
Until I met Kariya…
I left Soul Society.
At the end of my travels, I found myself
in the World of the Living.
Why…Why am I here?
Why am I…
It's a great crime to come to
the World of the Living without permission.
I can no longer return to Soul Society…
Will I…wither away here like this?
That's fine…
If I do that, I can go to my captain…
Save us!
A fire?
Don't come!
Souls?!
What's going on?
A hollow?!
Run away!
Quickly, run away!
At that moment,
my body moved before I could think…
But…
Humph… Is that all, Soul Reaper?
Right now… I may not even stand
a chance against someone like this…
Today sure is great…
I filled my stomach with fresh souls
and now I get to eat a Soul Reaper…
Am I going to die here?
I can die?
And yet…
What crossed my mind was not
the relief that I could finally die…
But the fear of death…
I was pitiful…
I learned how lowly and small I was.
But even then,
I could not let go of my dying body…
It's over, Soul Reaper!
Wh-What did you do?
Are you all right?
Oh, yes…
He completely stopped
the Hollow’s movement
with a single finger.
I've never heard of such a person…
This is your fight…
Here…
Soul Reaper.
What's wrong? You don't seem like
you'd lose to a Hollow like that…
I've failed.
You're ivy…
You can't live unless you
cling on to trees…
There's no need to be concerned.
Everyone has a weakness.
We can't throw those away,
no matter how long we live…
As long as we're within
the cycle of rebirth…
Won't you come with me?
I was charmed in an instant…
Your soul will meld with mine…
If you do that, glory will
forever shine upon your head.
How about it?
Won't you entrust yourself to me…
for wealth you have never known?
I told you, I refuse!
I see… That's too bad.
Damn!
I-I can't move!
You're not quite what
I thought you were…
I have no strength…
Master Kariya…
Aren't you going to
finish him off?
This person won't color my world
as richly as the Quincy…
Do as you like with him…
Wait!
Damn it… What’s going on?!
I should definitely finish him off!
What?!
All right, that's great, Ururu!
Next, ten degrees to the right
at the same angle!
– Okay.
– All right!
Yoruichi?!
Shunko!
Look out!
I-Is it an earthquake?! Thunder?!
Or a fire?! Is it Dad?!
This is bad!
At times like this, we should calm down
and escape without making a fuss!
– Calm down!
– Yes…
What's this? What's going on?!
This way!
I can sense Ishida's
Spiritual Pressure beyond this door!
What?!
Kuchiki!
Ishida! Are you all right?!
Y-Yeah…
Well, thank goodness
you're all right!
I was desperately trying
to think of a eulogy
in case something had happened,
– but it ended up being useless…
– Now let's run away!
I sense a Bount in this room!
What's wrong, Ishida?
What could it be?
Help me!
What are you saying?!
She's a Bount!
She's different!
But she's the one who first
attacked us…
What's the meaning of this?
I'll explain later!
All right…
Noba!
What's going on all of a sudden?!
Kurosaki…
Wait!
Sado, we've got to go quickly…
No… This way.
Kurosaki!
Don't worry. It's not serious.
Thank goodness…
Sister!
My beloved…
Level brea--!
Oh, it's nice to see everyone's safe!
And what a coincidence!
We've all gathered here!
I searched for Spiritual Pressures
and created an exit…
It's not a coincidence.
– Can you stand?
– Yeah…
We can't linger here.
We've got to leave
as soon as possible!
It seems they've taken Yoshino
and the Quincy with them.
Sorry. I let my guard down.
Master Kariya,
at this rate the plan will…
Let them go.
But…
Yoshino will…
come back to me…
And…
That Quincy as well…
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Darn! I don't think I can win
like this.
For times like this,
shall I lend you
my underground training area?
Right now it even comes
with an instructor.
Hello, I'm the instructor.
–Why you?!
–Huh? Who are you talking about?
–I'm the instructor.
–No, I'm talking about you.
–Shut up, be quiet!
–Why?!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Excuse me…
But why are you attending
a lieutenant's meeting?
I'm here because my squad's lieutenant
is in the World of the Living.
Byak-kun, you're so enthusiastic
about your work!
Say, say! I'm going to eat
after this meeting.
Want to come, too?
What's the next topic?
He's good…
Tune in again!