Ah...
You're alive.
And so weak...
Shall I put you out of your misery,
Zack?
Well, good morning. You never change, I see.
I'm impressed you can
even move in that state.
Why the hell are you here?
Are you surprised?
I knew you went chasing after
Rachel to try to escape my floor.
So just in case...
I took some minor safety precautions.
Although I still ended up like this...
Then I'll just hack you up again!
You shouldn't overexert yourself, Zack.
Huh?!
Just stop. I'm not exactly unscathed myself.
You still seem pretty damn energetic.
Well, I'm not like you.
I made sure to take precautions
as well as treat my wounds.
I'm pushed to my limit, too, you know.
I thought I'd decapitate you in your sleep,
but then you went and woke up.
It's unbearable!
So why are you walking
around with Rachel now?
And... where is she right now?
Are you being serious right now?
Like hell I'm gonna tell you
where she is, you dumbass!
Besides, what are you gonna do if
I tell you I killed her? Huh?!
You scum...
I'm the one who was looking
at her eyes for all this time!
And yet a dirtbag like you gets to kill her?!
That's enough of that nonsense!
Her eyes are special!
I spent my whole life
searching for those eyes!
Alive, but dead...
So silent and beautiful...
I won't let you have her eyes!
Her eyes belong to me!
I've been watching them all this time!
So what?
I'm not like you.
I don't care about her eyes.
But she wants me to kill her.
So the one who's gonna kill her...
...is me.
So you don't get to decide
what happens to Ray.
Rachel... wants you to kill her?
All right, then.
Now I know that she's alive.
The fact that you made it
to this floor proves it.
Oh, I know!
Now that you're in this shape,
I have a suggestion.
I actually have some medicine.
I could use it to help you.
What are you planning?
If you'll gouge out Rachel's
eyes and give them to me...
Get it?
I just told you I don't care about
Ray's eyes, but I won't do that.
For better or for worse,
she'd be boring without her eyes.
So I don't have anything to give you.
Not her eyeballs or anything else!
Ah, what a fool.
I'll be going now.
Gravely wounded or not, you're still scary.
Hold it!
You don't have the strength
to chase me down, do you?
Shut up!
Hey—
Wait...
Here we are.
Zack is honest and pure.
This floor, like him, is not complicated.
Go do what you came to do.
The place where I first found you.
My room is there.
There's a knife in the room.
Bring it... to me...
This is Zack's room?
The sofa's torn up.
And the blanket's so thin. It must be cold.
Can't use these.
This should work.
No medicine...
He spent all that time in here?
Did Zack write this?
What does this say?!
It's your name.
I don't know anything about Zack.
I'm going back to Zack now.
Did you do what you came to do?
Yes, so I want to go back quickly.
Very well.
There is something I am
curious about, as well.
Let us hurry back.
He's gone.
Staring at me with that look in
your eyes will achieve nothing.
Ah, yes. You really are the cause of
all these unfortunate occurrences,
Rachel Gardner.
What does that mean?
Did you find Danny on the hospital floor?
Well...
You didn't, did you?
Doctor Danny should be dead.
No, he is alive.
But I lack an understanding of his behavior.
What do you mean?
Danny is a serious, prudent man,
but for some reason,
he started to behave strangely.
Are you not the reason for that?
That wasn't my fault.
Anyway, I have to find Zack.
I have been watching your actions all along.
Huh?
As I watched you throw this
building's gears into disarray,
I took an interest in just who you are.
And if you are exerting a negative influence,
I must pass judgment on you.
Watching you search for medicine
for Zack gave me a bit of hope.
However, it seems that hope was in error.
Your actions have been far too
self-serving and merciless.
And when I asked you why
you wished to save Zack,
your answer was...
If he dies, it'll be a problem for me.
A problem? Why is that?
Zack swore to God...
...that he would kill me.
That was...
Yes, Rachel Gardner...
All of your actions have
been purely narcissistic.
No!
It's true that I want Zack to kill me,
but it's more than that!
Zack swore to God that he would kill me!
Even if he did swear to God,
do you have knowledge that
God would choose his promise?
If someone else made the same promise,
do you not agree that it is up to God
to choose which promise is realized?
And if God's choice does
not match your wish...
What would you do then?
Forgive me.
Perhaps that was a cruel thing to ask.
Now, then... before I pass judgment,
I must make preparations...
What is this?
Now, Rachel Gardner,
the deliberation on you continues.
What was that a second ago?
Zack!
There's a giant snake!
We have to run! Look, it's right there!
We have to hurry!
Whoa... wait...
Zack, hurry!
Shut up!
Huh?
Don't "huh?" me!
The giant snake...
There's no giant snake.
Are you high or something?
Hell, I was thinking you finally came back,
and you start spouting weird shit.
You're freaking me out.
You really can't handle
anything by yourself, can you?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why didn't you wait for me?
That bastard showed up.
Do you mean Doctor Danny?
How do you know?
His body was missing.
No wonder.
More importantly, you made it back alive.
Huh? What is it?
I'm sorry.
All the medicine Doctor Danny
had on his floor was gone.
The bastard did say something
about having medicine on him.
So it's true...
Did he say anything else?
Nothing you need to worry about.
Did you go to my floor?
Yeah.
Did you bring the knife?
Yeah, that's it.
All right, now I can...
Is that knife yours?
Yeah.
This was what I had first.
Okay, well, time to go...
You shouldn't be moving yet!
Will you get over it?
After all that sleep, I can move now.
No!
What's your problem?
I brought fresh bandages.
Let me see your wound.
Stop!
Don't touch me!
Don't do anything to me!
You don't have to do that.
This ain't gonna kill me.
What's with you?
You've had a weird look on
your face since you got back.
You remember what that
sadomasochistic bitch said?
Huh?
It pisses me off to think that she was right,
but she definitely was.
No!
You and I aren't tools!
Not that.
I remember that much after hearing
you say it the first time.
What, then?
I'm a monster.
Monsters don't die that easily.
Right?
Huh? What's your problem?
Don't make that weird face.
That's a normal thing to
expect of monsters, isn't it?
Well, whatever.
In any case, if there's no medicine,
I have no choice but to keep moving.
If you're not gonna come,
I'll leave you here.
There's a trail of blood.
Is that Doctor Danny's?
If he has medicine, we should go after him.
We don't even know where he is.
We'll follow the blood.
Huh?
Hey, Zack...
Yeah? What?
You called yourself a monster earlier.
Does that mean you're not human?
Huh?
Okay, here's a question for you.
What do you consider human?
Well...
What do you have to do to be an actual human?
What God wants?
Huh? The hell does that mean?
Is God the only thing you
know how to talk about?
Well, whatever I am, I'm the real thing.
I'm normal.
Or what?
Do you think your God wouldn't
want you killed by a monster?
No! That's not what I meant!
That's not true!
What're you getting all serious for?
Ugh, I shouldn't have said that, damn it.
Let's just go.
Hey, Zack...
Did you live in that room the
knife was in all the time?
So what if I did?
I was just wondering...
Huh?
It's the same with what
you were saying earlier.
I don't know anything about you.
So... I don't know why,
but I just got curious.
What the hell?
You're not making sense.
Um... But that room...
I think it could be cleaned up a little.
Shut up! I'm not going back there,
so what does it matter?!
A painting?
What's wrong?
Zack!
Don't just sit there!
Go in first and see if there's an exit!
Okay!
Zack, I found an exit!
Wait there!
Hurry, Zack!
Zack?
To hell with this shit.
I'm too wiped out to use my scythe right now.
Don't make me push myself that hard.
Let's go.
You can't move any more! Just rest!
You'll really die!
I told you... this ain't gonna kill me.
No, you can't. You can't move.
Why are you making that face?
What?
Rest here. I can go by myself.
This time, I'll find the medicine.
No, seriously, what's with
you all of a sudden?
Huh?
Telling me to rest,
trying to look at my wound...
That was...
Looking all gloomy...
Did something happen that
made you feel guilty?
No... I...
Anyway, I have to find that medicine!
Stop ignoring my question!
Also, if you go alone,
you'll just end up dead.
I have a gun.
So if I do see the doctor, I can...
Let me see that gun.
Give it here!
Okay...
Bang.
See? What were you gonna do
with a gun that's not loaded?
What're you trying to do?
You really were gonna just go off and die!
Do you want me to kill you or what?!
And yet you're getting all panicked
over whether I live or die!
What do you want from me?
What are you thinking?
Because you swore to God...
It all comes back to that, huh?
You actually believed a line
like that from a monster?
You don't lie, right?
Yeah, that's right.
My promise wasn't a lie.
Then—
But the thing is...
There is no God in this world.
You're wrong.
Huh?
If there's no God, I... I...
What am I supposed to do?
But it's not just because you swore to God.
Even if someone else had
made the same promise to me,
it wouldn't be good enough.
Why, then?
I... don't know.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Seriously, what the hell is with you?
Smile.
But I don't know if I can smile right now.
I know damn well that you suck at it!
I don't care! Just smile!
I'm going to sleep. Do what you want.
Hey...
Take this.
Dunno if you can actually use it, but...
Zack...
This time, I will be useful to you.