That’s awesome, Yuzu!
I'll hand this to you.
I'm Ginjo.
Kugo Ginjo.
He's fast!
No human can run that fast!
I don’t see any changes in
the reishi surrounding him.
So how is he able to
accelerate like that?
What was that light just now?!
What’s the point of me worrying?
It’s just the two of us today.
If it bugs you that much, I’ll
leave you to yourself…
No, don’t do that!
I wonder if Ichigo’s okay, though…
I’m sure he is.
It just seemed like something came up.
Came up?
You mean like, how he gets in a fight
with a gang of punks out for revenge
and then gets swept away
by some crazy woman?
Fights and a part-time job…
He’s living the teen life.
Getting kidnapped is his part-time job?!
You call that teen life?!
How is that “living the life”?!
What’s the matter?
I could’ve sworn we
were being followed…
Followed?
We’re not Ichigo, I can’t see
why anyone would be after us…
Look out! Above you!
That was close…
I thought I was gonna pee my pants…
Are you kids all right?!
Just barely…
Hey!
Who did that?! Watch
what you’re doing!
In any case, thanks.
Were you the one who was
following us, Arisawa?
Huh?
Following you?  What’re
you talking about?
I was just passing by.
It looked to me like someone
tried to drop a steel beam on you two…
On us?
Don’t scare us like that…
Oh dear…you failed?
It must suck to be turned
away bearing a gift.
That’s what you get for being mean
and not showing us what
that Ichigo guy looks like!
How very true.
What’d you come for?
I thought I told you
two not to follow me.
Oh did you now?!
We’re in this together.
You’re not our boss.
We don’t take orders from you.
In the first place, you
have no persuasive skills!
Let me do it!
I’ll persuade him in no time!
If I recall, he persuaded
us to work for him.
Shut up, Giriko!
You’re the only one he persuaded!
He didn’t persuade me,
and I don’t work for him!
And besides…
Put a sock in it.
That’s enough.
Let’s go.
I don’t like clinging to the past…
So long…
Welcome home, Big Brother!
Look!
My very first test!
I scored a 95!
Aren’t I awesome?!
PRAISE ME
Way to go!
Go and show Dad! He’ll be very happy!
Speaking of Dad, where’d he go?!
I don’t know.
Seems like he’s been
out since morning.
That so…
Well, I’ll be in my room.
Oh…Big Brother…
What is it, Yuzu?
Never mind…it’s nothing.
My face still looks flushed…
All I was going to do
was give him the bread
at the door and ask him a question…
Come on in.
How was I supposed to say no?!
WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED
Wanna come in?
And then Kurosaki tells me
to take home what I want!
He’s so sweet!
So sweet!
SWEET!
S-W-E-E-T… S-W-E…
Ouch!
S-Sorry about that, Big Brother…
Say…
Kurosaki… Has anything
happened to you recently?
Not really.
What makes you ask such a question?
Kurosaki…
You’re keeping something
from me, aren’t you?
You’ll be fine.
That startled me…
Who could be calling at this hour?
You’ll be fine.
Oh, it’s Ishida.
Hello?
What is it, Ishida?
UTAMARO
ENRAKU
I see…uh…huh?
What?!
Where’s Brother Ichi?
Upstairs…
I called him, but he
said he’d eat later.
Oh yeah?
That’s what’s wrong
with adolescent boys…
They’re all pervs.
Karin!
Mind not talking about
such things right now?
And besides, our brother
isn’t like that!
Okay, okay.
But you know, Yuzu, you
should stop holding
on to these illusions
about Brother Ichi.
He’s a guy, like everyone else.
He’s not some anime character.
I mean…
I don’t think of him like that!
I’ve heard enough!
What?!
No, I didn’t mean to…
I was just teasing you, Yuzu!
C’mon!
I don’t care!
Tonight, you’re doing
the dishes, Karin!
Good grief…
Looks like Brother Ichi gave
her the brush off again…
Better have him go and smooth
her ruffled feathers later…
Yuzu?
Brother Ichi?
Hey, wait up!
Where’re you going?!
Brother Ichi!
GENERAL HOSPITAL
Ishida!!
Kurosaki!
Inoue!
You’re already here?
Where’s Chad?
He didn’t answer his phone.
He’s probably working at the
construction site at this hour.
You even contacted Kurosaki?
Man…that was so unnecessary.
Ishida…
Unnecessary, he says…
As always, he still talks big.
I thought I wasn’t
supposed to have visitors.
What if my wounds get worse
from having all these people come in?
Are you an idiot?
Who do you think operated on you?
Something like this won’t
worsen your wounds.
A novice who nearly died because
he was cut down by an enemy
shouldn’t go telling
a doctor what not to do.
W-Wait a minute.
Cut down…by an enemy?!
What’s he talking about, Ishida?!
It’s none of your business…
What do you mean it’s
not my business?!
You were cut down!
If you can’t handle it yourself,
then we’ll have to do
something about it together!
Say something!
Sharing information is vital.
Are you going to let my
kind efforts go to waste?
You keep out of this!
Oh…that was so close…
An utterance another five
hertz higher in pitch
would’ve ripped the sutures…
Ishida…
I’m sorry, Inoue…
Right now, I really don’t
have anything to say…
Go on home.
All right…
URYU ISHIDA
KARAKURA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Kurosaki?
Oh… right!
Sorry you had to come
out this late, Inoue.
Let me take you home.
Huh?! No, I…
Uh…really?!
I’ll take her home in my car.
You should get home quickly.
Your old man seems like the type
who’d give me grief if
I kept you out too late.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
Kurosaki!
See you tomorrow at school!
Hey.
No shouting in the hospital.
Oh! I’m sorry.
It doesn’t look like he’ll be
much help, so I’ll tell only you…
Uryu wasn’t cut down by a Hollow.
But it wasn’t by a
Soul Reaper, either.
I checked the residual Spiritual
Pressure on his wounds, but…
To be honest, I don’t know if it
could be called “Spiritual Pressure.”
It was a kind of Spiritual Pressure
I’ve never felt before.
What does that mean?
Don’t ask.
What I’m telling you
is everything I know.
Uryu himself probably knows
nothing about his assailant.
It’s not that he didn’t
tell you anything.
There was nothing that he could tell you.
But…
Anyway, what is clear is that
you people are in danger.
Any idea who might be responsible?
No…
This is only conjecture, but…
The enemy, who possesses some power
we know nothing about, is probably…
Human.
Someone less Soul Reaper like,
and more like you and Sado.
Uryu, a Quincy, generally falls
into that category, as well.
If we’re to assume that Uryu was
attacked by someone going
after humans like themselves,
then it means the next one to be
in danger is either you or Sado.
I’ll see you home now.
Hey!  Wait!
I said, wait!
Don’t you understand the
meaning of “wait”?!
What do you want?
Want?
Do I have to want something
just to talk to you?
You fool.
Don’t stop me just for
something like that.
Besides, who…
are you, anyway?
I’m…
Looks like things aren’t
going as you had planned.
Well, that’s okay.
Let’s try a different approach.
Let’s eat.
What’s the matter?
Hurry up and eat.
R-Right…
I know…
What do you say we go
shopping after school today?
Didn’t you say there
were things you wanted?
-Yeah…
Bowling?
Yeah!
This is our last school year, right?
College entrance exams and stuff
are just around the corner…
This is our only chance
to go and have fun!
Why do we have to try so
hard to create memories?
Why not just do the stuff we always do?
You don’t get it, do you, Ichigo!
There's no telling what might
happen to us at any time!
I mean, just yesterday...
What happened?
Just yesterday...uh...
He thought a girl from another
school was following him,
but it turned out to be Arisawa.
R-Right! Right!
Funny, right?
Whatever…
I promised to take my
sisters shopping today.
Sorry...
We don’t need to tell him, right?
No, we don’t.
Yuzu!
Big Brother!
Where’s Karin?
She’ll be a bit late, so she said
to go on ahead to the store...
I see. Oh well...
Shall we go?
Okay…
Isn’t that…
The punk from the other day?
Why is he looking at us?
Ichigo!
Weren’t you with Asano and the others?
No, I already had plans to
go shopping with my sisters.
Hello.
Hey.
What’s up?
I told them I’d join them later, but
I can’t get in touch with them...
They’re out of phone range, maybe?
I hope that’s all it is...
But after what happened yesterday...
Yesterday?
What’re you talking about?
They haven’t told you?
Someone is targeting them?!
No... I don’t know, but...
You’d better go, Big Brother.
Yuzu.
They’re your friends, right?
Go to them...
Sorry about this, Yuzu...
Let’s go, Tatsuki!
R-Right...
Damn it!
I can’t reach them!
Tatsuki, we’ll split up!
You check the vicinity
of the bowling alley.
Got it?
Right!
I’ll search the area where
they were attacked yesterday.
It’s the construction
site over at third street!
Got it!
Keigo! Mizuiro!
Look out!
So you’re the one!
Why’re you after these guys?!
Are you that intent on
taking revenge against me?!
Revenge? It’s nothing like that...
I was just...asked by someone to do it.
Asked by someone?!
Bastard!
If only I didn’t have to hold this up!
Helpless, are you?
I’m going to take down your
friends one after the other!
And then...lastly, your family...
What?!
Don’t mess with me!
Hey you… Who asked you to…
Who’re you?
Damn!
Hey! Stop!
Damn it!
Let him go.
Ishida’s...
He sensed my Spiritual
Pressure and disappeared...
Why’re you here?
I just happened by.
Who was that guy?
Probably some punks looking for a fight.
That’s not what happened!
Are they the ones who
got Ishida, as well?!
These two are okay.
They’re unconscious,
but mostly unharmed.
I’ll call an ambulance
just to be safe.
As for you, don’t get
involved any further...
I can’t...no way!
Then let me ask you this.
What can you do?
What the hell’s going on, damn it!
What’s happening that
I don’t know about?!
Isn’t there...
anything I can do?!
Here's some advice. Act
now while you can.
That's if you want to
protect your family.
You have reached Xcution.
This number is unregistered.
Are you a new member?
Please state your name.
Ichigo...Kurosaki...
Mr. Ichigo Kurosaki?
We were expecting your call.
Welcome to Xcution.
Ishida’s dad… How is Ishida doing?
It is none of your concern.
And don’t address me as “dad.”
Then Ishida’s father?
Don’t address me as “father”!
Ryuken! Who cares about that?!
Uryu, you make sure to
address me as “Father.”
I refuse!
THE COMPLETE QUINCY
The Complete Quincy.
My long-awaited return to the
main story has put me
behind in my regular job.
Oh, welcome back!
Why’re you always here?
Because I have nothing else to do.
Aren’t you a doctor, like me?!
Even in the main story,
you’ve only examined a patient once!
That’s not relevant...
Shut up!