Hado Number 33:
Sokatsui!
Are you okay?
My bad. I got caught off guard.
Honestly…
You could’ve easily dodged
that attack with Flash Step.
I figured I could manage
without using it.
Instead, you nearly
got yourself killed.
Listen, your…
What?
N-Nothing.
It’s you guys again!
Imoyama!
Who’re you calling Imoyama?!
The name’s Kurumadani!
Ku-ru-ma-da-ni!!
Does it really matter?
Yes, it does!
Listen up!
Don’t do anything else
without my permission!
Sheesh!
Oh please, Imoyama…
He does have a good point.
After all, he is my replacement.
Try not to overdo yourself.
Okay.
Come on, you can do it.
Oh! Are you okay?!
It’s nice, isn’t it?
Being able to live a peaceful
and ordinary life.
Yeah…
So this guy’s excuse was because
he saw it yesterday on TV!
Can you believe that?
As always, your story
has no point, Keigo.
Excuse me?!
That’s harsh!
I was trying to liven up the mood
of our after-lunch conversation!
After? You’re still eating…
That’s not my point!
-Why are you always like this, huh?
-Kurosaki!
Yeah, okay.
Be right back.
Is Ichigo still doing
that thing of his?
I don’t know.
You’re okay with all of this?
Sure, why not?
I guess so…
I understand.
Rukia…
What’re you doing here?
Uh…just taking a walk.
What about you? You were
staying pretty late today.
Had to make up for the
classes I missed.
I had to skip school for a
while to deal with Aizen.
Don’t complain.
Your job is to be a student.
I know that.
Hey, Rukia…
What is it?
How long are you going
to be staying here?
That’s none of your business.
Oh yes it is.
You’re freeloading
at my place, remember?
Your family said I could
stay as long as I want.
That was Yuzu and my old man.
I’ll go back when my mission is done.
I see…
Shouldn’t we be hurrying home?
Your sister was excited about
making curry for dinner tonight.
Crap!
Yuzu asked me to pick up some pickles
for the side on my way home!
Then you’d better get going!
Yeah, see you later!
You fool…
Don’t worry!
I’ll protect you!
Now’s my chance!
Damn… Not now.
Rukia.
Thanks, Ishida.
Why’d you struggle
against a mere Hollow?!
I said thanks, didn’t I?
Sorry we scared you like that.
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Another Hollow?
Sure are a lot tonight.
Okay, let’s go, Rukia!
You stay.
Ishida and I will go.
Huh? But why?
You’re such an idiot.
Are you going to just
leave this kid alone?
You can come after you perform
Konso on this spirit.
Hey!
Kuchiki, about Kurosaki’s
Spiritual Pressure…
I know. It’s reaching its limit.
The Spiritual Pressure that was
restored using the Mod Soul was temporary.
His Spirit Energy is dropping rapidly.
He’s probably unable to
do even a Flash Step…
Then why do you allow Kurosaki
to continue fighting?
In his condition, he’ll…
I know!
I know that...
I understand your situation.
Kuchiki…you need to keep
Ichigo from fighting any more.
But what about Ichigo's feelings?
I’m aware of that.
However, he is losing his Spirit Energy
far sooner than we had anticipated.
It’s too dangerous.
I understand.
There you are!
Why’re you staring
blankly out into space?
It’s nothing.
Really? You’ve been
acting strange lately.
No I haven’t.
Then why won’t you
look me in the face?
You’ve been like
that for a while now.
There’s something you want
to tell me, isn’t there?
Yeah.
It’s okay. You don’t
have to tell me.
What?!
What’s with you?
First you tell me to say it,
then you tell me not to!
Sorry…
I just wanted to be sure.
Quit messing with me!
I apologized, didn’t I?
We’ve known each
other a long time now.
I can pretty much guess
what you’re thinking.
You really are a piece of work.
I’ll hear what you have
to say before you leave.
Huh?
Oh, she’s here!
You’re late, Kuchiki!
What…
What’s going on?
Isn’t it obvious? It’s ice-skating.
No, what I meant was...
You were staring at this
place the other day.
So I thought you wanted
to go ice-skating.
Huh?
Dummy…
What?
Nothing.
It gets really pretty here
during springtime with
all the cherry blossoms in bloom.
Then again, we can just
ask Byakuya and have
him show us cherry blossoms
anytime we want, huh?
What do you think my brother is?!
So why’d you bring everyone here?
What? You don’t get it?
Kuchiki! Kurosaki!
Hurry! Hurry!
Be right there!
Let’s go!
Wait a minute!
I’ve never done this before!
Outta my way! Outta my way!
Help!
Try relaxing a bit.
See ya!
Oh no you don’t!
Tatsuki!
Okay, I’m going to let go now.
Wait! Not so fast!
How’s that!
Gotcha!
Thanks…
Man, this sucks!
Why am I the only one stuck here?
Everybody looks like they’re
having so much fun!
Damn it!
I’m sure no one would notice
if I get out for a bit…
Mama!
This doll is moving!
Don’t be silly. That’s impossible.
But it is!
Wow! It’s pretty!
Why are there fireworks
at this time of year?
A theme park opened recently nearby.
They do fireworks every
day at about this hour.
There’s a place like that now?
What? You didn’t know?
It’s not big, but it’s
a pretty nice date spot.
Just the other day, I
went there with Chad!
It was fun.
It’s nice to spend time
like this for a change.
Yeah.
See you! Bye-bye!
Yeah, later.
That was quite fun.
Coming from you, that was a good idea.
You just can’t come out
and compliment me, can you.
By the way, something’s
been bugging me.
What is it?
That time…
How did you know where I was?
I had lost control of myself back there,
so I should have been difficult
to recognize, right?
I wonder…
Huh?
You don’t know?!
Compared to when we first
met, you became stronger.
Your Spiritual Pressure
went to a whole new level.
But you didn’t change at all.
Huh? What’re you…
A Hollow!
You need to keep Ichigo
from fighting any more.
Ichigo, wait!
What’s the matter?
I can feel its Spiritual Pressure
all the way over here!
It’s a pretty big one!
Let’s go!
Ichigo!
Damn!
It dodged me like I was nothing.
Ichigo!
Oh, no… His Spiritual Pressure’s…
Damn…not now…
Come on!
It’s huge.
Sorry, I’m getting in your way.
You fool! Don’t say that!
You’re not in my way!
If you get hurt, then
I’ll support you!
If you can’t move, then
I’ll fight in your place!
If you’re in pain, then
I’ll bear your pain!
We’re friends, right?!
Yeah, you’re right…
Ichigo!
I’m okay!
Rukia…can you stop its legs?
Yes, leave it to me!
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki.
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
This is my last time!
Ichigo…
Here goes!
Getsuga…
tensho!
Ichigo!
Are you okay?!
Just barely.
Honestly, you’re
always going overboard.
It’s like you just said…
No matter what happens,
I’ll always be me.
So don’t hide stuff
that you have to say.
You…knew about my mission?
I can sort of guess what the old
man and the others are thinking.
Ichigo…
I’ve put you through
a lot, haven’t I?
Ichigo!
What’s wrong?!
Are you okay?!
Yeah...
Sorry I made you tag along
with me until the very end.
Don’t say that…
You…fool…
We’re friends.
Don’t forget that.
I know that…
Now, rest…
Ichigo, you’re right…
No matter what happens,
we won’t change.
Kurosaki!
Huh? What?
Is this my place?
Yeah.
Oh yeah! My powers…
Ichigo…
Your body is going through the second
stage of Spiritual Pressure loss.
Soon, your remaining Spiritual
Pressure will be gone, as well.
I see. I knew it.
I figured it was about that time…
Can I go outside?
I don’t sense any spirit presence.
Even Rukia’s presence is
gradually fading away…
I really am…losing my powers…
This is goodbye, Ichigo…
Looks that way…
Hey, don’t make such a sad face.
Even if you can’t see me, I’ll
still be able to see you.
What the hell?
That doesn’t make me happy at all.
And I’m not making
a sad face, either!
Give everybody…my regards.
I will…
Bye, Rukia.
Thank you.
There’s no more reason for me
to stay at Ichigo’s place.
Then I’ll take you in!
I just came up with a
new design for you!
Wait! Let me cuddle him!
I can’t give up on this one,
even if it’s against you, Sado!
Please! Don’t fight over me!
You’re both creeping me out!
Up until now, my life’s
been nothing but fighting…
Starting with the next episode,
I’m going to make the most
out of my high-school life!
We still haven’t done
our sports festival…
And I also want to do
the cultural festival.
Oh, and then there’s
the class trip…
Brother!
You’re starting your last year in
high school with the next episode,
-so make sure you have everything ready!
-Huh?
Already?!
You’re kidding me!