Gyokaku Kumoi
has grown impatient
with the failed attempts
to assassinate Rurichiyo.
He bestows his veteran assassin
and his squad members
with powerful swords
known as the Bakkouto,
forged through
the Kasumiohji Clan’s hidden art,
and dispatches them
to the World of the Living.
Ichigo battles Hanza Nukui,
the leader of the assassin squad.
Using the knowledge gained
from their previous fight,
Ichigo targets
the Bakkouto Saiga’s weakness.
Instead, he finds himself trapped
inside a world of mirrors.
I know your moves!
Wha—?!
I told you before.
I never fall for
the same move twice!
That Zanpakuto derives its attack
from reflected light.
So if I shatter that, it’s all over!
I wonder about that.
What?!
I told you, depending on
the Spiritual Pressure of its wielder,
this sword can get
infinitely stronger.
Where am I?
Wha—?
Not yet?
Ichigo!
Mom!
That’s not good,
boys don’t cry.
Tell me Ichigo…
What made you want to
learn karate all of a sudden?
Huh?
That’s a secret.
Come on, you don’t
want to tell your mom?
Look, look, that’s so pretty!
You’re right! So pretty.
Ichigo, do you like sunsets?
They’re pretty,
but I don’t like them.
Huh? Why?
I start feeling a little lonely.
That’s not so! They’re pretty!
Mom!
M-Mom…
Ichigo Kurosaki.
This is the true power of my Saiga.
I’ll give you a good taste
of your worst nightmare.
That’s why I told you…
I don’t like sunsets.
Come back…Mom.
I’m sorry, Ichigo!
Where did you go?
Mom…
– Why?
I can’t find you anywhere.
I’m sorry, Ichigo!
I’m late.
Okay. Let’s go!
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Ichigo…
Where did you go, Mom?!
What’s wrong?
Oh my, I was just a little late.
Were you crying?
You promised me, right?
I’m not crying!
It’s just that, back then I… I…
Silly…
But because of what I did…
Who cares about that?
Okay. Let’s go home.
Everyone’s worried.
Mom?
Mom…
That hurts, Mom!
Stop it!
Mom…
My body…
This isn’t right!
Mom…
She died!
This…is not reality.
But…
Mom…
It’s not over.
It’s just beginning, Ichigo Kurosaki!
This nightmare will continue
until you go mad.
Stop it…Mom!
This is an illusion.
Damn it! This…
You really think this is
enough to bring me down?
In that case,
try to take her down!
You!
Your mother…
See if you can kill your loved one.
In the end, your resolve cannot
compare to the likes of us,
who have chosen
the path of blood and strife.
It’s over…Ichigo Kurosaki.
Mom…
Mom!
What?!
It’s…that black
Spiritual Pressure again.
Mom…
Everyone’s…fine.
Both Yuzu and Karin.
And Dad is his usual self.
I’m…all right.
I’m getting by.
Mom…
You are escaping the nightmare
created by Saiga?!
How can you
have such power?
I have to get going.
Everyone’s waiting.
Mom…back then…I…
couldn’t protect you, I’m sorry.
One more thing.
Thanks…for protecting me.
You have no right to step all over
someone else’s memories!
You…
You… You’re…
Bastard!
You’re…
Are you…being consumed
by your sword?
The Bakkouto…
The more spiritual power you pour in…
it’s power…will grow infinitely!
Something like this is nothing!
Stop it!
I won’t take orders from you!
You… Why fight that hard?
For the sake of the Kasumiohji Clan…
and for my sake.
Since ancient times, the Kasumiohji Clan
has been a distinguished clan,
proudly providing swords
to the royal family.
We too have historically existed
alongside them as their shadows.
Hey! Who are you people?!
And at times…
We would even deceive the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads themselves
to keep the hidden art behind
our sword making technique safe.
Even if it were forbidden…
It was all to protect
the Kasumiohji Clan.
That has been
our reason for existence.
Amongst them, I have fought
many bitter battles and survived.
And finally…
I acquired this power!
A power only
the chosen few are granted!
You’re saying you are
the chosen one?
That’s right! Then you…
How dare you!
If your purpose in being is to
protect the Kasumiohji Clan…
Why did you attack Rurichiyo?!
Because the weak have no right
to carry on the Kasumiohji legacy!
Just for that?
Rurichiyo is…
frightened…shaking…
Even when she’s smiling,
she’s afraid.
She…just wants to be free.
The princess of the Kasumiohji Clan
has no freedom!
That’s…not something
for you to decide!
What do you know?!
So that’s…your…true…power!
Interesting!
Why you…
Getsugatensho!
Not yet!
I won’t lose!
I’m not going to lose here!
Saiga!
Stop it already!
You’re not the chosen one!
What are you talking about?!
You’re just consumed
by that sword.
D-Don’t…be ridiculous.
Using that thing…
You’re just shortening your life.
What are you doing?
Shut up, Soul Reaper!
This is not the limit
of my power!
A Bakkouto would
never consume me!
Wait!
What are these guys?
I said it’s impossible.
I know, but I’m sure—
Oh, Mr. Kibune!
Greetings!
Greetings.
But he’s…
Then we should get
Lieutenant Hisagi’s advice.
Third Seat Kibune…
Where is he going?
This is…the Kasumiohji Clan.
Why is Third Seat Kibune here?
Where’s the lavatory?
This is like a maze.
I can’t remember.
What are you doing?
Uh… I’m trying to
find the lavatory.
Is someone around?
Lord Kannogi is the master here!
Why has he been left alone?!
I’m very sorry!
Escort him!
– Yes!
P-Pardon me!
I’m looking for the lavatory.
I see. Genga is dead.
What about Nukui and Douko?
Yes…
I am afraid so.
That fool.
This…is quite a sharp sword.
However, Nukui and
my brothers are dead.
But I have survived.
What do you think?
Next time,
I’ll take Nukui’s place.
Step down.
What?!
I’ll have nothing to do with
a small fish like you.
Why you…
You’re a fool.
Inoue, how are Ishida
and the others doing?
Recovering, but he suddenly
fell unconscious.
What? Why?
To help him feel better,
I gave him some chazuke
with ohagi mixed into it.
That’s why!
What did you say?!
MEN’S SOUL REAPER ASSOCIATION
MEN’S LAVATORY
A joint activity with
the Women’s Association?!
Yes, today we received an official
request from Vice-Chairman Ise.
That means they finally recognize
the Men’s Association!
Okay, let’s participate!
Yes, sir!
Are you in charge of—
For verbal threats
such as this,
it is imperative to react
with a firm disposition.
WOMEN’S SOUL REAPER ASSOCIATION
"HOW TO REJECT A HARD SELL" SEMINAR
What the hell are you—