Now, the world will be mine!
Just a minute.
As long as I am here,
I won't let that happen!
Evil alien!
What?!
Owner! I mean, Doctor!
Look out!
Look out! Look out!
And done!
That was close.
The evil alien, Kon,
who descended to earth and
hid among the earthlings
to commit villainous acts,
was captured by the righteous
scientist, Dr. Urahara,
and reconstructed into
the hero of justice, Karakurizer.
That is how Kon became
a hero of justice!
In order to return to
his original alien form,
he must put away all 108 Hollows
that killed Dr. Urahara's daughter!
Fight, Karakurizer!
For Dr. Urahara's sake!
Now is the time to fight!
Go get 'em!
Hey! What's with this storyline?
Huh?
People who didn't see the previous
episode won't have a clue!
And, you're doing a synopsis,
don't get so excited and yell!
Now is the time to fight!
Go get 'em!
Don't repeat yourself!
– You really love this stuff, don't you?!
– Go get 'em!
Hurry and get on with
a proper synopsis!
– Bonjour!
– Go, Kon!
I mean Konso Cop Karakurizer!
Karakurizer, away!
This is too lame!
I asked Ishida to
design the outfit!
It's totally useless!
I am the new emissary of justice,
Karakurizer Spirit!
– Karakurizer Beast!
– I am Karakurizer Erotic!
– Karakurizer Delicate.
– I am Karakurizer Tiny Devil.
Pleased to meet you.
Mission complete.
They're coming.
Oh, come on! Was that it?!
KONSO COP KARAKURIZER
FINAL EPISODE:
GREAT FORTRESS SHOWDOWN
What is that thing?
It's a Hollow.
Such a humongous Hollow.
I've never seen anything like it!
Neither have I!
Substitute Soul Reapers,
humans with strange
Spiritual Pressure,
guys who can see my form…
What the hell is going on
in this town?!
Ow ow ow ow!
Afro!
At any rate,
I don't know the details,
but there are rumors
that something terrible
is about to happen soon
in Karakura Town.
I hear that high-level
Soul Reapers from
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are responding in utmost secrecy.
Their response might
have something
to do with these
Hollows showing up.
Hey, what's he talking about?
Beats me.
I don't have a clue.
What's that bastard Ichigo doing?!
Unless we do something
about the source of all this,
we're the ones in danger!
Why do we have to be the ones
that take on this thing?!
Quit whining!
The owner chose you guys
to take his place!
What?! Nobody asked him
to choose us.
All right, all right, calm down.
More importantly,
we learned many interesting facts
about that large Hollow fortress.
This is based on analysis of intel
collected by Kanonji,
who is working surveillance.
You guys sure have
a lot of free time
to be putting stuff
together like this.
I don't have free time, you know.
Sorry about that.
I'm tied up with things right now,
so please ask Tessai
for the details this time.
You guys coming together
is such a huge help!
Now I can concentrate
on my own work.
Well then,
take care of things, okay?
Busy, my foot!
As you've just heard,
I will explain in lieu of
the owner from here on.
These are Combined Hollows
that have joined together
under the Hollows that
form the central nucleus.
However, they are not very
powerful Hollows by nature,
so it is taking time for them
to concentrate their power.
Ohh… I don't get it.
Well, you don't need
to understand,
but the point is that
the Combined Hollow Fortress
will be complete in
another several hours.
We don't stand a chance of
winning unless we hit them now.
How're we going to beat them?
With your power of friendship,
of course!
Power of friendship, what?
I'll do it!
What?
Right now, Ichigo and
the others aren't here.
In that case, we have no choice
but to do it, right?
Umm… Arisawa…
Are you serious?!
Recharging from a home outlet…
How cheap can a hero get?
Don't open it so suddenly!
You startled me!
What is it?
That body of yours…
it's Ichigo's, isn't it?
Well…
If you don't want to answer,
you don't have to force yourself.
Umm… Right…
I've been watching him
all this time.
But…
This doesn't concern you.
That idiot.
We don't have any choice but to
let them take care of Orihime.
That's why I…
I will do what I can.
You…
And besides…
Huh?
At any rate, I won't
be satisfied right now
unless I take out this
pent up anger on something!
So that's the real reason,
isn't it?
Huh? Were you here all this time?
It's cramped upstairs.
Afro's over there, too.
Right, Afro?
No, I don't care about him.
Yeah.
Say…
why'd you agree to
become a Karakurizer?
I didn't become one
because I wanted to!
The other day, someone said
Don Kanonji was filming on location
for the first time in a while,
so I went to have a look.
I went to his dressing room
to ask for his autograph.
For some reason, Urahara
was there talking to him,
when one of those strange
monsters appeared.
And then…
Look out!
Super Spirit Cane!
Kanonji defeated the monster.
Realizing that I could see it,
Kanonji said…
You have a superb power, boy!
And in the end, I became one
without knowing how it happened!
Gosh, just like me.
I didn't want to be the only one
to have this happen to him,
so I tried to get Mizuiro involved,
as well.
But…
Count me out, Asano.
He was quick to run away.
And that's why Honsho
came in his place.
You poor soul.
I don't need your pity!
Just do something about this!
Everyone.
Is something the matter?
Looking at your face all of
a sudden is bad for the heart!
How rude.
But more importantly,
I don't see Beast and Erotic.
If you're looking for us,
we're right here.
I was just picking flowers.
Using the john, eh?
Don't say that!
I'm sorry.
Now we have everyone here
except Spirit,
who continues his
surveillance duties.
We've completed our analysis of
the Combination Hollow Fortress.
As we suspected,
the weak point
is a single Hollow that forms
the central nucleus of the whole.
We want you to sneak inside
and destroy the Hollow that
forms the central nucleus!
You mean "see how it goes," right?
It is a coordinated operation based
on the teamwork of friendship!
I hear you, I hear you!
But you know,
we could use your help.
That won't be possible.
The owner, Jinta, and myself
are tied up with things to do.
We will, however,
let Ururu join you,
so please bear with us.
Yes, I'll do my best.
You're kidding me.
– Karakurizer!
Karakurizer!
Career Change!
So you've appeared, bad spirits!
Rizer Cannonball!
Did you see that?
Allow me to explain!
The main feature of
the Karakurizer Spirit's suit design
is the mask that shows natural
facial hair to it's best advantage!
Why can't you pay more attention
to battle-related features?
You're wrong!
Thanks to the beard mask,
his Spiritual Pressure increases,
which becomes
the striking power you see!
What kind of a feature is
that supposed to be?!
Impudent bad spirits!
Not bad at all,
Karakurizer Tiny Devil!
Tiny Devil and I will handle it here,
you guys storm the fortress!
Let's go!
Guess I'll have to…
Quickly!
That was rough.
Is this the entrance
to the fortress?
The real battle is about to begin!
I'm stoked!
How can you be so excited?
They appeared!
Leave them to me!
I'm in a bad mood right now!
Come at me, starting with
the ones who want to die!
An ogre…she's an ogre.
So cool!
Don't be afraid of
your own teammate!
Get them! Get them!
By the way, can these guys fight?
They'll be fine!
Keigo has
a body-enhancing mechanism
that takes advantage of
his ability to run away.
For Chizuru, we've attached
a special capability
tailored to her characteristics.
Are those things
going to be useful?
Hey, don't cling to me!
Karakurizer!
Leave this place to us!
You hurry toward
the nucleus of the fortress!
What? But…
Kon, your Rizer Beam
can surely defeat the Hollow
at the central nucleus!
Or rather, that is the only way!
What?!
Now isn't the time to tell me that!
I'm totally mentally unprepared.
Never mind!
Hurry and get going!
Nicely dodged.
You're pretty good
for a lowly human.
Who are you?!
I am an Arrancar, who has been
given power by Lord Aizen.
Are you the big boss
of this fortress?
I will not allow you people to
have your way any further.
Busted!
How dare you!
Allow me to explain!
Erotic's suit is equipped
with a Hyper Erotic Mode
that responds to her instincts!
When that mode is activated,
she can use a variety of techniques
that cannot be shown on television!
I thought there was nothing
but boring monsters,
but here's one sweet woman!
Since we've met,
I'll be your playmate.
What?!
When she is in
Hyper Erotic Mode,
Erotic's speed, for women only,
exceeds that of the Sonido!
What's going on?!
Stop it!
Rizer Doggy Style!
No!
Get going.
– R-Right!
– Oh, you're so cute.
Where the hell
are you touching! No!
Ohh… Poor thing.
If it's a woman,
is it anything goes with her?
Exactly!
Erotic boasts invincible strength
when her enemy is
a beautiful woman!
More importantly, though,
I think you'd better
look out behind you.
Huh?
You'll be fine!
Delicate, your suit
is equipped with
a mechanism that enhances
your ability to run away!
Use that technique to
your greatest advantage!
Why're you so hyper?!
Wasn't explaining
the suit your only job?!
Don't worry about the details.
Good morning…
Tsuchinamazu!
Afro!
I came immediately.
Anytime, anywhere!
I am the elite Soul Reaper
currently in charge
of Karakura Town,
Zennosuke Kurumadani,
that's me!
Damn it.
Why is this happening to me?
Huh?
I-I'm sorry!
Hello?
Could it be that this monster…
can't move?
This is my chance!
I can do this!
What the—?!
Huh? There's another one?!
I knew it! This is too much for me!
Hey! Phony shopkeeper,
do something!
Hey!
Damn it, there's nothing I can do!
I'm telling you,
I'm not cut out for this!
Was that…
Kanonji and the others?!
Boom.
Karakurizer!
I mean King Kararkura!
Throw everything you've got at it
and become a real hero!
Give it the finishing blow quickly!
You're the only one here now!
What is it with her?!
You belong to me,
little bunny rabbit!
– Caught you!
– No more!
Go, Karakurizer!
This is our…
– Power of friendship!
Everyone?
Do it, Karakurizer.
We will record what
happens here and
provide Kuchiki with
a full report.
To Sis?
I love you, Kon!
Damn.
In that case, I'll do it!
Here I go!
Special Technique
Ri…z…er Beam!
Blow away to kingdom come!
I did it! Serves ya right!
Huh?!
What? What? What?!
Karakurizer did it!
Let's all get out!
Hurry, all of you!
R-Right!
Cry, Benihime.
Are you all right, Kon?
Did we get them?
Yes, thanks to all of you.
Huh?
What happened?
They're fine.
They're just sleeping.
Sleeping?
Yes.
I'll explain the details to you
when everything is over.
Thanks to all of your efforts,
I was able to complete my work
without it being noticed.
Owner.
Yes.
Now then, it's time.
Peace was preserved
in Karakura Town.
Once again, when evil
stands in the way,
Karakurizer will appear again
without fail!
We don't need
narration anymore.
Thank you for your hard work.
As long as there is
evil in this world…
Go! Konso Cop Karakurizer!
I said that's enough!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today, we will explain
our true powers!
This is my sword, Ultima.
It is a glistening sword of light
ULTIMA
with a blade of reishi!
And, Dondochakka's body
contains all sorts of things,
from Bawabawa to swords!
SECRET
Why're you guys
doing this segment?
– Whoa! When did you?!
– Whoa!
Can't you tell?
We're going over things
in preparation for the showdown!
Showdown?
We don't even know
if you'll have a part.
Then don't call us here!
NO SCENES