Four?!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you do defeat me,
there are three Espada above me.
You can try a thousand times.
You will not be victorious.
It seems that I overestimated you.
Your development didn't
meet my expectations.
It's useless.
Look… That's going to disappear too.
Abarai!
Don't stand around doing nothing!
You can still fight, can't you?!
Finding weaknesses is your forte!
His tricks…
Isn't there anything
you can do about them?!
Don't be silly.
I have something!
All right… I believe you!
Don't shoot poorly!
That's no problem.
As long as you’re
not the one shooting!
Abarai.
How many seconds can you stall him?
Sorry… At most, about 20 seconds.
I see.
That's more than enough!
Let's go!
Don't interfere.
How exciting.
I'm going to personally
take a look at
what they're going to do
in that condition.
Wait one moment.
This…doesn't hurt.
Honestly, that Uryu…
Going off by himself.
I can't play the fool well
without a straight man.
Take a look at what I did just now.
I'd like him to note that I fell on my butt
because I was always like this
and not just playing dumb.
Did I fall into the middle of everything?
I sense an extraordinary
Spiritual Pressure.
Is it bad? This situation is bad, isn't it?
That's…
Dondochakka!
He went to Renji!
Anyway, what's that?!
Are you telling me that
he's in that amusing pose
just because he got mixed up
in this battle?!
Damn it!
He's not my friend anymore!
I'm going to cry!
Still… I found him,
so I should save him.
Please… Nobody notice me.
Do you hear a rustling?
Come to think of it, I do.
It's all right, Pesche!
You can do this!
No one will notice
your existence!
And I don't mean that
I have no presence!
– Could it be?
– A cockroach?
Roach?!
No! I hate cockroaches!
Someone your size?!
It's not a matter of size!
They can fly!
Flap, flap…
Their antennae move!
Twitch, twitch…
They glisten!
No!  I hate cockroaches!
That's annoying!
Is this really the time for that?!
– They really haven't noticed me.
– What do you mean “annoying”?!
– I'm starting to feel kind of lonely.
– I'm afraid of scary things!
Just a little…
I'd like them to notice me just a little.
Pesche!
You came out instead!
Wh-Wh-Where are you, Pesche?!
Did you come for me?!
D-D-Did you come to save me?!
I was terrified!
S-S-Stupid! Dondochakka,
don't make a fuss!
They're going to discover us!
Be quiet!
Shut up! I'm telling you to shut up!
Please shut up!
Take this!
How was that? It hurts, doesn't it?!
My butt got hit a lot,
so I'll give half of it to you!
I'll give half of my butt to you!
If only I could!
– Pesche, be quiet.
– If only I could…Huh?
– No!
– You two!
– Stop!
What's that?!
I was wondering what
you were going to do.
As I expected,
you're only using brute force!
How silly.
What are you doing?
Unfortunately,
I have no interest in things like this.
Inferno and war,
the sea barrier surges…
– Head to the south!
– Hey!
Say something.
Indeed, there's a big difference
in strength between you and my Shikai.
And I don't think I have
a chance in a power struggle.
But…
Even if the difference
in our power is great,
you'll hurt a little if you
get hit at point-blank range.
I was always terrible at Kido.
I was always scolded because I could
never control it and it would explode.
Now then, let's see who's tougher!
You or me!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Damn!
How impudent of you, Soul Reaper!
It's exactly as we had planned.
If Abarai attacks you,
whether he's successful or not,
you'll retreat in the opposite
direction from him.
As for your distance…
You seem to like
looking down on people.
If you get attacked,
you have a habit of moving
just beyond the reach of your enemy.
What of it?
You seem to like attacking people
when their backs are turned.
Do you think you've won, Quincy?
Yes…
I do.
Impossible!
I thought I sealed away
the Spiritual Pressures
of all your weapons.
That just means that there are things
in this world that you don't know about.
Shall I explain the situation in terms
that are easier for you to understand?
Hasta aquí…
It's over, Szayelaporro Grantz.
Damn!
– Lord Szayelaporro!
Wh-What was that technique
just now, Uryu?!
Sprenger…
It destroys everything within
the circle I drew with the Gintô
and the Seeleschneider.
Seeleschneider has the ability
to store reishi in its hilt
in the event of a battle with
an enemy that can diffuse reishi.
I can use that reishi to
temporarily revive its blade.
I used it to draw a Quincy Zeichen.
By dropping a drop of
the compressed reishi that's in my Gintô
I can create a giant explosion
within the circle.
It's powerful,
but difficult to use because
casting it takes a long time.
I can't use it in one-on-one battles.
I need help from someone I can trust.
Flattery won't do you any good.
I really am grateful to you.
Damn…
Wha—?!
B-Bastard!
– Lord Szayelaporro!
Lord Szayelaporro!
Damn…damn…damn…damn…
I'm honestly surprised that
you can stand after taking that.
Of course… I told you…
I analyzed everything about
your Spiritual Pressure.
Even an attack I've never seen before.
If the Spiritual Pressure is yours…
I can disperse the impact and…
reduce the damage…
the damage…
the damage, you fools!
– L-Lumina! Lumina! Lumina!
– Don't make a fuss!
I'll make you a new one later!
Y-Yes!
What's wrong? Why are you surprised?
I told you that my Octava Fracciónes
are a little special.
They're recovery medicine.
When I'm injured,
I can heal my wounds
by eating one of them.
That's how I made them.
How could you?
You monster!
I'd like you to call me a genius.
Wait! Where are you going?!
Where am I going?
I'm going to change my clothes.
It's embarrassing to fight in
these worn-out clothes, don't you think?
– Stop fooling around!
– Hey…
Think about it.
I have to change because
you tore my clothes to shreds.
Wait quietly.
And use that little brain of yours
to think of your next plan.
While I'm changing,
I'll also be thinking of
grotesque ways I can kill you.
Ichigo…
Don't die…
Ichigo!
Out of the way, kid!
Seis Espada…
Lord Grimmjow.
I thought so.
S-Stop!
Kurosaki…
Heal him.
What's the meaning of this?
Ichigo!
Ichigo protected me and
took a direct hit from a Cero!
took a kick, too!
I was a burden on Ichigo!
If I weren't here,
Ichigo would have been all right!
It's all my fault!
Please…
I want you to save Ichigo!
Shut up!
Quit your yapping, kid!
If you make a noise again,
I'll wipe you out!
O-Okay…
He'll be healed without you asking.
Shut up and watch.
An incredible Spiritual Pressure is
swirling around Kurosaki's wounds.
I can't…reject it.
Who did this?
Ulquiorra…
Grimmjow.
This is how he does things.
I'm not sure whether
he's aware of it or not.
I see.
He always punches a hole
into prey he becomes fond of
in the same location as his own.
I'll teach him the punishment
for attacking someone else's prey.
Nel and Inoue…
Kurosaki!
I-Ichigo!
Shut up!
If you have time to make a fuss,
then heal him already!
You're… Grimmjow!
Why are you with Inoue?!
You shut up, too, and get healed!
I came here to settle things
with you when you're fully healed!
Grimmjow, is that why
you're making me heal him?
I told you to shut up!
He's dying,
but I'm letting you heal him!
Don't complain!
Hurry!
Ulquiorra will catch on
sooner or later and come back!
Before he does…
Szayelaporro, I never thought that you
healed yourself by eating those things.
You want to try some?
I've prepared Fracciónes
in a variety of ways:
Western, Japanese, and
Chinese flavors, to match my tastes.
Yes, yes! I want to
eat a curry-flavored one!
Don't try it!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
L-Lady Yoruichi!
I am Squad 13
Third Seat Kiyone Kotetsu!
I've always been a fan of yours!
Please give me your autograph!
Oh well…
Pass me some paperboard!
You're a thousand years too early
to be outwitting me!
P-Please stop, Lady Yoruichi!
UNABLE TO RECOVER