Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Oh, yeah… I came home, didn’t I?
Good morning…Ichigo!
You’ve improved, Ichigo.
I’m impressed that you were able
to ward off my Congratulatory
2nd-Semester Wonderful Kick.
Shut up…
Then, take my “Crazy--
I said, quit making such a racket
first thing in the morning!
Kurosaki Clinic
Ichigo, Dad…
Breakfast is ready!
What in the world are they doing…?
Huh? What happened to you, Dad?
Leave me alone!
By the way, Ichigo,
have you put on more muscle?
Huh?!
I didn’t notice yesterday.
I-Is that so? Never mind that…
Have you two finished
your summer homework?
Uh-huh! We finished really early.
We had nothing else to do while
you were on your trip, you see.
Oh… By the way…
That Kanonji guy came by twice.
He said he’d made you
a disciple or something…
That’s right!
No… You see, uh…
Your guard’s down!
Still can't beat your dad!
What's the big idea?!
Oh! Dad! Ichigo!
I…chi…go--!
‘Morning…
Good morning, Ichigo!
Yo, Mizuiro!
Long time no see, Ichigo.
And I…
Good morning, Ichigo!
Oh… Tatsuki, long time no see.
Yo!
But, it sure has been a while…
You weren’t home at all.
Good morning. Huh?
Chad and Ichigo have nice tans…
Huh? Do I?
What? Don’t tell me you two
went off somewhere together?!
Huh?
What are you doing looking
at each other?!
Don’t tell me something developed
between you during the summer…
Quit letting your imagination
run wild!
By the way, Inoue.
How’d you enjoy your visit
with your relatives?
Huh? Me? I had a great time.
So many things happened…
Oh? What sort of things?
Huh? Well…
We went to a weird place…
Huh?!
Weird place?
Yeah. It looks sort of like
an Edo period town
with people carrying swords…
And there was this cat
that could talk…
Then that cat turned
into a girl and…
All right, all right… I understand.
Just keep it up through
our second semester!
‘Morning! Come on.
Sit down, everyone!
What’s up with you?
Okay… So, everyone’s here?
Very good, very good.
Oshima and Sorimachi aren’t here,
but those two are delinquents,
so that’s okay.
Hey, should you be saying that?!
What a thing to say!
Now, then… Shall we collect
our summer assignments?
Thank you, Rukia.
Thank you.
Where are you?
Come on out here!
That voice is…
Ichigo Kurosaki!
I know you’re up there!
Don't hide! Come on out!
Ichigo, you know him?
That 60's looking guy!
Hey, Ichigo! Don’t keep me waiting!
Oh… How nostalgic.
Kurosaki, is that your…
He's a relative!
Oh, is that so…?
Nostalgic for her…?
How he’s dressed?
Hurry up!
Why you--!
Yo!
What do you mean, “yo”?
What’re you so excited about?
What…? What the heck
are you doing here?!
What’s it to you where I am?
There’s no reason
for you to ge--
Sure there is!
Yelling to me like that!
Man, but this gigai
is pretty confining.
I’m amazed Rukia could stay
in hers so long…huh?
What are you doing here?
Uh…drop it! I’ve been put in charge
of this Karakura Town.
Mr. Urahara told me where you were,
so I came to see you.
You got a problem with that?!
You did?
Yeah!
When you’re only a lieutenant?
You got demoted.
That’s not it!
It’s your fault because guys like
you are leaking Spiritual Pressure.
What are you talking about?!
Huh?!
That’s what I’ve been trying
to tell you. See?
A Hollow…
All right. These are all
your assignments, right?
What should I do?
This is bad… It’s getting closer!
Ichigo! What are you doing?!
There's one with no name on it!
Summer's over. Shape up!
Damn! This gigai…!
What’s the matter?
I can’t get out of it! Damn!
Hey, Ichigo, you go!
What are you talking about?!
Damn!
And so…
He did it!
What are you doing, Inoue?
Huh? Oh…
Oh!
Nice work!
Cut the crap!
Don’t just leave your body
lying around like that.
Hurry up and get back in it!
I finally got out.
I have to go back in?
Now, don’t you ever come to
my school again without a good reason!
Why?
Got it?!
It’s still so hot…!
Ow! Brain freeze!
But it’s so refreshing…
But it’s painful…
You have to eat a little at a time.
Yeah. Tatsuki, is your injury
to your right hand all right now?
It was nothing.
Besides, the championships
are coming up next month.
I’m in tip-top shape.
You’re really something, Tatsuki…
Compared to you I’m…
Orihime…?
Oh! Mm… Here it comes again!
Did something happen?
At your relatives’ house…
I-I wasn’t much use at all.
To tell you the truth…
I thought I might be able
to be of some help.
But, I might have just been
in the way…
Orihime…
Oh, but that’s when
I heard your voice saying…
”Hang in there!”
That’s why I decided
to do all I could.
That’s good enough.
You went because
you wanted to, right?
It’s not for you to decide
if you were of help or not.
You came right back here.
Welcome home, Orihime.
Uh-huh…
I, Orihime Inoue…will do my best!
Are you all right?
A hundred times fine!
Kurosaki Clinic
I’m home!
Hi! You’re just in time for dinner.
You’re late.
Damn you…
Is this payback for this morning?
Dinner in this house is at 7:00.
Have you forgotten that?
Shut up!
Come on, you two!
Leave them alone.
That’s the only way
they can show affection.
How about seconds?
There’s no reason to hesitate,
just because you’re a freeloader.
Here, now, how about another serving,
Mr. Freeloader?
Uh… In that case…
You’re the first to get seconds…
Oh, please don’t hesitate,
Mr. Freeloader.
What is the matter?
Uh… In that case…
Well, even a freeloader would
like seconds! Eat up! Eat up!
Quit calling him freeloader, freeloader!
How can he ask for seconds?
Right, Mr. Freeloader?
I can’t ask for seconds…
Hey! Clean the front of
the shop tomorrow morning, will ya?
What?!
It’s only natural for a freeloader
to do that much.
You’re going to ask for seconds, right?
Come. How about it, Mr. Freeloader?
By all means…
Thank you for the food.
Jinta, you’re too mean…!
He’s more sensitive than he looks.
I must say…
Pitiful…
Forget that… Kisuke!
What is it?
I haven’t been back in
this town for a while,
but I sense something unnatural…
Do you have any idea
what’s going on?
Hmm… There is some disturbance
in Spiritual Pressure,
but it’s nothing to
get excited about.
Hmm…
After spending time there,
for the first time,
I think that I might be able to discover
the reason behind my strength.
I only went because I wanted
to be of some use to Ichigo.
I wanted to do what I could for him.
But, I couldn’t…
That’s why I don’t know
what I should do.
We can only struggle.
Huh?
We received all of our powers
through Ichigo.
So, if we’re going to stay with him…
In order to do that,
we have to enhance our powers!
Chad… Didn’t this cause
an uproar before?
Huh?
Hurry, Chad! Oh! I’m sorry!
Hurry! Hurry!
We’ve got to get out of here!
Those who have gone themselves
to Soul Society
and learned the reason behind it…
can no longer keep their eyes closed.
They can no longer keep
their ears covered.
But I…
Such an ominous moon…
Ohh…
What’s with that subdued reaction?!
You trying to make a fool of me?!
No…uh… What can I say?
You can’t get away with trying
to be obsequious!
This is what your sisters did to me!
I’ll take you to Ishida tomorrow!
Listen, you! I’ll bet
you’ve gotten lazy!
Damn you!
Don’t act like a big shot…
just because you got that
Substitute Soul Reaper Combat Pass
and can freely turn into
a Soul Reaper!
I’m not acting like a big shot!
What’s the matter with you…
complaining all the time?
How can I not complain?
Why didn’t you bring
Rukia back--?!
S-Stop it…my cotton’s gonna...
I went…
to stop Rukia’s execution.
I didn’t go to bring her back.
You don’t know anything
about what went on there.
Quit yapping about it!
Sure! I don’t know anything.
How could I?!
But you’re sadly mistaken if
you think can do everything by yourself!
What are you talking about?
Well, I’m doing the best I can too.
And yet…and yet… Rukia…
I want to see her! I want to see her!
I want to see her!
Shut up and go to sleep!
All right.
There! A bunny!
Huh?
Brother!
Orihime, you were waiting
for me again?
Welcome home!
I was making a bunny. See!
It looks just like one!
Come. Let’s go in.
You’ll catch cold.
Wait! This is big brother bunny.
I have to make an Orihime bunny!
I see.
Then let’s make it together.
Okay!
Brother…!
Brother…
Oh… Why…?
Yes…?
I’m home…
Brother…?
A Hollow…?
What in the--?
Hm… A job so late at night…?
Strange…
You seem to be well, Orihime.
I am…
Brother… Did you…?
Yeah…
I was able to go to Soul Society.
Don’t worry…
I won’t become a Hollow again.
I’m so glad! You got there safely?
Yes. You went too,
didn’t you, Orihime?
To Soul Society…
How did you know?
That much I know…
What is it, Brother?
I was thinking you haven’t changed
at all since you were little.
You were always worried about me.
Do you remember?
Making snow bunnies
with your frostbitten hands
while waiting for me?
Yes…
Hey, Ichigo! Wake up! Hey!
Hey!
You’re finally up…
You’ve let your guard down.
Shut up! What are you
doing here at this hour?
What could it be, but a job?
Come with me.
Huh? Why do I have to?!
Or is it that, just like Rukia,
you can’t handle things by yourself?
What’s that?!
Will you shut up?!
It’s the middle of the night!
Wh-What’s that?!
Huh?
After you had the nerve earlier,
to ignore my feelings for Rukia
and fall fast asleep…
One, two, three sheep
have jumped back
into the corral, damn you!
Hey, by any chance, is this…?
I don’t have any cavities…
Oh, so it is a Soul Candy…
You mean it’ll move even when
you place it into something like this?
Why are you so interested in that?
Well…when I got here,
I forgot all about it…
So that’s why you had so much trouble
getting out of your gigai?
So what’s this job you mentioned?
Oh… I got a strange message
on my Soul Pager.
Well, it’s not much Spiritual Pressure,
but can’t you feel it?
Oh! Inoue!
Yeah… It’s near Orihime Inoue.
You should have told me that earlier!
Let’s get going!
O-Okay!
Help…me…
Oh, no… I wasn’t worried.
When I was little,
I probably felt lonely inside
an empty home.
I remember being relieved
whenever you came home.
I feel the same.
When I was with you,
I felt relieved.
Really?
Orihime…
Yes?
Isn’t there something
that’s troubling you?
For you to dream about me…
What…? What is this I sense?
Inoue…?
How did you know about my dream?
I told you I know, didn’t I?
How about stepping out
for a breather?
There it is!
What?!
What in the world…is that?!
Now, let’s go.
Brother…
There’s nothing to worry about.
Come…
Is that supposed to be
the gates of Hell?!
Ichigo!
Ishida! Chad!
Inoue!
It disappeared…!
Inoue…!
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
I wonder where Inoue
disappeared to.
Say, why don’t we follow
her scent?
Yoruichi, can we ask you to do it?
Sure. Leave it to me.
You mean cats can do that?
If you’re me, it’s a piece of cake!
I knew you were capable of great things!
Just kidding.
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Golden!
Perfect!
Hey! What do you mean?!
Who told you to make me
look so fancy?!
I just did a little rearranging!
You went too far!
Just look at me!
You made my mane out of lace
so I look more like
a lace fairy than a lion!
This should make you happy.
You should’ve done this
to begin with!
Thanks!
The back of his head is
in Quincy style, but…
I won’t tell him that.
Tune in again!