This is way off the mark.
Did Mr. Urahara make a mistake
in his calculations?
I summoned you here.
Kageroza!
I tweaked the Precipice World a bit.
Why?
Why are you after Nozomi?!
What did you…
hide in Nozomi?!
My, my, so many questions.
Let me answer just the first one.
Why did I summon you here?
Very simple.
To erase your existence.
Erase my existence?
Why me?
Answer me!
What?!
You shouldn’t exist.
You’re not human.
You’re not a pure
Soul Reaper or Hollow.
You’re an anomaly.
I am unable to create a
Reigai of you from Reishi.
You are the unaccountable variable.
Quite frankly, you are
a thorn in my plans.
Goodbye…Ichigo Kurosaki.
What’s wrong?
Kurosaki’s Spiritual Pressure just…
completely disappeared.
-What?!
What do you mean, Mr. Urahara?!
Exactly what I said.
His Spiritual Pressure
suddenly vanished.
That can’t be!
Hado 4…
Byakurai.
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
- Scatter…
- Senbonzakura.
You’re not getting away!
Nigeki Kessatsu! Suzumebachi!
Very impressive, Captain Soi Fon.
Despite your slight build,
you took my attack head on.
However, you lack the destructive
force to defeat me
with a single attack.
As long as your attack
is Nigeki Kessatsu,
your target is a dead giveaway.
By reading the trajectory,
redirecting it, and striking first,
victory will be mine.
Will it go as planned?
Clones?!
If my destructive force is
insufficient, I’ll use numbers!
Tenken!
Too slow.
Not happening!
You’re not getting away!
Shunko!
Ryujinjakka!
Bushogoma.
Kyoraku!
Worry about yourself!
Very impressive, Old Man Yama.
You weren’t Head Captain
all these years for nothing.
Not even all those injuries
will make you go down.
But your Spiritual Pressure
is gradually weakening.
If your attacks had the power
they had at the beginning,
I wouldn’t be able to heal
these wounds so easily.
Definitely.
If we continue this strategy
of wearing you down,
the battle will eventually end.
Is that all you have to say?
Oh man…
Looks like he has no
intention of giving up.
We have no choice.
This doesn’t look good.
The captains who have entered
seem to be struggling.
Any sign of Ichigo?
I’m afraid not.
Then is Kurosaki…
The last reading I had on him
was in the Precipice World,
just as the Cleaner was approaching.
I can only surmise he was swallowed up.
By the Cleaner?
No way…
That can’t be.
Just a minute ago, he…
What’s the matter, Nozomi?
You seem very glum!
Not really.
Don’t worry.
Everyone will protect you!
Okay, I’m on my way!
It’s…my fault.
Nozomi…
No!
Ichigo…
So…
You’re still able to move?
If I can’t hit you with
Suzumebachi’s second sting,
then I’ll simply wear
down your strength until
you can no longer avoid it!
Don’t worry!
It’ll take more than
that to kill Ichigo!
Oh come on!
You can’t believe what I say?!
He’s right.
It would take more than
that to kill Kurosaki.
Yeah.
Besides, Ichigo chose to do this.
There is no need for you
to feel responsible.
Nozomi, what everyone says is true.
So don’t blame yourself.
Nozomi, that bastard Ichigo
always keeps his promises!
So trust him and wait.
W-What’re you looking
at me like that for?!
How…can you have so
much faith in him?
The two of you are always…
I-It’s not that I have
faith in him or anything!
We’re not even friends!
We’re simply servant and…
Okay.
But, the situation is definitely bad.
Maybe we should go to the
Soul Society as well.
Now you’re really
worrying for nothing.
Yeah.
Don’t underestimate the captains.
This is where it ends.
Tenken!
What?!
I let down my guard.
I didn’t think you had
that much strength left.
I will do whatever it
takes to defeat you
and go help Genryusai,
the man who taught me
how to fight as a Soul Reaper!
That isn’t going to happen.
What?
The Head Captain’s fate…
is about to be sealed.
Master Genryusai…
let’s put an end to this already.
It’s too bad, Old Man Yama.
You must’ve noticed it.
The Head Captain’s Spiritual Pressure
is growing weaker.
Not just the Head Captain…
Kenpachi Zaraki, Toshiro Hitsugaya
and Byakuya Kuchiki.
None of the originals
shall reach Kageroza.
You people underestimate that man.
What?!
For the past thousand years,
Genryusai has remained as the
most powerful Soul Reaper.
Oh, damn.
Taste my Ennetsu Jigoku
to your heart's content.
You no longer seem to have your speed.
You don’t appear able to move either.
True.
I don’t seem to have
much Spirit Energy left.
Captain Soi Fon, why do you fight?
Because this is my duty.
I see.
Just the kind of answer I’d expect
from you, Captain Soi Fon.
But that can’t be all.
What?!
Someone who becomes captain
cannot increase her powers
without bearing some burden.
There must be something.
A reason for you to fight.
It seems you do have something.
We are all fighting for that
which we cannot compromise.
Let’s settle this.
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
You no longer have any means
of avoiding my attacks.
I wouldn’t be so sure.
I also have my last resort.
I see.
But a contest of strength
is what I desire most!
Bankai! Jakuho Raikoben!
This goes against my pride, but…
Genryusai…I am on my-
Another large Spiritual
Pressure is gone.
Captain Zaraki, Captain Komamura,
and even Head Captain Yamamoto.
None of them were able to make it here.
The remaining Spiritual Pressures
will soon be gone as well.
You can’t fight any
further with those wounds.
You still won’t give up?
There is only one head
of the Kuchiki Clan.
There is no need for two.
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Bankai,
Are the captains that amazing?
Yes. But there is nothing
to be afraid of.
His noble presence…
And his wealth!
His unparalleled artistic sense…
-That’s who our Captain Kuchiki is!
I don’t get it.