I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
PROTECTION
Hey, Mr. Hollow...
Sorry, but Ichigo is out right now...
PROTECTION
Oh... sorry about that...
I still haven't introduced myself.
I'm Isshin...Kurosaki.
Remember this...
You can't tell how strong your opponent is
by the size of his zanpakuto...
Only then can you talk to me
about Soul Reapers, boy.
I-Impossible...
With just...o-one strike...
What's going on?
Were we saved?
It's all right.
This is crazy...
He's incredibly strong...
Is he really Ichigo's...
- ...stupid father?
- Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yahoo!
Did you get it?
Your revenge...
You came...
Urahara.
It's been a while, Mr. Isshin.
Well... It looks like your skills
haven't faded.
I'm relieved.
What's this? That's a pretty normal thing
for you to say.
Of course!
I would hate it if you blamed me
if your Spiritual Pressure
had withered away.
I see... Don't worry.
I wouldn't blame you if it had faded
along with my skills.
How is it, being a Soul Reaper
for the first time in 20 years?
Not bad.
Do you...feel better?
I never hated that Hollow
to begin with.
If there was something
I've hated for over 20 years...
It would be my weakness that night
when I couldn't save Masaki.
That part of you never changes...
You're just like your son.
I'm not like him!
You are!
I say I'm not!
Then I'll leave it at that.
Speaking of your son,
have you noticed?
Yeah.
As you've predicted...
they've made contact.
The Masked Army. The Visored.
The Visored?
What is that?
They called them
the Masked Army.
THE MASKED ARMY
VISORED
They're an outlaw group of
former Soul Reapers
who tried to gain Hollow powers
by using forbidden techniques.
Their whereabouts and
aims are unknown.
This is troublesome.
The only thing that I do know is that
the Visored and the Arrancar
are not teamed with each other.
But they're not our allies...
The Visored hate Soul Reapers
as well...
Yeah...
But they made contact
with your son.
That must mean...
Yeah... They're preparing for
some sort of battle.
Just like we are.
They have probably noticed
the sudden change in the Arrancar.
So that Hollow really had
its mask removed...
A broken mask...
An Arrancar.
BROKEN MASK
ARRANCAR
So now they're going to
read this as Arrancar?
Until now, we've detected
the naturally occurring Arrancar
from time to time...
But compared to the mock Arrancar
we've confirmed up until now,
this one's level of perfection was
like nothing we've ever seen before.
Mock Arrancar didn't change
for decades,
but they suddenly jumped a level.
It's all so sudden...
You understand what this means, right?
This means...
Sosuke Aizen...
He made contact with
the mock Arrancar
and is trying to create a true Arrancar...
...using the Hogyoku's power.
According to my calculations,
the Hogyoku was supposed to
take another year to mature.
Of course, that power isn't complete...
That Arrancar was still incomplete.
He has jumped a level,
but his Spiritual Pressure was impure.
He was probably a test subject
to gather information
on how well he could fight
at this level.
They're at this level now,
but the Hogyoku's power is immense.
Aizen will probably be
pushing his research
so that they can be used in battle.
He'll lead those completed "true" Arrancar
and a Menos army...
And come to crush the world.
What should we do?
Let's do what we can.
Whatever the case,
this is the situation.
Enemy or ally,
we're all going to make a move.
The Visored...
Us...and...
Soul Society...
Oh... Someone's coming
in this direction.
This Spiritual Pressure...
It's your son.
It'll be troublesome
to see him...
Come on, everyone.
Let's all go home.
- O-Okay.
I see...
All right. I'll be there immediately.
Tsk! What a pain...
Thank you all for coming at
such short notice!
We shall now commence
the Captains' meeting!
KARAKURA FIRST HIGH SCHOOL
What was that Spiritual Pressure?
There's no trace of anyone...
Damn! This is all because of Hirako...
I'm a Visored.
You're the same as me.
Come with us...Ichigo.
You shouldn't be on that side.
If you want me to restore your powers...
Swear to me that
you will not involve yourself
with Soul Reapers from now on.
Swear it.
Good morning, Kurosaki!
Good morning, Ichigo!
Hirako...he came to school
as if nothing happened.
Oh! Good morning!
Umm... Hirako?
Ah! You remembered my name!
Good morning, Orihime!
Hold on a second!
What is it? How noisy...
Who are you?
Who am I?!
What's with that,
"I've been here longer than you"
sort of attitude?!
I-I've been here way, way longer!
You've already been hurt...
Anyway, let her go!
Inoue doesn't like it!
Are you stupid?
If she didn't like it she would
have screamed or hit me.
She hasn't done anything.
That means that she doesn't mind.
Right, Orihime?
W-What's with that
arrogant attitude?!
You're the one who's doing
something bad!
I-Isn't that right?!
I'm not wrong...am I?!
It's all right. You're not wrong.
Leave him to me, Keigo.
Ch-Chizuru!
Orihime is a nice girl who
won't make a face
even if you do
something bad to her.
So an idiot like you clinging on
to her without realizing that
has no reason to live in this world!
Umm...It's a bit strange to be
saying this to an ally...
but by that logic,
you should be the first one to die.
Justice in my hands!
Death to swine! Special attack,
Chizuru Genocide!
You don't have to kill him...
Come here for a second, Hirako.
What?
What's wrong with Ichigo?
Snapping like that...
Since when was he
the hot-blooded type?
I-Ichigo?
Ow!
That hurts... What is it?
You don't need to get so mad...
It's not as if Orihime
is your girlfriend.
Of course, there's no way
that someone like you
could get anywhere with
a beauty like her.
That's not it!
Anyway, apologize to Inoue afterwards!
You should do that!
Like I just said, there's no reason
for you to tell me that.
Hirako...
Why are you still coming
to this school?!
Don't be unreasonable.
It's a student's duty to go to school.
Didn't you come to our school
to recruit me?!
In that case, you don't have
any business here anymore!
Why?
Did you really think that
I'd give up so easily?
I'm persistent...
I'll hang around you until you say yes.
It's too late...
Once you become a Visored,
you can't go back.
Whatever you may think,
you're already on our side, Ichigo.
Orihime...
The big guy...
Four-eyes...
You think of them all as your friends,
don't you?
They're not...
They're only your friends for now.
If you continue to be a Soul Reaper
as you have been, sooner or later...
Your inner Hollow'll swallow you up.
You'll lose your sanity...
It's over if that happens.
Your power will destroy everything.
Your friends...and your future...
Everything will get pulled in and crushed.
You've already realized that, haven't you?
Your inner Hollow has become so large
that you can't handle it anymore.
Come with me, Ichigo.
I'll teach you how to maintain
your sanity.
Ichigo!
Want to go into town on
the way home?
Sorry.
I want to go home by myself.
Ichigo?!
M-Mizuiro!
There's something wrong with Ichigo!
Really? He gets like that sometimes.
Well, that's true, but that's not it.
Ichigo is more...
It's difficult to put into words, but...umm...
You're just imagining it, Mr. Asano.
Woah! You're suddenly speaking
to me politely?!
Huh?! Is something wrong, Mr. Asano?!
Wh-Whoa. Again?!
Why is everyone distancing themselves
from me?!
I hate you all!
How tiring!
I shouldn't do things
I'm not used to doing...
What was that post-break test?
How stupid...
Besides, why do I have to go to
Ichigo's school to recruit him!
I still don't like that.
That hurts...
Hey! Who did that?
You...
H-Hiyori!
What's taking you so long,
you spineless worm?!
Sorry!
Where is Ichigo Kurosaki?!
Um... Not yet...
Not yet?! What's the meaning of this?!
Just talk to him and bring him to us!
I told him, but he wouldn't listen!
Then bring him to us by force!
What?! That's not what
you told me the last time!
I found you.
Orihime!
Shinji.
Why is someone following you, baldy?!
Even if we asked Kurosaki
he'd probably say that it was nothing.
So I came to ask you in person...
Hirako...
Who are you?
What do you want with Kurosaki?
Did you think that we'd tell you
if you just asked?
Hiyori Sarugaki!
Huh?
Not, "Huh". It's my name!
Tell me your names!
Orihime Inoue...
Yasutora Sado.
A "princess" and a "tiger", huh?
Those are pretty impressive names!
We're a "monkey" and "flat"!
Hey, I'm so jealous!
What's "flat"?
I'm the only one that's not a living thing.
Don't make such
forced comparisons, stupid.
And she's got big breasts
and smooth hair!
She's really annoying!
You're just jealous.
Plus you're only holding
those things against Orihime.
Fine.
Anyway, I have nothing to tell you.
You're going to die here.
I'm very sorry!
Wait...
Don't, Inoue!
Sado...
You know, right?
We can't catch up to them
with our power.
Besides, even if we could...
We would be killed...for sure.
Shinji, hey, let me go, baldy!
I want to slap them around!
You can't. Are you stupid?!
We're after Ichigo!
No need to cause trouble
with others just yet!
Shut up! Let me go!
Don't give me an enema.
I said... "Stop"!
Hey, baldy!
What are you going to do
if I can't get married?!
Shut up! It's punishment!
It's punishment
for a kid who won't listen!
What?!
I said, "stop"!
I hate humans...
I know.
I also hate Soul Reapers...
But I'm telling you to wait
a little longer, stupid.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
You've come.
Tell me your answer.
I want you to restore my powers...
my Quincy powers!
I don't want to borrow power...
I want my own power...
And?
I swear... That I will never again...
involve myself with Soul Reapers
and their associates.
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
This and this and this...
What are you doing, Rin?
Akon, I was asked by the Lieutenant
to prepare substitute soul candy.
Is someone going to
the World of the Living?
The people on this list.
It'll get pretty noisy there.
What? Are they that noisy?
ho's going?
Who's going? Who's going?
Well...
Yeah?!
- Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
- Mornings have sure been rough lately.
- Are you all right, Abarai?
- Good morning, Lieutenant Hisagi!
Hey! Good morning!
That was a squad member
from Squad 7, right?
Yeah... We became friends during
the Bount incident.
Oh yeah...
Iba is strangely conscious of you.
He said something like,
"Squad members don't respect me
as much as they used to."
He doesn't need to be worried
about that...
It's hard to believe that people
used to respect him.
That's a pretty cruel thing to say.
You spineless worm!