Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
So few people showed up.
Huh?
The squads with both the captain
and lieutenant in attendance are…
The Head Captain’s Squad 1
and our Squad 2…
Plus Kyoraku’s Squad 8.
Squad 5, 11 and 12 can’t be helped…
but what about the rest?
Even Unohana of Squad 4 is missing.
B-Brother…
Rukia Kuchiki…
Do you have any final words to say?
Yes…
Just one.
This is…!
Yeah… It seems like it’s begun.
It’s begun…!
Let’s hurry, Matsumoto!
Right!
This is bad, Kiyone!
Looks like the execution has begun!
Isn’t the Captain ready yet?!
Shut up! I hear you!
You don’t have to yell,
you stinky bearded monkey!
Captain!
– Captain!
– You’re yelling, too!
Captain, are you ready?!
Kuchiki’s execution has begun.
We must hurry!
Cap…tain?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Breaking the seal took a bit longer
than I thought.
But this should work.
Our appeal to Central 46
did not go through,
so this is the only recourse
we have left.
Let’s go!
We will destroy the Sokyoku!
Right!
What is that?
I wonder if the execution has started…
Huh?! Then we must hurry!
I’m going on ahead.
Huh?!
Why?
I don’t care about the execution,
but Ichy might be there.
And I have to help Ichy.
Thank you…
Huh? You’re so funny!
Why are you thanking me?
Helping Ichy is only natural!
After all, Ichy is Kenny’s friend.
Well, I’m off!
I’ll take care of the strong ones.
You take care of the small fry.
She’s so fast!
And so strange!
Thank you, Yachiru.
Very well.
As you wish,
I shall allow the Ryoka to return home
unharmed after the execution.
Thank you…
How cruel.
He has no intention of sparing them.
It is not cruelty, Isane.
It’s kindness.
Captain Unohana!
Where have you been?
If this is the unavoidable fate,
the least we can do is
ease her of any worries…
and give her some piece of mind.
Release the Sokyoku!
Look…
The Sokyoku has been released!
Ichimaru sent my heart
into turmoil earlier,
but now it’s slowly starting
to regain some peace.
Is it because of
the Head Captain’s promise?
Or could it be because
while my mind was in chaos trying
to think of a way to stay alive,
my brother acted so serenely,
not even turning to look my way?
Thank you, Brother.
Nanao…
Don’t look so pained.
You’ll make me sad, too.
I’m not pained…
Wh-What is that?!
This is the release of Sokyoku?
It's shape…!
Wow… I’m surprised…
Kiko-oh!
The spearhead of the Sokyoku
has taken on its true form
as the officiating executioner
to render the ultimate punishment!
Execution will be over when
the prisoner’s body is pierced by it.
I’m not afraid.
I’ve lived a good life.
I was blessed.
I met Renji and the others…
I was taken in by Brother…
Guided by Kaien.
And…
I was saved by Ichigo.
This is not suffering.
I am not sad.
I have no regrets.
My heart leaves nothing behind.
Thank you.
Farewell.
Hey.
I-Ichigo?!
You fool!
Why did you come again?!
Huh?
You should know by now!
You can’t defeat my brother!
You’ll be killed this time for sure!
I’m resigned to my fate!
I don’t need you to rescue me!
Go home!
This can’t be!
He stopped the Sokyoku with
only a single zanpakuto?
The Sokyoku that is said to have
the power of a million zanpakuto?
Just who is this guy?!
Nanao.
Do you think that’s the boy that
Ryoka was talking about?
Yes…His appearance matches
all the reports we’ve received.
I see…
So they’re the ones who
made it in time, I guess.
Ichigo!
Backing out to prepare for
a second attack, huh?
Fine, bring it on.
Stop, Ichigo! Enough already!
You won’t be able to stop
the Sokyoku a second time!
You’ll be torn to pieces!!
Ichigo!
C-Captain Ukitake?! And Kiyone?!
Hey there, Mr. Handsome.
You made us wait a while.
Captain Kyoraku!
Sorry, breaking the seal took a while.
However…
This ought to do it!
That’s the symbol of the Shihoin Clan.
Stop them!
Huh?
They intend to destroy
the Sokyoku!
Me?!
I don’t know what’s going on…
but in that case, I’ll just…!
What are you doing, Ichigo?!
Isn’t it obvious?
I’m just gonna break
this execution stand!
Don’t!
That’s crazy!
Listen! Listen to me, Ichigo!
The execution stand of Sokyoku is…!
Never mind.
Just shut up and watch!
Ichi…go…
"I don’t need you to rescue me,"
you said.
"Go home," you said.
You talk too much.
I told you that I’m rejecting
all your requests.
This is the second time.
This time for sure…
I’m here to rescue you, Rukia.
I’m not going to…
say thank you. You fool…
I know…
The Sokyoku’s execution stand…
He destroyed it!
W-What is he anyway?!
I-Ichigo…
Huh?
Let me ask you…
What’ll we do from now?
Is there a way to disappear…
with so many eyes watching us?
We’ll make a run for it.
Impossible! They’re captains!
We can’t get away from them!
Then we’ll beat them all
and get away.
You’re not the only one…
Inoue, Ishida, even Chad, are here.
Ganju and Hanataro, too.
I’m gonna rescue everyone
who helped out and get away.
From the look in his eyes…
from his words…
I can feel Ichigo’s strength
flowing into me.
You’ve become strong, haven’t you,
Ichigo…
Wh-What?!
So you’ve come, Renji!
Renji!
Rukia!
I’m so glad, you’re alive! Renji!
I figured you’d come.
Of course!
Who’d save Rukia if I didn’t come?
Heh.
Here.
H-Hey, Ichigo…?!
What’re you doing?!
W-Wait!
Hey, you’re not gonna…!
Catch!
You idiot!
You fool, Ichigo!
What if I dropped her, you idiot?!
Take her!
Wha--?
Don’t just stand there!
Take her already!
That’s your job!
Don’t let her go even if it kills you!
Renji!
A-Abarai…
Don’t just stand there, you fools!
After them! All lieutenants, go!
Yes, sir.
Go ahead.
Huh?!
You’re in the way!
Now run! Itegumo!
Bite! Gonryomaru!
Crush him! Gegetsuburi!
Impossible…!
He’s not even using his zanpakuto…
I told you,
I could see your moves…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Kurosaki! That…that appearance…
Not bad, huh?
Yoruichi let me borrow it.
I see. You finally understand
the necessity of a mantle.
Huh?
All right, I acknowledge you as
my Mantle Mate from now on.
I’m taking this thing off then!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
– Golden!
My name is
Zennosuke Kurumadani.
Due to the arrest and incarceration
of Rukia Kuchiki,
who was in charge
of this region,
I have been sent
as her replacement.
Huh?
A Hollow!
All right, let’s go!
Karakura Superheroes!
Karakura Red is on the way!
Hey kid!
Why am I doing this?!
Bohahahaha!
Wh-What was that just now?
Tune in again!