Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
So Aizen wasn’t enough for you…
You even had to hurt
Hinamori this bad…!
To make her grip her sword
so hard that her hands bled…!
Whatever are you talking about?
I told you…
If you ever made Hinamori bleed,
I’d kill you!
That will never do.
Draw your sword in a place like this…
and I’ll be forced to stop you.
C-Captain Ichimaru…!
Stay back, Izuru…
You don’t want to die yet,
do you?
Don’t be stupid.
It’s not enough just to stay back.
Get lost, Kira…!
Out of my sight…
and even farther.
If you’re within ten miles of me…
I can’t guarantee
I won’t kill you by mistake!
An opening.
As expected of Toshiro Hitsugaya,
Captain of Squad 10…
A child prodigy of the sort
that comes along
only once every few centuries.
How very dangerous…
You’re serious, aren’t you?
Incredible…!
What an amazing Spiritual Pressure.
At this rate…!
Here I come!
Well, Squad 10 Captain?
How do you like being cornered?
I see…
I shouldn’t have underestimated you…
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
Or I’ll end up
regretting it afterwards.
No, not so fast…
Because your true regret begins now…!
You pushed me to it.
Regret this in full!
Reign over the Frosted Sky!
Hyorinmaru!
A dragon of water and ice created
from overflowing Spiritual Pressure.
And…it can even control
the weather…!
This is the first time I'm seeing it.
The most powerful zanpaku-to
of ice and snow
wielded by Captain Hitsugaya…
Hyorinmaru!
So much water…! What speed!
I couldn’t dodge it…!
Captain!
It’s over! Ichimaru!
Pierce his flesh…Shinso!
You sure you wanna dodge this?
She’ll die…that girl.
Hinamori!
Matsumoto…!
Forgive me, sir.
I was returning to
my quarters as ordered,
but I sensed Hyorinmaru’s
Spiritual Pressure and came back.
Please sheathe your sword,
Captain Ichimaru.
If you do not…
I shall engage you from here.
Day is breaking…
Only two days left.
It’s true that Ichigo is improving
with startling speed.
Compared with that of
ordinary Soul Reapers,
his growth is hard to believe.
But that only concerns
his fighting skill.
His spiritual power
has not risen as high.
Okay! Warm-up exercises, finished!
Where’d Yoruichi go, though?
I wanna get started soon.
Can he achieve Bankai
in only two days
going like this?
Maybe I should extend
the deadline…?
According to the information
I gathered,
after Rukia had entered
the Seireitei,
her execution grace period was
cut five days short to 25 days.
So after Ichigo’s three days
of training,
the execution would’ve
been the following day.
We had no time to spare.
But for good or bad,
when we came here, we were chased
by a Cleaner in the Senkaimon,
and tore through
the Dangai Precipice World.
That shifted the time axis
in our favor
when we fell into Soul Society.
In other words, even after
our three days of training,
we’ll still have eight more days!
It’s possible to extend
the training!
But what do we do…?
Kisuke developed that
training program based on himself.
The only one ever to succeed
was Kisuke himself!
Yoruichi!
Moreover, the 3-day period
is what it took
for Kisuke to achieve Bankai.
And he determined that
a longer time period
would be dangerous.
Yoruichi…!
He said…
Don’t worry!
Mr. Kurosaki’s natural abilities
are greater than mine!
So I believed him and
began training Ichigo.
Hey! Yoruichi!
But there’s no guarantee that
Ichigo’s soul
can withstand
the longer training period.
HEY! Yoruichi!
Come on out, I said!
Hah?! Or are ya so scared
of me that you ran away?!
I’ll wait one more day…
And if there’s still no change
in his spiritual power,
I’ll just have to risk it…
What did you say?
Did you not hear?
Then I shall repeat the notice.
Your date of execution has been
changed once more, Ms. Rukia Kuchiki.
The execution will
take place tomorrow.
If you hadn’t come,
Hinamori would’ve been dead.
Thanks, Matsumoto.
No…
Wait, Ichimaru!
Instead of coming after me…
Look after the Lieutenant
of Squad 5.
He always disappears
without telling me where he’s going…
a bad habit.
That still hasn’t changed.
Gin… Where are you trying to go?
That letter of Aizen’s…
How much of it was forged?
Captain Aizen…!
The power of Sokyoku
that is going to be released
at Rukia Kuchiki’s execution…
The plot to use that power
to destroy Soul Society…
Was that line true?
If it is true…
If that’s what Ichimaru
is after… I’ll…
Hell Butterfly…?
Reporting to
the Captains and Lieutenants.
A change has been made
concerning the execution date
for prisoner Rukia Kuchiki.
The execution will take place
29 hours from now.
This ruling is final.
There will be no further changes.
That is all.
Captain!
The execution and
the release of Sokyoku’s power…
If that’s Ichimaru’s aim,
I can’t let this execution proceed.
Come with me, Matsumoto.
We’re stopping the execution.
To all Captains and Lieutenants,
reporting…
a final change in the execution date
of prisoner Rukia Kuchiki.
The execution will take
place 29 hours from now.
I repeat. There has been a final change
in the execution date
of prisoner Rukia Kuchiki.
The execution will take place
29 hours from now.
This ruling is final.
There will be no further changes.
There’s no mistake.
That’s his Spiritual Pressure…
He seems to be making
steady progress.
But what’s this sense of
unease that I’m feeling?
Something…
I sense something
ominous approaching.
I was wondering what
you were doing, holed up in here.
That’s your zanpaku-to’s true form?
Secretly training for Bankai?
That looks like fun…
Lemme train, too.
Renji!
“What’re you doing here?”
That’s the look you’re giving me.
Hell, no special reason.
We’re outta time.
So I just wanted someplace
where I could concentrate on training.
Out of…time?
Whaddya mean?
Well, okay. I guess I'll tell you…
They changed Rukia’s
time of execution.
What?!
The new time is noon tomorrow!
I hate to admit it but my powers now
ain’t good enough to save Rukia.
That’s why I came here.
Don’t worry. I ain’t gonna mess
with your training.
I’ve already mastered manifesting it.
Only a little more until Bankai.
I’m just gonna do my own thing.
T-Tomorrow…?
But…he’ll never reach
Bankai by then.
Are you just gonna quit,
Yoruichi?
Weren’t you the one
who started me on this training?
Then don’t be the first one
to give up!
But Ichigo, if you can’t reach
Bankai by tomorrow…
I told you…! Don’t talk about “can’t.”
If tomorrow’s the deadline…
We’ll just finish it today!
His Spiritual Pressure…!
This guy…!
So tomorrow is the execution…
I know… Before the execution, I’ll ask
that Ichigo and the others
be allowed to return
to the World of the Living.
I belong to the Kuchiki clan, after all.
They might allow it.
The execution is tomorrow…
When I heard that,
I was surprised,
but strangely enough I wasn’t sad.
It must be because of
the dream I had last night.
That dream about the night
I’ll never forget.
Sir Kaien…!
Sir Kaien!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Sir Kaien…
Nothing of me…is worth saving…