I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
This is…  Her Spiritual Pressure is
going out of control?!
Rantao! Hang on!
I can use this artifact
to remove the spirit energy
that's going out of control inside you!
I've reached my limit.
It's not safe here!
Let's go somewhere safe!
Do you think you can get away?!
You managed to escape death,
but this is it.
Die!
Looks like you’re in a bind.
Kurosaki!
Brat!
Ishida, are you all right?
You don't need to worry about me…
What about you, Rantao?
I'm all right…
Ishida, take Rantao and
get away from here…
Sorry, but I'm going to
take on Kariya!
It seems like that's our only choice…
Yeah…
Bankai!!
Here I go!
Stop!
Getsugatensho!
Are you all right?
Thank you…
Ishida!
Inoue…
Thank goodness…
You're safe…
Huh? What happened
to your artifact?
It broke…
It broke?
Wasn't it supposed to explode
if it broke?
Yeah… As I reached my limit,
I realized how to use the artifact
for just amplifying reishi…
That way, it wouldn't explode
when I surpassed my limit
because it was already empty.
I see…
Did you understand that?
Not at all!
It doesn't matter as long as he's safe!
But listen!
Stop going off on your own!
Everyone was worried about you!
Okay…sorry…
Are they there?!
Yeah, they're all right!
Where's Ichigo Kurosaki?
He's fighting Kariya.
Captain!
Yeah. I know.
We can't let Ichigo Kurosaki handle
this burden on his own.
We're going, too.
Wait!
Who are you?
Oh… This is Rantao…
Rantao?! The exiled engineer, huh?
She created the Bounts?
You're a Thirteen Court Guard
Squads Captain, aren't you?
Yeah…
I want you to do something for me…
At this rate, Seireitei will be finished!
Huh?
What do you mean?
You know that Kariya has
absorbed the Jokai Crest
into his body, don't you?
Yeah…
We've already researched that.
The Jokai Crest is definitely powerful…
But he'll need time in order to
use its full power.
In other words, he's probably
buying himself time right now…
Yes… But the Jokai Crest power
that's in Kariya isn't a big deal.
There's a different power
we need to worry about…
A different power?
“Jokai Crest” is the general term
for giant reishi-generating devices
we used to use.
There were probably, at least,
several dozen within Seireitei.
One day, a Jokai Crest went out
of control during an experiment…
When it exploded, it annihilated about
a tenth of Seireitei…
The leaders at the time took this
very seriously and sealed away
all of the Jokai Crests that
were in Seireitei.
What?! There's more than one?!
If Kariya blows up the Jokai Crest
that he's absorbed into his body…
It would probably set off
all the other Jokai Crests…
That is Kariya's true goal.
If all of the Jokai Crests explode,
their destructive force would
be unfathomable…
Why are such things in Seireitei?!
Because they're dangerous,
and dangerous things need
to be kept in sight!
I see…
“People often know little of…”
"what's happening in
their own backyards,” right?!
Not quite…
What should we do?
We just have to seal each
Jokai Crest with kido once more.
Many years have passed,
and their current seals have weakened.
They'll react to Kariya's explosion.
Captain!
All right… We'll arrange to have them
re-sealed immediately.
Do you know where
the Jokai Crests are?
Here is…
Rantao!
I'm all right…
I told you before, didn't I?
I'm fighting with my Spiritual Pressure
sealed away.
I'm overextending myself…
I've just reached the limit to
which I can be active…
Sorry, but I leave the rest to you…
Matsumoto, let's go!
Yes!
What will you be doing?
We…
We're going after Kurosaki!
Kurosaki is fighting.
We can't just run away.
Besides, I've got to heal
Kurosaki's wounds!
Inoue…
Ishida, let me carry Rantao.
Let's go once we've taken Rantao
somewhere she can rest.
Thank you, Sado.
All right, now that it's decided,
let's go!
We're finally drawing towards
the conclusion!
Let's see this to the end.
Everyone…
All right! Let's go after Kurosaki!
I commend you for keeping up
with me this far…
I told you…
I'm going to settle this!
Do you know what kind
of place this is?
Yeah. I know.
Far better than you…
This place is perfect
for settling this.
Yeah…
Flash and Burst!
Nijigasumi!
You're…
SEIREITEI LIBRARY
What?!
Rantao gave us this.
It's a copy of a map that shows
where the Jokai Crest seals are.
My, my… After all that’s happened,
who would have thought that
there was still such a thing left?
It seems that we stayed up
all night for nothing…
Captain! Now's not the time
to be saying that!
Have you told
the General Captain?
I've sent Matsumoto to see him.
We should get some orders soon…
Whatever the case,
to seal this many Jokai Crests,
we need to mobilize all of
our remaining captains,
lieutenants,
and high-ranking officers…
What'll we do about Kariya?
Ichigo Kurosaki's gone after him.
Captains, lieutenants,
and squad members of all ranks
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
this is an urgent report!
The ryoka are after an ancient item
known as a Jokai Crest.
We've confirmed
the existence of several.
The Jokai Crests need to be
sealed away immediately.
Issuing a level one
precautionary warning!
Everyone is to head to
a Jokai Crest seal!
We shall use hell butterflies
to lead you there.
You too, Lieutenant Matsumoto.
Go to a Jokai Crest seal.
Yes!
Given the nature of the circumstances…
I shall directly lead everything.
Captain Komamura, assist me.
Understood.
Excuse me.
It seems like the fight
on Sokyoku Hill has begun.
Yeah!
All of the Soul Reapers in Seireitei
have been mobilized…
It seems that Ichigo Kurosaki
is the one fighting the ryoka…
We should start
preparing to evacuate.
Let's ask Lord Byakuya
for instructions.
Yes…
Ichigo…
You're still alive?!
Master Kariya…
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
Where are Koga and the others?
They died.
Died?
Yeah… They all died.
Is that so…?
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop!
I said, “Stop!”
I can't do that!
What are you doing?
You're all worn out…
What are you doing, Ichinose?
If you…
If you told me
to destroy Seireitei,
I would have no choice
but to do so…
I have abandoned this place…
My heart would not hurt
if it disappeared.
That's what I thought…
I saw my respected captain in you…
That's why I served by your side.
But…
We've come to serve justice.
Why do you stand before us?!
How stupid!
Is that really your goal?
Relying on people and loyalty
are different things.
Don't talk as if you understand!
Come on!
Kenpachi Zaraki!!
During my battle with Zaraki,
I remembered something
I had forgotten…
I wanted to turn the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads…
Seireitei into something even
slightly better than what it is…
That was my wish…
My captain and I wanted
the same world…
That's why I worked my hardest
by my captain's side.
My ideal will not change
even if he is gone.
But the emptiness of
my captain's death
changed my desires into revenge.
Master Kariya…
You've gained the power
to change Soul Society.
I shall kneel before you once more
if you will use your power
to rebuild Seireitei…
But…
If…If you will only use it for revenge…
I will stop you!
Nothing can be born of revenge.
Now that Koga and
the other Bounts are dead,
the only one who can stop you
is me!
Master Kariya…
Ichinose…
I can't do that.
You're not getting away!
You can't stop me with your power.
Thanks for all your help…
Thanks to you,
you've allowed me time for
the Jokai Crest's power
to spread through my body…
Kari…ya!
Kariya!
You bastard…
Do you know what you just did?
What are you trying to say?
You killed your comrade!
He served by your side…
What about it?
“What about it”?!
He was your enemy…
Why do you pity him?
I don't pity him!
But I'm saying that
I can't forgive you
for killing your comrade
so coldly.
I never thought of them
as comrades.
They were pawns I used
to achieve my goal.
You bastard!
I'm going to settle this
with you now.
Zeige Dih, Messer!
Wh-What's this?!
What is that?
What fierce wind!
And I can sense Kariya's
Spiritual Pressure rising rapidly!
Let's hurry!
I didn't think there was
a need to show you my doll…
But it seems I'm almost out of time.
This is my doll, Messer!
You can't come near me anymore!
You've sure got confidence.
What are you doing?
Renji…
Why are you here?
I couldn't find my captain,
so I came for him directly.
Anyway, you…
Renji…
I want you to do something for me.
What is it?
Take me to the Sokyoku…
You…
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Soon.
Soon I'll be filled with
the Jokai Crest's power
and I will wipe Seireitei
from this world.
There's nothing anyone can
do to stop me anymore!
Kariya… I'll stop you!
I won't let you destroy this world!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!!
– Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Here?
Yeah. Kurosaki and the others
should be resting here.
Everyone sure has it hard…
All right, I'll use
my soothing powers…
I have a message.
– The Substitute Soul Reaper has…
– No…
– …begun fighting the Bount.
– You can't…
– Return to your command posts.
– All right.
– You can't touch that…
Stop…
Hey, everyone!
SILENCE…
Again?!
R-Regretful…