One by one, Ichigo and his friends
fall before the powerful Espada.
Then captains of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads,
under orders from Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto,
appear before them.
After arriving in Hueco Mundo,
each captain begins
to battle the Espada.
Byakuya Kuchiki takes on
Espada Number 7, Zommari Rureaux,
who tries to use Rukia,
who has been knocked unconscious
by Aaroniero, to deliver a blow.
I’ll kill you…
simply…
because you
pointed your sword
at my pride.
Lord Aizen!
Banzai!
Meanwhile,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi fights
a difficult battle
against Szayelaporro,
who uses a doll with which
he can control the five senses.
It’s over.
No way.
This is so easy, that it’s boring!
I thought there would be
more to it than this!
Yeah right.
What?!
Mayuri had observed
Szayeaporro’s strategy,
and as a defensive measure
against the doll,
he had made replicas
of his internal organs.
Furious,
Szayelaporro switches tactics
and uses his long tentacles
to grab Nemu as a hostage.
My goodness…
Everyone keeps chattering.
It’s so noisy!
Bankai.
Tear him up…
Konjiki Ashisogijizo!
This gas…
Is it some kind of bacteria?!
Damn!
Thank goodness!
You’re conscious!
Lieutenant Kotetsu?
Hanataro?
Why are you here?
Oh, your treatment
isn’t completed yet!
Please lie still.
She’s right.
You can’t get up yet.
Brother…Byakuya!
Silence.
Didn’t you hear
Lieutenant Kotetsu’s instructions?
Lie still until they’re done.
Brother… Your overcoat.
It doesn’t matter.
You’re wounded!
I said don’t bother.
Right now, rest and wait until
you are healed completely.
In order to be prepared for
the real battle that
lies ahead of us.
Not bad.
For a Soul Reaper.
I don’t like it.
You still have room for talk?
I said to get serious and attack!
Most would avoid
being cut by this.
Then it wouldn’t be fun.
Besides, I said to get serious!
What kind of cut is this?!
Keep talking!
That was good.
That attack wasn’t bad at all.
So you’re not just about
brute strength.
That’s got nothing to do with it.
The sand interfered with
my swordsmanship, that’s all.
Is that so?!
Kurosaki!
Inoue…help…
Right! Hang on, I’ll…
Not me.
First…
Please heal Nel.
All right!
I’ll heal her right away!
I can hear…
I can hear it.
It’s still continuing.
The battle of the ruffians.
Can you see that, Abarai?
I-I don’t want to see it at all,
but I’m seeing it.
It ate him!
I can see that.
Quit describing something so sick!
What?! You asked me if I saw that!
I was just responding to you!
But you don’t have to
describe it to me!
Abarai! The poison has
infected you too!
What?
W-Why are you okay?
That poison has already
infected me once.
I’ve probably developed antibodies.
Not fair! How can that be?!
Why only me?!
What’s not fair?!
I almost died once!
Well, whatever…
Hurry with the antidote!
Hey Mayuri Kurotsuchi!
Ishida!
How can you be so carefree?
It’s common sense to change
the mixture of a poison
after every use.
W-Why you…
Don’t strain yourself.
It’ll make the poison
spread faster.
Developed antibodies?
Not allowing that to happen
is what makes one skilled.
Never mind that!
Just give us the antidote!
Otherwise…
Didn’t I tell you to calm down?
Umm…Master Mayuri…
I’m sorry.
May I ask you to
help me untie this?
Hey!
You heard her, right?
Why don’t you help her out?!
You’re so irritating.
Here’s the antidote.
Hey! Don’t throw it!
Hey!
The bottle cracked!
What’s happening?
Something’s odd.
Hey! Mayuri Kurotsuchi!
Hurry up and untie her!
W-What is that?
Did you think you killed me?
That voice…
Szayelaporro!
I shall tell you?
The ultimate, the most exalted
power of my La Lujuriosa
is known as “Gabriel.”
It is the power to regenerate
by using the enemy itself.
The power to infiltrate
my foe’s body
and absorb Reishi from within.
Well, it’s probably more correct
to say replace.
In order to regenerate,
the cells are reconstructed.
This reconstruction requires
all the Reishi inside
the enemy’s body to be overtaken
so the target is killed off…
to bring forth the rebirth.
Now then…
Let’s start over with
the self-introduction…
Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
That monster!
Did you understand this,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi?
This is how I continue to be
reborn into a new existence.
The phoenix is said to be immortal.
When it grows old,
it hurls itself into flames,
and from the flames
it is reborn as a new life.
Understand?
This is what immortality
and perfection means!
It’s not about transcending death.
It’s about incorporating death
into the cycle of life.
One whose existence
is not interrupted
by something such as death.
One such as myself,
who repeats the continuous cycle
of death and rebirth!
That is what you would
call a perfect being!
The demise known
as death does not exist for me.
Even if you kill me,
I will rise again before
a definitive death.
Understand this.
I cannot be killed.
You cannot defeat me.
Not in an eternity.
Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
Captain Kurotsuchi?
M-Master Ma…yu…ri…
I’m very sorry.
What’s the matter?
Are you in a daze from seeing
your dear second-in-command
about to die?
You’re quite sensitive,
aren’t you?
Give it up.
She doesn’t have long.
Let’s see.
If I were to categorize it,
she’s like the leftover cocoon
after the butterfly flies off.
How interesting.
How nice.
Such an amusing power.
It arouses my curiosity.
And?
Is that all?
What?
It’s not, is it?
You went on saying
the “perfect being.”
There must be another power
you’re hiding, isn’t there?
What the hell kind of guy is he?
Don’t look so serious.
What’s wrong with telling me?
It won’t diminish you.
Don’t be stingy, show me.
See?
Do you think that anyone who
eats me will stay normal?
If I’m eaten,
my innards will dissolve to
infiltrate the target’s nerves!
I don’t know how your Zanpakuto
is constructed,
but if I take over the nucleus
of its driving force,
construction doesn't matter!
Even this thing called Bankai
becomes subject to my will!
Curse yourself!
Because your Bankai took
the shape of a living creature!
Wha—?!
My, my…
Did you think all would be well
if the tool defied its master?
I modified it to self-destruct
in the likely case of it
turning against me.
It seems…
you have no other hidden power.
Well then,
you can be my test subject
for a new drug I’ve developed.
You don’t have to be on guard.
W-What’s he doing?
I dunno.
That drug has been
administered already.
His speech just now…
There are several drugs already
placed inside Nemu’s body.
If Nemu is devoured,
or if her body is infiltrated
they are released to her foe.
What?! What drug is it?!
The place where you passed through
had this hidden inside.
Relax. It’s not a poison.
Let’s see…
You can call it
a “Superhuman Potion.”
Superhuman Potion?
In a battle between two masters,
the swords seem to come to a halt.
You’re familiar with that,
aren’t you?
It’s a prolonging of
your sense of time.
When your senses are
stretched to the limit,
such phenomena occur.
This drug maximizes that condition.
In other words,
it’s a drug that allows any person
to easily experience
that superhuman sensation.
What is this?
He’s speaking so slowly…
that I can’t understand.
Can you understand me, Espada?
With this drug, even to a child,
a bullet looks like it has stopped.
To a superhuman like you,
the actions of
an average man like me
must be so slow and boring.
Now then…
Does this sword look like it
has stopped?
This is the amazing thing
about this drug.
A master’s senses are sharpened
only at the instantaneous moment
when both swords cross
with one another.
But this Superhuman Potion
can enhance
that sensitivity by several times…
no, several thousand,
several trillion times.
The usual dosage of this drug is
one drop diluted 250,000 times.
But I made it special for you.
It’s pure and undiluted.
Right now, one second seems
like a hundred years to you.
In other words, as this sword
gets closer to you,
with your superhuman sensitivity,
the movement looks very slow,
like it’s going to take
several hundred years.
How wonderful.
And while your senses are
heightened to superhuman levels,
your non-superhuman body
falls heavily behind.
In other words, the body cannot
keep up with the movements
caught by the exponentially
sharpened senses.
Even if you try to stop it
with your hands,
it will take several
hundred years before
you can feel this blade pierce
through your hand.
I’m talking like this,
but who knows when
my words will reach you.
But, no need to panic.
Take your time to thoroughly
enjoy the sensation
of your heart being pierced
by my blade
until your dripping fluids
turn into sand.
And so, I bid you adieu
until a hundred years from now.
How did you infiltrate
into the body?
Through the pores.
This woman’s pores
are quite enlarged.
She really needs to take
better care of her skin.
Nemu, didn’t I tell you to use
the same cosmetics as me?
I’ll sew up every one
of your pores!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
And with that,
the budget meeting for the fiscal year is closed.
TEA CEREMONY CLUB | FLOWER-ARRANGEMENT CLUB
| CALLIGRAPHY CLUB | MEN’S SOUL REAPER ASSOCATION
Whew…
One moment.
C-Captain Kurotsuchi!
I’m beginning new experiments
on Reishi.
But it’s a bit…underfunded.
Telling that to me is…
– I understand.
– Huh?!
All those who approve of transferring the money
Budget Breakdown: Women's Soul Reaper Assn. 250,000
Men's Soul Reaper Assn.
Tea Ceremony Club 150,000
Flower-Arrangement Club 150,000
Calligraphy Club 150,000
originally allotted to the Men’s Soul Reaper Association…
What?!