Deep in Las Noches,
inside Szayelaporro's palace,
Ishida and Renji battle against clones
of themselves created by Szayelaporro.
Look what you did to my palace.
How will I explain this
to Lord Aizen?
I'm very displeased.
Ishida!
Delicious.
Upset by Ishida and
Renji's resistance,
Szayelaporro uses the power
of his La Lujuriosa to create a doll
with which he controls Ishida's five senses.
This doll has toy-like body parts.
Inflicting damage on the body parts
causes damage to Ishida as well.
It is a deadly and ruthless power.
Szayelaporro toys with Ishida
and wounds him.
Furthermore, a doll linked
to Renji is also created.
Why you…
Don't make a fuss.
Just because I crushed
this petty thing.
My, my…
Just like kids…
Humans and Soul Reapers.
And Quincies too. All of you.
You're all so vulgar.
Meanwhile, Ichigo has emerged
victorious from a fight
to the death with Grimmjow,
and he rescues Orihime.
Now before him, a battle between
Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora, and Nelliel loomed.
Why did you stop your sword?
You did too.
You're so irritating.
I remember the old days
when I'm fighting you.
You haven't changed at all.
Not a bit since back then.
There.
I somehow managed
to get out.
Pesche! Are you all right?
I'll save you in a minute!
Thanks, Dondochakka!
This is so heavy.
I need to take a break.
Hey! Don't stop to rest!
I can almost see outside!
Even if we can see outside,
the only thing in sight is Renji and
the others beaten up by Szayelaporro.
That's right.
I was thinking back then…you know…
Hey, I can see outside!
When Szayelaporro does his sword release,
it sorta looks like udon noodles.
Now that you mention it…
Maybe we should nickname
Szayelaporro's attack
"Szayelaporro Udonz."
No, I don't think so.
Oh, is that so? Then why'd you
bring it up in the first place!
You're the one who said
it looked like udon noodles!
Quit babbling nonsense
and get me out.
Pesche, you're the one
who's babbling.
I'm out.
Oh no! We can't waste time here!
Master Nel…
Nel…
W-Wait, Kurosaki! You're not…
Nel is in a bind.
I have to help her.
Kurosa—
Don't move.
I won't let you get in
Master Nnoitora's way.
That woman…
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck is a rock.
A rock that resists Master Nnoitora's
blade must be destroyed.
By Master Nnoitora himself.
There, we're done.
I'm glad we ended it in time for lunch.
If I'm late, those two will be worried.
Hold it!
I said this was to the finish.
Stay until we're done.
By that, you mean until death?
Do you even need to ask?
I refuse.
Don't talk like you're worth it.
What?!
We all transformed from humans
to Hollows, becoming beasts.
And as Arrancar,
we regained our reason.
Those who possess reason need
to have a purpose to fight.
You don't have that.
There's no reason for me
to fight you.
I have no obligation to kill you.
Sure, there's a reason!
I don't like you!
That's not a reason.
That's instinct.
You are a beast.
I don't acknowledge you
as a warrior.
You are not worthy of
being my opponent.
I don't intend to be responsible
for a life that doesn't belong to a warrior.
Damn you!
Nnoitora…
Are you all right?
Can you stand?
Don't get too friendly with me.
Just because I can't beat her,
don't think you're my equal, Tesla.
Why Master Nelliel?
Why not some other Espada?
I don't like it!
I can't stand a female being superior
to a male in the battlefield.
That's all.
Do you remember?
You called me a beast.
Said I'm not a worthy opponent.
Well? How does it feel to be
beaten by that very beast?!
Pesche! Dondochakka!
Where are you?
It's time for dinner.
Pesche! Dondochakka!
Where are you?
Where are you hiding?
Huh?
Pesche… Dondochakka!
Where could those two
have gone?
I'm hungry.
Hey.
Not you again.
Are you looking for something?
It's none of your business.
Walking around with your weapon
is very threatening.
If you want to look strong,
you should put it away and walk.
Pesche… Dondochakka…
I-I'm so sorry…
Master Nel.
You tore off their masks forcefully.
How could you?!
So what of it?
They were weak. That's all it is.
Well?
I gave you a reason to
fight me, didn't I?
No…
This is not a reason to fight.
What?
But you injured my dear friends.
And you're going to pay for that!
Damn it!
I can't stand this.
You're slow!
You'd probably say only
beasts act like this.
As if I care.
Fighting is simply about
winning or losing.
Reasons, or whatever,
don't mean crap.
Reason isn't a part of fighting
to begin with.
You looked for a reason and lost.
It makes me sick.
Want something?
Your job is supposed to be over.
Szayelaporro.
Such cold words.
Weren't we comrades who joined
forces for our mutual goals?
Let me witness the end at least.
I don't recall joining forces
with you.
I took advantage of you, that's all.
You would fight Nelliel.
And I would inspect
my new device.
That is why I choose to
join your fight.
Cooperation is forged out
of common interest.
Because it's advantageous,
that's all.
So philosophical.
Makes me want to puke.
Nelliel…
It's not power that divides us.
It's experience.
Before you heal that wound
and return to Las Noches,
I will surpass you.
To a higher place where
your sword cannot reach me.
Let's go.
Don't order me around.
Even though you're not
an Espada?
Oh…
You found an opening
in your fight against Nelliel
thanks to the device
that I developed.
I don't think you should speak
to me like that.
Isn't that a fact? That's what I mean
by common interest.
That Spiritual Pressure…
She turned into a kid?!
How exciting. I've never seen
such a phenomenon.
Spiritual Pressure flowed out from
the wound where the mask was cracked.
And the soul itself shrank.
Or…
Who cares about your theories?!
Look at you now, Nelliel!
That body suits you perfectly!
Looks like we won't have
to cross swords.
That's my only regret.
What is this place?
Who are you?
Wha—?
Has she lost her memory?
Head…hurts.
P-Peshce!
Be quiet, Dondochakka.
There's only one path
we can take.
Master Nel…
Master Nelliel Tu Odelshcwanck
has died.
Her mask was split open,
her power lost as well
as her memory.
That is not Master Nel
before us.
So…
We must protect her.
From Nnoitora and Szayelaporro,
from suffering and hardship.
From all dangers and disasters.
We must take Master Nel,
who has grown so weak,
and protect her with our lives!
As one who has sworn to serve
Master Nel as our master…
That is our one remaining,
and final duty.
What a persistent fellow you are.
I've brought you down
countless times.
Why can't you just lose
consciousness?
I said you're too persistent.
I just broke your left Achilles' tendon.
Now, what shall I break next?
If I play with too many organs,
your life will be at risk.
Damn you!
Now, now, don't move.
Do not move.
Didn't I tell you earlier?
I don't want to hurt you
too much.
So just be good.
What's the meaning of this?
Okay, I got it!
Now, Dondochakka!
Release Bawabawa!
I gotcha!
What? How come that's coming out
of Dondochakka's mouth?
Bawabawa is one of
the Combat Spirit Bugs
that Dondochakka houses
inside his body.
But we haven't told
Master Nel about it.
We feared that information about us
would trigger Master Nel's memory to return!
Master Nel did not like to fight.
She was finally released from
the endless cycle of fighting.
We didn't want Master Nel to
regain her memories of fighting.
We wanted to protect her in peace.
That was our duty.
However…
Master Nel has the will to
fight right now!
If Master Nel says she will fight,
it is our duty to assist!
We cannot be bothered
by the likes of you.
Szayelaporro!
Here we come!
Will you still resist?
You sure don't know when
to give up, do you?
How unfortunate.
I thought it would be rough,
so I really didn't want to use it
so soon after I returned to this form.
Praise…
Dondochakka, we did it!
Did what?
Not showing your face
on screen signifies
you're a handsome man
of mystery and strength!
I'm sure we've caught
the hearts of the ladies!
I only appeared in shadows,
does that mean
I'm not handsome?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Pardon me. I have some documents.
What are you doing?
Be quiet.
Our captain is taking a nap.
Huh?! At this hour?!
He seems to be testing the theory that
"children who sleep grow tall."
ISANE KOTETSU 187 CM AND GROWING
I won't sleep starting today.