Give that back, you fools!
Do you really think I'll teach you
with such half-hearted resolve?!
If you don't want to teach me,
then I'll just have to
force it out of you!
Finally,
I can ask you directly.
Why did you decide to
work under Aizen?
Are you seriously
asking me that?
Man, why did you have
to come here, anyway?
You know, Rangiku...
You're a nuisance.
What?!
His sword... Something's different.
Then let me test you!
Test what?!
Not yet?
Ichigo!
What's this? Captain Aizen...
It looks like he's still letting
those kids run free.
Boy, he sure is one mean fellow.
Mizuiro! Honsho!
Huh? What? You
two are awake?
He says his cell phone
ran out of power.
Sorry. But I'm good now.
I borrowed a charger from
the convenience store.
Borrowed?
You mean...
Don't get technical.
It was an emergency, and the
clerk wouldn't wake up.
Well, yeah, I understand, but...
I got us some food to
tide us over as well.
See?
Hey!
There's beef jerky too.
If you want something
salty, eat that.
It gives me a pretty good idea
of what your usual diet is like.
You do look like the type who
only eats stuff like this.
Huh?
Ever since middle school,
all I've eaten was home-cooked meals.
What? But I thought
your family...
No! Not my parent's cooking.
There are plenty of girls out there
who are good at cooking.
You just need to look for them.
That's right. You are that kind
of person aren't you?
I know! Isn't it annoying when
he reminds you about it?
Makes you wish you hadn't come
looking for him, right?!
You do, right?! Right?! Right?! Right?!
- No, I don't!
- Stop touching me!
So, have you heard
the situation?
I got the gist from Keigo.
What's most important is that some
dangerous guy is coming for our lives.
So, I got these.
A stun gun for each of us.
Where'd you get those?
They're no good.
It won't work against him.
He can immobilize us
just by approaching.
He even turned Kanonji's stick into ash
just by coming in contact with it.
Not a stick! Say "cane"!
That powerful, huh?
He's definitely not human.
Let's leave these here then.
What's the matter, Chizuru?
You look like you're in a daze.
O-Of course I'm in a daze!
I'm completely numb!
I can't tell what's going on here!
How can you guys adapt
to all of this so quickly?!
You're hiding something I
don't know, aren't you?!
Explain!
Well...
He's here!
W-What?!
What's coming?
I don't know enough to
explain it to you, okay?!
This is no time to be arguing!
Let's go, boys and girls!
Come on! Stand up, Kojima!
We have to get away!
G-Give me a good explanation
later, okay?
Even if you don't understand
it yourself!
H-Hurry!
We'll use the alleyways!
We'll go behind the buildings
and get to the outskirts of
town without being seen!
What?
Is that who you meant?!
Are you thinking,
"How'd he find us?"
You're mistaken.
I simply stopped pretending
to be looking for you.
Wow.
It really does turn to ash.
What?!
What are you doing, boy?!
You mustn't throw things
like that at people!
Then how about this instead?
Come on! Everybody run!
No!
Is this boy crazy or something?!
Will you shut up?!
Not to sound like Kanonji,
but you sure do some crazy stuff.
It didn't work, after all!
Damn it!
Keigo!
This sword belonged to a guy
who dressed just like Ichigo!
It just might get through
to that guy!
Idiot!
Even if the sword gets
through, you'll die!
Asano!
Boy...
I can't let you take such
a risk by yourself.
Kanonji...
Let's go, boy.
Give that back, you fools!
Ouch! Ouch! My arm! My arm!
A new face?! Are you an enemy?
Mr. Afro!
Mr. Afro?
What sort of silly name is that?!
This is no time for such jokes!
Look who's talking about
having a silly name!
And quit being so loud!
Now's not the time!
A-Are you all right, Mr. Afro?!
Don't overdo it! You're shaking!
Quiet! I'm not shaking!
I can't let amateurs use
my Zanpakuto!
Good morning,
Tsuchinamazu!
Wow...
Okay! Now run!
Huh?
What?
I have returned,
Captain Aizen.
What's going on?!
Do you think that guy is here
to save us, or something?
No matter how you look at it,
it doesn't seem that way.
I'm afraid it's the exact opposite.
This is really bad.
You're back.
What about the woman?
I killed her.
Indeed.
Her Spiritual Pressure
has disappeared.
I'm surprised.
I thought you had a little
more affection for her.
Affection?
I don't have any such thing.
I told you the first time I met you.
I'm a snake.
My skin is cold. I have no heart.
I use the tip of my tongue to find
my prey as I slither on the ground
and engulf what I like whole.
That's the sort of creature I am.
Isn't that
what I told you?
Wh-What're you just standing
there for, boys and girls?!
This is no time to be gawking!
Th-That's right!
Let's get away! Quickly!
My, my...
I've grown tired of catching mice.
What will you do with them
after you kill them?
I'll string their corpses up somewhere
on the outskirts of town
where they'll be easy to see,
then get to work on
creating the Ouken.
Sounds good to me.
In that case...
I'll handle killing those kids.
Gin...
Sounds good to me.
In that case...
I'll handle killing those kids.
Gin...
The only way to escape the
power of Kyokasuigetsu is
to touch its blade, before it puts
you under Complete Hypnosis.
It took me decades
just to get that single
fact out of you.
Not a single person among the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads knew that
but they all thought they could
kill you, Captain Aizen.
Watching them made
me very nervous.
The only one who can kill
you is me, Captain Aizen.
I knew that.
I brought you with me, knowing
what your objective was,
because I was interested in
how you would try to kill me.
But I'm disappointed, Gin.
Did you really think you could kill
me with something like this?
No, I didn't.
Can you see this?
There's a chip here.
Just now, I left that chip inside
your body, Captain Aizen.
What?!
My Bankai's power...
I told you about
it before, didn't I?
Sorry, I lied.
It doesn't extend
as long as I said.
It doesn't extend as fast as I said.
However,
when it extends and contracts,
it turns to dust for just an instant.
Also...
Inside the blade, there is a powerful poison
that dissolves and destroys cells.
Looks like you understand.
When I withdrew my sword
from your chest,
A single chip of my blade didn't turn to
dust and was left inside of your heart.
Gin!
If you're going to say something,
you'd better do it fast.
Well, even if you try,
you're going to die anyway.
Kill'em, Kamishininoyari.
Gin... Damn you!
You'll die with a hole
through your heart.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Gin...
It's over.
It's over now.
W-What is that?!
How would I know?!
It's hopeless!
We're all going to die!
Chizuru, pull yourself together!
What could that be?
I don't know!
But I get the feeling it's something
seriously bad!
I win...Gin.
Even without being inside of me,
that Hogyoku you took...
...belongs to me.
What...the hell?!
He's the one.
He's the boss.
I'll...
kill him.
If you were to turn into
a snake tomorrow,
and began devouring humans,
and from the same mouth that
you devoured humans,
you cried out to me "I love you!"
Would I still be able
to say "I love you,"
in the same way I do today?
Arrancar Encyclopedia
I have sad news for all of you.
With no more Arrancars
left to talk about,
this will be our final segment
of the Arrancar Encyclopedia.
They put me through so much crap,
but that is also finally over.
So it wouldn't hurt to have things
done my way for this last...
Huh?
Wait!
I'm not finished yet!
Huh?
Why is it ending like this?