I've reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul Reaper, that is.
I knew about you since
you were born.
What?!
You were special from the
moment you were born.
That's because you're
a human and...
You talk too much...
Aizen.
D-Dad?
Hey, say something.
Dad...
Ow!
That was close!
You bastard!
Keeping his distance, I see.
A wise decision.
You've been watching
for quite a long time.
Gin.
I haven't just been watching.
I just couldn't find an opportunity
or a need to help you.
I see.
It's been a while.
This time, I won't
be holding back.
Raikoho.
It's been a while...
since I've fought you.
Do you remember the
last time we fought?
Oh, this isn't good.
Unacceptable.
A guardian of the gate isn't supposed
to open the gates.
A gatekeeper who lost isn't
opening any gates.
When a gatekeeper loses,
it means... "death."
When I slashed Jidanbo's arm, you
got all mad and attacked me.
What the hell are
you doing?!
Impale him, Shinso!
I remember thinking of you
as an interesting kid.
I don't remember.
Liar.
Are you trying to taunt me?
That's not it.
I'm not saying that I don't
remember your sword.
I don't remember your heart.
Whenever I face an opponent,
I can slightly tell what my
opponent is thinking.
I can't read their minds,
but I can tell why they're fighting,
what they want from me,
or whether they're looking
down on me.
During battle, I'm desperate, so
I usually notice it after it's over,
but the stronger my opponents are, the
stronger their hearts are conveyed.
You're quite the poet.
Shut up.
You have none of that.
Even when you were fighting me,
you weren't looking at me.
I don't know what you were
looking at, though.
You know...
I thought you were
an interesting kid,
but you're actually kind of creepy.
You're one to talk.
I can understand why Captain
Aizen is interested in you.
Do you know how far my
Shinso can extend?
No, I don't.
The length of a hundred swords.
When I was little, people used to say
I carried a set of hundred swords.
I'm not interested.
Then do you know how far
it can extend in Bankai?
I didn't come here to be quizzed.
What, you give up?
How boring.
Oh well.
I'll tell you in measurements
that you can understand.
Thirteen kilometers.
Must be hard to imagine just from
hearing the numbers, huh?
So let me demonstrate.
Here I go.
This time, I'm not holding back.
Bankai...
Kamishininoyari.
Why do you look surprised?
There's no way a Bankai couldn't
stop another Bankai!
You know...
You really are a creepy kid.
Gin?
How scary.
I better deal with you while I can.
Otherwise, things may
get troublesome.
When did his sword shrink?
Did I get distracted
and miss it?
No, I never took my attention
away from his sword.
There's no way that I couldn't have
seen a sword that long shrink.
Now then... What should I do?
You easily stopped my Bankai.
I guess I have no choice
but to fight.
That's an impressive sword.
I feel like mine will break
just from attacking it.
Yeah right.
Then why don't you
break already!
If my hunch is correct, he
only shrunk his sword.
He hasn't ended
his Bankai.
If my hunch is correct...
Once he points that
tip at me, it's over!
At this distance...
Just as I thought.
The scariest thing about
your Bankai's ability
is not its length or its
destructive force.
But its contraction.
I was thinking...
Telling me about its length
serves no purpose.
In fact, not telling me about it
would be to your advantage.
Swinging your sword and slicing
up the town serves no purpose.
In fact, attacking me head on
would be to your advantage.
You showed me those things to distract
me from its contraction.
Am I wrong?!
Wow...
He noticed that in my first attack
and dodged my second attack.
How scary...
He still has room
for improvement.
But he's not good
enough, yet.
Since you've figured it out,
I guess I have no choice.
I'll tell you how fast Kamishininoyari
can extend.
Did you hear that?
It's 500 times that speed.
Kamishininoyari isn't the
longest Zanpakuto.
It's the fastest Zanpakuto.
Even if you know that, you
have no chance of winning.
What's wrong?
You're getting slower.
Are you already at your limit?
Yes, it seems like it.
I've reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul Reaper, that is.
What?
My soul is going to
be restructured.
What are you talking about?
The Hogyoku's will is finally
beginning to understand
my thoughts.
Concentrate.
Ignore his swinging attacks.
Pay attention to when
he makes a thrust.
Don't let him point
it at me!
Just kidding.
You're too jumpy.
You bastard...
I swear I'll break your sword!
Fine. Try it if you can.
I've reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul Reaper, that is.
What are you talking about?
The Hogyoku's will is finally beginning
to understand my thoughts.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Can't you tell?
I'm saying that the Hogyoku
has a will of its own.
That sounds like
nonsense to me.
I can't blame you for being
unable to sense it.
Even I didn't know the Hogyoku had its
own will until becoming its master.
What do you think the
Hogyoku's power is?
Is it the power to dominate
two opposing forces-the boundary between
Hollows and Soul Reapers?
No.
The Hogyoku's true power
is the ability to manifest the
desires of those around it.
What?!
Can't you tell?
I'm saying that the miracles
that happened around
Ichigo Kurosaki, Rukia Kuchiki,
and Kisuke Urahara
were all manifested by
the Hogyoku's will.
What are you saying?
The reason why Kisuke Urahara mistakenly
believed that the Hogyoku's power
was the power to control
the boundary between
Hollows and Soul Reapers is because,
as its creator, that is what he desired.
Rukia Kuchiki passed all of her spiritual
powers to Ichigo Kurosaki
and lost her Soul Reaper powers
because she was still suffering from
the pain of killing Kaien Shiba.
Yasutora Sado and Orihime Inoue
developed special powers
because deep in their hearts, they
hated being considered helpless.
I knew about the Hogyoku's
true power.
No, I suppose it's incorrect
to say that I knew about it.
More correctly, I knew that
its power was not the
power to control the boundary
between Hollows
and Soul Reapers like Kisuke
Urahara thought it was.
Because
if that was really its power,
Shinji Hirako and the
other Visoreds
would never have become
complete Visoreds.
The Hollowfication of
Shinji Hirako and the
other Visoreds was a Hollowfication experiment
as well as a confirmation
of the Hogyoku's powers.
The experiment was a success.
Kisuke Urahara's activation
of the Hogyoku's power
evolved Shinji Hirako and
the other Visoreds
into complete Visoreds.
And I had a hypothesis on
the Hogyoku's power.
I had Rukia Kuchiki go
to Ichigo Kurosaki.
Naturally, there are limits
to the Hogyoku's power.
The Hogyoku has the power to manifest
the desires of those around it.
But if the target does not have
the power to achieve it,
nothing would happen.
In that sense, it has the power
to guide you to your desires.
Living creatures are odd things.
They're able to achieve
their petty wishes.
You bastard...
You stopped that well.
That's pretty good for sheer luck.
Who are you calling
lucky, stupid?!
I-Ichigo...
What is it?! Don't bother me!
I'll be able to handle him soon!
Don't interfere!
Sorry, Captain Aizen.
Did I interrupt your conversation?
It's all right.
I just finished talking.
Dad! What is that?!
What's going on?!
How should I know?!
I had no idea what was going
on when you came flying in!
And I still don't know
what's going on!
What do you mean
you don't know?!
You're the one who's
been fighting him!
Stop complaining!
If you want to know, ask Aizen
yourself, you pain in the ass!
Honestly...
The Hogyoku is very
aptly named!
It has the power to destroy the wall
that separates those who are gods
from those who aren't!
So you've come...
Kisuke Urahara!
You and your father are so alike.
What? I'm nothing like this guy!
No way! My son is nowhere
near as good as me!
See? That's what
I'm talking about.
Yeah, right!
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today I'm going to talk about
my Bankai, "Kamishininoyari."
It can extend its blade
up to 13 kilometers.
Thirteen kilometers is difficult
to comprehend.
It's the size of about
39 Tokyo Towers.
For Yammy... I'd say
about 260 Yammys?
Plus...
Whoa!
If I ever forget anything,
I can retrieve it as long as it's
within 13 kilometers of myself.
H-How convenient.