Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends
have marched into Hueco Mundo.
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
Hey, are you the first one here?
Devour! Glotoneria!
I was just making you dance
on the palm of my hand.
Don't underestimate me!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Ulquiorra appears before Ichigo.
Sensing that Rukia is in danger,
he ignores Ulquiorra
and tries to go save Rukia.
But Ulquiorra taunts him.
So Inoue really didn't go to
Hueco Mundo of her own free will!
I'm going to go at full strength!
Bankai!
A Bankai, huh?
What is that form?
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
It's as if he's like us.
It's over.
Getsugatensho!
Impossible…
Ichigo!
Nel?
I thought you were going to die!
I thought you were
going to die, Ichigo!
Umm… Yeah, like right now.
You used such extreme power
even though you're a wreck!
That's crazy! Don't do that!
I was really worried about you!
Don't…Don't do that anymore!
– Ichigo… Ichigo…
– Sorry, Nel.
It seems like I made you worry.
Ichigo!
Mucus! Mucus! Mucus!
Huh?
I swallowed it.
That's nice.
All right…
Let's go!
Are you all right, Ichigo?!
I'm all right.
We can't waste time here.
What?
My, my…
I couldn't even stop it with two hands.
I'm a little surprised.
Was that your best?
It seems like it was.
How unfortunate.
Nel, are you all right?!
Nel!
Hold on! I'm going to let you
rest somewhere and…
You took out that mask just when
you blocked my Cero, didn't you?
Your reaction time is impressive.
But this time,
it broke instantly.
You can't bring it out again.
Give up.
Who's going to give up?
You're the leader of
the Espada, aren't you?
That means that if I defeat you,
this battle is pretty much won!
I see…
That's unfortunate.
Wha—?!
Four?!
Yes…
Quatro Espada, Ulquiorra Shifar.
Of the Espada, my strength ranks…
Fourth.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you do defeat me,
there are three Espada above me.
You can try a thousand times.
You will not be victorious.
It seems that I overestimated you.
Your development
didn't meet my expectations.
This is it.
If you can still move in that condition,
leave this place immediately.
If you can't move, then die there.
Your path ends here, Soul Reaper.
Kurosaki?
It’s a lie!
Kuchiki and now Kurosaki?
That can't be!
Ul…
See? The princess is by herself.
Orihime…
Let's play.
That was the reaction I expected.
You really are amusing.
But I've told you many times.
You can't damage an Espada
with just your Shikai.
Quit your blabbing.
Get out of the way!
This is also as expected.
How simple.
I got you to move.
Wha—?!
Didn't you notice?
Wasn’t it supposed to
be as expected?
Who cares if you
sealed away my Bankai?
Who cares about your data?
Zabimaru is my arms and legs!
I say that it's too early
to take me lightly
just because you can
read my movements!
The battle's…just beginning!
You're not getting away!
How unfortunate it must be
for you to be so incompetent.
I told you that I received
all of your data.
Your attack speed is, naturally,
very basic information.
Go!
I told you…
You no longer have any way
to win or escape.
What?!
Once you use your trump card,
it's no longer a trump card.
Lumina, gimmie! Lumina, not fair!
I'm tired of this.
What?
I told you, I'm tired of this.
Don't you understand
words anymore?
Your Zanpakuto is a power-type.
There's nothing special about it.
The way in which it changes forms
is also very simple.
I'm well aware this is rude,
but there's nothing interesting
about it anymore.
Let's finish this.
What's this?!
Fracciónes…
We Espada are given Arrancars
ranked undecimo, eleventh, and lower
for direct subordinates
as a testament to our right to rule.
Those are the Fracciónes.
There are Espada
who have only one,
and there are Espada
who have a ton of them.
My Octava Fracciónes
are a little unique.
They're Hollows that I modified
and had Lord Aizen turn into Arrancars.
So what of it?
Well, let's stop
with the useless chatter.
Anyway, you're no longer worthy enough
for me to fight you directly.
Now then…
The show’s over.
Bastard!
L-Let go of me!
All of you, don't interfere.
Of course, I won't interfere either.
At least make the epilogue exciting.
Umm…
Hmm?
I see.
You live in a nice room.
Yeah…
Hmm?
This is a really nice room.
Lord Aizen likes you, doesn't he?
It’s true isn’t it?
Everyone is infatuated with you.
You're a star!
You're really amazing.
Five people came
to save their princess?
That's…
Say, Orihime… Do you think that
you're really something?
Humph! How lame!
Or do you think that
this is only natural?
I don't think that.
What? Did you say something?
I couldn't hear you.
I don't think that.
Hey, Menoly, did you hear that?
She doesn't think that!
How unexpected!
Let me give you
some good advice, Orihime.
Don't get cocky, you skank!
You're a human!
Don't stay at Lord Aizen’s side!
Huh? What is that?
She's really annoying!
Shall we beat her up?
Why not?
I'll stop when she starts crying.
That's a good idea!
Orihime…
Show us your ugly tearful face!
Oh?
I'll edit your numbers
so they're better.
I never expected you
to hold on so long.
This is troublesome.
Once he's like this,
it's not easy to stop him.
How unfortunate.
I may not be able to collect
your body in its complete form.
It's unfortunate for you that
this building isn't made of Sekkiseki.
Your Spiritual Pressure
was reverberating
from beyond three walls.
What's wrong?
You look like you've
taken quite a beating, Renji Abarai!
You're…
Ishida!
Occasionally, your Spiritual Pressure
will increase momentarily.
How does that work, Soul Reaper?
It's willpower!
Simple-minded people
always say that.
What?!
Stop, Renji, it's exactly as he says.
Back me up here!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Now then.
I guess I'll have some tea.
Wh-What's this?!
Soi Fon… Kiyone!
What is the meaning of this?
I'm sorry, Ukitake.
I have nothing against you,
but I'm going to do this!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
– I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
– Shall I take off the bottom?
Stop!
SUCCESS