Welcome to my castle, Las Noches.
Shatter, Kyokasuigetsu...
I am the emperor, Barragan Ruizenban!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Now then...
Preparations are finally complete.
We will soon begin our invasion
of Karakura Town.
I will wipe out Karakura Town,
create the Ouken,
and bring down the
Soul Society.
The door to a new world
will be opened.
Stark, Barragan, Halibel...
I'm counting on you three.
We shall not fail
you, Lord Aizen!
Invasion, huh?
Y-You bastards!
Jakuho Raikoben.
Go.
Oh, dear...
It looks like another one of
your allies has gone down.
Captain!
A-Are you all right, Captain?
Stop doing that.
I told you, it's disgusting.
It made a crack in the
Shiju Saimon barrier.
The Jakuho Raikoben...
Its power is truly incredible.
Are you all right?
Of course she's not, fatso!
What if she'd died?!
Under normal circumstances,
I can only use the Jakuho Raikoben
once every three days.
I used it twice in one day.
I'm going to make sure you
compensate me for this.
Yes, of course.
I will trap Mr. Urahara in one of my
barriers for a month, as promised.
The barrier...
It can't be!
Unforgivable!
Wh-What?!
No...
Unforgivable!
It's not possible...
Completely unforgivable!
Unbelievable... He's still alive after getting
hit with my Jakuho Raikoben?!
Is he immortal?!
I'm going to kill you.
I'll do it with my own hands.
I am the king of Hueco Mundo.
I am a god. I will never die.
You will regret your
insolence towards
the emperor... and turn to dust!
What's driving him
to go this far?!
Is it his loyalty to Aizen?!
Do you really think that will
prevent you from aging?!
I will kill you!
How impudent!
Do you think mimicking a
Hollow will work against me?!
Know your place!
I am the emperor, Barragan Ruizenban!
I am the god of Hueco Mundo!
Hachigen Ushoda!
Puny, puny, puny, puny!
How puny you are!
Soul Reapers, humans,
Hollows, Arrancars...
Their respective differences,
and the quarrels between them...
Free will, freedom, animals, plants,
the moon, the stars, and the sun...
They are all of little importance!
The only thing that is absolute
in this world is my power!
Everything aside from
that is a trifling matter.
I hold supreme power. The world
should be under my control!
Equality cannot exist if there
are rivaling powers!
Look! To me, your lives are
equal to those of ants!
I commend you!
I'm surprised an ant like
you has injured me!
Feel proud of yourself in hell!
Wh-What is this?
You said it yourself.
It's your power, the only thing
that is absolute in this world.
I thought it was strange...
Everything that touches your power
grows old, rots, and turns to dust.
So why don't you turn to dust?
From there, I came
up with a theory.
You have surrounded your
body with something
that can stave off your power.
So if I placed your power
inside of you,
a place where your power would
normally never reach...
My power? But how?
Where's your right arm?
What is the meaning of this?
I've given it to you.
He severed his own arm with a barrier
and transported it inside of Barragan!
Th-That old man is crazy.
If your power is absolute,
then you yourself should not be
able to withstand that power.
I had no proof of this when
I made this gamble.
But I'm glad that I made
the right call.
Curse you, ant!
Defying a god...
Unforgivable, unforgivable!
This is unforgivable, you ants!
The word "god" is not very familiar to us
Soul Reapers and the Soul Society.
Thus, we are unable to understand
the weight of your words.
Please forgive our lack of faith,
god of Hueco Mundo.
C-Captain! He did it!
He did it!
You can still move?
I won't die...
I can't die yet.
I've sworn revenge.
You... I will kill you!
I will do it with my hands.
I am a king... I am a god...
I will never die...until I kill you!
Ushoda!
Die with me!
I don't need any.
I'm bored.
Nothing is more meaningless than an
army without an enemy to conquer.
Don't you think so?
Even if I ask, I suppose no one
is going to disagree with me.
What's going on?
Gagamel's been killed!
Wh-Who are you?!
Unforgivable.
Get them!
Wait...
This is just the thing I need to
pass the time. I'll handle them.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Aizen... Sosuke Aizen.
You must be Barragan,
king of Hueco Mundo.
Indeed. And what are you?
Seeing that you do not wear masks,
I can tell you are not Hollows.
Are you humans?
Or are you Soul Reapers?
Hmph. Well, it doesn't
matter what you are.
I was getting pretty bored.
If you hadn't shown up,
I would have split my army into two
and had them kill each other.
In any case, I suppose
I should greet you.
Welcome to my castle, Las Noches.
How amusing. This place with
no roof or walls is a castle?
I don't need a roof.
As king, all of Hueco Mundo's
skies are the roof of my castle.
I see the king of Hueco Mundo
has a sense of humor.
Stop, Kaname.
There's no point in quarreling.
Yes, sir!
Anyway, let's have a
chat, your majesty.
Could you take a look
at my sword?
My Kyokasuigetsu...
What is this all about?
I wish to ask your majesty
a question.
A question?
That's right.
Are you satisfied with your
self at the moment?
What?
Have you ever felt that the world
was not the way it should be?
Do you wish to achieve
higher greatness?
I shall help you.
Obey me.
If you do, I will give
you greater power.
Greater power, you say?
That's right.
My research will soon
be complete.
My research to transform Soul Reapers into
Hollows and Hollows into Soul Reapers.
By removing the boundaries between
these two opposing states of being,
one can achieve higher greatness.
You could step forth
into a new world.
Laughable! Laughable!
Greater power?! A new world?!
Don't make me laugh, you ants!
I am king of Hueco Mundo!
The king of the world!
No one can surpass my power!
No world exists other than
the one I open up!
I see.
Get them, my minions!
Crush these arrogant ants!
My, my...
I shall take you on.
You're going to be killed by
the king of Hueco Mundo.
Consider it an honor.
Isn't it ironic, king
of Hueco Mundo?
What?
Even though you're a Hollow,
the way you wield your weapon
and your giant black form...
It looks a lot like that
of a Soul Reaper.
Silence!
Fool.
You talk big, but is
that all you've got?
Honestly... How pathetic...
Wh-What?!
Y-You... Why are you alive?
My Zanpakuto, Kyokasuigetsu, has
the power of complete hypnosis.
Complete hypnosis?
In other words, the person you
defeated was an illusion.
Shatter, Kyokasuigetsu...
Wh-What is this?!
This is your world.
Y-You bastard!
Don't do anything pointless.
You can't kill me.
Yes... On that day,
I made a vow.
That I would take
my revenge on you!
back my throne!
Die with me!
I will kill you.
I will do it with my hands.
You will regret giving me power!
I am a king! I am a god!
I will never die!
I will chase you down forever!
Sosuke Aizen!
King of Hueco Mundo...
Even you were but
just a tiny life
who feared death and
tried to avoid aging.
Oh my. It looks like they
really defeated him.
Where are you looking?
I'm your opponent.
Don't be so hasty.
Let's take our time, okay?
I don't have any time
to waste with you.
After I'm done with you, I've
got to kill that bastard Aizen!
That's too bad...
Number Two is dead and
no one says anything.
How sad.
What's wrong?
Be quiet, Lilinette.
Are you crying?
Ouch!
Hey! Stark!
Stark?
I'm usually not the type
to avenge others, but...
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
You and I both have
Kansai accents.
I was hoping we could get
to know each other better.
You have an Osaka accent.
I have a Kyoto accent.
Don't put us in the same league.
What's the difference?
The Osaka accent
lacks elegance.
I take back what I said!
I swear on my loyalty to Osaka
that I will defeat you!
"Dead spirits are said to float around
in the outskirts of town."
Ichigo!
What are you doing here?
Renji said that he wanted to practice
his Kido in secret, so I'm helping him.
Hey, Rukia! Don't tell him!
It's your fault for not
having any control!
Come on, Renji, once more!
O-Okay... Shakkaho!
You fool! How many times do you
have to do this until you get it?!
Shakkaho!
- What is that supposed to be?!
- So that's the story...