I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians of
the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who
keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Aizen, who has brought chaos
upon the Soul Society,
has begun to set his plan
into motion.
Arrancars, created by Aizen
using the Hogyoku,
a material that removes
the boundaries
between Soul Reapers and Hollows,
appear in Karakura Town.
Meanwhile, the Visored,
Soul Reapers who have Hollow powers
appear before Ichigo.
Once you become a Visored,
you can't go back.
Come with me, Ichigo.
But at that time,
Aizen's formidable Arrancars
had gathered in Karakura
and begun to battle the advance troop
led by Captain Hitsugaya.
Dance!
Sodenoshirayuki!
D Roy, who appears before
Ichigo and Rukia,
is destroyed by Rukia's ice-snow
zanpakuto, Sodenoshirayuki.
But immediately after this,
Grimmjow appears before the two.
Ikkaku is confronted by Edrad,
Illfort stands before Renji,
and Hitsugaya and Rangiku face
Shawlong and Nakeem.
And they call upon
their various true powers
as they begin to battle.
What's the matter?
Is that all a Soul Reaper is?! Huh?!
You haven't told me
your name yet, you big oaf.
Introductions aren't necessary
since I'm about to kill you.
Is that so?
It seems you and I have
different styles of protocol.
"Always introduce yourself to
the one you're about to kill."
That's the final etiquette that
I teach to every pupil I train.
If you're putting your life
on the line, you'd want to know...
...who it was that killed you.
Know me as Third Seat
of Zaraki's Squad, Ikkaku Madarame!
But don't bother to tell me
your name.
Just make sure
you remember my name!
It's the name of the man
who will kill you!
What?! Why don't you use
your zanpakuto?
Is that thing on your waist
just for show?!
We Arrancars have iron-like skin
known as "Hierro,"
which swords cannot penetrate.
It's our armor!
My bare hands are enough
to handle your sword!
Oh yeah?
I see. It seems you're pretty aware
of what kind of attack
it'll take to lose an arm.
I'm to draw my zanpakuto for
a Soul Reaper like you?
How humiliating.
Don't say that.
I'll even let you release it.
Wh-Wha-?
What's going on?!
Who are they?!
Weren't you listening just now?
He's the Third Seat on
Zaraki's Squad, Ikkaku Madarame.
He's the second strongest man
on Squad 11,
Soul Society's most powerful squad.
Y-You're from this afternoon!
Don't you have to go to his aid?
Aren't you his fellow officer?!
Why don't you understand?
Huh?
Look at that happy face.
Ikkaku is having fun.
It's been a while since he's faced
such a formidable opponent.
"Go to his aid" doesn't apply to us.
It's more like, "can't go to his aid."
Can you understand?
No, I don't understand.
Having fun?
Can't go to his aid?
Then is there a guarantee
that he'll win?
- Nope.
- What is that?!
What if your comrade dies?
What'll you do?!
That's obvious.
Be happy for him.
His style is rough,
but his strength is certain.
He provokes a reaction.
However...
He attacks with his sword
in his left hand
and defends with the sheathe
in his right.
So naive.
Since I've ascertained that
he only attacks with his left...
I can instantly differentiate between
his attack stance and defense stance.
Which means...
I can easily find an opening!
He attacks with his left!
His sheathe is in his left hand?!
Damn, I missed...
I intended to cut your head off.
What kind of guy is he?
Deceiving me into thinking
his offense was simple,
making me think his attack patterns
are predictable,
and creating an opening for me...
Then the instant I attack,
he switches the sheathe to his left.
What a haphazard way of fighting.
It's full of flaws.
Even if his blows are powerful,
if he's unlucky, he dies.
He doesn't fight to win...
He fights because he enjoys it!
At first glance, he looks like
he's thinking through his moves.
But that's not so.
He fights as though killing is a game.
This guy considers his own life...
as just a tool for battle.
That huge slap technique with
all that Spiritual Pressure in your hand
is amazing.
I lost two teeth 'cuz of that.
Well, never mind...
I'll get Akon to make me
some cheap replacements later.
All right. Ready for the second round?!
I've just about learned your moves.
Five, maybe six exchanges.
And I'll force you to release
your zanpakuto!
I see...
It seems I underestimated you.
For someone like you,
it's not whether it's necessary or not.
I should just release my zanpakuto
to fight you, right?
Are you acknowledging
my strength then?
No... I just think that a fool like you,
who loves to fight,
needs to be taught a lesson
about what it's like
to feel uncontrollable fear in
the depths of your bones.
So that you never again think
that fighting an Arrancar is fun.
Awaken! Volcanica!
What's...that?
"What's that" is all you can say? Huh?
This is what we Arrancars call
"releasing our zanpakuto"!
Bad... This is really bad!
I think you said in your protocol that
you tell your name to
the man you intend to kill.
I'm Arrancar Trece, Edrad Liones!
What is this guy's Spiritual Pressure?!
He's an Arrancar, too?
Is he really...
...the same as that one earlier?!
The level of Spiritual Pressure...
is way too different!
Which one?
I'm asking which is the stronger one?
This is bad!
Ichigo, let's retreat for now!
I guess this isn't the one.
D-Damn it...
Rukia!
The zanpakuto of Arrancars
has the nucleus of our power
sealed into the sword.
It is completely different from
the swords of Soul Reapers.
In other words, the "release of the sword"
signifies the release of
ourselves and our power.
Do you understand?
This appearance is my true self.
And this Volcanica
is my true strength!
Yes, Yumichika Ayasegawa,
what is your request?
The enemy's destructive power
has magnified
to unexpected proportions.
Requesting an area freeze for
a radius of 300 units
around Ikkaku Madarame.
Yes.
Several souls may become
entangled in this.
As for the buildings,
take it out from our mission
allowance as usual.
The safety of the souls is the top priority.
Roger.
I would expect
the same increase in power
from the other assailants.
Toshiro Hitsugaya,
Rangiku Matsumoto, Renji Abarai,
Rukia Kuchiki, and Ichigo Kurosaki.
Request the same area freeze
for them as well.
Also...
Prepare a Squad Funeral
for Ikkaku Madarame.
"Funeral"? Does that mean
you think he's gonna die?!
What's wrong?
When an Arrancar releases
his zanpakuto,
his battle strength increases exponentially!
Spiritual Pressure of your level
can never withstand it!
Extend!
Hozukimaru!
Is it over?
Give it up.
Knowing when it's over is also
a fine trait in a warrior.
You fought well.
I don't want to have to
beat you to a pulp.
How unfortunate.
Sheesh...
I never expected this
much difference in strength.
Well, it can't be helped.
Right now, everyone else
has their hands full
with their own enemy.
So no one will notice.
Well well... I really didn't expect
to use it in a place like this!
Watch carefully.
And don't tell anyone about this.
Ban...kai!
Wh-What?! What's going on?!
I see... So he's using it...
Did you say...Bankai?
Yeah, I did.
Bankai...
Ryumon...
Hozukimaru!
That's pretty awesome.
Don't flatter me.
There's not enough Spiritual Pressure yet
for you to be impressed.
You can decide whether
it's awesome or not...
...after you're dead!
Impossible.
He cut through my Volcanica?!
Power...!
His Bankai doesn't increase his Kido,
his speed or his defensive abilities
but it doesn't increase speed
or defensive power.
It's an accumulation of sheer power...
Amazing destructive power...
However, relying only on that power
makes him slow to counter my attacks!
I have the will to win! I have no fear!
Before he can cut off my arms...
I will surpass his strength
and kill him!
It will be power versus power!
I cannot lose!
Strange... That zanpakuto...
The Spiritual Pressure has
gone up even more!
Seems you noticed.
Unlike me, Hozukimaru likes
to take his time...
Even after Bankai,
he continues to sleep.
So my opponent and I have to
keep exchanging vicious blows
to force him to wake up or else,
the power won't manifest.
But when he starts to wake up...
the dragon starts to turn red.
And when it's all dyed red,
for the first time,
Ryumon Hozukimaru reaches
ultimate strength.
Here I come!
Sure!
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
It's time for Professor Grimmjow's lecture
on Arrancars.
The words in front of our names
are numbers.
Seis means six. Trece is thirteen.
This'll be on the test, so remember it!
Professor! What's 15? Fifteen?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers...
Err, Captain...
I have a favor to ask.
Even if I'm away, you don't have
to attend the Lieutenants' Meeting.
Captains are responsible for
the duties of their lieutenants.
I know, but...
If Rukia is away,
do you plan to attend
the Women Soul Reaper
Association Meeting?