Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Not much left.
This side, too.
It's almost time to replenish.
Kurosaki Clinic
Internal Medicine - Pediatrics
Hey, I brought you breakfast.
Come on out! Hey!
Hey! I said breakfast–! Huh?
She's not here…
Where'd she go?
That idiot!
Don't you think Brother's
acting weird lately?
He eats so much more now.
And he always rushes back
to his room.
Ichigo is 15 years old.
An impressionable boy
in the springtime of life
would only go and lock himself
in his room for just…one thing–
Cut it out!
And quit analyzing me,
dirty old man!
What are you saying?!
It's because I'm your father!
Why can't you understand?
Who'd understand such a thing?!
Your breakfast will get cold.
How peaceful…
Clean-up batter, Jinta Hanakari.
Here's the wind up and the pitch!
With a perfect back swing, he lets it go!
A homerun!
Jinta, you'd better get to work
or Tessai will scold you.
Urahara Store
Shut up, Ururu.
I'm not cleaning up out
of fear of Tessai!
Huh? Aren't you sweeping
because you're scared?
I'm not scared!
Besides, you're too cocky…!
You're my underling!
Am not! I'm three years
older than you!
I'm not talking about age!
I'm talking about rank!
W-Who are you?! Huh?
Never change, do you, runt?
Is the boss in?
Welcome…
Hey Jinta…It's too early to
open up shop. Huh?
Ms. Kuchiki!
One moment, please.
I'll wake the boss up.
Sorry, but I'm already up today.
Good morning, Tessai,
Jinta, Ururu…
And welcome,
Ms. Kuchiki.
I just received a delivery yesterday.
What would you like today?
One spare of the Kikanshinki fuel…
and which rank?
The cheapest one.
"D" then.
And 60 pieces of Somafixer and…
This may be none of my business,
but too much of this can be toxic.
If you over-synchronize with the gigai,
it'll be quite painful when you leave it.
I know that, but…
Lately, my connection with
the gigai has been weak.
And it's difficult to move my body.
Want me to check you out?
I'll give you a discount.
No, thank you!
Right.
By the way, has the thing
I ordered been delivered?
Oh, yes it's here. Ururu,
get it from the storehouse.
Uh, yes!
It says "new item" on the box.
Um…new item …new item…
Oh…
Found it!
Is this the only kind you could get?
Don't say that.
That one's the second most popular
and was hard to get.
But…
You can't fake it forever.
I know that.
Everyone, good morning!
Oh, good morning, Kuchiki.
You look so lovely again today, Kuchiki!
It's not like you.
Third period is over already.
I had to go home for something.
By the way, Kurosaki…
May I see you a moment?
Huh? What is it?
If you need to talk, tell me here.
Are you all right, Kurosaki?
Oh no, I'd better take you
to the infirmary!
Didn't she just hit him?
Nah, we didn't see that.
Here!
Huh? What is it?
Gikongan, Substitute Soul Pills.
It's a capsule that will force
a soul out of the body.
When one swallows that,
a substitute soul will enter and
the real soul can leave the body.
If there's ever a time when I'm not here
and you confront a Hollow,
use that and transform into
a Soul Reaper.
It says "Soul Candy".
T-That's because the Women
Soul Reapers Society complained
that Gikongan didn't sound nice,
so it was changed.
Why's it a duck?
Shut up! I personally wanted
the rabbit-shaped container, Chappie!
I see… You wanted a rabbit, huh?
Why're you looking at me
like that?!
Are you belittling me?!
I…didn't really get
your explanation just now.
Take one! Then you'll understand.
Huh? My soul really did leave!
Are you shocked?
In that empty shell of a body,
there's a substitute soul.
So no one will notice
that your true soul is gone!
Nice to meet you.
My name is Ichigo Kurosaki.
My favorite phrase is
"Early to bed, early to rise."
Early to bed, early to rise?!
Isn't it amazing?
It's not amazing?
What IS that thing? What part is like me?!
A mission. Perfect timing.
Leave him here.
And we'll head for the site!
A-Are you crazy?!
Let's go!
No way! They'll know he's a fake!
Hey! You!
Make sure you attend the next class!
Leave it to me, Master!
Take your time.
Huh?
Defective Merchandise
Look closely. What does it say?
Read it.
Defective Merchandise
Defective
Merchandise                           Defective Merchandise
De…fective…Merchandise?
Defective merchandise! Defective!
You sold a customer damaged goods!
Get your act together!
You and your stupid bangs!
Oww!
Hey, hey… No fighting.
But this Gikongan is going
to be trouble.
I know. We'd better take care
of this right away.
Otherwise, who knows what he'll do?
Awright…feels great.
I finally found a mobile body.
Now I'm free.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Huh? You're Kurosaki in
ninth grade group three.
What did you just do?
That fence is broken!
W-What's with that look?!
Huh?! He flew!
Hah-hah, he's surprised all right.
Yahoo! It's lunchtime!
This girl!
Don't get so excited over lunch.
What're you saying, Tatsuki?
A healthy high school girl comes
to school just to eat her lunch!
Okay, okay. I get it, so sit down.
Tatsuki, what do you have for lunch?
I have bread with sweet bean jam.
How nice. Unfortunately,
I only have an ordinary lunch.
See? You make your
own bean-jam rolls.
Good girl!
Hime! Let's eat lunch together!
Yeah. OK.
Oh, how cute!
You bite into a whole loaf of bread and
smile with crumbs around your mouth!
This is ninth grade, group three, right?
I got a bad feeling…
Y-You…! How did you get up here?
How? You saw, didn't you? I jumped.
Well, wasn't that amazing?
Are you surprised?
Maybe he came from the next class room
through the window.
He jumped from the ground!
You saw it?
No, I didn't.
Righteous! Everyone's eyes are on me!
They must think I'm amazing.
What a feeling!
And the girls in this class
are good-looking!
Every single one of them
is above average…
I've been cooped up for so long…Huh?
Oh...!
Super size!
Hello, pretty girl.
Will you tell me your name?
Ichigo! Do you know what
you're doing?!
This better not be some joke!
Hey, up close you're pretty cute too.
Why the rush back to
the classroom?
I'm worried…if he's doing okay.
You don't have to worry,
he'll be fine.
I don't know about that.
I've been getting these bad vibes.
As you said, we'd better hurry.
Told you.
Why you...!
Die!
Watch out!
What's the problem?
I just kissed your cheek.
What's the big deal?
You're not in grade school.
Shut up!
Stop her, Chizuru…
D-Don't be stupid!
How could I stop a beast like that?
Stop right there!
You…
He's coming, Ichigo!
Right!
Now, there's nowhere to run.
You, I mean, me! Why?!
Kurosaki…
What's he doing by himself?
Who cares?!
W-What's going on?!
It's a poltergeist!
So long!
What's going on with him?
He can't be…
No, there's no mistake…he's a…
Mod Soul!
Ichigo!
That was Kuchiki, right?
I didn't see…
I didn't see anything.
Who cares about that?!
But Ichigo…!
I'll never forgive him!
She's a demon.
Tatsuki…
Orihime?
Weren't you scared? Poor Hime!
It's all right. Think of it as just
an attack by a stray dog.
No…
That wasn't Kurosaki.
Huh…?
Dammit!
We lost him! Lost me!
It's a moratorium.
What?!
This is no time for
your mumbo-jumbo talk!
I have to capture me, no, him!
You saw it, too!
The riot he caused in class.
I, I mean, he used my body and
took advantage of Inoue
and Tatsuki and k-k-k-…
Kissed them.
Arghh! Don't say it!
How embarrassing!
Huh. A kiss is like a greeting.
It's no big deal.
In the book I read recently,
even worse things have happened to…
Don't lump it all together!
My classmates were grabbed
and kissed! That is a big deal!
What books do you read anyway?!
After I built up my image so carefully!
He was building up his image?
You called him a Mod Soul, right?
Just what is that?
Once, a project called "Spearhead"
was begun in the Soul Society.
Spearhead?
Yes. A soul that had been modified
for combat was placed into a person
who had died and whose soul
had left its body.
They were to be used to fight Hollows.
It was a despicable plan.
Mod Soul
These souls that were transformed
for this project…
once  placed into a body, they could make
one part of the body super-human…
An Artificial Soul made for fighting...
That is a Kaizo Konpaku, Mod Soul.
Do you understand so far?
Yeah. That drawing of yours erased
all the tension, though.
But the Spearhead Project was cancelled
because it would force corpses to fight.
Furthermore, all the Kaizo Konpaku,
Mod or Modified Souls
that were in the development stage
were ordered destroyed…
but to think, some are still around.
Does that mean…
that guy was created
by the Soul Society…
and rejected at the whim
of the Soul Society?!
Exactly that.
And you accept that?!
It's not a matter of accepting or not.
Mod Souls must be destroyed.
That's the order of
the Soul Society. Do not forget.
The laws of the Soul Society are made
for the purpose of protecting human souls!
Now let's go! You want to get
your body back, don't you?!
I wonder how he feels in my body.
They were created thoughtlessly
and condemned thoughtlessly…
But he survived somehow
and found a body…
Yet he has to keep running.
I wonder what he's feeling?
Yay! This is great!
Everyone's looking at me
and they're in awe!
This is unbelievable!
There!
I heard that Mod Souls
had all sorts of power.
I'm glad my power makes
me stand out!
Go!
Huh? What's going on?
P.E. is so boring!
Cutting class… Perfect!
Darn! Lost again!
Fight! Who do you think
created you?
Kill him off.
Yeah, those who don't obey
their masters…die!
You really deleted him!
So what? I'll make a better one.
W-What do you want?
Cut it out!
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Hmm…in the next episode…
I can't do it.
What now, Chad? After all that?
Oh no…the time!