Ulquiorra, coming in.
So you've come...
Ulquiorra... Yammy...
I was just finishing up.
How much of the Hogyoku
has awakened?
It's gone about halfway.
Things are going as planned...
For Soul Society, that is.
It's only natural.
You wouldn't be able to tell
unless you held the Hogyoku
in your hands.
Kisuke Urahara sealed it away
as soon as he developed it,
and he never unsealed it.
Even he probably
doesn't know.
After being unsealed and
in a sleeping state,
when the Hogyoku temporarily fuses
with someone
with the Spiritual Pressure
of a captain...
For an instant, it displays the same power
as if it were completely awake.
Could you tell me your name,
my new comrade?
Wonderweiss...
Wonderweiss...Margera.
Do you remember
the instructions
I mentioned about
a month ago, Ulquiorra?
Yes.
Put it into action.
I'll give you the final say.
Take with you
whomever you like.
Understood.
Oh yes...
Do you wish to
go as well...?
Grimmjow...
Baldy!
"You're already dead..."
Don't you think that
this line is deep?
He's in the middle of battle,
telling people who haven't realized
that they've died that they're dead.
"Don't you realize it?
You're alive, but you're already dead."
That line's not something
in line with Schiele.
Anyway, could you stop reading
the manga I buy before I do,
and telling me
what happened?
Wake up, you bastard!
How many times do you think
you died just now?!
I know!
You think that Soul Reapers
have the godly ability
to keep on dying,
don't you?
Well, they don't, baldy!
Shut up.
Dinner!
Gather round!
The guy who gets here last
has to wash the dishes!
Oh?!
So, Hiyori, is Ichigo making progress
in maintaining his Hollow transformation?
You can tell by looking!
Not at all!
Right now, it's just a little
over ten seconds.
He's worthless!
That baldy's not worth talking about!
Crap...
Maybe he doesn't have any talent.
Give up already!
Shut up, erotica woman!
You're not participating
in my training,
so you've no right
to say that!
I am participating, stupid!
Did you forget that I secretly
lent you some erotica?!
You didn't lend me anything!
Don't make jokes like that!
They sound true.
Don't be bashful...
I borrow some once every two days.
I'm not like you!
I read some twice a day.
I know!
Anyway, I've never been like you,
you perverted woman!
I'm not perverted!
I'm just very curious!
People call that perversity!
What?! But you're
interested, too!
I'm not...
- Wait up!
- A little over ten seconds in a month.
As I thought,
we need time to do this.
The Hogyoku completely awakens
at the end of December...
We have two months
until then.
We've got to go
a little faster.
There you are.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Hisagi...
Well, I was watching them while
I was taking a bit of a break.
They're training in preparation
for the showdown in winter.
It's Kuchiki and
Orihime Inoue...
Do you know her?
Yes... I met her in
the World of the Living.
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
It looks like they're
enjoying their training.
Oh! You think so too?
What?
Captain Ukitake,
I have a personal request.
A personal request?
What is it?
I want you to open the training ground
behind the barracks.
The training ground?
Why now?
Yes, sir! A friend and I
want to train
in preparation for
the showdown in winter!
You're...
C-Captain Ukitake!
I've brought you Orihime Inoue!
What are you saying,
you stinky-armpit monkey!
I'm the one who brought her!
Don't lie, you snotty woman!
Anyway, Captain Ukitake...
Would you like more tea?
Hey!
That's not fair!
You promised
that we'd decide
who gets to pour him tea
with Rock-Paper-Scissors.
The person who makes
the first move wins!
S-Sorry...
for being selfish.
And I came here so suddenly...
Inoue!
There's no need to be modest!
Our final goal is
our showdown with Aizen!
As long as we have
somebody with powers.
A Soul Reaper or a human,
it doesn't matter which!
Look! I'd even want Chappy's help
in this situation!
That's right, pyon!
Kuchiki, you don't need to
adjust things to my level.
Anyway... Let's train!
S-Sorry...
It's fine as long
as you understand.
Let's do our best, Inoue!
Okay!
When she asked me
to open up
the training ground with
such a desperate look,
I was wondering
what was wrong.
But I'm glad that
she's made a good friend.
Even if...she's a human?
Don't say that...
Sorry.
No. It's all right.
Friends are good even if
they lead different lives.
And besides,
she's not normal.
When she comes to Soul Society,
she might become a Soul Reaper.
Hado 33: Sokatsui!
Santenkesshun!
I'm not finished yet!
Kotenzanshun!
Don't hold back!
Your hesitation is your enemy!
O-Okay!
Hado 4:
Byakurai!
Santenkesshun!
By the way,
why are you here?
Do you have something
you have to do?
Oh yeah!
Here, here...
SEIREITEI NEWS
Here's this month's
Seireitei News.
There's a mail-order
catalog inside.
Huh? Why are
you doing this?
I'm overwhelmed...
Squad 10's captain and
lieutenant are both
in the World of the Living.
Squad 11's captain
is sleeping
and I don't know where
their lieutenant is.
BIO LAB SIX
DO NOT ENTER
I'LL KILL YOU IF YOU COME IN
Squad 12's captain and lieutenant
haven't come out from the lab.
I honestly never knew that
a captain's duties were so hectic.
Captain Tosen never asked
his subordinate to do things.
Now then,
I'll be on my way.
Come on...
relax here for a bit longer.
I told you, I'm busy.
I don't mind watching
two girls train, though.
Invite me again when I have
a little more free time.
Four months...
A short time to heal the soul...
It's an even shorter time
to get stronger.
I can only hope this temporary peace
lasts as long as possible.
No!
Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
You bastard!
Take this! Take this!
Break! Break!
Damn it!
Aw... This is so annoying!
Shut up!
Can't you be quiet
for a moment?!
But Fujikujaku is
so annoying!
He's so overbearing
and arrogant
and thinks that he's the most
beautiful person in the world.
It's terrible!
I don't think he'll ever
manifest himself!
Or rather...
I won't do it even if
he asks me to!
What are you talking about?
He's exactly like you.
My Haineko is selfish,
temperamental, lazy and stupid.
This is really what you would
call not getting along.
I hate this.
Wow...
You're exactly alike!
Rangiku, you're the type of
person who would look
at a picture of yourself and
say "this isn't how I look"!
What did you say, Yumichika?
Say that once more!
I'm Yumichika, so I will!
Both of you shut up!
Concentrate!
I'll send you back
to Soul Society!
Honestly...
Can't you even calm down and
communicate with your swords?
Those clouds
are moving fast...
Did you say something,
Madarame?
No...It's nothing.
Arrancars?! No way...
Don't you think this is
a little too early?!
It is indeed too early.
But we don't have any time
to think about why they've come.
Oh?
We've come to
a nice place.
There are some pretty strong
Spiritual Pressures wandering around.
I'll go there first.
What are you talking about?
They're Soul Reapers!
They're probably the reinforcements
from Soul Society
that Mr. Number Six
was talking about.
Right?
Oh! Sorry.
You're "formerly" Mr. Number Six.
The guy I want to kill
isn't in there!
Oh!
Hey. Wait, Grimmjow!
That bastard!
Leave him alone.
He's just an Espada dropout.
He can't do anything.
The guy I want to kill
isn't down there either.
Do you want to fight the guy
who cut off your arm,
the one who beat you up,
or the one who reflected your Cero?
All of them!
Hey! Let's go, newbie!
How long are you going
to just stand there?!
Another strange one's joined us.
A signal!
We've got an Arrancar signal!
What about the Gentei Kaijo?!
We've already
received permission!
What color is the signal?!
It's a crimson signal!
It's an Espada!
I'm Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya!
What a coincidence...
I'm also a ten!
I'm Arrancar Diez, Yammy!
Diez?! Number ten!
An Espada, huh?
You seem to know
a lot about it...
It seems you fought
someone pretty talkative.
Are you an Espada, too?
That's right...
My name is Luppi.
My rank is Seis.
I wonder if I
should kill him?
Let go of me!
I told you,
we still can't let you!
Your friends from Soul Society
are stationed here for things like this!
Leave it to them!
But I've been training
for times like this!
What good is it
if I don't go!
Let him go.
Hey! What are you thinking?!
Shinji!
Kuchiki!
Yes! I got word of it
just now!
The Kido Corps should be
opening the gate right now!
Hurry to the Senkaimon
in front of the barracks!
Yes!
Oh! Wait!
I also...
You can't, Inoue!
Huh?
You don't have
a Hell Butterfly.
Even if you go with me
through the Senkaimon,
you'll be sent to the Dangai,
Precipice World.
I've given out orders to stabilize
the walls of the Dangai, Precipice World,
so that you can
pass through it safely.
It'll take about a half hour,
but you can go to
the World of the Living then.
I know you're in a rush,
but it's important not to be
hasty at times like this.
Got that?
Yes.
Don't make that face, Inoue!
I'm going ahead.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay!
It can't be!
The Espada?!
And there are several of them...
It's too early!
Wasn't the Hogyoku supposed
to awaken later on?!
What in the world
is going on?!
Hey. I've been looking
for you, Soul Reaper.
That's my line.
I'll show you...
how much I've changed
in the past month!
Bankai!
A Bankai?
So what of it?
Did you forget?
Your bankai didn't do
anything against me!
Did you forget?
My attacks gave you that scar
when I used my Bankai!
I want to ask you
one thing, Grimmjow.
What happened
to your arm?
I discarded it.
It's unnecessary to kill you
with two arms.
I see.
Then I don't need to
hold back!
If you don't want to die, then don't!
Right now, the amount
of time I can maintain
a Hollow transformation
is eleven seconds flat!
I have to settle this
within that time!
URAHARA'S SHOP
I told you that you can't!
You've overused your powers!
I'll go. You rest here!
B-But...!
That's right,
it's as Abarai says.
But Abarai is
exhausted as well.
Both of you rest here.
Instead,
I'll go.
Are you really sure
I don't have to go?
You don't have to.
Instead of that, organize
the merchandise that I purchased.
You don't mean all those things
you bought, do you?
Kurodo, Noba, help him.
Leave it to me!
No problem.
I'll be off!
He ran away...
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers...
SEIREITEI NEWS
EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT
Aw... Busy, busy, busy,
busy, busy, busy, busy!
Is Rangiku's article finished?
Not yet!
What?!
I've brought Squad 8's article.
Thanks. I'm glad that Squad 8
always sticks to deadlines.
It's only natural.
There's an Arrancar signal
in the World of the Living!
It's an Espada!
What? I've got to go to cover
the event for a special feature!
That's not what
you're supposed to do...