The Tendoshu...
So they've gotten off their fat
asses to save their little toy.
It's rather unfortunate,
dog of the Hitotsubashi.
As I told you before,
nobody can ever judge me.
You are the ones who will be judged.
Lord Sadasada, it appears that
you've suffered a serious setback.
I won't bother asking
for an explanation.
No matter the reason,
it is not in the interest of
any of the parties involved
to allow further commotion on
the sacred palace grounds.
You must have your
reasons for rebelling,
but we will be intervening
in this matter.
We will take temporary
custody of Lord Sadasada.
Would you not agree that
his sentence should
be determined after
thorough investigation?
And while your cause
may have been just,
you must be punished for
disrupting the gover—
That won't be necessary.
I apologize for the
long trip you've made,
but this is a domestic affair.
It only makes sense for us
to settle this ourselves.
Sh-Shigeshige?!
Why, if it isn't the shogun.
I'm glad to see that you are safe.
But are you sure about that?
We proposed this solution
with you in mind.
Sheltered by your uncle, you
have grown to be a gentle lord.
Would you be capable of
executing the beloved retainers
who have turned their swords on you?
None of them have turned
their swords on me.
They may be branded traitors
and enemies of the state,
but I know what it is that
they strive to protect.
They do not follow laws written by
politicians for their own convenience.
They do not serve the
empty title of shogun.
They follow their convictions.
They serve their souls.
That is what they fight for.
You can sully their reputation, but
you cannot tarnish their hearts.
If I were to call that a crime
and punish them for it...
My entire army would become criminals
for turning their swords
on their foolish ruler.
If I tried to punish them all,
this nation would crumble.
Shigeshige! You bastard!
They have committed no crime.
The blame lies with the shogun family
that was unworthy of ruling them.
Uncle, I am prepared to accept
responsibility for failing to stop you.
Resignation
We can go to hell together.
A-Are you going to give up
your position as shogun?!
Please leave.
This is
Samurai Country.
Unsetting Moon
You did a spectacular job, Sasaki-dono.
Nobunobu-sama was impressed by
the devotion you demonstrated
by carrying out your
mission while injured.
You will be rewarded once
the Hitotsubashi faction
establishes a new government.
Our greatest enemy, Sadasada, has been
imprisoned after his
crimes were exposed.
And what's amazing is
that Shigeshige stepped
Resignation
down as shogun to take him down.
We are now in position
to name Nobunobu-sama as
the next shogun with ease.
Nezu-dono, this is a
government hospital.
There are ears everywhere.
Impossible. The Hitotsubashi's
time has come.
Nobody would dare to
stand against us now.
I beg to differ.
The walls have ears and
the doors have eyes.
And there are...
...fairies on your shoulders.
Demons!
I must get going!
Take care!
I never dreamed that you
would come visit me.
It appears that despite your appearance,
you have the hearts of fairies.
Well, you're lined up to be
the next police commissioner.
Why not start kissing some ass?
We'll come to your funeral.
Have you come to take my life after
realizing you were being used?
We would be happy to let you use us
if it meant a tyrant could be toppled,
but if your goal was to make our lord
take the fall to protect
us, we'll take steps.
Loyalty to your lord?
Topple tyrants?
Is that truly why you
took up your swords?
If you believe I orchestrated the
shogun's fall for the sake
of the Hitotsubashi faction,
you are sorely mistaken.
Not even an elite could have
predicted this would happen.
To think that the ruler
of a nation gave up his position
for the sake of a mere samurai.
To think that the wild monkeys
would take up their swords
for an ancient promise.
That man defies all reason.
That Sakata Gintoki...
I hope that capricious girl's stubborn streak
wasn't a result of his bad influence.
What do you say, Nobume-san?
Unfortunately, I'm not naive
enough to believe that
replacing the shogun
will change this world.
Instead of depending
on foreign countries,
we should build a nation
that can compete with them.
That is the dream of the
Hitotsubashi's leader,
but I'm not one to go in
for such a pipe dream.
I have much bigger plans in mind.
You don't need to worry.
The Tendoshu should
make their move soon.
You should be guarding Sadasada,
not hanging out here.
I had a report from my men.
The crow's carcass vanished.
Sadasada failed us.
He was so obsessed with
maintaining power that he
failed to notice the foundations
crumble beneath him.
It would be detrimental to
restore him to power now.
A fool who could not keep
up with Hitotsubashi
holds no value as a
ruler in the first place.
We should have cut that worthless
puppet loose sooner.
While he may hold no value as a
puppet, he can still serve as bait.
Have you returned, messenger
of the heavens, Yatagarasu?
It took a while to restore my
meridians and keep myself alive.
Who would be capable of
injuring you so severely?
A demon who fell for the bait.
Ah, a demon...
Sadasada is a figurehead
of the Joi suppression.
We need him to draw out certain foes.
There is no need to fear
the Hitotsubashi faction.
They are nothing more than
puppets, much like Sadasada.
The ones using this chance to sneak
into the heart of the country...
They are our true enemies.
And we need that puppet to
bring out those demons?
It took you long enough.
I'd grown tired of waiting.
I was thinking that the Tendoshu
had finally abandoned me.
Now, unlock this door and release me.
It's too bad, Shigeshige!
You will never get to
judge me! No one will!
Not even the heavens can judge me!
Huh?
That's right.
You won't be judged by the
shogun or the heavens.
You will be judged
by me.
Y-You're...
Don't bother trying to remember me
since I'll bring the Tendoshu
and those worthless crows...
No...
I'll bring the heads of every person on
this planet down to hell with me.
Say hello
to Sensei for me.
Yes.
Those demons are our true enemies.
The students of Shoyo.
It appears that you were
a step too late, Oboro.
So you're not fooling around,
Mukuro...
No, you go by the name Imai Nobume now.
Once, you served the heavens and
were named one of the Naraku
Three at a young age,
yet you now side with a student
of Shoyo and turn your
blade on the heavens?
Isaburo said he would go along
with that man's grand scheme.
So I will do the same.
I see.
Then one of us will have
our feathers plucked
the next time we meet.
Wait.
Were those two anything like Shoyo?
No.
One was trying to protect
Shoyo's legacy.
The other was trying to
destroy Shoyo's legacy.
But they had one thing in common.
They both
had such sorrow in their eyes.
I suppose this is karma.
A man who built an empire
through assassination
was finished by an assassin.
Well, it could get ugly if the
public learned this happened
right after that big ruckus,
so the official announcement will
be that he died of illness.
I can understand that
you're not happy about it,
but we've been given orders.
What about the killer?
Well, I can't tell if
they're even interested
in finding out who it was.
Did the Tendoshu kill him
so he couldn't talk?
After they mobilized all those
people to rescue Sadasada?
I'm pretty sure that
the Tendoshu were still
looking for a chance to
take back Sadasada.
The assassination was
carried out despite that.
No...
It was probably meant
as a declaration of war
from the Hitotsubashi to the Tendoshu.
To prove it, we have an imperial
decree from the Emperor.
What? Shogun-sama's
resignation was denied?
Yes.
My brother has been
ordered to continue
supporting the Bakufu
now that our uncle is gone.
Oh, that's great!
We were worried that Sho-chan
quit because of us.
Those fools are probably thrilled,
but it's obvious that the
Tendoshu were behind this act.
Which means that the Tendoshu see
the Hitotsubashi as their enemy.
Shigeshige has only been set
up as an interim ruler.
Does the Hitotsubashi faction
intend to fight the Tendoshu
to take control of the government?
Well, I don't know if they're
trying to take control,
That's mine.
or if they want to get rid of the
Bakufu and throw the world into chaos.
Either way, there's a lot
of action in the shadows.
Wait. If the Bakufu's a mess
right now, that old man is...
He managed to survive.
But he probably can't
step outside the palace,
much less visit Yoshiwara.
His health is certainly a concern,
but the palace is on lockdown,
and there are even guards
watching the shogun.
No one is allowed to enter or leave.
Your Highness, it is
time for you to return.
Nobume-san...
That look won't help.
Well, I figured this would happen.
Seriously, what were we fighting for?
The doctor said that she won't
make it through the night.
This may be the last moon
Lady Suzuran ever waits for.
Don't be sad.
Suzuran-san and the rest of
you all tried your best.
Did you think that I didn't
know you were sneaking around?
Honestly, that was quite
a mess you caused.
I was quite worried since you've
started to act like Gin-san.
That's why I tried to
keep my mouth shut,
but I guess it didn't matter in the end.
Hinowa, did you know who
Suzuran was waiting for?
Hard to say. But considering
how long she's waited,
he must have been a wonderful man.
That much I do know.
Isn't that right, Suzuran-san?
Hinowa-chan, could you
help me with my makeup?
It's time to fulfill our promise.
Where are you going at this late hour?
You're running off to amuse yourself
in Yoshiwara with that body?
You'll die.
I can't afford any further commotion.
Please restrain yourself
and return to your room.
I understand that I'm
disobeying orders.
If you intend to cut me down, go ahead.
I no longer have any arms
for your blade to take.
You can help yourself
to my legs or head.
However, those young people helped
revive the promise we once made.
The thread tied to my soul
cannot be severed by any blade.
Normally, I would forgive an elderly
man's desire to fool around,
but the circumstances will not allow it.
I cannot allow anything to
happen that could potentially
aggravate the tense political situation.
I will warn you one more time.
Please return to your room.
Okay, all done.
You look beautiful, Suzuran-san.
Every girl wants to look pretty
for the man she loves.
Now, Tsukuyo.
Bring the kimono.
What are you doing?
Tsukuyo?
Tsukuyo-chan, did you make that
promise with your special man?
No...
Was it an important promise?
We'll bring the old man
back to Suzuran together.
Then you should believe in it.
A good man will always
keep his promise.
Isn't that right?
Yeah...
You're right.
What?
How did you get in here?
If you wanna play Kick the
Can, follow the finger!
Me!
Wh—
What are you people doing?
Why is the shogun here?
This is too many people to
use rock-paper-scissors,
so Hijikata can be It.
Screw that!
Look at all these people!
That would be torture!
Enough.
I've seen enough internal strife.
As shogun, I will choose
someone to be It.
Grampy, if you will?
Please stop this.
You've allowed outsiders inside,
and now you're abandoning
your responsibility?
Go grab the can.
It probably flew all
the way to Yoshiwara.
Okay, everybody hide.
I loathe the moon.
With nightfall, it brings you to me,
but it also takes you from
me when dawn breaks.
I wish the moon would never leave us.
Then you would always be here with me.
The moon will come with the night again.
And someday, when it does,
I will take you with me in the morning.
Wait before the cherry blossom tree
on the night of the next full moon.
Do you promise?
I promise.
Promise.
You
finally came.
The final moon brought you to me.
But I must apologize.
Both the cherry blossoms and I have
withered during the long wait.
What are you talking about?
Nothing has changed.
The cherry blossoms are every bit
as beautiful as they once were.
Maizo-sama...
Am I dreaming?
Will you be gone when the moon leaves
and I wake up in the morning?
No, the moon tonight will never set.
You will never awaken from this dream.
We will always,
always,
be together.
I promise.
We have an announcement to make
on the progress of the movie!
If the next image shows five or
six storyboard booklets,
we're well on our way.
Take it away!
Huh?
Huh...
What...
Er?
That's odd?