In the Rukon district,
incidences of mysterious deaths
occurred among the Soul Society
where people vanished,
leaving just their clothes behind.
Squad 9 was investigating
in the field
when someone attacked them.
Captain Kensei Muguruma and
Lieutenant Mashiro Kuna's
Spiritual Pressure disappeared.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
determined
that a worst-case scenario
had occurred.
Urahara, who had sent
Lieutenant Hiyori Sarugaki to
the scene following the request
by the aforementioned Squad 9,
tries to go after her, but…
Let me…go there, please!
No.
My second-in-command is
headed there now!
I must…
Kisuke!
You're making a scene.
Pull yourself together!
Didn't you make the choice
to send her?!
Can't you see that your panic
is an insult to her?!
Ultimately, however, five members:
captain of Squad 3,
Rojuro Ohtoribashi,
captain of Squad 5,
Shinji Hirako,
captain of Squad 7,
Love Aikawa,
Hachigen Ushoda,
lieutenant of the Kido Corps,
and Lisa Yadomaru, lieutenant of
Squad 9, are chosen to go.
When the members arrive,
they are confronted
by an abnormal figure.
Shinji!
Are you all right, Hiyori?!
K-Kensei!
What's going on with that?
Is that really Kensei?
That mask…
That Spiritual Pressure…
It is almost like he's a Hollow!
I'm not sure, either.
Maybe it's Kensei, maybe it's not.
Anyway, what's certain is we'll die
if we don't draw our swords.
What Shinji and the others
saw was Kensei,
whose Spiritual Pressure and
appearance had been transformed
into something resembling a Hollow.
Kensei, who had lost himself,
attacked.
Reluctantly, Hirako and
the others fought back.
However, Kensei displayed
extraordinary power,
and when Mashiro, who had
also been transformed, joined in,
the five gradually began
losing the fight.
Behind you, Rose!
Gochu Tekkan.
Bakudo 63: Sajosabaku.
Hey! Thank you for your rounds.
C-Captain Kyoraku?!
What's the matter?
Why're you out at this hour?
Well, I had a bit of
trouble falling asleep.
Maybe I'm thinking too much?
– Huh?!
Nothing.
It seems like Lieutenant Aizen
had trouble falling asleep too.
– Good night, Lieutenant Aizen!
You men should call it
a night yourselves.
– Good night, Captain Kyoraku!
'Night.
Huh?
Excuse me.
Um…
Nanao Ise…right?
Huh?! Y-Yes, sir!
I'm honored that
you remembered me!
Yes.
Well, you are the youngest child
we have here now.
You see, I remember the names
of every young girl here.
Besides, you came to
see me every month.
Oh.
That's right.
Today's the first of the month.
Yes.
That is why I thought
I'd like to read
with Lieutenant Yadomaru
again this month.
I see.
But, I'm sorry.
Lisa isn't here tonight.
Why?
She's on an important mission.
But don't worry.
She'll be back in the morning.
I'm sure of it.
Stop it.
Kensei, you weren't the kind of
weakling who would strike a girl.
Right?
Hey, are you okay, Lisa?
I'm okay.
You're not okay.
Quiet.
Anyway, at this rate, either way,
we're not going to last.
Hachi…
Isn't there any other way?
There is.
However…
He easily broke through Sajosabaku.
This time, we'll have to go at him
with maximum force.
To do that, I'll need
all of you to create
a sure-fire opportunity for me
to use a Bakudo.
However, my Bakudo may take us all
along with it, as well.
Is that all?
Love…
I'll draw him to me.
While I'm doing that,
capture Kensei!
I'm going too!
Me too.
With those injuries?
Are you crazy?
I can do it alone.
You watch my back.
Show off!
Look who's talking!
Rose!
I know!
How solid can he be?!
Hachi!
Bakudo 99!
Kin!
A Nineties-level Bakudo
without an incantation, eh?
Gotta hand it to you.
I overextended myself…a bit.
Okay then.
What shall we do now?
Can't you do something using Kido?
Even if you want me to,
if I don't know the cause,
there's nothing I can do.
What's the matter, Hiyori?
Are you okay?
Hachi, heal this one for starters.
Shin…
Shinji…
Let go of…
me!
Hiyori!
What the hell's going on?!
Wha—?
No!
This is…
Lisa!
Rose! Hachi!
You're…
Tosen!
Why did you do that to Kensei?
You betrayed him…
Your own captain?!
He didn't betray him.
He is loyal.
He just…
loyally followed
my orders, that's all.
Please don't hold it against him,
Captain Hirako.
Ai…zen.
I should've known it was you.
So you were on to me?
You're good.
Of course I am.
Since when?
From the time you were still
in your mother's womb.
I see.
I've always felt that you were
someone dangerous.
Someone who couldn't be trusted.
That's why I chose you
as my lieutenant.
I did it to keep an eye you, Aizen!
Yes, I appreciate that,
Captain Hirako.
Thanks to your deep distrust of me,
you didn't realize.
I just told you that I did.
No.
You didn't realize.
During this past month…
that wasn't me…
who has been following you.
What?!
I am able to make someone
mistake any phenomenon
for something else at will.
That is the true power of
my Zanpakuto, Kyokasuigetsu.
I refer to its power as…
"Complete Hypnosis."
Complete hypnosis, you say?!
You are a sharp man,
Captain Hirako.
If you had received me
as your second-in-command
as other captains ordinarily do,
perhaps you may have
seen through me.
However, you did not.
Because you did not trust me,
you never got closer
than a certain distance,
never opening up to me,
or giving me information,
and never tried to
get closer to me.
That's why you never realized.
Even if I switched places with
a completely different person.
I had the man who took my place
memorize everything
about my normal behavior patterns
and my patterns of interaction
when dealing with you and
other squad members and captains.
If you understood me deeply,
even slight differences
in habits or behaviors
would have seemed
out of place to you.
You are lying there
defeated because
you remained totally
unfamiliar with me.
Do you understand now?
Captain Hirako?
Aizen…
And one more thing.
Earlier, you said
you chose me as your lieutenant
to keep an eye on me.
You are mistaken.
What?!
Just as a captain has the
right to select his lieutenant,
squad members have
the right to refuse an assignment.
While that right is
very rarely exercised,
I also had the choice of not
becoming your lieutenant.
Why didn't I do that?
Because it was the ideal situation.
Your excessive suspicion and
wariness of me
was truly ideal for my plan.
Do you understand?
You did not choose me.
I chose you, Captain Hirako.
Maybe you should be apologizing
to your friends.
Because you were chosen by me,
you ended up down there on
the ground with your friends.
Aizen…
Thank you for going for
my cheap taunt.
Damn it!
You're doing this to me too?
Aizen!
Damn it!
You're doing this to me too?
Aizen!
What is this?!
As we thought,
it looks like an agitated state
accelerates the Hollowfication.
Hollowfication?!
What is that supposed to mean?
You don't need to know.
Sh-Shinji?
Kaname.
Yes, sir.
Stop!
I don't know what's going on.
But if you think everything will
go according to your plan,
you're gravely mistaken.
Oh.
Even though the Hollowfication
has progressed that far…
Come to think of it,
didn't Aizen just say…
As we thought,
it looks like an agitated state
accelerates the Hollowfication.
Which means that
if I maintain my composure,
this strange process
won't progress?!
What shall we do?
You can go ahead and continue.
We'll just have one less sample.
So I'm a sample?
You say interesting things.
Looks like he's losing.
Yeah, it looks that way.
What is this?!
I don't know what's happening.
Am I suffering, or…
It's almost as if someone other
than me is doing the fighting.
It's no wonder we had
a hard time dealing with Kensei,
even in groups.
But at this rate,
I may have a chance!
I'm sorry.
I will finish him right now.
There's no need to worry, Kaname.
I expected this to happen.
Besides…
The speed at which
Hollowfication occurs
differs from individual
to individual.
That was quite
an interesting sight.
But that's as far as you go,
it would seem.
Let's end it, Captain Hirako.
In the end, remember one thing.
Betrayal you can see is trivial.
What is truly frightening is
betrayal you cannot see,
Captain Hirako.
Goodbye.
You people were
wonderful test subjects.
Damn it!
Well…
What an interesting guest.
The Past Arc finally comes
to an end next week!
I get to appear at last!
You wish, Ichigo.
It seems there will be another
story following the Past Arc.
What? You mean?
You'll be stuck in the Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers
for some time to come.
Who is the main character of
this anime supposed to be?!
The Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
There are times when we provide
a place for Soul Reapers
who come to
the World of the Living.
Sorry I'm late.
No problem,
we were just about to start.
Now,
with regard to the next activity of
the Men's Soul Reaper Association…
Why're you guys holding
your meeting here?!
There's no meeting hall that
the Soul Society will let us use!
Please go home.