Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Good evening, everyone.
For this week's
"Burarei"
we're broadcasting live from
an abandoned hospital in Karakura
where ghostly screams are heard.
What will we witness tonight?
And now,
let us welcome him to the stage!
The charismatic medium of
this new century...
The messenger from the Underworld...
Mister...Don...Kan'onji!
Spirits…are always…
with you!
Live Broadcast of
Special Program
Checking Out Spiritual Hot Spots:
Ghostly Screams in an Abandoned Hospital
Bohahahaha!
Huh? There's almost no reaction.
Don't you
know what this means?
B-Burarei...
Correct! Isn't it a fun show?
Then, Ichigo, can you join...
– Bohaha--
– Banzai!
T-Tatsuki! What is it?
C'mon, I'll join you on
the "Bohaha" thing.
Why…?
Yo! Ichigo!
– Asano here.
– And Mizuiro.
Bohahaha!
Not going?! Why?!
It's the best Japanese TV
program on!
And it's coming to Karakura Town for
a live broadcast!
You'd have to be dead to be
a citizen of this town and not go!
So I'm a zombie.
Big deal. Now, get lost.
I even asked Rukia!
Hello Ichigo.
Look, Rukia... Bohahaha!
Oh no... I'm too embarrassed to do it.
Oh come on, Rukia. Do it.
That woman!
She's adding to her repertoire
of tricks.
Kan'onji!
He’s so cool!
How are you all?
I'll let you babies listen to
the cries of the spirits tonight!
Well, Mr. Kan'onji?
How is this place?
This place reeks with
the smell of spirits.
This really...
Smells like bad spirits!
Bohahaha!
Cut to commercial!
I hate shows about spirits.
Everyone, please follow the guide to
the spirit purification hall!
Kurosaki!
Huh?
Umm… I'm sorry about the other day.
For what?
Tatsuki said that you don't like these kinds
of programs.
I didn't know.
It's all right.
I don't mind.
Bohahahahaha!
Look at those guys,
even though they know
I hate it.
But you still came.
Why is that?
My dad and sister are
big fans of this show.
And that's why you came?
I guess. Couldn't just let them come alone.
You're very kind, Kurosaki.
Huh? Isn't it normal?
Uh-huh, you're right. It's normal.
Normal.
Hey Orihime!
We're leaving you behind!
Tatsuki, wait!
Geez...all these people!
All caught up in this.
What's the matter, Ichigo?
Bohahaha!
Why you--!
Now now, what's that serious look for?
Take advantage of this and enjoy it.
Shut up, I'm always like this.
You must be exhausted from school
and Soul Reaper work.
There will be hard battles ahead.
Use this opportunity to spread your wings.
Rukia, you…
By the way,
just what is this festival about?
You came along without knowing?!
Geez, are there really spirits in an
abandoned hospital like this?
Why?
If there were,
wouldn't you Soul Reapers
have helped it cross over?
Not necessarily.
Spirits that inhabit a place
like this
are usually Fixed-location
jibaku spirits.
Since these spirits assimilate
into the earth,
they're rarely detected by
the Soul Society or Soul Reapers.
There is only one condition
under which Fixed-location
jibaku spirits show themselves.
When humans invade their territory.
What's the matter, Chad?
Do you hear something?
Huh?
C-Cut it out, Chad.
You're giving me the creeps.
Maybe it's just your imagination.
Maybe... Sorry, I'm just imagining it.
I shouldn't have come, after all.
Huh? What's wrong, Karin?
Nothing.
It's the cry of
a Fixed-location jibaku spirit.
It seems there is one, after all.
It's not a Hollow's cry?
You're aware that the occurrence of
Hollows follows several patterns.
One is when
a Fixed-location jibaku spirit
who feels a strong attachment
to this world is left alone...
and ends up becoming a Hollow.
Such as this spirit.
Then he’s…
called a Plus, one on the verge of
becoming a Hollow...
a Demi-Hollow.
He feels like a Hollow to me,
that's for sure.
But he's not wearing that white mask.
Also, the hole in his chest
isn't fully opened yet.
The hole in a Hollow's chest
signifies that the heart is lost
and has become a mass
of simple instincts.
The skull-shaped white mask shields
the bared instincts from the outside world.
Neither of these is necessary
if the heart is still intact.
When a human dies,
the chain of fate is
severed from the body.
Usually the spirit
waits for a Soul Reaper to guide it,
but if they have regrets and
cannot let go,
their chains become bound to
the object of their regret.
This Demi-Hollow's heart
is being held by the hospital.
This hospital is mine!
I won't let anyone
have it!
You guys better not come in!
I'm going to become a rich man here!
– And I'm gonna ride a pink Cadillac,
– What a disgusting spirit!
– and drink pink Dom Perignon!
– Coming back from commercial!
Something's about to begin!
Spirits are always with you!
– Bohahaha!
Hey, is this okay?!
Don't get excited.
It usually takes several
months to become a Hollow.
Now then, the time has come
for Mr. Kan'onji's purification
of the spirit!
We don't want the spirit
to become agitated
with this many people around.
We can do the Konso after
the festival.
But...
There is a frightening scream
just before one becomes a Hollow,
it will be in much pain.
Does that Demi-Hollow look to be
suffering to you?
Huh? Who are you?!
Are you going to taint
my hospital, too?!
You've got guts!
Look at that weird hat!!
Doesn't look like it to me.
You see?
Unless the partially closed hole in
his chest is damaged in some way,
it'll take another half
a year to become a Hollow.
I'll let you cross
over peacefully, baby!
Ohhh!
There it is! The Super Spirit Cane!
For him to use it at
this early stage is truly unusual!
What's he doing?!
That fool!
It will only speed up the process
of becoming a Hollow!
Yes!
Kiru-kiru-au-nan, au-maku-kiru-nan!
Stop it!
What's that guy doing?
Security! Hurry it up!
This way! Transform into a Soul Reaper!
Get her!
Let go!
No!
Let me go, dammit!
Who did that?!
Hello…
Geta clogs and hat dude?
Don't just sit there.
Hurry and go!
R-Right!
Hey! What happened?!
Why are you here?
Yes?
Move, leave this to me.
Hey you!
Stop it!
What?!
Mr. Kan'onji is flying
through the air!
W-What's with you, boy?!
Can you see me too?
Of course!
I'm the charismatic medium of
this new century!
I see! You're dead,
and you're a fan, huh, boy?
You're gonna get it, punk!
Don't tell me I'm too late?!
He disappeared?!
Yeah! Mission complete!
– No way!
– The soul purification is complete!
No...
In the instant a Demi-Hollow turns
into a Hollow,
it disperses then reforms
in another location.
Furthermore, if his heart was held
by this place...
Kan'onji! Kan'onji! Kan'onji!
Yeah! Thank you!
Above you, Ichigo!
Look up!
W-What is that?!
That's called a Hollow, and...
Hmm...
I feel it, I feel it!
It reeks of a super
dangerous spirit...
I get it!
You must be the evil boss come to
avenge that soul!
Not really...
T-The pain... Let me eat you!
– Hold it!
– Huh?!
Run, boy!
Come on, bad spirit!
Don Kan'onji, the charismatic medium
of the new century, will take you on!
I'll devour you!
What're you doing?!
Why didn't you run away, boy?
You're the one who
should run away!
Huh? Run?! What are you saying?
Damn!
Just as I thought.
Wonderful!
Although the conditions
are the worst.
So, what will you do?
Golden chance!
Get away!
What's going on?!
– Mr. Kan'onji did some unusual moves...
– I see...
– then went into the building!
– So that's how you're going to fight.
The glass at the entrance is shattered,
and the walls are destroyed.
Mr. Kan'onji must be battling
with some unknown force!
Don't worry.
A Hollow of that level won't
be a problem for Kurosaki.
But...!
It's not good to create
too much of a fuss.
Besides, Kan'onji seems to have
a bit of power.
Let's let them handle it.
W-Why are we running away, boy?!
You're the one who said to run!
I meant only for you to run!
I cannot run away!
Huh?!
Why should I run while you stay?!
Explain that!
Well...
Well, I...
I am the hero, that's why!
Huh?
Are you aware of the ratings
that my show pulls in?
I'm not gonna bother answering.
Correct! 25%.
One in every four citizens
watches my show.
And many of those viewers...
are children!
The children watch my every move
and become inspired.
They see me stand up to evil spirits and
understand what courage is.
Do you understand, boy?
I cannot run away
when these children are watching!
Kan'onji...you're...
Now, let's go back and
fight that monster.
Wha--?!
Fool! You can't!
What if the audience gets involved?!
That spirit is going after people with
high spiritual energy,
like you and me.
Without a doubt,
it's gonna come after us.
And if we fight here,
at least no one in the
audience will get hurt!
Boy...
I'm amazed...
You've thought it through
that far?
– Boy!
– Hold it!
It's here!
Let me eat you!
Huh?!
Not enough room!
Damn! This room is too small
to use my Zanpaku-to!
W-What's this?!
I can't get it off!
Damn! I can't get him!
Huh?
Arghh! Hey!
Are you all right, boy?!
He came again!
Huh?
Run! Kan'onji!
D-Dammit!
H-Hey...!
Kan'onji…
Are you hurt, boy?
Get outta here!
You can't handle him!
Boy!
Huh?!
I know my power,
and I know the difference in power
between the enemy and myself.
But I have been impressed by you.
You put the safety of others first.
Great!
You are my comrade,
let me call you "friend."
Err...that's all right.
Arghh! Kan’onji Style
Ultimate Technique!
Cannon Ball!
Kan'onji!
Even if this body is blown apart,
if I can die as a shield
for the kids of the future,
I shall have no regrets in life.
Friend!
Hold it!
Sorry, but this is the end!
You did it!
Great! Magnificent! Magnificent!
Magnifi--!
Kan’onji.
Don't get too excited.
Huh? Why, boy?
You defeated the monster!
You should rejoice! Huh?
What?!
No way! He's the one who...
What's this?
That's a Hollow.
When the chain that links
his soul is broken and
a hole opens up in his chest,
the spirit becomes a monster without
conscience, a Hollow.
Chest? Hole?
No...
What have I been doing
all this time?
I am ashamed of myself.
Hey, quit crying, Hero...
Everyone's waiting.
What's wrong?
Answer their cheers.
That's a hero's duty, right?
Boy...
Oh! Mr. Kan'onji's soul purification
seems to be over!
Mission Complete! Bohahaha!
Bohahaha!
Way to go, Kan'onji!
Boy, that was a magnificent battle.
I admire your courage and power.
Lend me your strength from now on, too.
Oh, well...once in a while, sure.
Thank you.
From today, you are…
my number one pupil!
That's a demotion!
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Rukia and I headed out to
exterminate Hollows,
– but someone beat us to it.
– Bohahaha! I'm Don Kan'onji!
Now everyone repeat after me!
– A mysterious figure watches us...
– Bohahaha!
I can't hear you!
– Shut up, will you?!
– One more time!
– Please, go home, I'm begging you!
– Bohahaha!