Hilda, in lieu of thanks,
let me give you a warning.
It is true that the Great Demon Lord
wishes the brothers to work together.
We are fully supportive of that.
But the Master's retainers
surely think differently.
Will it be Lord En or Beelze-sama
who takes the greatest glory?
They think this is a test to see who would
be better suited to inherit the throne.
Some might appear who would go to extreme
measures to cause harm to Beelze-sama...
Behemoth...
The 34 Pillar Division.
Yeah... They're strong, but
a little... in the head.
So anyway, Oga, it was?
My servants might be coming
to destroy you pretty soon.
Well, do your best!
Man, what a pain...
Hey, hey! This is a new product!
Steamed strawberry chocolate natto rolls!
Sounds like it'd go well with...
...punch!
My steamed strawberry chocolate natto roll!
No Shirt, No Shoes, No Assassins.
Madame Aoi, you're like
super ennui and stuff!
Is that one of those "sighs
of a girl in love" things?
Hey! Don't be ridiculous!
Demons, huh?
Tora!
I've given Izuma-kun the message.
Yeah, thanks for that.
But you know how he is...
I can't tell if he'll really come or not.
He'll come. For sure.
You still think the same way
you did when we were kids.
Take this!
It's all about the fighting with you...
What the heck is this?
Who the hell chucked this thing?
Tora, you stink!
Hey! Shizuka!
God damn it!
Go! Do it, do it...
Total defeat once again!
Satura, give me money!
We're all out!
We're what?!
You little brat! Stop bein' so damn loud!
And who do you think you are?
I'm the guy who kicked your butt
10 times in a row, little twerp!
You suck, big time!
I am a gaming genius!
If I don't win, that's because there's
something wrong with the game!
I can't let that stand, can I?
Himekawa, you bastard! What're
you doin' showin' up everywhere?
Think you're a cockroach or somethin'?
Oh? Although this happens to
be an arcade my family owns...
So isn't it you coming
on my turf to play games?
What's that, punk?
Who're you callin' a punk, punk?
Oh?
Eh?
There is no game in the
world that I cannot win!
Yeah, but you majorly suck.
Missy here said you ain't
got no money left, remember?
Just go home to mommy already!
Missy?
Kids like you should practice at home.
I don't wanna.
A true ruler goes forth
to perfect his skills!
I am royalty who invites friendly
tête-à-têtes with the lowly commoners!
What? Is he right in the head?
There sure are a lot of
weirdos in this town...
Hey, brat. Then why don't you
play online games at home?
Online games?
Dialog box.
Access point.
Subdirectory.
Access time.
Hard disk password.
Virtualization.
Got all that?
Stop wastin' our time!
What a revolution!
Humans may be lowly bugs not worthy
of being squashed under our feet,
but I'll give 'em credit for their games!
Okay! Satura, Isabella, Yolda!
Let's go right now to Akihabara or wherever!
But I told you, we're out of money!
H-H-Hey, Lord En!
Lord En!
What's with that guy?
Kids these days.
Japanese ramen really is good.
Whoopsie...
You'll pay dearly for that.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Beel-chan, today's dinner
is going to be a real treat!
It's Hilda-chan's special croquettes!
Mom's going to roll up her
sleeves and teach her!
I was thinking that it'd
be good for the Master
to have some Human World
croquettes once in a while.
I will roll up my sleeves and be taught!
I'm not following in the slightest.
Fine, whatever! Try
helping once in a while!
Here, put this on.
Don't go joking. Why should I wear that?
Even though Tatsumi brought back
a wife and kid out of the blue,
Mother tried her best to just accept
it and make the best of things, but...
He doesn't have any concept of how hard
Mother yearns to form the bonds of family!
Okay! I get it!
Right! Now, take this...
That's good, Hilda-chan. Now,
continuing from before...
First, please check if the
potatoes are boiled yet.
H-Hilda-chan, what?! Why is it red?!
Unless you boil them in the lifeblood
of a Demon Pleated Blowfish,
you can't kill off the potatoes, yes?
They're tough little suckers.
We're not doing Macao-style tonight!
We'll start over.
Oh, we don't have any more potatoes.
Tatsumi, go buy some for me.
Me?
You should make Hilda go!
Then the both of you go, if you please!
What's her problem?
Come on, Hilda... Let's go.
I really just don't get it.
Demons, huh?
What are they?
If it isn't Kunieda-san...
Izuma-senpai...
Still studying this late?
No wonder you're Ishiyama's
Class Representative.
You're a serious scholar.
That's not it exactly...
But be careful.
There are some things in this
world it's best not to know.
Oh, look at the time.
Be careful on your way home.
Later.
What's gotten into you all of a
sudden, trying to learn how to cook?
I thought it would please the Master.
And...
Because I owe your mother
for her hospitality.
I thought it would be good
to help her sometimes.
Human World croquettes aren't so bad.
Demons, huh?
I wonder what Demons eat?
Well, compared to Demon World croquettes
ours don't bite, or run away, or fly...
I'd say they win on those points.
You think?
But the enjoyment is in rounding
them up, and cutting them down...
The next time we meet, I'll
just ask him straight out.
What do they eat?
Croquettes.
It's cold... The nights have
definitely gotten chilly.
You still going to wait, Tora?
I told you I gave him the invitation
but don't know if he'll come!
And I told you, you don't
have to wait with me.
This is my fight.
Put it on.
Sheesh.
It's always fighting with you.
You're such a little kid.
I should warn you.
He's already the current master of the Izuma
8 Spirits Style at his age.  The master!
I know. Stop yakking about it.
This is the deciding match.
Hey there, you're late!
Let's fight!
U-Um, Oga...
Huh?
Demons... They can... eat croquettes?
Yeah. They're Baby Beel's favorite.
Then, natto and stuff too?
You can eat it. Right, Baby Beel?
Wow.
There are a lot of foreigners
who can't stand the stuff...
Well, he's not really a foreigner, after all.
O-Oh, I see your point.
I'm heading this way, so...
Oh, I see.
Hey, Kunieda.
Will you come and try some
croquettes I make sometime?
Sure. Thanks.
I'll look forward to that.
Kunieda?
Get down!
What's this?
Hey there.
So this fool is the
Youngest's Contract Holder?
Who the hell are you?
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division.
One of the best fighting
tribes in the Demon World...
This is the worst case.
I never expected them to come this fast.
You are called Hildegarde, yes?
You are mistaken.
We are not one of the best...
We are the best in the Demon World.
Kunieda!
My name is Hecados!
The 8th Pillar of Behemoth's
34 Pillar Division.
Like I care!
Let her down, jerk!
She keeps getting knocked out recently...
And wait, how are you
doing that? That's creepy!
I'll make this woman be my Contract Holder.
You already know this.
For we demons to wield our
true power in the Human World,
we must form a contract with a human.
Of course, it can't be with just anyone...
It must be someone strong and compatible...
This woman seems to be quite the catch.
This is excellent...
I can get a head start on everyone else.
Other Demons are coming?
Or wait... They're already
waiting in ambush?!
Honestly, your toughness is
going to give me nightmares.
This is the first time you've
gotten me to go all out.
All out? That's BS!
You're still holdin' back!
I can tell that much!
Bring it on! I'm seriously gettin' riled up.
What's he saying? He's already a wreck!
You're a strange man.
The more I fight you, the
more I fall into your pace...
This is gettin' a little fun...
Let's make things even more
entertaining! Shall we?
Izuma-kun...
It might be okay, since it's you...
Here I go, Tojo Hidetora!
What the hell is that?!
Izuma-kun?
This is my...
...full power!
You there... Do you know what's required
for a Demon and a human to form a contract?
What's with this guy?
Something needed for a contract
between Demon and human?
If I can't impress him here, I'm screwed!
Hey, come on... I've had a Demon
Lord on my back for 6 months now...
You seriously think I don't know that?
Oh?
A smile!
Blood.
A blood contract.
Since long ago, Demons have taken human
blood into their bodies and followed human orders.
I knew that!
When I said "smile," I meant "blood"!
Don't think me a fool!
Fool.
Wait, blood?!
You must have presented your
blood to the Youngest somehow.
Did I do that?
He's been splattered with the blood
of my victims quite a lot, but...
Oga.
If we let him form a contract, we're through.
Will you draw his attention for me?
I will take Kunieda back during that chance.
Oh? What's that supposed
to mean, Demon Maidservant?
You mean that we'd be evenly matched
prior to my forming a contract?
Fascinating. Let's test that.
I'll show you the difference between us.
This is our chance. He's
still underestimating us.
Or more succinctly, this
is our only chance...
Here we go!
Uh, don't wanna.
I don't wanna just draw his attention.
He's come all this way, so let's
fight him for real and pay him back!
Agree, Baby Beel?
Simpleton!
I am telling you he is not an opponent
you can fight at your level!
Um, I wasn't trying to say
it was your fault, Master...
Is your strategy session over yet?
Anyway, keep a fixed distance from him.
And hold his attention on you!
I don't care if you die, but the
Master's safety is foremost!
Got it?!
I got it.
I'll be a decoy or whatever.
But you'd better rescue Kunieda in return.
Don't go dying on me either.
Make up your mind!
Oh, yeah... This is the first
time I've fought alongside you.
And what about it?
You'll pay if you hold me back.
Just so you know...
I heard your entire plan.
Seems like it.
Here we go, Baby Beel!
Zebel Blast!
You surprise me, human!
You can control the Youngest's power?
It's not something I do on purpose, though!
But y'never know 'til you
try! Right, Baby Beel?
Now just up and die!
But, I hate to say...
You won't be killing me
with something like that.
You're kiddin' me...
No, it was plenty.
Too late.
Oga!
Right!
Right then. Good going, Hilda.
I misjudged y-
You... planned this... from the start...?
You can have that woman.
The biggest obstacle is
the Demon Maidservant.
You.
Hilda!
Everything is for Lord En.
Spinning, spinning, spinning yogurty...
Kanzaki-senpai, this is no time for
leisurely singing yogurty jingles!
Oga's wife's done for, and Madame
Aoi's in serious trouble!
Oh, sounds fun.
Which school did it?
They're as strong as demons!
It's life or death! SOS to the max!
On the next Beelzebub: On
the Brink! What'll We Do?!
There's no need to worry!
I, Kanzaki Hajime, will
beat the crap out of them!
Whoa, Kanzaki-senpai, that's
awesome! You're like, a manly man!