It's Mappy!
You're looking well.
I'm going to get rid of the Hollow!
Awesome, Kenny!
Keep it going!
Yachiru!
I'm going for a little workout.
Go find somewhere to play!
Okay, sure!
I thought I felt an awfully
familiar Spiritual Pressure.
Was it my imagination?
Father... Mother...
No!
Help!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Thank you very much, Mr. Soul Reaper.
That Hollow
was the one who killed my family.
Now everyone can rest in peace.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
If I had come here sooner
I may have been able to
protect your family.
No, you don't have to...
There is no need for you to apologize.
No, it was my fault.
I'm sorry.
Um... My name is Mayu.
If you don't mind,
please tell me yours.
I'm Masayoshi.
It's written with the
characters for "justice."
Masayoshi...
Mappy?
Yachiru?
It is you, Yachiru!
It's been a while!
It's Mappy!
You're looking well.
Um... Is this enough wood for the fire?
Yes, that's more than enough!
That'll last us until
morning. Thanks.
Want some konpeito sugar candy?
Yes, please!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Have some, Mappy!
Oh, no thanks.
I don't like sweets.
Is that so?
You're not only the
lieutenant of Squad 11,
you're chairwoman
of the Women's Soul
Reaper Association as well?
You're really working
hard. That's terrific!
Yeah, you might say that!
What've you been doing, Mappy?
I've been traveling as part of a
Partisan Squad that goes
after drifting Hollows.
That's hard work.
Not really.
It's like going on a trip.
It's the perfect job for me.
It's no fun staying
at home, you know?
Don't you have a family?
I had a wife.
Had?
A Hollow...killed her.
That day, we got into
a fight over nothing
and I left on a mission
without making up with her.
Several weeks later,
when I finally got back after
finishing my assignment...
I wish I could have at least
told her, "I'm sorry."
I wanted her forgiveness. A
simple "that's okay."
I despise Hollows!
I'm going to get rid of
every single damn Hollow.
And some day,
I'm going to cut down the
Hollow that killed my wife!
I'm going to see to it that not a
single person has to suffer
like Mayu and I did
because of Hollows!
I'll kill every last one of them!
That's the promise I
made to my late wife!
Sorry, I sort of got carried away.
Not at all. I'm rooting for you.
Please keep going until you
defeat every last Hollow!
You can do it, Mappy!
Thanks!
Masayoshi is amazing, isn't he?
He is?
Yes. He's wonderful.
Oh... If you go straight from here,
you'll come to the forest you
were talking about, Yachiru.
But it's awfully far.
No problem. I run very fast!
Thank you for showing me the way.
Um...Ma...Ma...
It's Mayu.
Mayu-Mayu! See you!
She's fast!
"Mayu-Mayu"?
Kenny!
You've cut down so many!
Where have you been?
Guess what...
Remember Mappy?
Mappy?
Oh, you mean Masayoshi?
Right! I ran into him for
the first time in ages!
He looked good!
You met him?
I sure did!
Yachiru...
Huh?
We became friends right after
we both joined the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
Mappy, want some konpeito sugar candy?
Thanks, Yachiru.
I can't get enough sweets.
These are great! Can I have some more?
Sure!
Want me to come with you?
No.
You don't need to come, Kenny!
I'll be going then!
Are...
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
I'm okay.
Um...
Here.
For me?
Have some.
Thanks.
It's delicious. Thank you.
Mayu-Mayu!
I want one too!
S-Sure. Here.
Delicious!
I remember your wife was
a great cook too, Mappy.
Yeah... She was, wasn't she?
Say, what did you argue
with your wife about?
Something silly.
Tell me!
It was because...
Because...
That day... That day, we...
What's the matter, Mappy?
I sense a Hollow.
Huh?
I don't sense anything.
Yachiru, look after Mayu.
I'm...
going to get rid of the Hollow!
Mappy!
Damn Hollow...
Masayoshi!
Yachiru, Mayu, you're safe now!
Thank goodness.
I found you, despicable Soul Reaper.
Um... Masayoshi...
When you finish your work here,
you'll be going somewhere
else, won't you?
Yeah.
Chasing Hollows and
getting rid of them.
That's my job.
I...don't have a family.
Would you mind if I went with you?
Mayu, I...
It's getting dark, so
we should go home now!
Huh? But, um...
See you later, Mappy!
Y-Yeah, later.
Um... Yachiru...
You shouldn't get too close to Mappy.
Huh?
This is far enough.
See you!
Masayoshi...
Mayu?
Mayu!
You've come at last.
Masayoshi...
Let Mayu go!
Oh, I'll let her go, all right.
Are you all right?!
Y-Yes!
We have no more use for that woman.
There's nothing to worry about, Mayu.
I'll take them down!
So that no one has to be sad anymore.
Masayoshi...
Mayu... Will you come with me?
What?
Mayu, I promise you...
I'll kill every Hollow
until none remain!
Yes!
Thank you.
In that case... I'd better
get rid of them quickly!
A Zanpakuto... What a laugh.
What do you mean?
Get him!
Mappy!
Where'd he go?
Hey!
Damn...you...
Masayoshi!
Stay back!
Mayu-Mayu...
I told you not to get close to Mappy.
Oh Yachiru... You're late.
Did you have trouble finding
our Spiritual Pressures?
It's already over.
Though, the one I wanted revenge against
wasn't among them.
Yachiru?
What's the matter?!
I got rid of all the Hollows.
No, there's still one left.
What? Where?!
Right in front of my eyes.
Huh?
Yachiru?
H-Hey... Yachiru?
I don't see anything.
Yes, there is!
Because Mappy...
you're a Hollow.
D-Don't be ridiculous.
How am I a...
Mappy used to love sweets.
Mappy, want some konpeito sugar candy?
Thanks, Yachiru.
I can't get enough sweets.
You still have a heart, Mappy.
You're looking well.
Sorry, I sort of got carried away.
Thanks!
But...
One day, even that will be gone.
One day, you'll completely
become a Hollow.
That can't be!
I'm not a Hollow!
Not a Hollow!
I'm...
What was your wife's name?
Her name?
Do you remember?
Her name...
Her name was...
Why? Why can't I remember?
Why?!
I'm not a Hollow!
I'm going to get my revenge on
the Hollow that killed my wife!
The one who killed your
wife is you, Mappy.
What...happened?
You Hollow... You bastard!
You killed her!
I...I'm the one?!
Kenny told me about it.
While you were chasing after
a Hollow, it possessed you.
When you saw yourself in the
mirror after killing your wife,
your consciousness took over the Hollow.
But... Just like you forgot
your love for candy...
and even your wife's name...
One day, your consciousness
will also...
That can't be...I...I...
Yachiru...
M-Mayu..
I won't die...alone!
Masayoshi!
Mappy!
Mayu... I'm glad you're all right.
I'm sorry.
I promised you I'd kill every
Hollow until none remain, but...
I'm so sorry.
It's all right! It doesn't matter.
Thank you.
Mappy...
Remember this? It was your favorite.
It's sweet...and good.
Mappy...
I'll keep on fighting...
so no one has to be sad anymore.
Is it over?
Yes.
Here.
You can have them all.
Kenny, you're so sweet.
Let's go.
Right.
So the next one's going to be our
last stand-alone episode, huh?
Guess it's natural for
me to wrap up the...
Kurosaki, I'm going to be staying in
the World of the Living for a while.
Toshiro?!
Will I cause you some inconvenience?
N-No...
Good. Be seeing you then.
My chance for action.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Kenny!
I caught this many!
Nice. So did I.
Yay!
By the way, it's been several
days, but we still haven't
reached the Seireitei.
We're lost, aren't we?
Yeah.