Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Hinamori!
Wha--?! I-It can’t be!
Captain Aizen!
Captain Aizen… No… No…
Captain Aizen…!
What’s all this racket,
so early in the morning?
Oh…? This is a terrible situation, isn’t it?
Be careful…
Be careful of Squad 3.
Especially…
when Aizen goes out walking alone.
So, it was you!
Kira… Why…?
I’m the lieutenant of Squad 3.
No matter what the reason,
I cannot allow anyone to raise
a sword against the captain.
Please…get out of my way…Kira!
I cannot.
Move! Get out of my way!
No!
Can’t you hear me? I said to move!
Can’t you hear me say “no”?!
Deflect it…
Tobiume!
Releasing your Zanpaku-to
in a place like this…
How thoughtless!
Do you realize what you are doing?!
Do not confuse public matters with private,
Lieutenant Hinamori!
I see…
Then I have no choice.
I shall dispose of you as an enemy.
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Don’t either of you move.
Hitsugaya…
Arrest the two of them!
Hitsugaya!
Hinamori! Is this any time to be
clashing swords with each other?
Shouldn’t your first priority be to
lower Capt. Aizen down from there?
I will make the report to
the General Captain.
Put those two under detention.
Take them away.
Sorry, Captain of Squad 10…
that you had to waste your time
on one of mine.
Ichimaru…
You were about to kill Hinamori,
weren’t you?
Now… What are talking about?
I’ll tell you this now…
If you allow any of Hinamori’s
blood to spill…
I will kill you!
That’s scary…
I’d better keep a close eye on her to
make sure no bad guy gets to her.
What’s going on?! Captain Ichimaru!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Oh! What’s this…?!
Captain Aizen is…
What in the…?
Get Captain Aizen down.
Y-Yes, sir.
What the--?!
Hanataro! What are you doing,
sleeping on my knee?!
How disgusting!
My only good pair of pants is slimy
with your drool! Bastard!
Damn it!
He’s exhausted.
Don’t give him a hard time
over a little drool.
I-Ichigo…
A-Are you all right, already?
Yeah. Thanks to Hanataro.
Your aches and pains
are gone too, right?
Huh? Oh…now that you mention it…
It looked like he was up treating
your wounds early this morning,
even though he was tired
to the bone.
I see… I guess he was helping me
out before I even knew it.
Hmm? What is it?
Things are gonna get even
harder than it’s been, hereafter.
The enemy’s probably getting
very irritated about now.
You’re serious about doing this,
aren’t you?
Your heart is set on it, I hope.
She’s…waiting.
I didn’t come here to tour
the sewers, after all.
Please stop it! Please stop!
You shouldn’t come on to me like this.
I-I’m sorry…
Oh! G-Good morning…
What the heck were you
dreaming about?
I-I can’t say…
SADO
Chado…?
No. It’s Sado.
You’re huge! Is that our uniform?
I’ve never seen you before.
I’m scheduled to transfer to
Mashiba Middle School today.
I’m in class 2-F.
We’re the same age?!
I mean, we’re in the same class?
Good grief…
Why didn’t you hit back?
Well, in any case,
thanks for helping me out.
Hey, should you be standing up?
Y-Yeah…no problem.
You sure? You really got pounded.
You’re bleeding.
Don’t be ridiculous.
If not for the rocks and stuff they used,
I would’ve won.
So, these guys are
third-year students.
Did you do something to them?
Nope… Upperclassmen just
don’t like my hair.
They don’t like anybody who stands out.
That’s all it is.
Isn’t it the same with you?
I mean, you must really stand out.
Well, shall we get going, Chad?
It’s Sado. You’re wobbly, you know…
You don’t like being called Chad?
It’s cool, don’t you think?
Like Dominic Chad…
Never heard of him. Who is he?
You’ve never heard of him?!
Then, how about Chad Smith?
Never heard of him.
But I have heard of
Eugene Chadbourne.
Who’s that?
It was a dream.
Dreaming of the past…
just like an old man.
Where is he?
Is he there?
No…
Okay, this warehouse next.
Group Three, go ‘round the back!
Right!
But, thank goodness…
If I’d been woken by
a knock like this…
it would’ve turned into
the worst day ever.
And…just what is that?
In order not to get tired out,
and to continue working like workhorses,
every member of Squad 4 is
supplied with this special nutritional tonic.
Really?
There’s a picture of a skull on it.
Are you sure you weren’t tricked?
Take one tablet, and amazingly…
And here I go.
Well, shall we?
– Wait, wait, wait, hey!
What is it?
What do you mean, “What is it?”!
Did that pill do anything?
It didn’t, did it?
What are you talking about?
Doesn’t my face look like
I’m full of energy?
It looks the same as a minute ago.
I think you were tricked, after all.
‘Kay. There’s no one around.
We just fought here yesterday.
It seems weird that there
aren’t any guards around.
The enemy probably wouldn’t think
we’d still be hanging around here a day later.
I suppose so…
Boy, I’m full of energy now!
I tell you, you don’t look it.
Hey, by the way,
you think the others are okay?
Like the guy with the glasses
and white cape,
and the chick with walnut-colored hair…
The “chick”?
That word’s not “in” anymore.
I don’t think “in” is
the word anymore, either.
Owwie! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Ishida and Inoue are
a hundred times smarter than me.
So that means…
you’re a hundred times
dumber than they are.
That’s what it means.
Owie! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Those two wouldn’t take on enemies
they know they can’t beat.
They’re fine, I’m sure…
What about the other one…Chad?
There’s even less cause
to worry about him.
Why’s that?
I can sense it…
Huh?
I can sense it, his Spiritual Pressure.
Ever since we landed here.
Besides…
I can’t imagine Chad ever losing.
Damn… Y-You’re a monster…
Where is Senzaikyu?
S-Senzaikyu?
When I asked where Rukia Kuchiki was,
the last guy just said that and fainted.
I don’t know where it is. Tell me.
U-Uh… T-Thataway…
It’s way over there.
That white tower-like thing.
That’s Senzaikyu.
Oh… Please spare me…
I see… Thanks.
Uh, no… Don’t mention it.
Turning your back on your enemy…
You’re a fool!
I-I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
D-Don’t kill me!
Save me! Forgive me!
Please! I’ll forget I ever saw you!
Don’t…come after me again…
Huh? N-No…
I won't do it again.
He’s not going to kill me? Really?
Now…
We’re finally here…
Let’s go! On to Senzaikyu!
He’s here!
It’s the Ryoka!
It looks like he’s broken through
the guardhouse.
Captain Kyoraku…
Huh?
What, he’s here already?
Oh, well… I guess I’ll head out, then.
Are you really going?
It’s just one Ryoka.
I’m your assistant,
but I should be more than enough.
Listen, Nanao…
It’s old man Yama’s orders, after all.
He doesn’t want anyone thinking
we’re still having problems with the Ryoka.
Grown-ups hate losing face, you know.
Besides…
it would be awful
if my Nanao went out to fight
and ended up being injured.
Since when am I “your Nanao”?!
Oh… You’re even more heartless
than usual.
That’s what’s so wonderful about you!
I got it! I got it, so hurry up and go!
Yes, ma’am.
Now, don’t look so worried.
It’ll be over before you know it.
I’ll just have some fun.
Dammit! This sure is a long staircase!
How many steps are there anyway?!
Quit griping, will you?!
I’ll see you later!
Huh?!
Didn’t I tell you?
That medicine really works.
– No way!
Okay, we’re here!
No one’s around.
Security’s lax here, too.
Okay. We’re going straight through
to the inner area.
Wha--?!
Huh…!
W-What’s with this impossibly
powerful Spiritual Pressure?!
Wha…What’s doing this?!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
By the way,
have we eaten anything lately?
I'm hungry.
Then let's go to the cafeteria.
Okay, let's go eat some fried rice.
Not that way, this way!
Funny… I've waited so long,
but they still haven't come.
Kenpachi's been stood up.
Oh! Here it is! Here it is!