Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Get a hold of yourself!
Noba.
You've been quite entertaining,
but you're 100 years too early
to be sealing us away.
Shall we put an end to this already?
Baura!
I know.
We have to run away!
It's no good!
Noba--!
This way!
It's no good!
I guess this means he's not
letting us get away.
Flash Step…
It's no good…
I can't go that far with my current,
limited Spiritual Pressure.
It's difficult to fly while carrying
the both of them…
What in the world should I do--?
Rangiku. You could manage
if it was just you.
Leave us behind and run!
You can use us as decoys.
You could manage
if it was just you…
I can't do that!
Stop saying silly things and
just think about getting away!
When he attacks, we're going to run
as far as possible with my Flash Step!
All right…
Made you look!
Damn!
Noba!
You did it in that condition…
No problem.
We've bought ourselves some time,
but it won't be long
before he catches up to us.
The Spiritual Pressure
that's clashing across town…
It's probably… Shuhei and the others.
We've gotten quite far away from them.
It seems they lured us out.
With Noba in this condition,
it looks like it's impossible to
neutralize the enemy's power.
We're going to immobilize
the doll and catch it.
Then we're going to make it
cough up Ururu.
Don't put it so simply.
It's because of Noba that we can tell
when he's going to appear.
It's hard enough as it is to dodge…
We can't make an aimed counter attack
in that instant.
We can't deal any damage
just by attacking it haphazardly.
If we at least knew when he'll appear,
I could attack his belly
where his scales look thin.
We need someone to be a decoy again.
At any rate, it's dangerous for us
to stay here. Let's move.
Yeah!
Noba, we'll leave your gigai here.
Gigai?
Noba is a mod soul
created for anti-Bount use.
This body is a gigai that Urahara made.
Is that why he could tell
where the Bounts were?
Rangiku, could you take out
Noba's Gikongan, Soul Candy?
A Soul Reaper can do it, right?
Chad…
I'm all right…
Mod souls won't die…
as long as…their pills aren't destroyed.
But…!
No problem…
I can still move through space
with this body.
Noba…
Maybe…
Maybe we can still manage.
If we can combine my kido with
Noba's Bount tracking power,
we may be able to catch that Bount.
What?
But it might use up the rest of
our spiritual power.
It's all over if we miss.
What must I do?
Noba!
We were created to defeat the Bounts.
Countless souls have already
fallen victim to them.
I'll do what I can.
All right.
We have one chance.
Noba and I are going to use kido
to drag him out.
We can't move during that time,
so you're going to attack.
Blow him away with the same attack
that surprised Captain Kyoraku!
Curse them. They should have died!
They may be planning something, but…
This will be their grave!
Go, Baura!
Let's do it here.
Yes!
Noba…
Synchronize your Spiritual Pressure
with mine.
No problem.
Here we go!
Noba… Rangiku…
This is…
Have they…synchronized?
Southern Heart, Northern Eyes,
Western Fingertips, Eastern Heel.
Gather bringing wind,
brush away rain and scatter!
Bakudo 58!
Kakushitsuijaku!
57… 89…
95… 103…
122… 136…
184… 190… 202…
Rangiku--!
I can't find him… Does the Bount
Spiritual Pressure act differently?
Tracking successful!
He doesn't seem to notice…
He's coming!
Which way?!
Where's he coming from?
The opportunity that these two have
created… I can't waste it--!
It's from above!!
They wouldn't expect an attack
from above!
Wha--?!
How do they know where I am?!
Ururu!
Oh… I'm back.
U-Ururu…
Curse you kids!
That'll be enough for today.
We'll finish this later!
Don't say whatever you like!
Baura!
They escaped…
In the end, you held back.
Couldn't you have defeated him
if you hit him with all of your power?
I couldn't have saved Ururu
if I did that.
That's what I thought.
But you did a good job!
Chad!
DEPARTMENT OF
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT
This is it! This is it!
This is the Bount data!
I don't know who hid it, but it wasn't
anything that I couldn't handle!
But this is really interesting!
I never knew that the Bounts
had such a secret.
I wonder if I can get my hands
on a Bount and do research on it.
I think it's easiest if I go
to the World of the Living, but…
There's no time for that.
And the Soul Reapers who have gone to
the World of the Living to watch the Bounts…
There isn't enough time to get
one of them to help me, either.
I wonder if there's something
I could do.
This is…
I see…
So this is why they needed
a certain Quincy!
A person with special abilities who can
bind his reishi, deny their unification
and force that to become power.
That man could do it…
Nemu!
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Take research material Q141 with you
and go to the World of the Living
right now!
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Q141, correct?
And once it is delivered
into that man's hands…
Damn!
Why do I have to guard
a place like this?!
W-Well…
It was Captain Zaraki's orders.
Shut up! I know that…
The gate!
What's this?!
Someone's there.
Stop sneaking around!
Show yourself!
He's hiding somewhere?
Where is he?
What was that?!
Inform the Captain!
E    mergency! Emergency!
There's an intruder in Seireitei!
All Squads…
To their defensive posts! Repeat!
Emergency! Emergency!
There's an intruder in Seireitei!
He's here… He's definitely here!
Someone is definitely
running in front of me…
So why isn't there
any Spiritual Pressure?!
There?!
Extend! Hozukimaru!!
You're trying to torment me
while you're invisible, huh?!
Bring it on!
He's completely erased his presence.
Move…move!
I'm going to get you
as soon as you move!
I've got you!
Captain Kuchiki!
I've come to inform you!
What is this fuss?
Is it an intruder?
We don't know the details yet.
But…
What is it?
The Stealth Force has just
sent a secret letter from
General Captain Genryusai Yamamoto.
From General Captain--?
It's a nice moonlit night.
Too bad…
Sorry, Captain… He got away.
It doesn't matter…
Huh?
I don't know who it was, but…
he sure is a wimp for causing trouble
while erasing his Spiritual Pressure.
But I've been bored lately…
This might kill some time.
But…I can see it.
The Hollows…and the people
being attacked.
Master…
I want to become stronger…
I want to become a strong Quincy
and protect everyone from Hollows!
Don't squeeze your underarm too much.
Hold your bow in the position
easiest for you.
Yes…
Pull the arrow straight back.
Be sure to pull straight back…
And release your hand.
You don't fire…
You release…
All the basics begin
from this movement.
Try it several times.
It's difficult.
A Quincy's arrow is released
for those you want to protect.
Those I want to protect?
You'll understand in time.
Those I want to protect…
Uryu… Take a look.
There is nothing difficult outside of
the basics I have just taught you.
Anything beyond that
depends on your heart.
Heart…
Quincies release arrows
with their hearts
to protect the ones they cherish!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Rangiku. I found that Bount's hideout
while everyone was fighting.
Yumichika, when did you do that?
With my brains and beauty,
it was simple.
Aren't you doing most of the dirty work,
despite saying you didn't want to do it?
I won't tell you where it is.
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers After These Messages!!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Say, I didn't notice earlier, but…
Did we have to return Noba to his
stuffed animal at that critical time?
His abilities are higher in the gigai,
aren't they?
There's a problem.
What?
He can't do it unless he sticks
to a body…
If he was in a gigai…
It's impossible for Noba…
No problem.