Of course, he is a monster.
I suppose it can't be easy.
But it's okay.
If you put a bullet through his head
from this distance, he's sure to die.
You bastard...
R-Rachel... Why?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I want to kill Zack myself.
Ah... I see.
Of course.
I'm tired.
I want to end it here.
I'm sorry, Doctor. I can't...
...live with you.
What are you playing at?
Hey!
Just kill me now.
I can never be forgiven, anyway.
But first...
The last thing I want to do,
all on my own,
is make you my own.
So do it, then.
You wanna die?
You wanna kill me?
You wanna end it?!
What the hell are you talking about?!
You're making no damn sense!
I know that.
Then stop saying stupid shit!
It's not stupid!
I'm being serious!
Is that right?
Did you think a dumb brat
like you could kill me?
If you want it all to end, I'll end it!
No! No, no!
You're about to get what you wanted!
Stop!
Don't kill me.
Don't kill me the way I am right now.
Because you're...
...not my God anymore.
My God...
...doesn't need me anymore.
...is dead!
Yeah, that's right.
I killed your God.
I killed him.
But I'm not dead.
You get it, don't you?
Who was it that said he'd kill you?
My... God—
Wrong!
It was me. I said it.
No one else. Not your God.
I am the one who's gonna kill you!
But I'm... unclean.
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?!
I'm a murderer!
I've killed tons of people
because I like killing people!
Unlike you and Danny, I don't waste time
running and thinking about pointless shit!
I don't give a rat's ass
about parents and gods.
Don't even joke with me about doing
what I do because of crap like that!
I decide what I want to do, and then I do it!
I'm me, and you're you! Am I wrong?!
I'm... me?
Yes! So make your own decisions for yourself!
Well, Ray?
Who do you see in front of you right now?
Zack?
Exactly.
Not God or anyone else, right?
Yeah.
You've always been Zack.
For someone so insane,
you're way too serious.
I'm the one standing in front of you.
If you understand that...
Ray, wish for me!
If you wanna die,
swear you will be killed by me!
Swear it to yourself... and swear it to me!
O-Okay...
I swear.
I swear to you, Zack!
Good.
I'll swear it to you, too.
Hey, are you gonna sit there crying forever?
But...
Idiot.
More importantly, how do we get out of here?
I mean, this is your floor, isn't it?
Yeah.
Don't you know where the exit is?
I don't remember ever going
any higher than this.
I never cared to.
Huh?
Hey, where are you going?
I do know there's a front door.
Try pushing hard on this.
Huh?
Just try and push it.
Fine.
All you had to do was push it...
Shut up!
It's open, ain't it?
What's inside here?
Nothing.
Nothing?! What the hell?!
Huh?
Something's written there.
"Miss."
So, where's the exit?
Are there any rooms you
never went into or anything?
No.
I searched every last inch of
this floor so I could lay traps.
There are no the stairs
leading up and no elevator.
No one's ever come down here from above?
No...
But Doctor Danny always went outside.
Maybe he squirmed in through the vents?
Ugh, creepy!
And like hell he'd do that! Think more!
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
There must be an exit
that's not on this floor.
Huh? What does that mean?
I think there's an exit
on the next floor down.
Hold up!
What did you mean?
People who came here from
outside rode the elevator up.
It must have been because they were
brought to the floor below this one.
I don't really get it, but we
need to go down, right?
Damn! It won't work.
The power's off.
What do we do?
It's okay.
I remember where the power supply is.
The switch is in the room with the music box.
Oh, right. That one.
Zack... can I go by myself?
Huh?
This is the last time I'll come here.
I want to say goodbye.
Why do you have to go alone?
I guess I'm a little embarrassed
to let you see it.
Okay, fine.
I'll keep watch here. Get moving.
Okay. I'll be back soon.
I'm sorry. I won't have time to sew you up.
Why...
The gun...
Be calm.
I'm certainly not going to bite you.
What do you want?
There is something I wish to ask you.
Zack was not your God at all, was he?
I know that now.
So it seems.
But do you truly understand what that means?
Zack and I made a promise to each other.
It had nothing to do with God.
Zack is not God,
an absolute being, any longer.
You have turned Zack into a being
that is neither an angel nor God.
There is no one left upon whom
you can rely to grant your wish,
because you made your vow
with someone who was not God.
He may well betray you.
If you still believe that vow to be absolute,
then what makes him different from God?
I don't particularly believe it's absolute.
I trust Zack.
But both promising and trusting
were decisions Zack and
I made in our own hearts.
So even if my trust is betrayed...
It was my choice to trust him.
I'll bear responsibility for my own heart.
I'm prepared to accept that he isn't God.
And having said all this,
do you still wish for death?
Yes.
Why?
Your thinking has so drastically changed.
Even then, your wish remains unchanged?
It's not as if I, myself,
have actually changed.
I've only accepted who I am.
That's all.
And I don't wish to be forgiven anymore.
There's no one left who would forgive me.
That's why I still want to die.
I can't go on living.
I see.
Then you have made your own decision.
Yes.
And...
Actually, the rest is a secret.
For goodness' sake...
You've left God behind entirely.
One final question.
Rachel Gardner, just who are you?
I'm me.
No more or less than that.
Ah, I see.
You spoke almost as if you consider
yourself and Zack to be equals.
But that might not be so far from the truth.
Young girl who could not be an angel,
but proved not to be a witch,
you are absolutely certain
that you are Rachel Gardner?
Are we finished?
Yes.
Then would you let me
press the elevator button?
Very well.
You won't interfere?
What did I tell you?
I have no intention of interfering.
I'm going now.
Do as you please.
Father, where is the exit?
Do you expect me to answer?
I answered plenty of your questions.
I think you could answer mine.
Is it on the next floor down?
Inspect the stained glass in the cathedral.
All right.
I won't come back here.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
I turned on the elevator.
Took you long enough.
The priest didn't come here?
He's still around?!
He didn't do anything to me, though.
And he didn't interfere.
What's his deal, anyway?
Oh, my gun...
Huh?
In the living roo—
Pick it up quick and let's move.
The doctor...
That bastard's still alive?
I think he's the monster here.
You can't use that anymore.
Let's go.
What is it?
They were supposed to be my parents.
I guess this is goodbye to them.
Why don't you tell them bye-bye,
like the kid you are?
Right...
Bye-bye.
Tch! Where's that bastard Danny?
He might be hiding.
Wanna hunt him down and finish him off?
I think that would be hard.
He seems to know this building really well.
Hanging around would be dangerous.
Hmph. You're no fun.
That's weird.
Huh?
The elevator was below.
So what?
It should've been stopped at this floor.
Did someone ride it down?
That means...
Get back!
The hell? No one's in here.
You said something about
saying goodbye back there.
Did you get to do it?
It turned out to be a simple goodbye.
That room was a total mess.
You should've cleaned it up.
Was all the stuff in there yours?
Everything I was given since I came—
It wasn't yours, then?
I'm not sure.
I sewed and patched them up
to try to make them mine,
but stuffed dolls don't respond,
so I don't know if they were mine.
But I did treasure them.
So I told them goodbye.
Oh, the music box was
something I already had.
I got it as a gift when I was little.
I really liked the sounds it made.
So why didn't you bring it with you?
I don't need it.
I remember the sound, and all
the memories it gave me.
As long as I have that,
I don't need anything else.
Where's the exit?
The priest said to inspect the stained glass.
He told you that?
In return for answering
lots of his questions.
Huh?
Where'd that glasses bastard go?
I think this is the exit.
Sure, sure.
So I have to move this, right?
Damn, but it's heavy.
Hey!
What?
Don't you, "What?" me! Help me out!
Shit, my arms are dead!
Was I useful?
A little.
Is there really an exit here, though?
I don't know, but I don't
think that priest would lie.
Hey, Ray.
I think we both just had the same thought.
Stand back!
Will this take us to the surface?
I think so.
You don't sound sure.
The priest didn't say anything about that.
But we have no other choice.
Yeah, I guess.
How far up do these go?
What is it?
I remember now.
Huh?
When I was brought here, I was
blindfolded the whole time.
So what?
I remember going down a long staircase.
Really?!
If we go up these, we'll come
out at the surface.
All right!
Damn, this is one long staircase.
Huh? What are you doing?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You...
...seem more human now.
Let's go. And don't trip.
What's wrong?
Take it.
You're letting me borrow it again?
I'm giving it to you.
It's pretty banged up, so I
dunno how useful it'll be,
but it's better than nothing, right?
Thank you.
The emergency system has been activated.
Initiating building detonation sequence.