Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
How about some tea,
Lieutenant Ise?
Have I been working that long?
I'm sorry for using your desk…
I don't mind.
These temporary headquarters
feel like camp to me…
I know it's a bit foolish,
but I'm sort of enjoying it…
I know…
Oh!
Lieutenant Hinamori brought in
some cookies she baked herself.
Cookies baked by Hinamori?
Is something wrong?
No… I just remembered
an unpleasant memory…
Oh! But they're just
regular cookies.
See?
Thank goodness.
I'll make some tea.
That's odd…
Is something the matter?
I can't find the tea leaves.
That is odd.
I just bought some the other day.
Recently, a lot of things have
been turning up missing.
Like rice, or soybean paste…
Now that you mention it,
my captain was saying how his
secret stash of sake disappeared.
Hanamaru…
My Hanamaru is…
This is the clearest image caught
by the surveillance camera.
It's hard to tell what it is…
According to the images,
the intruder snuck
into the barracks
and stole four chickens:
Hanamaru, Hanae,
Hanakichi and Hanaemon.
Chickens?
Ever since the Muramasa Incident,
Squad 4 has been so busy that
the members barely
have time to go home.
So they've tried to become
more self-sufficient
by raising chickens and growing a
vegetable garden at their barracks.
Their tomatoes and
eggs are delicious…
I was in charge of
raising the chickens…
They were all fine yesterday…
The fence around the coop wasn't
ripped and there weren't any holes.
If we're to assume
the culprit stole the chickens
by opening the entrance door,
then it cannot be the work of
a simple-minded animal.
Could it be connected with the rash
of recent thefts at the barracks?
You don't think the Sword Beasts
are responsible, do you?
What do you think,
Captain Unohana?
I can't eliminate the possibility,
but we lack enough
information to be sure.
I traced the footsteps,
and confirmed that
the alleged culprit
escaped via
the underground waterway.
I'd like you to identify the thief
who escaped via
the underground waterway
and take him into custody.
So, why was I summoned here?
There's a possibility that
the thief may be a Sword Beast.
So just to be safe.
We're counting on you.
Well, it will be a good way
to pass the time.
I guess.
Sorry to make you do this, Nanao,
but I'm counting on you!
I, Nanao Ise, and my three-man team
will get on it immediately!
We're counting on you!
Catch the thief!
Bring back my snacks!
We believe in you!
How's it looking?
See for yourself.
Is this their present position?
Yes.
But I must say,
conducting a search and
mapping the underground
waterway is certainly ambitious.
Why waste the opportunity—
it's killing two birds
with one stone.
Will they be okay?
I'm sure they'll be fine.
This place sure
has some "ambience"…
Yes, it does.
There are a lot of scary stories
about this place…
Oh? What sort of stories?
Well, stories such as
how people have died,
gone missing, or have been
trapped underground
while they were working
on extending the waterway.
They say you can still
hear their eerie voices.
That's a good one!
Maybe our thief is one of them!
Ridiculous!
That's just a common ghost story!
In the first place,
there are no such things as
ghosts in the Soul Society…
What's wrong?!
Something touched my neck!
Was it an enemy?
Uh…if I may…
That…was a water drop…
Huh?
See? Up there.
Water is dripping from the spaces
between the stones.
Spooked by a water droplet…
You're quite a scaredy-cat,
aren't you, Lieutenant Ise?
W-What was that?!
What was that just now?
It's a trap!
A booby trap!
Yeah…
It would appear we're
unwelcome guests.
The enemy might be
hiding nearby.
From here on out,
let's proceed with caution.
What is it?
Look!
That spot, where the color
is different…is a trap.
It might be a hole,
or maybe a land mine…
But putting it smack in the middle
of the path is pretty amateur…
DO NOT CROSS
I get it!
We just have to walk
along the edge!
Wait! Wait! Wait! No!
Nothing's happening…
I was sure I was
going to go boom…
You imbecile!
Don't be so careless, you fool!
I'm sorry…
Thank goodness it didn't go off,
but seriously!
Be quiet!
What is it?
Can't you hear that?
Hear what?
The sound of water.
There aren't any leaks here.
It's different!
It's a lot bigger…
More like rushing water…
Run!
What the hell is going on?!
It's a time-delay trap!
It tricks you into thinking
nothing happened,
taking away
your chance to escape!
You fool! This is no time for
a leisurely explanation!
Everyone all right?!
Just barely…
Damn! What is this place?!
I don't know…
It seems like we were
swept quite a distance…
I thought you knew a lot
about this place!
Yes, but I don't know because
I've never come this far.
Oh, boy. Things are
starting to look pretty bad.
Look, how can you
be so nonchalant?
Useless brat as usual.
Ikkaku!
Third Seat Madarame?!
Not now, Ikkaku…
You're taking the joke too far…
Right, Lieutenant Ise?
Ikkaku! Hold on!
I'll save you!
Stay away!
I'll figure something out!
Don't worry about me
and get out of here!
Ikkaku!
Third Seat Madarame!
What was that thing?
More importantly…
Ikkaku sacrificed himself
to save us…
There's no need to worry!
A Zanpakuto and its master
are of two separate bodies,
but share one heart.
He's not dead.
I can tell.
Hozukimaru…
Do you smell something?
Huh?
What is that smell?
What is this?
No, it can't be…
No…are these…
Could these
grilled chicken skewers be?
Huh?
This sake…
This belongs to my captain!
See, it has his name on it…
Then these are all the items that
the thief stole from the barracks?
It would seem so.
Hey! Stop!
You're not getting away.
Hanataro!
Seventh Seat Yamada!
He's the thief!
Please catch him!
Huh?!
Huh…huh?
But…
I'm so sorry!
Why are you apologizing
all of a sudden?
Anyways, lift your head
and show us your face.
You're!
You know him?
No, not at all…
Don't confuse us
with your reactions.
I'm sorry…
But there's something
awfully familiar about him…
Hey!
What'd you do with Ikkaku?
I'm sorry…
Who are you,
and why're you here?
I'm sorry!
Can't you say anything
other than "I'm sorry"?!
I'm sorry!
Look…it's about time
you came clean with us!
Ikkaku!
Huh?!
What?!
So you've come, you monster!
That's a huge Sword Beast!
So you were responsible,
after all!
I'm sorry!
Nanao Ise, protect them!
Right!
Ikkaku, I'll get revenge for you!
Bankai!
Ryumon Hozukimaru!
It slipped?
Damn!
Dammit! Let go of me, monster!
Hado 31, Shakkaho!
Ah! Hozukimaru is!
Seventh Seat Yamada!
You must fight too!
What?
You're a Soul Reaper,
can't you at least attack
with your Zanpakuto?
But…my Zanpakuto is
mainly used for healing, and…
And what?
I thought I wouldn't need it
for this search so…
I left it back at
the barracks in my room…
What?!
Lieutenant Ise!
What…should I do…
What should I do?
What should I do?!
What are you doing?!
If you do that, Ikkaku will!
I don't know why but I feel great!
That Zanpakuto is!
Fill up! Vermillion Hisagomaru!
So from what I understand,
the thief was…
the manifested form of
Seventh Seat Yamada's Zanpakuto,
is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Why didn't you say so
at that time?!
Well…I didn't realize it at all.
But what a fitting story for you,
Seventh Seat Yamada.
As Hisagomaru tells it,
he also manifested
because of Muramasa.
However, he had no
complaints against his master
and immediately tried to
return to sword form,
but was, of course,
unable to do so…
He thought his master
had rejected him.
And in his dejection,
he went to live like a hermit
in the underground waterway.
What?!
You mean the reason I'm not
able to return to my original form
isn't because
my master hates me?
That's right…
As you can see, we're unable
to return to our previous form.
So that's what it was?
Well, that's such a relief,
so my body went limp.
And what about
the grilled chicken skewers?
What?!
I would never eat a live chicken!
Then where did those
grilled chicken skewers come from?
Those were already prepared
dishes from the kitchen!
See, they're here.
Ah!
Hanamaru! Hanae! Hanakichi!
And Hanaemon, too!
Then why'd you
take the chickens?
The reason is…
I made up my mind
to live alone…
But I was still lonely, so…
Hisagomaru!
It's all right. You're not alone.
You have me, I'm your partner!
Master…
Hisagomaru!
– Master!
– Hisagomaru!
Just a minute.
There's one thing
I want to know…
Where is Hisagomaru?
The one who's at
the center of all of this?
Uh…well…you see…
We got separated
on our way back.
Where did everybody go?
Captain Unohana, my Itegumo
has manifested itself as well.
I know that.
Itegumo is right here!
I see it.
But we're watching scenes
from the next episode, right?
Let it go, Isane.
Even Hisagomaru got to have
screen time, so why only me?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I'm home!
Is that you, Ichigo?!
What's the matter, Yuzu?
There were sounds
coming from your room,
so I though you were
already home.
You don't think…
it's a burglar?!
They wouldn't!
Ichigo?
You stay down here!
SWORD BEAST
COUNTER MEASURE HEADQUARTERS
I knew it…
Who is it?! Who did this?
What?!