These criminals are guilty
of murdering Bakufu officials
as well as the leader
of those snooping dogs.
Stop.
We've heard enough, Your Highness.
We already know the rest of the story.
Try to commit a crime that's
worthy of this punishment.
What crime will you be guilty of?
The crime of
ripping off a lord's
topknot down there.
Are you sure about this?
You'll be sacrificing
everything for Yoshiwara.
It's too late.
I already made a promise.
I see.
In that case...
Promise me this.
We will all return alive.
Five Pinkies
I promise.
We'll bring the old man
back to Suzuran together.
Finished with your last farewells?
Nobume-san?
Are you joining us?
As a survivor of the Mimawarigumi,
I must fulfill my mission.
Besides...
I'll get to cut people up.
Hey!
Out of the way, mobs.
Or else we kill the princess!
Your Highness!
How dare you disrespect Her Highness?!
A hundred executions wouldn't
be enough to punish this crime!
Shut the hell up!
Zip your stinkin' mouths!
Every time someone speaks,
I cut off a finger.
Gin-san, assuming that
we manage to survive,
we won't be able to
live in Edo anymore.
H-Help!
Why is this happening to me?!
This is the only time her
acting has been believable!
How are we supposed to explain this?!
She said to zip your stinkin' mouth.
That applies to me, too?
How many times did you speak?
I-I don't know...
Okay...
I don't feel like counting,
so I'll do this.
What?!
Your Highness!
Okay, you talked again,
so one more time.
We understand! Let them pass!
Okay, you talked again,
so one more time.
Enough! That's enough!
That went well.
No, that did not go well, Your Highness.
The damage to our reputation
is irreparable now.
I was really nervous, but it was funny
how everyone was so surprised, right?
Right.
The Three Sadisteers can shut up!
However, it would be dangerous to
continue this charade, Your Highness.
Please find a place to hide.
Please let me help you see this through.
I didn't know what I was doing,
but I was the one chaining
Grampy inside the castle.
Grampy probably wanted
to leave the castle
All right!
far more than I did, but
I never noticed a thing...
Behave yourself,
Your Highness!
He was always watching over me.
So it's my turn to help him.
Even if it means he'll
scold me for misbehaving.
Soyo-chan...
Let's hurry.
My uncle is over here.
Your Highness?!
Wait!
She just knocked herself out
after saying she wanted to help!
Odd Jobs
This looks like a murder scene now!
And why did she write Odd
Jobs as her dying message?!
We can't let anyone see this!
It's faster to destroy the evidence.
You're too fast!
Oops, I really embarrassed myself.
Wait.
My embarrassment is faster
than my mouth can move.
Enough with the Ikkoku-dou!
What have you bastards done?!
There's a whole horde coming for us!
Hold on, Soyo-chan!
Kill every single one of the rebels!
No mercy for the women and children!
Women and children?
That's some big talk!
Naturally, that scum
would be served by scum.
This nation has no respect for women.
Open fire!
Show that you can stop
the women you sneer at!
Show that you can defend the castle
built upon the tears of those women!
Since you've forgotten about them,
we'll have to remind you!
Kill them!
These women
have come to topple a county.
Good grief.
We've got three nation
breakers with us.
That sounds tougher than
taking on the shogun.
I'll give you some advice.
Call for reinforcements.
You might be the shogun's
personal guards,
but you're probably too soft from
all the peace and quiet to take us on.
Meanwhile, we're still at war,
fighting for our lives every day
against those psychos!
Gin-chan, how many do we each take?
One hundred, two hundred...
Forget it. I'm putting myself to sleep.
Listen up.
Stay close together.
Trust the rest of us to watch your back
and focus on the enemies
in front of you.
As long as you're standing,
we're all standing.
Become the blade for
taking down that wall.
We're gonna crush the
shogun's silly toy box!
It's time to seize
this country!
S-Stop them!
Form a wall!
We can't let these rebels
get any closer to our lor—
Weak!
Weaker than Zazami Original!
And you call yourselves
the shogun's samurai?!
W-We can't stop them!
Not from the front, the
right, the left, the rear!
There's no opening!
The five rebels are
like a giant bullet!
Move!
We're going to shoot
down these crazy fools!
Fire!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
W-Watch our flanks!
Second round loaded!
Blow 'em to smithereens!
Again!
Hurry up with the next shot!
W-Wait! Our comrades are inside!
That was mean, Kagura-chan!
Why am I the only one
getting this treatment?!
Shit! They took the cannon!
We finally made it to
the shogun's place.
Huh? I don't see an intercom.
Oh well.
We'll have to use this.
Wait!
Not that!
Anything but that!
Shogun-sama!
Come out and play!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Shogun-sama.
The #1 delivery lady, the courtesan
Suzuran, has come to see you.
And it's too late to request a change.
Did you wash that filthy ass of yours?
You won't be getting any sleep tonight.
Life is filled with surprises.
You must be the first in
history to insult the Bakufu
and sully the Tokugawa name
in such a fashion.
If you intended to beg for mercy,
you've only added to your crimes.
You are the criminal here.
I, Imai Nobume, vice-captain
of the Mimawarigumi,
know everything you've done.
Tokugawa Sadasada,
you are under arrest for the
assassination of Bakufu officials.
A surviving Hitotsubashi
dog is talking about
judging me in a court of law?
How can you judge me when
I rule this country?
When I am the law?
If we cannot judge you on the surface,
we will judge you underground.
The woman's tears you
spilled in Yoshiwara...
The man's blood you spilled...
The heavens may forgive you,
but the law in Yoshiwara,
Lady Death, will not.
Release that man.
Where did you take him?
I just asked you a question!
When disaster strikes,
some choose to curse the heavens.
When misfortune befalls you,
it is the will of the heavens.
The fate the heavens have dealt.
You must silently accept that fate.
Our blades serve as the
voice of the heavens.
Who are they?
Be careful. That's not
your ordinary cult.
They're a group of assassins
who have served
the rulers of this nation from
the shadows for a long time.
Men of taboo who were eliminated
from central government
when we entered a period of peace.
When the Oniwabanshu was disbanded,
Sadasada turned to them
for his shady business.
We are the Yatagarasu for the heavens.
The Tenshoin Naraku.
Oboro...
The leader of the Tenshoin and
the strongest Naraku warrior.
That man is involved in this?
The one to judge is heaven.
In other words, the shogun.
The earth-crawlers are the
ones who are judged.
That is how the world works.
You are only allowed to
look up at the heavens.
However, you need not lament.
The heavens do not
always bring disaster.
The heavens also bring good fortune.
I believe you were
looking for that man.
Gr-Grampy!
If you can escape alive, you will be
able to reunite him with Suzuran.
Though I doubt he will survive
long enough to reach Yoshiwara.
Even if he does survive,
he's lost the pinky he swore on
and the arm he used to hold her.
He should just end his miserable life.
So much for loyalty when he's
betrayed me not once, but twice.
The heavens are punishing
him as a result.
And now he's literally an
earth-crawling worm.
Hey.
The pinky he swore on is still around.
He's got five pinkies right
here that are gonna drag you
from heaven to hell.
Wh-What are you...?
You've endured so much.
You've been through so much.
I'm sorry that you had to wait so long.
But there's nothing to worry about.
The moon you have longed for
has risen.
In the land where you once made a vow,
there is a light that will
shine through any darkness.
This moon will never fall.
Shinpachi, Kagura, please guide him.
We'll bring up the rear.
I'm allowed to cut down
whoever I want now, right?
Yes, do as you please.
In the morning, this will have
been nothing more than a dream.
You're buying time for
an old man to escape?
Do you really think you can escape
from my grasp?
I'm not running away.
Is it gonna be the sun or the
moon that sits up in the sky?
Let's settle this once and for all.
How about it, heavenly errand boy?
Let's go!
What are you doing, Gintoki?!
Pull yourself together!
If you want to die, I'll
cut you up right now.
You were hit in a pressure point.
By a poisoned needle.
Is it bad?
It'll paralyze you,
and kill you if the poison isn't removed.
You seem to be struggling.
It's rare to see someone
last so long against you, Oboro.
Actually, it's happened once before.
There was a demon who chose
to oppose the heavens.
You still have that same
look in your eyes,
White Yaksha.
Yo—
You're...
Gintoki?
Oh? Do you know him, Oboro?
My Lord, he is an orphan
of the Kansei purge.
Kansei purge?
Are you from Yoshiwara?
Then you wouldn't know.
The Joi war...
When the nation was opened
up, the ignorant samurai
accused the Bakufu of selling
the country and revolted.
As our relationship with the Amanto
soured, we put down the samurai.
Ever since, this nation has
been in a state of civil war.
As the war dragged on, the Amanto
began intervening in domestic affairs
under the pretense
of cleansing the rebels.
Ironic that the Joi revolt led
to increased Amanto influence.
And then the Tendoshu instructed
the Bakufu to initiate
the deadliest cleansing of the
century, the Kansei purge.
Every last Joi rebel, from
the minor agitators to
the public officials, was
targeted as part of the purge.
The brutal crackdown led to a
sharp decline in Joi activity.
Oboro and his brethren were
instrumental in that process.
They were led by his predecessor,
but he was every bit as
skilled in the martial arts.
My Lord, that wasn't the
end of the samurai.
While many samurai threw away their
swords after losing their leaders,
some were plotting to rescue
one of those captive leaders.
They were these men, the ones
known as the last samurai.
They were the students of
the evil criminal who dared
to oppose the heavens,
Yoshida Shoyo.
His students took up their swords
to rescue their teacher.
G-Gintoki?
You lost your teacher?
Do you recall that name, my Lord?
Yoshida Shoyo...
Was there such a person?
Do you think I remember the corpses of
every worm I stomped on my way to power?
If he happened to be a major
criminal, I might remember him.
What was his crime?
Actually, I can't recall either.
I do remember that he
taught sword and pen
to some children in the country.
That was it?
However, my Lord, we
were told to crush such gatherings
as they might foment rebellion.
I see. And I was correct to order that.
Yoshida Shoyo...
His crime was creating
dissenters like him.
Wait, Gintoki!
Why is the demon who battled the
heavens and fell to the ground
still wandering around here?
Why is the demon who lost everything
to the heavens still howling at them?
You, all of you, should
have learned your lesson.
You can shout, you can scream,
but your voices will
never reach the heavens.
And neither will your sobs.
Gintoki!
Will you make the same mistake
again, White Yaksha?
You can sit there and watch
until you bleed to death.
As everything you tried to
protect is destroyed again.
Shoyo is also watching
as the student he sacrificed
his life to protect
falls apart without protecting a thing.
Don't you leave...
Don't you leave!
You bastards are...
Gintoki!
Kagura-chan!
Die!
Move...
Move!
Please...
Excuse me.
What are you doing here
so late at night?
Excuse me, could you please
show me your license?
Good evening.
This is the police.
To be continued...
I can't wait for summer!
I'm so excited!
No kidding. I'm getting
goosebumps already.
Yup, when we go to the
theater this summer...
How many Pokemon will we get?
You're excited about that one?!
Pinky Swear
The situation is looking grim
when the Shinsengumi and
Mimawarigumi arrive!!
The revolt that began with five people
will reach its climax next week!!