Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo.
They finally reach Las Noches.
Upon breaking into the palace,
the group decides to split up
and go down separate paths
in order to look for Orihime.
Each of them encountered
powerful Arrancars who were waiting,
and a fierce battle began.
Ishida fights Arrancar Number 105,
Cirucci Sanderwicci,
whose ever-changing whip
puts Ishida into a predicament.
But Ishida is unexpectedly
saved by Pesche,
who was lost after
looking for Nel.
Angered, Cirucci releases
her zanpakuto and attacks.
Rip…
Golondrina!
Who should I slice first?
You're not getting away,
four eyes!
She knocked it away!
It's as I thought. All those feathers
are vibrating at high speeds!
That turbulent sound that's been
reverberating is proof of that!
Here! One more!
I have no choice.
Wha—?!
What…is that?
How unfortunate.
I was really hoping to hold off on
using this until a little later.
Shall we continue?
I'm glad that I took precautions.
When I left the hospital
with Mr. Urahara…
I figured it would be of some use,
so I borrowed it from
the hidden storehouse in the hospital
using Mr. Urahara’s ability.
Seeleschneider…
The only bladed Quincy weapon.
You “borrowed” it from a hidden
storehouse without permission?!
Y-You thief!
Shut up!
I never said that I took it
without permission!
Then did you take it with,
or without permission?!
Without!
See, you took it without permission,
you thief!
Whose side are you on?!
Just be quiet already!
What?! How can you talk like that
to the person who saved your life!
You're pathetic, Ichigo!
I'm Uryu!
What?!
What is it this time?!
You're Uryu?!
That's right!
Then who's Ishida?
I told you! It’s Uryu Ishida!
Ah… Which means that
you're not Ishida Uryu!
Enough already!
Quincy…
Wha—?
I see… So you're a Quincy, eh?
You know about them?
I feel honored.
I know about them.
They're that poor tribe
that was wiped out by
the Soul Reapers, aren't they?
But that's all I know!
That's right!
So why is someone like you
helping a Soul Reaper?!
I just don't understand!
I don't need to answer you.
Why don't you pay more attention
to your feathers instead of me?
Did you forget about earlier?
That wasn't a fluke or
a temporary rise in Spiritual Pressure.
A long flight record…
Will you stay quiet already?!
Humph!
Honestly. You're so ungrateful!
High-speed vibrations are destroyed
by even greater high-speed vibrations.
Seeleschneider works
like a chainsaw.
Reishi oscillates
at three million revolutions per second
along its Reishi blade.
Quincies are highly perceptive.
From what I can see,
the reishi on the surface
of your feathers oscillate
at about 1.1 to 1.3 million
revolutions per second.
That's less than
half of Seeleschneider’s.
So… In short, my feathers don't work
against you anymore, right?
Yeah. That's right.
Okay.
I didn't think that you could freely
remove your released form like that.
Is it the same for all of you?
We can't freely do this.
I discarded it.
What?
I can't go back to that form again.
The formal name for
our zanpakuto releases
is Resurrección,
or “Returning Blade.”
It's something that brings back
our original Hollow attack abilities
to our Arrancar bodies.
We can only return
to human form again
when we return our abilities
back into sword form.
Changing our forms without returning
our powers back into sword form
is the same as
burning off our own arm.
I’m bad at conserving energy.
I expend a lot of Spiritual Pressure
just by wearing these arms and feathers.
So if I can't use them,
I may as well discard them.
And it's much more useful…
To gather that excess
Spiritual Pressure.
Is this battle something you
really need to go that far to win?
Huh?! Are you stupid?!
If we didn't have to win, then we wouldn't
have started a war in the first place!
Arrancars are soldiers.
The Espada are their leaders.
We were born to kill
and defeat our enemies.
Forgivable defeats?
There is no such thing!
Not anywhere!
I should have done this sooner!
Take this!
There!
Tsk! Come to think of it,
there's no need to fight in a form
that leaves me vulnerable
to hits from your sword!
If we have swords
with the same abilities,
then the one with
the longer reach will win.
What is it? Have you given up?
The same ability?
You seem to be getting
slightly the wrong idea.
Seeleschneider's Spiritual Pressure
vibrations aren't for cutting.
It uses vibrations to loosen the bonds
between the reishi of the object it cuts
to make it easier
to take its reishi.
A Quincy battle is about gathering
the reishi from the surrounding area
and fighting with it as a weapon.
Seeleschneider is
the strongest embodiment of that idea.
Your reishi is pretty much mine.
Y-You've got to be kidding!
Also, you've got
another thing wrong.
Seeleschneider is not a sword.
Quincies don't use
any weapon other than bows.
Sorry… I win…
Cirucci Sanderwicci.
Indeed, one’s reach
was the winning factor.
Let's go, Pesche.
Is that all right? She's not dead.
The choice of whether someone
lives is in the hands of the victor.
I am the victor of this battle.
I pierced her soul chain,
the source of spiritual power production.
Arrancars are Hollows who have
become more like Soul Reapers…
Their soul structure
should be similar.
Letting her live may
be an insult to her,
but I have no intention of
stooping to their standards.
Even if she awakens
and comes after me,
she won't have enough
power to fight me.
I see…
If that's the case, that's fine.
Come on, let's go, Ichigo!
I'm Uryu.
Damn it.
That's quite a slight.
Lord Cirucci Sanderwicci…
I've come for you.
Please be quiet.
Damn it.
How trifling.
You're just no match for me,
Arrancar Number 107,
Gantenbainne Mosqueda.
It's useless.
A human who can't
even use a Sonido
will never be able to get
his attack to hit me!
I keep on telling you that.
Right, Yasutora Sado?
If you still want to fight,
I won't stop you. But you'll die.
Try and see if I'll die.
You only use
the force of strength.
But attacks like this
are useful too, you know.
I’ll say it to you once more…
You'll really die.
Right now, I have
no intention of dying.
Jeez. You've got some guts.
What?!
I told you that I have
no intention of dying.
Yasutora Sado,
I understand your feelings.
I suppose I've got to
fight you at full strength.
That's right…
I have to get past you.
Sounds pretty interesting.
I'm not finished yet!
You fool!
Uno!
Dos!
Cientos!
Stand, Yasutora Sado.
I know that you're still
hiding your power.
You're strong… Guys like you
shouldn't fight like this.
Swear, in the name of God…
that we'll fight fairly.
No response, huh?
That makes me sad!
Sorry.
I wasn't exactly hiding it.
It's just that ever since
I came to Hueco Mundo,
I sensed something about my power
that's different
from when I was in
the World of the Living.
I was puzzled
by that something,
and I wasn't able to get
a grasp of my power until now.
But I've finally grasped it…
I can use my full power
from here on.
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante.
This is my right arm's true form.
Ichigo and the others have
Nel and her group with them…
No one's come to me.
If you're jealous,
I'll trade places with you at any time.
What are you saying, Ichigo?!
We're best friends!
A best friend would
never get my name wrong.
|THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today we will discuss
sword releases.
An Arrancar's sword release is called
a Resurrección, or "Returning Blade."
An Arrancar does this to bring
its original Hollow attack abilities
to its Arrancar body.
What do you think? I'm pretty sexy
even when I'm released, aren't I?
But if you fly around like this,
won't we be able to see up your skirt?
I'm armored under my skirt too,
so it's all right!
What?! Just what do you think
men's fantasies are?!
I don't care!
I'm sorry.