[Flashback]
[End flashback]
That's right. Come on.
Getsugatensho!
This is a battle for all of us.
Los Nueve Aspectos.
Shall we end this, Komamura?
Justice...
is not something you can
see with your eyes.
It is also not something that
can be described in words.
I'm sorry, Tosen.
I cannot kill you.
You really...aren't Captain
Tosen anymore.
When you couldn't see, you could
have easily dodged this attack.
Reap...
Kazeshini.
I'm over here!
What's wrong, Aizen?!
I'm getting the better of you!
I've got you!
So that's it?
It was all nothing more
than a visual illusion?
your power is a far cry from my
ability to control all five senses.
It's child's play, Shinji Hirako.
Komamura...
Hisagi...
Don't speak.
Your Hollow powers are
allowing you to breathe,
but your throat is slashed.
You don't need to speak.
Our relationship was
a fleeting one.
It was our fate to cross blades...
and come to understand
each other.
I won't ask you not to hate me.
I won't ask you not to hold
a grudge against me.
Just don't throw away
your life for revenge.
Just like when you
lost your friend...
If I lost you, I would have
a hole in my heart.
Thank you...
Komamura.
Captain!
Aizen!
I won't forgive you, Aizen!
Behind you!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
What?!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Ryoka boy...
He blocked my first attack!
Your attack was good, but the
place you aimed for wasn't.
The back of one's neck is any
creature's greatest blind spot.
Did you think that I would
participate in this battle
without placing proper
protection?
Let me guess what
you're thinking.
You think you made an error of
judgment in your first attack.
You think you should have Hollowfied
yourself before attacking.
You think that if you had done
that, it would have ended this.
Am I wrong?
He's right.
I had to take him down with
the first blow. I knew that!
Do not look at his Shikai.
In order to do that, I have to take
him down with a single blow!
I must kill him.
Kill!
I was careless!
Somewhere inside of
me, I was scared.
I thought that I might lose control
of my Hollowfication.
I made a momentary
error of judgment!
Attack me.
I will show you that your
thoughts are arrogant.
That's right. Come on.
Getsugatensho!
What's wrong? It
didn't reach me.
Is that all you've got?
Listen well, Ryoka boy.
Your attacks are meaningless
against me.
You seem quite confident.
So my Hollowfication doesn't
scare you, is that right?
That's not what I'm
talking about.
Then what?
Are you saying that my zanpakuto
can't kill you?
You don't seem to understand.
I guess I have no choice.
I'll explain it to you in a way you
can understand, so listen closely.
I'm telling you that your
blade cannot reach me.
That's quite the claim.
Then I guess I'll
put it to the test!
I tried to explain it nicely,
but it seems like I still haven't
convinced you.
You could never convince
me with that!
I do know!
You're saying that
you can dodge
my Getsugatensho any
time you want, right?
In that case...
What's wrong?
You haven't reached me.
My timing was perfect.
I was sure of it!
Is this the power
of his zanpakuto?!
Don't worry.
I haven't been using my Kyokasuigetsu's
powers in our fight.
This is just my basic strength.
What?!
Why are you distancing yourself?
If you want to hit me, you
should come closer.
Or perhaps...
Are you afraid to lose sight of any
part of me by getting closer?
If that's the case,
how silly of you.
Properly distancing yourself
is only meaningful
when you're fighting someone who's
the same strength as you.
It's pointless for you
to do that with me.
See? I can even reach
your heart just like this.
Let me ask you one
thing, Ryoka boy.
Why do you fight me?
What?!
Do you have a grudge
against me?
No, you don't.
The fact that you're here means that you've
gotten Orihime Inoue back safely.
And from the expression on your face,
none of your friends have died.
Can you really hate me from
the bottom of your heart?
It's impossible.
Right now, you have no hatred.
You're just fighting out of
a sense of responsibility.
You won't be able to
reach me with that.
The will to fight without hatred
is like an eagle without wings.
You can't protect anything
with that.
Your powerless friends only serve
as weights to break your legs.
Don't let him overpower
you, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Komamura!
He's a master at provocation.
If you lose yourself,
you'll lose your life.
Don't let your guard down.
Don't worry.
I know the reason
why the captains
who went to Hueco Mundo
sent you here first.
I won't let you see
Aizen's Shikai!
We will fight to protect you.
Fight to protect me?!
What are you saying?
That's crazy.
You're all in terrible shape!
What do you mean it's crazy?
Letting you fight alone
is far crazier.
If you went alone, we can't settle
our own personal grudges.
So don't try to do this
by yourself. It's cocky.
This is
a battle
for all of us.
You sure charged in
without thinking.
That's pretty reckless,
Captain Hitsugaya.
We won't get anywhere unless
someone attacks.
Missing this opportunity would
be playing into your hands.
I commend you for not using your
Kyokasuigetsu from the start!
I commend you as well...
for having the wisdom
to not face me alone.
Are you saying I'm playing
dirty, Captain Aizen?
If that's how you're interpreting it,
I'll correct myself, Captain Kyoraku.
Toshiro... Kyoraku...
Ichigo Kurosaki...
I thank you.
Back there...
I won't forgive you, Aizen!
If you hadn't attacked Aizen,
I would have lunged at
Aizen in my fit of rage,
and I probably would have died.
Thank you.
Komamura...
Aizen said that you
have no hatred.
And that your blade
cannot reach him.
But we know.
Even without hatred,
you've ended countless battles.
You've protected countless people.
Your desire to protect
is good enough.
That is enough for you
to reach Aizen.
I don't mean your blade,
but your soul!
He sure likes to talk a lot.
Why didn't you bring Orihime
back with you?
If she was here, she could
heal us right away.
And then we could have fought
Aizen in perfect condition.
Hirako...
Then again,
you did bring back Unohana,
who's more rational, so I'll forgive you.
Yours was probably
the right choice
for this battle.
Listen, Ichigo.
We're going to protect you.
In exchange...
I want you to protect the things
you want to protect.
How long are you going
to stand there?
They can only create an
opening for an instant.
You're going to lose your
chance if you do that.
Don't think that we're prepared
to die in this battle.
We're fighting for survival.
Saving the world is just a
cause that sounds good.
We're fighting for our survival
and your survival,
so that we can protect everyone
else from Aizen.
Don't fall behind,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Hold on! Wait for me, Captain!
That's right...
What is your duty?
Your duty
is to protect that town.
Go. You are Karakura Town's
Substitute Soul Reaper.
What's there for
me to worry about?
These are the Visoreds
and the Captains!
I must believe in them.
It's all right if I
ask for their help.
I'll take a good look
at the direction
this battle will take!
Too bad. I was so close.
You seem quite confident,
Captain Kyoraku.
If you think that, I'm
doing pretty well.
For someone who's launching
sneak attacks, that is.
Aizen...
You mentioned earlier...
Right now, you
have no hatred.
You're just fighting out of
a sense of responsibility.
You won't be able
to reach me with that.
The will to fight without hatred
is like an eagle without wings.
You can't protect
anything with that.
You don't seem to know,
so I'll tell you.
The only time a captain swings
his sword is when it is his duty.
Swinging a sword out of hatred
is just filthy violence.
We don't call that a battle.
Aizen...
You truly are unworthy
of being a captain.
How interesting.
You hate me more than any captain
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
I never expected
you to say that.
Are you saying that you're not directing
any hatred at me with your sword?
Or perhaps...
When Hinamori recovered and came
to the World of the Living...
Did all of your hatred disappear?
How rude.
I'm talking right now,
Captain Kyoraku.
You still love to butt in.
It's a bad habit of yours.
I'm not very good at
listening to men.
I get bored listening to them.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll continue talking as I
take on the two of you.
That's enough talking, Aizen!
Bankai...
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
It's as you say, Aizen.
My sword is filled with hatred.
I didn't come here to fight you!
I came to violently kill you!
Argh! Komamura! Komamura, you're...
What about me?
Your fur, it's... I don't
know, all fluffy!
Oh, sorry about that.
Captain Hitsugaya's Spiritual
Pressure was so cold
that my body seemed to
have reacted this way.
So that's your winter coat?
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers...
Captain, how about we stop by
for some Japanese sweets?
You'll gain weight, Isane.
Ugh... You're right.
Are you two coming in?
The anmitsu dessert
here is the best!
Here, take a look!
See? See?!
Kote!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Let us be going, Isane.
Um... Yes, ma'am!
Retsu Unohana
Skilled in Kendo