Lake Toya
Hey, I'm back.
Didn't you hear that Gin-san's back?
Don't you idiots know how
to welcome someone?!
Man, they're so mean.
Are they upset about the
six month vacation?
Seriously, kids need way
too much attention.
Hi!
Long time no see,
Shin-chan, Kagura-chan!
How's it going?
Sorry I ran out on you for so long.
I brought you some Shinsengumi
manju, so cheer up.
Honestly, what were you doing?
You're late.
Get dressed.
We have a visitor.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Hurry up!
Kin-san!
Kin-chan!
Kin-san?
Be sure to watch Kintama in a well-lit room
and sit some distance from the TV!!
Oh, sorry about that.
I've got a splitting headache after
drinking too much last night.
Sorry about the poor reception.
I'm Odd Jobs Sakata Kintoki.
Please have a seat,
sir.
Nobody with Natural Straight
Hair Can Be That Bad
Sorry, I'm in the wrong place.
What the hell?
I'm so drunk, I ended up in a different
anime and pulled a Breakfast Attack.
Yeah, that was a shock.
I didn't hear about this
show being on TV Tokyo.
It looks like a ratings bomb
to me, so I'd be worried.
The last time I saw a
first episode this bad,
Gintama was switched to a different
time slot six months later.
Maybe I should have
given them some advice.
Like, to add a special
attack or something.
And Kintama is such a crass title.
Why not something flashy
like Kin no Exorcist?
They'll need to give that boring
four-eyes a bunch of moles
and turn him into the
main character's little brother
if they want the manga
to sell a million copies.
And if they're going with
a heroine that's a kid,
Sada-Sada Haru-Haru
Gobbles everyone down
they should make her small
enough to be a mascot,
then make her dance with that dog.
Tears everyone up
Tomorrow will be another bloody day
The nail in the coffin would
be the main character.
He's too polished.
Nobody's gonna remember a
guy with straight hair.
The main character needs wavy hair.
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
Snack Otose
Anyway, their faces looked
awfully familiar,
despite being a new show...
Whatever.
Time to go home.
Where is home?
Wait, it's not my hangover.
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
The sign's changed, but
that's clearly my home!
This isn't Ao no Exorcist
or Aka no Exorcist.
It's Dumb and Dumbercist!
That was clearly Shinpachi and Kagura!
The title changed from Gin to Kin.
Gintama
Kintama
Gold is more valuable than silver,
but the title's gone down the gutter.
But everything else about this show
is clearly Gintama!
So, so...
Who is this guy, this man
with blond straight hair?
Who is Sakata Kintoki?!
I wasn't gone that long.
What?
How?
Why?
So who was that guy anyway?
He kind of reminded me of Kin-chan.
Really? My head isn't that screwy.
That's right.
You were born with straight hair
and a straight personality.
Why was the main character's throne
changed from silver to gold?!
Oh, so you have a job for us?
You just turned around
and left earlier.
Is it something difficult
to talk about?
Just let it all out!
Odd Jobs is here to help people!
Oh, really...
Then I'll talk.
The thing is, you see,
I left the house for a while, and when
I came back, something was wrong.
The entire anime was wrong.
I've lost my place.
Ah, I see.
Like returning from a business trip
to find your wife with another man?
Yeah, yeah...
A strange man was wearing my bathrobe,
digging through my fridge,
and eating my pudding.
That would make me mad!
Right? Don't you want to kill him?
I'll **** the ***** ****
*** ** **** *****!
I'm gone a few months and ***
****** ** * **** into my house!
What the hell is his deal?!
Anyway, there's some
paperwork to be done,
so please give us your name.
Sakata Gintoki.
Wow, even your name is like Kin-chan's.
Are you long lost brothers?
They've completely forgotten
about the main character?!
Stop it, now.
He wouldn't want this
loser as a brother.
Hey, that's cold, Gran.
Gran, too!
Absolutely, gold is
much better than silver.
You're joining in, Catherine?
And Catherine!
It didn't take them long to
switch from silver to gold!
What's going on?!
Did they pawn off five years
of memories with Gin-san?!
How did you erase all the
time spent with Gin-san?!
And worst of all...
Now, now. Have a drink,
Gin-san or whatever.
We may not be related by blood,
but men can form bonds by
having a drink together.
If you're having problems, let me know,
brother!
...he's a much better main
character than Gin-san!
Super, Kin-chan! That's
why I love you!
Way to be a man, Kin-san!
And he's much better
liked than Gin-san!
Well, let's get going.
Honestly, he's too nice.
Don't do anything stupid.
Yeah, I'll leave this here to be safe.
That'll cover this month's rent.
Hold on. I don't charge
this much for rent.
Please, you must be getting old.
In that case, you might as
well forget about your job
and go visit a hot spring.
Come back in one piece!
And he certainly has enough
money to be golden!
My eyes! This guy is blinding me!
So my dull silver luster was
devoured by his golden shine?!
That's why everyone forgot about
Gin-san and switched to Kin-san?!
Seriously?! Are you serious?!
Gin-san's given you over
sixty volumes of DVDs!
Year 1
Year 2    Year 1
Year 3    Year 2    Year 1
Year 4    Year 3    Year 2    Year 1
Year 5    Year 4    Year 3    Year 2    Year 1
If you line up sixty volumes of DVDs,
that's enough room
for Tamo-san to take a nap!
Sleep your heart out!
Young Jump
Meanwhile, that guy's
only been on a single DVD
Kintama
Bonus DVD
that came with a volume of manga!
You can't even fit Tamo-san's
sunglasses on that!
He's still wet behind the ears!
Yet, look at the love he's getting.
In half a year, while I was gone,
he's repainted this city,
this anime, from silver to gold?!
So, Bro, about your request...
Do you want to punish your wife,
or do you want payback
on the other man?
Which would you prefer?
Neither.
Huh?
What do you want to do then?
Forget about gold and silver!
I'm going to paint this town red!
Could you help me carry these DVDs?
Oh, sorry!
The sixty volumes are so heavy
that my hands slipped!
You're going to die from the impact
of sixty volumes of DVDs to your skull!
Kin-chan!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Kochikame VHS tape collection slam!
Stop it!
If I let him survive, it'll be big trouble!
Complete One Piece DVD collection slam!
Stop!
Hey, stop it!
Naruto slam!
Bleach slam!
Didn't you hear me tell you to stop?!
What do you think you're
doing to our Kin-san?!
Kin-chan! Kin-chan, get up!
You're despicable!
Kin-san was trying to help
you, a total stranger!
Kin-chan!
How could you do this to him?!
Hold on, Pachi-boy.
I'm not a total stranger.
Don't call me Pachi-boy!
How do you have the nerve?
Tell me you're lying, Kagura!
This is all an act, right?
You're trying to trick me again.
Get lost.
Never show your face
in this town again.
If you come near Kin-chan
again, you'll get it.
W-Wait, Shinpachi! Kagura!
Who is this Kin-san you
keep talking about?!
Didn't the three of us work
together as Odd Jobs?!
Are you saying the
sixty volumes of DVDs
we spent together meant nothing?!
What are you talking about?
We spent sixty volumes of DVDs
with Kin-san!
A-A samurai?
Enough jabbering.
Are you in heat, fool?
Every episode's been edited!
I-Impossible!
This is... This is...
Wh-Who would have done
an edit job worse
than To Love-Ru Doki Doki?!
You think you can beat the
lightning speed of my sword?!
This one, too?!
Is he okay?
His hair's so wavy.
Perhaps he needs help?
No, you should stay away from him.
He might be one of those
wavy-haired con artists.
Let sleeping waves lie.
But we can't just ignore him.
I know. Let's ask Kin-san for help.
Yes, Kintoki has helped us many times.
He'll know what to do.
What's going on?
This DVD is also...
Guess who?
Sa-chan!
Do you recognize me?
Who are you?!
That's odd. I thought he was Kin-san.
So this DVD is also...
What do you think?
This is the Kabuki district, where
Kintoki and his friends live.
Oh, it reminds me of Yoshiwara.
Right?
There's strands of torn-out
hair everywhere.
And this one!
Hurry, Elizabeth!
Win the Costume
Grand Prix!!
We've spent six months perfecting
our techniques to use against Kin-chan!
Why would you do that?
Cut me some slack!
Okay, you pass!
I-I haven't just been forgotten.
My existence has been wiped
clean from this town,
from the sixty volumes of DVDs...
Sakata Gintoki's accomplishments
and history
have been stolen by Sakata Kintoki!
Pops, give me another one
so I can forget everything.
Honestly, you should
stop for the night.
If it's money you're
worried about, don't.
You'll forget I was
ever here soon enough.
What are you talking about?
Give me a hot one, Pops.
One for this guy, too.
Oh, sir. Thank you.
There are times when men have no choice
but to drink.
Right, Bro?
What happened?
Nothing.
I have nothing left.
Nothing at all...
Did you lose at the tracks?
Yeah, something like that.
I gambled my life and lost
it all in a single night.
A golden horse stole victory
at the very last second?
B-Bastard!
Calm down, Bro.
I bought you a drink
as a peace offering.
Sit down and join me.
Don't mess with me!
I told you to drink.
B-Bastard!
Who the hell are you?!
What did you do to Shinpachi
and everyone else?!
I didn't do a thing.
Didn't you watch the DVDs?
They should have been self-explanatory.
Bullshit! I was the one
who did everything!
But how can you prove it?
You're the only one who believes that.
Nobody can even remember you.
I can guess what you're thinking.
That I'm using illusions
to trick everyone.
But there's another way to look at it.
You're the one who's gone crazy.
Your memories are all delusions.
As you watched my success,
you began to think that you were me.
Maybe, as you were watching
those sixty DVD volumes,
you were fantasizing that
they were about you.
That's impossible!
But you're the only person in
this world who thinks that way.
Don't you get it?
You're the one who's crazy.
You're the only one complaining.
Weren't you watching?
Life goes on just fine without you.
I dare say it's going better
than in your fantasy world.
That's reality.
Nobody's looking at you.
Nobody needs you.
Because I'm here.
There's no place for you here.
Hey, watch where you're going!
Hold it right there!
I told you to wait!
Yeah, he's right.
Damn drunk!
Don't show your face
in this town again!
I'm the one who isn't
needed in this world.
You Will Not Defeat Me!
I'm the one who doesn't belong
in a prime time anime.
Sir, time's up.
S-Sir?
Wait, look!
B-Boss!
I'm burned...
Completely burned out...
Not gold, not silver...
I've been reduced to white ash.
The End
Don't try to end the show so
you don't have to pay up!
It's not over yet! There's
plenty more to come!
Stand up!
Stand up, bastard!
Shut up, dog.
Leave me alone.
You can ignore a side
character like me.
I told you to go away...
Sadaharu...
Sadaharu, do you recognize me?
I found you.
The gold hasn't gotten to
one person, one animal,
and one machine.
I've been looking for you, Master Gintoki.
Ta-Tama...
Why are you...
Do not worry.
The rest of the world may
have forgotten about you,
but you will always
remain in my data bank.
Because I always hold
the reset button when
I turn off the power and go to sleep.
I'm sure you do the same thing.
True,
your luster may not have
been as bright as gold...
You only shined on occasion.
You were always arguing and fighting.
You had wavy hair. You were lazy.
You were the king of sexual harassment.
You never paid the rent.
You paid your people late.
Still, you were brighter than
the fake glint of gold plating.
When you were angry, your
entire soul was enraged.
When you laughed, you laughed
with all your heart.
Your silver was much more beautiful.
You haven't forgotten
that light, have you?
You haven't allowed that fake
light to trick you, have you?
In that case, you should stand
up and take this sword
to repaint this world that
has been repainted gold.
You will never lose to Sakata Kintoki.
Kin-chan has your back
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
You won't lose to a blond.
You won't lose to straight hair.
You won't lose to gold.
Lake Toya
Try to remember what
color your soul is.
I haven't forgotten.
I will never forget.
My soul has been colored
by every one of you fools.
It's a dirty silver!
This isn't over yet.
I'm just getting started.
Gintama Episode 253
Nobody with Straight Blond Hair
Can Be That Good
We're taking back our color.
We're taking down this world of gold!
Gintama Episode 253
Nobody with Straight Blond Hair
Can Be That Good
Let's go!
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
Uh, excuse me.
Is Kintoki-kun here?
Sorry, I'm taking a bath right now.
Could you wait a bit?
Oh, it's okay.
Then I'll leave this letter
of challenge here.
Oh, maybe I should just come back.
What are you doing?
Are you here to fool
around? Are you an idiot?
Well, for some reason, it feels awkward
to step inside my own home,
but at the same time, I don't
want to wreck my own place.
Come over here.
Do you believe we can
win without a plan?
I'll be blunt.
The way things stand now, it's
impossible for you to win.
Didn't you just say I will never lose?
Straight blond hair, honest,
and fairly well-off.
How could you ever defeat
someone who has conquered
every one of your weaknesses?
Huh? What?
Are you trying to beat my ass
or tear my rectum out of my ass?
Which is it?
I'm beating your ass with your rectum.
Start by reading this.
You must know your enemy
before you can start a war.
An instruction manual?
Are you serious?
Instruction Manual
Confidential
How am I supposed to find
information about him in here?
He's not a plastic model.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was washing my head.
Huh? Nobody's here?
Yes, Sakata Kintoki was created
by Gengai-sama at the request of
Shinpachi-sama and Kagura-sama
as a substitute Odd Jobs leader.
A perfect Sakata Gintoki who
had overcome his weaknesses.
Ginpla Collection
Perfect Kintoki
The Perfect Super Golden Alloy,
Sakata Gintoki Unit 02.
Or Kin-san, for short.
To be continued...
Kintoki and Gintoki
Next time on Kintama:
Kintoki and Gintoki.