After Kira's efforts allowed them to obtain the Bakkouto,
which provided proof of treason,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
stormed the Kasumiohji Clan
and subdued their
squad of assassins.
Cornered, Kumoi took Rurichiyo hostage
and attempted to escape,
but Amagai, who suddenly
appeared at the scene, killed him.
Amagai was the mastermind in
the shadows who plotted the chaos.
Amagai, who had been plotting
the assassination of Genryusai for years,
aimed for this opportunity when
the Soul Reapers were called to
help take down the Kasumiohji Clan,
leaving Genryusai unguarded.
Amagai used the power of the Bakkouto Script
to neutralize Ryujinjakka,
and released his own Zanpakuto
to settle the score quickly.
Now, Ichigo, who had raced to the scene
with the aid of Kenryu and the others,
stands in Amagai's way.
Now is the time for me to
take my revenge for my father!
Out of my way, Kurosaki!
Shut up!
I've been listening to you
all this time.
You bastard.
That was nothing but selfish babble!
If you want revenge,
do it yourself!
Don't involve people
who have nothing to do with it!
You stay out of this!
You don't get it, do you?
Move!
You're the one who doesn't get it.
If you want me to move…
you'll have to force me!
Ichigo…
Rukia, take care of Rurichiyo.
Understood.
Kurosaki…
You are a curious one.
You refuse to back down?
Bankai!
It's useless.
What?!
What the—?!
I thought I told you.
My Bakkouto seals
the Spiritual Pressure of Soul Reapers
and the power of
their Zanpakuto.
Your attacks are
no match against me!
Leave the princess behind
and be gone!
Shut up!
I'm not handing over Rurichiyo!
You just don't get it.
It doesn't matter.
Either way,
the princess's fate is set.
What are you talking about?!
She can curse her destiny of
being born to the Kasumiohji Clan.
I'm not letting…
that happen!
There's no way you're going to kill me
with that soft swordplay!
Getsuga…
tensho!
Damn!
What's going on?
The Bakkouto should have sealed
this man's Spiritual Pressure,
but that technique just now,
though weak in power…
Raika!
Sorry, but I have no intention
of dealing with you forever.
I'm not done yet!
I'm not taking that!
Think again!
Ichigo!
Sorry to make you wait.
It's your turn at last.
You're kidding, right?
I'm just getting started.
Damn you!
Bastard.
You said you sealed
the power of my Zanpakuto,
but I still have power to spare!
You fool.
If you had just stayed down quietly,
your life would've been spared.
Shut up!
If that's how you want it…
then I have no choice
but to end your life!
You can't beat me by
just bobbing and weaving!
Again?!
How can he be exposed
to my Bakkouto's power
and still have this much speed?!
He should be affected
by the Bakkouto's power,
but instead Ichigo's power
is increasing.
This Spiritual Pressure…
Did he just reduce the damage
by using his Spiritual Pressure?
This man must be…
What's the matter?
Kurosaki…
What is the meaning
in fighting me here?
Meaning, you say?
I'm saying there's no need for you,
a person from the World of the Living,
to throw away your life intervening in
internal strife within Soul Society.
That has nothing to do with it!
I'm protecting Rurichiyo!
That's all there is!
That's laughable.
Are you saying it's that easy to throw
away your life for a complete stranger?
Captain Amagai's
Spiritual Pressure is rising!
If that's all your life is worth…
then die.
Kenryu! Enryu!
Where's Ichigo?
Is it over?
Is what over?
Nothing's ended yet.
What is that mask?
And what is that Spiritual Pressure?
Hollowfication…
I knew it.
He's fast!
This power…
it's completely different from before!
Interesting.
Don't underestimate me!
I see.
So that's the Hollowfication
I've heard stories about.
My Bakkouto has the power
to suppress the Spirit Energy
of any Soul Reaper
and render their
Zanpakuto powerless.
But when it comes to the power
of a Hollow, it's a different matter.
So it was because of this
power that you were able
to beat the Bakkouto up until now.
I get it now.
That's why Ichigo was able to fight
even under the influence of the Bakkouto.
And by Hollowfying,
he was able to reduce the
effects of the Bakkouto even further.
Right now, Ichigo is more than
a match for Captain Amagai.
Then I'll have to
get serious as well.
Why?
Why are you so
consumed with revenge?
You probably
wouldn't understand.
The emptiness of
being left behind.
The hatred you feel towards
those who remain.
The consciousness of those
who hold those feelings
is controlled by never-ending
feelings of darkness.
You always think of but one thing.
Their death.
What is my existence?
No matter how much you think about it,
the answer is always erased
by a voice that says, "Until you kill them,
you'll never see the answer."
Then it dawned on me.
That I would kill them and
my destiny at the same time!
Why?
Huh?
You possess the ability
to become a captain.
So why don't you have
the strength to move past that?
If I can accomplish my revenge,
I do not even mind death!
That is my strength!
As I thought, you don't want me
targeting your mask?
Ichigo!
I'm not going down so easily!
Curse you!
You're not getting away with this.
I'm taking you with me.
Your shape, your form, everything…
I'm going to incinerate it all!
Gouen Ryuga!
What's happening?!
Ichigo!
– Ichigo!
– Lady Rurichiyo!
Ichigo! You can stop now!
I do not want to see anyone get hurt
because of me anymore!
Don't worry.
Wait just a little more.
I'll make it so…
you won't have to make…
that sad face anymore!
You're still coming at me?
Damn right!
What are you doing, Ichigo?
I realize you can
prevent a flame attack
launched from an upright position
that way, but…
But still…
What is he trying to do?!
I know what it is!
Captain Amagai's weak spot
is his right side!
Given the space that
huge weapon needs,
if he can get inside of it
and target the Bakkouto…
I already knew what
you were aiming for!
You're after my right side…
the Bakkouto, aren't you?
Getsugatensho!
Lady Rurichiyo!
Lady Rurichiyo…
Are the two of you all right?
For you, Princess,
we would do this any number of times!
Rukia!
It's still too early for that!
No… It can't be.
I knew it. It's not over yet.
There is no end.
Until I accomplish my revenge…
Shigekuni Genryusai Yamamoto…
Rurichiyo Kasumiohji…
And Ichigo Kurosaki…
You too!
I will take you all
with me to hell for sure!
Stop it! You can't do anything
in your condition!
As I told you…
I will not find my answer
until I kill them.
And beyond that…is death!
Th-That's…
That mask… So Ichigo was
no ordinary Soul Reaper?
You are correct, Lady Rurichiyo.
Ichigo Kurosaki is in fact
a Mod Soul Reaper
created by
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
Oh, how amazing!
Stop it… Stop it!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Excuse me, sir.
A letter from Captain Kuchiki.
Thank you.
Please tell him I have indeed
received the letter.
It's almost time, Captain.
Is it already that time?
Sorry, but I must
excuse myself now.
Here you go, sir.
Please make yourself at home,
Lieutenant Abarai.
Y-Yes, sir!
W-What were those for?!
It's for his pet dog Goro.
Oh, is that right?