One hundred ten years ago…
At that time,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
had different members,
but there were some
very familiar faces.
The captain of Squad 5
was Shinji Hirako
who currently resides in the World
of the Living as a Visored.
Other Visoreds also held positions
as captains and lieutenants.
Furthermore,
Aizen was the lieutenant
under Hirako in Squad 5.
At that time,
Squad 12 captain Hikifune
was promoted to
the Royal Special Task Force
and left her position open.
Yoruichi Shihoin, who was the captain of
Squad 2 at that time,
personally recommended
the Third Seat in her squad.
Huh?
Umm… Don't tell me
I'm the last one?
I'm sorry I'm late.
And…
Nice to meet you all.
Jeez…
Looks like we got
a pretty loose one this time.
Like you should talk.
Umm…
May I enter?
Don't act like a wimp!
You're now a captain!
Stand tall and enter, Kisuke!
R-Right.
Yes, be quick and enter!
Now…
We shall proceed with
the installation ceremony.
I'm sure the rest of
you captains have heard.
Seven days ago,
Squad 12 Captain, Kirio Hikifune,
was ordered to
relinquish her position
due to a promotion elsewhere.
As a result, a search had begun
for a new squad captain,
and notice was sent
to other captains.
The following day,
upon Squad 2 Captain
Yoruichi Shihouin's recommendation,
the Third Seat from
her squad was summoned.
And yesterday…
I, Genryusai Yamamoto,
along with the three captains
who were present,
conducted an exam to evaluate
his qualifications
to become a captain.
We found no complaint
in his abilities and character.
Therefore, former Third Seat
of Squad 2,
Kisuke Urahara is promoted
to captain of Squad 12.
Umm… And so…
I'm your new captain.
Nice to meet you.
I won't accept this!
I already don't like
the fact that
Captain Hikifune is
gone so suddenly!
But you're from Squad 2?!
That's the Stealth Force!
Someone who spent his time
secretly killing people
can't possibly make it
as our captain!
Lieutenant…
You're going too far
in front of the captain.
What's that?!
I'm just bluntly saying
what you're all thinking!
Don't you guys feel the same?!
How can we follow
this new wimpy jerk?!
Well…
That's not…
What's so funny?!
I just insulted your old squad!
Why don't you react?!
Aren't you angry?
You coward!
Well, I'm now the captain
of Squad 12.
That's what I decided when
I woke up this morning.
"Once I get out of this bed,
I will belong to Squad 12."
I decided to become someone
who would get angry at
criticisms of Squad 12.
To be able to choose what
upsets you and what doesn't.
I believe such things constitute
"being able to start over."
Don't you agree?
What's that supposed to mean?
So silly!
Oww!
What the hell is he wearing
underneath those hakama trousers?!
Cripes… That baldy…
Now how can I get back at him?
What?!
W-What's going on?!
We're moving. Moving.
Move? Who's moving?
Captain Urahara's moving.
Don't call him captain!
Makes me wanna puke!
And what's with
all this furniture?!
There's so much junk!
Oh… What's the matter?
What're you gonna do
with so much stuff?!
Do? Well, my promotion
was so sudden…
And I felt bad asking
the squad members
to help me with
something personal.
But as you can see,
I couldn't manage by myself.
I won't accept this!
Oh, didn't you say that earlier?
And I'll say it over
and over again!
I refuse to accept
all this stuff! Ever!
Lieutenant?
Lieutenant!
You seem to be all right.
I'm not all right! Baldy!
Oww!
Damn! I can't stand this!
I can't stand this!
Every time I say it,
I can't stand it even more!
Umm…
Are you really all right?
About what?
You're not hurt?
Here, a first-aid box.
I'm the lieutenant of Squad 12!
I'm not a wimp like you.
I wouldn't even get
a scratch from that.
See?
Now, now, let's tend to that.
Oww…
Tend to your own face!
Umm…
Thank you all for helping me
move in yesterday.
I know I had a lot of things,
but I was able to fit them
all in the captain's quarters.
Are you crazy?
How could they all fit?
No, really. They fit.
Wanna come and see?
As if!
And…umm…
Stop saying "umm…"
That's so irritating!
Oh…sorry.
And? What is it? Speak up!
Oh…
Huh? What was I going to say?
How should I know?!
Oh! Right, right!
About the objectives of
Squad 12 from now on…
I thought about it all night.
About what we should stand for.
Oh? Let's hear it then.
Speak.
I'm still thinking.
– Huh?!
Still thinking?
Thinking?
And anyway…
I have lots of things to unpack,
so I'd like you to
wait a bit longer
and give me time to think.
Are you some kind of kid?!
"Still thinking"?!
What is that supposed to mean?!
What's with that face?
I always look like this!
What're you staring at?! Baldy!
I'm not bald, idiot.
You probably heard the rumors
and came to make fun of me.
Didn't you, baldy?!
Why would I do that?
I'm just catching some sun, idiot.
I could care less about
your squad, idiot.
Quit calling me "idiot",
you idiot!
I was going to
tell you something.
Now what was it?
Umm…
Quit saying "umm"
when you're around me!
Oww…
What's the big idea, Hiyori?!
Hey! Stop right there!
What's with her?
She's so upset.
Nice weather.
It sure is.
You got that right.
Oh… C-Captain.
E-Excuse us!
Oh no, at ease, at ease.
Don't worry about it.
When things are slow like this,
you get so relaxed.
Yeah.
Well, I guess it's okay.
It's not like we've been
ordered into action.
There's nothing to do, after all.
You're right.
Hey!
Oh…
Hello.
Not "hello"!
What're you doing?!
Well…
It's just so peaceful.
And serene…
You're just sitting there
in a daze, you idiot!
That's true, but…
And you two!
This idiot's contagious
loose manners
have infected you both!
Now now…
In our long span of life,
relaxing moments like this
are very important.
You're too relaxed!
If this goes on, our squad will be
known as the hangout for losers!
Although I don't accept you
as the captain,
if you're
"someone who would get"
"angry at criticisms
of Squad 12"
then show me what you've got!
Fine.
However…
How about we do this
with our bare hands?
No need to use our Zanpakuto.
Spar with the lieutenant
without weapons?
That's so reckless.
All right! Here we go!
Go ahead. You can attack me
from any direction.
Come!
He's so weak.
He didn't even
have time to dodge.
– Captain!
– Are you all right?!
That guy…
He totally read my move!
And yet, well aware that he
would get hit, he moved back.
Could he have done so to spare me
embarrassment from the others?
Why? What kind of man is he?
I don't get it.
As expected…
You seem bored.
Oh, Captain Hirako…
Just call me Shinji.
We're both captains.
What do you think of Hiyori?
A pain in the butt?
No…
She was close to Captain Hikifune…
thought of her as a mother.
It'll be hard to win her over.
You're right.
I want us to get along, but…
It's just not going as smoothly
as my predecessor.
Are you being truthful about that?
I don't like to act like
I know it all.
But hear me out as one who's been
captain a bit longer than you.
Those who rule…can sympathize
with those who serve,
but they must not show it.
Do things the way you like.
And if no one follows,
then you just weren't
the right vessel to lead them.
And besides…
You don't look the type
to be much good at
thinking about
how others feel.
Well anyway…
Don't let this bother you too much.
You and I seem to share
something in common
and I couldn't help but
be a busybody.
'Night.
How long are you going to
stand there and watch…Sosuke?
I'm impressed.
How long have you
been aware of me?
From the time you were
in your mama's womb.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Captain.
What is it?
You're a frightening man,
after all.
That's my line.
Yoruichi…
It's just as you said.
Being a captain…looks like fun.
W-What…
What the hell is all of this?!
Oh, good morning, Hiyori.
Just where do you
think this is, you?!
This is the captain's room!
The captain's room!
You can't just go and
do your own renovations!
It's okay.
I mean, it's my room.
What?!
Besides, it's not a renovation.
I just did a little rearranging.
How is this "rearranging"?!
There's absolutely nothing
of the old room left!
It doesn't have to be right away.
Just a little at a time…
Just try to understand me…
a little at a time.
And I'll try to understand you…
a little at a time, Hiyori.
Okay?
No way!
Oh yes…
I have a favor to
ask of you, Hiyori.
W-What is it?
I want you to come with me
right now to the Maggot's Nest.
Maggot's Nest?!
A sad voice resonates
deep within Seireitei.
An ominous shadow
beyond the gate.
Next time, the young girl sees!
A cursed labyrinth
spreads underground.
The mystery of the Maggot's Nest!
Don't miss it!
What the hell are
you talking about?
Is that supposed to be a promo for
some sort of suspense-horror movie?
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
The Combat Pass certifies that
one is a Substitute Soul Reaper.
SUBSTITUTE SOUL REAPER
COMBAT PASS
A Hollow?
Don't use the Combat Pass
so freely!
Or you'll have trouble
dealing with the body
after you transform
into a Soul Reaper.
If you use a Soul Candy, you won't
even have to leave class!
Kon! Take care of the rest!
You can count on me!
Take that!
Sorry, Ichigo.
What the hell did you do?