I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Soul Reapers...they are
the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers
who keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Aizen, who had taken the Hogyoku
from Soul Society,
has finally made his move.
And the battle between
the Arrancars and the Soul Reapers
has finally begun
to manifest itself.
The life-and-death struggle
between Edrad, an Arrancar,
and the Squad 11 Third Seat,
Ikkaku Madarame,
was extremely fierce.
Awaken!
Volcanica!
Well, well... I really didn't expect to
use it in a place like this!
Ban...kai!
Edrad released his zanpakuto,
Volcanica.
In order to match this,
Ikkaku used his Bankai,
Ryumon Hozukimaru,
which he had been hiding.
That's pretty awesome.
You can decide whether
it's awesome or not...
when you're dead!
Unlike me, Hozukimaru likes
to take his time...
Even after Bankai,
he continues to sleep.
But when he starts to wake up...
the dragon starts to turn red.
And when it's all dyed red,
for the first time,
Ryumon Hozukimaru reaches
ultimate strength.
At the end of a mighty clash
of power,
Ikkaku finally defeated Edrad.
Rukia!
Rangiku...
Toshiro...
Matsumoto...
Crap...
So this is all a captain can do,
even when he uses his Bankai...
I'm very disappointed...
It seems like you really were
the biggest disappointment.
Why you...!
I'm not finished yet!
You're fast for someone
your size, brother.
Shut up!
Crap!
Is that the best your Bankai
can do, brother?!
A piece of trash like you
is a lieutenant?!
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
aren't all that great, are they?!
You bastard!
Captain Hitsugaya,
Lieutenant Matsumoto,
and Lieutenant Abarai are
having a tough battle.
Crap!
The Spiritual Pressures of
the Arrancar are far greater
than we had anticipated.
At this rate...
I know! Aren't we going
to get permission yet?!
Danger...
Danger... Danger...
Renji's in trouble!
He looks like he's having
a tough battle...
It's a big problem.
What should we do?
What can we do?
What's with him?
He looks like he's going to lose...
Come on, what will you do next, brother?
If you're not going
to do anything...
Then I guess I will.
An opening!
What did you do?
What is this?!
Now!
I'm going to use my power
to make him see illusions.
Then Kurodo is going to
change into you
and attack him with
Noba's teleportation!
I'm over here!
Stop!
That sort of attack won't work
on him!
It's all right! We'll manage!
Kurodo! Noba!
Kurodo!
All right!
Don't underestimate me!
Wha-?!
You brat!
L-Lirin!
K-Kurodo!
Lirin!
Noba!
Did you think you could
stop me with that?
The whole lot of them...
Honestly...
Ururu? What's with you?
I told you to sleep...
She's...
The Arrancar's strange Spiritual Pressure
is affecting her.
Wait! Ururu!
Crap!
Now then,
let's put an end to this, brother!
Crap!
Who are you?!
Danger...
You are dangerous...
Dangerous to us...
Enemies are dangerous...
Enemies must be...eliminated.
Ururu...you...
Crap...
You piece of crap!
You brat! Making fun of me!
Crap...crap!
I'll do it...I'll do it!
Impale! Del Toro!
This is our, the Arrancars',
zanpakuto release, brother.
You bastard!
Get away, Jinta!
Okay!
Do you think that
you've stopped me, brother?
Freeloader!
Before you die,
I shall tell you my name, brother!
Arrancar Quince... Illfort Grantz!
Illfort has released his power...
Has he gotten bored? Does he want to finish
things quickly?
Or did he get seriously
wounded from
an unexpected counter attack
which forced him to release his power?
That wouldn't happen...
How silly.
I'm not finished yet!
You flung your tail at me.
This is the best you can do
when you're desperate?
I am very disappointed.
You have fewer ice flowers,
don't you?
What about it?
Those flowers that float
behind you
probably serve as
a countdown to the time
when your Bankai comes to an end...
Am I wrong?
You are young.
Your Bankai is probably incomplete.
Bankai requires enormous amounts
of spiritual energy.
Even if you are a captain,
it will be difficult to remain in Bankai
mode for long periods of time.
Your incomplete Bankai is
especially remarkable in that respect.
You had twelve petals...
You only have three left...
In other words,
when all of them are gone
your Bankai will go away.
It would be easy to defeat you
once that happens,
but despite how weak you are,
it would be unsporting to behave
that way towards a captain.
I shall crush you in that state at
my maximum fighting power.
Snip!
Tijereta!
Wha-?
I guess I'll tell you my real name...
Arrancar Undécimo...
Shawlong Qufang.
I give you my regards, little captain.
As I expected of a captain!
Even if I've shown you
the full might of my strength,
you face me and don't run away.
Wonderful!
It truly is!
You say your name is
Shawlong Qufang?
I want to ask you one thing...
You called yourself
Arrancar Undécimo...
Undécimo... It means that
you're the eleventh.
Does that mean that
you're the eleventh strongest
of the Arrancar?
No...
Our numbers are not
a strength hierarchy,
but our order of birth.
But only for those below me...
Let me make this easy to explain.
When we are changed from
Hollow to Arrancar,
we are given numbers from eleven
onwards by order of our birth.
Those of us with especially
outstanding killing abilities are given
the numbers 1 through 10
by order of our abilities.
These chosen ten are
called the Espada.
The number they were given
is branded somewhere on their body
and they are given the authority
to control us lower numbers.
I shall make this clear.
The strength of the Espada is
in a different league than ours.
Furthermore, one of those Espada
is with us right now.
He has been given
the number six by Lord Aizen.
Seis Espada...
Grimmjow Jeagerjaques.
Crap!
Hey! Are you making fun of me,
Soul Reaper?
I don't feel like killing you
as you are at all.
Show me your Bankai
while I'm holding back on you.
If not, you're going to get
a big hole in you...
Just like that Soul Reaper lying there!
You bastard!
Bankai!
So this is the guy.
Is it ready yet?!
I won't be able to hold out
at this rate...
Isn't it ready yet? It's late!
She's still breathing...
Squad 10 Lieutenant,
Rangiku Matsumoto!
Your "Gentei Kaijo" permission request...
has been granted!
Thank you!
Captain! Renji!
We've been granted
a Gentei Kaijo!
It's finally come!
I've been waiting for that!
What's this?
Gentei Kaijo!
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
Aw man, the Arrancars
are too strong!
It's all right.
They have a Gentei Kaijo.
A Gentei Kaijo is a big technique
that triggers an explosion
by releasing a limited Spiritual Pressure
bomb made with kido.
- Really?
- He's lying.
Don't tell such convincing lies!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
KON'S MANLY EROTIC CONQUEST
OF SOUL SOCIETY
Golden!
- What did Hanataro do?!
- It's a guy from Squad 4! Get him!
Damn it!
- Your earlier treatment hurt!
- Wait. He's a Soul Reaper!
- It's your fault!
I could use this zanpakuto,
couldn't I?
Take this!
This is Hanataro Yamada's zanpakuto!
- Huh?
My zanpakuto, Hisagomaru,
heals the person it cuts!