Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Let's have fun! Byakuya Kuchiki!
Scatter…
That's not working.
How fun…
Looks like your speed is
only good for running away!
Laughable.
Scatter…
Impressive…
Captain!
Brother!
Rukia!
You can't go near him right now!
Brother!
Move!
I will not allow you to pass!
Damn it!
Getsugatensho!
Don't concern yourself
with me any further…
Otherwise, next time I'll be
forced to take your life…
Take my life, you say?
Fine! Go ahead and try!
I've always wanted to have
a fight to the death with you.
You're finally on board!
Come at me with that spirit…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
I see.
Then you leave me no choice.
What the—?
Brother!
Wait, Rukia!
Let go, Renji!
I must go to my brother!
Oh no!
What is that?
Byakuya!
You!
Damn…
Wha—?
W-Wait…
How long do you intend
to keep running?!
You dodged that nicely.
You thought you couldn't dodge it,
so you used your arm
in that instant to counter.
That was a smart decision,
but you just gave me more targets.
This time what shall I aim for?
Why? Our speed
should be equal.
And yet…
Is it so strange that you
can't catch up with me?
What?
You, the fastest Reaper
in Soul Society,
and I, your Zanpakuto,
are just about equal in speed.
But while my attacks
make direct hits,
your attacks keep missing me.
"Oh dear, oh dear!"
That's written all over your face.
That's why you're
completely hopeless.
Too bad! I wonder what
it'll take to get me?
I'll bet you've never fought
with anyone smaller than you.
When equal in speed,
the one who is smaller, me,
will have the advantage.
Isn't that common sense?
Your thinking is way too biased.
Why, even the way
you feel about Yoruichi…
When she's gone, you hate her.
When she returns,
you tag along wherever she goes.
Don't you ever walk
the middle ground?
What would you
know about Yoruichi?!
A lot!
I was your Zanpakuto.
She's the one making you rot!
What's with that look?
Oh, did I upset you?
You can't quite get me, can you?
Your attacks never work, do they?
Well, I'll deliver
the finishing blow!
Can you keep up with my moves?
Where shall I strike
the final blow?
Right here!
W-What?!
Th-This is…
W-Why?
I concentrated the power of Shunko
around the Homonka you aimed for.
A sword will not penetrate it.
Sorry, but I do not rely
solely on my Zanpakuto.
That is what I was taught,
how I trained to get to this point.
What?
Found you!
Is this hide-and-seek?
Oh!
Found you again!
Yay! Now let's play tag!
Wait, wait!
Gotcha!
Ban…k…
Hey, thanks for
interfering with my fight.
Because of you,
Kuchiki got away.
So how are you gonna
make up for that? Huh?!
What the?
That is my Zanpakuto.
You can't just do whatever
you please with it.
It is my duty to administer
the punishment
for betraying its master.
Why you—
I must get back quickly.
Looks like you had a rough time.
Y-Yoruichi!
What is it, Soi Fon?
Stop! Please, not that!
– What are you saying?
– Let go!
Your body has been infused
with a deadly poison.
You must be treated quickly,
or it will be too late.
I don't need that stuff!
I've already heard that
your treatments don't really work!
Goodness!
Who told you such a thing?
Ishida! Ishida told me!
Oh… That Quincy.
I knew I should have
restructured him too,
so that he wouldn't
talk unnecessarily.
"Too"? Did you just say "too"?
Which means, you intended
to restructure me too!
You talk too much!
I just meant that since
I'm treating you anyway,
I can restructure you
without charge.
You should be grateful!
Why would I be happy
being injected
with something that's
totally suspicious?!
Nemu!
What?! What's going on?!
– Hey!
– Please calm down.
Hold him down, Nemu.
– Let go!
– Yo.
I don't care what
you do to him,
as long as he's still
able to fight me.
Kenpachi…
Hey, don't just stand there.
Stop him!
Why?
I don't care if you're
a machine or a monster.
As long as I can have
fun fighting with you.
Why you—
Hang in there, Icchi!
By the way, how come the poison
isn't affecting you two?
Well… Umm…
We held our breath so that we
wouldn't breathe in the poison,
so we were fine!
Strange…
The poison is supposed to
enter your body
whether it's breathed in or not.
Maybe it doesn't work on idiots.
Or, I bet it's that…
I'll bet Captain Zaraki's Spiritual
Pressure repelled the poison.
Kyoraku! Ukitake!
Sorry we're late.
Are you all right?
Captain Kurotsuchi…
Thank you for
tending to everyone.
Squad 4 will take over from here.
I'm saved!
Please be quiet.
Let me go!
My poison cannot be
so easily treated
by those unfamiliar with it.
Please rest assured.
We just treated Isane
and the others
who had been
attacked by Ashisogijizo…
We've already analyzed
its contents.
That was unwarranted!
Next time,
I'll come up with a poison
that even you, Captain Unohana,
cannot analyze so quickly.
I'm looking forward to it.
What are these two
sparring about?
Captain Unohana…
You said the Ashisogijizo
attacked?
Yes…
before coming here,
Konjiki Ashisogijizo
infiltrated the Seireitei.
Hado 31, Shakkaho!
Ban…kai…
Oh no! It's catching up to us!
Hinamori!
I'm sorry… I think the poison
has taken effect…
You…always overdo it.
I'm glad it went well…
Hinamori!
What's wrong?!
Rangiku!
Matsumoto!
Kotetsu!
Not me too?
Fortunately, Ashisogijizo
went on its rampage
close to the Squad 4 barracks.
The four are being
treated there now.
Their lives are not in danger.
They should recover
after some bed rest.
Thank you, Unohana.
Captain Unohana!
Lieutenant Kira was discovered
between the collapsed buildings.
In addition,
we found Third Seat Madarame
in a corner of the courtyard
and Fifth Seat Ayasegawa
beyond the forest—
all of them unconscious!
I understand.
Everyone,
I can handle things here.
Please go ahead.
– Yes ma'am!
Hey, what about your Zanpakuto?
Was it okay to break it?
It doesn't matter.
This was necessary
in order to explicate
the way the Zanpakuto
are being brainwashed.
Huh? So earlier,
you made it submit?
Hardly. It simply self-destructed.
It's no different from that
ruffian breaking Wabisuke.
Then you…
Quiet already.
I broke it in order to
discover new information.
And it's none of your business.
You don't care about
losing your own sword
for the sake of an experiment?
Of course not!
You're so reliable
at times like this.
Kuchiki, are you all right?
I'm sorry to cause you concern.
It's fine. Just stay still.
Yes…
You couldn't stop Byakuya?
No…
Just what…
does he intend to do?
Good work…
Are you heading for
the World of the Living?
Follow me.
Now then…
I guess I'll go.
Where are you going, Zaraki?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm gonna find Kuchiki
and challenge him.
Ken, that sounds like fun!
You won't find him
just searching blindly.
Yoruichi!
Yoruichi Shihoin, you're back?
They really did a number
on this place.
So, do you know
where they are?
No!
What?!
But I've located
the Head Captain's whereabouts.
Wanna go?
It's here.
Renji, do you know where
my broken Sodenoshirayuki is?
Speaking of which,
Zabimaru is missing too.
Oh, Captain Kurotsuchi
took them all.
He said he's going to
repair them.
That's good—What?!
We've got to get them back
before he restructures them!
Sodenoshirayuki!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Now that I've manifested myself,
I think I'd like to dress up a bit.
Oh, this is nice.
Hmm…I'd like something cute.
Oh, this one's nice.
Well, that old lady wouldn't
comprehend how cute this is.
Well, that young girl wouldn't
– Excuse me, I'll take th—! Huh?