Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
It's been quite some time
since I last saw your face.
What's with the change
of heart, Komamura?
How can you still smile
like that, Aizen?!
You betrayed all of us!
I will not forgive you!
You too…
Tosen!
S-Sorry…
I didn't think anyone was here…
This way.
Huh?
That's odd…
Sorry, I mean…
I didn’t think you were there.
I'm Kaname Tosen.
Pleased to meet you.
You really are good at
hiding your presence.
I can't see, but I was never unable
to sense someone's presence…
Komamura?
You're Komamura, right?
It's been a while!
I see. You've also joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Do you want to join my Squad?
I have a wonderful superior!
I'm sure you’ll like him, too.
You’re Komamura, right?
I've heard about you from Tosen.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Squad 5 Lieutenant
Sosuke Aizen.
Why did you become
a Soul Reaper?
In order to repay the kindness
to one man who saved me.
A debt of gratitude, huh?
That is your style.
What about you, Tosen?
Me? Well…
Tosen!
Explain yourself if you can!
Or can’t you?
How regrettable, Tosen!
Bankai!
Impossible…
Aizen is still standing next
to Tosen…
Hado 90.
Kurohitsugi.
They’re both captains…
yet there's such a difference in strength.
Kyokasuigetsu's perfect hypnosis
is flawless.
There’s no way to escape it
even if you know it’s coming.
Hado 90 without the chant.
How scary.
When did you learn
how to do that?
No, it was a failure…
I didn’t even get a third of
its true destructive force.
Ninety really is hard to control.
Now then…
Sorry, I hadn’t finished
explaining, had I?
Kurosaki!
Stay back!
Kuchiki!
Oh no no.
You shouldn’t be moving.
Inoue! Ishida!
What incredible Spiritual Pressure!
Rukia Kuchiki…
When I found out you were
in the World of the Living,
the first thing I did…
was to eliminate the Central 46.
Wha--?
Isane probably told you
“Sosuke Aizen faked his death
and hid his whereabouts.”
“Afterwards, he slaughtered Central 46.”
But that's not true.
As soon as I discovered you,
I immediately killed Central 46
and used my Kyokasuigetsu
on the entire central underground
assembly hall.
So that it looked as if Central 46
was still alive and having meetings.
We always had one of us three
in the underground assembly hall.
Since then, we had been acting
as Central 46
and been issuing all
of their orders.
To make sure of your arrest,
I sent those two from Squad 6
to apprehend you.
In order to separate you
from the humans…
I ordered the immediate return
and destruction of your gigai.
In order to completely evaporate
your soul
and take the Hogyoku
from within you,
I decided to have you executed
with the Sokyoku.
The only time we weren't in
the underground assembly hall…
were the few hours surrounding
the two Captain's Meetings.
I faked my death soon after that
and hid underground.
Because I knew there was a possibility
that the execution might fail
because of you guys.
There are only two ways
to remove a foreign object planted
directly into a soul.
You can use an intense thermal disruption
like the Sokyoku
which will evaporate the soul
that envelops it…
Or by some other method that will interfere
with the soul's composition
and forcefully separate them…
In the unlikely event that
the execution by Sokyoku failed,
I had to find that other method.
For that, I needed the information
kept within the underground assembly
hall's Daireisho Archive.
I looked up Kisuke Urahara's
past research.
He was the one who developed
the technique
to plant a foreign object into a soul.
So I figured that…
the technique needed to remove it
must be hidden somewhere
in his research.
Yes.
This is…that answer.
Wait--!
I'm surprised.
It's so small.
This is the Hogyoku…
I see.
The soul is unharmed.
What a wonderful technique.
But, too bad.
I have no use for you anymore…
Kill her, Gin.
Oh well.
Shoot 'im dead, Shinso!
B-Brother!
Brother!
Brother…why?
Why did you save me?!
Let's go, Jidanbo!
All right!
Bones of beasts scattered
far and wide!
Steeple crimson crystal!
Steel wheels!
Wind in action!
And the sky at rest!
The sound of flying arrows,
fill the hollow castle!
Hado 63: Raikoho!
Sis!
Jidanbo!
This is another face I haven't seen
for quite some time.
Don't move!
If you move a muscle…
We'll cut off your head!
I see.
Kukaku!
Hey, Yoruichi!
I had too much free time…
And since I was out on a walk,
I thought I'd check in!
Well. That sure was flashy.
What should I do?
Don't move.
Sorry, Captain Aizen. I got caught.
This is it.
What did you say?
Don't you understand, Aizen?
There's no place…
left for you.
Aizen…
Captain Aizen!
It's over, Aizen!
What's so funny?!
Oh, sorry. It's time.
Get away from him, Soi Fon!
I-Impossible!
Menos Grande!
The Gillians!
How many of them are there?!
No, wait…
There's something else in there!
It's a bit of a let down…
I wouldn’t have minded being
your prisoner a little longer…
Goodbye, Rangiku.
I’m sorry.
You're going to run away? You…
Stop!
Head Captain!
That light is called “Negacion.”
The Menos use it to help save
their fellow Hollows.
Once enveloped by that light,
it is impossible for those
within and without to interact.
It's an isolated world.
All who have fought Menos know…
The moment that light fell
on Sosuke Aizen
it became impossible to reach him.
Tosen!
Come down here, Tosen!
I don't understand!
Why did you become
a Soul Reaper?!
Wasn't it for your friend
who passed away?!
Wasn't it to carry out your justice?!
Where has your sense of justice gone?!
I told you, Komamura.
The only thing I can see with
my eyes is the least bloody path.
Justice is always there.
The path I follow is justice!
Tosen!
You've joined with the Menos…
Why?!
To reach higher.
Have you fallen so much, Aizen?
You're too arrogant, Ukitake.
No one stood at the top from
the beginning.
Neither you, nor me,
nor the gods.
But that unbearable vacancy
of heaven’s throne ends now.
From now on…
I will stand atop the heavens.
Goodbye, Soul Reapers.
And goodbye, Ryoka boy.
For a human,
you were quite amusing.
Groups Two and Three,
care for Captain Kuchiki!
Groups Seven, Ten, Eleven,
and Thirteen
all help to heal Captain Komamura!
Lieutenant Abarai has received
stage six treatment.
Groups Eight and Nine,
prepare for transport!
Let’s go!
They’re all seriously wounded!
Let’s move it!
Brother!
Please stay back.
He’s being treated right now!
I'm all right.
See to the others…
P-Please, Captain Komamura!
That's good. Slowly…
Excuse me… Third Seat Iemura.
What should we do?
Help treat the Ryoka.
Huh?
B-But…
You must’ve realized by now.
They saved the Soul Society.
Now move!
Y-Yes!
But…
That Ryoka girl…
What's with her ability?!
Good work!
Captain Unohana!
What’s the condition of Captain Hitsugaya
and Lieutenant Hinamori?
They’ve escaped death.
It’s up to them now.
Isane is continuing to treat them.
Who's left?
Captain Kuchiki and the Ryoka boy!
It doesn't seem like
the Ryoka needs our help.
Huh?! Is…that so?
You were reckless…
Captain Kuchiki.
Rukia Kuchiki…
Come here.
Captain Kuchiki is asking for you.
Rukia… Are you there?
Yes, Brother…
There’s something I want to tell you.
An old story…
From fifty years ago.
In that year,
before the first plum-blossoms bloomed…
I lost my wife.
I know. Lady Hisana.
I was told that I looked
like your wife.
That’s why you took a liking to me
and welcomed me into the Kuchiki family
as your younger sister.
That's right.
I ordered everyone in the household
to tell you that lie.
Huh?
Hisana was…your older sister.
Hisana died in the World of the Living
and was sent with you
to “Hanging Dog.”
But life was too difficult there…
She said she left her baby sister
and ran away.
Hisana regretted that.
Even after she became my wife,
she searched for you
almost every day.
Then, in the spring of
our fifth year together…
Lord Byakuya…
please find my younger sister…
And if you ever find her,
please don't tell her that
I was her older sister…
Save your strength.
Don't talk anymore…
No… Please don't let her know.
Please protect my younger sister
with your strength…
I abandoned my younger sister…
Hisana…
I have no right to be called
her older sister.
But please allow her
to call you “brother.”
A plum blossom opened…Look.
I'm sorry for depending
on you until the end…
I'm sorry I couldn't repay
the love you gave to me…
These past five years
that we’ve spent together
have been like a wonderful dream…
Lord Byakuya…
I found you the following year.
I immediately welcomed you
into the family.
It was the same as with Hisana.
The people of the household objected,
saying that allowing someone
from the Rukon District into a noble home
was against their law
and would tarnish
the name of the Kuchiki family…
But I defied everyone.
I wanted to fulfill my promise
to Hisana no matter what…
But, it's also true that
I’d gone against the law…
So I made a vow in front of
my parents' grave,
in order to admonish myself.
I vowed that I would
never again break a law,
that from then on, no matter what,
I would uphold it.
I was so desperate to
make Hisana’s wish come true,
I made two vows that
I should not have made…
When you were sentenced to death,
I didn't know what to do…
My vow to my parents
to protect the law,
and my promise to Hisana
to protect her younger sister…
I didn't know which vow
to uphold…
Who would enforce our laws
if we didn't uphold them?
If I were you, I would fight the law.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I thank you.
Rukia…
I'm sorry…
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Yoruichi, you let me borrow
all kinds of tools,
but where do you keep them?
My other form is a cat.
You know about the robot cat
with a pocket with
infinite capacity, right?
It's the same with me.
So that was it!
You're stupid, aren't you?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden!
Jinta!
Really…
Skipping out on store duties.
Where did he go?
Jinta…
Oh no!
That…is…not…RIIIIGHT!
Finished!!
It's not finished!
Tune in again!