Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Konpaku, Mod Souls…
were fake souls created
to battle Hollows.
However, the project was abandoned
as inhumane
and the order was given
to destroy all of the Mod Souls, but…
Urahara Store
Well, I guess that's it.
Um…Mr. Kisuke…
Hmm?
Uh… I'm sorry…
This is all my fault…
You're angry…
aren't you…?
Huh?
Not at all.
Why are you getting so scared?
We're in this together, aren't we?
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
Mr. Kisuke…
Now, now…
There, there…
Manager, everything is ready.
All right. Shall we go to collect
our merchandise then?
– Yes.
– Okay.
Uh…that guy…
What's he doing all by himself?
If I stay calm, I can easily
read your moves!
Damn!
Come back, you!
Wait, Ichigo!
We have an order!
What?! At a time like this?!
A Hollow is about to appear!
It's near!
Oh, damn!
Let's go!
Teacher!
Hashigami! Kaneda! Ino…!
What are you yelling about?
A strange high school student
attacked us!
He had orange hair…
A high school student?
Huh?
Oh!
What can this be…?
I think you boys play
too many video games.
Damn…
That Soul Reaper and those
kids ruined my good mood…
Damn!
Oh!
A Hollow…! I sense a Hollow…
It's around where I was…
Is it going to attack those kids?
Kill him off.
Hah-hah-hah…
So what? I'll make a better one.
Hah! "Clean up after school,"
she says!
Why should we do this?
Why doesn't she believe us?
Probably because
we're always misbehaving.
That's right.
And she even confiscated our games.
What's wrong?!
My Soul Pager isn't working right.
What?!
Is the battery dead?
What're you talking about?!
You should have bought some spare
batteries instead of pining after a Chappie!
I can't figure out the location
of the Hollow.
Damn!
W-What was that?
I-It's that high school student!
W-What's that?!
Blood?!
What's that?
That's it!
Okay!
Huh?!
That's…
That idiot!
Huh? Hey, Ichigo!
You interfere with my meal,
then you run all over the place.
I don't know who you are,
but you're not strong enough to
be messing with me!
Exactly!
Oh!
Y-You… Why…
are you helping me –
You! You're hurt!
Whose body do you think this is?!
If a two-bit one like this
can bloody you up this bad,
don't even think about fighting!
What do you mean?!
I had to fight it because
you took so long getting here!
Shut up! You're supposed to be
a battle-ready Mod Soul!
How pitiful!
What's with you two?!
Shut up!!
Hey! What's wrong?!
You idiot! How reckless
can you be?!
Once you crack its head,
the Hollow will disappear on its own!
And you had to...
– go kick it again.
– There's no one here.
Are you boys pulling my leg?
No! It's true! You have to believe us!
Then, where is this bleeding
high school student?
But it's true… Right?
All right. I want you to stay and
clean after school again tomorrow, okay?
What…?! Wait a minute!
Teacher!
Didn't you hate them?
So what? If I didn't help them,
they would've been killed.
And I won't let anyone get killed.
Soon after I was created,
the Soul Society ordered
all Mod Souls be destroyed.
In other words...
my date of death was determined
the day after I was created.
I…
I trembled in fear every day,
inside that pill,
as I watched the others
around me disappear, day by day.
Even though I was able to slip out
of the warehouse
by hiding among other pills,
I was always afraid that I would
someday be discovered and destroyed.
All the while, I wondered:
Why should others determine my fate?
Why? Why can't I decide for myself?!
Isn't it up to me whether I live or die?!
That's why…
That's why I…won't kill anyone…
And I don't want to see anyone killed.
Oh, my… Here I finally found you
and you're all battered up.
Looks like all the equipment
we prepared was for nothing.
Huh?!
Huh?
Wha--!
Collection completed.
Let's go home, everyone.
What?!
But I thought I'd finally
be able to fight it out, after all this time.
W-Wait…
Wait a minute!
What are you going to
do with that?
Do with it?
Destroy it.
Y-You can see me?
Who are you guys?
Well, how can I answer that…?
A greedy merchant.
Hey, you can't take that!
What's this, Urahara?
Do you take back goods you've sold to
people without giving them a refund?
Oh, well, I guess I'll refund you then.
That's not necessary.
I'm satisfied with this item.
Besides, you guys work outside
the laws of the Soul Society.
You're not really obligated
to collect these things, are you?
Don't blame me if you run into trouble.
We're going to be hiding out.
Don't worry.
I've gotten used to trouble lately.
Here…
Let's go home.
Uh, okay…
Hm? What's the matter, Ichigo?
Man… Abusing my body,
knowing it wasn't his…
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Are you listening?!
You must look very
strange to outsiders.
I don't like it!
Rukia, what do I do to
complain to him directly?
Hm? Well, you'd need to insert it
into a body without a soul –
in other words, a dead body.
Got it! A dead body…!
Let's see now…
I'm not going to find one lying around!
Quit yapping.
Huh?
This is…
Hey…
In other words,
all I need is a receptacle, right?
Huh? Yes, but that's not…
Oh, but this body I'm in
isn't a real body either…
Rukia…
Please pardon the inconvenience during
the construction.
O-Okay, let's give it a try.
You sure? So, what do I do?
You put it into its mouth, I guess…
Okay…like this?
Humph. It didn't work.
Looks like it.
That hurts, you idiot!
You! Ichigo Kurosaki!
I challenge you again!
Huh, what…? Y-You're huge!
No, I'm small! What's going on?!
My hands have gotten so cute!
Ohh… I'm all soft!
Hey you, Mod Soul!
Huh?
I don't think our discussion was over!
Let me go!
I'm gonna take real good care of you!
Prepare yourself!
Then I guess I'll take you on as I am!
Hey! Wake up, Ichigo!
It's morning!
Morning! Morning!
How's that? Give up?
If you give up,
then wake up and apologize!
If you don't, I'll get in your school bag
and follow you to school.
The girls in your class will say,
"Oh, Kurosaki… you carry
a stuffed animal around? How weird!"
Ow…! Let go of me, you…! Oh!
Yammering away first thing
in the morning…
I told you to shut up and
act like a stuffed animal, didn't I, Kon?!
Why the heck are you calling me Kon?!
It's hard to call you Kaizo Konpaku.
Kon's good enough for you.
That's no reason for you
to call me Kon!
Doesn't it sound sort of silly?
I know! Why don't you
call me Kai, instead?
I like Kai. Call me Kai.
– No way.
– Why not?!
Because Kai sounds kinda cool.
I wouldn't like it.
Damn you…
Don't get smart! You…
What's all this racket,
so early in the morning?
I can't even take
my time changing clothes…
Huh…?
Huh?
N-Nice angle…
I'm glad I'm a stuffed animal…
Ow…! Stop it! Stop it!
My stuffing's coming out! My stuffing…!
Ichigo, I'm coming in.
Kojima and Asano are…
Huh?
What are you doing?
N-N-Nothing. I'm not doing anything.
What are you doing,
so early in the morning?
It isn't early anymore.
Kojima and Asano are waiting for you.
What?!
Oh! It's this late already?!
Ohhh! I'm going to be late!
Your toast is ready,
so eat before you go.
Sorry! I overslept!
I'll be right out, so wait for me!
Hey, this is unusual!
Well, take your time,
but hurry, okay?
Sure!
Say…
What is it?
You erased the memories of
my classmates again, didn't you?
Of course.
You wouldn't want them to remember
what happened yesterday, would you?
Well… I guess not.
Too many things have
been happening.
and it's like…
it's only natural…
Ichigo, I'm going on ahead.
Ichigo…?
What's wrong?
Nothing…
Ichigo…
Say, Tatsuki, your elective
was art, right?
Huh? Yeah.
Did you do your assignment,
"Me in the Future"?
Yes, I did. Why?
Let's show each other
what we've done.
I have no confidence at all.
Sure.
Here!
Wow, you're good!
I'm going to be the female
vale tudo champion someday!
This is so nice.
Mine is too awful to show you.
What about you, Orihime?
What did you draw?
Thanks for asking!
Actually, in my heart,
I call it my masterpiece!
Oh really? Show me.
Ta-da…!
"The Future Me"
Maximum speed: 380 kph!
From my mouth,
flames of 20,000 degrees Celsius,
and from my eyes,
special destructive rays!
No, Orihime! That's definitely not what
you were supposed to draw!
– Huh? What? Why…?
– Do you want to get detention again?
But wait, there's more…
Oh!
Good morning, Ichigo!
Huh? Oh!
Oh, good morning, Inoue!
What's with him?
He's sure in a good mood today.
Isn't he, Orihime?
Huh? Orihime?
Mmm… But…
Michiru, what's the date today?
Huh? It's June 16…
I see…
He's not in a good mood.
He acts like that when he's really tense.
Oh…
Tatsuki…?
Don't worry…
I know the reason why.
Tomorrow,
he's going to skip school.
Ta-da! And now,
Kurasaki Clinic will be closed
tomorrow on the 17th.
I would like to
discuss our duties for tomorrow!
And since, as your father,
I am the chairman,
I get to make all of the decisions!
What do you mean?
You can't call this a discussion!
Hey! Raise your hand if
you want to speak, Chief of Staff!
C-Chief of Staff…?
Not exactly unhappy
Yuzu will be the lunch
staff officer, as usual.
Aye aye, sir!
Karin will be the porter!
Huh?! What happened to
"Chief of Staff"?
Oh, I just had my hair cut.
What do you think of it?
– Don't come near me! Stop it!
– Come on. Take a look!
It looked like fun.
What was?
What? The family meeting
you had, of course.
So, what? Are you playing hooky from
school and going on a picnic tomorrow?
A picnic?! That sounds good!
– Say, Rukia…
– Huh?
About my job as Soul Reaper…
Can I take the day off tomorrow?
Wha--?
What are you saying?!
Of course, you can't!
What's going on with you?!
You've been acting strange
since this morning.
It's the day she died…
Tomorrow's the anniversary
of the day my mom died.
That's not quite right…
To be precise,
it's not the day she died…
it's the day she was killed.
Oh! Good morning, Inoue!
Tomorrow, he's going to skip school.
If… If I were the rain…
would I be able to connect with
someone's heart,
the way the rain connects
the never-intersecting sky and earth?
Huh?!
I...
Yay! Yay! Go!
Go! Go!
Shucks…
Yay! We did it!
Okay, one more time!
I won't lose this time!
What's the matter, mister?
Sorry, something just came up.
Aww no…
Here you go.
Yay!
So, who is it today?
The thirteenth division's
Rukia Kuchiki.
Kuchiki…?
And what has that
young lady done?
She has stayed too long
in the human world.
Is that all?
We wouldn't call you out if that were all…
There's something behind it.
Find out what it is.
I can be a little rough, I take it?
Leave at once.
That Rukia Kuchiki…
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Next! Amazing suspense!
"The Isshin Kurosaki
Serial Murder Case -
The Madness over a Huge Serving
of Pot Stickers and
The Sweat of a Sorrowful Father
Sealed in a Bean Jam Ricecake
by a Beautiful Nurse!"
There's no such show!
There'll even be some
"wardrobe malfunctions"!