Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Scatter!
Reign over the Frosted Heavens!
Roar!
Above you!
Damn!
THE PREVIOUS DAY
He went that way!
Don't let him get away!
There he is!
Hey, that's a nice weapon
you've got there.
Want to see whose is stronger,
yours or mine?
– Kazeshini!
– Yeah, I know.
"Quit playing around," right?
C'mon! C'mon! C'mon!
Too slow!
Damn you…
What the hell?!
Well done, Kazeshini.
You're getting quite good at this.
What's the matter?
No…nothing…
What? Is it over already?
Abarai.
Sorry we're late.
Monkey's big butt always
slows us down, see?
What?!
– No, that's okay…
– I wasn't at fault for being
– It wasn't much of
– late today! It was Renji's!
a Sword Beast, apparently.
Sword Beasts have been appearing
a lot less frequently lately.
You're right.
Perhaps there are only
a few of them remaining…
Reconstruction of Seireitei
is making progress,
so things look like they're
finally getting back to normal.
Yeah.
You've been eating nothing
but sweets lately—
Maybe you're the one
who's gotten fatter?
I'm a growing boy, so it's okay!
You and I together are one.
If you're still growing,
then so am I!
Hey…
That Sword Beast just now…
It returned to sword form even
though I never struck a fatal blow.
What?!
A lovely moon, wouldn't you say?
It's too bright for my liking.
Hey.
Huh?
Now there's something new.
Seeing you guys hanging out.
What's going on?
There's nothing
unusual about that.
Our masters hang out quite often.
Your masters, maybe.
So, what's up?
Something happen to
your beloved masters?
Huh?!
Who's in love with his master?!
You're asking for a reaping!
Okay, okay. It was just a joke.
I thought we came here
to discuss something.
Signs of that Sword Beast
have appeared…
Is that true?
I'm positive…
A Sword Beast was sucked dry
of its Spiritual Pressure
and returned to sword form
before my very eyes.
It's his doing.
Sword Beasts were
originally Zanpakuto
that lost their masters
and became wild…
They have a finite amount
of Spiritual Pressure
and eventually lose
their power and disappear.
They're one step away
from dying out.
Yeah…
But this guy is able to
take Spirit Energy
from other Zanpakuto
and make it his own.
I'm able to do that,
as well, though…
What makes him troublesome
is that he was one of
those very rare Zanpakuto that
far surpassed his master's power.
Why is that troublesome?
To him, his master was a nuisance
from the very beginning.
Now that his master died, he can
show off his powers to the fullest.
I see…
In other words, he's using
his overwhelming strength
to take in the power of others to
become even more powerful…
This isn't good.
He's the worst kind of enemy
the Soul Reapers could have.
It'll work out.
Looking at it another way…
If we defeat this guy,
the Sword Beast hunts
will come to an end.
It'll be a grand finale for us.
Waitress!
Another round, please!
Coming right up!
Rangiku, too much alcohol
is poison to the body.
I'm well aware of that!
That's right…
She's not a child who
doesn't know when to stop.
Oh, you know me well, Haineko…
– Geez… Oh, those two…
– Hey stop it, don't get so close!
Do you want this?
Go ahead—you can have it.
We're sharing the orders.
Here you go.
So tell me, why'd you bring Captain
Kyoraku's Zanpakuto with you?
What's the problem?
We're part of the same squad.
Where's the other half?
She is drinking with
the Captain at the barracks.
Oh really?
And you're okay with leaving
the two of them together alone?
What is there to worry about
with a Zanpakuto?
I like this.
It's nice to have a meal
with everyone like this
every once in a while.
The food seems to taste better.
Hinamori…
You haven't touched your sake.
I'm here today to enjoy
the food, so no thanks.
What?
Are you saying you
won't accept my sake?!
Stop giving Momo a hard time.
That's all right, Tobiume.
Now, now, let's all calm down.
I'll accept your sake.
Will that do?
What's up with you, Haineko?
You're awfully
level-headed today.
Yeah. That's because
I'm a mature woman.
Now that's my Zanpakuto!
Well said!
Maybe you could learn
something from her, Rangiku.
What?!
Thank you very much!
Rangiku, pull yourself together.
I can't drink another drop…
Good grief…she always
ends up like this…
What's the matter?
We want to take in
the night breeze for a bit…
Can I leave Rangiku with you?
Uh, sure, that's fine…
Our apologies, Momo.
Don't worry about it.
It's nice to talk with
your friends sometimes.
I feel sick…
Rangiku! Not now!
We'll rush you back to
the barracks, so hold it in!
Oh…give me a break…
Just a little more.
We're almost there!
I warned you this would happen!
Thank you, Rangiku.
It was fun.
What's got you so sentimental?
We finally found him.
Understood.
Oh boy…
I never figured
you'd get this big…
So it was you, after all, Kirikaze.
You were the one who was most
dissatisfied with your master!
You have the ability to
transform into mist.
You used that power to
enter the bodies of others
and suck away their
Spiritual Pressure…
That's disgusting.
But to grow this massive from
stealing the power
of other Sword Beasts…
Anyway, let's get started.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
He turned himself into mist!
What?!
Scatter!
That was uncalled for!
Now is not the time.
So quit complaining.
Let's go!
Why you!
Your backside is wide open.
Okay, that's as far you go.
I'll show you that you
don't have a monopoly
on sucking away
Spiritual Pressure.
Wow, that was quick.
We didn't all have to come…
What's wrong?!
This can't be!
Undo your technique!
Bastard!
Guess this is as far as I can go…
Look out!
Sir Gonryomaru!
Roar!
Above you!
Damn!
Renji!
Bakudo Number 63! Sajosabaku!
He's going to transform into mist!
I've put a stop to that.
Lady Rukia!
What's the matter with you?
You're in the middle of a battle—
don't let down your guard!
Come on, pull yourself together.
You're ruining a pretty face.
Rangiku…why are you?
Did you think we didn't realize
something was going on?
Momo…
Stupid fools!
What'd you come here for?!
Who's the fool here?
What can you do
in your condition?
All of you are also reaching
your limits, aren't you?!
Everyone…
It's okay.
Right now, just concentrate
on the enemy!
But this Sword Beast's ability is
too dangerous for Soul Reapers.
She's right!
That's why we came
without telling you…
Shut up!
What are we to you?!
Swords alone… Soul Reapers alone…
are not enough!
Only when we're paired together
can we show our true power
for the first time.
Didn't you learn that lesson from
what happened to Muramasa?!
Don't go doing things
by yourselves.
Renji…
You're right…we were wrong…
What?!
Kazeshini…
What?
We're going to take care
of this quickly, right?
So give me a hand.
Right.
He's going after
the Soul Reapers!
Sodenoshirayuki!
Scatter!
Pierce!
Reign over the Frosted Heavens!
Is this it for me?
Sir Hyorinmaru!
I can't do any more with
the Spiritual Pressure I have left…
Don't give up!
We told you—you're not alone!
Lady Rukia…
You'll be all right
You and I are always together.
Yes!
Come, Sodenoshirayuki!
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki!
– Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Wabisuke!
Tobiume!
Kazeshini!
Haineko!
– Raise your head!
Wabisuke!
– Snap!
Tobiume!
– Reap!
Kazeshini!
– Growl!
Haineko!
He can't transform into mist.
He's weakened considerably.
Renji!
Let's do this together!
Right!
We'll give you our remaining
Spiritual Pressure as well!
Renji… We threw all the feelings
we had towards you.
And you've always answered
to those feelings.
Zabimaru…
That's all we need.
Renji, it's been fun.
Yeah.
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Hikotsu…taiho!
They've all disappeared,
as we expected…
Just as the Sword Beast reached
the limits of
its Spiritual Pressure,
the Zanpakuto became
depleted to the point
where they could not maintain
their manifest forms…
Their appearance was
a temporary form
manifested through the medium
of Muramasa's powers…
They knew this would
eventually happen.
Yeah.
There's no need to feel lonely.
They've simply returned to where
they originally came from…
We can always see them…
Don't you feel their presence?
Yes.
It's a very nostalgic feeling.
Though they're no longer
in those forms…
They will always be
together with us.
Renji…
Huh? What is it?
No, it's nothing…
It's finally over now…
Yes…
Let's go back to the Seireitei.
The producers are finally done
with shifting the story around.
Thank you for waiting,
Master Ulquiorra.
Understood.
Mind if I have a cup of tea
before we begin?
Don't worry!
Ichigo's not here yet,
so take your time and enjoy…
I'm already here.
What?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Why're you here, Ichigo?
You're awfully early!
I didn't have any scenes
and got bored!
At this point,
you're the main star in name only.
Don't be so blunt about it!
Anyway, let's get started
with the next arc!
Master Ulquiorra's
still having his tea!
Since when did you
become so selfish, Ichigo?!
That's the reason why
no one treats you like a star!
That's going too far…
Huh?
– You're too slow.
– Kurosaki! Hurry up!