Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Did you win?
I lost.
You fool...
The fact that you're alive
means it's a win.
Don't lie...
If you were me,
you wouldn't say that.
Grimmjow...
Welcome back, Grimmjow...
What's the matter?
Don't you have some words
of apology to share?
Grimmjow?
Not really.
Why you--!
It's all right, Kaname.
Besides, I'm not angry.
Lord Aizen!
Grimmjow's recent actions are
the manifestation of deep loyalty.
That's what I consider it.
Isn't that so? Grimmjow!
Yes.
What're you doing?
Tosen?
Lord Aizen!
Please authorize his execution!
Kaname...
It's personal, isn't it?
You just don't like me,
that's all.
Is that the way a Director General
should act?
It is my belief that those who
disrupt harmony must not be forgiven.
That's all.
For the organization?
For Lord Aizen's sake.
Hah! You're so good at making
a case for the cause!
Yes, it's a noble cause.
And your actions show
no cause.
Justice without a cause is...
nothing more than killing.
However, killing in the name
of a cause...
...is justice!
Hado 54...
Haien!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Damn!
You bastard!
You cut off my arm!
I'll kill you!
Grimmjow...
If you attack Kaname right now,
I will no longer be able
to forgive you.
Playing with your subordinate again?
You're not nice, are you?
You were watching...
Gin?
You knew from the start that
if you say such things
in front of him...
...Kaname would do that, didn't you?
I wonder.
And we even lost five Arrancars...
That's not a problem.
They were only low-class Gillians.
There is no change in our plans.
If we ready top-class Vasto Lordes
and complete the Espada...
...there will be no foe in our way.
The resonance of Spiritual Pressure
has stopped.
The enemy is...
What's the matter?
Are you so worried about
the Soul Reapers and their fight?
What're you talking about?
The only thing I'm concerned about is
whether my powers will really return
with a method like this?
You don't trust me?
It's hard to.
In this secret room,
made from Spiritualized Silver
and Spiritualized Glass,
I keep countering your arrows.
Doing something like this
over and over...
Will it truly return
my Quincy powers?!
Of course!
As long as you don't die.
Brother! Brother!
Time to eat! Let's eat!
Time to eat... Brother...
Huh?
Found you...
He's not here. Dad!
Brother's gone!
She scared me!
What?! What about Rukia?!
Brother...
Rukia is gone?!
What's the matter?
Oh, you're okay, Rukia!
Brother is gone!
Do you know where he went, Rukia?
Ichigo?
Pyon!
You're better already?
Yeah.
- It healed at an unbelievable speed.
- I'm so glad, pyon!
No kidding...
Thanks, Inoue.
Huh?!
You keep getting better and better.
O-Oh, that's not true at all.
I'm just...
Are you healed, Rukia?
Ichigo!
What's with that face?!
Do you feel responsible
for my injury?
Stop being so full of yourself!
One's injury is caused
by one's error.
I'm not that weak to be protected
by the likes of you!
So stop looking so grim!
Yeah.
About the Hollow within you.
Why not ask Urahara about it?
He's the one who trained you.
Then he might perhaps know
about the inner Hollow within you too.
I don't feel like asking
Mr. Urahara.
I'm sure he already senses
what's happening to me right now.
And if he knew the way
to resolve it...
...I'm sure he'd have taught it to me
before I went to Soul Society.
But he didn't.
That means even he doesn't know
how to suppress this guy.
He trained me.
I'm truly grateful.
So...I don't want to keep
questioning him.
Ichigo... Where have you gone?!
Ichigo!
I know...
It's no good...like this.
Mmm... Looking good!
Now that's what you call
wifely assistance!
Do you even understand
what that means?
What did you say?
Uh, err...Thanks, Sis...
for taking care of my friend...
No problem. No problem at all.
If you like,
you can stay here forever.
I don't mind.
It's not enough.
Huh? What's not enough?
Could you mean "love"?
Is that right? Really?
Don't worry. A lonely man
who doesn't know love
should be enveloped
with unconditional love.
That's the kind of woman
I want to become.
Yeah, dedicate your life to it.
What?!
Oh, nothing!
I have to go to school.
See you!
Hey Keigo! Wait!
Don't run. Keigo!
My, my... So many are absent today.
Ishida, Kurosaki, Kuchiki, Sado...
These guys again.
What are they up to lately?
Well... I'm sure Kurosaki and the others
won't do anything wrong.
I'll let them go.
What do you mean by that?
All right! Let's start class!
Guess...who!
What's the big idea, Matsumoto?!
Wow! Captain,
you got it right the first time!
Who would get it wrong?!
What are you doing up here?
In this world, kids in uniform
have to go to school.
My report!
That it was easy thanks to
the Gentei Kaijo?
Those guys were small fries.
They weren't Vasto Lordes.
Nor were they Adjuchas,
the rank below that.
Even we of captain rank couldn't
defeat Gillians
without our Gentei Kaijo.
That's how strong they are.
Yay!
C'mon Ururu! Get with it!
Who do you think we're doing this for?!
For you! You!
Oh...
Your injury is healed, so look happier!
But, I... I just got better and...
I kind of want to be left alone
to recuperate.
Shut up!
Oomph! You need oomph!
Once more! Yay!
My arm hurts...Jinta!
Yay!
- It hurts!
- I think we should leave it at that.
Huh?
Mr. Urahara...
Oh, it's Sado. What's up?
Please...! Please train me!
Come again?
This'll be on the test,
- so take notes now, got it?
- I wonder what happened...
- Let's start with page 43.
- to Kurosaki?
I'm surprised you knew where we were.
Ichigo.
That face looks like you've finally
decided to become one of us.
You're so bad at detecting
Spiritual Pressure,
I'm surprised you found this place.
Well, I figured you'd come,
so I released a whole lot of
Spiritual Pressure
to make it easier for you to find.
Say, Ichigo...
Your coming here means that
you've decided to join us, right?
Nope!
Huh?!
Me, join you?
Don't kid yourself! I'm here to
take advantage of you guys.
What?!
I won't join you guys...
But I want you to show me
how to suppress the Hollow inside me!
You sure take us lightly.
As if I'd teach you, idiot!
I'll get it outta you.
How?
By force!
Don't make me laugh.
What a difficult fellow...
Dammit!
That boy named Ichigo...
He's not bad,
holding his own against Shinji.
Stupid, look again.
Shinji isn't serious at all.
It doesn't seem like Ichigo
is fighting seriously either.
It's quite obvious that he's nervous.
Nervous about what?
Hollows.
That kid is fighting scared...
He's nervous about releasing
his inner Hollow.
That's the level the kid
we're trying to recruit is at.
Huh? Where are you going, Hiyori?
Hachi... Put up five more barriers.
- Okay.
- Huh?
Ichigo, you...
Shinji! Move!
I told you, put up five more!
But...I couldn't do it in time!
Oh well, never mind.
Ichigo, let me say one thing.
You've got this all wrong.
Wrong?
It's true we're trying to recruit you.
However, it's not something
for you to decide.
What do you mean?
The power to choose is on our side.
Whether you want to join, or not...
That's not the issue.
We look at your power.
Then it's whether
we really want you or not.
That's all.
Think about your position carefully!
You don't have the right to choose!
If you have the power,
we will make you one of us.
We'll teach you how to
suppress your Hollow.
However, if you have no power,
who cares!
You'll disappear to wherever,
become a Hollow,
and die a shameful death!
If you understand,
change to a Hollow...
And we'll take a look
at your strength.
I refuse.
You're not too bright.
You don't have the right
to choose.
Didn't I say that?!
Change to a Hollow?!
If you're scared and
don't want to change,
then it can't be helped.
I'll directly drag out...
the Hollow inside you!
With force!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hold on, Hiyori!
Hiyori!
What's scaring you?
A mask doesn't
make you a Visored!
Of course
we can change into Hollows!
Don't be scared, Ichigo!
I'm not nice like Shinji.
If you don't change into a Hollow...
...you...
...will really die.
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
This secret room built inside
the hospital...
When was it built?
I made a slight change in the blueprint
and built it secretly.
Are you sure doing something like that
didn't compromise
the building's sturdiness?
That is important...
- Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
- Golden!
This is good! I don't know why,
but I can win!
Die!
Huh?!
But when the gauge of
Vermillion Hisagomaru is not full,
it's really weak!
- Yes it is!
- Huh?!
I saw that, kid. You're not bad!
Play with me!