Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
I shall go…
Boy, this hill is really steep.
Is it? It doesn't bother me.
But if you say things like that…
Hang in there, Yuzu! Don't give up!
Dad is on your side!
See?
Ignore him, Yuzu!
If you pay attention to guys like him,
it will only encourage him.
How naïve. Even if you ignore me,
I'm automatically encouraged!
Run!
My deathblow: Father's Slide!
Begone…to the ends of the earth!
Now's our chance. Let's go.
Boy, it's only June,
but it sure is hot today.
It was June 17 that day too,
but what a difference.
Oh, someone else is here.
You're right. I wonder if
she's here to visit a grave too.
Huh? But…
she's waving.
Ichigo, do you know her?
No! I don't know her!
Not at all! If I say
I don't know her, I don't!
There's something
familiar about her…
I remember now!
She's a classmate from
middle school!
It's all coming back to me!
Oh, boy! I feel so nostalgic.
I think I want to talk to
her all alone, right now!
And so, I'll go and have
a talk with her.
You two go ahead and
visit Mom's grave!
Ichigo!
What? Karin,
what do you mean by that?
Well, I think the time for you to
let go of your brother is close at hand.
Huh? What do you mean?
Karin, wait a minute!
Why the heck did you follow me here?
Idiot! What if a Hollow
appears when I'm not around?
That's no reason to…
I mean… If you're gonna follow me,
be more discreet!
Well, pardon me…
I didn't think of it.
What are you mad about?
I'm not really mad…
"Killed..."
That's what you said
about your mother, right?
I didn't say that.
Who killed her?
I never said that. Forget it.
You said you've been
able to see spirits
ever since you can remember,
didn't you?
Then, answer one question.
The one who killed your mother…
Wasn't it a Hollow?
There is that possibility.
If your spiritual capabilities
were such
that you were able to see souls
since you were so little,
the Hollow that came after you
may have killed your mother
by mistake–!
I can't take this anymore!
You've got to be kidding.
As far as you're concerned,
Hollows are responsible for everything.
There was never
anything funny about it,
but when you give that
as a reason for it
there isn't anything
that's less funny!
Sorry to disappoint you,
but you're way off base.
It wasn't a Hollow or anything.
The one who killed my mom…
was me.
Hey, Ichigo!
Huh? When Ichigo was little?
Why do you ask,
out of the blue?
Did something happen?
Yes, well actually…
I might have found out
about his secret.
His secret?
Yeah. Ichigo might really be
a hero protecting the earth!
A h-hero, is he…?
I think I was around four
when I first met that hero.
He came to my dojo with
hair an unbelievable color,
holding the hand of an unbelievably
beautiful mother,
and with this unbelievably
goofy grin on his face.
He was skinny and wimpy
and looked so weak.
He really was a weakling…
Speaking of which,
I was the first one to
make him cry.
I just poked him once,
as a joke.
It didn't even take ten seconds.
But even if he had been crying,
as soon as he saw his mother
who came to pick him up
he'd immediately break out
into a smile.
I hated that about him.
A boy shouldn't be so happy
when he's lost.
That's what I thought,
looking at his smiling face.
He was such a wimpy mama's boy…
but he seemed really happy
like he was having a great time.
And then…when we were nine…
his mother passed away.
Yeah… We were still nine.
He was still a wimp,
always clinging to his mother…
but she died…
He didn't come to school
from that day…
I wondered what he was doing,
so I went looking for him and
I found him on the riverbank
where his mother had died.
He was there with his book bag
on his back.
When he got tired, he'd crouch down,
but then he'd stand up again.
Day after day, he seemed to be
searching for his mother, all day long.
I couldn't bear to see him like that…
Ichigo, back then.
Tatsuki…
"I killed my mom…"?
The one who killed your mother…
Wasn't it a Hollow?
What an idiot I am…
Hey, Rukia!
What is it, Kon?
Didn't I tell you not to come
out until I called you?
But, Rukia, it's pretty
hot in here.
I can't take it.
Can't we go home yet?
Didn't I tell you?
We've got to stay near him,
or we'll be too late if a Hollow
makes an appearance.
That's all you think about,
Hollow, Hollow, Hollow…!
Listen, if your job is all you
think about,
you're going to lose
all your friends!
Oh… Awk!
I-I'm sorry. Are you mad?
What is it?
Hm…I sure slept well… Huh?
Good morning!
You!
I get nothing but these
trying missions, you see.
I can't keep them up
unless I get plenty of sleep.
S-Soul Reaper…?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Mission…you said?
See ya!
Yeah. See you tomorrow!
Oh!
Oh my… What a mean truck driver.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry. Let's switch places.
I'll walk on the road side.
It's okay.
I'm wearing a raincoat,
so I'm all right.
I'll protect you from stuff
like what just happened.
My, how reliable…
But no…
I can't let you take the road-side
so long as you can't beat Tatsuki!
I won a point from her last time.
There, you're all cleaned up.
Hm...
Let's go!
Huh?
Mom, can I hold your hand?
Of course.
I would always feel at ease…
whenever my mother was nearby.
Huh? What's that girl doing?
Back then, I still couldn't tell
the difference
between humans who were living
and those who were dead.
– Wait a minute, Mom!
– Ichigo…
No, Ichigo!
When I was really little,
my dad told me they gave me
the name "Ichigo"
which contains the meaning "to completely
protect one thing you set your mind on."
When I heard that,
I decided to protect my mother.
I decided that, but…
I don't know what caused it…
but it was clear that it happened
as she tried to save me.
I just loved my mom.
Not only me…so did Yuzu and Karin,
who were only four.
And Dad loved Mom, too.
Our whole family revolved
around her.
And she was snatched away…
from that center…
by me.
Kurosaki Family Tomb
It's been a while, Mom…
Have you been well?
Well, if you're dead,
there's no being well or not, I guess.
We're all doing great – me,
Yuzu, and Ichigo, too.
Quit crying, already, Yuzu.
You do this every year.
We're 11 already this year,
we're grownups.
I know… I know that, but…
You don't know anything…
Now, now, now!
Cheer up!
It's time now for our annual "Kurosaki Family
Headstone Dominoes Tournament"!
A full two-and-a-half hours
of tombstone toppling–
Why don't you go and
start your life over from scratch?!
There'll be some
"wardrobe malfunctions," too…
To be honest, that shaggy guy
has so much energy it's annoying.
There'll even be some peeks!
Go away!
Wait!
Just who are you?
Answer the question.
It's been a while…
The name Rukia Kuchiki was famous
back at the Soul Reaper Academy.
Adopted into the
noble Kuchiki family…
you were known as the
'Princess from the Rukon District.'
Oh, and I'm Eikichiro Saidoh.
I was two years ahead of you.
You remember me, don't you?
Come on!
I was pretty popular too.
People used to call me
"that funny guy."
See?!
I don't remember you.
R-Really?
Oh, well.
Anyway…
I have a few questions for you.
You can't hide it forever…
Are you from Stealth Force?
Ding! Ding! Ding! Ding!
Ta-dah… You are correct!
Quit fooling around!
What is it you want?!
Ichigo! Where are you?!
Rukia is… Huh?!
Rukia is…!
Here we go…
You!
Ichigo!
They're getting pretty
irritated over there…
They wonder why you
haven't come back.
Hollows appear.
Orders come in too.
That's why I haven't gone back.
That's all there is to it.
Then why are you dressed
like that?
Dressed? What does it matter,
how I dress?!
Oh, well, I guess you're finally
coming of age.
What are you talking about?
Don't hide it. Don't hide it.
It's him, isn't it?
The guy who's mother is said to
have been killed by a Hollow.
The guy with the spiked hair!
What are you...?
Is it pity?
Or, are you looking for pleasure
in the human world?
It's none of your business!
Shall I sew that mouth of yours shut?!
Don't be so embarrassed.
It's best to be straightforward.
But…doing it with a human boy…
Guess you can't say it–!
No good, huh…?
Too bad. I thought that would
be a good excuse.
If I don't get an answer
the superiors will be happy with,
I'll have to take you back,
even if I have to drag you.
Is that a threat?
Well…
I have no intention of
returning for a while.
Now you've done it…
I have no choice.
Rukia!
Hey! Who are you?!
Yo, Spiky! You can see me?
Kon, who is this guy?
How should I know?
What?! You're the one who
said it was an emergency!
Hey, Spiky…
What about you? Who are you?
I'm…
Ichigo! Don't!
I'm a Surrogate Soul Reaper!
Soul Reaper…?
No way…
What a stupid joke.
That's too funny.
Really, Rukia Kuchiki…
This is a serious crime.
A serious crime…?
What's he talking about?
Oh, well. It's no fun fighting
a dumb Gigai, but anyway…
Let's do this, Spiky!
W-What?!
D-Damn it!
Huh?! Ughh…
It's the end!
Huh?!
Ugh…
Stupid Ichigo…
Interesting. You transformed,
and you're a human.
How did you get that ability?
As if I'd tell you after attacking
me out of the blue!
Ichigo! Back away! This is my...
You don't have your sword.
What can you do?
Out of the way, Kon!
What's wrong?
Karin…?
There you are!
What's the matter?
Where's Dad?
He said he was going to have
a talk with the priest.
That good-for-nothing…!
I'm going to have you keep
me company for a while.
The bigger the bait, the better…
Karin…?
Heh-heh-heh…!
Yuzu! Run!
He's strong…
What's with you, anyway?
Is brute strength all you've got?
You have no idea how to fight.
Shut up!
What is it?!
It's a Hollow!
A Hollow?!
Where is it?!
Close…and… Look at this!
This spiritual energy…
It's quite a big one!
Hmm… Seems pretty strong…
Aargh! What?
You want to fight again?!
Ichigo, now's not the time!
Your family
might be in danger again!
Let's go!
H-Hey…!
Oh, no!
Karin!
No! Don't come near!
Karin! Karin! What's going on?!
Yuzu!
What's happening…?
Yuzu…
What did he mean
by "serious crime"?
Don't worry about
my problems now!
We've got to save your family first!
Aren't you going to ask me
anything about my mother?
If I do, will you answer me?
It's your problem…
a deep…deep problem.
I have no way of asking
you about it.
No good way of asking you without
tracking mud into your heart.
That's why I'll wait.
When you're ready to talk,
tell me about it…
I'll wait until then.
Oh dear, this is a problem.
What should I do?
Yuzu…
You're so noisy.
One hostage is good enough.
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
I decided…to protect…