Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Is that so? I understand.
Will you continue to investigate?
Yes sir!
How was it, Kyoraku?
Did you learn anything?
No. Old Man Yama is still missing.
What about on your side?
We're having a difficult time.
However, Captain Soi Fon's
Punishment Force
is rushing to assess the situation,
so we're steadily learning
the damage to each squad.
Furthermore, as each
squad restores function,
they are setting out to
capture the Zanpakuto
which have
manifested themselves.
Cripes… Out to capture
their own swords?
What a sorry state of affairs.
Also, about Byakuya
who is missing…
It seems
he purposefully extinguished
his Spiritual Pressure.
That's strange.
Yes.
It seems the situation is
not very promising.
Captain Unohana.
You're here!
Oh, I don't believe for a moment
that you didn't sense my presence.
You frighten me.
And Kuchiki? How is Kuchiki?
Well…
Her life is out of danger.
But her wound is deep,
and she remains unconscious.
I guess we should
be grateful she's alive.
I'm sorry we had to
turn your barracks
into a makeshift command center.
That's perfectly all right.
At a time like this, we cannot
scatter our military strength.
My Squad 4 will do
everything we can.
But our top priority right now
is to stop the Zanpakuto
and their rampage.
About that…
I had a request from Squad 12
for test subjects to analyze data.
I just came from seeing
Captain Kurotsuchi.
You went, Captain?
What is it?
You personally went to see
Captain Kurotsuchi?
This is not the time to
wonder about such things.
According to Captain Kurotsuchi,
currently,
Zanpakuto have become completely
independent from Soul Reapers.
Independent?
So if we err in the way
we deal with them,
it's possible the Zanpakuto
themselves will be destroyed.
North Block 12, nothing to report!
We found nothing in
South Block 75 either!
Then where could
they have gone?
To disappear like that without
leaving a trace of
Spiritual Pressure.
They're not mist or smoke.
They have to be somewhere.
No, maybe they did just disappear.
Huh?!
What do you mean?
They are originally Zanpakuto,
after all.
They may not be in their
manifested state anymore.
Lieutenant!
Then how do we find them?
Don't sound hopeless!
Listen, our very existence as
Soul Reapers is on the line.
We must capture them at all cost!
– Yes sir!
What is this wind?
Hold it.
That's a sharp blade.
Such sharpness and speed
aren't common.
That swordsmanship…
Doesn’t seem like
it's a stranger's.
Are you…
Kazeshini?
So you recognize me, eh, pal?
I came here wondering
just maybe…
Damn it. There must be a clue.
Where is the Captain?
It's useless!
Who is it?!
Here! Over here!
It's useless for an idiot like you,
no matter how hard you think!
You're awake.
Lieutenant…Kotetsu?
Your wound hasn't healed yet.
You need to rest a little more.
Where am I?
This is the Squad 4 barracks.
You were unconscious,
but luckily,
they were able to save you
and bring you here.
I want to release all Zanpakuto
from their Soul Reapers.
In order to do that, I needed you,
Ichigo Kurosaki, to come here.
You let Rukia go on purpose?
Welcome to my world.
Ichigo!
Where is Ichigo Kurosaki?!
There was no report from the one
who brought you here.
Each squad is trying to
assess the situation
and take care of their wounded.
There aren't enough hands
to search for the missing.
Ichigo…
Where is this?
Why?
Why am I here?
Old Man! Old Man Zangetsu!
Aren't you here? Old Man!
Is it true that he left my body?
Exactly!
W-Why you…
It seems you finally understand.
I'm inside my mind!
What are you doing here?!
Did you forget?
I am a Zanpakuto.
If I use its powers,
entering the mind of
a Soul Reaper is effortless.
What are you planning?!
What are you trying to do?!
What is your master thinking?!
Master?
I killed my master.
You killed…your master?
With my will, it's easy.
And Ichigo Kurosaki…
I've taken an interest in you
as a Soul Reaper.
What is that power of yours?
What is it that changes you
in that manner?
Like I'd explain to
a jerk like you.
You just don't get it, do you?
Your power is nothing
before my power.
Your defiance is useless.
Answer my questions.
And if I refuse?
How pitiful!
Damn you!
Just… Just who the hell…
U-Umm…
Who are you?
You really don't know?
Really…
You're so hopeless, Renji.
After all the years
we spent together.
All the years?
Sorry, but I don't know any woman
with a mane like yours.
Huh?
Well, Renji?
Are you still going to say
you don't remember us?
N-No way…
You two are the manifestations
of my Zanpakuto?
Why that look of shock, Renji?
Y-You used to be
a plain monkey and snake!
You're so stuck on petty details.
It's not petty!
There's a huge difference!
Listen, Renji.
Do you realize how much
you relied on us?
Relied on you?!
Yes.
Right, Snake?
What are you doing?!
Oww!
A big one!
Listen, you little brat!
Why'd you hit me?
That hurt, you big-assed broad!
Leave my hips out of this!
And learn to carry
your own weight!
Oh shut up!
You carry all your weight
on your hips!
Stop talking about that,
you perverted brat!
Who're you calling
a perverted brat?!
Sorry, but if you don't have
any business with me,
can you come back later?
I really don't have time for this.
Huh? What did you say?
Renji, you don't think…
…we're going to let you go?
What?
Renji, I think you have
the wrong idea.
We came all the way here
to get rid of you.
Wait! Why?
Why must we fight?!
We heard the voice.
Yes… A voice that
stirred our instincts.
Instinct?
Yes. I will fight.
Because that is
my natural instinct!
Awaken! Awaken your instinct!
It lies in a deep,
dark part of you.
Now…show it to me.
Old Man…
You're up, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Now, release it.
The instinct inside you.
I-I can't move my body.
Now manifest it!
Show your inner self!
You've come.
Hey…
Did you call for me?
Damn, what a fast sword!
This is all it took to graze you?
Your strength isn't much
without me, eh?
You really think so?
Isn't your strength my power?
Really?
I think that’s just what
you tell yourself.
What?
You don't know what
my true desire is.
What are you trying to say?
What is your purpose
in separating from me?
I heard the voice…
Telling me to listen
to my instinct.
Instinct?
Yeah.
You don't understand me at all.
You don’t understand
what my blade truly wants!
What do you mean?
You don't like the shape
of this blade, do you?
Well, look very carefully.
Doesn't it look like
it could carve up a life?
Owwww!
Quit playing around, Snake!
What're you saying?!
You didn't even move, Monkey!
Oh really?
Well now, Renji.
You seem to be taking us lightly.
Why don't you draw your sword?
Idiots! Like I could take
you brats seriously!
Besides, I have no
reason to fight you.
Is that an excuse because
you know you can't beat us?
What a hopeless man, Renji.
What?!
I'd like to say there's no rush.
But we don't have time to play
with a weakling like you!
W-What?!
W-What's going on?
What’s he doing here again?
Interesting… The inner world
of a Soul Reaper.
And the other Ichigo Kurosaki
who appeared from it.
The one who exudes
the Spiritual Pressure of a Hollow.
Just what are you?
Me?
I'm his real self.
You could call me
his true instinct.
Instinct.
You are, you say?
The power Ichigo Kurosaki
displayed when we fought…
It was the same as a Hollow's…
I see…
You are the source of that power.
I wonder…
Now, it's my turn
to ask a question.
Just who the hell are you?
I am Zanpakuto Muramasa.
I free Zanpakuto.
Zanpakuto respond to my voice.
And my power awakens
their true instincts.
So that's why even
Old Man Zangetsu…
And Rukia's Sodenoshirayuki too…
Fine.
If you possess
the power of a Hollow
and are Ichigo Kurosaki's
true instinct,
then in turn,
you can use my power
to release the instinct
that is inside of you.
It's over.
Why is the Zabimaru
monkey female?!
Isn't that your secret desire,
you pervert?!
Is that right?
Rukia, there's a reason for this!
I'll never forget the night
you made me submit to you!
You're awful.
Huh?
Orihime Inoue…
ORIHIME INOUE AND
RANGIKU MATSUMOTO
PRESENT TODAY'S CUISINE
…and Rangiku Matsumoto…
– …present today's cuisine!
Kurosaki! Ishida!
We're making a vegetable stir-fry!
Say, how do you chop this?
Oh, let’s just put it in whole.
It's getting a bit watery.
Then let's make a stew instead!
Good idea!
Is a watermelon a vegetable?
Of course it is!
Just put it in!
All done!
Looks yummy!
– Here you go!