Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Follow me, Izuru.
See you later, then.
Shiro-chan.
Don’t call me “Shiro-chan”
and don’t pat me on the head!
When you get into
the same school as me,
I’ll call you by your last name.
Forget it! Who wants to join
a school for Soul Reapers?
I’ll come home from
the dorm to visit, okay?
See you!
Don’t come back, Bedwetter Momo.
“Kagekiyo and Shizuka Kira”
I’ll be going now,
Father and Mother.
Rats! We’re gonna be late!
It’s your fault!
Sleeping in a tree…!
I was looking for you all over!
Shut up! It’s none of your business
where I sleep!
Agh! I should’ve left without you!
Welcome, new students.
Our Soul Reaper Academy is
a school of proud tradition that builds…
the Stealth Force and the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads of the future!
I ask that you apply yourselves diligently
and uphold the pride of our school!
I am your instructor…
Gengoro Ounabara.
This Freshman Class One took
the top scores in the entrance exam.
In other words, you are
in the advanced class!
Rather than merely serve
your future squads,
train hard to excel
in your various pursuits!
Excellence isn’t limited
to the advanced class!
If you train just as hard as they do,
you too, could be just as good,
That Renji. How impudent…
if not better.
Group 1, step forward.
Yes, sir!
Hado exercises! Begin!
Ruler!
Mask of flesh and blood,
all things in the universe fly!
That which names all in nature!
Gathering of heat and war…
Beyond the seas in reverse,
take steps to the South.
Hado 31!
Shakkaho, Red Flame Cannon!
Wow! Awesome...
Good! Next!
Yes, sir!
That was amazing, Ms. Hinamori!
You did it in one shot!
Luck, it was just luck!
I barely hit it…
It was still great.
Others couldn’t even reach it!
Wow!
Did he do that?
Wow, amazing!
He hit it dead center!
Huhh… He’s pretty good.
I didn’t know there was
a guy like that in my class…
Next, Group 3!
Yes, sir!
Whoever he is,
I’m not gonna let him show me up!
I’ll hit the bull’s eye in one shot!
Hado 31! Shakkaho,
Red Flame Cannon!
Wh-Wh-What…?! What was that?!
It exploded…how…?
Abarai, stay after school.
Yes, sir…
Match! Abarai!
Are you all right? You’re not hurt?
Hey, you were too rough!
Kira, you okay?
Yes, sir…
You seem quite tired.
Huh?
You’re…
I’d like to take a break, too.
May I?
Uh…sure…
Your blows left me flabbergasted.
I was overwhelmed by your power,
and I couldn’t counterattack.
My arm’s still numb.
Ah, sorry.
I didn’t mean anything by it.
I messed up during the Hado practice,
so I wanted to make up for it.
“Zan Ken So Ki”
We must master each discipline
in order to become Soul Reapers.
Our work’s cut out for us, isn’t it?
Y-Yeah. I guess so…
I’m Izuru Kira.
Pleased to meet you!
Won’t you tell me your name?
A self-introduction and
a handshake?
So you come from a good family…
Huh?
Shaking hands ain’t my style.
I’m Renji Abarai.
Nice to meet ya too.
Right! Likewise.
Huh…? What’s that?
Huh…?
Uh, what’s happening?
Huh? Oh, the captain of
a Court Guard Squad is visiting us.
What? A captain?!
Wow!
W-Watch it!
That’s…a captain…?
Anyhow, the captain
is amazing!
The Spiritual Pressure
surrounding his body
is totally different from ours!
Hey, are you listening, Shiro-chan?!
Quit calling me Shiro-chan, I said!
Why come home
on every day off, anyway?
Do you have that much free time
at the Soul Reaper school?
But I came home just to visit you…!
I never asked you to.
When I become a Soul Reaper,
I’m going to join Captain Aizen’s Squad 5!
Hey! I’m serious about this!
Hey!
Wh-What’s the big idea, Renji?!
What’re you daydreaming about?
Six months, and you still ain’t
adjusted to school, yet?
Hah! You should talk…!
That’s a big load.
Do you have field training today?
Yeah! We’re gonna practice fighting
dummy Hollows in the World of the Living.
Wha…?! No fair!
How come it’s only your class?!
Besides, why should only you
be in Class 1?!
It is fair! It’s ability! Real ability!
Grr…
So long! I’m gonna come back
way better than you!
Look forward to it!
Moron! I’m gonna be way…
…way…
First, a short introduction.
I’m a 6th grade student, Hisagi.
I’m Kanizawa.
I’m Aoga.
We three will guide you.
What?
Are those upperclassmen famous?
Don’t you know?
Not all of them,
just the one in the middle.
Shuhei Hisagi.
He is assured of a post in
the Court Guard before graduation,
which hasn’t happened in
the last few years.
They say he’s even certain to
get a Seat Officer post.
By the way, he failed
the academy’s entrance exam twice.
So I might be better
in terms of talent
since I got
the highest score for it.
Now we’ll break up into
groups of threes.
Look at the lots you drew earlier
and find your teammates
with the same mark.
So that’s what these were for…
Who’s our third teammate, though?
Uh…excuse me…
Hello, you two.
Oh, it’s you, Hinamori…
Hello there.
Okay, so you’ve formed your groups?
We’ll explain today’s exercise.
6th grade students have already
entered the World of the Living
and built a barrier around
a suitable area.
You are to engage in
practice combat
with dummy Hollows within
that perimeter.
The 6th grade students will create
a combat-ready environment,
but they won’t assist you
in the combat itself.
Got that? Fine. Let’s go!
It’s begun!
Maintain barrier strength!
During practice,
it’s common for the real thing to attack!
Right! This is a safe zone, though.
This is part of our own training, too.
Don’t let your guard down!
Right, right.
Crap!
Hinamori! Coming your way!
Hado 31 Shakkaho,
Red Flame Cannon!
Kira!
Abarai!
Easier than I expected.
It was our teamwork.
No one could’ve done it alone.
Stupid! I could’ve won by myself, easy!
Heck, I wish I could fight a real Hollow!
Hah, only your talk is big!
I got more than that…!
C’mon, let’s go back.
Hey…hey!
C’mon! I know, I know.
Hey, what’s wrong, Hinamori…?
Oh. No… It’s nothing.
It’s about time to wrap up.
It ended safely, for now.
This is Hisagi
from the meeting point.
Barrier unit,
what’s the situation there?
Hey, come in!
What’s wrong, barrier unit?
Can you hear me?
Hey! Answer me!
Hey!
What’s wrong?
Strange…
No answer from the barrier unit…
Hisagi!
What’s that…?
I wonder…?
C’mon!
Wha…What’s that?!
It’s huge…
Crap! A Huge Hollow? No way!
Why didn’t we sense its approach?!
Bastard, you killed Kanizawa!
No! Aoga!
Aoga!
Run, Freshmen!
Get as far away as possible!
So that’s a real Hollow…?
Fool! What’re you doing?! Run!
Soul Society, requesting assistance!
This is Shuhei Hisagi,
6th grade squad leader!
At World of the Living, point 1026!
Being attacked by
a Huge Hollow at NW 2128…
Why…?
Why are they all running away?
What’re you doing, Hinamori?!
We were told to run!
Orders must be obeyed!
But…
It’s impossible!
It got two 6th grade students in a blink!
But…!
Hinamori!
Damn! I can’t see…!
Fine…! I ain’t done yet!
You…!
Forgive us, sir!
For disobeying your order!
We came to save you,
so overlook this, okay, sir?!
Ruler!
Mask of flesh and blood,
all things in the universe fly!
That which names all in nature!
Gathering of heat and war…
Beyond the seas in reverse,
take steps to the South
Hado 31!
Shakkaho,
Red Flame Cannon!
Now, sir!
Right!
How could such
a gigantic Hollow get so close?!
I don’t know.
I never heard of it before,
but it probably can conceal
its Spiritual Pressure.
We’re not strong enough to defeat it!
What should we do?
I contacted Soul Society!
We’ll just have to hang on
until help comes!
Wh-What’s happening?!
Things are getting blurry..!
It can’t be…
It called its friends…!
So many Huge Hollows…!
It’s crazy…!
No… It can’t be…
No… I don’t want to die…
I don’t want to die…ah…aa…
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We came to rescue you.
Y-You’re…!
Captain Aizen of Squad 5.
And Lieutenant Ichimaru!
You persevered well.
It must’ve been scary.
You’re safe now.
We’ll take over now.
You go and rest.
My, there are quite a lot of them…
Slay them, Shinso.
Captain Aizen…
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Rats! I’m too hungry
to concentrate on training!
Ah, well. Here, my emergency rations.
Thanks…!
Hey, what’s this?
This is jelled chicken meat.
And this is to remove hair balls…
You’re still eating cat food even after
you’ve returned to human form?
Hey, it’s pretty good.