The bodies were riddled with both
knife wounds and bullet holes,
leading to the conclusion
that they were murdered.
About a week had passed since their deaths,
and the physical damage was severe.
The bodies had been unnaturally
sewn together with thread.
Sewn together with thread?
The couple's daughter, Rachel Gardner,
was found unharmed near their bodies.
She was escorted to safety,
but her behavior suggests a
state of confusion, which—
The glasses bastard!
Why don't we chat in a
little more depth today?
It's okay. You don't need to be scared.
Oh, you looked at me!
You really do have such beautiful eyes.
You see, one of my eyes is artificial.
I was born missing one eye.
It bothered my mother terribly.
It stressed her out so much...
that her eyes turned very dark.
In the end, I couldn't
even see myself in them.
But still, I loved my mother.
Her eyes were precious to me.
Did you...
...hate your parents?
No.
Then why did you do that to them?
Do what?
You cut and sewed them up, didn't you?
Oh...
That was because I wanted a family.
What made you want to do it?
I found a puppy in an alley near our house.
It was tiny and weak.
I wanted that puppy.
So I was going to ask Mom and Dad about it.
But that day...
Who do you think is the
breadwinner around here?!
No one has any need for an alcoholic
police officer like you.
Shut up!
What are you doing?
I wonder if they'll listen to me.
Where have you been at this hour?!
Keeping quiet as usual, eh?
Does your head even work?
Hey...
You got a problem with me, too?!
What?!
Do you take pleasure in making me miserable?
What? What's so funny?
I'm going to buy my own happiness.
Happiness? Then buy some
happiness for me, too!
I'm miserable, so buy me
some of this "happiness"!
Outta my way!
Hey, Dad, listen...
What?!
Are you gonna get in my way, too?!
Um...
You're a filthy man.
You're only going to ruin my
life with your filthy hands.
You've torn this family apart.
Um...
All that booze has ravaged
both your body and your mind!
That's what made you crazy!
Stop it!
I told you to stop!
Hey...
It's your fault.
Listen to me.
Hey, Mom...
I'll show him.
I'll make him scream.
Mom?
What?!
I want to talk to you about something.
I don't have time for you right now!
But if I do things without asking
you first, you get mad at me.
So I want to ask—
Shut up!
Why won't you do as I say, either?!
It's because of you that I
can't get out of this hell!
I hate you!
Go to your room!
If I do as you say, will you listen to me?
Go right now!
Neither of them would listen to me.
I went to see the puppy again after that.
Its little body was trembling.
And when I tried to pet it, it bit me.
I don't...
...remember what happened after that.
The next thing I knew,
I was in my room...
...fixing that puppy.
Fixing it?
What happened after that?
That day...
That day was really hectic.
Very good. Good puppy.
You can stay with me forever.
It's your fault! She's nuts
because you're nuts!
You're wrong! It's not my fault!
You don't need to worry.
I'll go check on them, okay?
You made both of us go crazy!
What did you say?!
You're like some foul
vermin that brings misery!
How dare you?!
Hey... What are you gonna do?
What are you doing with that?!
No, stay away... Stop! Stop!
And then... what did you see?
You saw...
You saw, didn't you?
I never needed this in the first place.
Everything in this house makes me miserable!
So you...
...can die, too!
Hey, wait up, Rachel!
It's okay. Don't be scared.
You think I've gone crazy?
Rachel!
But you're the same as me.
Look at you, talking to that thing.
You did that, didn't you?
You killed it, then you
stitched up its slashed belly
and sewed its mouth shut.
Did it make you feel good?
This puppy is mine now. That's all.
No one needs you.
What's that?
I asked you what that is!
It's Mom's.
She was hiding a thing like that from me?
Hey, Dad...
Huh?
Be part of my...
...perfect family.
Dad...
I'll...
...fix you.
I sewed my parents' bodies together.
I replaced Dad's bad arm with a stuffed arm,
and I stitched up Mom's mouth to
make it look like she was smiling.
I made them the perfect Mom and Dad.
I see...
Then the three of us played
with the puppy and had fun.
So when the police took them away, I was sad.
Rachel, I understand your sadness very well.
Can I ask you one more question?
Another small animal died at the
orphanage you stayed in, right?
Do you know why it died?
Did you kill it?
I heard you were taking care of it.
That's right.
I loved it very much.
But it was no use.
No use?
Yeah. I wanted it.
I wished I could make it my own.
But for some reason...
Nothing worked.
Nothing worked, huh?
Tell me, do you want more
things to call your own?
Rachel, my mother committed suicide.
My eye killed my mother.
Your eyes look exactly like hers
did the last time I saw her.
They're dark, silent,
and above all, beautiful.
I love your eyes.
That dark radiance in
your eyes will forever—
Is this supposed to mean
I know all about Ray now?
What's the point of showing me this?
Seriously, screw that eyeball freak.
Hey! Open up!
Don't be rough, please.
The door's already unlocked.
Zack...
All right, Ray. Answer me.
Do you kill all the people
who come to this floor?
Hey! Answer me!
Did you hear me?!
Don't be rough with Rachel, please.
You piece of—
It seems you know everything now, Zack.
That was some pretty sick shit you showed me.
Forgive me. It's my job, you know.
I don't care about that.
I haven't gotten my answer yet.
Do you kill everyone who comes here, Ray?
Are you gonna kill me, too?
No. That's—
Rachel!
It's not good to lie.
Tell him the truth.
Go on!
I guess I'll have to, then.
Zack, everything is just as you—
Stop!
Oh, well. We don't need to
talk about that anymore.
The priest made her this floor's
resident at my request.
But she had a mental breakdown.
All over a single Bible.
You were always so calm.
What made you lose your mind?
I just wanted the things
that I'd consider perfect.
I couldn't allow it to be any other way.
But it said in the Bible...
...that the one who could really
never be forgiven was me.
And that's why you wanted
Zack to kill you, right?
But I think you know, Rachel,
that no matter how much you read the
Bible or realize your own mistakes,
that feeling you have won't go away.
Oh, how absolutely awful and wonderful!
Well, Zack, you get it now, don't you?
Now is the time to choose your path.
You can be killed here,
or you can give up on being
Rachel's God and leave here alone.
What'll it be?
Is what he's saying true?
She deceived you!
Did you...
...lie to me?
Zack...
Will you continue to be my God?
Are you trying to get me
to make your decisions?
I'm...
...not your God.
Excellent! That's exactly right!
Rachel, now you can be your usual self.
I'll grant any wish you have.
I'm unclean. I've sinned.
I've always known that.
But it was no use.
I don't understand why
just knowing something is a sin makes it bad.
Zack, you won't do it?
You really won't be my God?
Nope.
But I want one.
I want my own God.
That's not loaded.
I loaded it!
Ray!
Oh, Rachel! Your eyes look more
beautiful in this moment than ever!
Ah, Rachel! Rachel!
I'm sorry, Zack.
I said I'd let you go, but I can't.
My top priority right now is what she wants!
So I'll—
You really want to kill me?!
Hold up!
What beautiful eyes you have, Rachel!
I promise I'll grant your wish for you!
That bitch!
Ray! Don't you run from me!
Don't start playing with fire.
You still hate fire, I see.
Shut up! Enough of this shit!
Damn it!
Don't you mess with me!
Quit screwing around!
How long are you gonna keep running around?
You gonna shoot me?
You're going to die now, Zack.
If you say you're gonna kill me...
...then I'll just kill you first!
That's not good enough anymore.
I still believe that I need to die,
that I need to be killed.
But since I'm unclean,
God doesn't want even that much for me.
I'm not needed.
And yet, it was you who promised to kill me.
But when I found out there was no God,
you became my new God.
Ray, listen to me.
I'm no God.
Yeah. I know.
When the lie was exposed...
...my new God...
...died.
You won't even listen to me.
You just keep saying whatever
you want and running away.
All you ever do is run away, isn't it?
Say something!
She has nothing more to say to you.
You're not usually this unguarded.
Damn you!
Get violent, and I'll kill you.
Rachel, this is taking a bit too long.
It's not like you.
Of course, he is a monster.
I supposed it can't be easy.
But it's okay.
If you put a bullet through his head
from this distance, he's sure to die.
You bastard...