So you’re…
one of them, too? Ishida!
Ishida…
Kurosaki…
Don’t you get it?!
The guy who cut me
is the guy standing behind you!
Kurosaki!
Ginjo…
why?
Your Fullbring is mine.
I remember now…
Damn!
Oh dear…
He's one of his friends, right?
I think it would have been better if I
cut him with my Fullbring instead.
What are you talking about?
He’s going to be the key.
Kurosaki's fate depends on
whether he can notice the
difference between what
happened to this guy and
what’s going to happen
to our next targets.
Besides, it's no fun if we can't lose.
Come on.
Hurry up and cut me.
You and I are going to become
enemies who once betrayed each other.
We're really going to do this, huh?
I guess I have no choice.
That's what happened.
If I cut someone with my
“Book of the End,”
I can slip my existence
into that person's past.
If I cut that person again,
they return to normal.
I would be working closest to you.
So to keep you from suspecting anything,
I had Tsukishima slip his
existence into my past as an enemy.
It was the first thing we did
before doing it to the others.
That’s not the reason why.
We didn't cut you because
you'd be the closest to him.
It was because you have
the worst acting ability.
Don't be stupid.
My acting was pretty good back there.
But you referred to
Ichigo as "Kurosaki"
right after I cut you.
You cut him before cutting the others?
That's right. How very perceptive.
You saved me the time to explain things.
After I cut Ginjo,
I slipped memories into the
other Xcution members as well.
But I didn't make them
hate me as much as Ginjo.
I didn't have to worry about
the acting abilities of
the others quite so much.
Shut up.
Looks like Kugo has succeeded.
Looks like it.
Everything we've done is
to achieve this moment.
I think I can safely assume
that things have gone our way.
So what are we going to do now?
We just have to wait.
Once Kugo does the final touches,
our mission will be complete.
I get it now.
In short, not only did
you plan all this out,
you changed Inoue's, Sado's and
Kurosaki's sisters' memories
so you could corner Kurosaki.
You talk as if you figured
it out before you got here.
I wasn’t able to deduce that it
was the power to change people’s past.
However…
I realized something was wrong from
the Spiritual Pressure
lingering around everyone.
You each took different actions
to take down Kurosaki, didn't you?
You figured that much while
being immobile? I’m impressed.
But that's just the end result.
What?
Tsukishima and I have been following
the same plan to achieve a single goal.
Ever since the beginning.
That’s what you’re gonna do. Okay?
No way…
Don’t you think that’s
a little too much?
What?
Are you saying you can’t
listen to my orders?
Now, now, Shishigawara.
We shouldn't force him to do things.
But you will remember.
That in the past, I saved your life.
It seems a single incident wasn’t
enough to convince him.
In that case…
Now then…
Let's move on to the next stage.
I'm not interested in what his reasons
were for trying to get our help.
We set things up so he would team up
with us from the beginning.
Nice, here it comes.
There we…go!
My Fullbring…
I wanted to regain my power.
But I couldn't find any way to do that.
I just had to tolerate it.
Powerless… For seventeen months…
I thought I had finally found a way.
I thought I could finally protect
everyone with my own power.
But…
But…!
Is he crying?
Poor thing.
Just let him cry.
We have no use for him anymore.
And we'll probably
never see him again.
Is that it?
Is there nothing I can do anymore?
Let me be a Soul Reaper
for a while longer.
I want to become strong.
I want to become strong and
protect people from Hollows!
Those who are attacked by them.
And I’m going to beat him!
Otherwise…
I won’t be able to face my mom!
Give it back!
My power...
Give it back to me, Ginjo…
What are you babbling about?
You got back your power because of me.
What's wrong with me taking it from you?
Even though I'm done with you,
I'm not going to kill you.
You should be thanking me.
I said, give it back.
What more can you do?
I don't know.
But I can't give up!
He’s…?!
Give it back…
Give it back.
Give me back my powers!
Ginjo!
Dad… Urahara…
I see…
So that's it?
Have your memories been changed too?!
You idiot…
That isn't me.
Take a good look.
Look at who's holding that sword.
You should be able to see her now.
Rukia!
No… That's impossible!
Rukia…
Yes.
It’s been a while, Ichigo.
You’ve become so strong and mature
since the last time I saw you…
Not!
Ouch!
Crying like a pathetic fool!
You turned into a wimp the moment
I stopped keeping my eyes on you!
Pitiful!
Urahara told me about the
power of this Tsukishima guy.
He can write over the past…
It is indeed a terrifying power.
But so what?!
No matter how much he changes your past,
he cannot change your future!
Lost bonds can be forged once again!
Am I wrong, Ichigo?!
Rukia…
Can I say one thing?
He didn't change my past, you know.
Don't make fun of me
with that serious look!
That's dangerous! You idiot!
Even if it's been a while,
that's a pretty harsh reaction!
You fool!
This sword has no blade!
Come to think of it, what is that sword?
This is a sword that
Urahara prepared for you.
Thanks to this, I can give
you Soul Reaper powers again!
Don't be ridiculous.
Just because he looks like a Soul Reaper
doesn't mean his powers have returned.
The reason why Kurosaki was
able to become a Soul Reaper
the first time around
was because he already
had Soul Reaper powers to begin with.
But he no longer
has any Soul Reaper powers!
That's because I've taken them from him!
He has absolutely nothing.
There's no way your
Spiritual Pressure alone
could bring back his powers!
You idiot!
It’s not just Rukia.
Renji!
Byakuya!
Toshiro!
Kenpachi!
Ikkaku!
We put all of our Spiritual
Pressure into that sword!
Restoring Ichigo’s Spiritual Pressure
would be a piece of cake!
You said your name was Ginjo, right?
You only stole the top layer
of Ichigo's power, which was
fused with his Fullbring.
The power that comes from within Ichigo
is not something that
you could ever steal!
Ichigo!
They don't know that this isn't enough
to make you give up hope!
They don't know what kinds
of hopeless situations you've overcome!
Show them, Ichigo!
Show them that despair
isn’t enough to stop you!
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
That sure is amazing!
Things won't be that easy!
He's fast!
And his Spiritual Pressure
has increased as well!
It seems that your
strength has increased.
But it's nothing to be surprised about.
Your Getsugatensho has
gotten more powerful,
but is that all you've got?!
Guess again!
This isn't enough to kill me, Kurosaki!
You idiot.
That wasn't a Getsugatensho.
That was the force created
from swinging my sword.
What the hell?
What the hell is this
Spiritual Pressure?!
Getsuga…
tensho!
Ichigo! Allow me to explain
what I have been doing
for the past few months.
Nah, you don’t have to.
Oh, come on.
Aren’t you curious to know why I have
a Lieutenants badge on my squad uniform?
Now that you mention it, how…?
And so! I drew some pictures to
show you how I spent my days!
On second thought, no thanks.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I'm going to give a quiz this time!
Just like the last time…
What?!
You're the one who said to act
as if I've never seen you before!
I didn't say to make fun of me!
I'll shoot you!
You already did, see?!
Hey! I'm trying to ask a question.
What if you hit me?!
Soul balancers like us…
Do you want me to hit you?!
You four-eyes are way too serious…!
It's just a quiz.
Why are you being so mad?!
You two!
Hakuren!
Now answer the question!
I don’t think they can...