Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Everything went
according to my plan.
I thank you, Soul Reapers.
And…Ichigo Kurosaki.
You bastard!
Sorry, but I've gotta go.
I don't care to talk
to you any longer.
Farewell, Genryusai Yamamoto
and the Soul Reapers.
There is nothing you can
do against me anymore.
Get out of the way!
Whoa!
This is frustrating.
It's as if he's just playing
around with us.
It seems he plans to
keep us trapped here.
He's mocking us!
This won't stop us!
What?!
Ichigo!
It shot at me?!
Things won't be that easy.
Damn it! Muramasa,
that bastard…
Head Captain…
Where has Muramasa gone?
He's headed to
an enriched spiritual zone
in the World of the Living…
Karakura Town.
What?!
Karakura Town has
the thing that he wants.
So this is the current
enriched spiritual zone…
Karakura Town…
Byakuya Kuchiki…
Thanks to you, I was able to
find the place I wanted to go to.
I thank you.
I just did what my pride
demanded of me.
An enriched spiritual zone
is a spiritual hotspot.
If we stay here, lots of spiritual
things will be drawn to us.
In that case, I'll deal with
the Hollows that draw near.
All right.
I'm going to save my emotions
until after I've achieved my goal.
I'll keep watch over him.
I'm counting on you.
Byakuya Kuchiki…
What are you thinking?
I don't have time.
I must hurry.
Are you serious, Old Man?!
What would Muramasa
want with Karakura Town?!
Ichigo!
Oh, no!
Concentrate!
We need to escape first!
Yoruichi!
Could we escape from there?!
Yes. It isn't completely
sealed off yet.
Shunko!
Ichigo! Cover me!
Everyone, this way!
I'm counting on you!
What?!
W-What?!
It sealed up!
Yoruichi!
I'm all right!
Ichigo and the others
have started up.
I wonder if Ichi is all right.
If he improves his skills,
that'll be interesting to see.
And if he dies, I'll just fight
the guy who defeated him.
Well then…
We should let loose too!
Stop fooling around!
Get serious already.
I already know.
You couldn't go all out
because of your buddy.
That's why I cut him down first.
There's no one to get in our way.
The real fun is about to begin!
It looks like you're finally
going to get serious too, Kenny.
Yeah.
Stand back, Yachiru.
Aye aye, sir!
Bankai.
This is interesting!
I hope you have power
that matches your size!
Shunko!
Show yourself already!
Okay.
I knew it was you two.
We'll get you for earlier.
I'm not supposed to defeat
other people's Zanpakuto,
so I held back, but you
escaped pretty quickly.
Well, aren't you cocky.
You shouldn't
underestimate our power.
Honestly, old ladies are
all so overconfident!
You're not sexy at all,
even in that outfit!
Girls don't understand
the allure of an adult.
I don't need to understand that!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be saying that!
Now…
Muramasa's orders were
holding us back before,
but things won't be
so easy for you now!
That's right, it won't!
Good grief.
I guess I have no choice.
I guess I'll show you girls
how a truly great woman fights.
Getsugatensho!
Hado 63!
Raikoho!
Oh, dear…
It isn't working at all.
How can we break through this?
Damn it!
It's not easy, but with time,
I could control him.
But we don't have time.
If we don't hurry up
and stop Muramasa,
he'll dispel the seal.
The seal?
What seal?!
Is that why Muramasa
went to Karakura Town?!
Tell me!
What is Muramasa trying to do?!
Muramasa is after Koga.
He's trying to revive
the Soul Reaper Koga,
the master of
the Zanpakuto Muramasa.
Muramasa is a Zanpakuto that can
enter another person's inner world
and control the Zanpakuto
that lives within it.
His master, Koga, once led
a rebellion against Seireitei.
The Zanpakuto controlled
by Muramasa
not only denied
their masters' power,
they also attacked them and
thrust Soul Society into chaos.
We suffered great casualties but
finally managed to seal Koga away.
Muramasa's Soul Reaper master…
That's the back story?
But Muramasa said that
he killed his own master.
That's one of his lies.
Koga still lives within
the seal even now.
And the seal is in
Karakura Town…
I've never heard about that.
It's a secret event that
was never recorded.
Then what did Muramasa gain
by entering your mind?
Something only I know—
how to free Koga.
If he becomes one with Koga,
he might wipe out
the enriched spiritual zone
known as Karakura Town!
It's all my fault.
So this is the place.
It's almost time, Koga…
Who's there?!
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Santenkesshun!
What the—?
This is our—
What?
Huh?
I'm almost…
You can't move yet!
You're…
I'm almost finished.
This power… Who are you?
Huh? Umm… I'm, umm…
I heard that someone came
to the World of the Living,
so I came to check things out.
Are you one of the Substitute
Soul Reaper's friends?
Huh?
Why did you save me?
Why? I can't ignore
an injured person.
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki's enemy.
I thought so.
Even so…
How should I put this?
I can't just let you be.
Besides…
You looked like you
were in so much pain.
Ridiculous…
What is this?
This ominous Spiritual Pressure
is like that of an Arrancar…
Ishida! Sado!
You had friends with you?
Are you our guest
from Soul Society?
Are you all right, Inoue?
Getsugatensho!
All right!
I'm not going to make it!
Are you all right, Ichigo?!
Damn it…
If Muramasa dispels the seal,
it'll be my fault.
I have to stop him!
I'm going to try this
once more from above!
What?!
Oh, no!
What?
Reign over the Frosted Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Toshiro! Hyorinmaru!
Sorry I'm late!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Are your wounds better now?
Yeah. Anyway, these flames…
Are they what I think they are?
Yeah. It's Old Man Yama's
Ryujinjakka.
He even got to
the Head Captain's Zanpakuto…
Where is Muramasa?
Muramasa is…
He's headed to Karakura Town.
What?!
He's planning to revive
his Soul Reaper master.
His Soul Reaper master?
Let's just say,
the situation is terrible.
Damn it.
This is an emergency.
The first thing we must do is
get Ichigo Kurosaki out of here.
What? Really?
I…
If you feel responsible, then do
what you can to stop Muramasa!
Got it!
Let's go!
Yeah.
Bankai.
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Ryusenka!
Now, Kurosaki! Go!
Okay!
We're counting on you, Ichigo.
Now then…
It looks like I need to give
my sword some harsh punishment.
Just you wait, Muramasa!
I will stop you!
Are you the Substitute
Soul Reaper's friends too?
– That's right.
– No, I'm not!
Anyway, I'm a Quincy!
Quincies and Soul Reapers
are enemies! By definition—
Get to the point.
In other words, we're his friends.
I told you, Quincies and
Soul Reapers are—
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Something I can buy with this…
Rukia!
I bought something nice for you!
I hope this cheers you up a little…
Look, Renji!
Captain Ukitake was
concerned about me
and bought me
this giant Chappy!
Isn't it cute, Renji?!
So what did you want?
Umm… It's nothing.