Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Captain!
It's the captain!
The captain is here!
Captain!
Oh, Captain!
You're not going?
I'm fine.
Besides, this'll be
a good chance for
everyone to get to
know the captain.
But they look all tense and
nervous around him.
Still, I never thought
that the captain
would let us use his mansion
for flower watching.
The battle with the Zanpakuto
has left everyone worn out.
This is my brother's way of
helping everyone to relax.
You should be grateful!
Yeah, yeah…
Come to think of it,
wasn't this place blown to bits?
By your Zanpakuto, that is!
I mean Squad Six hasn't even
begun making repairs!
The Kuchiki Clan has
money and connections…
– And with their secret techniques,
– Lieutenant! Please come join us!
– repairing this place is easy.
– Everyone's too nervous to talk!
Come on you guys…
You can't even talk to
the captain without my help?
Renji wasn't listening
to me at all!
Unbelievable!
Stop that!
Who are you guys?!
Stand down!
Oh no!
Damn it…
Dance…
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren!
You're not getting away!
You're… Sodenoshirayuki!
I told you,
you're not getting away!
Somenomai…
Are you all right,
Sodenoshirayuki?
I'm fine, Sir Senbonzakura.
Are you all right, Lady Rukia?
Y-Y-Y-Y-You guys!
I thought you returned
to being swords?
What are you talking about?
What?
I do not recall making
such a statement.
That's true, but…
Don't blame us for making
the wrong assumption.
What?!
What's all the fuss about?
How?
What?
This is most unusual.
I never expected you to visit me.
Umm… As you can see,
our Zanpakuto are still manifested.
Of course they are!
Huh?
I undid their brainwashing,
but I never said I turned them
back to normal.
Here!
Take a look!
That's the situation.
Don't bother asking me
such questions when I'm so busy!
Nemu! Back to work.
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Wait, Captain Kurotsuchi!
What is it? I'm busy.
Please answer
one more question.
One more?
It's about this Zanpakuto.
Oh, that.
That's the result of a Zanpakuto
going out of control
after Muramasa manifested it.
A Zanpakuto going
out of control?!
You know that Muramasa's ability
affected not only captains,
but also regular
squad members, right?
Some of them were unable to
defeat their Zanpakuto and died.
This Zanpakuto is one of those
who went out of control,
as a result of losing its master.
I didn't know…
Usually when a Zanpakuto's
owner dies,
the Zanpakuto
disappears as well.
But something abnormal
must have taken place.
They are no longer Zanpakuto
or Soul Reapers or even Hollows.
You could say they are mutants.
I know…
I think I shall name them
"Sword Beasts."
And why did that sword suddenly
lose its manifested appearance?
We don't know.
It no longer has
any spiritual pressure.
One of them escaped, right?
Capture it and I may be able
to answer your question!
Oh…
One more thing…
The power of
a sword beast is equal
to that of
a Zanpakuto's true power—
in other words, its Bankai.
Even if they belonged to
lower-ranking Soul Reapers,
their power is probably
far greater than you think.
Well, try not to
get killed by them.
Zanpakuto that have
lost their owners
and have gone out of control…
This is quite troublesome,
isn't it, Big Brother?
Those fiends caused massive
damage to the Kuchiki Manor!
Their actions cannot be forgiven!
That's right!
You two were the ones who
destroyed most of the mansion!
The question is, how do we
capture Zanpakuto that escaped?
Oh! There you are!
Captain!
It's almost time to take over
the next Seireitei guard duties.
Is it?
Rukia…
For now, I'm going to leave you
in charge of handling this case.
Yes, sir!
I'll leave Senbonzakura with you.
Use him however you like.
Are you sure about that?
Absolutely.
I have a suggestion.
Perhaps we could destroy
one of the barracks
to get the attention of
everyone in Seireitei.
That might surprise the fiend
and get him to come out.
We're trying to rebuild
at the moment!
We can't cause more destruction!
Then how about we
freeze the entire town
along with the fiend?
The town itself will
remain unharmed.
Out of the question, you fool!
Why must you two come up
with such drastic solutions?!
Think of the trouble
you'll cause around you!
Is it a problem?
"Can't do this," "Can't do that,"
I have no idea
what you want us to do.
That's what I'd like to say!
In that case,
how about we do this?
Thank you everyone,
for your hard work!
Cheers!
– Cheers!
You two can really
down those drinks.
Oh, you bet!
But I never thought
a day would come
where we'd actually get
orders to throw a party…
I'm so happy!
It really is awesome!
Hey, you!
Why are you manifesting again?!
I do as I please!
– Well don't come out!
– Now, now, it doesn't matter
– which form she's in.
– Just keep on drinking, okay?
Just keep on drinking, okay?
Oh! Bring more drinks over here!
What is this?
Oh!
Well… Umm…
It's a party!
I can see that.
I got an order to
let you use this area.
But I'm asking you
why this is necessary.
It's to capture a Zanpakuto
that has gone out of control, sir.
We believe it likes parties.
What?
The fiend crashed
a flower viewing party
that was held by
the Kuchiki Clan.
So we're throwing another party!
You're basing it just on that?
Is that unsatisfactory, sir?
Are you being serious?
The fiend isn't showing up.
That's odd.
"That's odd…"
Not!
Could it be that we
didn't party hard enough?
We partied more than enough!
I hope your reason
for suggesting this
wasn't so that you could have fun!
By the way,
I don't see Sir Senbonzakura.
Senbonzakura is
passed out over there.
– Huh?
– Oh, don't be so heartless…
– Your mask is coming off!
What?! What are you doing?!
Kuchiki…
Don't you think this is enough?
Captain Hitsugaya…
I'm sorry for all
the trouble we caused.
Don't worry about it.
Ever since
the Muramasa incident,
my squad members
haven't had time to relax.
It's a good breather for them.
Captain…
Let's drink some more…
Shut up! I'm leaving!
What? You're no fun.
You're no fun!
Kuchiki…
Take care of putting out the fire.
Yes, understood, sir!
Oh, Captain!
Wait for me!
I'm very sorry.
It seems this plan
wasn't very good.
Don't worry about it.
You did the best you could.
We were just unlucky
this time around.
Lady Rukia…
It's kind of nice to talk to you
like this once in a while.
What's wrong?
We Zanpakuto are nothing
but weapons meant for fighting.
Perhaps we do lack heart?
Sodenoshirayuki…
I prided myself on my power.
Which is why I wanted to
act on my own just once.
That's how Muramasa was able
to worm his way into my heart.
I thought that I could do
anything by myself.
But this incident made me
realize that I was mistaken.
As a weapon, I have nothing.
Without your heart,
I'm just a tool of destruction.
You're wrong!
You're absolutely wrong!
You and I were always together.
You watched over me through
difficult and painful times.
Your existence has
saved me so many times.
I was able to stay strong
because of you.
So don't say that you're nothing.
Lady Rukia…
This spiritual pressure!
Let's go!
Yes, ma'am!
Let's capture him!
Stop! That's enough!
Lady Rukia!
I won't let you do that!
If I don't distance myself,
I'll be at a disadvantage…
Hado 33!
Sokatsui!
Lady Rukia!
I'll back you up!
Okay!
Sokatsui!
Somenomai!
Tsukishiro!
Lady Rukia…
Lady Rukia!
Sodenoshirayuki…
I understand.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am!
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren!
One, two, three, go!
So what did you do with
the Zanpakuto you captured?
I sent it to the Department of
Research and Development.
That's probably
the right thing to do.
Captain Ukitake…
About that sword beast…
Yes…
That probably won't be
the last time we see one.
I've received several reports
of such incidents.
I thought so.
And the Zanpakuto
have manifested again.
I guess that means we still
haven't solved this case.
And of all times…
We've got to rebuild Seireitei
as quickly as possible…
This is problematic.
Take that!
Cut it out, you two!
Be a little more quiet!
Okay!
It'll be all right.
We will do what we can to help.
That's right.
I'm counting on you,
Sodenoshirayuki.
Yes, ma'am!
Why were the cherry blossoms
in full bloom at this time of year?
There's nothing strange about it.
Do you know something
about that, Sodenoshirayuki?
I do. Isn't that right,
Sir Senbonzakura?
That's right.
No wonder there were so many
injured people afterwards…
THE ARRANCRA ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today, we'll be talking about
a new enemy—the "Sword Beasts."
Sword Beasts are Zanpakuto
that have gone out of control
after their owners have died.
"Sword Beast" is written with
the characters for
"sword" and "beast."
Why are you
the one explaining this?!
I accidentally came in thinking
I would have screen time
beginning with today's episode.
Can you at least
let me do this part?
Didn't Ulquiorra tell you anything?
Ulquiorra - > Yammy -> Wonderweiss ->
Stark -> Barragan -> GIN
It seems that
some wrong information
got mixed in along the way.
Is this a game of telephone?