Orihime has been abducted
by the Arrancars.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo,
the world of the Hollows.
They crush the Arrancars
standing in their way
and make their way to Las Noches,
Aizen's headquarters.
But the Guardian of the White Sand,
Runuganga,
drags them into the Forest of Menos
deep beneath the desert.
Rukia is separated from Ichigo and
the others when they enter the forest.
She meets a mysterious
Soul Reaper named Ashido.
Long ago, Ashido followed
Hollows into the Forest of Menos.
He fought Hollows by himself
for many years.
Ashido… Why did
you bring me here?
If I talked, you'd respond,
ask questions, and speak.
I wanted to let
my friends hear that.
Rukia goes with Ashido to
look for Ichigo and the others.
But deep in the forest,
the Adjuchas that control the forest
had set a trap and were lying in wait.
If we defeat him,
the Menos will get slower.
Yeah…
Fire your Cero!
Aim there, Gillians!
Rukia!
Ashido!
I'm sorry, Ashido!
Don't worry.
You've brought a burden
with you today, Ashido.
You should worry
more about yourself!
Ashido, you got hurt
because of me.
I'm going to defeat that Adjuchas!
What are you two chatting about?!
Maybe I should defeat you first!
Dance…
Sodenoshirayuki.
Somenomai…
Tsukishiro.
Reconsider your thoughts…
about whether I'm a burden.
Ashido… I'm sorry.
This is your friend's…
Ashido, it may not be
my place to say this, but…
Maybe you should return to
Soul Society once more.
I understand your feelings
towards your friends,
but the situation has changed.
Things aren't like
they were before!
More to the point, you're alive!
Your deceased friends will
forgive you if you leave this place.
I decide my own path.
Let's go on!
Yeah…
This is Nel and the others'
Spiritual Pressures!
You're sure they're here, right?
What should we do?
It's obvious!
We barge in and swipe them!
We can't waste time here forever!
We've got to start looking for
Rukia as soon as possible!
Wait! It's dangerous to barge in
without knowing the situation inside…
Hey!
What's this?
This is…
They're not here.
Seriously, you guys!
There were only traces
of their Spiritual Pressures.
Crap!
It looks like they were
moved elsewhere.
Do you know where they are?
Let's go!
Over here?!
Where are they?
Hey!
Nel, you're all right!
Why are they there?
Ichigo, run away!
Nel!
I was going to get you
with one shot, but I failed.
Oh well…
Don't move, Soul Reaper!
Don't move a single hair!
If you do, the Hollows
are going to eat them!
They're going to eat us!
Hurry and save us!
Crap!
It seems like you were
planning to draw us out
by using them as bait
from the beginning.
That's not all!
The guy who Lord Aizen placed
in charge of this forest
says that he wants to
fight Ashido one-on-one.
So we drew you out.
Ashido?
That's why we made you come
to this amusing place!
Amusing place?
That's right.
What's this Spiritual Pressure?!
Let's hurry!
Where to?
The exit!
Whoa! Where do you think
you're going, Ashido?
Itsugo!
– Ichigo!
– Did they do it?!
What?! Where did they go?!
Ichigo!
Bastards!
Nice, Ishida!
Yeah…
Did you see our team play?!
You shouldn't talk!
Dejected…
We don't have to
hold back now!
Let's go!
The Soul Reapers are
fighting over there.
It's easy to get
an understanding of
their Spiritual Pressures
from here, isn't it?
Do you want to save them?
But I won't let you pass!
You're going to sense
your friends getting hurt
and you're going to die
being unable to do anything about it.
You wretch…
Let's finish this already, Ashido!
Stand back.
I've fought him many times.
Las Noches placed him
in charge of this forest.
Unlike the others,
he can't be underestimated.
But…
I'll settle this!
This is my final job in this forest.
Ashido…you…
Afterwards, I want you to tell me
what's going on outside.
Ashido!
What?!
Don't underestimate me!
Crap!
Roar! Zabimaru!
On to the next one!
Crap!
Getsugatensho!
What's this?!
– Ichigo! I'm scared!
– That was so scary! Hold me!
They suddenly began
to move more slowly.
Did you notice?
Your friend's Spiritual Pressure
disappeared instead.
Crap!
It's over!
Run away, Rukia!
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren.
What?!
Are you all right?!
Yeah… Let's hurry.
Wait!
Thanks…
Don’t mention it.
Here I go!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Getsugatensho!
It looks like we’ve
cleaned things up.
Yeah!
Is everyone all right?!
Yeah…
We're saved…
Yeah.
Apparently the exit is up here!
The Hollows told us earlier!
Really?
Yeah, it's true!
Wait! We can't leave
without Rukia!
That's right.
We know where the exit is…
Let's go look for her!
There's no need for that.
Rukia!
Ichigo! Renji!
Rukia, you…
Kuchiki, I'm glad that you're safe.
Yeah… Sorry for worrying you.
Who is that?
His name is Ashido…
He's a Soul Reaper like us.
A Soul Reaper?!
He saved me and
allowed me to get here.
“Get here”?
The exit really is up here?
You didn't believe us?!
How persistent!
I'm scared!
It's no good! There's no hope!
Don't give up!
We should thoroughly…
Wait! They're still far away.
Ichigo, our goal is to save Inoue.
Let's get out of here.
Ashido knows where the exit is.
Let's hurry!
All right.
It's up ahead.
Did we get in from here?
This isn't where you came in.
Once you pass through here,
get on the current of sand!
You'll get to the surface!
All right. Let's go!
They've come!
You won't get away, Soul Reapers.
You're still alive, huh?
Go back! Get going!
But…
Ashido!
It's coming!
Oh no… It's collapsing!
Everyone, let's hurry!
Ashido! Come with us!
I'll go afterwards!
Go on ahead!
Why you…
Don't interfere!
Ashido!
Rukia, look out!
Crap! Why you…
L-Lord Aizen!
Ashido!
Save your…friend!
Ah! We got back to
the surface alive!
I never thought that I'd live to see
the gleaming moonlight ever again!
Furthermore,
we're almost at Las Noches!
– We did it! We did it!
Ashido said that the Adjuchas' powers
changed recently.
I couldn't tell him,
that fellow Soul Reapers
joined the Hollows
and are trying to change the world
with the Hogyoku.
Ashido had been fighting for
several hundreds of years
under here as a Soul Reaper.
I couldn't tell him…
Rukia…
Along with saving Inoue,
let's steal the Hogyoku from Aizen!
Hey!
We're leaving!
Yeah.
Rukia…
Yeah… Let's go.
Ashido, I'll come back for you.
Until then…
It unexpectedly suits you.
When did you get here?!
Just now… Don't make a fuss
about everything. It's annoying.
I've come to inform you.
Your friends have
entered Hueco Mundo.
Why?
This wall…
What's the deal with it?
It doesn't seem to be
made of Sekkiseki.
If it's not Sekkiseki, then we
can break through by force!
Let's go, Renji!
Don't boss me around, idiot!
“Why,” you ask?
They've come to save you.
Aside from that…
They have no other reasons.
Umm…
What is it?
These clothes fit me perfectly.
I was wondering how you knew my size.
Everything is as Lord Aizen
has intended it to be.
What?! He knew just by looking at me?!
That's amazing!
Inoue, that's not what you're
supposed to be surprised about.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hisagi, what should we do
if our Zanpakuto breaks?
Did yours break?
This is just theoretical.
I could fix it for a fee.
C-Captain Kurotsuchi?!
By the way, here's a catalog.
Zabimaru is a monkey,
so option four is possible.
This is…
ZABIMARU
PRODUCT CATALOG
You can change their sex?!
Please do this for me!