Care to let me run
in front of you?
Yes.
Please do.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
That hurt, you piece of crap.
How dare you cut my leg!
I'll kill you, you damn bug!
Oh good.
So you can punch.
That last one only
gave me an itch.
I thought you were
some giant fly.
If you're going to hit me, do it
with all your might, maggot.
You're an impudent little fly!
I'll skip the explanation of what
goes into a Garganta.
If you go the other way, you'll get
to the World of the Living.
Got it.
Make sure to watch
your footing.
One misstep inside, and
you'll wind up in some
unknown space between the World
of the Living and Hueco Mundo.
You won't be able to get back.
Well, that would provide some
interesting data as well.
What is it?
Come to think of it, when
Mr. Urahara saw us off,
he talked to us from
a high place too.
What?
Since you're the second Chief of
Research and Development,
you must have been Mr. Urahara's
apprentice or something, right?
You two are kind of similar.
How dare you!
Bye!
Isane.
Take care of the rest.
I will, Captain Unohana.
Ichigo...
I see... Fascinating.
Ichigo Kurosaki is a
fascinating man!
Master Mayuri...
I thought it might be interesting
to trap him in the Garganta,
but I changed my mind!
I'll take my time
putting some fear into him
once this battle is over.
Fear that'll make him think of this
battle as a pleasant memory!
Understood, Master Mayuri.
I'll think up a plan.
For a worm, you're pretty tough.
Don't talk big!
Eat this!
Can't fight back anymore?
It's over.
I'll crush you like a damn fly!
Damn it! My finger!
How dare you cut off my finger!
I'm not done yet!
You damn bug!
Why did you stay behind,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi?
How odd.
That doesn't seem like something
you'd care to know.
There should be more
things that are
of interest to you in the
World of the Living.
So why stay here?
What are you plotting?
Oh? How very cautious of you.
Don't worry.
I'm not planning anything
that'll scare you.
It's just that, at the moment,
the corpses over here
are more interesting.
That's all.
Once the battle in the World
of the Living is over,
someone will open up a Garganta
from the other side.
I'll use that to go to the
World of the Living,
and take my time to examine
each of the corpses.
What is it?
What is it?!
I asked you, what is it?!
If you have something
to say, say it!
Okay?!
Well...
I never expected you
to say such a thing.
I was a little surprised.
What?
That thing you just said...
It sounded as if you were implying
that sending Ichigo Kurosaki
to the World of the Living
would end the battle.
It sounded as if you believed
that Ichigo Kurosaki
would be victorious.
Nonsense.
Absolute nonsense.
I never expected such words to come
from you, Byakuya Kuchiki.
Hang on, guys!
Kurosaki.
I want to ask you something.
You encountered Sosuke Aizen
at the Sokyoku Hill
once before, right?
Yeah. What about it?
What did you think?
There wasn't much
to think about.
He had monstrous strength.
I was completely helpless.
He didn't even use his Shikai.
It was a one-sided battle.
"He didn't even use his Shikai."
Did I hear that correctly?
Yeah.
That's good.
Huh?
The fact that you had such
a large difference
in strength was your
greatest fortune.
I shall tell you now, Kurosaki.
At the moment, you are probably
the only person
in the World of the Living, Soul
Society and Hueco Mundo
who can fight Sosuke Aizen.
What do you mean?
I shall tell you
about the powers of his Zanpakuto,
Kyokasuigetsu,
and the requirements
for activating it.
This is my Zanpakuto,
Kyokasuigetsu.
Its ability is complete hypnosis.
Complete hypnosis?
But the Kyokasuigetsu is
a water-type Zanpakuto.
It confuses your enemies
and makes them
attack each other by using
reflections created
from mist and water.
That's what you told us,
Captain Aizen.
You gathered us Lieutenants together
and demonstrated it to us!
I see...
So that was actually
the hypnosis ritual.
Correct.
Complete hypnosis dominates
all five senses.
It can cause everything about
a target, including its form,
shape, mass, feel, and even smell,
to be mistaken for an enemy.
In other words, it can make
a fly appear to be a dragon,
or a swamp appear to
be a field of flowers.
All I need to activate it
is to show my enemies my
Kyokasuigetsu's release.
Anyone who sees it, even once,
falls under complete hypnosis.
From then on, complete hypnosis
takes hold of them
whenever I release
my Kyokasuigetsu.
Anyone who sees
it...even once?!
That's right.
We, the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads,
Kisuke Urahara's men,
with whom you are
acquainted with in the
World of the Living,
as well as Sosuke Aizen's
subordinates,
the Arrancars and
the Espadas...
Everyone who is possibly
involved in the battle in
the World of the Living has
seen Aizen's Shikai.
That's right, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Everyone but you.
You possess a Spiritual Pressure
that rivals that of a captain
and you have not seen the
Kyokasuigetsu's Shikai.
So as long as I don't
see Aizen's Shikai,
I won't fall under his
complete hypnosis?
That's right.
Your advantage is very
important in this battle.
No. More accurately,
if you lose that advantage,
this battle is over.
Kurosaki...
No matter what happens
in this battle
from here on out, do not look
at Sosuke Aizen's Shikai.
Ever.
Got it.
Thanks, Unohana.
I'm glad I heard that before
I went into battle.
Hearing that is more
than enough.
I'm the only one, right?
Then it's decided.
I'm going to defeat Aizen!
You're too slow!
I told you, that itches,
you worm!
Oh? His brain isn't the only
thing brutish about him.
If he's able to knock that
giant body into the air,
he's got some brute
strength in him.
Damn it.
You're starting to really
piss me off!
I am so pissed!
Damn bug! You damn bug!
But if he's going to defeat him,
I wish he'd do it quickly.
I'm dying to dissect
that Espada.
It appears
I'll be dissecting the Squad 11
Captain before the large one.
That should be enjoyable too.
How does it look?
They are severely injured.
But I can handle it.
Please save them.
I will.
Ichigo...
Um, Kurosaki...
Care to let me run
in front of you?
Huh? No, that's okay.
If you're worried about my Spiritual
Pressure consumption,
I'll be... fine.
Kurosaki...
Care to let me run
in front of you?
Yes.
Please do.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Whoa...
The path looks so
nice when done
by a captain's Spiritual
Pressure.
In fact, the difference is so great
that it's making me sad.
What are you talking about?
We're no different in terms
of Spiritual Pressure.
Huh?
From what I can see, your
wounds have healed.
Yet, you were making a mess
even in your best condition.
Your sloppy Spiritual Pressure
is just not suited
for this sort of task.
Sloppy?
Th-That's not true!
If my Spiritual Pressure were
completely recovered,
I could do a little better!
You look a little too awake
to be daydreaming.
Hold on!
Don't you think you're
being a little mean?!
I'm not daydreaming, or joking!
Take a look at this!
I only have a right sleeve, right?
When I do Bankai,
my Shihakusho changes too.
And it seems
this transformed Shihakusho
is also part of my Bankai.
As proof of that...
When Inoue healed
my wounds earlier,
only part of my
Shihakusho was fixed.
Normally when Inoue heals me,
it'd fix my Shihakusho as well.
So I asked her why.
Apparently, Inoue can
heal wounds quickly,
but it takes her a while to revive
a person's Spiritual Pressure.
But Rukia and the others were
in trouble, so I hurried off.
I went off without having my
Spiritual Pressure restored.
So this is all the Spiritual Pressure
I have right now!
See?
If I were at my best,
I could do better!
Impossible...
His Shihakusho is less than
half of what it usually is.
Does that mean that he only has
half of his Spiritual Pressure?
I was under the
impression that
his Spiritual Pressure rivaled
that of a captain at his best!
Kurosaki, you should
run in the front.
I'm going to restore your
Spiritual Pressure
as best as I can while
we're on the move.
On the move? While
we're running?
You can do that?
I can.
When healing with Kido,
we start by restoring one's
Spiritual Pressure.
The restored inner
Spiritual Pressure
and the healer's external Spiritual Pressure
then heal the body itself.
Okay...
In other words, restoring
the Spiritual Pressure
in a body that has been
healed is quite easy.
Please move to the
front, Kurosaki.
O-Okay.
If this really is only half
of his Spiritual Pressure...
He may really be
our trump card!
Someone
who can end this battle.
I've got you!
Get away from me,
you damn bug!
That hurts!
You bastard!
One more!
M-My leg!
Good, I was getting
tired of waiting.
I almost fell asleep.
But now it looks like I
can begin dissecting.
Nemu, prepare to dissect.
Yes, Master Mayuri.
He finally went down.
He was pretty tough.
Hey, are you done, big guy?
Hey, Byakuya Kuchiki!
He's no good!
I'll let you handle the rest!
I don't know what
you mean by that.
What are you, stupid?
You must be bored from
watching all this time.
We just need to finish him off.
I'm letting you take care of that.
I see.
You're telling me to clean up
after your unfinished job.
Who do you think you are?
What?
I don't like finishing off those
who are weaker than I am.
Stop complaining and do it!
I refuse.
Finishing someone off
is a job that is suited
for a brute like you.
What?!
Damn it...
Damn it!
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
You're amazing Unohana, with your
skilled healing powers and all.
Why, thank you.
Must come with age, doesn't it?
Unohana?
It's shameful for a man to talk
about age in front of a lady.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, ma'am.
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Is something wrong?
Um... I feel like I'm
forgetting something.
Something that starts
with "Hana"...
Hana?
Hana.
Hana...
Hana?
Hana.
Hana!
Hana Megane (Funny Glasses)!
Oh!
I can't seem to concentrate
on the job without this!
Now, let's continue on
with the treatment!
Where is everybody?!