Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo.
They crush the enemies
standing in their way
and finally make their way
to Las Noches.
Upon breaking into the palace,
the group decides to split up
and go down separate paths.
They begin fierce battles
with powerful Arrancars
who are waiting for them
deep within Las Noches.
Whirl! Giralda!
This time… Let's trade blows
at full strength, niño!
All right.
That wasn't even good enough
to be a warm-up exercise.
Hado 73: Soren Sokatsui!
What a fool.
If you hit me with that attack directly,
you would have at least scratched me.
This is most important to me!
It proves that you
are not Sir Kaien!
Now that it is clear,
I can kill you without remorse!
It's over. I'll show you
an Espada's sword release.
Devour! Glotoneria!
Oh no.
Look, look!
Curve, curve!
What's wrong?
Are you giving up already?!
Damn!
That's not a shield.
Don't be reckless!
Damn.
D-D-D-Danger!
I'm in danger!
Not only am I in danger because
I followed the weakest of the bunch…
PESCHE'S STRONG-LOOKING
FACES RANKING
He's also fighting
someone really strong.
What should I do?
He looks like he's going to die.
Maybe I should save him.
No, wait.
Think hard about this,
Pesche Gatiche!
Even if I were to go out,
what could I do?
No…but…
I can't continue to
watch this happen!
I can almost…see her underwear.
How does that feel?
Does it hurt, white four eyes?
It looks like you don't even
have the strength to respond.
In that case, hurry up and…
J-Just a little more…
Just a little more…
Who the hell are you?!
You're Pesche Gatiche, right?
Impossible… I only said my name once,
but he's remembered my full name!
A-And you're Uryu Ishida.
That's right.
A smile?!
C-Could it be that this man…
Do you love me?
Why?!
What are you saying?!
That's disgusting!
Shut up!
Who is that termite-like guy?
Is he a termite?
Wha—?!
A-A termite? How rude!
Call me a stag beetle
at the very least!
That's not much of a difference.
There's a big difference!
Stag beetles are
black, shiny, and cool!
But you're white.
I don't want you of all people
telling me that!
You're completely in white!
It's fine if I'm in white!
I have pride in my whites!
Pride in your whites?!
You talk as if you're a detergent.
Are you making fun of me?
I told you to shut up!
Oh no!
It seems that termite
is a friend of yours.
W-Wait! He's a Hollow!
He's not my friend!
H-How cruel!
I thought that we were friends!
You idiot!
So he says!
You even remembered my name!
Are you stupid?!
I said I wasn't your friend so that she'd
divert her attacks away from you!
What?! I appreciate
your thoughtfulness!
I've failed though!
Anyway, why are you here?!
Kurosaki told you to go home!
Oh, that!
You've noticed
something important, Uryu!
You're suddenly chummy.
Actually, I'm looking for Nel!
Nel followed after you guys
screaming for Ichigo.
Where has Nel gone?!
Who is Ichigo?!
I have no clues.
Oh!
Could it be that
you're actually Ichigo?
I'm Uryu!
You just said that I was Uryu!
Ichigo is the pointy-haired
Soul Reaper!
Pointy-hair…
There were two.
Which one was he?
The orange one!
Don't you remember anything?!
What are you blabbing on about?!
Crap!
She caught up with us because
I was dealing with your silliness!
Bump!
Leave this to me, Uryu!
Leave it to you?
There's nothing
you can do to her!
It's all right!
I have a special ability!
A special ability?
I can create a liquid that makes
anything it touches incredibly slippery!
You're worthless!
Aww, you're so annoying!
Stop! It's useless!
Be quiet and watch!
Get out of the way!
Pesche Gatiche!
Wha—?!
Phew…
Did you see that?!
Your attacks are nothing!
Also, I don't really
want to see your underwear!
You peeked, didn't you?!
W-Wait!
I didn't see it yet.
I couldn't really see it.
That's why I don't
really want to see it!
Wh-Why are you looking at me
like that, too?!
I wasn't peeping!
Oh?
N-No! Please, Uryu,
I want you to believe me at least!
Why?!
You two!
Quit making fun of me!
I-It seems like you haven't
learned from my super attack!
As if I would!
Huh?! Huh?! Huh?!
Uryu, you saved me.
I thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
Please, don't be rash!
A-All right…
But you saved me!
I must repay you
for your kindness!
I will defeat her!
You don't seem to
understand at all.
Oh, are you going to fight me?
Of course!
If I don't, then who will?!
You're probably just going to
create that strange liquid again.
Here I go!
You're pretty predictable!
That won’t hit me!
Are you stupid?
Hey…
All right! I can produce
a limitless amount of this liquid!
You made a mistake
when you underestimated me!
I feel sorry for her.
I call this liquid “Infinite Slick”!
It's annoying that
its name is kind of cool.
Come on! Don't laugh.
You run away now!
– What?!
– Don't ask why!
Something like that
will only be successful once.
Rip…
Golondrina!
From the way you're fighting,
you don't seem to be
taking me very seriously.
You're the first enemy
I've encountered in a while,
so I was going to
take my time with you.
Wha—?
I, Arrancar Number 105
Cirucci Sanderwicci,
am going to crush you!
Now then…
Who should I slice first?
You run really fast,
don't you, four eyes!
Wait! Wait!
Come on. I'm not finished yet!
I'm not going to be stopped here!
Then I will fight with you!
Hey, don't ignore me!
It's embarrassing!
Enough!
I'm going to turn you
into paper-thin chips!
Stop running around!
She sure enjoys
doing evil things!
You're one to talk!
That’s the sort of comeback
I was hoping for!
Hey!
You're not getting away,
four eyes!
She knocked it away!
It's as I thought. All those feathers
are vibrating at high speeds!
That turbulent sound that's been
reverberating is proof of that!
That won't work!
Huh? Where did you go,
four eyes?
I told you that doesn't work!
Hey, Uryu!
What have you been doing?!
You're still here?!
I thought I told you to run away!
Uryu, could it be that you used
a useless attack in order to protect me?!
Don't call it useless!
Just run away! Don't interfere!
Wait, Cirucci,
or whatever your name is!
There's a saying,
“If you run after two hares,
you will catch neither.”
In this case, you should
give up on him and go after me!
Y-You idiot!
Then, I won't hesitate.
Wh-What?! So suddenly?!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are
you doing, Uryu?!
I was trying to protect you!
I want you to get out of the way!
You don't need
to worry about me!
No, I refuse!
I'm going to fight with you!
And I’m saying I'm going to
slice up the both of you together!
I've got to do something
about those feathers!
Uryu, what should we do?!
I know!
Pesche!
Use your Infinite Slick
once more!
Infini… What is that?!
Infinite Slick!
Your weird liquid!
You named it!
Weird liquid? How rude!
I want you to call it
“Infinite Slick”!
Just make some already!
How bothersome!
You sure are hopeless!
You can't do anything
without me!
Take a look.
It seems…I've run out of it.
Why?!
Didn't you call it Infinite Slick
because you could create
limitless amounts of it?!
Well, umm…
You were lying?!
Well… Not really a lie.
I was giving the impression that
I could create limitless amounts of it.
You were lying!
Yes… It was a lie.
Sorry.
Why did you lie?!
Well…I thought it sounded
cooler that way.
Don't give me that!
But…
There are moods to situations.
This is a battle!
There are no moods!
Oh!
What are you doing?!
Damn it! It's annoying
being with you!
I'm the one who's annoyed!
Die!
Did you feel it connect?
Ah… I know that.
It's called a Flash Step, isn't it?
Too bad…
Mine is called a Hirenkyaku.
Hmm… Hirenkyaku, huh?
How exactly are they different?!
A Flash Step again.
It looks like you can
run away quickly.
But how long do you think
you can you keep running away?
It's as she says…
Uryu can't attack as long as
he's carrying me.
I'm being a burden.
That's good enough, Uryu!
Use me as a shield
and create an opening!
Leave my corpse behind!
Ride on!
Why are you crying?
You're really stupid, aren't you?
Sh-Shut up.
I was just imagining the climax.
– Pesche…
– Yes?
This may hurt a bit,
but endure it.
Huh?! C-Could it be?!
Are you really going to leave
my corpse behind and live?!
Oh?
Oh! Right in my crotch!
Sorry, Pesche.
But now…
I can focus on this battle!
Stop blabbing on!
I see… The blades continue
to vibrate at high speeds
even after they're separated
from her body.
She can also reload at ease.
As long as she has those blade feathers,
I have nowhere to attack up close.
But those feathers
deflect my long-range attacks
before they can hit.
Here! One more!
I have no choice.
Wha—?
What…is that?
How unfortunate.
I was really hoping to hold off
on using this until a little later.
Shall we continue?
Prepare yourself, Cirucci!
We're going to use our united attack
of friendship, the Infinite Pesche Quincy!
I'll repel that attack
with my feathers!
Sorry to put a damper on things,
but he's not your opponent.
And that attack doesn't exist.
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
– The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today, I shall talk about
a slightly odd Arrancar.
Aaroniero is the only Gillian
in the Espada.
That's because he has
his Glotoneria ability,
which allows him to gain the abilities
and Spiritual Pressure of a dead Hollow
by devouring it.
We can evolve infinitely.
No one is a match for us.
Hmm? So which is Aaro
and which is Niero?
I'm Aaro.
And I'm Niero.
– Hey, Aaroniero is not a group name!