Hey there.
Why...
Are you okay with this?
Well...
You should be careful.
It may have already begun.
And just what is this?
Um, it's a lemon.
That's a lemon?
It's "The Lemon's Scream."
Are you sure that's how you want to draw it?
This is how the lemon looks to me.
It's not in line with the
objective of the class...
But I suppose it's all right.
That said, you should save things
like this for the art club.
Okay. I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
Go ahead and finish it up.
Are you a fan of Munch?
Yeah, kind of.
Mochizuki definitely has a
drawing style all his own.
The lemon is screaming?
No, actually, it's the world that's screaming.
The lemon is covering its ears
because it's terrified of the sound.
So, you're in the art club, huh?
Yeah.
It just started up again this year.
Are you planning to join
any clubs, Sakakibara?
I haven't decided.
Would you be interested in the art club?
Me?
Yeah, I mean...
What are you drawing, Teshigawara?
An apple.
Apples don't have arms and legs.
This is how the apple looks to me!
Be serious!
I am sort of interested...
Hey, what do you think of Ms. Mikami?
I'm not sure how to answer that.
Well, I guess that's understandable.
Yeah.
She's not here?
Doesn't looking at Munch's "The Scream"
make you feel scared, or uneasy?
Uneasy?
Yes.
I feel uneasy about everything.
The painting draws out that emotion.
That's why I like it.
You like it because it makes you uneasy?
It doesn't do any good to pretend
you can't see what's going on.
I think...
...it's the same for everyone.
Yo, Sakaki!
Talking about Ms. Mikami over here?
Let me in on that!
Unfortunately, we were talking
about something a little darker.
What do you mean by...
...something darker?
The feeling of uneasiness
enveloping the world.
What's that supposed to mean?
Haven't you ever felt that way?
Of course I have!
Like when I finally made it to the 9th grade,
only to end up in the cursed class 3...
Listen, Sakaki...
I've been wanting to tell you
something since yesterday.
Don't you think that's a bad idea now?
Well, maybe, but...
What...
What's wrong?
Nothing. I've gotta go.
Hey, Sakaki!
That's not a...
Hey.
Was it okay to do that?
Do what?
They didn't try to stop you?
I guess not.
What are you drawing?
Is it based on some kind of model?
Or did you make it up?
Both, I guess.
At the end,
I'm going to give her enormous wings.
Is she an angel?
Who knows?
What were you doing out
in the rain yesterday?
I don't dislike rain.
My favorite is the cold rain
that falls in midwinter,
just before it turns into snow.
What's wrong with your left eye?
You've been wearing that eyepatch
since I met you in the hospital.
You want to know?
If you don't want to tell me, it's okay.
Then I won't.
You should head back to class.
I haven't seen you here before.
I'm Sakakibara, from the 9th grade's class 3.
I just transferred here.
I'm Chibiki, the librarian.
You're welcome to come
here anytime you like,
but you should get going now.
Yes, Sir.
Why, Rei?
Rei!
Chibiki, eh?
I'm pretty sure that was his name.
He acted like he was the master of that place.
He does give that impression, doesn't he?
The master of the library.
Antisocial, always dressed in black,
he gave almost all of us girls the creeps.
Did he say anything to you?
No, not really.
Okay.
Has the auxiliary library
always been in that room?
Yes.
But it only became the auxiliary library
after the new building was finished.
By the way, Kouichi,
are you going to join a club?
Well...
Actually,
I was invited to join the art club today.
Do you like art?
It interests me.
I'm not very good at drawing, though.
But still...
Um, I've never told anyone
this before, but...
If possible, I'd like to go
to a fine arts school.
Oh? That's news to me!
I'd like to study carving and sculpting.
Does that sound crazy?
First of all, your father
will undoubtedly oppose.
Second, even if you graduate,
you won't have any marketable skills.
Talent is a key factor, of course,
but without some luck on your
side, you're likely to fail.
But if that's what you want
to do, you might as well try.
It's just pathetic to give up on something
before you even give it a shot.
Pathetic?
Yes. That's important, isn't it?
Whether you look good or
pathetic in your own eyes.
You think so?
Sakakibara!
Sorry. We're swamped during the day.
Is it okay for me to be here?
It's totally fine.
Thank you.
So, what are you reading these days?
The author you recommended to me, John Saul.
If only I could get my coworkers
to read his stuff, too.
But that's not what you
came to talk about, is it?
No.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Did a girl die at this hospital last Monday?
Last Monday?
You were still here then, weren't you?
Why do you ask?
Something happened that made me wonder.
I get the feeling you're asking for a reason.
There were no deaths among the
patients I was in charge of.
Changing the subject, then...
Did you see a girl
wearing a school uniform in any
of the wards that day?
A girl, again?
She had a dark blue blazer, short hair...
and an eyepatch over her left eye.
An eyepatch?
So, an ophthalmology patient?
Hang on!
You saw her?
No.
But a girl who died...
There might have been one.
Really?
It's possible.
I think it was a girl, anyway.
I heard someone say a young patient died.
What was the patient's name?
Want me to find out for you?
Can you?
Sure, I could ask around.
If I dig anything up, I'll call your cell.
I know I've already asked,
but are you sure it's okay for you to do this?
We'll just say you were
concerned for a classmate.
You seem to have a good
reason to want to know.
But in return, you'll have to
tell me that reason sometime.
Got it, mister horror lover?
As you all know,
haiku is a type of fixed form poetry
consisting of seventeen syllables,
divided into lines of five, seven, and five.
However, the term "haiku"
itself is relatively new.
The name was coined approximately
one hundred years ago by
a man named Shiki Masaoka.
Prior to then, the poems
were called "haikai."
There are three important
rules for composing haiku.
Sakakibara.
Are you heading home now?
Got a minute?
I see.
So you were born at Yomiyama Hospital.
My family moved to Tokyo
shortly after, though.
And you lived in Tokyo from then on?
Yes.
Did you ever come back to visit?
My mom died right after she had me,
so not often.
I see.
Why do you ask?
I get this nagging feeling
I've met you before.
Somewhere.
Maybe you're mistaking me for someone else?
That's part of why I wanted to ask.
So annoying.
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean you.
I'm annoyed that I can't remember it clearly.
You shouldn't let it bother you.
This is part of being
the head of countermeasures.
I have to do a good job.
What exactly does the
head of countermeasures do?
In simple terms, I'm in
charge of devising and
executing countermeasures
to protect the class.
Protect the class?
Devising? Executing?
I want to make sure you understand
the situation class 3 is in,
and the rules we must follow.
Akazawa!
What?
Hold on...
Actually...
What?!
Honestly,
I miss one day of school,
and this is what happens?!
See you later.
Misakichou 3-3
The Hollow Blue Eyes of Yomi at Twilight
"The Hollow Blue Eyes of Yomi at Twilight."
What is this?
Feel free to drop in.
-Studio M
Hello?
Sakakibara?
Ms. Mizuno?
About what we discussed the other day.
I found it.
They said it was a junior high school girl.
Apparently, she was an only daughter,
so her parents were devastated.
And her name?
What was the girl's name?
I'm not sure, but...
Yes?
I think her name was Misaki, or Masaki.
Something like that.
I only heard it secondhand,
so I don't know if it's—
Welcome.
My, it's unusual to see a
boy your age here.
Are you a customer? Or perhaps...
Hello.
Um, this is a shop, right?
Are you a junior high student?
Yes, at Yomi North.
Admission: 500 yen
In that case, I'll give you half price.
Is this a doll shop?
About half and half.
I also sell,
but not at prices a junior
high student could afford.
But, please, take your time looking around.
I have no other customers.
I could put on some tea as well, if you'd like.
Thanks, but I'll pass on the tea.
Very well.
Then, please take your time.
More This Way
Is that...
Mei? Why are you here?
Oh? So you don't dislike this sort of thing?
Why are you here?
Why?
I wasn't hiding because
I wanted to surprise you.
You just happened to come while I was here.
Did you think it looks like me?
Yeah...
It does, doesn't it?
But only half.
Maybe less than that.
Why are you here?
I don't dislike these things.
And why are you here, Sakakibara?
Well, um...
I was just walking around, and...
I mean, I don't know this
town all that well yet,
and when I stumbled across
this place, I got curious.
I see.
Some people say dolls like
these are creepy.
But you don't think that?
No.
These two are my favorites.
Their faces look so peaceful.
It's strange to me that can they look so calm,
even though they're attached.
But maybe that's the reason they're calm?
Impossible.
It would make more sense for them
to be calm if they were separated.
Shall I show you?
Shall I show you...
...what's under this eyepatch?
Bone work.