One hundred ten years ago,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
of that day
were different from the present,
but there were some
very familiar faces.
The captain of Squad 5 was
Shinji Hirako, who currently
resides in the World of the Living
as a Visored.
Other members of the Visored
also held positions
as captains and lieutenants
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
At the time,
Kisuke Urahara became
the captain of Squad 12
upon the recommendation of
Squad 2 captain,
Yoruichi Shihoin.
I am considering creating
an organization
under the control of
Squad 12
unlike anything ever seen
in the Soul Society.
I'm calling it the "Department of
Research and Development."
I want you to assume the seat
of deputy department head.
Kurotsuchi Mayuri.
At about the same time
at the Kuchiki Clan residence,
a young Byakuya practiced
his swordsmanship.
At Squad 13's barracks,
Kaien Shiba was being persuaded
by Jushiro Ukitake
to be promoted to lieutenant.
Each, with their own motives,
spent their days thinking of
the future of the Soul Society and
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
But glimpses of the start of
a nightmare were already showing.
Nice.
Your skill is even better
than I had heard.
How was our Third Seat?
Awful. No competition at all.
I see.
Glad to hear it.
After swinging
back to the past and
giving a glimpse of
a moment in time,
the pendulum swings
several years forward.
The incident occurred
nine years
after Kisuke Urahara
became captain.
Hey. Good morning.
Oh!
'Morning, Hirako.
I said you can call me Shinji.
You're such a pain.
'Morning, Mayuri.
I told you to be less casual
and call me Kurotsuchi.
You are an irritating fellow.
What a pain in the ass.
Oh, by the way,
have you heard about that story?
About what?
Ouch!
W-What was that for, Hiyori?!
All of a sudden?!
You haven't greeted me yet!
What's with greeting the other two
and leaving me out?!
Why do I have to greet you?!
This mouth! This damn mouth!
Oh yes, Captain Urahara,
have you already heard?
Heard about what?
About the violent deaths
in the Rukon district.
That's it!
That's what I was talking about!
Good follow up, Sosuke!
Violent deaths?
Yeah…
In the past month or so, there have
been a series of incidents where
residents of the Rukon district
have been disappearing.
The reason is unknown.
Disappearing?
You mean, they went somewhere
and never came back?
Are you an idiot?
You call that running away.
If they ran away, who cares?
They can do whatever they want.
But this is different.
They literally "disappear."
Gone, without a trace,
leaving only their clothes behind.
If they died and became spirits,
the clothes they were wearing
would disappear as well.
They didn't die.
They vanished alive,
unable to retain human form.
That's the only explanation
I can think of.
Alive, but unable to retain
human form?
Sorry. I'm just telling you exactly
what I heard from Captain Unohana.
I don't know what it means.
At any rate, Squad 9 is
already there to investigate.
Hey, hey!
Are you listening to me, Kensei?
What do you mean by "unknown"?
Tell me, Kensei.
Quiet! Unknown means unknown!
Quit babbling.
What's with you?!
There's no need for
a captain to go
just to investigate
something unknown!
It's unknown, that's why
we're going to check it out!
An advance party went out!
Ten people!
You could've just waited
for them to report,
but you're so impatient, Kensei!
You show off!
– Lieutenant, please, you're doing it again.
– I'm sick of this…sick.
– Captain! Please calm down, Captain!
– Stupid Kensei, you show off!
– You know she's always like that!
– Stupid!
First of all,
when did I ever tell you
to come along?!
You don't need to come along!
Go home, take a crap,
and go to sleep, idiot!
I'm your lieutenant, so I always
have to be with my captain!
You're the stupid one for
not knowing that, Kensei.
Stupid!
– Captain!
I'm sick of this!
I'm hungry!
I want to eat ohagi!
The kind with kinako
on the outside!
– What should we do, Captain?
– Nothing but kinako ohagi will do!
– Ignore her!
– I want the big kinako ohagi!
If I don't get away,
I'll end up like that.
I have to get away.
But I can't yell.
My legs won't move.
But…
Go!
Run!
Now!
Faster! Run faster!
What're you doing?! Run!
You have to get away right now!
A Hollow!
It's enormous!
What's that?
It's a child!
Let's go.
Damn it!
Shoot… It won't let go!
Move!
Hey! Hurry and get away!
You don't want to die, do you?
Back off, you guys!
– Yes, sir!
Blast away!
Tachikaze!
Is everybody all right?
– Yes, sir!
Hey! What're you crying for, kid?!
You're alive.
You should be happy.
Laugh!
That's asking too much, Captain.
No, it's not.
Come on, stand up, kid.
What's your name?
Shu…Shuhei…Hisagi…
Shuhei, is it?
That's a strong-sounding name.
Stop crying!
Why're you crying again?
I said stop crying!
Good grief…
Kensei!
Mashiro…
Where the hell did you go
during the battle?
In those bushes!
I found this on the ground!
See? A shihakusho!
There were a whole bunch
of these here! Ten of them!
Ten…shihakusho?!
Captain, they must be…
What, what?
Are ten sets important? Tell me!
You idiot.
It matches the number
in the advance party!
Huh?! But these were
taken off over there!
How could they have been taken off
with the sash still tied?
How could they have
taken off their tabi socks
with their sandals still on?!
Eishima!
Yes, sir!
Contact Central 46!
Souls have vanished.
We have our first
Soul Reaper casualties!
Yes, sir!
Todo!
There's a possibility of
an unknown pathogen
that disintegrates souls!
Request that Squad 12
send lab personnel!
Yes, sir!
Kasaki!
Sir!
Have the main squad
standing by and send tents.
We'll set up camp here tonight!
Yes, sir!
If this is the work of an enemy
targeting Soul Reapers,
they will eventually
target the Seireitei.
We'll crush them here before
they get near the Seireitei!
– Yes, sir!
Get going!
Captain! What about me?
We're checking the area.
Come with me!
Kid! You go on home!
Before it gets dark!
Understand?
What? Are you serious
about camping out?!
Will there be ohagi
for dessert?!
No. If you want some,
get it yourself.
Kensei, you're a butt!
Nice. Very nice.
Hey! I'm still waiting for
container number 22!
You're still over there?!
Hurry it up!
For goodness sake,
at this rate,
it'll be dark before
you bring it here.
Oh, shut up!
I was being nice
and helping you,
so that's no way to talk to me!
Cut it out, you worm!
What're you so angry
about all of a sudden?
That side of you,
quite honestly, is a turn off.
I said shut up!
Why do I have to assist you
in the first place?!
I'm a lieutenant!
What's your rank? Tell me!
This is absurd.
I have no need for
such a thing as rank.
Then I'll tell you!
You're third! Third!
Got that?!
I'm the lieutenant!
You're third!
You mustn't order me around!
Do you understand?
Here at the Department of Research
and Development,
I am the deputy department head,
and you are the laboratory chief.
I outrank you.
If you insist on
following squad rules,
then as long as you're here,
you must obey me.
Kisuke!
Yes?
What is it now?
Please try to be quiet.
I haven't had much sleep, you know.
Do something about this guy!
You haven't taught him well!
Huh?
What is that?
Oh, you mean this?
It's a prototype of a new gigai.
You remember what
Hirako said this morning?
About the incidents
in the Rukon district
where he believes people
were unable to retain human form,
and their souls would vanish.
Supposing that what
he says is true,
I thought that if we were to
place a soul
that was on the verge of
disintegration into a human mold,
the soul would not vanish.
I'm trying to see if I could apply
gigai technology
into making that mold.
You're…
Excuse me!
I am Izaemon Todo,
Sixth Seat of Squad 9!
Is Kisuke Urahara,
captain of Squad 12 here?
I have come to convey a request
from Kensei Muguruma,
captain of Squad 9!
I see.
I understand.
I will select personnel immediately
and send them on their way tonight.
For the time being,
please go back and
help Muguruma.
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much!
Now then…
You heard him, so…
Hiyori, please go there.
Why?! I don't want to!
Why not send someone
lower in rank?
All you do is complain.
If everything is
disagreeable to you,
why not quit being a lieutenant?
Why are you so disrespectful,
Akon?!
You're asking for it!
It's ready, deputy department head.
Good work.
This really pisses me off!
Sorry about this.
Hiyori, you're the only one
I can confidently entrust
a task like this to.
If there's anything
you think you'll need,
you can take it,
even from the captain's office.
A sample from the site of
the vanishing souls
will be very valuable.
I'm counting on you, Hiyori.
Damn it!
I'm gonna demand more
for expenses later!
Remember that!
Don't let anyone know
about that, okay?
What took you so long, Todo?!
I'm sorry.
I was the only one who
went directly to the barracks.
Forgive me.
I'll relieve you.
Go inside and rest.
How can you be so lax?
Now that you're back,
the three of us will keep watch.
We'll take turns,
one man at a time,
every two hours.
Right now, Kasaki is resting inside
with the captain and the others.
You take watch over there.
Okay, understood.
How could she fall asleep
so nonchalantly
under conditions like this?
Hey, your collar's open.
Kensei, you pervert.
You're annoying even in your sleep.
Want me to whack you?
What happened?!
Todo?
You…
Todo!
Damn it!
Keep your guard up, Kasaki!
The enemy is still nearby!
Mashiro! Wake up, Mashiro!
Kasaki!
What is this?
You…
Captain Hirako, why was
Squad 9 sent to investigate?
Kensei and Mashiro are
constantly fighting.
It's so noisy,
the Head Captain hasn't been
getting much sleep lately.
It's part of his solution
to the problem.
Oh really? Look who's talking.
The Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
Found her?
No.
Damn! How far did she go?!
I'll search over there next!
Okay, do that!
Searching for Soul Reapers
who forgot their Soul Phone
and came to the World of the Living
is an important job of
Substitute Soul Reapers.
Matsumoto!