Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
But still, if it’s true what
that bald guy said,
and even if Rukia is in
that white tower…
The problem is which road
to take to get there.
Oh!
Oh, that’s right. I have a map.
We wouldn’t want to run into
any Captains along the way, huh?
Rukia… Are you talking
about Rukia Kuchiki?
Huh?!
Just as I thought…
It’s her, isn’t it?
Then that “white tower” you referred to
is the Senzaikyu.
I…know the hidden way
into that tower.
Huh, I would have never thought
of using the sewer system.
Yes, this sewer system runs
underground throughout the Seireitei,
so we can go anywhere
without running into obstacles.
Don’t the others know
about this entrance?
It was under an ordinary-looking tile…
Yes, everyone knows about it,
but I doubt they’ll catch up
with us down here.
Why’s that?
The only ones that fully comprehend
this complex system
are members of Squad 4,
those of us who specialize
in relief and aid.
Oh, I see, this system is also used
as a pathway for relief and aid.
That’s why only the relief and aid company
needed to master this system.
Not exactly…
It’s just that it’s Squad 4’s duty
to clean up the sewer system.
We’re weak, so…
we wind up
with a lot of menial chores.
Gee, I kind of feel sorry
for this Squad 4.
No… It’s really not all that bad.
Hanataro.
Huh?
Why are you doing all this for us?
We’re your enemies.
And just because we want
to go to the White Tower…
Hey, Ichigo.
Why are you guiding us
without question?
I know a lot about you…
from listening to Rukia.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Please… Save Rukia!
Here is the situation report.
Sir Ikkaku Madarame,
Third Seat of Squad 11,
and Sir Yumichika Ayasegawa,
Fifth Seat, same squad…
The above high-ranking Seat officers,
due to serious injuries,
will withdraw from the front lines.
A detailed damage report
for the individual squads
is still pending investigation.
However, regarding Squad 11…
There is a report stating that
they were nearly annihilated.
Squad 11?!
No way…
In just a few hours since
entering this realm,
they’ve managed to wreak
that much havoc?
Hah, how pathetic.
At this time, there are three
confirmed Ryoka,
of which two have taken
a member of the Squad 4 hostage.
We have intelligence indicating
that these two, with the hostage,
are headed this way.
However, since a while ago,
we have been unable to detect
their Spiritual Pressure,
therefore, their whereabouts
are unknown.
Either way, we need to collect
more information.
Frankly, it’s been a while since
our Fourth Seat reported in.
I think he’s been defeated too.
Can you check in
on the West 20 area?
The Fourth Seat of Squad 7…
You mean Jirobo –
the Kamaitachi?
Yeah.
Jidanbo’s brother, huh?
He’s defeated too?
What in the world is going on?
Gosh, they’re all pathetic.
This certainly has turned
into a horrible mess, Abarai…
We need to act more carefully.
That Squad 11 gets too temperamental.
You, stop spreading misinformation.
Abarai…?
I did no such thing…
Rangiku, calm down.
Before Rukia was captured and
placed in the Senzaikyu Shishinro,
she was held
in Squad 6’s barracks.
I was assigned to cleaning duty
for that area.
To be honest,
I was scared of her at first.
After all, she is nobility.
But…
But?
Rukia scolded me on my first day.
Umm, Miss Rukia, I’ll be starting
today’s cleaning chores now.
I’d rather you not call me that.
Umm… But…
Just address me normally.
Uh?  Umm… Ah…
Then… Rukia?
Thank you…
Y-Yes!
Her voice was much kinder
than what I had expected.
I was quite relieved.
Ever since that day,
my daily cleaning at the barracks
gradually has become something
to look forward to.
And little by little, Rukia started
telling me all kinds of things.
Umm, Rukia? I don’t know much
about the human world,
but what’s it like over there?
Like the things to eat or drink…
Oh, I’m sorry!
I mean, it’s nothing!
I’m sorry.
They have a beverage called a
“juice” that comes in a paper package.
What kind of a drink is that?
It is a difficult beverage…
Huh?!
There is a trick to drinking it.
Even I had difficulties with it.
Is that so? There’s a drink that
even you had difficulties with…
Hanataro, you may not be able to drink
it even after hearing the trick.
Really?!
That guy,
he taught me how to drink it.
Rukia, was there anything unusual
in the human world?
Did you know that
a Mod Konpaku
can be inserted into
inanimate objects as well?
What?! You mean those illegal things?
There was this guy who placed one
into a stuffed doll found on the street.
Stuffed doll?
That’s the thing made with
cotton and such, right?
To put it into something like that…
There sure are some reckless folks
out there…
Yes… There are some
reckless ones out there.
Of all the tales Rukia told me
of the human world…
the majority of them were always
about this one person.
Shortly thereafter, an official
execution order was sent to Rukia.
Don’t make me repeat myself.
For a first-degree offense,
Rukia Kuchiki shall be held
in maximum security.
In 25 days, she shall be sent
to the Central Execution Grounds
to be executed.
Rukia… The person you gave
your Soul Reaper powers to…
Is that the same person
you often speak of?
His name is Ichigo Kurosaki.
I only spent two months with him,
but strangely,
I felt I could trust him from
the bottom of my heart.
And yet…
Because of me, his destiny became twisted
and he was terribly hurt.
There is nothing I can do
to atone for this…
She looked very sad
as she said that.
How’d you say?
She’s a strange Soul Reaper, that one…
Yeah, she’s a strange one.
Huh?
That’s why we’re here
to rescue her.
Ah? Hey!
W-Wait a minute!
Did I say something wrong?
How should I know?!
Hey, Ichigo!
I only spent two months with him…
but strangely, I felt I could trust him
from the bottom of my heart.
And yet, because of me,
his destiny became twisted
and he was terribly hurt.
There is nothing I can do
to atone for this…
That idiot! Isn’t that all my fault?!
I swear, I won’t let you die.
Rukia!
Uh… It’s okay! You can come up.
This exit is the closest to the tower.
Wow! It seems like a long time since
I’ve breathed fresh air!
There, that’s the Senzaikyu!
We’re definitely closer to it,
but look at that!
It looks like it’s going to be
a rough road ahead.
The mist is clearing!
Let’s hurry.
Hmm?
Is something the matter, Ichigo?
There’s someone by the stairs.
It’s been a while.
Do you remember my face?
I would have liked to forget it,
but there’s still a mountain
of payback I owe you…
Renji Abarai!
That’s a surprise,
you remembered my name, too.
That’s pretty good.
Why, thank you.
W-Who is this guy?
His Spirit Pressure is on a completely
different level than those earlier guys.
T-That, that person is…
Renji Abarai!
The Lieutenant of Squad 6!
Lieutenant?
I’m truly surprised…
I thought you’d be dead after
Captain Kuchiki’s attack.
Ah, hey! Wait a minute, Ichigo!
I don’t know how you managed
to survive,
but you’re something else, all right.
But this is as far as you go.
As I’ve told you before,
I will kill the one who stole
Rukia’s powers.
As long as you’re alive,
Rukia can’t get her powers back!
How can you say that after
taking her back just to kill her!
I’m coming through!
Try it if you can!
If only you can defeat me!
It’s starting,
and the opponent is Abarai, huh?
He’s already defeated
the Third Seat.
Next, he had better defeat
at least a Lieutenant.
Otherwise, he won’t be much fun
as my opponent.
Kenny, how is it that you don’t sense
other people’s Spirit Pressure,
but you can tell they’re fighting
from far away?
That’s because I’m strong.
Hmm… That’s weird.
Hey, have you found anything?
No, not at all.
It’s been a while since these
Ryoka crossed over
and while our casualties keep rising,
we can’t seem to find them at all!
It means that they’re that crafty.
The Captains and Lieutenants
are keeping in close contact
to obtain the latest
status report details.
Hey! In that direction…
They found Jirobo
of the Squad 7 fallen!
What?!
They’re gone…
Uh-huh.
It seems Ichigo and the others are
doing quite a number out there.
The security is getting tighter.
Well, I think we can handle
those Soul Reapers now…
What’s the matter, Uryu?
This Spirit Pressure…
It’s Ichigo, and the other one is…
Renji Abarai!
Ichigo… You sure met up
with a tough one…
Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
Do you feel fine?
Are you running a fever?
I’m okay, so don’t worry about me.
That’s good to hear.
You space out sometimes,
so I was worried.
Aw, that was no fun.
See you later!
Good, then let’s hurry!
Ichigo’s spiritual power is rising…
His opponent’s Spirit Pressure
is quite strong…
I had better hurry.
Ichigo, you’re fighting
against a Lieutenant!
No matter how strong you are,
you can’t win!
No…
That may not be the case.
Please take a good look at Ichigo.
Incredible! He’s completely
overpowering Lieutenant Abarai!
He… Ichigo…
What exactly is he?
That’s what I’d like to know.
Hey, Ichigo Kurosaki…
How do you plan on saving Rukia?
How?
Even if you defeat me here,
there are still 11 Lieutenants left.
And above them,
there are 13 Captains.
Unless you defeat them all,
there’s no way to save Rukia.
And you think you can do that?
Of course! Who cares
how many Captains there are?
Or how many Lieutenants?
It doesn’t matter! I’ll defeat them!
I’ll defeat them all
if they get in my way!
What’s that? Where do you
get your confidence from?
Why are you so worked up over this?
Your Zanpaku-to has changed, huh?
Don’t think you’re stronger
just because of that!
Don’t get cocky!
Huh!
Roar!
Zabimaru!
I-I can’t stop it!
Yikes!
Ichigo!
I-Ichigo…
You seem to think…
that you already know my strength
just by fighting me once.
Let me tell you something.
When the ranked Lieutenants
and above are sent outside,
our powers are severely limited
so that we don’t adversely
affect the human world.
My strength right now is
five times greater than before.
So no matter how strong you become,
there’s no way you can defeat me!
So that means that attack there…
was the best you’ve got?
Didn’t affect me! Not at all!
Thank you! If 11 of these are
what I’m dealing with,
I think I can handle it!
The idiot!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
As I’ve said before,
we Soul Reapers have our powers
severely limited in the human world.
My strength right now is five times greater
than it was when I last fought you!
I’ve been training and I’ve become
ten times stronger than before!
Then I’m a hundred times
stronger than that!
I’m a thousand times
Actually, I’m ten thousand
times stronger!
Then I’m a hundred thousand
times stronger than that!
I’m a million times stronger
in addition to that!
Well, too bad, I’m plus
ten million times stronger!
Then I’m a hundred
million times stronger!
I’m infinite times stronger!