Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
This is…
Whose work is this?!
I never thought that they would enter
the Shishinro, Repentance Cell
and plant a bomb…
Why would they do that?
It's a declaration of war…
Shishinro is made of Sekkiseki.
Spiritual attacks cannot damage it.
Despite that…
I never thought that they
would take the time
to plant something so tedious.
I sense immense spite…
Add more people to
the investigative team.
We must pinpoint
where they’re hiding!
–Yes!
It's the Bounts, isn't it?
I've failed. They got us!
Let's get them back!
Hey! How is Rukia?!
Are you listening?!
How is Rukia?!
Her life's not in danger…
However, her wound is deep.
I'm going to let her rest here
until she recovers.
Thank goodness.
Well… This was all possible
because you strongly wished
to save your sister!
What wonderful sibling love!
Aren't you glad?
You're pretty good yourself!
I'm relieved.
Could you lend me a hand, Byakuya?
I need your help!
What?
In order to distract us,
they targeted Rukia,
because her wounds
weren't healed!
I can't forgive them!
Don't you feel the same?
I refuse.
What?! Why?!
Will you tolerate the Bounts
rampaging around?!
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are already on the move.
There is no need to
join forces with you.
– What?!
– Kurosaki!
Return to the World of the Living.
Is that so…
Yesterday's enemy is
also today's enemy, huh?
Let's go, Inoue!
Huh? But… Umm…
I'll leave Rukia to you, Byakuya…
Oh…
Take care of Kuchiki.
Oh. W-Wait a second!
Hold on!
This looks like fun…
Can I join?
What are you betting?
Well…
Is this all right?
You're betting your life?
You're new here, aren't you?
You still think this is
the World of the Living…
This is Soul Society.
The pain is the same, isn't it?
How interesting!
Let's do this!
H-Hey!
You think you're so great!
I'll break your nose!
What?!
I win.
H-He's cheating!
He's got to be cheating!
What's wrong?
Are you afraid?
You're a Kusajishi resident…
You're said to be the worst
in the Rukon District.
You bastard!
Wh-What's with you?!
What's wrong?
Is that the most strength
you can put into it?
Are you my next opponent?
Y-You bastard!
Wh-What did you do?!
Stop.
He's not someone you can take on.
Oh well… I thought I could play a little…
Ichinose… Help me stop Kariya!
A Soul Reaper?!
Why is someone from Seireitei here?!
Seireitei… No…
I'm no longer a Soul Reaper…
What the hell are
you talking about?!
There's only three of them!
Get them!
Die!
Be a little more discreet.
I see… I'll be careful next time…
No matter how big
Rukon District is,
we'll be found immediately
if we do things like this.
That's not a bad idea either…
Jeez…
Wh-What are you?!
Why have you come here?!
Let's just say that
we've come for some fun.
How about it?
Want to play with us?
What do you mean?
We're going to turn Soul Society
upside down!
Could it be that you're…
I didn't see anyone like them
on the south side!
I see! All right,
go around the east side!
– Yes!
The Ryoka are cunning!
Don't let them get away!
– Find them!
– Are they there?!
– Hey, what's wrong?
– Did you find them?
– Find them immediately!
– I'm sorry…
Hurry! Don't let the
other squads get ahead of us!
Wow! Everyone's really busy!
They're rushing around over there!
They're busy over here!
Oh! He fell down!
Say, I wonder if Smoothie
and Yun-yun are trying their best.
This is a race to see who
can find the Bounts first, isn't it?
Are you going to race too?
Of course not…
I'm going to the toilet.
Is that all?
Are you bored?
No… I'm just a little relieved…
Why?
Since Maki is with the Bounts,
you wouldn't have fun
fighting him if you met him, so…
None of that matters…
What matters is what he's like now.
Hmm… Then either is fine…
KUKAKU SHIBA
I'm tired!
We've got no clues even after
walking around this much…
I wonder why the Bounts
broke into Seireitei
to destroy the Shishinro,
Repentance Cell…
They probably wanted
all of Soul Society
to know that they've come here.
What do you mean?
Is that something like
an announcement of a crime?
They took the time to do that?
Are they stupid?
They want revenge…
It would be a problem if
no one noticed.
Well, we never knew what
they were thinking to begin with.
They seem to be enjoying
their crimes…
Chad!
Sorry… I couldn't make it to
where Kuchiki was fighting…
Me neither… Byakuya's the one
who saved her.
Then…
Yeah… She's getting treatment
at Byakuya's house…
I see…
This wouldn't have happened
if we were more useful…
You seem tired, Master Kurosaki!
Wh-What's this?!
We shall show you
something good!
KUKAKU SHIBA
What are you going to show me?
Here we go, Shiroganehiko!
Ready, Brother!
– There! There! There! There!
KUKAKU SHIBA
Yes! A grand sight!
I feel the same, Brother!
Amazing! They're open, they're open!
How about that, Master Kurosaki?
Well…even if you ask me…
What is this?
What do you mean,
"What is this"?!
What do you mean?!
Are you saying you're not impressed
by this magnificence?!
What's that?!
Brother!
Aren't those guys Ganju's…
The Great Kukaku Arms are broken!
Are you serious?!
They were acting big
for newcomers…
It was the first time
I saw someone
who could silence the guys
from Kusajishi!
Kusajishi, huh?
Is it Kariya?
Who knows?
But Kusajishi is
a good place to start.
What do you mean?!
The dregs of society
gather there…
Well, it's one of the most dangerous
places in Rukon District…
In other words, they're strong.
They'll be quite a force if
they can be unified.
Big Sis! I was about to say that…
What are you talking about?!
Anyone could figure that out!
That aside…
Why in the world did
you guys go there?
U-Umm… How should I put this?
We went to inspect…
Inspect what?
W-Well, it was a sort of
an intelligence game…
So?
So… W-We were studying society…
I told you not to do things
you can't do under the bright sun!
I-I'm sorry…
So what are you going to do?
I'm going!
Every lead is important,
no matter how small it is!
I thought you'd say that!
I'm going too…
Ishida!
You're back?
Yeah… Ganju, take me with you!
I'm going to defeat Kariya!
All right! Then, tomorrow morning…
What in the world are you
talking about?!
You're going right now!
We're going to kick those
Bounts' butts!
Y-Yeah!
But Big Sis, it's easy to get lost
in that area at night…
Did you hear me?
Y-Yes!
Let's go!
Everyone!
All right!
What are these?
Don't refer to them as “these”!
Listen up…
From the left is,
Bonnie,
Connie,
Tony,
Annie,
Sunny,
Honey,
Manny,
Nanny,
and Kanbe!
Hey! Why is the last one
so different?!
Wow!
They're so cute!
So your name is Kanbe?!
All right, everyone!
To your positions!
– All right!
You too!
H-Hold on a second!
I don't want to ride on
any boar you prepared!
Hey, you. Hey!
I'm taking a different course!
Hold on, Ichigo!
I don't know how long I'll take
to reach our destination
if we ride these things!
That bastard…
Doesn't know how long
I'll take to reach our destination?!
Kurosaki, that bastard,
ran away…
Damn!
Don't underestimate
Bonnie's abilities!
Let's go, Bonnie!
The Kuchiki…house?
I see… I was saved…
It's warm…
Big Brother?
Ugh… I-I'm tired…
Where am I?
Who am I?
Just kidding…
I can't go on…any longer…
No, remember…
I'm not a guy who would die
in a place like this!
Thank you for waiting!
This will warm you up.
Thank you.
Here you go.
The thing that I won't forget
even if I forget everything,
even my name and address…
The shape of happiness!
A soft, bouncy, and sweet…
Lady!
H-Hold on, this…
Don't talk! Beginners tend
to bite their tongues!
Go!
Well, this is amazing!
This is the first time
I've ridden a boar!
– This is fun!
– It sure is!
All right, we're now going
into the forest!
Don't hit your head
against the branches!
Rest here for a while.
Are your friends going
to gather?
There's no one around here
who won't listen to us!
I'll gather the number of people
you wanted by tomorrow!
How encouraging.
Now, excuse me.
I'm very sorry…
for taking you to a place like this…
Why are you apologizing?
I'm having fun.
Say, Ichinose… What about you?
Ichinose!
I'm very sorry.
Ichinose's been acting strange
ever since he got here…
I think something's really
bothering him.
That's the same for you, too.
Since coming here,
you've been a little…
Yes, you look like
you're in high spirits.
High spirits, huh?
That's right.
I am in high spirits…
This is so much fun…
I feel as if this is the first time
I've been free…
Like I've been cramped up
all this time.
Kariya…
I'm going out.
Master Kariya!
It seems someone amusing
is coming.
Then I'm going, too…
You unify the thugs!
I'm…going to greet this guy myself!
Ganju's coming through!
Hold on…Ganju!
Umm… hold on!
What?
What is it?
It's difficult for me to say this,
but have we lost…the path?
Brother…
Is that delicious?
Well, oh, yeah!
Tell me if you want more!
Ooh…I want to be a part
of this family!
How is it, Lirin?
No response…
They're not here either…
Hmm…
Well! That’s-that!
Let's just say that this-is-this
and that's-that!
Hey, are you just going
to leave them?
I don't care! Don't ask me!
What about you?
He was…suspicious,
but he intimidates me
in a strange way.
Are you fawning over him?
I'm not! I feel we should just
think things over a little…
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
I have something
I want to ask you.
What did you say?!
We're from Kusajishi!
I see… Then that makes it easier…
What?
A-Are you all right?
Don't underestimate me…
I, Ganju Shiba,
am the previously self-proclaimed
“Deep-Red Bullet of
West Rukon District”…
And the currently self-proclaimed
“Karakura Town's Fastest Cashier,
Flash Numeric Keypad!”
– So they're all still self-proclamations…
Let's go, Bonnie!
So you're…Jin Kariya…
Yeah…
It seems like you're just doing
whatever you like…
Rukia Kuchiki…
It seems that the Soul Reaper
that Yoshi cut was your younger sister…
Are you here to avenge her?
It doesn't matter.
I just have to kill
Soul Society's enemies,
no matter who they are…
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather
trust and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won’t get started if you don’t act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Yes, yes, yes! The fight of
the century is about to begin!
Byakuya Kuchiki versus Jin Kariya!
We still have good seats!
We have snacks, lunches,
and cold drinks ready!
We're also selling special goods!
How about a Byakuya towel or
a Senbonzakura key chain?!
Don't make a business out of this!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Your sister sure is scary…
Yeah… Just once, I’d like to
make her say “uncle”!
In that case…
There!
Ganju…
Today, I'll do whatever you
want me to do!
Huh?!
KURODO
Come on.
Clear up your pent-up anger!
I see… Then…
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid Big Sis!
What did you say?!
Uncle--!
Kanbe--!