Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
I don't have any sense...
of being in school right now.
And I can't feel the fact that I was beaten
by those guys from Soul Society...
almost killed by them.
Or the fact that she's
not here right now...
Or the fact that not one of
my classmates remembers Rukia.
Bohahaha...
Say, are you still into that?
So what? The time's ripe for me.
Orihime, have you made plans
for summer vacation?
Not yet.
Orihime, then come and
stay at my place.
My parents will be going abroad.
No way!
Why not?
I know exactly what you're up to!
– Is this what it means...
– I'm not even thinking
– to go back to the Soul Society?
– about bathing together or anything!
What are you blabbering about?!
You disappear from this world
and from people's memories...
Every evidence of her existence
disappears...
into white.
Now then...
That's about it for reminders.
All right, students,
don't die before September!
Class dismissed!
Yes!
That Ishida cut class, after all.
I thought he might still remember Rukia.
Ichigo!
Turn! Turn! Turn! Turn!
Now then, where's the watermelon?
No! That's not it!
That’s right!
Summer means the sea!
And the sea means summer!
And so, I, Keigo Asano,
am planning
a 10-day trip to the seaside
from tomorrow!
Fireworks, scary outings,
and even a co-ed outdoors bath!
Lots and lots of things to do,
both fun and embarrassing!
Sorry, I have plans, so I’ll pass.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm not too keen on the ocean.
I've got an inter-high tournament,
so I can't go.
If Orihime and Tatsuki aren't going,
then I guess I won't...
I can't go this time, either.
I'm sorry,
I'm leaving for Hawaii tomorrow.
What?! With that older girlfriend?!
Actually, with her and
her nine other friends,
so that makes 11 of us
including myself.
What?!
What did you say?!
Don't tell me it's you
and ten other girls?!
Why does he always pick on me?!
Strange...nothing feels out of place.
Even with Rukia gone,
our world continues to turn...
I guess... Rukia was originally
from the other world.
There was really no place
for her here.
Then what'll I do?
Inoue...
What is it?
Something wrong?
Where did Rukia go?
Why has everyone suddenly
forgotten about Rukia?
I thought you would know, Ichigo.
Then Rukia returned to
the world she came from?
Yeah...
But what a shock.
That you were able to see through us.
Since when?
Ever since the incident
with my brother.
Huh?
I see...
Yes...
I'm really grateful about that time.
You guided my brother...
I'm sure he's happy
on the other side. I can feel it.
Really?
Yes.
I wonder if Rukia is doing well
on the other side, too.
She probably has family
and friends, right?
I have to bring her back.
Huh? But...if she's happy there...
She's in a predicament where
she could be killed any time.
Well then, you'll probably say this:
Who cares if she has family
or friends over there?
As long as she's alive,
they'll be able to meet again.
If she's dead, it's all over.
You already know what
you want to do, right?
She was really here.
And her place is here.
Thank you, Inoue!
Chad...
Kurosaki Clinic
How boring! It's summer vacation
and Ichigo goes off without us!
Yuzu, it’s about time you--
All right! How about sleeping
in Dad's bed tonight?
Quit your jokes!
And just talk in your dreams!
Oh, just thinking about that
makes me feel uneasy.
Gee...those words really hurt me.
Good morning, Lieutenant Abarai.
Mornin’!
Wait! Wait!
If you fly away,
I'll get in trouble!
I guess I have no choice...
Hi! I'm Jennifer. I'm a blood type A,
Pisces. E-cup bra size and--
What are you doing?!
Renji! Aren't you off duty today?
I'm here to check on the prisoner.
Is she still sulking?
I’m not sulking.
Then, why don't you eat?
I'm just not hungry,
“Mr. Lieutenant.”
What?! You got a problem that
I'm the Lieutenant?!
Not really.
Way to go, Mr. Lieutenant!
You are so strong, Mr. Lieutenant!
Your eyebrows look so weird,
Mr. Lieutenant!
Why you--! I'll kill you!
Come out of there, you!
Say Renji...
Huh?
Am I really going to die?
Of course! It'll be immediate execution
for someone like you!
I see.
I guess so.
Huh?
Stupid! I was just joking.
Just a joke.
Which is it, idiot?
Who's the idiot here?
Making us worry with your antics.
Captain Kuchiki is probably asking
for clemency right now.
I wonder...
Fool! He's your older brother!
As if he'd let his sister die.
No...
He would kill me.
Huh?
I know full well...
what kind of man he is.
Forty years after being taken in
by the Kuchiki family...
he has never once looked at me.
URAHARA STORE
CLOSED TODAY
Huh?!
What is this?!
Imagine! A huge cavern
beneath the shop!
Pipe down! You don't have to yell.
I'm pretty damn surprised.
Then that's fine.
Let's get started with this
"lesson" or whatever.
All right, as you wish.
Dammit! What's the big idea?!
Hard to breathe, huh?
When you're in the form of a soul.
Right now, your Soul Sleep, which is
the wellspring of your spiritual energy,
and the Soul Chain, the booster,
have been destroyed.
In other words,
your soul is like that of the average person
who has no spiritual power.
So first, we must restore
the spiritual power you have lost.
Then what do I do?!
Well, rather than explain it,
why don't we just do it?
Hey, are you ready?
Nice to see you.
Lesson one! Please fight her.
Huh?
The rules are simple.
Lesson One will be over once
either one of you are rendered immobile.
Please knock her out.
Are you kidding?! You expect me
to hit a little girl like her?
I think it'll be quite difficult.
Please put those on properly.
Otherwise, you'll die.
This is so silly! No way!
See? Don't say I didn't warn you.
He isn't coming out.
Did he die?
I wonder.
Oh, there he is.
Oh, he's going after her!
Oops, he ran right past her.
Cripes! What was that?!
If I get hit with that, I’m dead!
Hey! How do I put this on?!
Ichigo, your forehead!
Your forehead!
Huh? Like this?
And then, you holler
as loud as you can:
Take this! Power of justice!
Armor of justice!
Justice headband! In place!
Okay, got it!
Awright!
As if I can do that!
See? No time to feel embarrassed.
Take this! Power of justice!
Armor of justice!
Justice headband! In place!
Well, well, he actually did it.
Why you--!
Behind you! Behind you!
Aw man...!
Awright, come at me!
Dammit! This thing isn't any good!
Unless I run around like this,
I'll be killed!
Wait a minute!
If I can run around,
it means I'm keeping up
with her speed.
Then...!
Come!
Oh?
Hmm...
I can do it...
I won't aim for her face.
Just a little blow to her headgear.
Then, because of the difference
in size, I can...
Dammit! I got her face!
Safe!
One more time, please.
Congratulations!
Huh?
Lesson One is cleared!
Huh? Why? I lost to her, didn't I?
Oh, I didn't say a thing about
downing Ururu to clear Lesson One.
But...
After all, she has the fighting skills
to counter Soul Reapers.
No way can a human soul beat her.
By the way, are you still
having trouble breathing?
Huh? Now that you mention it...
Which means, the restoration
of your spiritual energy was successful.
This lesson was for one-shot battles.
Whether you could dodge
the first attack or not.
Spiritual energy increases fastest when
the soul is in danger of being destroyed.
If you can raise your spiritual
energy sufficiently,
then you can dodge the punch
and it’s all good!
And if I can't...
You'll die.
Why didn't you say so first?!
I had faith in you...
that you would succeed.
Now then, your spiritual energy
is back.
So...let's celebrate and...
Huh?!
Go straight into Lesson Two!
Lesson?
Are you interested in taking it?
B-But, so out of the blue like that...
Rather, the problem is...
The cat.
What do you mean?
Hmm...
Ichigo has begun preparations
to enter the Soul Society.
If you also want to use the powers
that have awakened inside you,
then take my lessons.
You can decide whether
you're really going or not after that.
I'm going.
Chad...
I... um...
I won't force you.
Oh! There! There!
Uryu! Hello!
Huh? Orihime! Chad!
What are you doing here?
We asked Yoruichi to follow
your spiritual aura.
Yoruichi?
What are you doing? Camping?
No!
You're training, huh?
Who's there?!
Where are you looking?
Over here.
I'm Yoruichi.
Huh?! A cat?! A cat is--?!
So? What's the big deal just
because a cat can talk?
Don't be such a wimp.
Yes, Uryu. It's no big deal.
No... I don't think it's strange if
one is mildly traumatized by it.
Men have such
a hard time adapting to things.
I'm sorry. But what did
you want with me?
Actually...
Ichigo is going to the Soul Society?
Ichigo is going to rescue Rukia.
So I thought we should tell you, too...
Unfortunately, it's got nothing
to do with me.
Rukia's life is in danger!
I'm a Quincy and I can't forgive myself
for losing to a Soul Reaper.
That's why I train.
Rukia is not my concern.
I see... You're doing your best
in your own way, huh?
I'll think it over carefully again.
It's certain that
I'm undergoing changes...
I'm afraid, but I want to
know what it is.
See you, Uryu.
Sorry Orihime...
But I can't let anyone
see this training.
Please watch over me, Sensei...
I'm gonna die!
Precisely. Once the Chain of Fate
is broken,
you can no longer return
to your physical body.
You’ll just die.
Quit talking like it doesn't matter!
Then, let me tell you
something that does.
The chain will begin the Encroachment
at the point of severance.
And when it reaches your chest,
you will become a Hollow...
and it will be the end.
What?!
If you don't want to become a Hollow,
you must become a Soul Reaper!
Huh?!
Once you clear Lesson Two,
you will regain the powers of
a Soul Reaper!
Which you choose is your decision.
Hah! You don’t have to ask me that!
Okay! Then let's do it.
Go!
Are you shocked?
By my ruse?
Hey hey...
It's awfully deep.
I did my best.
Owwee!
Wha--!
What are these?!
Binding Spell 99 –
Restrict!
It was bold of me,
but until this lesson is over,
your arms shall be sealed.
Dammit! Why you--!
Ichigo!
Climb back up here
in that condition.
That is the lesson...
otherwise called Shattered Shaft.
Idiot! As if I can do such a thing?!
I don't think you have time to
wonder whether you can or not.
At the bottom of the Shattered Shaft,
you have 72 hours, or three days,
before the chain is
completely Encroached.
You must come back up here
as a Soul Reaper before the time is up.
Otherwise,
we'll have to kill you.
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
Jinta! Ururu!
How quickly do you think Ichigo
can come back as a Soul Reaper?
I say five hours!
About 12 hours...
Well, I'll wager a thousand points
on him not returning...
Hold it, you!