Ichigo’s battle ended
with a victory over Grimmjow
and the rescue of Orihime.
The fight against
the Arrancars continues,
but that is a story
to be told later.
From here on,
a totally new story unfolds.
Now the curtain rises
on a currently unknown battle.
Did you hear, Captain?
Squad 3 is getting a new captain!
I’m a captain.
I’ve already been told.
The official announcement is to be made
at tomorrow’s squad leaders’ meeting.
That Kira…
When did he learn
to do a Bankai anyway?
Kira is not the new captain.
What?!
He’s not?!
Don’t scatter the documents!
I don’t know the details
about the new captain.
Is that right?
Well, I didn’t think Kira was
suited to be captain anyway.
I wonder who it’s going to be then.
We’ll find out tomorrow.
Never mind that, get back to work!
I’m so curious.
Yesterday our Expedition Unit returned
after completing a long-term assignment.
Without suffering a single casualty,
I may add.
That is a great achievement.
At the present time, Squads 3, 5, and 9
are without captains.
As the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
we cannot allow this situation
to remain unresolved.
Therefore… Yesterday the man in charge
of the Expedition Unit was summoned.
Under the attendance of I, Yamamoto,
and two other captains,
we deliberated over his capabilities
as a squad captain.
Our decision was unanimous.
Hence, I shall now introduce you all
to the new captain
who will be replacing
former Captain Gin Ichimaru.
The new Squad 3 Captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
Shusuke Amagai, enter!
Shusuke Amagai…
Ever heard of him?
Nope.
A new face we’ve never even heard of
is gonna be our captain.
I hear he’s been away on
a long expedition to suppress Hollows.
Who cares about that?
The point is that a total stranger
will suddenly be our captain.
Can we follow such a guy?
I know,
but Lieutenant Kira’s no better.
Yeah.
‘Morning.
I hope the new captain is nice.
You’re right.
We can’t depend on him.
He wields…
two Zanpakuto?
A solid presence.
I’m Amagai.
I’ll do my very best.
I lack experience,
so I ask for your guidance.
When you’re a captain,
there’s a lot of protocol and it
may be hard to get used to at first.
Just come to me if
you have any questions.
Yes sir! Thank you very much.
Who were the two captains
who sat in on the deliberations?
Does it even matter?
One empty post has been filled now.
We should be glad.
Well, you’re right about that.
In time, we’ll see just
how good Shusuke Amagai is.
Finally, one position
has been filled.
That means nothing.
There are still two more to fill.
At any time, or any place,
a void causes discord.
One who is evil tries to
display its power
by targeting the most vulnerable spot,
by targeting such a void.
Is he…the new captain?
Let’s see…
Who’s the Lieutenant?
I’m Squad 3 Lieutenant, Izuru Kira.
I’m Shusuke Amagai.
I’m the newly appointed
Squad 3 Captain.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
A pleasure to meet you.
And he is Makoto Kibune.
Like myself, he’ll be joining
Squad 3 starting today.
He belonged to one of
my Expedition Units.
But he’s skilled,
so I recruited him.
He’ll be the Third Seat.
I’m Kibune.
Pleased to meet you.
So that’s him?
He’s wearing the captain’s coat.
He’s the one, all right.
Well…
Compared to the other captains
he’s kind of…
What’s the matter?
Well…
You see, Squad 3 was fine without
a captain until yesterday.
Stop!
Well, I know how you all feel.
After all, someone you don’t even know
suddenly shows up and tells you,
“Hey, I’ll be your captain
starting today.”
I don’t blame you
for feeling put off.
But, I will say this much.
As long as I’m your captain,
I will protect you.
That is a captain’s duty.
But you don’t even know
how good this captain is, right?
Well, you’re right, but…
As far as the squad is concerned,
there’s a huge feeling of uncertainty
towards the captain.
And the thought of having to pull them
all together tomorrow is…
I’m not sure.
Jeez, what’s the big deal?
It’s just a case of them teaching
the cocky new transfer student a lesson.
I know. But I’m the one
who’ll be caught in between.
Okay, okay. You’re nervous
about the whole thing.
Well then…
Here. Good ol’ sake.
Drink away your worries.
I can’t drink in broad daylight.
Silly…
That’s why it tastes so good!
Oh, yeah. Why not have a party
with all the Squad 3 members?
A few drinks and you’ll
all be buddies in no time.
Is that how it works?
Just take my word for it and try.
I see.
So that’s where you
hide your sake bottles, eh?!
Captain…
This is… I mean…Kira was…
Matsumoto!
This is…
It’s a welcome party for you
and Third Seat Kibune, sir.
Huh? For us?
Well, thank you everyone.
I received some advice that
this will help solidify our bond.
Please, sir.
Let me pour for you.
Huh? Oh, I…
Is something the matter?
Sure.
– So much…
– Huh?
Oh, nothing.
All right! Okay, everyone!
Let’s begin the welcome party for
Captain Amagai and Third Seat Kibune.
This is bad. I’ve never been
to a party this depressing.
It’s having
the opposite effect.
Now, a toast from Captain Amagai!
Sir, take a shot of sake.
O-Okay. Everyone,
I’m counting on you all!
Captain, I see you’re
one who can drink!
Not really.
A-Are you all right?
Jeez…
Throwing a party like this for me.
I’m so happy.
Yup. I feel great.
Captain? What’s wrong?
Captain Amagai!
What happened?
– What’s going on?
– Is he…
Captain! Captain!
Actually, the captain has
zero tolerance for alcohol.
Huh? He just had one shot.
He gets drunk on pickles
made from sake yeast.
Then why didn’t he just refuse?
Well… I think he read the mood
and felt he shouldn’t refuse.
Someone! Get me a pail
of water and a towel.
Yes sir!
What’ll we do, Lieutenant?
I guess we can’t continue the party
with Captain Amagai in this condition.
Shall we wrap it up?
Now, now…
Since you set up
this opportunity for us,
why don’t we talk a bit more
and get to know one another?
I’d like to learn all of your names
and faces as much as I can.
I hear Squad 3 is having a party.
Yes, in broad daylight.
It’s a welcome party
for Captain Amagai.
How nice.
What’s nice?
Sake tastes best when you start
drinking during the day, Nanao.
‘Cuz you can get really plastered.
I wonder if this Captain Amagai
is a drinker.
I wouldn’t know.
I wonder if we can
become friends.
Who knows?
You’re no fun, Nanao.
Thank you.
What’ll we do?
Ignore him.
After all, we’ve managed until now
with just Lieutenant Kira.
Who needs a captain like that?
That’s true.
I was a fool for taking
Matsumoto’s advice.
Lieutenant Kira.
Third Seat Kibune.
The solidarity of Squad 3
is very strong.
You think so?
I understand you’ve
kept the squad together
in the absence of a captain.
I’m very impressed.
It was nothing.
A directive for Squad 3 of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
This is an emergency!
Menos have appeared in
the Precipice World in Area 0035!
Presently, they are headed
towards Soul Society!
There are 13 of them!
Thirteen?!
That many Menos in
the Precipice World?!
That’s impossible.
I am ordering
Squad 3 of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads
to defeat the Menos who have
infiltrated the Precipice World!
Make preparations immediately
and go to the Precipice World!
Well?
What should we do?
I don’t know.
Lieutenant! We must go!
But…
It can’t be helped!
I will request that the Restrictive Current
be quarantined!
You must take command!
All right.
We will now enter the Precipice World
to destroy the Menos!
It seems Squad 3 will be going.
Perhaps the Seireitei is
on the verge of change.
What?
A man who distinguished himself
in an expedition assignment
is suddenly named as captain.
That never happened before.
I know, but…
Who were the two captains
who participated in
Shusuke Amagai’s appointment?
I don’t know.
But I do know this much…
Something new is beginning.
We will split into small groups of four
and confront the enemy.
Our enemies are Menos!
Take every precaution!
Enter!
They’re coming!
Each group spread out!
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Out of thirteen Menos,
five have been destroyed!
Eight remain.
Everyone, just a few more!
Hang in there!
Yes sir!
What’s that?
The Restrictive Current is back!
Why?!
It’s supposed to be quarantined!
The Restrictive Current.
That’s impossible!
What’s going on?!
The Restrictive Current Cleaner
has appeared!
Distance to Squad 3…
200 meters!
The cause is unknown!
It can’t be stopped!
Third Seat Kibune!
What’s the meaning of this?!
I don’t know.
I know my request to quarantine
the Restrictive Current was received.
Retreat!
I will cover the rear!
We must hurry!
Thanks, Third Seat Kibune!
Hurry!
We can’t outrun it!
Move!
Captain Amagai!
Stay back!
Are you nuts?
I thought I told you…
As long as I’m your captain,
I will protect you!
Please take a good look at
Captain Amagai’s true power.
Kibune…
You’re sure you requested that
the Restrictive Current be quarantined?
Yes.
I can’t believe the Department
of Research and Development
would miss such a request.
Something is strange about this.
But, whatever.
Anyone hurt?
N-No sir!
Good.
Kira!
Yes sir!
Good work.
Just what I’d expect from someone
who filled in during a captain’s absence.
No… It’s nothing.
I’m glad you’re all okay.
Let’s go back!
He’s an extraordinary guy.
Yeah, he’s amazing.
Captain Amagai!
Are you ok?
He’s…
This man…
He did that while still drunk.
Someone, help me.
R-Right!
Let’s go back. Lieutenant Kira!
R-Right.
Why did you choose
to send out Squad 3?
It was the perfect opportunity
for the newcomer to show his skills.
According to the report,
Squad 3 was in the midst of a party.
Was there a reason you
sent them into battle drunk?
It was an initiation!
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Today, we’ll talk about
Ichigo Kurosaki’s Hollowfication.
When Ichigo Kurosaki hollowfies,
the frightening Spiritual Pressure
is like an Espada’s.
Why am I in this corner?!
Why? You’re more like
an Arrancar than a Soul Reaper.
Not!
By the way, is it true that
Squad 3 has a new captain?
Yup, seems like it.
Oh, it’s him.
I see. Well, it’ll be tough.
Huh? You know him?!
As if!
Hang in there, Izuru.