Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Do not get involved any further.
Brother!
Hey, hey, aren't you
going to finish him off?
Looks like you were having fun.
Why're you all here?
Is that any way to greet us?
Muramasa said to lend you two
a hand, so we all came.
Beat those Soul Reapers
to death already!
Get away, Rukia!
I'll hold them off here!
In your condition?
Don't be ridiculous!
Just get away!
Stop prattling!
Your lives will end here!
What is this?!
Don't move!
Hold it right there!
Yo!
Who did you say you were
gonna beat to death?
Damn you!
Rukia, are you all right?!
Byakuya…
Seems we're
completely surrounded.
Well, anyone would notice,
the way we were making
such a huge commotion
in the middle of the night.
Byakuya Kuchiki and Zanpakuto,
we are taking you into custody.
What?
So many of us here and you
aren't going to fight us?
What was that?!
If that is your wish, we'll oblige.
We're ready to go anytime.
Don't fall for their cheap taunts.
We'll start by surrounding everyone
so they cannot escape from here.
We can break them down
individually afterwards.
You make it so complicated.
If we're going to do this,
let's get started!
We won't run or hide!
He's so right.
Hold your ground!
Don't let them get outside
the boundaries of
the Squad 6 barracks!
Those who don't want to live,
come at me first!
I'll cut you all down
with my blade!
What?!
Sorry…
I won't allow you to
run wild any further.
You!
Yo. Today there's
no one to interfere.
Let's take our time and finish
where we left off the other day!
You want to settle the score, eh?
I won't hold back, partner!
I wouldn't want it any other way!
You're not getting away!
Thank you, Tenken.
Two-on-one? Fine.
It's been a long time.
How've you been?
Not bad. You're looking well.
Thanks to you.
I was able to get away from
the cause of my stress…
Huh? I haven't identified myself.
How'd you know it was me?
Oh, I knew right away.
After all, just looking
at you disgusts me…
Fujikujaku.
Would you mind not calling me
by that name?
I find it objectionable.
My name is Ruriirokujaku.
If you keep calling me by
that other name, I'll kill you.
Give it your best shot.
Rukia! Renji!
I'm fine. But Renji…
It's not that bad.
Stand back.
I'll bring these guys
to their senses.
Leave him to me.
You return to Muramasa.
All right.
Byakuya!
Move!
You're not getting past!
What's the meaning of this?
Captain, we haven't
finished talking.
You still don't understand
that it's useless?
I will risk my life to stop you!
Wait, Renji!
We don't want you to think
that this is all we've got.
Right. We still haven't
gotten serious yet…
Thanks, you two…
Scatter…
I won't let you!
Shikai doesn't work…
In that case…
Bankai!
Getsugatensho!
You look good
holding your sword.
Huh?
And that feather on your face…
although it's probably faux,
it looks good on you.
I hadn't had much opportunity
to take a good look at you,
but I love your style.
W-What're you talking
about out of the blue?!
Now if you'd just coordinate
yourself with genuine items,
you'd look much better.
But overdoing it would make
you look trashy, instead…
What're you trying to say?
I know! Shall I give you
one of my feathers?
These are real.
Forget it. I don't want
those ugly things.
Also, it might be nice to
add a few extra touches
to your Shihakusho!
Yes, that would be marvelous!
Hey!
But to accent your
lovely complexion…
Cut it out!
You're mocking me, aren't you?!
Heavens no.
Your face disgusts me.
You are the worst, after all.
Anyway, whatever your attitude is,
it doesn't matter to me.
You do know why I took the trouble
of choosing a location to fight
that's away from
everyone else, right?
Because you don't want everyone
to see my powers, right?
Exactly.
You might regret
having been so confident.
I won't regret it.
That's how I fight, Fujikujaku.
I told you, if you keep
calling me by that name,
I'm going to kill you.
Where are you looking?
Just what I'd expect of
the commander of the Stealth Force.
What's the matter?
It's been bothering me
for a while now…
But whose Zanpakuto are you?
I'm Gonryomaru!
Gonryomaru?
Gonryomaru, Zanpakuto of Squad 1
lieutenant, Chojiro Sasakibe!
Oh! So you're his sword!
You're so plain, I couldn't tell.
Curse you! You mock me!
Tenken…
Do not console me.
This is all happening because
Chojiro Sakakibe is always
pushed into the background…
So that's it?
Is that why you
betrayed your master?
Shut up!
It's a stupid reason.
Not that it matters.
I'll render you motionless
in a moment.
You can say what you want
before your master!
I won't make it so simple for you!
What is this?
What's the matter with you?!
For someone who talks big,
all you're doing is
running away, coward!
Coward? Are you talking to me?
Damn right.
Last time, too, you couldn't win,
so you quickly ran away.
That makes you a true coward!
A fight is waged according
to the situation.
I don't consider
running away cowardice.
Forcing the fight and losing—
that's a foolish act.
You sure talk a lot of
lame nonsense…
Oh well…
Today I'll slice you to bits
before you can run away.
Are you really
Hisagi's Zanpakuto?
What?
It would seem Hisagi has been
suppressing his internal negativity
without realizing it.
You're a manifestation
of his stress—
his destructive impulses—
aren't you?
What?! Hey!
Are you saying I'm stress?
Am I wrong?
Quit messing with me!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Now then, Hisagi's always
helped me out, so…
Sorry, but I'm taking his revenge.
Damn you…
I'm not done yet!
Extend!
Hozukimaru!
Oh… You've regained
your Shikai, partner?
Yeah!
What's wrong?
Is that all you've got?
You're weaker than
you were last time.
That's bull!
I just haven't gotten serious yet.
I see…
I do remember you
being a slow starter.
Okay, then…
I'll wake you up right now!
What? Done already?
Bankai…
Don't push your luck, partner.
You've finally gotten serious…
The real fight starts now!
Over here!
Damn!
I've still got more!
What? Done already?
Stupid…
It's not over yet!
Your spirit is impressive…
But you'll need more than that
to win the fight.
You've always had
this silly stubbornness,
but you always got crushed
in head-to-head battles.
What?!
I'm saying you should improve your
skills before you go talking big.
Why you!
I just warned you,
and look how you held up.
Are you really stupid?
You're the stupid one.
What?
When did you…
I know what you're trying to say…
Even so, I'll do things my way.
I'll do things my way
and get ahead!
What's a man if he can't
do things his way?!
Well said, partner!
Then use your strength
to hold me down!
You don't have to tell me!
You're good…
Just what I expected
from my Zanpakuto.
You, too.
Thanks to you, I've awakened.
What're you doing?
This is the end.
I won't back away from this line.
Hozukimaru, I will take
all of your force
and send it right back at you!
A bright red Ryumon attack
is harsh.
Perfect.
Come at me, Hozukimaru!
I am Third Seat in
Zaraki Squad…
I'm Ikkaku Madarame!
Pretty good…
Damn right.
Serves you right…
Lieutenant Iba!
Oh, Lieutenant Kotetsu.
What's the situation?
Captain Soi Fon
and the others are
engaged in a battle at
the Squad 6 barracks.
I'm told Stealth Force
has the enemy surrounded
and is preventing them
from moving.
I see.
Then we should join
them there, as well.
Yes…
It seems there are
many wounded.
What is it?
What happened?
There!
It can't be!
After Hisagi, Omaeda,
Matsumoto, Hinamori…
Now it's my turn.
Come at me, my Zanpakuto!
Iba, what was your
Zanpakuto's name again?
Come at me, my Zanpakuto!
What was its name?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
You know, your friend should
coordinate his Shihakusho too,
don't you think?
Huh?
He has highlights on his eyes,
so his kimono should
match his eyes.
If he considers bald to be stylish,
then he should accent that
with a ribbon.
And also, you and he should wear
matching feather accessories.
Yes! I think that's great!
How about a flower print
on our kimono?
Nice!
Huh?