Trouble arises over
succession rights
in one of Soul Society’s high-ranking
aristocratic families, the Kasumiohji Clan.
Their princess, Rurichiyo Kasumiohji,
traveled to the World of the Living.
Ichigo reluctantly agrees to
become her bodyguard.
Rurichiyo, who is unaware that
her life is being targeted,
turns Ichigo’s life upside down
with her naive behavior.
Elsewhere in the Soul Society,
Shusuke Amagai has become
the new captain of Squad 3
and works hard to take on
his new responsibilities.
He went over there!
Get him!
We lost him! Which way?!
This way!
Hurry! Don’t lose him!
Stay still.
I got you.
Third Seat Kibune.
Good job!
You’re putting too much effort
into this, Lieutenant Kira.
Lieutenant, please confirm.
Oh, okay.
MISSING CAT: MALE -AGE 3
No mistake, this is the cat.
Mission complete then.
Why are we chasing after missing cats
for the aristocrats, anyway?
Yesterday, it was security guards
for a clothing store sale.
Recently, it’s been nothing
but this kind of work.
I’m sure our captain
has his reasons.
What do you think, Lieutenant Kira?
Huh?
Well, that’s… I wonder.
I prefer work that I can
be more enthusiastic about.
Now, now…
That aside,
how about we go for a drink?
Sounds good.
Let’s go.
How about you, Lieutenant Kira?
I have to write up our report.
Excuse me.
You’re back, Izuru.
What’s wrong?
No it’s…
I was a bit startled by
being called by my first name.
I thought it would help me
fit in with the squad more
by calling everyone
by their first name.
Don’t like it?
Uh…well…
It takes some getting used to.
Oh, I see.
I thought it was a good idea.
Guess I’ll think of something else.
Here is today’s report.
Oh.
And…
About tomorrow’s schedule…
What’s this about doing wall repairs
for the Squad 12 barracks?
Wall repair is just that,
repairing a wall.
That’s not what I’m trying to say.
Why do we have to do that?
The others in the squad are also…
Kira, you may not like
hearing this, but…
Squad 3 is the one
whose previous captain,
Gin Ichimaru, betrayed us.
You understand, don’t you?
Once you lose trust,
it’s difficult to gain it back.
I don’t know how things will play out,
but it’s better to do this than not.
Relax, Kira.
Seeing you makes me think that
the previous captain, Gin Ichimaru,
played too big of a role
in this squad.
Huh?
You’re different from Ichimaru.
No one expects the same from you.
Having a charismatic captain is
one way to bring together a team.
But it can easily break down
once that pillar of support is gone.
That’s why I want to re-build a new squad
together with you and Kibune,
with the three of us acting as
the pillar of support for this squad.
So, what happened
to Third Seat Kibune?
Well…
IZAKAYA KAMEGAMEYA
He’s drinking with the others.
After the fight the other day,
Inose and the others seemed to have
warmed up to Third Seat Kibune.
I see.
Then I think I’ll call it a day too.
If something’s bothering you,
go take a break and have some fun!
Huh? Um…
See you later.
Have a nice evening, sir.
Today, you’ll be trained in
a new fighting method.
Recently, there’s been an increase
in strong enemies like the Menos.
Such as that Precipice World incident
from the other day.
From now on, you must practice
working together with
your fellow squad members in battle,
or else you’ll die.
Anyway, this training is to
make sure that doesn’t happen.
Kibune…
Sir!
Pick one of these colored headbands.
I’m going to say a color
and those wearing that color
will be the enemy.
The rest of you take on
the enemies in groups of three.
But, the enemy color
will change periodically.
The moment I say another color,
the roles will reverse.
This is to help you develop
your decision-making reflexes.
Kibune, you get in the group
and lead this exercise.
Sir!
I will join too.
That’s okay, Kira.
Huh?
I devised this battle method back
when I was with the Expedition Unit.
I want Kibune, who’s familiar with
the operation, to lead this training.
Yes, sir.
Sorry.
Let’s go!
– Yes, sir!
First, purple!
Uh…
Aida, come with me!
Yes, sir!
Inose! Join me in back!
Sir!
Next, yellow!
Next, red!
Good! Keep it up!
Amazing…
Since when did everyone
become so organized?
Captain Amagai’s
fighting methods
are different from anything
we’ve done before!
Captain Ichimaru never used
group fighting methods.
It actually felt like we could put up
a good fight by working together!
Yeah!
I really like Captain Amagai’s style!
And Third Seat Kibune too!
That guy seems more reliable
than Lieutenant Kira!
Soon there might be
a change in Lieutenants.
Idiot, you’re going too far!
Oops…
Lieutenant Kira.
Huh?
Oh, Third Seat Kibune.
You’re okay…
with what they said just now?
Well…uh…
Is that so?
I must say, Third Seat Kibune,
you’re amazing.
Not at all.
I can’t compare to how you,
Lieutenant Kira,
have organized
Squad 3 until now.
That’s not true.
Everyone seems to
have accepted you.
More than me.
But…
It’s fine!
Don’t bother with me!
Oh, sorry. I’m a little tired.
If you’ll excuse me.
One more!
You’re a strong drinker, Kira!
Okay, you can have
some of my drink!
You sure can drink.
Say…
Did something happen?
It’s okay!
Squad 3 is going to
change from now on!
It’ll be different than
the Squad 3 before.
Okay, okay!
When the captain changes,
the atmosphere of
the whole squad changes.
I can understand your confusion.
Thanks to Captain Amagai,
Squad 3’s reputation has improved.
He’s done good
in such a short time.
I…think so to.
Then be proud!
If you act like this,
how can I put it…
that new Third Seat guy
in Squad 3…
Third Seat Kibune.
Yeah!
He could take away
your title as Lieutenant!
Huh?!
That’s right,
I’m unreliable anyway.
Iba!
Huh? Uh… Yeah…
Uh oh,
I think we touched a nerve.
Welcome!
Party of two, this way!
– Welcome!
Do you have a private room?
Yes, we do!
Speak of the devil.
Why’s he with Captain Kyoraku?
So, cheers.
I’m happy to have
been invited for a drink
with the new squad captain
everyone’s talking about.
I’m still new to this role,
so getting to know the senior members
is also part of my job.
So, what is it you wanted
to talk with me about?
I’ll be straight with you.
Sounds good.
I don’t like beating around the bush.
About the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads…
Would it be possible for the squads
to work more closely together?
That’s…a difficult subject.
I don’t expect to be able to
do so right away, but at this rate…
Now, don’t get so excited.
Oh… I’m sorry.
But, I like your thinking.
It’s not bad.
You understand!
Amagai, you’re young
but you’re pretty thoughtful.
Oh no! Not at all.
I know!
If we’re talking about these things,
maybe we should talk with Ukitake too.
You mean the captain of Squad13?
Yeah. This doesn’t mean
I won’t cooperate.
I just don’t like taking the lead.
So, next time,
let’s call on Ukitake and talk.
What do you think?
By all means!
Okay! Let’s start again
with a toast!
Huh? You’re not drinking?
No…I…uh…
Come on.
Thank you!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don’t tell me…you can’t drink?!
Really?
Lieutenant Kira, East Area 7,
no unusual activity.
Good job, Third Seat Kibune.
All’s quiet in the inner court.
Is that so?
That’s good to know.
Is something wrong?
Uh, no… It’s nothing.
Oh, yes!
How about some tea?
Lieutenant Kira.
What is it?
Sorry for being
so rude in asking but,
why do you always
seem so unconfident?
Huh?
Well…
Uh…
Urgent message?!
There’s a suspicious shadow
near the execution grounds.
Lieutenant!
Lieutenant! Third Seat!
Uh… You are…
Shinta Seko.
Sorry, I couldn’t
remember your name.
That’s okay.
I’m still new and
don’t have a seat ranking yet.
Where did it happen?
Near this hole.
I saw the suspicious shadow earlier,
and tried to go after it.
What happened?
Well…
It seems to have disappeared
inside this hole.
Inside the execution grounds?!
Nothing would survive
this fall, right?
At this rate…
Lieutenant!
Third Seat Kibune…
Are you all right?
I’ll be fine.
I see.
But why did
the ground suddenly…
It’s impossible to climb up.
There should be
an entrance somewhere
that brings in
the criminals here.
Let’s look for it.
Yes.
This Spiritual Pressure…
This is…
Why in a place like this?
So many…
But if it’s only this level of Hollow…
Stop it!
Rampage…
Reppu!
Third Seat Kibune…
This is bad!
If the Hollows get outside…
What is he doing?
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
What are you doing,
Third Seat Kibune?!
Just putting and
end to the Hollows.
But, what about Seko?
That fool has failed to carry out
his duties as a Soul Reaper.
Falling into enemy hands,
and now lying before us in disgrace.
What?
As one who has taken up
the role of a Soul Reaper,
he should be prepared
to die in battle.
By becoming a burden,
this scum has endangered us all.
He doesn’t deserve to live.
How could you say such a thing?
Why do you attempt
to save that scum?
You’re too soft!
What?!
It’s that attitude of yours
that made you fail to prevent
the former captain’s rebellion beforehand.
Isn’t that right?!
That’s…
I…
It appears you lack
the will as well.
Hey!
Are you guys all right?
Captain Amagai…
Captain! A member was attacked
by Hollows and is heavily injured!
Wait there!
I’ll have the med crew
get down there!
Please!
Captain, what about the Hollows
that fled into the sky?
Yeah, some squad members nearby
saw it and informed me.
We took care of it.
Is that so? Sorry.
We’ve transported Seko
to the Squad 4 facility.
However, his wounds are deep.
We’re not sure if he’ll survive.
I see…
And about the ground
that collapsed…
There are traces of it being
made to collapse that way.
Was there anything you noticed?
Is something wrong, you two?
Uh… That is…
No, nothing.
What? So strange of you two.
You! What are you going to do
about my test Hollows?!
Were those Hollows
from Squad 12?
Yes…
It seems someone has
unlocked the testing facility
and had freed all the Hollows.
Who would do that?
How should I know?!
Nemu!
You weren’t watching carefully,
and this is what happened!
You fool!
I’m sorry, Master Mayuri.
Damn it,
I’m really upset!
Captain of Squad 3!
You, too!
Why didn’t you try
to keep them alive?!
I can’t do my tests now!
Now, now…
Don’t get angry.
What is it?!
There’s no one here.
A malfunction?
Abarai, why where you
with Iba today?
He forced me come with him
to discuss the future of
the Men's Soul Reaper
Association.
There’s no chance against the Women's
Soul Reaper Association, anyway.
You’re so right.
It’s that kind of attitude
that gets us ridiculed!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Byakuya, what is it that you
wanted to talk to me about?
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Itchy! I found you!
Yachiru,
what are you doing here?
I fixed up Byakki’s house
and made a hidden tunnel.
I’ll show you too!
– Okay, okay! Sorry, Byakuya.
– Hurry up!
How long do you intend to
address me by my first name?