Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
All right, explain to me...
the rules of this battle.
We’ll use this.
Huh? What is that?
It’s bait for Hollows.
If I crush it and scatter it around,
Hollows will come.
What?!
The victor will be whoever kills
the most Hollows that
gather in 24 hours.
Well? Isn’t that easy to understand?
Quit kidding around!
You’d endanger the lives of
the town’s people
just for our battle?!
Just who do you think you are?!
Don’t make such a fuss, braggart.
No need to worry about other people.
I’ll kill every single
Hollow that comes.
If you are confident that
you can protect others from Hollows,
then you should accept
this challenge.
That’s number one.
What kind of face is that,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
Change it back!
Chase away the Hollows!
Soon, the town will be overflowing
with Hollows lured here by the bait.
Let’s just say the die is cast.
Huh?!
Isn’t there something else
you should be doing,
besides grabbing onto me?
That’s if you really want
to protect
as many people as possible
from the Hollows...
Why you--!
Have you forgotten?
Hollows tend to attack those
with high spiritual energy.
Yuzu! Karin!
Dammit!
Hey, wait Ichigo!
He hasn’t noticed, after all...
That there are people
around him
with high spiritual powers
besides his family.
But don’t worry.
I’ll kill every one of them.
And...you’ll realize how
weak your own power is,
here at the point of no return.
I detest Soul Reapers!
It’s true.
You’re the cutest of all, Mika!
Truly?
Can I really believe you, Yoshi?
Of course...
How's about a hug?
Huh? Someone will see us!
Dammit!
Quit making out in broad daylight!
You’re just ghosts!
It’s all right. No one is looking.
Mika!
Yoshi!
Hey! Arisawa! Break’s over!
Arisawa!
Coming!
Tatsuki!
Orihime?
Do you have a moment?
That’s right...that day when
I went to Orihime’s house...
I have almost no recollection
of that day.
Just that I felt so much pain...
and that I thought I saw
someone who looked like Rukia...
At first, I thought I was dreaming.
But when I mentioned it to
Orihime the following day
she had seen the very same dream.
And ever since that day,
I started to see strange things.
Tatsuki...
– I can see you!
– Hey Tatsuki...!
You and I are butt friends!
Aghh! It’s so annoying!
Huh?!
Oh, I’m sorry. What is it?
Umm... it’s not that important, but...
Hey, what’s going on?!
The windows on the first floor
are shattered!
– Anyone hurt?!
– I wonder what happened.
Let’s go, Orihime.
Okay.
Okay! Let's go!
Hey Kurosaki!
Hurry and kick it!
Number three!
Huh?!
She’s probably gone somewhere
to play around this time.
Where could she be?! Dammit!
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
What is it, Urahara?
Huh? Dammit!
A Hollow...
at a time like this!
Sorry Urahara,
we’ll continue this later.
What? The signal is gone.
I get it. Ichigo is doing pretty well.
Gone again?
What’s happening?
It’s not really broken, is it?
Again?
So many Hollows,
at this rate is...
not...possible.
What does this heavy and
agitated Sprit Energy mean?
Just what is happening?!
Move!
Where are you?!
Hurry it up, Chad!
If you keep stalling,
lunch specials will be over!
I’ll make you pay the difference!
Huh? That won’t do.
Damn right that won’t do!
So move it!
What a bad feeling.
I’ve had this feeling before...
Hmm?
Cut it out, will you?!
I’m eking out a living with
what I make from my part-time job!
My life’s as tenuous as a bug’s!
I’m not like you carefree students
who can eat just by being alive!
Sorry.
I risk my life just for
a bowl of rice!
Repeat it!
I-I risk my life just for
a bowl of rice.
All right. If you get it,
let’s go!
Unless it’s on sale,
don’t buy meat!
The expiration date is
just an approximation! Right!
What’s happening?
Was that a gas explosion?
What is that?
Just that area is...
Hey Chad! Are you all right?!
Let’s get out of here!
Shigeo! Harutoki! Run--!
He’s coming after me?
I see. Well then...
Chad! Where are you going?!
I don’t know what that
big thing is,
but if it’s targeting me,
then it’s simple.
I just have to run.
Run to where there’s
no one around.
Run!
Oops, sorry.
Kurosaki! What’s with you anyway?
You space out then kick
the ball just anywhere.
Are you serious about playing?!
Huh?
W-What, y-you wanna fight?
Then bring it on!
We’ll show you...
I’m sorry. I think I’ll go home,
after all.
Huh?
H-Hey! Wait, Kurosaki!
It’s no good today...
I keep thinking about
that weird air
and can’t concentrate on soccer.
I’ll take a bath and go to bed early.
You’re Ichigo’s friend.
The one with the parakeet.
Ichigo’s sister?
What’s a grown up like
you doing here alone--?
W-What is that?!
W-Wha--?!
What is it?!
It stopped moving.
Is it watching our moves? Or...
Damn it!
If I could see him
a bit more clearly...
It’s coming again.
Huh?
What is it?
Just what is that thing?!
Can you...see it?
See?
What are you saying?!
It’s so clearly visible!
You...
Mister, behind you!
Gone? Where’d it go?
Where are you looking, Mister?!
To your right! Run!
Mister, don’t tell me
you can’t see him?!
I can see just a bit of it.
Which means,
you really don’t see him.
It can’t be helped then.
Hold me tight.
I’ll see him for you!
Wha--?! You can’t!
I can! Let me do it!
It’s not the first time
I’ve seen a monster like that.
It’s bothering me...
what do they have to
do with Ichigo?!
Ichigo?
To the left. Dodge!
Right!
Mister!
Are you all right, Mister?
Kurosaki!
What happened?
This guy’s covered in blood!
Did you fight him?
Did you beat him up?
Stupid! Don’t come!
Get away!
What a thing to say!
We’re just worried about you!
You’re always like that!
Leave it to a girl!
I'll say! Let's go!
Don’t tell me you hit
someone again, Yasutora?
What’s the point of
hitting someone?
You hurt those who hurt you,
and what’s left?
Yasutora, you are strong.
You are big.
You are beautiful.
You were born with everything
people wish from God.
People who are different
are suppressed.
I don’t know about other things,
but that’s the way things
are in this world.
But Yasutora...
You must be kind.
You must learn why you
have such big, strong fists.
Find out.
I know, Grandpa.
My fists aren’t big so that
I can hurt others.
My body...is big...
so that I can protect.
I know all that.
I know that...
But that’s why...
even just a little...
I want you to lend me
your strength!
What...is that arm?
Mister!
Mister! Your arm...!
Is it all right?
So un-cool!
Why would you make a gesture
like that?!
Mister!
I don’t understand...
That armor on my right arm
appeared out of nowhere.
And from it... something
amazing was released.
And suddenly, I could see
that monster so clearly.
I don’t understand...
not at all.
Just...
You’re not hurt,
Ichigo’s sister?
Stupid! You’re the only one
who’s hurt.
I see. That’s good.
It’s not good!
What’s good about getting hurt?!
If even one person
gets hurt, it’s NOT good!
That’s just the logic of guys
who want to be all heroic!
In that sense,
you’re just like Ichigo!
Aghh! I can’t stand it!
You just wait here!
I’ll call my dad and
have him treat you!
Don’t move from that spot, Mister!
Ichigo’s sister, huh...?
Just like Ichigo...
the way she kicks.
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Into a somber Karakura town
under attack by monsters
suddenly appears
the Fighter of Hope, Orihime!
With six henchmen,
she tosses out evil one by one.
Inoue, what are you talking about?
Next week's preview.
That's too convenient.