Good morning, Captain Omaeda!
-Captain Omaeda!
This is a miracle!
Damn you.
Stupid Soi Fon...
What? Must've been dreaming.
That dream sure felt good.
Maybe I'll go back to sleep.
Oh my god!
I was only going to take a short nap,
but I slept for three hours!
I'm such an idiot!
I'll be in big trouble if
I make Captain Soi Fon mad!
Gotta get back quickly!
That's as far as you'll get!
Say your prayers, kid!
A Soul Reaper?
What's he doing here?!
In my current state,
I'm at a disadvantage!
That hurt.
I thought there was a Hollow here.
Oh well.
Gotta hurry...
Please wait!
Huh?
Thank you for saving my life!
What?
Me?
Yes.
Please at least tell me who you are.
Huh?
Uh... Yeah...
I'm...with the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads...
Squad 2...
Squad 2 Captain!
You're...a...captain?!
I blurted that out without thinking.
Oh well, he's just one kid.
Captain, thank you so much for
saving Ryuzaburo's life.
Please have a drink, Captain!
-Captain!
Well, who cares!
Captain!
That's right! I'm a captain!
Everyone, bring more food for the Captain!
So? Did you really go to
the Hollow's cave and get it?
Sure did!
I win the game of courage!
-Awesome.
But you had help from a captain.
No fair!
There's no rule that says
someone can't help me.
This is a blast! A blast!
Come! Let's have another round over there!
Sure!
Captain!
Captain, thank you very much!
Captain, you're our hero!
I want to be like you, Captain!
Would you come to visit us again?
Sure! I'm always willing
to look after you!
-Captain!
You bet!
I can't eat anymore.
Oh crap!
I can't be idly spending time here!
No, really, it's the truth.
I saved a kid named Ryuzaburo
from a Hollow, and...
Really, seriously! Please believe me!
Otherwise, there's no
reason why I'd be tardy!
I didn't neglect my squad duties!
Relax.
Your presence wouldn't be missed.
It's sad when you put it that way.
In any case, you're to work at
cleaning the Seireitei
grounds for the time being.
By yourself.
You can't be serious! What's with that?!
Clean, by myself?!
I am a lieutenant, you know?
That wouldn't be right!
I told you.
Your presence wouldn't be missed.
But I... Yes, ma'am...
Jeez...
If you could come,
there wasn't any need for me to come too.
Don't be like that.
Why can't we?!
Because, boys, it's not allowed.
I'd really like to let you in,
but I can't allow anyone to go any
further without the permission
of a Soul Reaper.
We're telling you!
Once we see the Captain, he'll know!
We're friends of the Captain!
You say that, but...
Hey, Jidanbo!
Long time no see!
You're a rare sight.
If it isn't Ichigo.
What's going on?
These kids insist that I let them in.
We beg you! Please let us in!
We're here to see the Captain!
Captain?
The Captain saved me from a Hollow!
We showed our appreciation,
but he disappeared all of a sudden.
Yoruichi, isn't there something we can do?
Jidanbo...
I'll take responsibility.
Let these kids in.
So, who is this Captain?
The thing is...we don't know his name.
Come on!
Then, was there something about
the Captain that stood out?
He was kind of husky!
And huge!
And pointy!
Husky...
Huge...
And pointy...
Maybe Kenpachi?
But couldn't you say
Komamura is pointy, as well?
Around the ears?
No... That guy stands out too much.
Ordinarily, wouldn't they
say he looks like a dog?
Oh... He said he was the captain of Squad 2!
This is ridiculous.
Why do I have to do this sort of work?
Huh?
Omaeda... Just the man I want to see.
Let's ask him where Soi Fon is.
-Huh?
-Captain!
What's going on?
You guys?! What're you all doing here?!
Captain!
Why did you leave so suddenly?!
Well, umm...you know...it was...
Oh no!  What should I do?
I lied about being a captain
and ate and drink so much.
I can't turn back now.
What's going on, Omaeda?
Captain, your name is Sir Omaeda?
Look, you!
What's the big idea,
addressing the Captain with no respect!
That's rude!
You say "Captain," but...
The captain of Squad 2 is Soi-
Yoruichi, you too!
This, and then that, and whatchamacallit...
And that's what happened.
I'm begging you, please.
Wait, but that's just lying.
Very well.
Huh?! Yoruichi?!
Thank you! I owe you!
Oh dear, this sounds like fun.
I can't believe this person.
Awesome!
So this is where the Captain lives.
Of course! He's the Captain!
Okay, you boys have seen enough.
Now hurry on home!
Already?!
We want to see a little more of
the Captain doing your job!
Can't we, Captain?
Of course you can!
By Captain Omaeda's authority,
you boys can do whatever you want!
No...that's not a good...
Just as I thought.
She's having fun with this.
Madarame and Ayasegawa...
What a troublesome pair to run into.
Hey.
Yo.
H-Hi...
Just a minute, you two!
You people owe Captain Omaeda
a more proper greeting!
Huh? Greeting?
Stop that! No!
Like this! Standing at attention!
"Good morning, sir!"
Now you try it!
What a funny thing for you kids to say.
I'm not letting you off
just because you're kids.
Huh? What's up Ichigo?
What the heck?
And that's how it is.
I'm sure he'll make
it up to you properly.
If that's the case...
Right, Ikkaku?
Good morning, Captain Omaeda!
Why me, too?
Come on.
It's an easy side job.
Damn... This is an expense I don't need.
Aren't you thirsty, Captain!
Hey you two! Bring him tea right now!
Tea, you say?
Yes! Right away!
I'll kill you, Omaeda.
Come on.
I'm getting out of here while I can.
What's the matter, Captain?
Your tea is coming!
No, I don't want it.
Thank you for waiting!
I've brought you your tea!
Why're you here, Matsumoto?
Yumichika told me!
Right, everyone?
-Captain Omaeda!
You people, take the Captain
somewhere where he can relax!
Be careful about it!
-Yes!
H-Hey, just a minute!
They took my wallet, my watch,
my ring...everything.
This is costing me big time.
Damn...
What're you doing?
I don't have anything left to give you!
Captain...Soi Fon!
I thought I told you to be
on cleaning duties by
yourself for the time being.
Well...I was...
Oh no... This is bad...seriously bad!
I'll ask you once more.
What are you doing here?
Insolence!
You!
That's no way to speak to him!
No, don't! Not this person!
-Just who do you think this
-person before you is?!
-He is Sir Omaeda,
-captain of Squad 2!
What's with those canned lines?
What is the meaning of this?
Marechiyo, you're in serious trouble!
Goodbye, my days in Seireitei...
Hello, unknown future.
I'm done for.
I apologize, Captain Omaeda.
A miracle! This is a miracle!
I've truly been saved by the gods!
Is it really okay to let this go on?
What's the matter with you!
You should've said that from the start!
Now, Sir Omaeda!
Give this misguided woman orders!
What?! No, um...
You were saying something earlier
about cleaning by yourself?
Oh she is enjoying this so much.
Now... What's next?
Then...
Another bowl!
Yes, right away.
Another bowl for me too!
Captain is out of sake!
Yes!
What next, Sir?
All right, then...
That's the spot. Harder, right there.
This is the best!
I'm glad we came!
Yeah...
We're so lucky to have
met such a great man.
It's like a dream.
Man...
That bastard Omaeda was so insulting to me!
That coward could never be a captain!
Anyway you look at it,
he hasn't got what it takes.
His face, that is.
I swear. I'm going to kill him!
What did he mean?
It means he was lying
about everything, right?
Ryuzaburo!
Captain nothing!
We acted like fools!
It's your fault!
I'll see you, then.
Next time you come,
I will look after you as the captain!
He's talking like that again.
It's all a lie.
What's the matter, Ryuzaburo?
Next time, shall I give you
some training in swordsmanship?
You'll become strong like me!
What's with him?
It was all a lie!
Liar!
I've been waiting for you.
Now give it back.
This is the piece.
With this, my powers will return.
All that's left is to devour you.
Man...
You keep adding one hassle after another!
Stay here and be still!
R-Right!
Fool!
Don't think you can catch
me with that slowness!
You're not getting away!
Surprised?
My movements may not be that fast.
But if I use the power of my tail,
I can completely suppress
the speed of my enemy.
Damn!
Bastard...
He suppressed my speed.
This is bad.
This is really bad!
I need to get help immediately.
What are they doing here?
I'm... I'm a...
I'm a captain in front of those kids!
And a captain...
A captain shouldn't...
He's no good, just like they said!
He's different, after all.
What's different?
Huh?
It's true that the guy's not a captain,
but it doesn't change the
fact that he saved your life.
Was it the title of captain
that you were appreciative of?
Or were you appreciative of him,
the guy who saved you?
This time, keep watching.
Watch your hero.
Damn it!
I'd be running away by now if
they weren't looking at me!
Well, I can't run away, not with
the speed I have in these legs.
Huh? If they weren't looking at me...
Gave up so soon?
Then it's time I devoured you!
Well? How does Gegetsuburi taste?
Bakudo Number 21: Sekienton!
How's that?
Can't see me very well, can you?
I can't see you, either...but
that doesn't matter!
Smash'em!
Don't underestimate me.
Thank you, Mr. Omaeda.
Demoted from "Captain"
to "Mister," eh?
What can I say? You lied.
Well, that's true, but...
But it's cool.
My friends said they want to
become strong Soul Reapers like you, Mister.
What about you?
Me too!
I'm going to become a stronger
lieutenant than you, Mr. Omaeda.
I get it, I get it!
Hurry on home.
Bye!
All's well that ends well, eh, Omaeda?
I suppose.
Well, let's go back and have some tea!
Captain!
Have some tea?
Please stop!
I suppose he brought this on himself.
I just got my public
image to look good!
You're one to talk, Yoruichi.
I'm sorry!
I feel so tired.
I'm heading back now.
Yoruichi, open the Senkaimon will you?
Oh no you're not!
Huh? Why?
There's still more stories
like this coming up for a while.
We're having you get caught up
in another mess for the next episode as well.
Please, enough already!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I'm sorry!
I'll never do it again!
Isn't that enough?
Lies have their uses, you know.
See?
I understand.
I'm saved.
But it's also said that
what goes around comes around.
What?
That's right!
Ouch ouch ouch.
But "tread on a worm and
it will turn on you."
I see.
You had it coming.
Right!
Isn't this fun?