You're kidding, right?
Behind you!
Getsugatensho!
What's wrong?
You haven't reached me.
Is this the power
of his Zanpakuto?!
Don't worry.
I haven't been using my Kyokasuigetsu's
power in our fight.
This is just my basic strength.
What?!
Don't let him overpower you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Komamura!
Don't worry.
I know the reason
why the captains
that went to Hueco Mundo
sent you here first.
We will fight to protect you.
Fight to protect me?!
What are you saying?
That's crazy.
You're all in terrible shape!
What do you mean it's crazy?
Letting you fight alone
is far crazier.
If you went alone, we couldn't settle
our own personal grudges.
So don't try to do this
by yourself. It's cocky.
This is a battle for all of us.
That's right...
I must believe in them.
It's all right if I ask
for their help.
I'll take a good look
at the direction this
battle will take!
Too bad. I was so close.
You seem quite confident,
Captain Kyoraku.
If you think that,
I'm doing pretty well.
For someone who's launching
sneak attacks, that is.
Aizen...
Swinging a sword out of hatred
is just filthy violence.
We don't call that a battle.
Aizen...
You truly are unworthy
of being a captain.
How interesting.
You hate me more than any captain
in the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
I never expected
you to say that.
Or perhaps...
When Hinamori recovered and came
to the World of the Living...
Did all of your hatred disappear?
Bankai...
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
It's as you say, Aizen.
My sword is filled with hatred.
I didn't come here to fight you!
I came to violently kill you!
What incredible Spiritual Pressure...
Yes.
And it's not just from
Captain Hitsugaya.
Captain Komamura, Captain
Kyoraku, and...
that masked bunch too.
They're raising their
Spiritual Pressures to the limit.
Matsumoto and Hinamori
might have a hard time
being exposed to this much
Spiritual Pressure up close.
But even with all this
Spiritual Pressure...
Will it be enough?
If my sword is filled with hatred,
then I'm also unworthy
of being a Captain.
That's what you want
to say, right?
That's right.
As long as I can kill
you in this battle,
I don't care if I lose my
position as a captain.
I will do everything
I can to crush you.
I won't give you a chance to
use your Kyokasuigetsu.
Oh? You won't give me a chance
to use my Kyokasuigetsu?
That's right.
Get ready, Aizen!
You don't even look like
you want to fight.
Fine. Even if you don't,
I won't hold back!
You're not going to give him a
chance to use his Kyokasuigetsu?
This is not good.
You've completely misunderstood
Captain Aizen's power.
Hyoryusenbi!
Hyoryusenbi...
Zekku!
Tenken!
Tengumaru!
Forgive me, Captain Hitsugaya!
I'm going to interfere!
You may not like this, but now's
not the time to be complaining!
Do whatever you like.
I never planned to fight him
one-on-one from the beginning.
That's a good attitude to take.
I couldn't follow his movements.
What incredible speed.
Group attacks, sneak attacks,
distractions, decoys...
Unless you combine all of the
fighting styles you know,
you'll never catch me.
How interesting!
Can you stay calm against
this many opponents?!
That's good, Rose!
Keep him like that so
he can't escape!
I know that!
Now!
Aizen...
He's not even fazed?!
He's tough.
He doesn't even have
a scratch on him.
Did you really think
you could crush me
with sheer numbers and power?
How naive.
No, my understanding
of the word "power"
is probably different from yours.
Let me teach you.
When I talk about power...
This is what I'm talking about.
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
Kinshara!
That's right.
Captain Aizen isn't feared
because he can use
Kyokasuigetsu.
Yes, Kyokasuigetsu's
power is terrifying.
But that alone would
not have been
enough to subdue those who
would rather die than to obey.
There was only one reason
why those powerful Espada
were able to function as a group,
despite their personal motives.
Because he's strong.
All of Captain Aizen's abilities
are far beyond anyone else's.
You're going to take precautions
against his Kyokasuigetsu?
Your plans aren't good enough.
You're going to take precautions
against everything else?
Your plans still aren't
good enough.
Even if you gather your minds,
and take precautions against
unfortunate events like the sky
falling or the earth splitting,
Captain Aizen's abilities are
far beyond your plans.
A Hollowfication?
I told you...
You're just failed
mock Arrancars.
The Arrancar follow me.
Mock Arrancars shouldn't
point their blades at me.
You're kidding, right?
Has the Stealth Force gone mad?
I never expected their
Supreme Commander
to be standing before
the enemy.
Don't expect beauty
out of battle.
Don't expect virtue in death.
Don't think that only
your life is at stake.
If you want to protect the
ones you should protect,
you should attack your
enemy from the back.
Ordinary Soul Reapers learn
this at the Academy.
The Stealth Force knows
this even better.
I never expected a traitor to be
talking about the teachings
of the Soul Reapers.
Hilarious.
I was once a teacher.
Central 46 was pretty stupid
for allowing you to teach.
That's why they got
duped by a traitor.
It's not good to talk
ill of the dead.
You were duped too, right?
I'm surprised.
Do you think I was duped?
Me, of all people?!
Clones, huh?
That's not a bad parlor trick.
I'm honored by your praise.
The Stealth Force is never
praised for its flashiness.
As thanks...
I'm going to finish you off
with this parlor trick!
Nigeki Kessatsu.
"Death in two stings," huh?
What an amusing technique.
But it won't reach me!
What?!
A battle between Soul Reapers is a
battle between Spiritual Pressures.
I can easily overcome your silly power
with my Spiritual Pressure!
What?!
How careless of you.
You created a shadow
on the ice.
Kyoraku...
You bastard.
It's over, Aizen.
You really are young.
You recklessly charge in when
you see a chance at victory.
That is your biggest shortcoming,
Captain Hitsugaya.
Oh no!
It's the other way around!
H-He did it.
He did it!
The captains...
finally did it!
Hey, Kira!
Why can't you be
a little happier?
You look unmoved as always!
O-Okay...
Oh?
You're able to get
up...Hinamori?!
Hinamori!
H-Hey...
Where are you going, Hinamori?!
Hinamori!
Good grief...
We finally turned things around.
Right, Ichimaru?
Guys...
You guys...
What are you all doing?!
Hi-!
Hinamori?!
Damn it!
When?!
When?
What an interesting question.
You know that my
Kyokasuigetsu's power is
Complete Hypnosis, right?
It can control all five senses and
lead people to hallucinate
all sorts of things.
Since when?
I'm asking you when you
used your Kyokasuigetsu!
Then let me ask you this.
When did you think that I wasn't
using my Kyokasuigetsu?
Shiro...
Why?
Wait,
Captain Hitsugaya!
You're full of openings.
No...way...
Aizen and Gin Ichimaru
are all that's left.
The rest is up to me!
Do you really believe we
are the only ones left?
You're not?
Aren't you forgetting someone?
No, I don't think so.
Are you sure?
I won't fall for your deception!
But I'm not deceiving you.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers...
These are the items I've
always longed for!
To think such a place existed in
this town in the World of the Living!
Magnificent!
This truly is a dream come true!
That was easy.
What joy and happiness this is!