Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Yuzu...
You're so noisy...
One hostage is good enough...
Karin!
Good.
I still have my hostage.
I've been waiting for you,
Soul Reaper.
Karin!
Ichigo...
Furukawa Family Plot
That bastard...!
What's going on?
Why you--!
You're the one who was
at the riverbank, aren't you?
Six years ago!
So what are you doing here?!
Six years ago?
Ichigo, don't tell me...!
Yeah... I tried to help her back then.
But when I realized it, she was gone...
and my mom was...
My mom was...
Six years ago, huh?
I don't remember things so long ago.
I see...
This is very interesting.
Grand Fisher!
That's his code name.
He hides himself and
gives the lure
that grows out of his head
a human appearance.
And when he finds those
who are able to see it...
In other words, those who
have high spiritual energy...
he attacks them and
increases his own power.
For over fifty years,
this Hollow has defied Soul
Reapers like us.
And his favorite is...women.
Which means...my mom was...
I see.
You survived even after seeing me.
What a lucky kid.
Perhaps at first I intended to
devour you
for your
high spiritual energy.
However...women always
seem more delicious.
Why that--!
Haven't seen a Hollow so disgusting
in a long time.
Karin!
Don't be so careless, you idiot!
Ichigo!
You're one bastard
I'll never forgive!
Disintegrate, you black dog
of Rondanini!
Look upon yourself and burn!
Tear out your own throat!
Binding Spell 9: Strike!
Do not interfere!
Now then, I'm going to
devour this girl.
What will you do?
Karin!
Stop!
Then will you let me eat you instead?
Karin!
Hey! You…
Why would you go that far...?
Soul Reapers keep fighting Hollows
no matter what happens.
Soul Reapers will never
forgive Hollows.
When a Hollow attacks indiscriminately,
and you lose something precious to you,
only an empty feeling remains.
I can't let that happen!
You've gotta protect, Spiky...
you understand?
Hey!
No way...
He can't have died if
he's a Soul Reaper!
Even Soul Reapers are not immortal.
Even if the form is different,
death is...
This guy’s asleep.
Hey, get up! It’s distracting!
Sis!
Whoa... this looks pretty bad.
Kon! Take the sisters and run!
What about you?
– Hurry!
– Right!
Ichigo, back me up.
Ichigo!
Rukia, get back.
What?
Just stay back this time.
I'll do it myself.
Don't be ridiculous! He is strong.
I told you,
he's been defying Soul Reapers
for over fifty years--!
Shut up!
Please…
Don't interfere.
This is...
my fight!
Karin! A-Are you all right?
Cripes! Acting all serious
with my eyebrows furrowed is tiring!
How does Ichigo keep such
an expression for so long?!
You're slow, kid!
It was gutsy of you to
tell your friends
not to interfere when that's
the limit of your strength.
Huh, kid?
Shut up…
I don't really know
how much Yuzu grieved after Mom died.
Or how lonely Karin felt.
You gotta protect, Spiky.
I decided to protect.
I'm going to...
destroy you!
Didn't your friend tell
you not to be careless, kid?
Now how many times have
you jumped right into the lion's den
without any strategy?
That's why they call you careless, kid!
You're too rash. Much too rash.
You push away your comrade
in the heat of the moment,
and jump right into your enemy's lair.
You’ll just die while I toy you.
– Ichigo!
– Stay back!
Stay back, Rukia!
I'm going to destroy him!
Even if my arms are ripped off...
even if my legs fly off.
I'll beat him!
And that's why I say you'll die.
Because you are young,
you fly off the handle easily.
And that passion distracts your heart.
And a distracted heart dulls your sword.
It's over, kid!
You're much too young to be
fighting me!
Ichigo! That's…
Why you--!
Even the most cold-blooded
Soul Reaper has one person
whom he can never kill.
That is a certainty.
By learning who that person is,
I have been able to
defy every Soul Reaper ‘til now.
And for you, this person is the one.
Right…Ichigo?
Ichigo!
And what of his honor?
If you lend him your strength now,
his life will
probably be saved.
But in doing so,
you will forever destroy his honor.
Now listen and remember this.
There are two kinds of battles.
We must always distinguish
between the two.
The battle to protect life...
and the battle to protect honor.
That's right.
This is a battle to protect his honor.
It is a battle in which
I cannot lend him my strength.
Don't help him... don't help him...
don't help him!
Don't die, Ichigo!
Oh dear, I fell asleep.
Damn!
Can you draw your sword
against this woman?
Why you--!
Do you realize what you're doing?
Don't you dare...
bring my mom’s image out to
a place like this!
You must not, Ichigo.
Put down your sword.
Don't hurt your mother.
Please.
Didn't I tell you?
Anger will dull your sword.
It will be over with the next blow, kid.
But I'll say this much for you.
Among those I have encountered,
you were the youngest,
and the most rash...
and the weakest Soul Reaper!
Ichigo!
W-Wha--?!
That’s…
Mom…?
His mother's thoughts are
manifesting themselves.
Does that mean the lure had
recorded his mother's thoughts
at the moment of her death?
Thoughts at the moment of her death?
I caught a glimpse of it earlier...
No telling how this battle
is going to end yet.
Ichigo…
I'm so proud of you!
Dad, Karin, Yuzu,
and you, Ichigo.
I'm so proud that
I was able to meet you.
Live, Ichigo.
With strength, with kindness,
and with a smile…
Thank you…Ichigo.
Ichigo…
Mom…
Is that what you were thinking
at that time...?
Anger dulls the sword...
That may be true.
However...you're wrong about one thing...
In order to beat a thing like you,
a dull sword is
more than enough!
If I were the rain…
would I have been able to
connect someone's heart
like the rain which connects
the never-intersecting sky and earth?
Ichigo,
I think I've come to understand
you a bit more.
Dammit! Dammit!
I won't forgive you!
You're just a Soul Reaper!
Wait!
Ichigo!
Stop! That's enough.
Neither of you can fight any more.
The battle is over!
Not yet! He's still not dead!
I still--
Ichigo!
You lived, Ichigo… Thank you.
He's something else.
The power of the Soul Reaper's
spiritual energy
is the power of
his life energy.
This kid could become a monster.
Time to go home.
I'm not so heartless as
to break up a serious couple.
I guess, Rukia, you've come of age.
Don't even go there!
Well, whatever...
When they find out, they find out.
Bye-bye!
Sorry. I couldn't get revenge.
Mom...
Well, if you show yourself
looking fit and healthy like that,
Mom will be relieved on the other side.
Don't eavesdrop on your own son.
I thought you quit.
When we first started dating
she complimented me.
She said that I looked cool
holding a cigarette.
Thinking back,
that was the first and last time
your mom ever complimented me.
That's why I smoke just once,
on this day every
year in front of her.
How can you keep smiling?
Why doesn't anyone blame me?
It's hard to take!
It'd be much easier if
you all blamed me for this!
Why?!
Why should we blame you?
Huh?
If I blamed you for
causing Masaki's death,
Masaki would scold me.
It's no one's fault that
Masaki died.
She was...
just the woman I loved,
who would give her life to
protect her own child.
And remember this:
You are the man whom the woman I loved
protected with her life.
Dad...
Oww…
Live well, Ichigo…
Live well, grow old well,
go bald well, and then die after me.
And if you can, die laughing.
Otherwise, I won't be able to face Masaki.
Shake off your depression.
You're way too young
to be burdened
by something cool like sadness.
I'll be waiting below.
Are you listening, Rukia?
Let me be a Soul Reaper
for a while longer.
I want to become strong.
I want to become strong and
protect people from Hollows!
Those who are attacked by them.
And I'm going to beat him!
Otherwise...
I won't be able to face my mom!
Ichigo…
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Wow! What a scary Hollow that was!
I was pitiful in this episode,
but next time,
come hell or high water,
I'll show my stuff, for Rukia's sake!
– There're no scenes for you next time.
– Huh?!