The showdown with the Arrancars
is in the winter.
Ichigo, Sado, Ishida, Rukia, and Orihime
are undergoing intense training
to get as strong as possible
in what little time they have.
Meanwhile, Hitsugaya's advance troops
remain in Karakura Town
and fight the powerful Hollows who appear
as they prepare for the showdown.
As that happens,
the situation suddenly changes.
A signal!
We've got an Arrancar signal!
What about the Gentei Kaijo?!
We've already
received permission!
What color is the signal?!
It's a crimson signal!
It's an Espada!
I'm Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya!
What a coincidence...
I'm also a ten!
I'm Arrancar Diez, Yammy!
Are you an Espada, too?
That's right...
My name is Luppi.
My rank is Seis.
Your friends from Soul Society are
stationed here for things like this!
Leave it to them!
Let go of me!
But I've been training
for times like this!
What good is it
if I don't go!
Let him go.
Kuchiki!
The Kido Corps should be
opening the gate right now!
Yes!
Oh! Wait!
I also...
You can't, Inoue!
Huh?
You don't have
a Hell Butterfly.
Even if you go with me
through the Senkaimon,
you'll be sent to the Dangai,
Precipice World.
I've given out orders to stabilize the walls
of the Dangai, Precipice World,
so that you can pass through it safely.
I know you're in a rush,
but it's important not to
be hasty at times like this.
Got that?
I'm going ahead.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay!
Hey. I've been looking for you,
Soul Reaper.
That's my line.
I'll show you...
how much I've changed
in the past month!
Bankai!
A Bankai?
So what of it?
Did you forget?
Your Bankai didn't do anything
against me!
Did you forget?
My attacks gave you that scar
when I used my Bankai!
I want to ask you
one thing, Grimmjow.
What happened
to your arm?
I discarded it.
It's unnecessary to kill you
with two arms.
I see.
Then I don't need to
hold back!
If you don't want to die,
then don't!
Right now, the amount
of time I can maintain
a Hollow transformation
is eleven seconds flat!
I have to settle this
within that time!
Wh-What is that?!
Sorry... I don't have
time to explain.
Getsugatensho!
What is this?
It's refreshing!
It's impossible to take on an Espada
without using my Bankai,
even if I'm using
a Gentei Kaijo.
I told you...
You can't defeat me
one-on-one.
Don't you understand?
Shut up!
Say something to him.
I'll really kill him.
I don't like going
two against one.
Oh yeah?
What a bother...
Yammy!
Let me take on that kid too!
Huh?
They're all so troublesome.
Let's go four against one!
I'll release and take you all
on by myself.
A Zanpakuto release...
I won't let you!
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Strangle! Trepadora!
What's wrong?
Is that the most damage your attack
can do while you're released?!
You blocked that well!
I honestly thought that
you couldn't stop it.
I'm a little shocked.
I guess captains are
pretty tough, huh?
But what if
that attack just now
had been
eight times stronger?
What?
Crap...
Captain!
I told you that we should
go four against one.
Oh! Sorry.
It was four against eight.
Crap... Not yet?!
There it is!
Renji!
Hey, Rukia!
Renji, what are you doing?
Didn't you get the notice that
the Espada have appeared?
Well, I did get a notice.
But I trained a little too much
and I exhausted
my Spiritual Pressure.
We're massaging him right now!
Yes, yes!
You fool!
What are you doing?!
Sorry, but they're not people
you should fight
if you're not in
good condition.
So Mr. Urahara set out...
Urahara?!
You've overused
your powers!
I'll go.
You rest here!
B-But...!
That's right.
It's as Abarai says...
But Abarai is
exhausted as well.
Both of you rest here.
Instead...
I'll go.
This power...
is not that of a Soul Reaper.
What did you do
in the past month?!
I told you.
I don't have time to explain!
You...piece of crap!
A Cero!
Piece of crap!
It's over, Grimmjow.
My mask...
It's over, Soul Reaper!
My...mask...
Looks like you over did it when you used
that power of yours just now.
You were panting a lot
as soon as your mask came off!
It's over, Soul Reaper!
I took quite a few hits,
but in the end...
You can't defeat me
with your power!
Why you...
It's useless.
This is pathetic.
Are you really Thirteen Court
Guard Squad officers?
How boring.
Crap!
Aw... I'm so bored.
Luppi took all of them for himself.
Then again, it's a bother to
go look for other prey.
Hey! Hey, newbie!
What are you doing?!
Aw... I'm so bored!
Matsumoto!
Rangiku!
Yumichika!
Crap! What are you doing?!
How repulsive!
Why you...
Crap!
Lady, you've got a hot body.
I'm jealous.
You're so sexy.
Maybe I'll punch you
full of holes.
You bastard!
Stop!
Well... I made it in time.
That sure was close.
Who are you?
Oh, hello...
I didn't introduce myself.
Lady Inoue!
Lady Orihime Inoue!
We have finished stabilizing the walls
of the Dangai, Precipice World!
Please pass through!
Okay.
Be careful.
Thank you very much!
I'll be off!
Huh?
We shall accompany you!
What?! It's all right.
You don't have to...
You are not a ryoka anymore!
You're a guest!
A guest?
It is customary for two Soul Reapers
without Hell Butterflies
to accompany a guest
as the guest comes and goes!
You may find this uncomfortable,
but please bear with us!
Okay... Then please
lead the way.
I've got to hurry.
It's all right.
I've become a little stronger
in the past month.
I'm sure I'll be
of help now!
So wait for me Kurosaki...
and everyone!
What's this?
Only two guards?
Soul Society is
unexpectedly incompetent.
They don't seem to know that
it's most dangerous when you travel.
Kisuke Urahara...
I'm the owner of Urahara's Shop,
a humble shop that sells cheap sweets.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh? There's someone
pretty strange...
He's from back then.
It's disappointing that
you have two guards.
But it's convenient that
the troublesome restrictive currents
have been frozen.
It's not in my nature to rush things
just so that we can talk.
Who are you?!
Are you an Arrancar?!
Wait! You have something
to tell me, don't you?!
That's right, woman.
I have something to tell you.
Sotenkishun!
Run away!
Please run away!
B-But...
Just run away! Please!
Ayame!
Oh? You can even heal
injuries that deep?
That's quite the power.
Come with me, woman.
Wha-?
Don't talk.
Say only "yes."
If you say anything besides that,
people will die.
I don't mean you...
I mean your friends.
Don't ask anything.
Don't tell me anything.
You don't have any privileges.
The only thing you have is
the rope to the guillotine
in which your friends have
placed their heads.
Understand this, woman.
This is not a negotiation.
This is an order.
Lord Aizen wants your power.
I've been ordered to
bring you back unharmed.
I'll just tell you once more.
Come with me, woman.
Hey everyone,
how about a massage from a mod soul?
Your fatigue will be cured
in one minute!
It's true!
My body feels really light!
What are you doing, Renji?
They helped me out earlier,
so I'm helping them
with their business.
You fools!
- We're very sorry!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
GRIMMJOW
If an Arrancar is born stronger
than an existing Espada,
they switch places.
Recently, Grimmjow got
his arm cut off.
So Luppi became
the new Number Six in his place.
LUPPI
I knew that I would become
an Espada sooner or later.
Oh? We seem like-minded.
For some reason,
the other Espada hate me.
I don't really like you either.
What?