You done?
Damn you…
I did enjoy that a bit.
But…now…
Stop!
Huh?
What?
Did you come to be captured?
Of course not!
Rain down, Arazomeshigure!
Interesting!
What was that?!
Hisagi!
Hey!
Meeting here like this
must’ve been meant to be.
Let’s play, boys.
Reap, Kazeshini!
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Whoa!
Going at full strength
right off the bat?
I won’t hold back against a captain!
It wouldn’t be fun any other way!
What’s with his…
Spiritual Pressure?!
This is how powerful they become
without their power restriction?!
You really shouldn’t be talking!
So you small fry are my opponents?
What a disappointment!
Are you okay, Nozomi?!
I’m okay.
You sure don’t look like it.
Shut up!
I just got dizzy for a second!
Yeah, right.
Your Zanpakuto…
How’s it work, anyway?
It absorbs the opponent’s power,
then converts it into my own energy,
and redirects it towards the opponent.
That’s the power of Arazomeshigure.
That’s one nasty power…
that an enemy has to deal with.
Good work, Ikkaku.
Not bad, woman!
This is fun.
I’ll take you on!
Sorry, but please stay
out of this fight.
I will avenge Ikkaku.
You two look after him.
W-Wait!
I don’t mind starting with you,
but come at me like you mean it!
I know.
I won’t bore you, Captain.
Bloom, Fujikujaku!
Nozomi, we need to get
Ikkaku to safety!
Ichigo!
Huh?
I’m going to help the others!
Nozomi!
Smash’em, Gegetsuburi!
What a filthy weapon.
And…
such a filthy face.
Don’t kill me!
I’ll pay you anything you want!
Trying to settle things with money
is something a vulgar person does.
Scatter…
Oh, no!
Senbonzakura.
When I get back,
I’d better clean off my sword.
Roar, Zabimaru!
More filthy beings.
This impostor sure talks a lot.
Brother!
Hey!
I’ll fight with you!
No!
We’ll take on the captains.
Right.
Nozomi, you look after the wounded!
Go right now!
Are you all right?!
You fool! What’re you…
Growl, Haineko!
Tenken!
El Directo!
Young lady…
Let us handle things here.
Get to safety quickly!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
Go quickly!
We won’t be able to protect you
while we’re fighting!
Shakkaho!
What’re you doing here?!
I-I was…
Look, just get away from here!
You’re in the way!
But…
Nozomi!
Fall back for now!
Don’t try so hard.
But I’m now able to do a Shikai.
I want to help everyone.
Those guys want to capture you.
If you dash out there,
you’ll be putting
a burden on everyone.
But if I don’t do something…
If I don’t do something…
No matter how hard they fight…
they can’t win against the captains.
Yumichika!
Stay away!
Don’t try to be strong.
Come at me all together.
It’s more fun that way.
Let me fight until the end.
If I don’t…
Ikkaku will laugh at me.
Yumichika!
Damn…
He’s got us cornered.
Rukia!
Renji!
Hold it.
I’m your opponent.
Besides, I still owe that
little girl some payback.
Hey, you guys!
Still playing around?
Let me join you.
Shut up, these guys are mine.
I have no interest in
fighting filthy people.
If I don’t do something…
You’re still able to move?
You should be dead.
Nozomi!
No more…
No more of this!
Whatever!
I’ll put you out of your misery!
You’ll be the one put
out of his misery!
Rain down, Arazomeshigure!
Damn it…
What was…that power?
That’s the power of
that girl’s Shikai?
See?
It really is a nasty power
for an enemy to deal with.
Interesting.
Seems like it got stronger
since the last time.
Looks like I’ll enjoy
it even more this time.
Wait.
That girl comes later.
We’ll get rid of the
other Soul Reapers first.
That was our promise to Kageroza.
Then let’s get it over with quickly.
Damn it.
Roar, Zabimaru!
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
Your filthy attacks will
not work against me.
My brother doesn’t
say things like that!
Bakudo Number 61: Rikujokoro!
Nozomi!
If her Zanpakuto uses
her opponent’s power,
we simply have to fight in a manner
that won’t allow her to do that.
Where do you think you’re looking?!
Damn it.
Getsugatensho!
Crap…
Not even close!
Ichigo!
It’s time you died!
El Directo!
Ichigo, your Spiritual Pressure…
Damn you!
Ichigo!
Are you okay, Nozomi?!
What about you?
You’re pale as a ghost.
I’m fine!
Ichigo…
Hado Number 33: Sokatsui.
No!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I don’t think so!
No!
Thanks, Nozomi.
Sorry about that.
That was nothing.
I can absorb much more.
Hey!
What’s with that satisfied
look on your face, Four-Eyes?!
Still refuse to give up?
You should all be dead by now.
Shut up!
Pathetic.
Kujo’s powers…
can not only absorb the Spiritual
Pressure of Zanpakuto,
but Kido and my Ginreikojaku as well.
Isn’t that right?
Yes.
I can absorb anything as long
as it's Spiritual Pressure.
What?! You can’t be serious!
It’s too dangerous!
I’ll do it.
What?!
I’ll do it if it
means saving everyone.
Besides, Arazomeshigure now
does what I want it to do.
I’ll be fine.
But…
Kurosaki.
In order to overcome the
enemy’s Spiritual Pressure,
we have no choice but to rely on her.
All right.
Got that, everybody?
Direct your Spiritual Pressure at Kujo!
What?!
What’re you going to do?!
Just do it, Renji!
Not under these conditions!
I don’t completely trust
that girl to begin with!
You can trust her!
Kira?!
We’ve seen how she fights!
Nozomi Kujo has what it
takes to be a Soul Reaper.
If you two say so,
then I’ll take that chance.
Well, Iba?
Guess I have no choice.
Fine, I’ll do it.
Getsugatensho!
El Directo!
Licht Wind!
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
What?!
Where are they?!
Did we get them?!
You did it.
Nozomi, that was awesome!
-Yeah.
-Nozomi!
-Stay away!
-Nozo…
mi…
Brother!
Did you think…
I’d be defeated by a
technique like that?
Hado Number 73: Soren Sokatsui!
Now I’ll finish you off!
What…the…
Old Man!
Ichigo, who is that old man?
Oh, he’s the Head Captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
I see. I’ll go grab a chair.
Huh?
I saw it on TV.
The young should give
seats to the elderly.
So I’ll go grab a chair.
It’s okay!
He looks like an old man,
but he’s not an old man,
but he’s still an old…man?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Today, we’ll be talking
about Kujo’s Zanpakuto.
Its name is “Arazomeshigure.”
NAME: ARAZOMESHIGURE
CRY  RAIN DOWN
Its Zanpakuto cry is “Rain down.”
It has the power to absorb
the Spiritual Pressure
of others before converting
it into its own
and releasing it all at once.
Huh?
Just for the record, Quincy also possess
the ability to take in Reishi
and Spiritual Pressure.
We’re just kidding.
Did you really think we could take
Spiritual Pressure just by touch?