Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Rukia Kuchiki…
Found you!
Give me that sword,
Soul Reaper.
My name is not Soul Reaper.
I am Rukia Kuchiki.
Kuchiki, do you like Kurosaki?
What?
I'll be sitting next to you from today.
My name’s Kuchiki.
Y-You…!
How do you drink this?
Huh? You just poke a straw
in it and drink.
Bohahahahaha!
Oh no! I'd better take you
to the infirmary!
Okay, I'll believe you…
Idiot! You think I'd believe that?!
I'll come up with a new concoction
of bean jam.
So let's eat it together.
Err... I'll think about it.
Not the same answer again!
You keep saying,
"I'll think about it."
Oh really?
Here, here!
Is it good?
If I'm going to have to leave
this place one day,
all this will be a burden.
Compassion, friendship and affection…
Kurosaki is just a friend.
They're a bother.
All these feelings aren't necessary
for a Soul Reaper.
It's unbecoming, Rukia Kuchiki.
I think I've stayed in
this world for too long.
Yes!
Huh?!
See, you understand.
Though, to put it another way,
because you stayed in
this world so long,
you were able to
prolong your life a bit more, Rukia!
Renji!
Are you Renji Abarai?
You had an assailant from
the Soul Society lurking right behind you,
but you were so deep in thought,
you didn't even notice until
I called out your name?
Granted you're in a Gigai,
but in just one or two months,
haven't you become a bit too lax?
Spit it out, Rukia.
Where is the human who
took all your powers?
What are you saying?!
Just because I'm in a Gigai
doesn't mean I've lost my powers.
Furthermore...
to assume that the one who
took my powers was a human…
It was a human!
Otherwise, there's no way
you would have
such a human expression
on your face!
You're from the Rukon District like me.
You were taken in by
the great noble family of Kuchiki…
and they spent a lot of time
and money
to make you an elite Soul Reaper!
Isn't that so?!
You are Rukia Kuchiki!
Looking so human…
There's no way that's a good thing!
Right, Captain Kuchiki?
Brother…Byakuya?
Rukia…
Passing on Soul Reaper powers
to a human is a grave crime.
Consider it compassion from
the higher-ups
for letting us handle
your execution instead of the Keigun.
Now tell us where he is, Rukia.
We're taking you in,
then we'll go after the one
who took your powers…
and we'll kill him!
Don't even try to protect him.
You realize it, don't you?
You didn't dodge my earlier attacks.
I’ve let you dodge them.
The next one will be fatal.
Take that!
Now…!
An unarmed girl being attack
by two men with weapons…?
It's not…a very pleasant sight.
I don't really go for that kind of thing.
You can see us?
Just who are you?
Just a classmate.
Classmate?
One who hates Soul Reapers.
Ishida…?
What are you doing here?
Sheer coincidence.
Nothing for you to worry about.
But if you must know…
I had a sudden urge to go to
Sunflower Sewing,
the sewing shop franchise
that's open 24 hours…
And that's why I was
walking here so late.
It's not as though I sensed
the presence of Soul Reapers
and came here to look,
taking the trouble of carrying this plastic bag
just so I could use it as an excuse.
Oh my…
I didn't know he was so clueless.
Well, I don't blame you
for being shocked, but…
I asked you a question.
Just who are you?
Well, don't answer
if you don't want to.
I'll just kill you first.
Wait, Renji! He has nothing
to do with this…!
What are you saying?
I did answer you.
I'm just Rukia Kuchiki's classmate…
one who hates Soul Reapers.
That's not an answer!
I'm Uryu Ishida. Pleased to meet you.
What's this change of attitude?
You may be a Soul Reaper…
but you'd still want to know
the name of your killer, right?
It's decided! I'm going to kill you!
I wonder if Rukia doesn't
intend to come back?
It's past two in the morning!
Oh well, I guess I get a break
from Soul Reaper duties tonight--
Huh? What the--?!
Where's it coming from?
Is it from here?!
You!
Kon!
What're you doing down there?!
Didn't you go on a journey?
Oh boy… Thanks for saving me!
Don't mention it.
In that position,
I couldn't see who came in…
so I had to listen and try
to figure out if it was you.
W-What're you doing?!
Is this what you do to friends who
had to endure such suffering for so long?!
Shut up! What friend?!
You stink!
That's not my fault… Sis…
Oh that's right! Ichigo!
Sis is in trouble!
Look! Don't come near me!
Huh?!
Look at this!
Don’t tell me you didn’t notice
this all this time?!
What is it?
Isn't it obvious?!
It's a farewell letter.
Farewell letter?
Then why were you in
the toilet instead of leaving?
Sheesh! It wasn't me that wrote it!
KUROSAKI CLINIC
After that incident, I went back
to say goodbye to Sis
before leaving on my journey.
Mind you, I didn't go back
with my tail between my legs.
But it was the honorable thing to do.
So I went for a quick stop.
Sis?
Sis left us all and went away.
Why?! Without telling me?
Shut up! Shut up!
How should I know?!
I was there with her!
And yet, she left without
a word to me!
Who cares about you?!
– Sis!
– Damn that Rukia!
What's she thinking anyway?!
Huh?!
"Enjoy decoding."
"BFor bcerbtain breabsons…"
"BI bmust bleave."
What the hell?!
"This is the hint."
What's it mean?
Geez! Too many "b" consonants!
So this must be a badger!
If we badger the "b's"…
Let's see…
"For certain reasons…
"I must leave.
"Do not look for me and…
"do not worry.
"Burn this letter when
you've read it. And…
"Keep yourself hidden for a while."
What's it all mean?
She doesn't explain
her reason for leaving.
Don’t you understand?
Huh?
Something must've happened.
Burn the letter…stay hidden…
Why is Sis so
worried about us?
Isn't it obvious?!
Something happened
between her and the Soul Society!
And so that she doesn't involve us…
Sis...Sis left all by herself!
Sis…what if...
she's dea--
Cut it out!
Let's stop jumping to conclusions.
All this talking…
It isn't getting us anywhere.
Ichigo…
Let's go, Kon.
I'm going to transform into
a Soul Reaper and go after Rukia!
Right! I'm with you! Huh?
N-Not again?!
There's no other way
except to stick my hand
into your mouth for a Gikongan!
No! No! Stop!
No!
Hold it!
Quit resisting!
Rukia's in danger!
I can't do a thing unless
I turn into a Soul Reaper!
Arghh… That's not the point.
Who likes to have
a hand rammed down his throat?!
Stupid! This is just
as disgusting to me, too!
Hello!
Seems like you're in a bind.
Is there something
I can help you with?
See? That's why you shouldn't talk big.
He's so strong…
He's increased his skills even more.
I couldn't stop him…
let alone move from this spot.
Now then…
Let's go with the final blow.
Remember this before you die!
Renji Abarai…is the name
of the man who killed you.
Wait!
Nice to meet you!
Wha--?!
Who are you?!
Ichigo Kurosaki.
The one who will beat you.
Nice to meet you.
Wearing Shihakusho?
Which squad are you from?!
W-What's with that
outsized Zanpaku-to?!
Oh? So it's big, after all?
I did think that it was
big compared to Rukia's.
But well…
Haven't had anything
else to compare it to.
The size of one's Zanpaku-to mirrors
the size of one's spiritual energy.
A kid this young with
a sword this size?!
Is he for real?
Ichigo, you fool!
Why did you come?!
I see. I get it now.
You're the human who
took Rukia's power, huh?!
Huh?!
Take this and that and that!
What's the matter?
Is that sword just for show? Huh?!
Damn you!
What the hell's the matter with him?!
Ichigo!
Don't go…
Ishida…
It's over, huh?
You'll die and Rukia will
get her powers back.
And, Rukia will die in Soul Society.
Huh?!
But what an idiot you are!
Rukia came here all alone…
Just so that she
wouldn't involve you.
You should've just stayed put at home,
but you came after her.
Did you think you could
do something?
You, a Soul Reaper by accident?
You can't hurt real Soul Reapers like us…
not even a scratch.
Sorry about that.
I know you were talking,
but you were so wide open,
I couldn't help myself.
But why don't you continue?
Not even a scratch, you said?
Why you--!
You were off your guard, Renji.
Captain Kuchiki!
That boy, Ichigo Kurosaki…
I thought I had seen
him somewhere.
I got a report the other day
from the Secret Remote Squad.
He injured the Menos Grande
quite seriously
and forced it to return to Hueco Mundo.
Huh?
What a laugh!
The quality of the Secret Remote Squad
has really deteriorated lately.
This kid? Wounded a Menos Grande?
Who'd believe such a story?!
I mean, Captain, take a look!
At his Zanpaku-to!
It's just big and pitifully useless!
It's obvious he hasn't mastered
his spiritual energy.
What's the name of your Zanpaku-to?
Huh? Name?
Did you ask?
You mean, ask Rukia?
So you name every
one of your swords?
I knew it. You don't even
know your Zanpaku-to’s name.
And you think you can
fight me as an equal?
Well, it's 2000 years too soon!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Look in front of you!
What stands before you is…
your prey!
It's all over, punk.
You will lose to Renji Abarai…
and die at this spot!
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
It's Kon Bleach Quick Facts!
Soul Reapers in the Soul Society belong
to Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Byakuya Kuchiki is
the captain of Squad 6.
Renji Abarai is the vice-captain.
And...
Which program are you imitating?
Do the preview!