Blood?
God despises those who lie
and those who are unclean.
What do I do now? This is where...
This is where I was.
Wait, Zack.
Wait...
No! Please!
Don't go!
Don't look in that room!
Hey, Ray!
What's the holdup?
What do I do? What do I do?
I have to think...
But... But...
Looks like the inside of an actual house.
Are these flowers fake?
Zack!
We don't know what might be in here.
Don't touch things at random.
Why are you freaking out over
dumb stuff like this now?
Are they corpses?
Damn, talk about gross.
Zack! Come on, Zack, please! Please!
Please...
What?
Please, just kill me! Kill me right now!
What's gotten into you?
Please! Hurry!
What're you talking about?
We're not outside yet.
Still!
I only wanna kill you when—
When I smile, right?
Cut it out. That's not the point.
What good would it do to kill you here?
I promised, didn't I?
Once we get outside and you show me a
good expression, I'll grant your wish.
Just get moving and find the exit.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Please, Zack, hurry!
Please! My God would—
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Get it together!
Hey!
What's been with you since we got here?
I can't kill you with that look on your face.
"My God," huh? You talkin' about me?
Tch.
She was looking at this book.
What's the big deal about this?
Huh?
Huh? The hell is this?
That bastard!
I got rid of the interference.
Danny, you piece of shit!
Don't make so much noise.
You'll wake Rachel.
Shit!
Open the door!
Sure, I'd be glad to open it,
but now isn't the time.
You did so well to come this far,
Rachel.
You do anything to her, and I'll kill you!
I won't kill Rachel.
Zack! You've been strolling along by
Rachel's side with no idea who she was!
She even called you her God!
Quit saying that creepy shit!
I have all the cards now.
I hold Rachel's safety and the knowledge
of where this building's exit is.
What?!
A poor fool like you who can't even read
doesn't deserve salvation,
but I'm offering it to you.
Try to know everything about her.
Search this floor, and you'll find out
just what truly suits her best.
Huh?
Depending on the answer you find,
I might let you out of here.
But only you, of course... you see?
That doesn't explain a damn thing!
Hey, Ray! Wake up!
She is sleeping to hide a wonderful treasure.
Cut the bullshit!
If you succeed in learning everything,
I'll open the door.
Tch!
If you want out of this building,
you'll do as I say!
Hey!
Damn it!
Fine! I just have to search
this entire floor, right?!
Tch.
Damn it.
Are these the people who live on this floor?
What is this bullshit?
Damn.
Do you think I'm stupid?!
Tch. Locked again.
Heh. This one's not tough to figure out.
Ow!
Tch. Try to make a fool of me, will ya?
Everything in here has been set
up like a bunch of stupid pranks.
Quit your yapping!
What a waste of time.
Screw this!
Rachel... Rachel...
Doctor!
You're finally awake.
Why so flustered?
Are you looking for someone?
If it's Zack... I chased him away.
He's wandering around on this floor now.
You're worried about him, aren't you?
No, that's not it.
You're worried about yourself.
Let me out of here.
I can't do that.
Zack won't die so easily.
Of course, that means he might find out
who the residents of this floor are.
Stop it!
What will Zack think when
he finds out everything?
What's this? You look pale.
What's the matter?
Please.... stop this.
Wait here with me to see if
Zack makes it back alive.
You?
Why'd you save me?
There would be no amusement
in letting it end so easily.
I suspected this would happen.
The girl is with Danny now, is she not?
And you are on the move in hopes
of getting her back. Am I wrong?
So what?!
I see you actually use your
emotions for such things now.
What's so funny?! Don't you
laugh down your nose at me!
Ah, my apologies.
My intention is not to ridicule you.
Then what's your deal?!
Oh, I was only wondering
what has made you this way.
Made me what way?!
Explain it so I can understand!
Well... such complicated matters
are unbefitting of you, but...
I will give you a brief
explanation of what I am doing.
Huh?
Since I was a youth, I have witnessed
people who believe in God.
Their faith is as beautiful
as it is blind and ugly.
At times, they use God as a mere tool
to denounce those they disagree with,
and even flaunt images of God
to serve their own purposes.
I always found it questionable.
How, I wondered, did God truly
feel when he saw such people?
What're you talking about?
You're not making any damn sense!
It matters not.
In any case, I decided that I would
stand in God's position, as God Himself.
This building is something of a garden
designed for me to conduct this test.
Those placed in Floor B7 are no more
than test subjects for observation.
In order to test and judge all
those people, I needed angels.
People who would not
hesitate to kill others.
Danny,
Eddie,
Cathy...
And you, Zack.
However, I thought that you might
be different from the others.
Huh?
You were pure and ignorant,
one who knew nothing but killing.
That is precisely why I
decided to make you an angel.
An angel?
But you violated the rules of this
place and sacrificed yourself
in an attempt to get out of here.
What, so you really do want to kill me?!
Listen to me!
Before, you only wanted to get outside.
But now, you want to get
outside with Rachel Gardner.
Am I wrong?
So what if I do?!
Why did you change?
Because...
What the hell are you doing,
just waltzing up like that?
Actually... I want to ask a favor.
Huh?
I want you to...
Kill me... please.
Smile? How?
Just smile, damn it!
You really did awesome back there.
What did I do?
I'm talking about when you
shot that insane bitch.
It felt great.
Yeah.
Still, I'm going to do it.
I want to sew up your belly for you.
Huh?
She's...
No... Never mind!
Very well.
I simply wanted to find out
what made you that way.
In other words, the two of you became
my new subjects of observation.
Either way, I still don't get it!
Oh, that matters not.
I don't expect you to understand.
Besides, my observation is not yet complete,
so the answer will not come so soon.
You're saying you've seen everything, priest?
I want to see what actions
the two of you take,
what you are trying to become,
and what you truly are.
Huh?
If that displeases you, I apologize.
Your apology doesn't do
me a damn bit of good!
In that case, allow me to lend you some aid.
The assignment Danny gave you
is not at all suited to you.
But first, let me ask you one thing.
How did you feel when Rachel
Gardner called you "God"?
What's with all you people?
You're creeping me out.
To me, it's all just a pain in the ass.
You all just look like a bunch of idiots.
I see.
Don't "I see" me! Tell me
what I should do next!
Enter the room above us.
That door won't open!
You need the plate.
Huh?
Just place the plate with the
resident's name on it onto the door.
So where is it?
How...
I guess you didn't know.
There are cameras set up here, too.
Zack!
He's still alive, I see.
It's even more of a mess than my room.
Clean this up, damn it.
Is that... Ray?
It's amazing that he's made it so far!
He's getting closer and closer, Rachel.
Perhaps I underestimated Zack.
Who knew he was capable of this?
You're cruel.
It doesn't matter what you say about me.
No one can stop it now.
It's only a matter of time
before Zack learns everything.
What... do you mean?
Once he enters that room...
It's got letters on it.
They're the same letters!
So that's it. I knew they looked familiar!
These letters are Ray's name!
So this room must be...
When Zack goes into that room,
he'll find out everything!
Zack, don't! Don't go in that room!
You can't hide it forever.
You know I'm right.
This is her room?
This stuff's all fake.
...this house, where police
responded to a report from locals
to discover the bodies
of Mr. and Mrs. Gardner.
The bodies were riddled with both
knife wounds and bullet holes,
leading to the conclusion
that they were murdered.
About a week had passed since their deaths,
and the physical damage was severe.
The bodies had been unnaturally
sewn together with thread.
Sewn together with thread?
The couple's daughter, Rachel Gardner,
was found unharmed near their bodies.
She was escorted to safety,
but her behavior suggests a
state of confusion, which—