Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Rukia Kuchiki is guilty of
first-degree offenses
and will be executed in 25 days
at the Central Execution Grounds.
That is the final decision
of the Soul Society.
You were very calm,
Captain of Squad 6.
Well done, well done.
Such calmness in the wake
of your sister's execution…
You are indeed a role model
for Soul Reapers, Captain.
Don't be ridiculous.
You and the Captain of Squad 9 are
the only Soul Reapers
who would fret over dying.
You think so?
Now what would two Captains
without their aides want with me?
Oh, we were just...
concerned that the Captain of Squad 6
would be feeling low because
his sister was about to be executed.
Our family lineage is
none of your concern.
So you're not upset, right?
Criminals are such
a bother to the nobles.
My, my… how unusual for a commoner
to understand
the subtleties of nobles.
Not really. I've always been
the sensitive one since I was a kid.
How about this?
Just to show my sensitivity,
I’d even offer to chop off the
criminal's head, before the execution.
I wasn't aware that at your present level
you could fell a person's head.
Want to try me?
You want to?
– Forgive us, Captain of Squad 6.
– Hey! Ichimaru!
– I never intended to offend you in any way.
– Let go! Why you--!
We'll be going now.
My regards to your sister.
H-Hey!
Whoa! You're all right, Tessai!
I mean, Mr. Tessai.
I'm not all right!
My glasses are in terrible shape!
But you're okay, right?
Oh well, keep those glasses
on even if they're cracked.
The owner drew his sword,
and it's getting very interesting.
Can't miss this one.
Not bad, even with that
wisp of a sword!
Oh, you flatter me!
But that doesn't mean
I'll go easy!
Fine with me! Dammit!
Hey! Wait a minute!
Hold on a minute!
I thought the Zanpaku-to was
the only sword
that could kill Soul Reapers
and Hollows.
He pulled that sword from his cane.
It can't be a Zanpaku-to.
Then even if he did get me,
it wouldn't hurt me--!
You let down your guard.
"He's not a Soul Reaper,
so it can't be a Zanpaku-to."
"So I can't get hurt even
if he cuts me." Right?
You are so naïve.
Wake up!
Benihime…
This is a Zanpaku-to,
totally authentic.
Wake up, Benihime!
Roar, Zabimaru!
You can't even ask the name
of your Zanpaku-to! A guy like you…
Zanpaku-to’s…name?
Yes…
Each Zanpaku-to has a name.
And this is...her name.
Let's go…
Benihime!
I compliment you for not running away
and countering my sword
with that broken one.
That's some courage.
However…
Benihime isn't so kind that
she'd let a sword like that stop her.
Dammit!
No way! No way can that be!
He cut my Zanpaku-to!
Weren't you told?
Your sword is big.
But that's all.
There’s no concentration of
spiritual energy in it.
It just distends and holds its shape.
That's why I can...
cut it easily like that.
Now you don't have a sword.
Will you still attack me with that?
C'mon, you just have
to knock my hat off.
You can do it with that hilt.
However, it won't be just
courage or guts that's necessary.
Let me just warn you…
If you still intend to fight me
with that toy…
I will kill you!
Huh?!
I'm gonna die! I'll really be killed!
Pathetic!
What am I?
Why am I running?
Is that all I was?
Is that the extent of
my determination?
Disgusting!
I'm disgusted with myself!
I'm so…
– helpless!
– You are so…helpless.
Mister…
Why do you run, Ichigo?
You haven't called me yet.
Look ahead, Ichigo.
You should be able to hear it now.
It is fear that makes
you shut your ears.
There is only one enemy,
and only one you.
What is there to fear?
Hey, what's going on?
Both of them stopped.
Abandon your fears!
Look ahead!
Go forward!
Never stop!
If you retreat,
you'll only grow old.
If you fear, you will die!
Call it out! My name is…!
Zangetsu!
W-What's going on now?!
What's that Zanpaku-to…?
There's no hilt or hand guard.
It's not even shaped
like a proper sword!
The other one was better!
Well now…
Since you have your Zanpaku-to,
shall we start
Lesson Three in earnest?
Sorry, Mr. Urahara…
Please dodge it.
Yes?
I don't think…
I have it mastered yet!
Wake up, Benihime!
Without this Shield of Blood Mist…
I'd have lost an arm.
Oh boy…
My hat's torn, too.
But…
I didn't think you'd do it in
one swing…
Ichigo…
You are one frightening kid.
Lesson Three cleared!
All right. It’s complete.
Thank you, Sensei.
You did it!
Terrific, Chad! You did it! Great!
You idiot!
Know your limits!
Look at the panic you've caused!
Now run away from the back.
All right!
But how unexpected…
that they could awaken
their powers in such a short time…
Chad has fallen down the stairs!
What's going on?
Aug 1, 6:30pm
After completing my training
at Urahara Shop,
I was told to stay at home while
they prepare to open the gate
to the Soul Society, but…
And here we are at
the long-awaited Fireworks Festival!
You're so excited.
Of course! How can you not be?!
Right, everyone?!
Absolutely, young 'un!
Not only that, I have special seats
that I've saved since seven this morning!
Shall we go over there?
No kidding! Right on!
Terrific!
Sometimes you're useful!
And how about you
cute ladies over there?
We’ll be there later.
All right!
Let's all go!
Let's go!
Geez, oh well… I guess I'll join them.
Sorry Tatsuki, it's always like this.
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
I know. Don't worry.
I'll catch up later.
Hurry and go.
Everyone is so energetic.
I'll say. It's tiring sometimes.
Tatsuki, does your hand hurt?
Huh? No, not at all.
Although, if I think about how this
caused me to lose first place,
it does hurt a bit.
But second place in
the Inter-High Tournament means
you're the second strongest
high school girl in Japan!
You're amazing, Tatsuki.
Hardly.
Oh yes…You're amazing!
It's been such a long time
since we last came here.
We only come in autumn each year.
Did I tell you?
My brother had this terrific knack
for catching red dragonflies on his fingers.
He'd point his fingers to the sky
and immediately,
a dragonfly would land.
It was like magic and
I loved to watch him.
That's why I wanted to be able
to do that…
But I couldn't…
This time, I'll protect you.
You're visiting relatives
from next week?
Huh? Yes.
Ichigo said he's going on
a trip next week, too.
Oh, yes…
I couldn't be first…
Huh?
But I've never regretted trying.
Even if it doesn't turn out well,
there are things you discover
just by doing your best.
So…so…
Once you've decided,
go forward and do it.
And in exchange…I'll…
I'll be waiting here…so…
So...
Fantastic!
Terrific!
Look at the sky!
It's so pretty.
Aug. 8, 1:00am
Let's see.
This should do it.
In seven days, at 1:00am,
leave your window open and wait.
I'm getting bad vibes all over…
Nice breeze…
W-What is that?!
What's happening?
Please come to the front
of Urahara Shop immediately.
W-What the hell is he doing?!
This looks like a dying message
at a murder scene!
I hope it comes off!
What's this… P.S.?
P.S.
If you thought this was
"like a dying message"
or something common like that...
you have no sense of humor!
Shut up!
Well, Yuzu, Karin…Dad…
Good morning!
Ichigo!
Dodging that attack…
– you ARE my son, after all.
– What the hell are you up to?!
B-Before you leave,
I want to give you this.
What is this amulet…so dirty.
How dare you call it dirty!
Your mother gave it to me long ago!
It is filled with luck
and divine grace!
W-What're you doing?!
I can't take this!
Damn right!
Who'd give it to you?!
Who?!
I'm just going to lend it
to you during your trip.
After you return, give it back!
Here! What do you say?!
You give it back, you hear?!
I'll shave if you lose it!
Oh…yeah…
I'm off then.
Right!
I'm a Soul Reaper.
Slaying a Hollow does
not mean killing it.
Wasn't it a Hollow...
that killed your mother?
So many things have happened.
You're just a human!
How dare you grab
my brother like that?!
And now…
You will die anyway…
so stay there and live
even one more second longer.
I won't let it be like
it never happened.
Oh, Ichigo!
Right on time!
Good, good.
Chad…why are you here?
Rukia Kuchiki once saved me.
I'm going, too.
Huh? What?!
What? You didn't hear?
Ishida…?!
No way will I remain defeated
by those Soul Reapers.
I'm going, too.
Huh?!
Now we're all here.
Orihime!
Please look after me!
Huh?! Hey! What's going on?!
Pretty slow on the up-take,
aren’t you?
Yoruichi…
Kid, don't tell me you didn't notice
the increase in the hidden powers
of these three.
While you were training
to regain your Soul Reaper power,
these three were also training
in their own way.
Instead of criticizing,
bow your head and thank them.
A...
A cat just spoke!
– He's not a cat. He's Yoruichi.
– A-A cat...!
I guess it is shocking, after all.
It’s his first time meeting him, I guess.
Yes, yes… that's it.
We can't keep talking outside.
Let's go inside.
Orihime…
What is it?
How much do you know?
I mean…it's going to
be dangerous.
I promised Tatsuki that
I'd go with you. And…
I promised to return.
W-Wow! All this space
beneath the shop!
This is so neat…
it's like a secret base!
Really?
What…
What a wonderful reaction!
I, Tessai, am deeply moved.
Don’t mention it.
All right, your attention please!
Here we go!
This is the gate that leads
to Soul Society.
It's known as Senkaimon,
which is written, "Tunnel World Gate."
Now listen very carefully. Before that…
– It's so easy to come out.
– Hey, warn me, at least!
So Ichigo is no longer inside Ichigo?
Of course not!
Don't talk like I'm not here!
Let's continue.
This gate has
a layer of Reishihenkanki,
Spirit-particle Conversion Machine
on top of a normal Senkaimon.
Spirit-particle… Conversion Machine?
Yes.
As you already know,
the Soul Society is a world of spirits.
It is impossible to enter that
world unless you have the form of a spirit.
However, only Ichigo,
as a Soul Reaper, can cross through.
So we will use the Henkanki
to convert you into spirits.
In other words…
Even without extracting our spirits,
by going through this gate…
Correct.
You will be able to enter
the Soul Society like that.
Okay, got it!
– Let's...!
– However...!
The time that we have
to open the gate and
connect it to the Soul Society is…
four minutes.
I-Is that enough time?!
Normally, it would be impossible.
What?!
It's a reckless idea to start with.
I'll do my very best and
hold it for four minutes.
If you can't cross over in that time…
you will be trapped forever between
the Soul Society and this world.
W-What should we do?
Go forward.
I told you that the heart
and soul are connected.
The important thing is
what you feel in your heart
and the will to move it forward.
I will be your guide.
Go forward…
Only those who can
do that can follow me.
Are you babbling in
your sleep or what?
That's why we're here!
You understand, kid,
that if you fail, you cannot return.
So I just have to win, right?
Exactly.
Are you ready?
Run in the instant it opens.
Right!
Let's do it!
I'm counting on you…
Ichigo.
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
W-What is that?!
– It's a mountain.
– It's a whale!
No, it's a gatekeeper giant!
Well, there you have it.
Kurosaki, you handle him.
– Go for it!
– You can do it!
You're the man!
Okay. Huh?
Err...I guess I am!