Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
One after another,
Barragan's Fracciones were defeated
by the efforts of Captain Komamura
and the lieutenants.
Nirgge, who fought Omaeda,
also fell to Omaeda's
speedy movements
that were contrary
to his appearance.
The remaining Fracciones,
Ggio Vega took his
Resureccion form, Tigre Estoque,
and gradually pushed
Soi Fon into a corner.
What is this? You're in the way.
How'd you appear all of a sudden?
Blow away.
Who told you to come
and rescue me?
I wanted to observe the strength
of an Arrancar's Resurreccion.
Don't…Don't mock me!
Look you! I'm going to show you
what true strength is!
Behold! This is Tigre Estoque's
actual battle form!
Tigre Estoque Sable!
Sorry.
I said my Suzumebachi
kills in two stings,
but you probably felt
only one, didn't you?
Damn…it.
Here I come again!
Haineko!
I told you, it's no use!
I can block an attack of
this level with Haineko…
Now how do I use it to attack?
Excuse me.
You're wide open!
Looks like Soi Fon and Omaeda
took care of their opponents.
Matsumoto seems to also
be struggling.
What are you thinking?
Nothing that concerns you.
Worried about your subordinate?
If you're going to fight me,
concentrate.
If you don't…
You'll die.
Don't underestimate me!
Not bad.
So you do know
how to use a sword.
If I have a choice,
I wouldn't use it too much.
Oh there you go again.
Good grief.
Say, mind if I rest over there?
Huh?
What sort of nonsense is that?
She's a total loser.
Three against one is
no contest from the start.
I won't hold it against you,
so why don't you call over
that kid over there.
Three against two would make it
more of a match, you know.
I just told you, it's no contest!
That won't work on me!
You're no competition
even against just me!
W-What?!
Y-You're!
Hinamori!
Is something the matter,
Captain Aizen?
No, it's nothing.
Nothing worth mentioning.
Your Spiritual Pressure
wavered for a moment just now.
What're you talking about?
Something happened.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hinamori…
Why did you come here?
Are you…okay now?
Yes.
Don't worry, Rangiku.
It's true I've come here as
the lieutenant of Squad 5
and wearing the insignia
of lieutenant…
But I've come in
the sense of being
"the one who looks after
her squad members."
I did not come as
Captain Aizen's subordinate.
That man is now…
the Soul Society's…
enemy.
Yes, he is.
If you understand, that's fine.
Hinamori…
Let's go!
– You might not have realized it…
– Right!
But just now, you said
"Captain" Aizen.
Be careful, Hinamori.
Are you done with
your boring conversation?
Tobiume!
I see.
So that explosion earlier
was the power of her sword.
That's quite good.
You appear to be a lieutenant,
but…
Two lieutenants aren't much
different than three against one.
Mila Rose! Sun-Sun!
Let's finish this!
Let's take care
of this silly battle
and get back to
Master Halibel!
Quit giving the orders, you fool.
You're the one
wasting the most time.
But…
I agree with your opinion.
See you! Holstein!
What…the hell is this?!
Didn't you wonder?
How I managed to make
my Tobiume
hone in on you the first time?
You're all considerably
stronger than I am.
In order to approach you
without you noticing me
to a distance where
Tobiuume can strike you,
I had to approach you
by using Kido
to conceal my physical presence
and Spiritual Pressure.
That's why I used the opportunity
to set a Kido net around Rangiku
while I made myself
physically hidden.
I never imagined
that all three of you
would be ensnared by it,
though.
Damn kid!
Snap, Tobiume.
Oh?
Oh, wow!
They're really going at it
over there.
What do you say, Mr. Espada?
Isn't it time we got rumbling,
as well?
Don't want to.
Don't say you don't want to.
Where's the love?
You say you want to rumble,
but you're not fighting
like you mean it, either.
You haven't even drawn
your second sword.
The short sword is used in places
where it's difficult to fight
with the long sword.
They're not meant
to be used together.
Oh really?
For someone who says that…
you've been switching your sword
from between hands as you fight.
And I'm not sure if you're
doing it subconsciously,
but your spacing is
a bit closer to the target
when you swing with your left hand
rather than your right.
You carry two swords,
one long and one short.
You're dual handed, with each side
having a different spacing.
And yet you claim you're
not a double sword user?
Is that even possible?
You got me.
I thought I had evened out
the spacing between left and right.
You have sharp eyes.
How scary of you.
And you can dodge!
Incredible!
You instantaneously adjusted
your spacing just now!
I couldn't tell that time!
Why thank you!
Aren't you going to
fight with them?
Of course not.
Two against one would be unfair.
Is this the time to be
saying such a thing?
Stark is strong, you know.
That old man is going to die.
He'll be fine!
Kyoraku is strong, too!
Don't say I didn't warn you.
He's really going to die.
You'll regret it.
Thank you. You're very kind.
I'll pray that that doesn't happen.
Is that so?
Then, shall we go at it, then?
That won't do!
Huh?!
You're still a child!
Fact is, you being
at this battleground
is not a good thing.
Child?! Me?!
Look, you! Age means
nothing to an Arrancar.
I know. But no means no!
To me, you are a child,
and a girl, at that.
I cannot fight you!
If you still selfishly
insist on fighting,
I'll force you to go home
if I have to!
You should go home and
play with a ball or something.
Fine. I get it.
If you're going to mock me
to that extent…
Let's get it on!
Oh boy.
Pretty good!
Isn't it about time
you got serious?
I told you,
I didn't want to get serious.
Then I want to ask you,
Mr. Espada.
What is it?
If I draw both swords,
will you get serious?
Give me a break.
You're entirely
strong enough as it is.
Drawing both would be a problem.
I see.
Then I have no choice
but to draw both.
So that's how it's going to be.
Are you all right, Hinamori?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It was the first time I used
that combination of techniques, so…
It's all right. That was awesome.
That was Hado 12:
"Fushibi" wasn't it?
It's the first time I've seen one
that was this wide and complex.
Yes.
I wove Shakkaho together
with Fushibi,
then covered it with
Bakudo 26: Kyokko
to make it invisible,
before carefully stretching it and
laying it out in a net pattern.
Incredible.
To be able to combine several
of these Kido in her own way.
This child
acquired such abilities.
It was difficult to concentrate
under these conditions,
but I'm glad it went well.
I'm glad.
She's in better shape
than I thought.
Thrust upwards, Cierva!
Eat Apart, Leona!
Strangle to Death, Anaconda.
That can't be…
I didn't think we could
defeat them with that, but…
They're practically unscarred.
When they do Resurreccion,
their injuries heal.
That's how they are!
Damn.
Get carried away, will you!
Here it comes!
Leave it to me!
It's huge!
Tobiume!
Haineko!
I'm sorry, Rangiku.
Just as I feared,
their strength has increased
several levels more than before.
If we're not careful, we'll take
the full brunt of their attacks.
I understand.
I will take that into consideration
and deal with them!
Deal with us?
You brats really know
how to get on my nerves.
Don't go saying things that
sound so full of yourself!
Hold it!
What good is it going to do to
get even more angry with them?
She's right.
Aren't you the one
who's getting
carried away saying
things like that?
Shut up!
Why do I have to get irritated
by you guys as well?!
Stop making things
more complicated,
and just shut up,
Sun-Sun
This could get troublesome
if it keeps going.
Then what do you
suggest we do?
We'll use "that" to take care
of them in one swoop.
Guess we have no choice.
To think we have to take "that"
out on the likes of them.
Quimera Parco.
W-What…
What is that?
What is that?!
Rangiku,
let's counter that monster!
Did you come up with an idea?
Yes. If we skillfully combine Kido,
I think we can create a monster
every bit as gross as that one!
Absolutely not!
In today's segment,
we'll introduce you to Kazeshini.
Reap, Kazeshini.
Shuhei Hisagi's
Zanpakuto Kazeshini
takes the form of two sickles
connected with a chain
when released.
Apparently, even Hisagi himself
does not know how they will move
when he swings them around
and throws them to attack.
Hisagi dislikes
the form of Kazeshini,
saying it reaps lives.
I've already proved that
swinging it around indiscriminately
results in injury.
Don't say that
like you're boasting.