That was a restless night…
Okay.
Let’s begin!
Hey Riruka. He’s all yours!
Yeah, yeah…
Hey, just a minute.
What?
Are you training me in that box again?
What do you mean, “again”?!
Besides, it’s been
upgraded for you this time!
You see?
This adorable birdcage will be
your training ground for today!
I can’t help but think
that going from a dollhouse
to a birdcage is a downgrade…
Ginjo!
What’s the purpose of
this training, anyway?
What is it you want me to do?
You’re right, I haven’t
given you a proper explanation.
Let me explain then.
Do you know what the definitive
difference is between you and us?
As Riruka once said, our group
is comprised only of people who
were able to use Fullbring since birth,
or acquired the power without realizing it.
Unlike us, you must acquire
Fullbring through your own will.
But…
Unlike us, who acquired our powers
naturally, Fullbring for you
is obviously not something we
can simply tell you to call up.
That is why it’s necessary to drive you
to physical and mental extremes
in order to awaken the power in you.
It is the only way we can help you ultimately
regain your Soul Reaper powers…
Do you understand?
Yeah…guess I have no choice.
All right, then be a good boy and…
But look…
What now?! More complaints?!
I don’t have time.
Training like the last time
isn’t going to cut it.
If you want to awaken my powers,
let me fight one of you!
Don’t be ridiculous!
You were just barely able
to do Fullbring last time!
Know your limits!
At your level now,
Mr. Chicken is plenty!
Even allowing you a huge
benefit of the doubt,
sending in Mr. Pork Mark II is
the best I’m willing to do!
Him again?
What do you mean, “again”?!
Listen, you’ve only just
become able to do Fullbring,
so raising the level won’t…
I realize that.
But that’s how I’ve
gotten stronger until now.
This time is no different…
I don’t get it!
I’m warning you, so
why’re you in such a rush?
Because there are guys I want to protect.
I can’t stand around doing nothing.
You look convinced.
Shush!
Can’t stand around doing nothing, eh?
You might be right.
Shall we ratchet up the training, then?
But understand…if you
die, don’t blame us.
Yeah.
Hold it.
Mr. Tsukishima?
What is it, Shishigawara?
What do you plan on doing next?
Next?
You know…
About going after Ichigo
Kurosaki or Yasutora Sado…
Geez…
You distracted me just at the good part.
I’m…sorry.
They go to the same school, right?
Huh?
What?!
I’m talking about Orihime
Inoue, who I met last time,
Yasutora Sado, and Ichigo Kurosaki.
Oh, yes, yes they all do.
Shishigawara.
I need you to do me a favor.
Will you do it?
Kugo, are you serious?
Yeah, it’s what Ichigo wants.
I’m not asking about what he wants.
Huh?
This guy wants to fight us?!
I’m against it!
I have no intention of helping him.
What’s gotten into you?
I’m against it, as well.
You, too, Giriko?
I can understand why you want to rush,
but the faster we progress with training,
the more intense the strain on Mr. Kurosaki.
If we attempt to force the
awakening of his Fullbring,
his Fullbring might go out of control.
I think all of us here except Mr. Kurosaki
understand what that means…
it means death.
The out-of-control soul of the object
will drive the user’s own
soul out of his physical body.
I think we should take our time
and do this one step at a time.
You have to admit, he makes a valid point.
All that doesn’t matter!
Do you remember...
what Kugo said?
We want to rid ourselves
of this loathsome power.
There isn’t a person among us
who uses their power with joy.
At least I don’t.
That’s enough, Jackie.
You want to protect something, you say?
Noble words,
but if you ask me, you’re
nothing but a fool
who does things for his ego without
considering the danger to his own life.
It upsets me just to use Fullbring.
I will not agree to use it
for this naive fool’s sake!
Oh well, then…
Hey Yukio.
No thanks.
But I haven’t said anything yet.
You’re going to tell me to
bring Jackie back, aren’t you?
Why not let her do as she wants?
Kutsuzawa.
Sooner or later, we’ll
need Jackie’s help.
I know.
Give me a moment, please.
You heard it, Ichigo.
Sorry, but we’ll have to do
things a step at a time.
Riruka!
Do it!
This time, Giriko’s powers take
effect in 10 minutes, so be careful.
Yeah.
I permit you!
You again, kid?
Hi.
Things won’t be so easy like the last time!
This is my pal, Bone-Skin.
It’s not Bone-Skin!
That’s it!
I’m chickened out!
I mean, ticked off!
Damn cocky…
Uh, hi, I’m Mr. Chicken.
Nice to meet you…
You prefer coffee?
He wants me back?
Yes.
You understand that too,
don’t you, Ms. Jackie?
You’re okay with it, Giriko?
To helping him, you mean?
No.
Your powers…
Have you heard this story?
A certain old man had
an old wound on his leg.
He could predict sudden changes in
the weather by how much it hurt,
and as a result, he never
got wet from the rain.
The point is: when you get to be my age,
you learn to live even with
things that once disgusted you.
Can I become like you, too?
That…I don’t know…
Do you regret it?
I don’t know…
It’s just that I can’t
get myself to like my powers.
Oh yeah…
You did have that technique, kid.
Be careful, Bone-Skin.
My name’s not Bone-Skin, you damn pig!
I’m positive I was cut.
But when I came to, there was no wound…
And for a split second, I thought
of that person as a “friend.”
If what Inoue said is true,
does that mean the power that
the enemy who is after
Ichigo, and us, possesses
is the ability to manipulate memories?
If the person who slashed Ishida and the
person who slashed Inoue
are one and the same...
I’ll try confirming it with Ishida…
First Ishida, then Inoue. Now I’m next?
Who’s there?!
Do I fight?
No…I can’t afford to
be the next one cut down…
Kugo.
What is it?
Don’t you feel it? This Spiritual Pressure.
You mean Chad’s?
Ginjo! What did you just say?!
Did something happen to Chad?!
If you don’t pay attention,
you’ll regret it!
Why’d you say that?
You know it’s going to
disrupt his concentration!
Shut up.
Ginjo!
I’ll tell you, so calm down!
Someone’s Spiritual Pressure
is closing in on Chad!
You mean, it’s?!
Hey, Ginjo!
Stop the training!
Let me out of here!
Can’t…
Right now, concentrate on your training!
We can’t let you out of there
until this training is done!
This is no time to be telling me that!
Chad is…
Are you telling us that Chad
would be defeated so easily?
That’s not what I’m saying!
Ichigo, what is it that you want to protect?
Is it the lives of your friends?
What? Are they arguing again?
Or is it the bond you have with them?
Seems like it.
If Chad were weak, I’d rush
over to him this minute.
But right now, we should
do what we need to do!
Isn’t that all there is to it?
I’m sure that’s what Chad wants, as well.
Didn’t I tell you?
He’s training because he
wants to protect something.
Now, Chad’s in imminent danger,
so he wants to rush to help him.
It’s all about his wanting
to play the hero of justice.
What?!
So you leave here and go to him, what then?!
You can barely use Fullbring,
you could rush to his side,
but you won’t be any help.
I don’t want anything to do
with a hero wannabe like you!
I won’t be of any help, you say?
Maybe you’re right.
But I’ve regained some fighting
power, if only a very little.
If I just stay here without
using my powers to help…
It will leave me with nothing but regret!
Regret, huh?
Fine.
If you want to go, then go.
I could care less.
But…
If you want to get out
of there, do it yourself.
If only it were that easy…
Is it time?
Yes.
“Time Tells No Lies.”
Damn! Not again!
Guess this means I can’t do a
thing unless I defeat these guys.
Damn!
It feel just like Getsugatensho, but
it’s actual power isn’t even close!
With such a lame weapon like
that, what’s there to regret?
Shut up!
The sword’s not the same as
the one I always fight with!
I get it.
I was throwing my attacks
too soon since this thing
doesn’t have a blade.
If I charge it more with my Spiritual
Pressure like I did with Getsuga…
I’ll give it a try!
Hey! Don’t break it!
He produced this much
destructive power just by
getting a small hang of it.
Amazing…
I’m out!
Sorry, gotta go.
Wait.
Yeah, I’m okay…
I was followed, but I
managed to lose the tail.
Right now, there’s no indication
that I’m being followed.
I see…that’s good.
Anyway, don’t worry about me.
Continue with your training.
Yeah, okay.
Sorry.
Strange, though…
I was followed, but that’s all.
There was absolutely no sign
that I was about to be attacked.
What the hell was that?
Looks like it went well.
Good work.
Sir!
Okay, let’s keep going!
All right, this time you’ll
be entering this fish tank!
Got it.
You’re awfully obedient this time.
Don’t you have anything to say?
Like, “You’re making me
get into that thing again?!”
Nope! Just do it.
Fine.
Ichigo.
I permit you!
Welcome.
Oh, so it’s you.
Not the plushie this time?
Now that we know you
don’t need them anymore.
I believe I haven’t
introduced myself to you yet.
I’m Jackie Tristan.
It’s nice to meet you.
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Let’s get this thing started!
Nice. I like the look on your face.
Aren’t you going to attack?
You haven’t brought out your Fullbring yet.
So naive…
This may be training, but
it’s still a fight.
You have to consider me your enemy.
Would you say the same
thing on a battlefield?
I probably would.
Unbelievable.
Fine then.
I’ll start.
“Dirty Boots”!
You ruined my birdcage!
I’ll pay for it later,
isn’t that good enough?
No! That was my favorite!
Then what should I do?
Oh, fine…
I’ll forgive you if you go eat
donuts with me just this once!
Donuts?
Wait, uh, donuts?!
Okay, I’ll be going now.
Go ahead. We don’t need you anymore.
Hey young lady!
Mind if I take one of these plushies with me?
You’re into girlie things like that?
Oh come on!
You can have one!
Now get out of here! You give me the creeps!
Thanks, young lady!
Look, I brought Mr. Pork!
Mr. Pork’s occupation:
Nursery school teacher