Seethe, Sumitsukigasa!
Are you planning to use
your power to rule the Soul Society?
Rule?
You still believe that nonsense?
My objective is to destroy
the Soul Society.
What?!
I can’t afford to waste any more time.
Die.
Ichigo!
His Hollowfication is undone!
Ichigo, are you all right?!
Rukia?
Impossible.
What just happened?
Kurosaki!
Inoue!
Take Ichigo and get away from here!
No, I can’t leave here.
What are you saying?!
That wasn’t Kageroza.
At that moment, my
consciousness went blank.
It’s me.
Yes, sir.
I need more fusion stabilizer.
Prepare it immediately.
Right away.
Fusion stabilizer?
So his fusion isn’t permanent yet.
Seems that way.
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Ignoring you was a mistake.
Although your Spiritual
Pressure is gone,
I cannot allow you to live.
Renji! Ishida! Chad!
Step aside.
Sorry, we’re not so obedient
as to do as our enemy says.
We won’t let you have your way.
There aren’t any idiots here who’d
hand over a friend to an enemy!
Friend?
You still say that?
You’re fools spilling your own
blood for the sake of others.
Are friends defined by the
worthless sacrifices one makes?
Then go ahead and disappear
right this moment!
Byakuya!
So close...
Are you okay?!
Hado Number 63!: Raikoho!
They’re keeping the pressure on.
Why did you take such
a risk to protect me?
Damn, they have us surrounded!
This is bad! The captains are...
Captain Kuchiki needs medical attention!
Oh no you don’t!
They’re not going to miss an
opportunity to hit us while we’re down.
Their strategy is to switch
in and out at will.
If one of us is injured and slowed down,
that is the person they attack.
But there’s no way
to get away from here.
Who cares!
All we need to do is kill off
the rest of them one by one!
The Reigai are trying to
separate and isolate us!
Shut up!
I hate little details!
Agreed!
What should we do?
If we lose even one combatant,
they'll use that opportunity
to take us out.
One small mistake,
and we could get ourselves annihilated.
Seethe! Sumitsukigasa!
El Directo!
Tsuginomai! Hakuren!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Oh yes.
If nothing else, I should’ve
been more wary of your weapon.
It weakens the bonds between reishi.
Exactly.
You’re not the only one
that can absorb reisihi.
Interesting.
You’re going to challenge
me by absorbing my reishi?
Whatever the battle,
I can’t see you emerging victorious
when you underestimate
the power of my friends.
What are you trying to say?
You’ll find out soon enough.
Pathetic.
What?!
Bakudo Number 4!
Hainawa!
Now, Ishida!
You can no longer escape.
What do you say we have
a contest of endurance?
What?!
I had you figured out a long time ago.
You’re able to create a
containment field by placing
those weapons in five corners.
To activate the technique,
it must consume the reishi
stored within its hilt.
You created the containment
as you attacked me,
but as you were doing that,
you failed to notice that I
used Sumitsukigasa to absorb
the reishi from your hilt.
Not knowing that, you
sacrificed your own allies.
In the end, that is all that your
so-called “friends” mean to you!
Oh I knew, all right.
I knew you’d see through
my Sprenger attack
and that you’d absorb the
reishi from my Seeleschneider.
However.
It’s over, Kageroza!
Don’t worry.
We’re going to imprison him like
this without triggering the explosion.
If we can continue to drain
the Spiritual Pressure
from the wound on his back where
the reishi bond was weakened,
it should be able to undo
his fusion with Kujo.
Don’t underestimate me!
Hajokuri!
W-What the hell is that?!
It’s swallowing up
Sprenger’s reishi?!
Hajokuri turns everything around it
into reishi and takes it in, then.
Die, Substitute Soul Reaper!
Dammit!
They won’t initiate an attack.
And why is that?
If we keep a tight formation,
they can’t use a strategy of
switching off on opponents to disrupt us.
I don’t think any of them will risk
sacrificing themselves
to break our formation.
So you threw yourself at them
in order to test their tactics?
You sure about that?
If one of you leave this place...
What would happen once our
side outnumbers yours?
This is great.
Let’s have a test of wills.
Dammit
What?
What’s going on?
Something’s strange.
Stop…stop it.
Stop it.
That was!
Is the fusion starting to break down?
Stop it!
Stop what you’re doing!
Nozomi!!
Ichigo!
Nozomi! I’ll get you out of there!
Don’t let that bastard
Kageroza swallow you up!
Ichigo…
Please…
Kill me.
What’re you talking about?!
This Zanpakuto can kill him.
Do it while I hold him at bay!
Quickly!
You know I can’t do such a thing!
Please.
I’m begging you.
You all protected me.
Now.
it’s my turn to protect everyone.
I can’t!
We’re friends!
We will save you!
Renji!
Ichigo! Step away!
I should’ve killed you
when I had the chance!
Rukia! Renji!
Friends.
Tell me, Substitute Soul Reaper.
Why do you people use that word?
Why do you cling to that word
when your backs are against the wall?
Why?
Why do you fight this way?
What?!
Why do you separate us
and attack the one
isolated from the others?
I understand it as a tactic,
but it doesn’t seem
like a choice that you,
who should possess the same
pride we do, would make.
To distrust others, loathe
your fellow members,
and consider isolation a virtue.
That must be the true
nature of Kageroza.
What’s wrong? Can’t answer?
Ichigo…
You see!
Friends are meaningless!
A solitary life is the only
true validation of existence!
I organized an invasion force
without help from anyone.
That force, is about to annihilate
the 13 Court Guard Squads
that refused to give me my due.
By resurrecting myself as a Mod Soul,
I was able to acquire the true power of
the Zanpakuto that I could not
wield in my original form.
This is truly the ideal existence
of solitude that I have strived for!
Pathetic…
Haven’t you realized?
Mod Souls are based on a
Soul Reaper’s reishi.
Which means you can’t
create them all by yourself.
And beside, you couldn’t wield
your true power without Nozomi,
who you severed from yourself.
You just proved that you
couldn’t do a thing
without those around you!
No one can do anything all by himself!
Refusing to acknowledge that makes you
a damn fool!
Are you accusing that his nature
is affecting our style of fighting?
You’re not going to break our
solidarity using methods like that.
Shut up!
You’re.
Don’t…!
I’ll put off eliminating
you just a bit longer.
You can watch the moment Nozomi
becomes completely mine.
Then you can die.
You.
What is the meaning of this?!
It means this!
That voice… Kon?!
Stupid dummy.
You fell for it.,
What do you say to that?
Serves you damn right!
Stop it! You’re creeping us out!
Oh…That feels good.
How did you?!
You want to know?
Let’s see…
MAYURI
Kurotsuchi pretended to be killed.
URAHARA
Then he liquefied his body
and found Kageroza’s lab,
so together we defeated my imposter,
NEMU
then removed the pill
from the lieutenant,
KON
and replaced it with Kon’s pill.
That’s what Clogs said!
You have me to thank for everything!
For what?!
You didn’t do a thing!
Yeah I did!
Here!
It’s a Mod Soul with
your Spirit Energy!
I kept my promise, Ichigo!
Now it’s your turn!
Listen to you.
You sorry excuse for a Mod Soul.
You didn’t create me!
I’m better than the ones you created!
Don’t show them an opening.
I know.
Those same tactics won’t work again!
What is it with you guys.
I told you to keep outta this!
Sorry about that, Captain.
This might be our last battle.
Please allow us to die with you.
Our place of death has
already been decided, sir.
What?
Suit yourselves.
Well, I suppose it’d be nice
to have someone cover my back sometimes!
Working together in battle?
Now that’s really out of character.
When it comes to
protecting what we must,
we’ll use any means we can.
Protect what you must?
Are you referring to your pride?
No.
We have but one thing that we protect:
The Soul Society.
Hang on, Nozomi.
You won’t ever be alone again.
We promise
to save you!
Let’s show this bastard
the power of friendship!
Go! Ichigo!
Bankai!
Good job, Kon.
But weren’t you scared?
This was nothing, if it
means I could save you two!
Wow, Kon!
But you were scared a little, right?
No, really, I wasn’t scared at all!
I’m serious!
This didn’t scare me a bit!
Say, I have a suggestion.
If we have to, we could eviscerate him.
When we’re done, we could
use him for experiments.
The pervert owner’s in this too?!
So…
Will you help us?
Noooo!