I won't give you orders right now.
I won't ask any favors.
I'm just asking you this...
Is it okay with you?
No matter how dull the look on your face is,
it's damn hard to hold myself back.
I mean, if I could hold back,
I wouldn't be in this
situation to begin with.
Oh... I see...
So that's all I need to do.
But even I can't stand lies.
You get what I mean, don't you?
Good girl.
So c'mon, I'm begging you...
Don't let me kill you just yet.
It's not like before.
This isn't to keep myself alive.
It's for Zack's sake...
...that I can't let him kill me yet.
I have to run.
Zack's lost his mind because of the drugs.
A dead end...
Zack...
Hi!
I'm impressed you made it this far!
I'm so sorry I cut the party short
just when it was getting good.
This is the firing squad room, so I shot you.
Just look.
You two are surrounded
by lots and lots of guns.
With the push of a button,
I can make them all fire.
Isn't it amazing?
It was so delightful...
seeing the falling-out between you two.
You in particular, Zack, are what
I'd consider the ideal criminal!
The way you can't control your impulses,
no matter how you fight them,
is just fantastic!
Shut up!
Zack, what's wrong? Did the
drug make you go crazy?
You're going after the wrong person.
I'll kill you!
You're so silly.
I told you, you're going
after the wrong person.
Zack...
Stay away from me!
You see?
I thought the pain of being shot
had made you a bit more rational,
but just look at you.
You just can't...
hold yourself back, can you?
So, Rachel Gardner...
I'm giving you that.
That makes you two even, right?
Go on... try to kill each other!
And I'll give the survivor an
even more fantastic judgment!
What would the meaning of that be?
Oh, stop it. You really are a boring girl.
What's the point of trying
to find the meaning in it?
Do you expect anything to come of that?
Nothing is ever going to
come of a criminal's deeds.
So there's no need to search for a meaning.
This is today's main event.
Now, put on an entertaining show for me!
Well, if you're gonna shoot me, hurry it up!
What's this?
Could you be afraid
to pull the trigger?
You can't escape being a boring girl
with no interesting qualities?
Be quiet.
Even if you don't shoot, I can't hold back!
I won't shoot you.
Oh, really?
Well, I want to kill you so bad, it hurts!
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm letting you
kill me while I'm boring.
You're damn right!
I'm gonna feel like shit after this!
I said if you're gonna
shoot me, then shoot me!
You can't miss at this range!
Ask all you want, but my answer is the same.
I won't kill you.
That's my choice.
I'm fine with being killed by you.
But...
I won't let this turn out
the way that woman wants.
Because you and I...
...are not tools.
To kill and to be killed...
...are our own choices.
Don't start saying interesting things now!
Damn it, I can't hold back any longer!
Come on!
At least let me see you smile! Right now!
What a lousy smile.
Your eyes are totally dead.
But if it ever turns into a
real smile, it'll be awesome.
Just imagining killing you like that...
...is making me smile more than anyone else!
So big, I could just kill myself!
Zack!
What?!
Ugh, disgusting.
I was wrong to call you the ideal criminal!
Rachel Gardner is a failure as a criminal,
and Isaac Foster was such a fool,
he killed himself to satisfy his own desire!
I'm so disappointed!
You put a damper on my judgment.
You really are a supremely
boring girl, Rachel.
I don't need to hear that from you.
You don't have the right to talk back to me!
Passing judgment on you
isn't the least bit fun.
This is agony, Rachel!
If this had to happen, I wish
it would have been Zack.
He would have looked so much
better with a body full of holes.
I can't believe you couldn't
even pull the trigger.
You're a failure as a criminal.
How did you even make it this far?
How... did I...
Well, I have no choice now.
Oh, my goodness! You're alive!
How wonderful!
You're going to... kill Zack?
Yes!
Who else but me could pass judgment
on such a fantastic criminal?
Don't.
Oh?
And do you think you can shoot this time?
Go on, shoot me!
I said shoot me!
Oh, come on.
I guess you can't shoot after all.
Unfortunately, though,
that gun wasn't even loaded.
Not that a failure of a criminal like you
could have fired it, anyway.
But...
I'm a bit impressed by the attitude
it took to point that gun at me.
Bang!
Since you're alive,
I'll have to keep you that way so I can
punish you while you're full of life!
No. I won't let you kill Zack.
Because Zack is the only one...
...who can kill me.
Bang.
What?!
You brat!
That's a hell of a way to
show what you really are!
I love it!
I'm going to judge you,
you criminal little girl!
I'll judge you!
You can keep that unfazed look on your face,
and I'll judge you!
Shut the hell up.
Don't look so happy about being shot!
It made me want to kill you so damn bad
that it woke me right up!
No... way.
This is real!
Open your damn eyes!
Zack!
I have... to judge you.
I'm going... to judge you.
It's a lot quieter now.
Zack... Are you okay?
Huh?
My gut hurts like hell. What do you think?
You looked really happy when
you sliced open your own belly.
Huh?
Don't put me on the same level
as that sadomasochistic bitch.
I just thought it'd be
better than killing you
with that boring face, and
then getting killed by her.
Anyway, did you see that bitch's face?
Yeah.
It was so damn brilliant.
You were pretty good, too.
I feel a lot better now.
Really?
Yeah.
So relieved, the pain in my
gut doesn't even bother me.
Okay, let's go.
You can keep going?
Shut up.
You just worry about yourself.
Shit! Not again!
I think it'll open if I
mess with these devices.
Okay. Do it.
Huh? What's going on?
This is how she was making those
sounds and controlling the lights.
Seriously?
What a pain in the ass she was.
Yeah.
Here it is.
Good. Let's go.
"To open the door, give your name to God.
If there are no lies in your life,
give Him your true name.
But, God does not need the sinner."
Does that say something interesting?
No, not really.
Then why are you staring at it like that?
Sorry.
I'm done now. Let's go.
This looks familiar.
This was the first area we passed through.
She was getting all fanatical
this close to us?
I wanna kill her!
Oh. I guess we already did.
Yeah. She's dead.
Hey, so how do we get out of here?
Let's try there.
The wall is open...
Oh, so this is how the whole thing worked.
So how the hell do we open it?
You can't work it with those stupid machines?
I didn't see a switch
to operate the elevator.
There must be some way...
Yeah, well, it's best to
leave the thinking to you.
This indentation...
It said "give your name to God"
on the wall back there.
Aren't those the things we used
when we took the pictures?
They'd fit perfectly in this indentation.
"God does not need the sinner..."
It should work now.
Hey, there's still one more of those.
I'll discard this one.
You sure?
Yeah.
Looks like we don't need it.
Hey, Ray...
You really did awesome back there.
What did I do?
I'm talking about when you
shot that insane bitch.
It felt great.
Yeah.
Why did you come to this place, anyway?
Huh?
I saw someone get killed,
so I came for counseling.
The next thing I knew, I was
in a room with a blue moon.
Huh? I don't get it.
Also...
The gun you shot that woman with wasn't hers.
Where'd you get it?
It's mine.
Where were you even keeping that thing?
In my pouch, wrapped in a handkerchief.
Why the hell didn't you use
that to begin with, then?
I won't kill myself.
God wouldn't forgive me if I do.
That's not what I...
Besides, you're the one
who's going to kill me.
I can't tell if you're really
smart or really dumb.
Well, whatever.
Either way, you were right
to shoot her when you did.
Just remembering it makes me laugh.
Your timing was perfect.
You're in a good mood.
Kinda.
You are, too, aren't you?
Yeah.
We're here, Zack.
Zack?
Zack...
Zack!