Enrage! Ira!
Bug off!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Ulquiorra!
Pick it up. Let's finish this.
The entity that was
fighting earlier
was me in Hollowfication,
with no consciousness.
That wasn't me.
If we're to settle this,
I have to be in an identical condition to
you or we won't be evenly matched!
Fine.
If that is your wish,
then I will oblige.
So this is it...
Kill me.
I refuse.
What?
I said I don't want to!
This is...
This is no way to win!
To the very end, you just
won't do as I want...
Just when I was finally beginning
to become a bit interested
in you people.
Are you afraid of me,
girl?
I'm not afraid...
I see...
I see now.
In this palm...
is a "heart."
The heavy Spiritual Pressure above
the ceiling has disappeared...
Did Ichigo defeat him?
And here I was planning to help
him out after killing these guys...
I never expected him to die first.
This isn't enough at all.
I spent all this time sleeping and eating
to store up my Spiritual Pressure.
Killing these leftover scum won't
come close to using it!
He's gotten bigger again.
What is going on here?!
He's definitely different
from the time
I fought him in the
World of the Living.
Take a look...
His shoulder...
It's number ten.
Did you guys go up against an
Espada before coming here?
Yes.
There's no need to answer
if you don't want to.
I won't ask for the outcome.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't do any better.
At any rate, we overcame
those guys.
And that guy is the weakest
of them all.
Freaking out at his size
won't get us anywhere.
Let's quickly take care of him
and go pick up Ichigo.
Huh?
What're you jabbering about?!
Defeat me, you say?!
Scum like you?!
Yeah, that's right, you giant oaf!
Don't make me laugh!
Enrage!
Ira!
He's gonna get even bigger?!
What?!
His number is...
No way!
What is this...
What the hell is going on?!
Who ever said that the ten Espadas
were numbered one through ten?
What?!
Espadas are numbered
zero to nine.
I am the sole Espada
whose number changes
when I've accumulated power
and completely released.
I am Cero Espada Yammy Riyalgo!
Scatter!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Bug off!
Renji!
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai, Tsukishiro!
Oh no!
You scum!
El Muerte!
What?!
Did you get him?!
No...
You guys are trash, after all.
Damn monster...
What's the matter?
Is that all you've got?
Shut up! The real battle starts now!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
No matter how many times
you try, it's useless!
This is lame...
What?!
Now! Rukia! Sado!
Right!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
Tsuginomai
Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del Gigante.
Don't get carried away!
That can't be...
He's not even scratched?!
That's why I said it was useless!
You possess that level of strength,
and you're only number three?!
My level of strength?
I don't recall showing you the
extent of my strength yet.
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Is that all you've got?
Dammit!
Pathetic.
Ola Azul.
Dammit!
Pathetic.
Ola Azul.
That can't be...
All the Captains are...
You sure are strong!
You surprise me, man...
Is that so?
You kept parrying my sword,
without losing your hat,
nor ruffling your clothes.
You're much more surprising.
Ola Azul!
Damn you!
This is no contest.
Can't you even make me
budge from this spot?
Now then...
Which of you shall
I split in two first?
C-Captain...
What?
Isn't it about time?
For what?
You know...
For Gentei Kaijo! Gentei Kaijo!
We've held back long enough.
It's about time we did Gentei Kaijo
and blow this old goat away!
Oh, what's that? You still have
a trick up your sleeves?
Damn right, you old goat!
If we do Gentai Kaijo, you'll be
gone in two seconds!
Sounds interesting.
Go ahead and try it.
We weren't looking for your approval
to do it! Right, Captain?!
We can't.
I beg your pardon?
A Spirit Restriction Seal is...
automatically secured onto
our bodies when
a captain-class person passes
through the Senkaimon.
Its purpose is to limit our
Spiritual Pressure to extreme levels,
so that the immense Spiritual Pressure
of captain-class individuals
does not unnecessarily affect
spirits in the World of the Living.
Gentei Kaijo means removing
the Spirit Restriction Seal
and releasing our true
Spiritual Pressure.
However, in an emergency,
it is possible to pass
through by removing
the automatic seal function of the
Senkaimon before entering.
What? You mean...
This time, we entered
the World of the Living without
getting a Spirit Restriction Seal.
There's no seal anywhere
on your body, is there?
You're right, there isn't one.
Which means...
If it's Gentei Kaijo you want, we are
already in a Gentei Kaijo state!
What?!
You mean we've been fighting
at full-strength all this time?!
Using all our strength?
With everything we've got?!
Oh no...
Captain...
So is this it?
This is the extent of a
Captain's strength?
Is this what Apache and the
others were beaten by?
Is this what Apache
and the others...
I will end this.
I will crush you with
overwhelming power.
And make sure you do not have
the will to get up again.
Hunt.
Tiburon.
So that's her Resurreccion...
Outwardly, there's not as much
change as I had expected,
but to take her lightly could
mean losing my life.
I must not...
Wh-What?!
So that's all you've got...
A mere ice dragon will
sink to the bottom of the ocean
with a single blow from a shark.
Captain Hitsugaya!
Kira!
Continue with the treatment.
But!
Don't you get it?
I'm telling you to trust them.
Yes, sir.
You're next.
I will have my revenge for those three.
What is the meaning of this?
I didn't think that
your speed and range
would suddenly increase so soon
after your sword release.
I'm glad I took precautions.
A virtual ice image...
I can use a trick like
this only once,
so I really didn't want to use it
until the very last moment.
Don't underestimate our strength.
Oh, so that's what happened...
What is it, Kira?
Rangiku once tried to dump her
workload on Captain Hitsugaya,
but didn't get any response, so she
ended up doing the work herself.
I remember she was
whining about it.
He used an ice mirror?
It must be hard trying to
escape from Rangiku.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I am counting on you
in this war, Soi Fon.
Yes, sir!
Do your best.
O-MA-E-DA
Anyway, do your best.
How could he have
forgotten my name?!
It just means that's
all you are to him.