Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
In order to prevent Aizen
from wiping out Karakura Town,
the Soul Reapers evacuated
the people of Karakura Town
using Tenkaiketchu,
relocating the entire town
to the Rukon district.
Madarame, Kira,
Ayasegawa and Hisagi
were assigned to
defend the pillars.
The four faced the Fracciones
sent by Barragan.
The battle between
Charlotte Chuhlhourne and Yumichika
escalated into a battle
over beauty.
Yumichika won by
unveiling Ruriirokujaku,
his Zanpakuto's genuine form.
Kira also emerged victorious by
entrusting his Zanpukuto, Wabisuke,
with his squad's
philosophy of despair.
Shuhei Hisagi
went against Findorr Calius,
who boasted that he could
control his strength.
Hisagi proved to Findorr that
a man who did not fear his sword
had no right to hold one
by using his Zanpakuto, Kazeshini.
However…
Madarame was…
defeated?!
That's one pillar down.
That…
can't be.
Ikkaku!
Don't do it!
Can you do anything against
an opponent that
defeated Madarame?!
I don't care!
Let me go!
If you insist on
getting in my way,
then I'll just have to
clear the way!
Don't be stupid!
Cool your head!
Shut up!
Out of my way!
H-Hey!
That was very disrespectful
language for a fifth seat.
I know you're distraught,
but mind yourselves.
Kira…
I used Gaten. He'll be fine.
More importantly,
if one pillar was destroyed,
what does that mean?
It's a Tensokaiki!
With the pillar destroyed,
the real Karakura Town
is starting to return!
This is bad.
We have to stop
the reversion somehow.
This bald guy seemed like
he was still concealing
some sort of strength, but…
If he's dead, oh well.
Not so fast.
Who're you calling "dead"?
Don't go deciding
that for yourself.
It'll take more than
that to kill me!
You're wasting your time!
If you're alive,
show that strength you're hiding!
Show it. Say "I understand."
You're going to die.
Say "I understand."
I…
under…
Don't make me laugh.
Strength I'm hiding, you say?
I have no such thing.
And even if I did,
I don't have the time to
use it on a small fry like you!
Is that so?
Then die.
Captain Komamura!
Tetsuzaemon!
Right!
We stopped the reversion.
These are for emergencies,
but as long as you fight
without breaking these,
it should be okay.
Iba…
He's humongous!
Bigger than Captain Komamura.
I felt that one quite a bit,
Soul Reaper.
Or should I call you dog?
Anyway, that was a good punch.
But…
It wasn't a real punch!
Captain Komamura!
That is what you call
a "real punch"!
And while I'm at it,
let me show you
what a "best punch" is like.
Breathe,
Calderon!
What?
What the hell is that?!
– What?!
What is that?!
It's too much trouble to smash you.
So you've shown your true form.
Interesting. I'll…
Hey, Iba?!
Where are you going?!
Shut up!
We're no match for an adversary
that sent the captain flying!
Huh?!
What's with that
yellow-bellied reasoning?!
Never mind,
we're getting out of here!
Heavy…
Weary…
But it can't be helped.
It's Lord Barragan's orders!
Damn…
Damn monster.
If that hit us,
it'd have been the end of us!
Quit dawdling! Let's go!
No way!
I'm fighting!
If you wanna run away,
you can run away by yourself!
You say you're going to fight,
but how're you gonna fight a guy
you were no match
for earlier?!
Or what!
Is it like that guy says?
Do you have some strength
you've being hiding?
No, I don't have
anything like that.
Then be a good boy
and come with me!
Hey!
There they are, those pesky…
His stride is huge!
He'll catch up!
Keep quiet!
Let go of me, Iba!
The two of us can't get away!
I said shut up!
It's over.
C-Captain!
Don't back away, Tetsuzaemon!
Ever!
Stand behind me!
Sir!
That had no effect, maggot!
But I was surprised.
I never imagined a maggot
like you could throw me,
a Fraccion of Lord Barragan.
Damn it.
Iba, we should help.
Keep still.
Iba…
Watch closely, Ikkaku.
That's what the captain of
our Squad is all about.
You lowly maggots have the audacity
to defy Lord Barragan.
It's so unbelievable.
It makes me yawn.
I see.
I'll stop that yawn for you.
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
Why you!
Too bad for you.
I've become accustomed
to your weight.
Damn it!
This time, I've got you!
Oh no! He can't use his arms!
If he gets hit with that
at such a close range,
he's in trouble!
Captain!
What is…
this guy?!
What is this?
What in the world are you?!
Oh yeah.
I haven't identified myself yet.
I am Sajin Komamura,
captain of Squad 7.
I'm ashamed to say,
as you said,
I'm a maggot-like fellow.
No mercy…
That's a good thing.
Real or replica town,
it doesn't matter.
Squad 7 could be in the red
for this fiscal season.
Captain will pay
out of his own pocket
for damages done
by the squad.
He won't let the squad
shoulder the bill.
That's the kind of man
Komamura is.
Is that for real?! All right!
Then I'm going to fight
without worry.
You're not included.
What you break will be deducted
from your salary. No arguments.
Captain, you're a tightwad!
I have so many things
I want to buy this month!
You're such a…
Umm…
I think it's a good thing
we didn't make it in time.
Yeah.
Amazing.
Damn right.
Your Bankai and his are
still as far apart as
heaven and earth, Ikkaku.
– Iba…
– Didn't think we knew about it?
You idiot!
Relax. I won't tell your captain.
But give it some
hard thought, Ikkaku.
Your job this time was
to protect the pillar,
but you allowed your pillar
to be destroyed.
Do you know why that happened?
Because you kept
your strength hidden.
It's your prerogative to die while
keeping your strength hidden,
but don't ignore your orders
because of that!
Don't hurt the squad's fight
because of your selfish pride.
As long as you're a part of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
orders are an absolute!
Even if it means squashing
your pride or honor,
that is the one thing
you must see through!
Iba…
I understand that.
But…
What do you understand, moron?
You're acting like a spoiled kid.
You think that if you die,
there's someone to take your place.
Somewhere inside of you,
that's what you're thinking,
so you can lose like
it doesn't matter.
Now wait…
I'm not going to let you
get away with saying that.
Who says I could lose
like it doesn't matter?
Well, isn't that the case?!
Where am I wrong?
Damn you!
You bastard!
Why did you charge him head on
with those injuries?
Even if you charge him head on,
it's meaningless
if you get crushed.
Do whatever it takes to win,
even if it means running away from,
or outfoxing the enemy!
I can't do that!
I can't fight such
a cowardly fight!
Then put on strength, damn it!
If you insist on having things
your own way,
then make yourself stronger.
When you fight an enemy,
win even if it means
you die doing it.
That's what it means
to do the right thing.
C-Captain!
Relax.
Unfortunately,
I'm a little hard of hearing today.
Chuhlhourne, Abirama,
Findorr, Poww…
Useless idiots.
I tried pricking my ears up.
So how do I look, Tetsuzaemon?
It was perfect!
We received gifts from fans
all over the country,
but most of gifts were
dog accessories and dog food.
That's fine!
Captain?!
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Today, we're discussing
Barragan's Fracciones.
Chuhlhourne's sword release is
Reinas de Rosas.
Abirama's is Aguila.
Findorr's is Pinza Aguda.
Poww's is Calderon.
Written as you just saw…
Except they're all dead now.
We're still left.
We're next!
Try not to die, okay.