Ichigo won his battle
with Grimmjow.
However, Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora, suddenly showed up
and overwhelmed Ichigo with
his great strength.
Nelliel, who regained her powers
in her attempt to save Ichigo,
reverted to her former child form
on the very brink of victory.
Once again, Ichigo found himself
in a pinch while facing Nnoitora.
However, he was saved by
someone he never expected.
What is this?
Kenpachi?!
Next.
Come on.
You’re next, right?
K-Kenpachi…
Why are you here?
I thought the Soul Society
pulled out of this fight.
Kisuke Urahara.
That guy was given a bunch
of orders from the old man
when the showdown
was set for winter.
One of those orders
was to stabilize
some sort of underground cavern
called a Garganta,
and once it was totally secure,
make it possible
for captain-level personnel
to pass over to Hueco Mundo.
For crying out loud…
I said I could
handle this by myself.
So you finally attacked.
We have only come to heal
everyone’s wounds.
We have no intention of
fighting with you.
Arrancar… Arrancar… Arrancar…
Hueco Mundo is quite
a treasure trove of riches!
Are you the one who
fought with her?
It was not me.
However, I was about to
administer the finishing blow.
I see.
Among the Espada,
my Sonido is the fastest.
And by a adding a small step,
I’ve completed something
resembling a pseudo clone.
You might say…
It’s like playing with magic.
Too bad.
Gemelos Sonido isn’t
limited to two bodies.
Farewell, captain whose name
I don’t even know.
The reason for your defeat is
the arrogance of not even
stating your name.
What?!
You are the arrogant one, Espada.
But do not fret.
The reason you will lose is not
because of your arrogance.
It is simply…
a difference in skill.
It’s cold.
I should’ve worn
something warmer.
That wasn’t nice
of Captain Kuchiki.
He disappeared the moment
he arrived.
Before we departed,
I thought I made it clear to him
that I can’t use the Flash Step.
That hurt.
Huh?
Which way should I go?
Arrogant?
Me?
Why do you believe that?
You are an enemy,
but you are a captain.
I consider you to be my equal,
and I have conducted myself
in that manner.
I have no arrogance.
An Arrancar…
considering himself
to be my equal…
I’m saying that in itself is
already arrogant.
I see.
It would seem…
arrogance is
part of your nature.
Very well.
Then I shall crush your hubris…
and your very being,
turn them into pulp.
Subside…
Brujeria!
What’s the matter?
You sensed that I was about
to unleash an attack,
but nothing happened.
You seem to want to say
that you don’t get it.
Unfortunately…
Something has already happened.
Your left leg has become mine.
What is this?
All things are subject to control.
Subordinates are under
the control of their superiors.
The masses are under
the control of their king,
clouds are under
the control of the wind,
and the light of the moon is
under the control of the sun.
The power of my Brujeria
is the ability
to take control of whatever
my eye stares at.
I call this power “Amor.”
You still look like you want
to say you don’t get it.
I sympathize with you.
It must be difficult when
you’re not too bright
and there are many things
you don’t get.
Even if you don’t get it,
if you experience it with
your body, you will understand.
Now then… Left leg come here.
It’s meaningless to resist.
Your control does not extend
to your left leg.
Now, take another step.
Oh…
You instantly slashed
your left leg muscles and tendons?
Indeed, now I cannot move them.
A swift decision and
immediate action. Magnificent.
All right then.
How about this one?
Oh…
You’re able to move that well,
even on one leg?
I have to hand it to you, Captain.
I am truly impressed.
Damn you.
Oh, there he is! Thank goodness.
I finally caught up with you!
It was mean to leave me behind,
Captain Kuchiki!
Didn’t I tell you that
I can’t do Flash Step!
I’m not very quick, and I felt
uneasy in an unfamiliar place,
and the inside of the building
was freezing cold,
and I was hungry,
and I didn’t know my way,
and I almost got lost.
Captain Kuchiki!
Your leg is badly hurt!
And is this Rukia?!
Rukia!
Quite the chatterbox has arrived.
Hanataro Yamada.
Y-Yes?
Stay back.
R-Right!
I’ll move back right now!
I’m in the way, aren’t I?
I’ll say it once more.
Stay back.
In my present state,
I cannot guarantee that I can fight
without getting you involved.
Captain… They both appear
to be stable now.
They’ll…
Isane, we must be vigilant.
If we had been even a little later
with our treatment,
their lives would’ve
been in danger.
And, this place is Hueco Mundo.
We are right in the middle
of the enemy base.
There’s no telling
what might happen,
so we must be cautious.
R-Right.
This Spiritual Pressure!
It’s Captain Kuchiki’s!
It’s not only Captain Kuchiki.
Captain Kurotsuchi
and Captain Zaraki
have also begun fighting.
Yes.
The three of them have
their Spiritual Pressure at full strength
from the very start.
The Arrancar…
The Espada are that sort of enemy.
Will they be all right?
Let’s have faith.
Then, when they are done fighting,
we will heal their injuries.
That is our job.
You’re quite tough.
You too.
Where is all that brute strength
coming from?
Captain Kuchiki, what is that?!
Captain Kuchiki!
C-Captain Kuchiki!
What are you—?!
Hado 1…
Sho!
The ice…
Stay back, Hanataro Yamada.
R-Right!
I see.
R-Rukia! Rukia!
You immediately discarded
not only your left leg,
but your left arm as well.
You instantly regarded the objects
whose control was taken away
from you as your enemies
and slashed them.
Even if they were your own body.
So fierce.
An icy cold decisiveness
toward yourself.
However, that decisiveness,
to my eyes,
appears slightly imprudent.
Rukia, get a hold of yourself!
I’ll treat your wounds right now!
Of your four limbs,
only your right arm
and right leg remain.
You are indeed overly arrogant
to challenge me,
an Espada, with only one arm and one leg.
Don’t you agree?
As I told you…
Between you and me,
our powers are as different
as heaven and earth.
This talk is tedious.
I discarded my left arm.
I discarded my left leg.
Even then,
we are still far from equal.
How unfortunate.
You appear to have even less
of an understanding
of your own abilities
than I thought.
There was one thing
I forgot to tell you.
These eyes of mine control
one object per eye.
I’m glad you realized what
that means so quickly.
Earlier, I released Amor
using two eyes.
In other words…
Rukia, you just have to
– hang on a little longer.
– In addition to your left arm…
I have control of something else.
I am able to control
one area per eye.
However…
If I control the head,
control extends to the entire body.
My control is not affected
by the person’s injuries.
Don’t move!
Throw down your sword,
nameless captain.
You have lost.
Bakudo 61…
Rikujokoro.
What is this?!
Damn! Move! Move!
Move!
Damn! Damn! Move!
Control, you say?
Such a thing…
holds no meaning
at all against me.
Bankai…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
W-What is this?!
Curse you…
Damn this!
I will control everything using
the Amor of my entire spirit!
Forget it.
You can control one object per eye.
That’s what you said.
The number of eyes on your body,
including your own two, is fifty.
With just those fifty eyes,
which of the hundreds of millions of swords
covering the sky do you intend to control?
You told me it was useless.
That there was nothing I could do.
Let me tell you something now.
The state you are in now…
That is what you call “useless.”
Damn it!
Move as I command!
Gokei, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
W-What?!
That guy, Zommari,
resembles a pumpkin.
Your captain wears
a tube of fishcake on his hair.
Pumpkins and fishcake
are both foods. They are equal.
Fishcake is a processed food.
It is on a different level
than pumpkins.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
There seem to be fewer carp lately.