Oh... Nice angle...
I told you that I couldn't help it...
You looked like you were standing
in a prearranged spot.
I told you, that was
a coincidence, too...
Give me a break.
It was a good view.
You're the one who
got the good view.
Why do I have to
give you a break?
S-Sorry.
That's crazy!
Look out!
Oh no!
Help!
Rangiku!
I know!
All right!
Jump into the river.
What are you doing?!
She's this way.
Oh no!
Swim properly!
I'm trying to, but all the water
I've absorbed is weighing me down.
I thought that I was going to die...
That's very cruel of you, Rangiku!
It was faster than
getting out of my gigai!
Thank goodness!
You should stay still for a bit.
Are you all right?
Where's Shintaro?
Shintaro?
Hey, is she all right?
I heard someone
fell into the river?
That's terrible.
Shintaro saved me!
Shintaro?
Is there someone here
named Shintaro?
Huh? H-Hey, Rangiku?!
What's going to happen to me?!
Take care...
What?!
Are you really going to be
all right by yourself?
Yeah. Thank you for dropping me off.
Phew... Acting like
a stuffed animal is tiring.
But man, this sure is
an incredibly luxurious mansion.
This TV's huge!
It's full of expensive-looking
furniture, too.
I wonder what kind of jobs
her parents must have
to be able to afford these things.
Oh no!
Shintaro, sorry to keep you waiting.
Hot!
It burns! It burns! It burns!
- It burns! It burns!
- Shintaro?
Oh... Well... I...
Wow!
Shintaro!
Amazing, Shintaro!
You really can move!
I can't breathe!
Oh, sorry Shintaro.
I thought that I was going to die...
Huh?
Aren't you surprised
that I can move?
No! I've been praying to God
that you'd be able to move!
This feels awkward...
Say, you're the one
who saved me, aren't you?
Oh...Yeah.
Thank you very much, Shintaro.
Really, it was nothing.
So what's your name?
I'm Miyuki.
We've been together all this time.
Why don't you know my name?
Oh, well... Umm...
I do know your name, but...
But?
When I fell into the river,
I lost my memory.
Oh? Is that so?
By the way, are you
the only one in this house?
That's right.
What about your mom?
She's at work.
And your dad?
He's not here.
Why?
He was a good-for-nothing,
so mommy dumped him!
A good-for-nothing...
Do you understand what that means?
Mommy is really busy and
she always comes home late at night.
So I look after the house by myself!
Oh? You're so little,
yet so admirable.
Yeah!
Hmm...
Say, Shintaro...
Let's play together!
What?!
Why am I being
dressed like this again?!
She's not teamed up
with Ichigo's sister, is she?
Here you go!
NOTE: THESE ARE RUBBER DOLLS!
Come on, Shintaro,
it's time for dinner.
Eat up.
Is it good?
I can't eat this!
Oh... Uhh, well, this is... Umm...
Yeah! Is it good?
It's delicious...
I won't last if I keep doing that...
Say, Shintaro, what do you
want to play next?
Play company? Play school?
No! Umm... Well...
That's it!
The weather's nice today.
Why don't we play outside?
It'll be a lot more fun to run outside
with your friends on a day like this!
I don't want to go outside...
What's wrong?
And... I have no friends...
But...
I don't need friends.
All right! I understand. Don't cry!
Aww... I don't know what to do!
You sure are a crybaby.
You're being mean, Shintaro.
Huh? Come to think of it,
why were you outside earlier?
Don't you hate going outside?
D-Don't cry!
I wanted to see our home...
The home where I used to live
with mommy, daddy, and you.
Your home?
Yeah.
When mommy and daddy
were friendly with each other,
we lived in a different home.
It was really big and really fun.
Mommy, daddy, and I,
and Shintaro, a big dog...
We all lived together there.
But I thought I was Shintaro!
No, a real dog called Shintaro.
But he couldn't live
with us in this house,
so mommy bought me
a stuffed animal Shintaro in his place.
Hmm? So what happened
to the first Shintaro?
Is he with your dad?
He got hit by a car and died.
Whoops... This is bad, this is bad...
But if you had so much fun there.
I'm sure you didn't want to move, right?
I had no choice...
Mommy's having a hard time.
Don't you think it's a bit cold of her
to act as if nothing happened,
even though you fell into the river?
It's all right. I told her not to call me.
Mommy's working hard at her job.
I shouldn't make her worry.
Besides, if I'm with you,
I can have fun without going outside.
This kid...
She's acting tough,
but she's actually lonely.
She must have wanted to
go to her previous home
because she remembered
something fun that happened there.
All right! Then let's go
to your previous home!
Huh?!
You want to go, don't you?
But...
I'll go with you.
Thank you, Shintaro!
Yeah.
Oh...
Oh no...
Whoa...
What a huge house!
You lived in this house?
Yeah.
But it looks like no one's living in it.
I don't know.
What? Is this the first time
you've come here since you moved?
Yeah.
What's this vase?
Shintaro was hit by a car here.
I see...
Hey.
What's wrong?
This place is dangerous...
We should get away from here quickly.
Huh?!
This bad feeling...
Say, Shintaro...
Miyuki!
Look out!
Crap!
We have no choice,
we're going into the house.
Shintaro!
Damn. It was planning to
force us inside from the start.
In any case, let's go.
Huh?
Shintaro, what's wrong?
It's a Hollow!
A Hollow?
An evil spirit!
Crap! Oddly, there have been
a lot of Hollows in this town lately!
Is something going on
that I don't know about?
Don't stop!
You bastard!
This is bad. We've got to
get away from here immediately.
O-Okay.
Crap! It appeared!
There are two of them!
Oh, there's just one...
But now's not the time to relax!
You're not going to let us pass?!
Say, Shintaro...
What is that?
Miyuki! You can see the Hollow?
I'm not sure... It's kind of blurry.
She can't see it clearly...
She can only tell
that something's there.
Now!
Shintaro!
It's all right!
But what are we going to do?
The Hollow has
closed off the gate...
Is beating it the only option?
He isn't chasing after us, is he?
Shintaro, what's going on?
I'm scared.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Crap. Are you serious?
I've got to fight in this body?
Miyuki! Look for an opening
and run away!
Shintaro!
You Hollow bastard!
This way, this way!
Miyuki!
You bastard!
I thought so...
Shintaro!
Miyuki!
Keep on running!
Huh?!
Shintaro.
I'm persistent...
Shintaro!
M-Miyuki!
Run away, Miyuki!
W-Wait...
Shintaro.
Crap... Miyuki!
I'm scared...
Shintaro. Help me...
Shintaro...
Help me, Shintaro!
Kon!
Rangiku... You're late...
SHINTARO
I see... He...
Shintaro! Get a hold of yourself!
Sorry, Miyuki...
I got you wrapped up
in something strange.
Shintaro, you're all in tatters...
Miyuki, you're really blessed.
Huh?
The one who saved you back there...
It was the original Shintaro.
Shintaro did?
Yeah...
He was worried about you too.
It seems like it's over for me.
Huh?! No!
I don't want that!
It can't be helped...
But...
But I was finally able to talk to you.
Wha-?
What are you talking about?!
Don't rely on me forever!
It'll be all right. Even if I can't talk,
I'll always be watching you.
You can make some
other friends from now on!
I don't need friends!
I only need you with me!
Don't say that!
I know.
Huh?
I know that you're actually lonely.
Your parents moved
for their own convenience
and your mom is busy...
So you try your best
not to cause her trouble.
But...
There's no need to
push yourself so hard.
Others have also flung me around.
I was made a mod soul...
And I was abandoned at
someone else's convenience.
But that wouldn't make
any sense to you.
Anyway, I felt like there was nothing
I could do, but my friends saved me.
Your friends?
Yeah...
They're all stupid,
and they're no good without me.
But that's what's
amusing about them.
So if you feel lonely,
make some friends.
It'll give your mom
some peace of mind.
It's almost time.
Huh?
It's all right. The original Shintaro
and I will be watching over you.
Good luck, Miyuki.
Aren't you going to respond to me?
Okay...
All right!
Bye, Miyuki.
Farewell...
Mommy...
That's one thing settled.
Tsk! She gave me a lot of trouble.
Why did you help that girl so much?
What are you saying?!
All little kids idolize me.
I'm Kon, the endearing!
Hmm?
Rangiku, why are there
so many Hollows appearing lately?
There are more than before,
aren't there?
Yes...
There may be a big battle...
What do you mean?
Nothing. Let's go.
Miyuki...try your best.
What are you doing?!
I'm going to leave you behind!
Okay!
All right! I finally get to be
the lead in the next episode!
It seems like it's going to be
an episode where Mr. Urahara is out.
Kisuke seems like he'd
have a lot of strange enemies.
Things are probably
going to get troublesome
when some strange visitors
show up.
People mature when
they overcome hardships.
A story like this again?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden...
Matsumoto, you clean up, too!
Even if you are in the World of the Living,
you're getting too lazy!
What is it?
The rules are to separate the trash!
You mustn't put everything
into the same bag!
I see...
Start over!
Okay...