Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Jinta…
What do you want?
–There…
–Umm, this isn't child birth.
You didn't have to boil
that much water…
Shut up!
It may be of some use!
I'm healing them with a special method.
Hot water is not needed.
Really?!
Are you stupid?
Ha!
What did you say?!
Why you…
You're just a stuffed animal!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Stop…stop…!
You're stinky!
You're dirty all over…
H-Hey…
All right!
I'll clean you right now!
Huh?!
Aaah…That feels good…
The water temperature
is just right…
Stop relaxing!
Stop!
My stuffing is coming out!
Keep it quiet.
We have injured people in here!
Keep it quiet!
Sorry…
Kurosaki…
Excuse me…
Can you be a little more cheerful?
The air is stagnant!
Ugh…it's bleak…
So what's the new information
from Soul Society?
There was progress at
the Department of Research
and Development…
What's that?
I'm in charge of the Department
of Research and Development.
There shouldn't be any data
I can't browse.
I removed the lock.
It took a bit of time, though…
I shall explain.
Nemu!
Yes. I am bringing it up
on the monitor.
These are Bounts. The ones who are
causing a stir in the World of the Living.
They're a tribe that, while human,
extend their life-spans by feeding off
of the human souls…
You dim-wit! Quickly!
Yes.
And as you know, these are Quincies…
In the past, these two tribes…
the Bounts and the Quincies clashed.
The Stealth Force took
this footage at that time…
Take a look at this.
The Bounts are clearly
targeting this Quincy…
What happens next?
This is a pretty old record.
It's all I have…
A “to be continued…”
I want to know how it played out…
I don't know if the Bounts of
that time got that Quincy.
But according to my records…
Nemu! Explain what happened
afterwards.
Yes. Afterwards,
it seems they continued to feed on
and absorb the souls of
living humans for a while.
What?
Originally there existed a kind
of law amongst the Bounts;
where it was prohibited to absorb souls
unless they’re from dead humans.
But after this incident,
it’s apparent that the Bounts continued
to absorb souls off of living bodies.
It’s evident in the data showing
a decrease in the quantity of souls…
Don't say anything unnecessary!
What happened afterwards?
I don't know…
But whenever they make
a large-scale movement,
they break their laws and
attack living humans.
Furthermore, for some reason,
they need a certain Quincy…
Whether these current incidences
are related to these old records…
I don't know…
But this much is sure…
The Bounts will begin to
openly attack humans.
Living humans, that is…
Yoruichi…Is that for real?
It might have been different
if it was someone else, but…
Jushiro Ukitake, of all people,
was in a panic when
he came to let me know.
There's no reason to question it.
Kariya is trying to use Ishida's Quincy
power to open a hole to Hueco Mundo…
Is that why they need the energy
from the souls of living humans?
Furthermore, why does he need
Quincy abilities to do that?
Right now we only
have circumstantial evidence…
We can't easily make a decision.
At any rate, we've got to stop Kariya
and the other Bounts
–from seriously attacking humans…
–Yoruichi…
What?
There's one thing
I don't understand…
They're sucking the souls
of living humans
and trying to use the Quincy power…
just to go to the Hollow World…
What does he…
What does Kariya plan to do?
We wouldn't have any problems
if we knew.
He's…
Powerful enough as he is…
What does he plan to do
by gaining even greater power?
Ichigo…you…
He's incredibly strong…
He's not using cheap techniques…
So why?
Kurosaki, are you afraid?
I'm not… It's just…
Thinking calmly…
In my current state…
I don't think I can win…
Ichigo…
Wh-What's that sound?!
Ganju.
Ah, it's been a while since
I last appeared!
Thank you very much!
Huh? Where's Shiba?
Umm… He was around there earlier…
Oh, I see!
He's probably gone to the bathroom.
We can't be sure of that…
No…It's the bathroom,
the bathroom!
Why are you limiting it to the bathroom?
You've made such a mess here…
Please fix it later!
Don't worry about small details.
Why'd you come here?
You even came on a boar.
Where in the world did you find one?!
Well, there sure are
unusual animals here!
You got it from the zoo?!
Well, he's nothing like my Bonnie…
BOAR
Oh, come to think of it, Kuchiki,
you don't know my cute Bonnie, do you?
So why'd you come here?
Oh, that's right…
Well, I sensed a gloomy
Spiritual Pressure
coming from somewhere in the town…
I'm the type to be bothered
by things like that.
So I followed the scent and here I am!
So it's you!
You're the gloomy bastard!
What did you say?!
It's true! I didn't notice.
Now that you mention it,
this is pretty bad…
Everyone, open the windows,
the windows!
Don't talk as if I'm garbage!
You're the same as rotten garbage!
I'm going to freshen you a bit!
Hey, old man,
do you know a good place?
Old man?!
I may look like this,
but I'm quite friendly with
your older sister, you know…
Well, if that's the case…
Come this way, underground!
Yeah, I'm thankful for this.
Let's go, Ichigo!
All right!
Ichigo, get out of your gigai!
This isn't a gigai…
–This is…
–This is fine, isn't it?!
What are you…?
Huh?!
I'll come join you as well!
Thanks! Let's go, Ichigo!
Hey! Now's not the time…
W-Wait a second!
Hey! Hey!
Prepare yourself!
Can we still use it?
I don't know…
If we fix it, perhaps…
There should be tools
somewhere around here.
I'll search for them…
No. That's all right.
Come on, come on, spin!
Stop it, Jinta…
Shut up! He'll dry well if I do this!
Hey!
Don't dry me out with clothes pins!
Especially in the middle
of the night!
Keep it quiet!
It's bad for the injured inside!
A-All right…
I told you!
Shut up!
Does it hurt?
No… It's not that bad
thanks to the healing…
I do feel bad for
getting you involved in all of this
when you don’t have anything
to do with it…
I am involved.
They're targeting me.
Even without my powers, I'm a Quincy.
Jin…Kariya told me earlier…
“I'm sorry for getting you involved.”
But…that's not what he really felt…
Yes. Probably not…
That's what shocked me the most…
No one knows what he's really like…
He's trying to go to
Hueco Mundo isn't he?
But I don't know what he plans
to do when he gets there…
But I don't think the cause is worth
going as far as to break our tribe's laws
and sacrificing humans.
Of course…
I…also attacked living humans…
I'm despicable.
But that’s…
We Bounts,
since long ago…
since we were born in this world…
No, since we appeared…
Our numbers have been decided.
Huh?
During a certain time,
Bounts appeared among normal people.
A sudden mutation…
We haven't appeared since then…
And…new life cannot be born
from Bounts.
Never.
We are a race that just dies…
Slowly, over many months and years.
That's why I'm telling you
you're scared!
How sloppy!
I'll straighten out your cowardliness!
Bring it on!
It seems you finally feel
like doing this!
You, go!
Huh? Why me?
Are you afraid, too?
What did you say?!
Then go! Finish quickly,
like the “Renji” you are.
Oh well!
Hey! What about you?
Here I go, Ichigo!
Take this!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
My, my, how pathetic.
With the state you’re in right now,
even I can easily take you on!
What did you say?!
Come down here, Ganju!
Don’t get distracted!
Here I go, Ichigo!
Seppa, turn to sand!
Huh?!
Senpen banka!
Take this!
This is bad! It got me, too!
Why you…
The Chili Pepper Smoke Bomb
is irritating my eyes!
Try and kiss my butt!
You bastard!
Come down here!
Stupid! There's no way
I'd come down there!
Here I go again!
Hm?
Hello… Oh, Hana, huh?
What is it?
We're busy!
The manager thinks you've gone
to the bathroom,
so come back quickly!
Oh, I see. Thanks.
Then I'll head back.
He said to come back.
The store's busy!
Huh?
Then I'll leave the rest to you!
What's with that?!
You invite me here
and leave by yourself?
Well, I was told to come back quickly so,
I'm going.
Take care!
What a way to run away…
Well… I guess it doesn't matter!
It's as he said!
What is this pathetic state?
You're full of openings!
Shut up!
Are you afraid of Kariya?!
I'm not afraid!
When did you become such a wimp?!
I didn't!
Roar!
Zabimaru!
Wait just a second!
Why is it so crowded?!
Oh… Would you like me to warm up
your packed lunch?
–Yes.
–Hey…
Aren't there any other employees?
Umm…well…
Manager, take care of the register!
Huh? Shiba's still in the bathroom, huh?
He sure takes a long time…
I'm going to check on him…
Manager, could you take care
of the register instead?
–Hey!
–Hurry up!
Yes!
Shiba!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I feel refreshed.
I'm going to the register!
See? He was in the bathroom!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Can I ask you something?
Do you have any pride as a Bount?
Huh?
I have it…
Pride as a Quincy…
The Quincies are a tribe
which was given a power by God
to protect people from Hollows.
Even if I'm the only one,
I will fulfill my heavenly duty
with pride as a Quincy…
Pride, huh?
What a nice sound…
When did you start to calculate
your chances of winning or losing?!
It's unsightly!
That's why you're scared!
You don't think you can win?
You never thought about that
when you charged into Soul Society!
It seems you've gained
a little determination!
D-Don't be so mad!
Wait…
I was just trying to give you
a friendly shove!
Thanks, Renji…
You're right…
There's probably still some in me…
Good bye…
Proud Quincy…
Thank you…
That woman…
will die this time…
There are people who can't
settle things without doing that…
Settle things?
Yes… How should I put it?
To settle the score with her life.
I'm going to go to Soul Society.
I can't stand being led by
vague information like this…
I'm going to check out the truth
with my own eyes.
Yes…
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
Honestly. So many people barging in…
I don't have enough ingredients
for tomorrow's breakfast.
–Jinta, I'll go shopping.
–Don't worry about it.
We just have to half
the freeloader’s portions.
Me again?!
Would you rather have only water?
Give me a break…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers…
– Golden…
So Ichigo, what kind of powers
did Kariya have?
Who knows?
I couldn't tell…
Huh? You fought him
and couldn't tell?!
Are you stupid?
Shut up!
You didn't see anything either,
so stop blabbing!
Why didn't you come with us anyway?!
We contacted you!
I didn't know anything about it!
My soul pager never…
It's batteries are dead…
Tune in again!