I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
I see… You reduced the damage
done to you by releasing
all of your Spiritual Pressure and
surrounding yourself with it.
I’m finally starting to
get your attacks…
So…?
Counterattacks are aimed
at the openings
that enemies leave
when they attack…
What good is that
if I don't provide any openings?
Defending yourself with
Spiritual Pressure, huh?
My, my… I'm not used to this…
My coat is all in tatters.
I see…
It really does seem to minimize
the damage done to one’s body.
My attacks are only counter strikes?!
In that case, I'll show you…
Messer's true form!
That's…
My power is wind.
Wind can generate static electricity
through atmospheric friction…
…and create lightning!
It's useless!
No matter how fast you move…
You can’t outrun lightning!
I got you!
What's wrong? Is that it?
You bastard…
Fine… I'm going to finish this.
Soon, the Jokai Crest within me
will fill up with power.
I never told you this, but there's more
than one Jokai Crest.
What?!
If I unleash my Jokai Crest,
it'll trigger all of the Jokai Crests,
and Seireitei will be reduced to nothing.
Why would you do such a thing?!
What's the point of killing your comrades,
the Soul Reapers and yourself?!
The Bounts are a rotten tribe.
They were given so much power
but they wouldn’t let go of their ties
to the Soul Reapers.
And the Soul Reapers are
even more rotten.
They selfishly created the Bounts
and used them for their own purposes.
I couldn't forgive any of that.
I will drag all of them down with me.
Soul Reapers, souls…
I'm going to destroy them all!
Are you crazy?!
I'm completely sane.
The world is the one that's crazy.
But that's enough…
Soon, this world is going to end.
What are you talking about?!
I won't let you…do that!
Ichigo!
Wait!
Let go of me, Renji!
This is Ichigo's battle!
Don't interfere!
But…
He's proved to be
Captain Kuchiki's equal in combat…
Believe in him!
I'm not going to let you
destroy everything!
My, my…
What can you do in your condition?
Shut up!
Just a little longer and
everything will end.
Oh well. I'll finish you off
before the world ends.
Crap! I don't have any energy!
I can't move my arm…
Move… Move…
Move!
It'll move.
Ichigo…
A black Getsugatensho…
Wh-Where did you get
that power?!
That's your inner power, huh?
But it seems even that power
has dried up.
I have a powerful ally known as reishi…
I can't absorb it?!
Why? Why can't I absorb
reishi anymore?!
Can it be…?!
She did that so I couldn't
absorb reishi, huh?
You've done it, Rantao…
It looks like you're not
invincible anymore.
We're on equal terms now!
It's a little late…
What?!
The time is near…
Just a little longer…
Just a little longer and I'll be filled
with the Jokai Crest's power.
At that moment,
I'll unleash the Jokai Crest
and everything will be over.
I won't let you!
I'll defeat you before you unleash
the Jokai Crest!
Can you do that?!
I will!
In that case, I'll show you how incredible
the Jokai Crest's power is!
What?!
I'm going to detonate one
of the Jokai Crests nearby.
All right, it's here!
Sentaro, take care of it!
Yes sir!
Captain!
Yes… The information that
Rantao gave us was right.
Seal this up quickly!
Yes!
There's no time…
I hope we make it!
There are too many locations.
Who knows how much time
it'll take to seal all of them.
Silence! I won't listen
to such nonsense!
It is the duty of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
to defend Seireitei!
We will do everything in our power
to stop the ryoka's plan!
You're going to detonate
a Jokai Crest?
Don't worry.
Detonating one of the Jokai Crests
placed within the court
won't affect the others.
Now learn the power
of the Jokai Crest!
Bankai, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
What?!
Byakuya…
You bastard!
It looks like I made it in time…
Yoruichi!
Sorry, sorry…
It looks like I'm late.
Ichigo!
Right now, Ukitake and all
the other Soul Reapers are sealing
the Jokai Crests in Seireitei.
Huh?!
But it's taking time…
Will they be sealed?
Will the Jokai Crests be activated…?
Or will I defeat him, huh?
I get it!
Whatever the case,
it's a race against time…
What are you going to do, Kariya?
It's obvious…
I'm going to defeat all of you
and accomplish my goal!
I'm your opponent!
You bastard!
Don't do it, Byakuya.
When he unleashes
his Jokai Crest,
we have to seal it away with
my Shunko and your Senbonzakura!
We'll be too late if
we’re fighting him as well…
Though I don't know if
we can completely seal it away.
Is that all your power can do?
Shut up…
Damn! I used up too much power
compressing the Jokai Crest.
I guess it can't be helped…
This is odd.
Kariya can't absorb
reishi anymore,
but his attacks aren't getting
any weaker…
No…
Instead it seems like
they're getting stronger…
Why…?
I see!
Ichigo!
Just a little more!
He's already out of spiritual power!
Right now, he's fighting using
the power of the Jokai Crest in his body!
What about it?
How silly.
This is a gamble…
The Jokai Crest will activate
in just a little while.
Will my body hold up…
or will you defeat me?
Heh! I told you that from the start!
I'm going to defeat you! I will!
What can you do when
you're panting like that?
What's wrong?
Are you finished?
I won't hold back anymore!
Can you handle this?!
That's…
Ichinose's zanpakuto…
Over here! He's over here!
What happened to the ground?!
Is Ichigo all right?
Kurosaki!
Everyone…
Kuchiki! Renji!
Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
Abarai, Sado, help Kurosaki!
We can't interfere.
No… We shouldn't interfere…
Kuchiki…
He probably considers
the Bounts similar to himself…
Ichigo is a Substitute Soul Reaper,
but he isn't a Soul Reaper.
He's human,
but not a normal human.
Until he gained
his Soul Reaper powers,
Ichigo wanted the power to
protect those close to him…
He got the power he wanted,
and from that point on
he was burdened with two worlds –
the World of the Living
and Soul Society.
He has a burden
we cannot understand…
But Ichigo bears this burden
and tries to move forward…
Could we do the same thing?
Bounts are also people
who are not people…
They suffered in two worlds…
Kariya can only be stopped by Ichigo.
He bears the same burden.
Then…the only thing we can do
is to trust him and watch.
Don't worry.
He'll win!
Yeah… You're right.
This is it!
I'm going to hit you with all
that’s left of my strength!
Then I'm going to settle this, too.
Let's go!
The Jokai Crest is backed
by all of the Bounts!
Can you withstand it,
Ichigo Kurosaki?!
And what have you ever done
for the Bounts?!
You're the one who treated
your comrades as pawns!
I won't lose to someone like you!
What do you know?
People hate those
who are superior to themselves.
Your friends aren't any different!
Over time, friends who you trusted
will come to fear your power
and distance themselves from you.
What's the point in protecting them?!
There is meaning!
There’s no reason to it!
I protect them because I want to!
I'd risk my soul!
Your soul?
No! He's activated it!
Byakuya! We're going to seal it!
Byakuya!
What's wrong?!
At this rate he's going to unleash it!
Byakuya!
Nothing matters anymore!
I'm going to end everything now!
Kariya!
It looks like it's over…
I'm a little disappointed.
I won't get to see whether you walk
down the same path that I have…
Kurosaki… I…
You idiot…
Chad!
Are you all right, Ichigo…?
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Everyone…
Ichigo… I was so worried about you.
– Ichi…Ichigo…
– Kurosaki!
I've got to heal your wounds!
No... You can do that later.
In the end,
he disappeared on his own...
Are you saying that he was planning
to do that from the beginning?
Who knows?
But he probably wanted to bring
his never-ending life to an end.
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Captain Ukitake! I've finished
sealing a Jokai Crest!
Captain! I sealed away three!
Correction! I sealed away ten!
Actually, it was fifty!
-Kuchiki, were there...
-It really was 100!
-...that many?
-Actually, it was 200!
-Captain, don't take them seriously.
-No, no, it was 300!
Sorry, but hide me for a while!
What's wrong Ganju?
My sister found out that I didn't
do much this time, It's bad!
I see...
But you're a little late...
Hey!
I knew you'd come here!
Sis... Why are you here?