No… That's impossible!
We put all of our Spiritual
Pressure into that sword!
Restoring Ichigo’s Spiritual Pressure
would be a piece of cake!
Ichigo! Show them, Ichigo!
Show them that despair
isn’t enough to stop you!
Right.
Your Getsugatensho has
gotten more powerful,
but is that all you've got?!
You missed!
This isn't enough to kill me, Kurosaki!
You idiot.
That wasn’t a Getsugatensho.
That was the force created
from swinging my sword.
What the hell?
What the hell is this
Spiritual Pressure?!
Getsuga…
tensho!
Sorry... I missed...
Next time, I won’t.
Must retreat!
I’ve got to retreat and regroup!
You’re not getting away!
What incredible power...
His physical abilities have
become even more powerful!
Did the Fullbring I gave him
increase his innate powers?!
Getsuga…
tensho!
Damn…
It’ll take more…
More than that…to kill me!
You feel it, right?
Rukia…Renji…Byakuya…
Kenpachi…Ikkaku…Toshiro…
No, that's not all.
Hirako…
Rangiku…
Unohana…
Hanataro…
Dad…
Mr. Urahara…
Yoruichi…
And even the Old Head Captain.
You have all of our powers, Ichigo.
I thought transferring your powers
to a human was a serious crime.
We didn’t have a choice.
it’s the Head Captain’s orders.
I understand the situation.
Bring that sword to me, Kisuke Urahara!
Head Captain, then…?
Regardless of how he went about it,
Ichigo Kurosaki saved our lives.
Now it’s our turn to
save Ichigo Kurosaki.
Even if it means breaking the tradition,
it would bring perpetual shame to the
13 Court Guard Squads to trample
on the debt we owe him.
This is an order of the Head Captain!
All captains and lieutenants
of the 13 Court Guard Squads
are ordered to place their Spiritual
Pressures in this sword!
Help Ichigo Kurosaki regain
his Soul Reaper powers!
That’s how it was.
Nice of the Head Captain,
don’t you think?
Don’t be stupid.
It’s not the kind of sane decision
you’d expect of a leader.
The Head Captain would’ve probably
never made a decision
like this in the past.
You changed all that, Kurosaki.
That power you received is the result
of the changes you made to
the Soul Society in all of your battles.
Accept it with honor.
What is it?!
No way...
There are two reasons why
the Head Captain decided
to restore your Spiritual Pressure.
The first is as we just told you.
And the second reason is him.
Long before you ever showed up,
a man was issued a Combat Pass
as a Substitute Soul Reaper…
then relinquished that
position and disappeared.
The first Substitute Soul Reaper,
Kugo Ginjo.
The first…
Substitute Soul Reaper?!
What’re you talking about?!
He’s…
When Ukitake first handed
you the Combat Pass,
he must have told you this...
The Soul Society also has a
law covering the emergence
of a Substitute Soul Reaper.
If the Soul Reaper is deemed
beneficial to the Soul Society,
it is customary to give this to them.
The Substitute Soul Reaper law
was created for him!
Captain Hitsugaya.
Be that as it may,
we’ll save the details for later.
Right now, concentrate all
of your attention on him!
You got that right!
You guys would have a problem
if he’s not focused on me!
Thanks, Kurosaki.
If I hadn’t taken your powers,
I’d be dead right now.
Kurosaki was crying.
Why?
Kurosaki and Mr. Tsukishima
are friends…
Why did it turn out like this?
Mr. Tsukishima is the one I love…
Way, way before I even met Kurosaki,
he always protected me,
and treated me with kindness.
I’ve always, always, admired him.
I want to do anything
Mr. Tsukishima says.
For Mr. Tsukishima,
I could sacrifice anything…
That’s how I felt.
But…
Why is it that it hurts so much
when I see Kurosaki crying?
It hurts…so much…
In my mind, in my heart and
even in the pit of my stomach.
Please don’t cry, Kurosaki…
Please don’t cry…
Please don’t cry!
Thank goodness…
Kurosaki isn’t crying.
Kuchiki…
Abarai…
Toshiro…
They all came to stop Kurosaki.
Something’s not right…
Why is everybody on Ichigo’s side?!
Didn’t they come to stop Ichigo?
It’s almost as though…
They’ve come to defeat Ginjo!
What’s the matter, you two?
Are you having doubts about your past?
Mr. Tsukishima…
That’s odd.
You don’t believe the
memories you share with me?
Who was it who protected
you from your parents
and raised you,
Orihime?
Who was it who gave you that pendant,
Chad?
S-Something’s not right with me…
I’m alive right now
because of Mr. Tsukishima, so…why…?
I…
I believe in…
Believe in Mr. Tsukishima…
Tsukishima!
Don’t keep cramming
memories into their pasts!
They’ll become unusable!
Think about how many you
ruined by doing that!
Whew. Thank goodness…
Hey, no fair…
Thanks to you carelessly
unsettling them,
we were easily able to
knock them unconscious.
Thank you very much.
Now Inoue and Sado have
been taken out of action.
They won’t have to suffer anymore.
We’ve already moved the
others to a safe place,
so you’re now able to fight
without holding back.
Kugo!
What? I knew it!
This is quite unfair!
How could you take Mr. Ichigo’s
power all for yourself?!
Hey! Giriko!
Yeah!
You promised to share it with all of us!
Hold on, you guys!
I don’t really care about
having Ichigo’s powers…
Shut up!
You don’t have to remind me about it.
I’ll give all of you guys a
portion of Ichigo’s power.
So this is what it’s like!
Wait…
Wonderful!
So this is the power of
Mr. Ichigo’s Fullbring!
It’s as though youth is
gushing out from my body!
Your comments are totally like
those of an old man, Giriko.
Aren’t you going to share
it with Shishigawara?
It’s not nice to leave him out.
Increasing his power would
only cause trouble.
When this fight’s over, kill him.
I thought he had an
interesting ability, though.
All right!
Here we come, Mr. Ichigo!
Feel with your own body
the wonderful power you’ve given us!
Look at him getting carried away…
It’s my fault their powers increased.
I’ll go.
Huh?
Hey.
What is this about?
Don’t tell me you’re going
to take on all of us alone?
I went easy on you.
You shouldn’t be dead.
Huh?!
Shouldn’t be dead, you say?!
You think you’re so cool?
You’re such a joke!
Don’t you get it?
It wasn’t a “You have
defeated the enemy!”
It was, in fact, a
“But they evaded your attack!”
“Digital Radial Invaders.”
You saw it, didn’t you?
We took your Fullbring, Ichigo Kurosaki.
A Fullbring that is worn
and emitted outward.
Thanks to you, I was able to
expand the area of incursion
of my “Invaders Must Die”
beyond the screen.
You’re too soft,
Ichigo!
Ikkaku!
At this point, don’t go trying to end
a fight by striking with
the back of your blade.
Kill them good!
You owe these guys that
for starting the fight.
Stay sharp, Madarame.
Sorry.
Not bad.
Shall I award bonus points?
No thanks.
Who the hell are you?
Looks like they spread out just right.
Well then, I’ll assign rooms.
Hold on, Kuchiki.
That one looks stronger.
Switch with me!
“Switch because he looks stronger”?
I can’t let that go.
In other words, I look weak to you?
Shut up.
It’s boring to cut down small fry.
You appear to be a muscle-bound idiot.
People like you need
to be crushed by force.
What do you think?!
My “Time Tells No Lies” is
also capable of something like this!
The simpler the terms of my contract
with the Gods of Time, the more
powerful it’s manifested!
My contract right now
is an exceedingly simple
“increase in power”!
Right now, I am more
powerful than anyone…
Impossible…
See?
What a bore.
You guys have changed quite a bit!
Yes, we have trained and become
stronger, both in mind and body.
We won’t get distracted so easily.
But you haven’t changed that much.
What?! Can’t you tell?!
Look at my height! I'm taller now!
You’re getting easily distracted…
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Today, I’m giving a quiz!
Question one!
Guess the name of my Zanpakuto, Zabimaru.
Ishida!
But he just said its name…
Doesn’t he know the meaning of “quiz”?
Okay then, Ichigo!
Um…Bucktoothmaru…?
“Bucktoothmaru”? What the hell?!
Didn’t I say it’s Zabimaru?!
You knew and still said it?!
Okay, moving on!
Hold on a second!
You’re going to let that go?!
Let what go?