Hey there.
So this fool is the
Youngest's Contract Holder?
My name is Hecadoth!
The 8th Pillar of Behemoth's
34 Pillar Division.
Anyway, keep a fixed distance from him.
And hold his attention on you!
I don't care if you die, but the
Master's safety is foremost!
Got it?!
Here we go, Baby Beel!
Zebel Blast!
You surprise me, human!
You can control the Youngest's power?
Now just up and die!
But, I hate to say...
You won't be killing me
with something like that.
You're kiddin' me...
No, it was plenty.
Too late.
Oga!
Right then. Good going, Hilda.
I misjudged y-
You... planned this... from the start...?
You can have that woman.
The biggest obstacle is
the Demon Maidservant.
You.
Hilda!
Everything is for Lord En.
What's with all these Demon Maidservants?!
Which Demon do they serve?
I-I have no idea...
Master!
Isabella, are you sure we have time for this?
Behemoth's servants are probably
already making their move.
It may be harsh for Beelze-sama,
yet we have no choice but
to leave him on his own.
Our mission is to watch
over and protect Lord En.
Can I have a picture?
Whoa! Hot girls!
Which café are you from?
What's wrong with you people?
This is...
Street King of Fighters!
And... 4?!
You can fight other people online?!
This'll be my online-game debut!
Satura, hand me money!
Satura, Isabella... Yol...da...?
Hold it, people!
What the...
Move aside!
Master, whatever is the matter?
You left me alone... and
went off somewhere...
We're sorry, Master!
Here, have a potato chip!
You think I...
You think I'm just cramping your style?!
M-Master?!
They've come.
On the Brink! What'll We Do?!
You're next.
Why, you...
Don't cry, Baby Beel.
Hilda's watching.
Master...
Please, escape.
You're still worried about Baby
Beel after what happened to you?
Fine then.
H-Hey, Oga, what are you-
Hilda-san...
Kunieda. Take care of Hilda.
I'll explain everything afterwards.
Watch over Hilda for me.
Spinning, spinning, spinning yogurty...
Kanzaki Hajime is spinning...
What's this? Tojo and that 4-eyed Pres?
Oh? Fighting here?
This should be interesting.
I think I'll watch for a bit.
Don't you think droppin' a heel on a
lady's head is kind of, like, rude?
Shut up!
What the hell are you doing here? Peeping?
Same to you, Kanzaki-senpai!
I was just on my way home
from the supermarket nearby!
Same for me!
Then, I just happened to hear those two...
It looks like two guys're
fightin' over a woman!
It's so totally like a love-triangle, yeah!
So, who'll win?
That's what's strange.
I mean, it's crazy.
Don't you think 4-eyed Pres
there's kinda... dark?
The crazier that black stuff gets
the more crazy strong he gets!
Tojo-senpai's pretty crazy too, so which
crazy's more crazy, Kanzaki-senpai?
I don't get what the hell you're sayin'!
You're the crazy bitch, crazy!
Who're you callin' a crazy bitch?!
Is that also part of the
Izuma 8 Spirits School?
Let's finish this.
It was fun. Let's do it again, Tojo Hidetora!
Tora...
This is it!
Too slow!
Pointless. This guy's not worth the effort.
We felt his power, so came just in case...
But it was a waste of time.
Yeah. He ain't up to Demon level.
Just a reject.
Perhaps a descendant of some lower Demon
that was banished to the Human World?
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division
Pillar Master: Naga
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Divison
Pillar Master: Graphel
I guess we should have
gone where Hecadoth went.
I've brought your beverage!
Oh?
That's not a good sign.
Um, what the hell are you doing?
How would you like a
refreshing, cool beverage?
Get out!
Can't even talk anymore, Contract Holder?
I have nothing against you.
But as long as you remain Lord
En's enemy, I will eliminate you.
That weapon he's got is making this rough!
It's harder to close the distance
than I figured it would be.
Oga!
Stay back!
This is my fight. Stay
quiet and watch over Hilda!
That's right, woman.
Watch, helplessly, as he dies...
Behemoth's orders! This man must die!
Too late!
Got you.
Oga!
Actually...
...I'm the one who got you!
Let's see how you handle
one at point blank range!
What's with those guys?
They barged in just when
things were getting good.
Hey!
I don't think this is a good time!
Huh? What's it matter?
A little longer!
Let's wait a little longer!
Tap out!
What the hell are they?
These guys are real...
Demons?
Yes. Unlike you, they're real
ones born in the Demon World.
And they're coming to this town?
I suspect as much.
Listen well, Izuma-kun. I need to warn you.
Do not fight them even if they confront you.
I'm sorry, Principal.
I owe you a lot.
You're the one who took me
in when I had no where to go
after using my Demon
powers at my last school.
When I came to St. Ishiyama, it was the first
time I knew there were others in my situation.
But that's exactly why I
can't follow your advice.
Because these guys have
come to eliminate Oga-kun.
Hold it!
You're going to break up our fight
and not even introduce yourselves?
I can't allow that.
Let it go. You're no match for us.
I wonder about that.
I thought I said...
...you're no match!
Peons like you should
know their place! Yeah?!
Rude, aren't you?
What power... Is this what
a real Demon is like?
You want me to start with you, huh?
Unhand me, Human.
You wanna get beat, too?
Tojo... Don't!
Don't go takin' my mark!
Go, go, Gohan-kun...
Perhaps a harbinger of bad things to come?
What are you doing?
I was just thinking of
changing into my pajamas...
I've already finished making the bed!
Now is not the time, or the
place... Or anything else!
You really did have me scared there.
He stopped it with one hand?
That was close, Contract Holder.
Begone!
Okay, that's enough.
Man, you're goin' nuts around town...
Who the hell are you?
Can't you tell, you piece of crap?
I'm his teacher.
I said let go!
Tora!
You think some better-than-average
human could win against a Demon?
Let's go, Graphel.
I know.
You runnin' away?
This ain't over yet.
You really should have just stayed down.
Don't...
...get any closer!
Oh, no!
Woman. You get in our way, and
we'll eliminate you first.
This is bad, Kanzaki-senpai!
Why are you passed out?!
Tora!
Don't you lay a hand on her!
Move it.
I told you not to overdo it!
Quiet.
You're pissin' me off.
I hate guys who always talk
about "guts" and crap...
A fluke?
Isn't he already unconscious?
He's fighting on pure instinct?
Tora!
That's enough!
You're really gonna die like this!
Hold it right there!
You didn't have to kick me twice...
You did well, Tojo.
Leave the rest to me.
Who the hell are you?
And I'll say the exact same thing to you.
Huh?
Which school are you from, punk?!
I ain't never seen a
uniform like that before!
You guys on a field trip or somethin'?
Idiot...
You're about to tangle with the
boss of Ishiyama, Kanzaki Hajime!
Kanzaki-senpai, that's crazy!
Stealin' the spotlight, all hyena-like!
Yeah!
And the next time you say
hyena I'll kick your ass.
Now we got a bunch of idiots
who think they're hot stuff.
I'll turn you all into mincemeat!
What? That's not a good sign.
Honoka?
What is it?
Um, it's not...
The big guy was wearing this for me!
I mean it's not like...
Hey!
You're...
Saotome...-sensei?
I don't know who you are, but if you
get in my way, I won't hold back.
That's pretty clichéd of you.
Try thinking a little more before you speak.
What?
And it looks like you've done a
real number on my students here.
Right, you piece of crap?
I'm gonna punish you good.
What is this overwhelming pressure?
My gut tells me to proceed with caution.
This man is dangerous.
I have to get rid of him immediately, or...
I'll ask you once more.
Who are you?
Whoa there...
Didn't your granny teach you to put down
your spear when you're talking to people?
Unfortunately...
...she was dead before I was born!
Oh, pardon me!
Fine, then I'll teach you.
What's this incredible Demon power?!
It's in Hecadoth's direction.
I can't believe this!
Is there anyone in the Human
World with such Demon power?
I think Hecadoth might be in over his head.
Enough playing around.
We'll meet up there.
Hold it, you!
Turnin' tail?
We'll finish with you later.
Be glad you're still alive, Humans.
All talk.
They got scared of my aura and ran off.
Seriously?
That's crazy! Hayena-senpai, you're crazy!
Who the hell're you callin' a hyena?!
Demons, huh?
I've got a lot to ask you, but
treating your wounds comes first.
Sorry...
And you take things way too far.
You might've gotten big, but you
haven't changed one bit on the inside.
Same with you.
What's that?
A Zebel Spell?
No way... A Spellmaster?
A contract with a Demon not on equal terms...
...where he's in control!
They still exist?
I thought they had all long perished
as relics from the old days!
I'm still here!
Don't make me sound like a dinosaur.
And wait... That mark...
Right from one to the next...
You people are disturbing the neighborhood!
You stirred up the hornet's nest, Hecadoth.
And out came the queen.
A Spellmaster, huh?
The three of us will take you on.
Whoa...
Watch closely, Oga.
This is a special lesson.
I'll show you the right way to use this.
Here we go!
For Demons #1:
Keep your arms tucked in,
feet at shoulder width...
Go tell Behemoth...
Wait a little longer!
They went back?
Now then, the real problem begins.
Hey, Oga...
Don't just stand there! Help out.
If we don't do something about Miss
Boobs here, she'll be in real danger.
Don't worry.
We will definitely save her.
Huh?
Alaindelon?
Honestly...
You can't even protect Miss Hilda?
You blockhead.
A black cat crossed my path!
My shoelaces snapped!
And even the stalks in my tea split in two!
So many bad omens!
What's your problem?
Anyway, what'll we do, Oga?
Those guys are sure to come back again.
Isn't it obvious?
There's only one thing to do
when you want to get stronger!
If a black cat's about to cross
your path, quickly turn around!
On the next Beelzebub:
It's Time for Training!
Training at my shrine?
Could it be... Secret special
training, just you and me?