I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers who keep
a close eye on the countless souls,
good and evil, that fill this world.
Aizen, who has brought chaos
upon the Soul Society,
has begun to set his plan in motion.
Arrancars, created by Aizen
using the Hogyoku,
a material that removes the boundaries
between Soul Reapers and Hollows,
appear in Karakura Town.
Damn it! I can't move my body!
I deny you...
so now you'll get in my way?!
Damn it!
Ulquiorra and Yammy defeat Ichigo,
but Urahara and Yoruichi manage
to drive them back in the nick of time.
Ichigo falls into a depression,
but before him appears
Captain Hitsugaya's advance guard,
who have been sent from Soul Society
to confront the Arrancars.
Fool!
It's those guys who beat you up
the other day!
More precisely,
there are three classes within the Menos.
The first is the "Gillian."
The second is "Adjuchas."
And the third is "Vasto Lordes."
They are the top class within
the Menos.
They are equal to humans in size.
There are said to be only a few of them
within Hueco Mundo, but...
I'll give it to you straight.
These Vasto Lordes are stronger
than our Soul Reaper captains!
If Aizen now has more than
ten of these Vasto Lorde
under his control...
It'll be the end of Soul Society.
We have returned...Lord Aizen.
Welcome back, Ulquiorra...
Yammy...
Now, tell me of your achievements...
in front of your 20 brothers.
Show me, Ulquiorra...
...what you saw and felt in
the World of the Living, everything.
Yes, sir.
Please have a look.
I see...
And that is why you decided
he was not worth killing.
Yes. Your orders were to "kill him
if he proved to be a hindrance to us."
How soft of you!
I would've squashed those bastards
with my first blow.
Grimmjow...
Whatever the reasoning,
if "kill him" was a part
of the order,
it would have been best to kill him,
of course! Right?!
I agree...
whatever the case, he's the enemy.
There may have been
no reason to kill him,
but there was even less reason
to let him live.
And besides, Yammy!
You were beaten up pretty bad!
You may say
he wasn't worth killing,
but it just sounds like
you couldn't kill him.
Damn you, Grimmjow...
Weren't you watching?
The ones who beat me up
were the guy wearing clogs
and the dark-skinned girl.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm saying I would have killed
those two with one blow as well!
What's that?!
Don't.
Grimmjow...
Do you understand that our problem
isn't this guy as he is now?
Huh?
What Lord Aizen is worried about
is not this guy as he is now,
but this guy's rate of growth.
True, his potential powers
were amazing.
But they were as unstable
as they were great.
If we leave things as is,
then there's a chance of him
either destroying himself,
or that we could bring him
under our control.
That's why I came back
without killing him.
That's why I'm saying you're soft!
If he gets bigger than you predict
and turns against us,
what do you plan to do?!
If that happens,
I'll get rid of him. That's all.
Can't complain about that,
can you?
Yes, well... That's fine.
Do whatever you want...Ulquiorra.
Thank you very much.
Say, is that really going to get it out?
Oh... It's out! This is it!
Ugh... It just seems so yucky...
The Soul Candy came out
so easily...
It sure is made simply,
or should I say poorly.
- That's the Department of Research...
- Hey...
- and Development for you, very unique.
- Hey, I said!
What do you want?
When are you guys
going back home?
What do you mean?
we're not going home.
We're going to stay until our fight
with the Arrancars is over.
Huh! You're staying?
But where are you going to sleep?
Let me make this clear.
We don't have enough space
to keep all of you!
Huh?! Not even me?
Y-Yikes! If you think about it,
you're the last person I'd allow to stay!
For that matter,
I have no idea why you would think
I'd let you stay in the first place!
What are you doing?!
You may undo a button,
but what's impossible is impossible!
Not even if you lift your skirt a little!
Damn! I will not give in
to temptation!
I'm a man who never gives in
If that's the case,
why don't you close your fingers?
Well, for now...
I'll have Orihime put me up!
What do you mean?
Did you already get her permission?
Not yet, but she's the type
that just can't say "no."
Wha--? Inoue and Rangiku will be
sleeping in the same room...
What a wonderful
forbidden flower garden!
How about a little mascot
for your flower gard-!
Do you want to come too, Captain?
You think I'd go, idiot?!
You should come! It'll be fun.
For you, maybe.
We're going too.
You have somewhere to go?
Of course not.
No need to worry.
And most of all,
I won't depend on you.
I'll find a place to stay on my own.
You'd better...
keep that wooden sword hidden!
Well then, I'll be going to
Mr. Urahara's place.
You're going to live off
of him again?
Of course not!
But...
There's something I want to
ask him about...
Is that so...?
Be careful!
So... Where do you plan to stay?
Hey! Wait a minute!
- Rukia!
- Don't be a fool!
This is the only place for me, of course!
Are you crazy?!
My family has seen you!
What excuse are you planning
to give them?!
Listen to me, you...!
Oh...
I smell a Hollow...
Shall we take care of it?
Leave it. Too much trouble.
There's that Soul Reaper Kurumadani
or whatever in charge, right?
Hm... I guess so.
But for a Hollow,
it smells a little funny...
Why do I keep worrying over it?
I feel stupid...
And you know, Kurosaki
has recovered!
And you know...
And...
I guess...
Kuchiki is really something...
I think I'm...a little jealous.
KUROSAKI CLINIC
And so you see.
I've lost everything...
my place to stay and
my money for food.
Oh boy...
Please let her stay here, Dad!
You've got it, Yuzu!
That's exactly what I was thinking!
Stay as long as you like, Rukia!
No, no...
Keep that thumb hidden, will you?
They'll catch on to your act.
Mother! Listen to me, Mother!
I now have a third daughter!
Of course, judging from
the way he's acting,
there's no sign
he has any doubts.
Yeah... It hit me in that instant!
A uniform, depending on
who's wearing it,
can become a lethal blade!
Like an invincible blade
that can shred our steel armor
of logic into nothingness.
Will you pipe down?
I'll leave you behind.
Huh?! Wait!
- You have no reaction at all?
- Ah, no... I don't mean you!
Hey! Hold it, will you?
Huh?
What is that...?
I'm really going to leave
you behind, Mr. Asano!
Quit being so formal!
I mean...! I saw this really
realistic monster up in the sky!
Will you stop that, Mr. Asano?!
Stop that!
You want to stay over? Here?
That's fine, but... Why?
- Great answer!
- O-Ow...!
I knew you'd say that!
That's what I love
about you, Orihime!
In that case, can I take a bath?
All the excitement today
got me all sweaty...
in my cleavage!
Oh... The bathroom's this...
Why don't you join me, Orihime?
Huh?
I've already had my-
Ouch! Ouch! That hurts Rangiku!
Oh! Just a minute!
What?
If you have nowhere else to go,
you can come in.
Huh?
Noisy woman.
How's the bath?
It's fine, but a little small...
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't mean it that way.
Say... Why are you so down today?
What? I-I'm not down...
You can talk to me about it.
I'll listen.
Oh...but...I'm not down.
If you don't talk to me,
I'll do something painful to you.
I'm sorry I was so weak!
And next time, I swear...
I will protect you.
Kuchiki is...really something,
isn't she?
Kurosaki was so depressed for
so long but she cheered him up.
She gave him a swift boot...
and made him perk up.
I'm terrible, aren't I?
I wanted Kurosaki to cheer up.
That's all I wanted...
Or so I thought, but...
When Kuchiki came back
and cheered up Kurosaki...
I should have been really happy,
and yet...
And yet...
And yet...I-I'm jealous...
of Kuchiki.
Kuchiki is kind and gentle...
strong and pretty...
and she cheered up Kurosaki.
I really like her...but why am I so...
I don't feel like this in school,
but when I return home
and I'm alone, I'm a mess.
Oh... This is so embarrassing!
I'm terrible...
Ran...giku...?
Ow-ow-ow...!
Silly girl.
Tickle-tickle-tickle-
tickle-tickle-tickle!
Please stop! Rangiku-san...
Ouch! Oh, I hit my head!
Silly girl...
You should just be yourself.
You and Kuchiki both...
Ichigo is still a kid
who can't stand up by himself.
That's why he needs both
you and Kuchiki.
What's wrong with being jealous?
Why, you're trying your best
to come to terms with
your serious emotions, aren't you?
Do you know?
It's so much easier to run away
from those emotions;
tossing them at the other person.
You're standing firm,
trying to deal with them.
That's really cool,
you know...Orihime.
There, there...
Let it all out, you!
You can cry on my chest, anytime!
Everyone here?
You didn't let anyone see you,
I hope.
Of course not.
Grimmjow...
Yeah?
On the way here,
I felt strong Spiritual Pressure
from several sources.
It doesn't match Ulquiorra's report.
Turn the Pesquisa
all the way up!
Just as I thought...
There are a lot more...
I guess they've called for
reinforcements from Soul Society.
If they'd nipped it in the bud,
things wouldn't have gotten
so complicated.
That's why I say you're soft...
Ulquiorra!
D Roy...
Shawlong...
Edrad...
Illfort...
Nakeem...
Capture all of them!
If they show even a hint
of Spiritual Pressure, capture them all!
FOR RUKIA♥
They just gave me
your sister’s room.
Well, that’s to be expected.
I was planning to stay in
your closet!
Don’t tell me.
Talk to my dad!
But that’s why I brought some things
to fix up that dingy closet.
Light! Bell! Massager!
A little window!
Worse and worse!
And didn’t you just slip in
the word “dingy”?
Here you go…
What is it?
Strange face…
Shut up!
Don’t you think it’s strange,
Yumichika?
What is?
This…This handmade riceball.
They’re handmade,
but so neat,
and packed in
this complicated wrapping.
They’re lined up in all the stores.
And according to the salesgirl,
they’re replaced several times a day.
I tell you, it’s insane!
I can’t believe that salesgirl
has that sort of ability.
I say there’s somebody
pulling strings in the background!
What a coincidence…
I just came to
the same conclusion!
I ate so much! I’ve had my fill!
It was delicious, Orihime!
R-Really?
Of course!
It didn’t look all that great,
but it tasted great.
Oh, I’m so glad!
No matter how much I cook,
there’s no one to eat the food
so I thought maybe there was
something wrong with my taste buds!
Oh, yes! Would you like
some ice cream, Rangiku?
Oh, that sounds good!
Let’s see…
If you put all kinds of toppings on it,
it’s even better!
What would you like?
– Delicious!
What do you have in yours, Orihime?
Would you like to try it?
What a weird color!
But it might be good!
– Yum!
Have you captured them all?
You will show them no mercy!
If they show even a glimmer
of Spiritual Pressure, kill them all!
Don’t let a single one escape!
Let’s go!
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
…And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
The blade of your Tensa Zangetsu
is as black as your heart.
Shut up! Why, your heart is
normally much blacker!
What are you saying?!
My heart is as pure and white
as this zanpakuto.
What’s with that zanpakuto?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
The mail is here.
Here you go.
Seventh Seat Yamada,
what about the rest?
Yes, well, they’re addressed
to Eighth Seat Ogido!
They’re mostly from women.
Eighth Seat Ogido is popular
with women.
Humph! I just can’t understand
why that guy is so popular!
Th-That’s right.
You have many finer points,
Third Seat Iemura!
For example…?
– Er, uh…
There’s none…?!