Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
A man named Muramasa
causes all of the Zanpakuto
to take physical form and attack.
Unable to use their Shikai,
the Soul Reapers are overpowered.
The Zanpakuto deliver
a serious blow to
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
in a single night and leave.
The Seireitei is now in
a confused, critical state.
Meanwhile, Rukia walks
through the Seireitei alone
in search of Byakuya,
who has gone missing,
when Sodenoshirayuki
appears before her once again.
Sodenoshirayuki…
You will now be free.
Rukia!
That was some show.
Who the hell are you?!
I am a…
Zanpakuto.
Hey there, what are you doing?
Do you see anything interesting?
That's none of your business.
What's with the attitude?!
That's really unpleasant.
Are you ignoring us?
Don't bother.
There's no point in fighting.
Our enemies are over there.
But…
They won't get away next time.
I'm going to get back
at that annoying bastard.
You’re right.
This time, I get to kill the guy
who calls me by a weird name.
Yeah. Let's teach them a lesson.
You're a Zanpakuto?!
That's right.
Sodenoshirayuki…
leave this to me.
You retreat for now.
Thank you.
Wait!
Where are you going,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
How do you know my name?
That is not important.
What?! What are you up to?
My goal is to release the Zanpakuto
from the Soul Reapers.
That's all.
I get it…
You're the one behind all this!
In that case, tell me how Rukia
can get her Zanpakuto back!
Ichigo Kurosaki,
what is a Zanpakuto?
What?
Zanpakuto are souls that are born
within the hearts of Soul Reapers.
They share the same power
as their Soul Reaper
and exist alongside
their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers find the power of
the Zanpakuto hidden
within their souls.
They converse with their Zanpakuto,
come to an understanding
and are able to draw from
their power by learning their name.
A few chosen Soul Reapers can
gain even more powerful Bankai,
by manifesting an incarnation of
their Zanpakuto and controlling it.
You and the captains
have done this.
But living alongside
Soul Reapers
is not the only way
for a Zanpakuto to live.
What do you mean?
I’m saying that a Zanpakuto
has its own will.
A Zanpakuto’s will?
Yes. Zanpakuto are not
a part of a Soul Reaper.
We are separate souls.
Our existence is equal
to that of Soul Reapers.
Do you find that unbelievable?
That is proof of how arrogant
you Soul Reapers are.
That's not true.
This is the reason why I exist.
I can understand
the Zanpakuto’s will.
I can talk to their souls.
And I can give physical forms to
those who share the same goals.
Impossible.
Zanpakuto who answer
my call become
separated from their Soul Reapers
and appear in this world.
That is the power given to me.
Why would the Zanpakuto
respond to you?
It is the will of Zanpakuto
who have been oppressed.
I…
I have never thought of
Sodenoshirayuki as an inferior.
Rukia!
That is just your
own one-sided opinion.
As you can see, Sodenoshirayuki
has responded to my call.
Stop pushing yourself.
Your have served your purpose.
What do you mean?
Do you really think
that you were able to
escape to the World of
the Living on your own?
What?
I want to release all Zanpakuto
from their Soul Reapers.
No exceptions.
In order to do that, I needed you,
Ichigo Kurosaki, to come here.
You let Rukia go on purpose?
Welcome to my world.
Ichigo…
It's all right. You rest here.
I won't let you get away with this!
Let's move away from here.
Do whatever you like.
Ichigo…
Getsugatensho!
Where is he?!
Put away your sword.
Damn it!
It's useless.
What is this?!
Damn it!
What the hell did you do?!
You bastard!
Hear my voice.
Follow your instincts
and release your soul.
Discard your fear. Look ahead.
Go forth. Don't stop.
If you turn back, you'll grow old.
If you're hesitant, you'll die.
Come. Your name is…Zangetsu!
What happened?
Ichigo…
Zangetsu… Why are you here?
Old Man Zangetsu!
What's the meaning of this?!
Answer me!
Weren't we of
one mind and body?!
Damn it!
You can still move?
It's over now.
Old Man…
Are you serious?
Damn it!
Getsugatensho.
Captain Unohana!
What's wrong, Isane?
Ma'am! I have a report
from Squad Twelve.
Zanpakuto have become
separate entities?
Yes.
What does that mean?
This is the conclusion that
Master Mayuri has come to
after testing this phenomenon
on his own body.
Could you give us the details?
Yes.
It seems the Zanpakuto's soul
really has left my body.
Interesting. Truly interesting.
Master Mayuri, aren't Zanpakuto
and Soul Reapers
different manifestations
of the same soul?
Normally, that is the case.
But now they have become
entirely separate entities.
Is such a thing possible...?
That's why this is interesting.
You're so worthless.
Don't act as if you understand!
But how was this made possible?
The situation is much worse
than I had imagined.
Umm… May I ask a question?
Since they're separate entities,
what'll happen if we defeat
one of the Zanpakuto
manifestations in battle?
I don't know.
Would we lose our
Zanpakuto forever?
It is possible.
But I cannot say
for certain because
we don't have enough data.
No…
I understand.
Let's leave this to
Captain Kurotsuchi.
Umm… One more thing.
Master Mayuri has a request
for you, Captain Unohana.
What is it?
He wants you to provide him with
data on the Soul Reapers who are
receiving treatment from Squad Four
so that he can analyze it.
Certainly. I will have it
all sent to you.
Also…
He wants to gather data
on you, as well.
Does he want Captain Unohana
to go all the way to
the Department of Research
and Development?
Yes. He said he needed
data on captains.
Very well.
Captain!
It's all right, Isane.
But… Umm…
But for Captain Kurotsuchi to
be personally inspecting your body
is so invasive.
We're in a race
against time, Isane.
Yes, ma'am.
In return, I want you to report
to us any new findings.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
Reporting!
Large-scale combat has been
confirmed in the Seireitei!
The Spiritual Pressures
at the scene belong to
Rukia Kuchiki of
Squad Thirteen
and Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki!
What's this?
Who the hell are you?
Aren't you Ichigo Kurosaki?
That's the other soul
that lives within him.
Other soul?
Getsuga…
…tensho!
Instant regeneration…?
This Spiritual Pressure…
As I suspected...
What's this?
I won't give it to you…
I'm not giving this body to you.
Don't do things
without my permission!
Zangetsu…
Zan…ge…
This man…
Why, Old Man Zangetsu?!
I'm bored with your internal world.
It's all buildings.
There's no greenery.
I want to see forests.
I want to see
the grandeur of nature.
I'll make a garden for you…
Why?
How come the Women’s
Soul Reaper Association
gets to go to the beach?!
We should also take
a vacation at the beach!!
We're going to have
a summer adventure!
That's right! Me too…
Me too!
It’s settled!
We're going to the beach too!
But the paperwork is tedious.
I'll do something about that!
Let's do it, Chairman!
– All right!
THEIR HARD WORK PAID OFF.
NOW, OFF TO THE BEACH!
What did we do to deserve this?