Aizen entered
the World of the Living
to wipe out
Karakura Town.
In order to stop him,
the Soul Reapers took up positions
in the World of the Living
to face the invasion.
Under orders from Genryusai,
to enable captain-class to battle
in the World of the Living,
Urahara constructed four pillars
on each side of
Karakura Town that formed a giant Senkaimon.
He then swapped
a fake Karakura Town,
that was built in Soul Society,
with the real Karakura Town.
Furthermore, Genryusai
stationed four Soul Reapers,
Ikkaku Madarame,
Izuru Kira,
Yumichika Ayasegawa
and Shuhei Hisagi,
at the base of each pillar
and assigned them
to defend the pillars.
The four easily
defeated the Hollows
that attempted to
destroy the pillars,
but they are now faced with
Espada Barragan's Fracciones
standing in their way.
Oh.
What is it, Ichimaru?
Well,
I get the feeling,
Izuru is really angry.
You're worried about
the subordinate you abandoned?
You can't blame him
for being disheartened.
It doesn't seem that way.
What?
I'm glad to see him doing so well.
I like it.
That's the face I wanted to see.
That's the face of a man in battle!
Scrape the Summit, Aguila!
– Break!
– Break, break, break,
– break, break, break!
Break down along with your spirit!
Break down along with your nose!
What do you mean, "Break down
along with your spirit"?!
Everything you say is so nasty,
you ugly bastard!
Yeah? Well you said,
"Break down along with your nose"!
The things you say when
inflicting damage are so specific,
it pisses me off,
you ugly bastard!
– Who're you calling "ugly,"
– you bastard?!
I've been listening to you call me
"ugly" over and over.
The one calling someone "ugly"
is the real ugly one, you know?!
Have you been counting correctly?
You've said ugly
three more times than I have!
If calling someone "ugly"
makes you ugly,
then doesn't that make you
three times uglier than me?
Shut up already!
It doesn't seem like talking
will do any good.
So I have a proposal.
Let's make it simple.
Proposal?
The one that dies is the ugly one.
I like it.
I can prove that I am superior
in both strength and beauty.
You really never stop talking,
do you?
That makes me happy.
You're welcome.
All right, shall I get
just a tad bit serious then?
Special kill…
Beautiful Charlotte Chuhlhourne's…
Miracle, Sweet, Ultra-Funky,
Fantastic, Dramatic, Romantic,
Sadistic, Erotic, Exotic,
Athletic Guillotine Attack!
Oh my, did he die?
Was that too strong maybe?
I'm not that easy!
That much power in one attack.
Damn monster.
Oh? Lost your energy?
You can't compete
with my beauty
if you're already like that,
you know.
Who's lost energy?
That "killing technique" just now,
I was just feeling sick because of
that god-awful name you gave it.
What?! Are you jealous?!
You're jealous of my unique and
exceptional taste, aren't you?!
It's jealousy, isn't it?!
Be honest!
Stop talking nonsense
while swinging that funny hair
all over the place!
Did you stick seaweed in there
to get that hairdo?!
S-S-S-Seaweed?!
How dare you call
my lovely black hair,
black as the darkness of night,
with its healthy, shiny cuticle,
seaweed, of all things!
If you're going to say that,
then you're a toadstool!
You black toadstool!
Black toadstool?!
When it's all said and done,
you're just feeling inferior
because you couldn't stop
my wonderful killer technique.
You're really too much.
Your mouth is the only thing
that's still active.
Why don't you give it another try?
Then you'll see just how
pathetically overconfident you are.
Oh really?
Since you insist…
Let's try this one more time,
shall we?!
Here he comes!
Go!
Special kill!
Beautiful Charlotte Chuhlhourne's
Perfect, Stylish, Dangerous,
Psychedelic, Variable, Economical,
Continental, Incredible,
Unbelievable
Shining Attack!
Take this!
So you can fight!
Still say I lack energy?
It seems you do have energy.
I'm glad.
That's what I expect of my rival.
Rival, eh?
Sounds like you've
acknowledged me.
Not that I'm glad,
of course,
coming from someone with
a weird hairdo like you.
What?!
You ugly piece of crap!
How dare you ruin my beauty,
so perfect in every way that
it leaves people gasping in
admiration and amazement,
so perfect,
it deserves more than praise!
Unforgivable, unforgivable,
unforgivable, unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
Is he going to do it?
Glitter!
Reinas de Rosas!
What?!
What the hell is that?!
That's a fresh reaction.
Nice.
A beauty truly unimaginable
to someone so ugly…
is how I'd describe myself.
This design, that goes from
my shoulders to my waist,
is an embodiment
of true beauty
that conjures
a silhouette of flowers.
And wonderfully
completes a look
that possesses both
novelty and elegance.
At the ankles and wrists is…
Shut up!
Sorry!
Oops!
I impulsively apologized!
I mean, that was sneaky!
No way.
I can't help it…it's so ridiculous.
Odd… I thought I heard
Yumichika's harsh laughter.
That couldn't be,
not during a fight.
Whoa!
I told you, you're too slow!
You can't win a fight with
just muscles, big boy!
I've finally calmed down.
Fine. All right.
In other words, it means…
Ugly people find it difficult
to even comprehend beauty.
Isn't that it?!
He's several times faster!
Don't be surprised just yet!
Damn!
Damn…
That single blow gave me
three fractures in my left arm.
Are you beginning to
appreciate my beauty?!
Screw you!
Then I'll teach you.
Be thankful!
You get to experience my aesthetics
from me personally.
Don't go pushing
your wacko aesthetics on me.
Wacko?!
Bloom, Fujikujaku!
Fooled ya.
What?!
You call that Fujikujaku?
What a plain name that matches you.
But all that happened is
your blade became four!
Special kill…
Beautiful Charlotte Chuhlhourne's
Lovely, Cutie, Fanatic,
Aquatic, Dynamic, Dometiti…
Oops, bit my tongue,
Thunder Punch!
Biting my tongue caused me
to lose half of its power.
But you did notice
how not only my speed,
but also my power have
increased as well, right?
It's all because of my beauty.
Feel it. This overwhelming beauty.
Power is beauty.
Beauty is power.
Isn't it about time you understand?
I can't.
I see…
So you can't understand.
Okay. All right.
Then I'll forgive you.
It isn't a crime to lack
a sense of beauty.
In fact,
it's worthy of pity.
Oh yeah?
Living with a vulgar aesthetic
is nothing but torture.
In that case,
relieving you
from that torture
is my duty, being the most
beautiful of things.
You say whatever you want,
don't you?
Accept this…
Special kill!
Beautiful Charlotte Chuhlhourne's
Final, Holy, Wonderful,
Pretty, Super, Magnum,
Sexy, Sexy, Glamorous Cero!
That's just an ordinary Cero!
Damn!
That's a dirty technique!
It's attack is so broad that
there's no way to get away.
It's over!
For whom?!
I told you!
What's the big deal about
your blades increasing?!
What?!
Okay!
I told you. It's over.
A princess always gets her way.
If I say it's over, it's over.
W-What…is this?
Rosa Blanka, the Sentence
of the White Rose.
My most beautiful,
most cruel technique.
Enveloped in this briar
covered with black,
you will die,
unseen by anyone,
smothered in white petals.
Unseen…by anyone?
That's right.
This ebony-black briar shuts out
all views from the outside.
People outside will
not even be able to
detect your Spiritual Pressure.
Not only will you
not leave the image
of the moment of your death
in anyone's eyes,
but no one will even notice
your weakening Spiritual Pressure.
There is no crueler end for someone,
who takes pride
in their beauty,
don't you think?
In anyone's eyes…
I see.
Thank you.
Tear in Frenzy,
Ruriirokujaku.
What is this?!
What is this? This thing!
It's futile.
Take a look.
Buds?!
It's becoming larger?
That's your Spiritual Pressure
collecting in there.
What?!
Those flowers are growing by
stealing your Spiritual Pressure.
From here on,
all the Spiritual Pressure
you radiate
will become that
of the flowers.
Do you understand?
Why'd you wait until now
to use such a technique?!
If you had fought
an ordinary battle,
I would not normally have
had to use this technique.
But didn't you say that yourself?
That inside this ebony-black briar,
no one would see me or
sense my Spiritual Pressure?
That's why I decided to
show it only to you.
To you, who will be defeated.
I don't want to show anyone
this Ruriirokujaku.
Ruriirokujaku?!
It's almost time.
The moment those flowers bloom,
will be your end,
Charlotte Chuhlhourne!
D-Damn it!
The flower petal was creating such
a great atmosphere near the end.
Are you sure that last scream
was satisfactory for you?
You have a point!
Oh, darn it!
How'd that sound?
Okay, let's do it over!
Unfortunately,
there's no time for that.
Damn it!
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
Okay, let's go to the next store!
Rangiku,
we can't carry any more.
Don't worry.
We have that official cloakroom
approved by
the Women's Soul Reaper
Association.
R-Rangiku!
Hold on to these for us, okay?
Thank you for taking care of them.
On to the next store!
The rooms of
Substitute Soul Reapers
are used as cloakrooms by
the Women's Soul Reaper
Association.
Please, no more of this!