Is your sister okay?
Yeah.
What?
Don’t get the wrong idea.
Huh?
I didn’t come because I owe you.
I want my powers back so
I can protect everyone.
That’s all.
You won’t admit it, huh.
This is…my…
That’s the symbol of your power, right?
Keep it secure.
I will.
Now for today's weather.
Rain clouds covering western Japan
are bringing in slightly
heavy showers to the
Shikoku region, with 10mm per hour.
The clouds will continue to cover
the Shikoku and Kyushu regions.
Periods of rain showers will
come in through the afternoon.
Yuzu, go to bed already.
What about you, Karin?
I... uh…have things to do.
Like what?
It doesn’t matter.
If this is about Brother Ichi,
I’ll stay up and chew him
out when he comes back.
I’m telling you to go
to bed because you have
to cook and stuff in the morning!
Brother’s got nothing to do with it!
I’m not worried about him!
It’s okay to be worried, you know!
Brother Ichi’s been
acting strangely lately,
and it’s only natural to worry when
he comes home very late
several nights in a row!
I said I’m not worried!
You are!
I’m not! Get off my case!
What?!
I’m home.
-Brother!
-Brother Ichi!
What? You’re both still up?
Go to bed already.
You’ll be late for school tomorrow.
Well?
Okay!
-Good night, Brother!
-Good night, Brother Ichi!
For the past week, I did
everything you told me to do.
So?
Why am I back here again?
You complain, and yet you came in.
Thanks.
Shut up!
You want your Soul Reaper
powers back, don’t you?
That’s why I’m here.
I thought we’d be doing some
training-type thing in a big place.
That’s right!
We are doing some training-type
thing in a big place!
What’re you staring at?!
Nothing…
You know, Riruka…
I think it’s time you
stop kicking the door open.
I don’t appreciate having to
see your panties every time.
Oh, yeah?
Yukio…
What makes you think you
can speak to me like that?
You think you can say whatever you want,
just because we have a guest?
Well, guess again!
A creepy geek like you who plays video games
all day has no right to
talk to me like an equal!
Got that?!
I’ve never, then or now,
thought of you and me as equals!
Sorry.
Could you repeat that again?
Oh, yeah? Yukio… What
makes you think you can…
You don’t have to repeat.
Let go of me, Jackie!
All right, all right…
Forget about that and get on with
explaining that box to Ichigo.
Stop nagging me!
You don’t have to remind me.
I’ll explain it right now!
What’re you just standing there for?!
Come over here so I can explain it to you!
Fine, already…
And why am I being yelled at?
Wait!
Stop!
You’re fine right there!
Don’t come a step closer!
C’mon, make up your mind…
Observe this box!
I’m looking.
Well?
Well what?
Isn’t it cute?!
Huh?
You should be happy!
This cute dollhouse is
your training facility!
What?
You don’t have to understand!
I’ll show you soon enough!
Show me?
My Fullbring!
My Fullbring is called “Dollhouse”!
I have the ability to move
people or things at will
into and out of objects that I
think are cute or that I love.
That’s your pass.
Okay, you can go inside now!
Go inside?
I permit you to.
What’re you talking…
That hurt…damn it…
What just happened?
You’re kidding me…
Well? Isn’t it cute?
Cute, my ass!
What the hell is that thing?!
Defeat him!
What?
You’re so dense.
Fight and defeat him!
That’s your training!
You’ll do fine!
He’s not strong, so it’ll be easy!
If you can use Fullbring, that is!
What?!
Damn it!
Why’re you running away? You’re pathetic!
Fight him! Be a man!
Are you an idiot?!
I can’t grasp the situation
I’m in right now!
Facing him is out of the question!
Explain!
How did I become so tiny,
and how did I get inside this toy box house?!
I told you.
That’s the power of
“Dollhouse,” my Fullbring.
Fullbring is the power of love.
Love?!
It’s the ability to draw
out the maximum power
from something a person loves.
A guy like Ginjo, who only
likes his pendant, turns
that into a weapon to fight with.
But I’m different!
I have many things that I love,
and I will find many more from here on!
I will spend my life collecting
things that I love,
and my wish is to die, smothered
by the things I love!
“Dollhouse” is the ability for
things that I’ve given permission to
move in and out of my favorite objects!
I just gave you permission and invited
you into my favorite box here!
You’re enjoying this, aren’t you?
Okay! Explanation’s over!
Now, mind getting on with defeating this guy?
Don’t be chicken!
You’ll be fine!
It’s set up so you can defeat him
if you’re able to use Fullbring!
Give it a try! Come on!
Are you nuts?
Is Fullbring supposed to be so easy
that all I have to do is try?!
I thought this was supposed to be training
to regain my Soul Reaper powers?!
Why do I have be able to use Fullbring?!
You sure yack a lot!
Just keep quiet and do as you’re told!
Do you have to have an explanation
to put your life on the line?
You suck!
Do you realize what you’re saying?
You’re speaking like a dictator!
Oh!
You’re getting better at dodging!
Shut up!
Don’t just watch, at least give me a hint!
It’s crazy to expect me to use
Fullbring without even a clue or hint!
A hint?
We were able to use Fullbring
from the moment we were born!
How would I know any clues or hints!
Are you stupid or something?
Hey, stupid!
Damn it!
Hey…enough already, kid…
Huh?
Stop running away and start fighting!
It can talk?!
Of course it talks!
Inside “Mr. Pork” is a scary dude
that I abducted from this neighborhood!
You did what?!
Wait, this thing’s name is Mr. Pork?!
Where’s the love in that?!
Stay still and let me kill you!
If I don’t beat you dead within 15 minutes,
this spell will become permanent
and I’ll be stuck inside this
goofy plushie for the rest of my life!
And you threatened him with a lie!
What do you mean, “goofy”?!
I’m sorry!
Okay! That’s all the advice from me!
Call me when you’re done, okay?
H-Hey, wait, you!
Nope!
Damn it, she closed it!
Hey, hey!
Let me out of here, hey!
I think I’ll have a snack!
-Let me out, damn it!
-Giriko, make me some tea!!
-Are you listening?!
I want a nice hot milk tea!
The same kind they serve at
the place in Henri Dubois!
Will he be all right?
Who knows…
Stop, you!
Let me beat you dead!
Damn…
She has no intention of letting me
out or giving any helpful advice…
What a nasty woman.
I said stop!
Simply running won’t get me anywhere…
I’ve got to think of something!
Fullbring is the power of love!
The ability to draw out the maximum power
from something a person loves.
But it didn’t seem like Ginjo
“loves” that pendant…
If I had to say, it was more
like an “attachment”…
Which means that for me to
become able to use Fullbring,
I’ll need an object like that.
Isn’t there something? Something…
If you’re so worried,
why don’t you help him?
I’m not worried!
Fine, whatever…
If he’s going to get killed so easily,
then he wasn’t all that much!
But Riruka…
Are you really sure?
That plushie has a timer, right?
It’s going to be…
15 minutes soon.
Thank you for doing the shopping, Mr. Chad.
What’s that?
This is crazy!
You’re already starting
his Fullbring training?!
What do you mean “already”?
The sooner the better!
Are you criticizing my methods, too?
There’s got to be something…
Ichigo!
Your Combat Pass!
Just a minute, Chad!
What’re you doing?!
If you’re going to learn Fullbring,
your Combat Pass is your only chance!
We think alike!
I was just thinking the same thing!
Time is up.
As stipulated, because Fullbring
was not detected within 15 minutes,
“Crazy Beast Mode” will be activated.
Please...don’t!
This is cruel…don’t…
W-What’s happening?
Oh…
It seems the timer has been activated.
Hey!
You didn’t tell me he was
going to become that hideous!
What were you thinking, Giriko?!
My, my…
You were the one who asked my help in
training Mr. Ichigo, Miss Riruka.
Yes, but…
You didn’t have to make it so hideous.
There must’ve been any
number of other ways!
Well, I couldn’t think of any…
Look, you...
Riruka!
Let Ichigo out of this box right now!
You mustn’t.
Like the plushie, that box
has a timer on it as well.
“If the organism inside
can survive for 30 minutes,
then it can exit the box.”
What kind of condition is that?!
You left the conditions up to me as well.
Removing Mr. Ichigo from the box now
would be a violation of the terms.
If you do that, the god of
time will seek retribution.
God of time?
I believe this is the first
time I told you about it.
The timer is set such that,
in the event of a breach,
all objects being timed
will be burned away without
a trace by the Flame of Time.
You’re bluffing!
You can believe me or not, that is up to you.
It’s not a bluff.
I’ve seen it happen many times…
Convinced?
Just so you understand, let me repeat myself.
If, before another 15 minutes go by,
either Mr. Ichigo or Mr. Pork
is removed from the box,
Mr. Ichigo, Mr. Pork and the box,
all three will be consumed
by the Flame of Time.
That is my Fullbring,
“Time Tells No Lies.”
Deactivate it!
That is impossible.
Once set, Time Tells No
Lies cannot be undone,
even by myself, who controls its power.
A mistake in setting the terms…
leads to death.
Don’t ever take it lightly.
Meddling with time is a frightening thing.
Oh…
Looks like the next tea is ready.
Would you like another cup, Miss Riruka?
Ah…a wonderful aroma.
God dwells in exact time.
What do I do?
If I’m to manifest this Fullbring
thing using my Combat Pass…
How do I do it?
Fullbring is…
Our ability is drawing out the
“soul” in an object and
putting that object to use.
I have to draw out the
soul of the Combat Pass.
How am I supposed to do that?!
How?!
Your pride!
When I first became able to
use Brazo Derecho Del Gigante,
what was in my heart was pride!
The material that forms
the basis for my Fullbring
is the skin on my two arms!
Skin?!
My skin is on the dark side because
I have Mestizo blood in me!
My appearance! My big body!
They’ve caused me lots of difficult times!
But I never lost the pride I had in my skin!
I was able to be proud…
because of my Abuelo!
My grandfather gave me
the strength to be proud!
Think back, Ichigo!
Remember the time when you
were proud of your Soul Reaper powers!
The Combat Pass will respond to your heart!
Remember!
Ichigo!!
When I was proud of my Soul Reaper powers?
There were…
Too many times to count!
If I lose this fight, I’ll be stuck
like this for the rest of my life!
It’s okay. You’ll turn back to normal.
I swear that chick is an evil witch!
I’m going to be stuck like this until
I get a kiss from the person
who knows true love!
Look at you, you’re a damn pork!
I heard that the patient
in the private room is the
hospital director’s son!
Then if I can make him mine,
I’d be like Cinderella?!
But isn’t he still a high school student?
Don’t you see…
Those studious types are all the
more worthwhile to seduce…
you know!
So…
Why are you bringing me my meal?
A patient mustn’t complain to his doctor.
URYU ISHIDA
NO VISITORS ALLOWED – FROM THE HOSPITAL DIRECTOR
Hurry and eat your meal quietly!
URYU ISHIDA
NO VISITORS ALLOWED – FROM THE HOSPITAL DIRECTOR
NO CHILD KNOWS HOW DEAR HE IS TO HIS PARENTS