Odd Jobs Gin-chan
What? A tour?
My friend, Satsuki-chan,
asked for an educational tour of
Odd Jobs to fulfill an assignment.
Stop offering to do stuff
that's a pain in the ass.
If she wants to see us at work,
we don't have any jobs today.
We haven't had any jobs in forever.
We don't want to ruin
the hopes and dreams of young children.
No!
I want to show them how great
Odd Jobs Kagura-chan is!
Do something about it, scumbags!
Stop tacking on random insults.
She's here!
You guys better act like grown-ups.
Don't do anything weird!
Welcome, Satsuki-chan!
Sorry, Kagura-chan.
I'm sure that you're busy.
Thank you!
I Can't Remember a Damn
Thing About the Factory Tour
This is our strategist/Supreme
Commander of Eastern Operations,
Strategos Shimura.
Supreme Commander of
Eastern Operations?!
Shut up and follow my lead.
Just say stuff that sounds cool.
Wow, Supreme Commander
of Eastern Operations...
Um, what kind of work
do you do at Odd Jobs?
O-Our president will explain that,
so come on inside.
President, the kids are
here for their tour.
May we come in?
He's turned the room into
a workshop or something...
Uh, President?
Bah, it's no use.
The naked refuses to
jack in to the solid.
U-Uh, President...
Could you shut the door?
If you let the heat escape,
my Patriot will cool down and harden.
Oh, s-sorry!
What's a Patriot supposed to be?
I have no idea what's going on,
but the president sounds
like a real craftsman.
Um, we're here to see you at work.
Do you prefer Calcutta or Meso Gear?
Huh?
If you're here, you must prefer one.
Ignore them.
Ignore their pleas for help.
I-I like Calcutta.
M-Me too.
They randomly chose one!
Me too.
They randomly chose Calcutta!
I see, you choose Calcutta.
Hmph, how precocious of you.
Here.
Calcutta should be
enjoyed while it's hot.
Th-Thank you very much!
This is Calcutta?
It looks like coffee.
Why didn't you just ask them
if they liked coffee or not?!
You're pissing me off!
I once tried to be
brave and try Calcutta.
But now I'm a devout fan of Meso Gear.
Edo Strawberry Milk
I believe that my
dedication to Meso Gear
was a product of that bitter experience.
He's throwing together
a bunch of fancy phrases
to say absolutely nothing at all!
Can we get started?
What do you Odd Jobs people even do?
Well, it's quite difficult
to explain what we do.
You could say that we are
essentially a secret society
involved in the production
and sale of this Patriot.
That would make us Patriot salesmen!
What is this Pastry...
Patriot.
What is this Patriot used for?
Don't make me laugh.
What is a Patriot used for, Kagura-kun?
Kids say the darndest
things, right, President?
What's with them?
They're pissing me off!
Let me ask you this then.
What's that below your nose?
Every person has a peculiar indentation
between their nose and mouth.
What is that used for?
I-I don't know...
Of course.
Now, back to the Patriot.
It's pretty much like that.
So you don't know either?!
Whether it's the indentation
below your nose
or the built-in microphone on the
Famicom's second player controller,
there are many things in this
world that make no sense.
However, humans are meant
to eat, poop, and sleep.
Everything else we do is useless.
Our creations fall into that category.
So after making a pompous speech,
all you're saying is that we make junk!
Okay.
So you do useless work
making useless stuff?
It seems that you didn't
understand what I was saying.
My point was that useless can
be valuable in its own way.
Yeah, but...
If all Odd Jobs does
is make useless stuff,
doesn't that mean the
members are also useless?
What's with this kid?
That's not nice, Daigoro-kun.
Satsuki-chan, we can call off the tour.
It's clear that these Odd Jobs people
do useless work that
doesn't help society.
Wait a moment!
While the Patriot may look
useless, it is, in fact,
a multimedia product which can be
used in a number of useless games.
Oh? Really?
What kind of games are
you talking about?
For example...
You can use the Patriot missile to whack
the head of someone who pisses you off.
You don't need the Patriot to do that!
I knew it.
I can't believe that people actually
pay you scum to make this trash.
Daigoro-kun?!
You sound like a different person
after the beating to your head!
Satsuki, I'm going home.
I've had enough.
Daigoro-kun!
Wait, boy.
You didn't drink your Calcutta...
Sorry, Mr. President.
I don't like Calcutta or Meso Gear.
I go for Bourbon.
That's pretty hard-boiled!
What's with this kid?!
I'll need to work hard to find
a real job so I don't
end up like you slobs.
Thanks for showing me what it's like
at the bottom of society, Odd Jobs.
Cheer up, Gin-san.
A child wouldn't be able to understand
how incredible Odd Jobs truly is.
The other kids said they had fun.
Though they tossed the Patriots
we gave them as souvenirs.
I started this business from scratch,
and I kind of like it.
But I guess kids aren't impressed...
Th-That's not true!
Okay, tell me this then.
What can this be used for?
Can't think of anything, right?!
'Course you can't!
I can't either!
I'm no different from
this piece of junk!
Odd Jobs is trash!
We do work that doesn't mean
a damn thing to society!
He's completely snapped.
It must have been a big shock to him.
Huh? Isn't that Hijikata-san?
We patrol the streets to
make sure there aren't any
bad people doing bad things.
That's the most essential
job of a policeman.
Ooh!
What is it?
Who would be a bad person?
Anyone who breaks the law.
So the law is always good?
In most cases, the law
can be considered good...
I have a question then!
You aren't allowed to drop down from
a train platform to the tracks,
but what if someone jumps down
to save a drunk who
happened to fall down?!
Would someone who stays on the platform
as the drunk dies be considered good?!
You take those situations case by case.
A law that's always changing
can't be considered a proper law!
I didn't word that right.
A person who makes trouble
for others is a bad person.
The law doesn't matter.
He just threw out the law!
He got sick of trying
and threw out the law!
By that logic, you would
be a criminal for exposing
us to second-hand smoke!
I'm sorry! Too much smoke for you?!
Please forgive me! Please forgive me!
This is bad!
He's about to lose it!
He's about to turn into a criminal!
Could you explain how much
trouble a person must cause
to be considered a criminal?
For example...
We have an individual getting
the snot knocked out of him
by the woman he keeps stalking.
Which one is the criminal?
Uh...
I was just joking.
In reality, policemen are...
...people involved in the production
and sale of this Patriot.
He threw out everything and
became a Patriot salesman!
What's going on?!
Is this a new fad?!
Pathetic.
You switch jobs when
the going gets tough?
Guess they weren't lying
when they said the police
in Japan were going to hell.
Now it's Hijikata-san's turn to lose it.
I didn't realize you could
use the Patriot that way.
Stop this foolishness.
Tsukuyo-san?
Please, lady!
We want to learn more about
the people who work in Yoshiwara!
And I told you to come
back in a hundred years.
Ooh!
Could you at least teach us how to
whip a man in a way
that brings pleasure?
There's a very familiar
freak mixed in there!
Now, that's the last
thing I would teach you.
I'm in a relationship
with this guy right now.
So you'll take responsibility
if something goes wrong
when the time comes?
Nothing will go wrong!
It's all in your head!
I guess it'll be too late
if something goes wrong.
Well, it's probably a good idea
to learn the general basics now.
Allow me to explain then.
If this is that, and this
is where you do that...
What are you doing with that Patriot?!
That's what girls are like?!
I was trying to give them a simple
explanation without revealing anything...
Stop playing dumb!
Teach me the secret
techniques of Yoshiwara!
Well, as you can see, our job isn't
always a walk in the park.
However, we never give up.
Believe in a better tomorrow
and stay on the trail.
That's how you become a stalker.
That's not a job!
Oh!
Yes, what is it?
Do you ever want to die?
What kind of question is that?!
A very good question.
It's not a good question!
A job is supposed to be painful.
In that case, you should look
for pain that you can enjoy.
How can you say that while
pretending to be a professional?!
That is naive!
There are many people with
jobs they absolutely hate!
Society needs these people to function!
Look at me!
You think I want to be a Patriot?!
Hey!
I seriously have no idea what
a Patriot is supposed to be!
But I don't have a choice!
If I don't do this, who will?!
This world needs Patriots!
The hell it does!
The people who always blame others...
...can never have a better life.
How would you...
How would you know how it
feels to be a Patriot?!
I know.
Huh?
After all... After all...
I'm working two jobs as
both a Patriot and a stalker!
That just means you fail at life!
Y-You too?
Yeah, you don't have to
bear the burden alone.
Ask me for help.
Th-Thank you.
Uh, excuse me.
So what's a Patriot?
No idea.
What are you people doing?
You grown-ups let a bunch
of kids bully you around.
It's the job of a grown-up to
teach kids what's important.
We can't let their tour end like this.
Daigoro, there's a letter for you.
Letter?
Invitation to an educational
tour of a Patriot factory.
What's this?
Daigoro!
You received an invitation too?
Oh, you guys also got one?
Invitation to an educational
tour of a Patriot factory.
I was gonna ignore it,
but I heard that we'll
get Dokkiriman stickers.
So, what's a Patriot factory?
Welcome to the Patriot Factory
We've been waiting for you, kids.
You brats, I mean, nice children
were chosen from around the world
to tour this factory of dreams!
I'm Pachi!
I'm Gura!
We'll be your guides on this
tour of the factory of dreams!
Isn't this a total rip-off of
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?
Excuse me, what is the
purpose of this tour?
What? You don't appreciate
our invitation?
Feel free to leave.
But you won't get any
Dokkiriman stickers.
And you'll lose your chance
to learn what Patriots are.
Who cares about Patriots...
Look! Look!
It's a Patriot factory!
No way! I don't believe it!
I never imagined that a Patriot
factory would be here!
I heard that they were only produced by
NASA, the FBI, and the NBA!
Let's take a look.
Wait, Sarutobi!
Chief, I found some suspicious people
who were investigating the Patriot.
I immediately shot them down.
Roger that.
So the Succeed Committee
has finally made its move.
The time of Ragnarok is upon us.
We must hasten the
development of the Patriot.
I also see some funny-looking kids.
Should I take them out?
They are my guests.
The last hope of humanity.
The children who will
inherit the Patriots.
Welcome to the Patriot factory tour.
Chief!
The kids aren't interested
in the Patriot.
I see.
But you've seen too much already.
Take them out...
You can leave.
Be careful on the way home.
This way.
Seriously! We should leave!
They'll kill us if we leave!
We'll have to do as they say and
tour the Patriot factory.
But...
Take a look at this.
History of the Patriot
You can see the history and
development of the Patriot here.
Here, you will find the
current Patriot design.
However, Patriots have been
around since the Jomon period.
Thanks to trial and error,
we were able to create one of
the essential tools in our life.
I've never used one before.
This would be the father of the Patriot,
the oldest one known,
which was created by
the chief of the Zugomanda tribe.
Isn't that a drumstick?
It may look like one, but
this is, in fact, a Patriot.
Look over here.
It says "not for
consumption" on the side.
It has to be edible if
there are preservatives!
The original Patriot was known as the
boned Patriot or Kin(Patriot)Man.
There's only one word
that would fit in there!
In the Heian period,
the Tang ambassador Zugomaru Kakinomoto
altered the design significantly.
He brought ingredients
back from the Tang
to make it a Spicy Patriot...
That's just spicy chicken!
And somebody took a bite out of it!
Zugomaru's still got
some around his mouth!
And in the Sengoku period,
Zugomanzo turned the
Patriot into something.
Why is it part of a combo now?!
Did Zugomanzo even do anything?!
This is like the history
of fried chicken!
And eventually we reached
the current Patriot design.
Why?!
You skipped over the
most important part!
Now that you have some basic
knowledge of the Patriot,
we'll give you a tour of the factory.
We'll see how the
Patriot is constructed.
As you can see, the Patriot
is made up of three parts.
The tissue box, which
is known as the solid.
Uh, you called it a tissue
box, so why call it the solid?
The toilet paper, which
is known as the naked.
And the stick.
Why did you stop coming up with names?!
You jack in the three
parts to create a Patriot.
Look at the conveyor belt.
I don't see a thing.
Maybe the place is a mess
because the chief is dead?
The chief is moving down the belt!
The first step is to fix
the broken factory chief.
That's where you start?!
Broken chief?! You're
the ones who broke him!
The factory chief was
broken to begin with.
Nobody respects the chief!
First, we use tissues
to wipe up the bloody body.
That's one of the
parts for the Patriot!
Start assembling the Patriot already!
Next, we use toilet paper to
wipe away his bloody past.
Who cares about his past?!
Make the Patriot already!
And then you use the
Patriot to wake him up.
The Patriot's already finished!
Why would you use a Patriot
to make a Patriot?
Then you repeat the process three times.
You're just abusing him!
And aren't these the
people who were shot?
The chief must settle past accounts
before he can be revived.
They're just getting revenge!
Heal
And finally, we send the factory
chief into the healing machine.
The factory chief is complete!
Nothing changed!
This is the completed form
of the factory chief.
He was born broken.
What was the point of
that whole process then?!
In the second step,
we give the assembled
factory chief motivation.
Otherwise known as giving
the factory chief a goal.
Enough with the chief!
The chief is absolutely necessary
for the production of a Patriot,
so this can't be avoided.
When are you going to make a Patriot?!
This is turning into a factory
for making factory chiefs!
I could only see the stars back then.
Hm? What's that?
They put him in a school uniform.
It's so fast!
I can barely keep up!
Hey! Look over there!
Do your best! Become the best
factory chief in Japan!!
Hooray! Hooray! Do your best!
Why are they acting like
he's on a train to Tokyo?!
We believe in you!
You can become the best
factory chief in Japan!
You can do it, Facto!
His name is Facto?!
Hey!
What kind of process is this?!
Now we have some kind of funky set!
You want to become a factory chief?!
You were destined to inherit
my toilet paper business from the
day you were born!
Who's that?!
Go to Edo to work for a tissue factory?!
Don't look down on me!
You think that toilet paper's
only meant for wiping the ass?!
Why is the factory chief's father here?!
This must be a flashback.
He was kicked out of his home,
which would explain the previous scene.
Darling!
Stop it!
Our son is making paper in his own way!
Now his mother's here?!
Let me go, Isako!
This is a discussion between men!
Ah, Facto!
Where are you going?!
I'm not finished with you yet!
Roof
What are they trying to do?!
Oh, he's wearing his old clothes again.
Oh, chief.
Good work.
He has a buddy with him now!
Why are you taking a nap here?
He's not taking a nap!
He's been out cold on the
conveyor belt this whole time!
Thinking about old times again?
Your old man was really something.
A family of toilet paper men
who refused to use tissues.
When wiping his ass,
blowing his nose, writing down notes...
He even used toilet paper
for the tires on his car.
Is the last one even necessary?!
You left your home
because you didn't want
to follow in his footsteps.
And so, you became the
chief of a tissue factory.
You still refuse to use toilet paper?
You're just as stubborn as your father.
Still, chief...
If your old man saw you now,
I'm sure he'd be willing to use tissues.
He never changed...
He was always so stubborn.
He used toilet paper to wipe
his ass and blow his nose.
When your tissues first went on sale,
he used toilet paper
to wipe away the tears.
Tissues weren't good enough for him.
Chief!
What are you thinking?!
You really think this
product will sell?!
I can't go along with this!
Hey, did you hear?
The chief has come up
with a crazy new product.
D-Don't tell me...
His job's on the line.
But he insists on going
through with the idea.
It can't be...
Hey, what kind of product
are we talking about?
No way...
Toilet paper and tissue join together.
The ultimate paper for
wiping away your tears.
Th-That's the Patriot!
We will now proceed to the final
step for creating a Patriot.
Look! Above the conveyor belt!
Come, Patriot factory chief!
Do you still think that
Patriots are trash?
this job is trash?
Jobs aren't meant to be compared.
When you willingly work for
the sake of someone else,
you're doing your job.
Every job deserves respect.
Because the world needs
all of us to do our jobs.
Would you like to try doing your job?
Go help the factory chief.
K-Kids...
You should have just gotten
your ass off the conveyor belt!
Good work, everyone.
Yeah, we took out the trash.
Those damn fools wasted our
time with that stupid show.
That was an educational experience.
Yep.
Next Episode: What Happens
Twice Can Happen Thrice
Next time:
What happens twice can happen thrice!