That's...
It's been awhile...Aizen.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
There are a lot of familiar
faces here.
Looks like we made it in
time for the main event.
Aizen.
Who...are they?
They're...
Shinji...Hirako!
Shinji Hirako.
Rojuro Ohtoribashi.
Rabu Aikawa.
Hachigen Ushoda.
Lisa Yadomaru.
I am assigning you five
as the investigation unit
in charge of this
vanishing soul case!
101 Years Ago
Aizen...
Maybe you should be
apologizing to your friends.
Because I chose you,
your friends ended up down there
on the ground with you.
Captain Hirako.
Aizen...
Damn it! You're doing
this to me, too?
Aizen!
What is this?!
Good-bye.
You were all wonderful
test subjects.
Damn it!
Well...
What an...
interesting guest.
K-Kisuke...
Why'd you...come...you idiot?
Lieutenant...Aizen...
Yes?
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
As you can see,
I just happened to find the members
of the investigation unit
in charge of the vanishing soul
case who were injured in battle,
and I was attempting
to rescue them.
Injured in battle?
You call these "injuries"?
You mustn't lie.
This is a Hollowfication.
The vanishing soul case...
Squad members disappearing
one after another as if erased.
And now, it's come to this.
Those were probably...
"Hollowfication" experiments.
Stand clear, Urahara!
Hado Number Eighty Eight!
Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
Bakudo Number Eighty One...
Danku.
That's impossible...
A lieutenant stopped my Kido using
Danku without an incantation?!
I brought all eight of them here.
And the new gigai prototype you
were working on, as well.
Yoruichi...
Get started on it.
From the moment you heard about
this incident from Hirako,
you envisioned the
worst-case scenario.
And you also came up with the
best solution to counter that.
I will pass sentence!
The unfortunate captain
of Squad 5 along with
the other seven
captain-class members,
who became the victims of
your heinous experiments
will be dealt with severely
as Hollows!
You are indeed the man
I thought you were.
Kisuke did say...
"There were no miscalculations."
That was the biggest
miscalculation of all.
As expected, everything turned
out in the worst possible way.
Man, we sure owe Kisuke...
And...
Aizen, too.
Let's go.
Shinji Hirako...
I figured you were hiding in
the World of the Living...
It's been a while since
we last saw them.
Is there anybody in the Thirteen Court Guard
Squads you guys want to say hello to?
No!
Shut up, Hiyori!
I wasn't talking to you!
What do you mean you
weren't talking to me?!
You're talking to everyone, right?!
I'm fine.
Me too.
There's no one in the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads I want to talk to.
Me neither.
Ichigo isn't here. I wonder why?
Hey! Where are you
going, Lisa?!
In that case...
I'll go say "hi" to the
Head Captain.
Hey! Wait, Shinji!
How long are you going
to play dead?!
Oh my...
What a surprise.
Look how beautiful you've become
since the last time I saw you.
Lie down right there!
I'll show you how strong
I've become!
Lisa-chan...
I'm glad you're doing well.
Idiot!
Indeed.
Did you come to settle
your grudge?
Against Aizen, that is.
I don't have anything
against you.
One thing I am upset about is
the fact that you placed an
incredibly strong barrier
around this place to fight!
If I hadn't found this guy
keeping watch outside,
we would have been circling
this area forever!
I'm very sorry!
I wasn't too sure whether
to let them in,
but considering the
situation in here...
It's fine.
Shinji Hirako...
Can we consider you
an ally for now?
Isn't it obvious?
You can't.
We're not your allies.
We're Aizen's enemies.
We're also allies...of Ichigo.
Ichigo...Kurosaki?
You're finally back.
Are you done talking?
Nope, but we can't waste
anymore time.
The enemy is losing
their patience.
What a noisy kid.
He's ruining the mood.
I hate it when he does that.
There is meaning to
Wonderweiss's words.
Sit back and watch.
What is he trying to do?!
It can't be...
Are those all Gillians?!
Let's go.
Mashiro Kick!
Kick!
You're all much too noisy.
This isn't a party, you know.
Please keep it quiet!
You're in the way.
Don't roll these big
things my way.
That's right... Come here.
Come near me...
And become enslaved
by my melody.
A-Amazing!
They're incredible...
They're incredibly strong!
Who are these guys?!
What do you think?
We've gotten pretty good at using
our Hollowfication, haven't we?
Aizen...
Let's end this.
I missed?
Don't be ridiculous.
You hit me.
I wanted to slice off everything
above your left eye.
I don't consider that a hit.
Big talk coming from a small fry.
You must really hate the fact that you're
going to be killed by a small fry.
Komamura...
Allow me to assist you,
masked visitor.
Are you sure you want to help
shady looking guys like us?
Then again, you look
pretty shady yourself.
You fought against those
Menos Grande.
That alone is enough for
me to call you an ally!
I have decided to fight with you!
I will not hear any objections,
masked visitor!
What a pushy fellow...
I'm no good with guys like this.
Komamura...
Listen to him go off like that...
But he has a point.
Guess there's no time to question
whether you're a friend or foe.
We don't really want to help
out you Soul Reapers!
But now's not the time
to be saying that!
That's right.
Strangers don't need a good
reason to team up in battle.
The enemy of your enemy
is your friend!
That's a good enough
reason to join forces.
Indeed.
I wanted the last one!
You stupid idiot!
Shut up!
You can have that large one
over there. Don't complain!
The big one...over there?
All right!
I love you, Kensei!
Uniting against a common enemy
is said to be one of
humanity's bad habits...
but that's not true.
It's not a bad habit, it's
a survival instinct.
In fact, it's at those times when spiritual
unions are at their most--
Ow!
What was that for, Love?!
We're done talking about that!
Stop talking nonsense and focus
on the things at hand.
Take a look. He looks strong.
Are you sure you want to
remove your masks?
We can only keep them
on for three minutes.
We're heroes, after all.
Mashiro...
Super Kick!
This is the exact opposite
of how it was back then.
I never imagined the day would come
where I would have to protect
someone from your sword.
I knew...
That someday we would
cross blades.
And one of us would die.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, Captain Komamura.
Please let me join this battle.
Hisagi...
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
A horde of Menos is nothing
to us Visoreds.
So, Shinji, how many
did you defeat?
It doesn't matter how
many I defeated!
What matters is how many
we defeated together.
I don't want to hear that from someone
who hasn't defeated any of them!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
What the hell is this?!
Baldy Shinji really
became a baldy!
I'm sorry, Captain.
I trimmed your hair while
you were asleep.
Ow, my stomach! My stomach
hurts from laughing too hard!
But it seems I overdid it.
You're all shiny now!
Do you have any idea how hard it was
to grow out my hair afterwards?!
Aizen...
You'll pay for that!