Upon the discovery
of Aizen's true goal,
the fierce battle between Soul Society
and Hueco Mundo
has been taken to
a whole new level.
The showdown will be in winter!
Until then, we must hone our skills...
and prepare for battle!
Ichigo, Sado, and Ishida
undergo harsh training
in preparation for the impending
showdown with Aizen.
Hitsugaya's advance troops
also remain in Karakura Town
and continue to guard the town.
One day, a new Arrancar appears.
Rangiku protects the soul of
a boy named Shota
who happens to be at the scene.
But the incident doesn't end there.
It's that sound!
That murky Spiritual Pressure!
It's the same as that
Mock Arrancar this evening!
Shota, I'm going to find out
where that whistling is coming from.
You go home by yourself!
I'm going too!
What, that again?
But if that Arrancar from
this evening has allies nearby...
All right! But in return,
I want you to stick close to me!
Huh?! All right, Ms. Rangiku!
Okay! Let's go!
All right!
S-Stop!
Help... Help me!
Stop! Go away!
Stop right there!
What's the meaning of this?
It isn't just its Spiritual Pressure
that's the same.
It even looks the same!
Oh no!
Why you...
Ms. Rangiku!
Stand back!
I'm feeling stronger!
What's the meaning of this?!
It looks exactly like the one
Ikkaku killed.
Are there two look-alikes?!
Who knows?
Take this! Take this!
Why you...
Shota, no!
Shota!
Captain!
Matsumoto!
Yes, sir!
Growl, Haineko!
It's over for you.
Matsumoto!
we're capturing it alive!
Yes, Captain!
What's so funny?!
Do you think you've caught me?
A third one?!
And a fourth one!
There are more!
What?!
I thought so.
They're Arrancars that look the same!
Growl, Haineko!
Shota!
It doesn't matter how many
of us you defeat!
What's this?!
This is Ayasegawa...
We are currently battling
Mock Arrancars...
We detected the Spiritual Pressure of
the Mock Arrancar.
that we encountered earlier!
I followed the signal
and encountered it!
But what's the meaning of this?
Isn't this the guy that
Ikkaku killed today?
Yes... In other words...
Captain!
Madarame! Ayasegawa!
we're in combat as well.
They can multiply!
Exterminate them all!
So he says.
It's a lot simpler that way!
Tsk! Things will never end
at this rate!
Hold on tight, Shota!
Okay!
Let's lead them into a wide area
and crush them all at once!
What wide area?
What about that park
we saw earlier?
That's it!
Matsumoto, go ahead of me!
Okay!
You have nowhere to
escape to anymore!
You're finished!
Captain!
You're the ones who are finished!
Frost unto the Heavens, Hyorinmaru!
That was wonderful, Captain!
Awesome...
Yumichika! Ikkaku!
Are you both all right?
Don't underestimate us!
Those guys weren't
a problem at all!
Though they were troublesome
because of their numbers.
I wanted to capture at least
one of them alive...
Huh?
That's...
Shota, what's wrong?
Yui! Yui!
Yui!
Shota, what's wrong?
It's Yui! She's my sister!
Huh?!
Yui! Yui!
It doesn't seem like
anything's wrong with her.
She's a normal soul.
I see...
Are you all right, Yui?
we're safe here...
That thing you said that
you had to do.
You were trying to find
your sister, weren't you?
Shota... What happened?
We were all in a car...
My dad, my mom, Yui and I...
We were going to
the amusement park.
See? Isn't that a nice sound,
big brother?!
It's just a lot of noise!
That's not true!
When I came to,
I had this chain.
And my dad and my mom
were gone.
Is that why you were searching
for your sister?
Y-Yeah...
Yui!
Yui... Can you tell who I am?
Big brother...
Thank goodness!
But why did she suddenly
appear in the park?
Do you have any ideas?
Well...
Shota... You're still...
Ukitake?!
Hey, Captain Hitsugaya.
It looks like you're having quite
a bit of trouble.
What's wrong?
It's about the Arrancar
you encountered...
I'm going to let someone from
the Department of Research and
Development tell you their findings.
I'm Akon of the Department of
Research and Development.
We're told the Arrancar that
you defeated appeared once again.
Yes... Furthermore, he multiplied
before our eyes.
We killed all of them
that were there,
but I'm not sure if
that's the end of it.
It's probably not over yet.
What do you mean?
When I checked a record of
the Spiritual Pressure in the area,
it matched that of all
the multiplied Mock Arrancar.
In other words, when they split,
they aren't separate entities.
Together, they form a single colony.
Does that mean that they share
a single consciousness?
Yes.
We believe that this Arrancar moves
several clones at once
in order to absorb as
many souls as possible.
They're like worker ants.
Yes...
Their main body is probably
hiding somewhere
and giving orders to the clones.
How troublesome...
Is there any way to find out
where their nest is?
It is difficult to pinpoint...
According to the report,
whenever they appear,
there's always a whistling sound.
Yes...
Whenever it appeared,
we always heard that sound.
S-Stop!
That sound restrains their victims,
and controls their movements.
I shall analyze that sound
so that we can pinpoint
when they will appear.
Take care of it.
Things sure have become troublesome...
I've bought some bento boxes!
Seriously though...
I'm always impressed by
these "convenience stores."
Along with rice balls,
they even sell these in
the middle of the night.
Welcome back!
Captain! They brought some
bento boxes!
Let's put together our plan
after we've had something to eat!
I'm stuffed!
Now then, about the Mock Arrancar...
I've already gone over
everything we know about them.
Whatever the case,
we must spread out over a large area
and prepare to quickly deal
with various situations.
Well, that about sums it up...
It looks like this will keep me
from getting bored!
We'll take turns watching the town.
Matsumoto, you stay here
and watch these two.
All right.
Shouldn't we perform a Konso?
Big brother...
No... We can do that later.
Really?
I see... You're very kind, aren't you?
Huh?
These siblings have
finally come together.
He's going to let them stay
together for a while.
Captain...
Shut up...
Let's go!
Big brother...
What a great bath...
I really love a bath before work.
Oh, how's Yui?
She's still sleeping.
What's wrong?
You finally got to see Yui.
Are you still hiding something?
You were behaving strangely
when my captain asked you
about what happened in
the park this morning.
Don't keep it to yourself.
Tell me about it!
It's nothing!
It's nothing?
It doesn't concern you!
What's going on?!
My body's moving on its own...
Who's there?
He's appeared!
This way, eh?!
How repulsive...
Wait!
Crap! Captain! Ikkaku!
Let's split up and go after them!
- Okay!
Yui!
Hey!
Why do you think she's here?
Well...
Just now...
I sensed that Arrancar's--
Shota!
Wait!
Where did it go?!
Hey!
It's all right. I'm not an enemy.
Did you see a monster?
Don't worry. It's all right now.
It's no good...
Crap!
Shota! Wait up!
It's dangerous here!
We've got to go back!
No!
Shota!
We'll look for Yui...
That's no good!
I have to protect Yui myself!
Shota, you...
Yui...
When did she...?
Yui! What were you doing here?!
I wasn't doing anything...
I just wanted to come to this park.
Big brother...
Now that you're here,
I'm all right now.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Damn it!
I...ran away...
Huh?
Yui... I left her here...
And ran away!
An Arrancar that multiplies...
In other words, if you leave one,
they'll keep multiplying!
What a coincidence.
I was just thinking the same thing.
We could fight as much as we wanted
with one of them!
We've got to capture one!
They're pretty energetic...
They probably got a stupid idea
into their heads.
- Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
- Let's eat!
Come to think of it,
we always use this room
as if it's ours.
Is that all right?
Orihime went to Soul Society
with Kuchiki,
so it's completely all right.
Oh yeah? Well, I thought so.
Though, I am sad that I can't eat
Orihime's delicious cooking.
Oh? She's really good at cooking?
We'd like to try some too.
You probably shouldn't.
Why?