Damn, this is one long staircase.
Huh? What are you doing?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You...
...seem more human now.
Let's go. And don't trip.
What's wrong?
Take it.
You're letting me borrow it again?
I'm giving it to you.
It's pretty banged up, so I
dunno how useful it'll be,
but it's better than nothing, right?
Thank you.
The emergency system has been activated.
Initiating building detonation sequence.
What's happeni—
Zack, run!
R-Right!
"Who really are you?
You should ask yourself.
Who am I?
The real myself or the one I believe to be?
An angel?
Or a sacrifice?
Know yourself and new doors will open."
No...
Tch.
Move!
Zack, it won't work!
Shut up and watch me!
Damn it! What do we do now?
Zack?
Are you okay?
I don't wanna burn to death.
It's okay.
We'll get out.
I'll do something.
Okay?
So... don't worry.
Shit... I'm...
Hey, Ray! What are you doing?
I'll get the iron bars open.
Move. I'll do it.
But—
Shut up! Just let me do it!
All right!
Sorry about that.
I'm fine now.
Let's go!
Yeah.
Yeah!
Zack, the stairway's brok—
Zack, are you enjoying this?
Quit talking! You'll bite your tongue!
I can see the exit!
Finally! Let's go!
Yeah!
Ray, think I can break through that?
Huh?
I can break through it.
You just have to say the word.
Zack, break through it!
Your scythe!
Can't use this anymore.
Let's get moving.
Yeah.
Bye-bye.
This building made us do some
jacked-up shit right up to the end.
You did good, though.
If you hadn't been here,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
The same goes for me.
All right!
We can finally say goodbye
to this damn building!
What's wrong?
Once we...
Once we get outside, you'll kill me, right?
Why bring this up now?
Is that what you want, too?
My desire to die hasn't changed, but...
If possible, I'd like you to
kill me because you want to.
I do want to die,
but the thought of being
completely alone when I do
makes me feel strangely sad.
But if you kill me because it's
what you truly want to do,
that would really make me happy.
I know it's selfish to say after
you gave me this knife, but—
I gave you that knife
to keep you alive until I get to kill you.
I've never given anything to anyone before.
And I don't do anything I don't want to do.
Really?
Give it a rest. How many
times have I told you?
I hate li—
You hate lies?
Don't say it before me.
Just be sure to make a
good face when I do it.
You've always sucked at smiling, you know.
Yeah.
Zack...
Really, you're awful. You're just too cruel!
I'm the one who activated
the emergency system.
Soon enough, it'll be a sea of
flames... Your favorite, Zack!
Screw you, Danny, you bastard—
You're so bold for someone
who's completely unarmed,
Zack!
I'm sorry to say it, but that promise
you two made won't be happening.
Zack...
I'm sorry... I promised to
be killed by you, but now...
Screw that! I told you, I hate lies—
I won't let you run or save her.
I won't let you do anything.
I won't let you kill Rachel!
How does it feel to have
your dream go up in smoke?
Why don't you tell me, huh?!
Shut up!
Don't say that! Be nice, now!
Hey, Ray, keep it together.
Don't make me a liar.
I can't let you die now.
There's nothing so entertaining
as a monster rendered powerless!
You're wrong.
He's not a monster.
He's not God, either.
Zack is...
...human.
He's human.
So...
Even if he doesn't give me
everything I want all the time...
It's okay.
Hey...
You don't care if he doesn't
give you anything?!
I've always given you everything!
I gave you food, clothes,
toys, and that entire floor!
Are you saying you didn't want all that?!
And what has Zack given you?!
A knife that might as well be garbage!
Oh... Or are you talking about
that silly promise, Rachel?
The one that lets you die?
It's not right!
I tried so hard to keep you alive!
I didn't want to live that way.
What I really wanted...
...was to be wanted alive,
even just for a moment...
...and to be wanted...
...in death.
After I made that promise with Zack...
...and started heading toward
the surface with him,
I finally realized that.
That's enough for me.
Then you should feel more despair.
After all, I just took that
promise away from you.
Shut up.
Quiet! Let me speak!
Shut up!
You didn't take it away.
A vow cannot be stolen.
Even if it can't be fulfilled,
that doesn't matter.
It's between the two of us.
I know that.
Zack, I'll carry our promise with me,
so don't call yourself a liar.
It's okay if our promise can't be fulfilled.
Hey... Ray...
Hey, Rachel...
You never looked at or trusted anyone.
If you'd kept your eyes just like that...
If you'd stayed lonely forever...
I wouldn't have minded dying.
And yet...
Why must you stray so far
from your loneliness?
You destroyed everything.
It's over.
Rachel, I'll put an end
to your wish and Zack's,
along with my own, right here.
I didn't expect you to be this self-serving,
Danny.
Why... would you do this, Father?
I'm not finished!
Zack, I'll finish you off right now!
Zack, can you still move?
Zack!
What the hell are you playing at?
If you're going to muster the last of
your strength, use it to leave here.
Shut up!
Any human who loses this
much blood is gonna die!
What's the point in getting
out if she's dead?!
Rachel Gardner is still alive.
If you get out right now, you can save her.
What are you talking about?
Go, and you will see.
Now, go quickly, Zack!
I'm telling you to go!
What a pretty blue moon...
But it looks like a fake blue moon.
The Girl's Exposed
Lie
I...
hate lies.
Zack's...
Past
The Building's
Residents
Rachel and
Zack's
Promise...