Okay, attention please?
Some of you may have already noticed,
but there's this little dot here.
Kind of like a secondary
sex characteristic.
But it's not pronounced
Gintama Dash or Dot.
Due to grown-up circumstances,
there has to be something here.
Because grown-ups grow hair down there.
But it's still pronounced Gintama.
Grown-ups keep their mouths shut
when someone's unshaven.
So with that lesson learned,
let's try this again.
Snack Otose
Apparently, she's got herself...
...a man.
I noticed that Catherine was behaving
rather oddly lately.
That explains why.
So, did someone lose a bet or something?
He's a regular here.
They've been on friendly
terms for a while.
No, seriously. This guy must have lost
This defies logic.
No man would ever be interested
in that nasty woman.
Clearly, she was the result
of a bad joke by God.
If he threw together some
leftover cat and housewife parts
to make a present for his grandchild,
which was then relegated
to chew toy duty, that would be her.
But don't you think that
Catherine-san looks prettier these days?
How?
You mean how the cat and
housewife parts fit together?
That's because God files
the edges and gives the
putty plenty of time to dry.
According to my data,
women become more beautiful
when they fall in love.
What?
That's just lip service.
Don't they tend to place their
hand on their cheek and sigh?
Just stop already.
Women, old and robot,
always love this topic.
My folder of love stories
is ten yottabytes.
That's ridiculously huge!
Listen to me.
You can putty up a Zaku
as much as you want.
It's never going to become a Gundam.
Fix your data.
Understood.
Master Gintoki can never
be like Hiro Mizushima.
Gajiro Sato is the best he can manage.
What's with the cruel gap
in wavy hair characters?
I'm back.
Look, the Zaku's back.
Tune her up, mechanic.
Sorry I took so long.
There was an elderly person
who needed help carrying something.
Please deduct it from my wages.
Z-ZZZ Gundam has returned!
Didn't I explain this to you?
Explain what?!
Her physique is completely different!
You can't pin this on an
idiosyncratic animator!
Oh, Gintoki-san.
Welcome.
Enjoy yourself.
Even her personality has been Newtype'd!
Why is she so polite now?!
Love can't change a girl this much!
Wait, love...?
You all know?
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
I'm sorry.
I planned to tell you
once everything was settled...
Everything was settled?
Catherine, are you...
Otose-san, I'm...
Snack Otose
...in a relationship with
someone who wants to marry me.
It's Too Confusing When Talking About the Poster Girl for a Poster Store, So Call Her a Sandwich Board
Suejiro Suemoto-san.
A regular at Otose-san's place.
That's how he got to know Catherine-san.
He's an up-and-coming entrepreneur
with considerable influence.
Hmm...
There are some real weirdos out there.
Sugar Content
People have always sucked up
to him because of his money,
so Catherine-san was like
a breath of fresh air.
Catherine-san!
Sorry about being late.
Please don't worry about it.
You should wipe off your sweat first.
Oh, thank you. I appreciate it.
Ah!
(My, Suejiro-san is so bold.)
Flower House
Oh, dear. My head is spinning.
This is so much fun.
Ah!
Whoa...!
Catherine-san...
Suejiro-san...
Wait a second.
Is this the right show?
Who wants to see them
fawn over each other?
Gin-san, we should be happy for them.
That would be the grown-up response.
Hah!
Grown-up!
Yeah, yeah.
So sorry!
In any case, business is
booming at Snack Otose.
It must be the charm of
a new wife or something,
since Catherine-san has
doubled her clientele.
And Suejiro-san seems
like a nice person.
He was a regular customer,
so he isn't going to tell
her to stop working.
Hmph!
Make sure you don't fall
for a woman like her, Sadaharu!
You never know when she's gonna
turn back into a chew toy.
Sugar Content
He lost all of his assets
when Lehman Brothers went bankrupt.
So he was saying that he can
no longer make Catherine-san happy...
So he wants to call it off?
Just goes to show that he's a man with
no money and no balls.
But Catherine-san refused.
She said that she would support him.
Huh?
Suejiro-san has a piece
of property left that
isn't in the Kabuki district.
He's going to open a new business there.
With Catherine-san.
So what?
That thief who showed up in
episode 12 of this anime,
is finally leaving in episode 206?
Well, it's like she's graduating,
becoming independent.
Otose-san will be a little lonely,
but I'm sure that she'll be the first
one to congratulate them.
Master Gintoki.
There is an emergency.
Could you come see Ms.
Otose immediately?
Uh, I have a little
emergency of my own here.
Could you leave immediately?
I will take over here.
Take over what?
Keep the bathroom clean!
Go see Ms. Otose now.
After walking through the cold,
I'm at terminal velocity,
or diarrhea city.
I have retrieved the appropriate data.
I simply need to continue
making ice cream, correct?
Chocolate.
And make sure it doesn't
fall off the cone.
Man...
What's going on?
She probably wants to talk about
Catherine-san and Suejiro-san's future?
-Gin-chan!
-Gin-San!
Catherine!
Are you okay?!
What was that for?!
Otose-san!
If you want to leave, scram.
I won't object or try to stop you.
But I can't stand
to watch people like you who dream
and can't keep their feet on the ground.
You can call me whatever you want!
But are you really saying that
Catherine's hopes are
just a pipe dream?!
Otose-san...
Catherine!
I've been saving up money
so I might open my own bar one day...
Snack Otose
I wanted to create a place
like this one, where
everyone was all smiles.
I wanted to become a
selfless person like you...
I see how it is, Suejiro-san.
I was wondering how you could
afford to open a new business.
That explains it.
Don't say that!
I just want to work together
for our future...!
Go ahead and get married,
be independent.
You don't need permission from me.
We're total strangers, after all.
Or is there more?
You came here because you wanted to
weasel money out of me and Catherine?
Otose-san!
That's crossing the line...
Always...
I always thought of you as my mother...
Fine, you old hag!
I don't need your permission!
And I'm never coming back to see you!
Roll over and die!
That's nice.
I feel a lot better knowing that I won't
have to see your face again!
Wait up, hag!
I'm not finished with you...
I'll give you that instead of money.
You can display it in your bar.
It'll be the perfect place to display
a cheap bottle of alcohol.
You old hag!
I'll make you eat your words!
I'll start up a bar that beats
the crap out of this run-down place!
I'll become bigger than you ever will!
Goddamn!
Catherine!
Catherine-san!
Hey, you thief!
Catherine!
Kabuki District Station
Write us a letter once
you're settled down.
And invite us over
once your bar is open.
We'll all come to visit.
Let me know if anything comes up.
I will be right there.
Thank you very much.
Sorry that this isn't
much of a send-off...
Where did Gin-san run off to this time?
Hey, Kagura-chan!
You should say goodbye.
Don't come back!
Come on, Kagura-chan!
But if it's too much to take...
If you can't put up with the in-laws,
you can come back after
raking him for alimony.
You'll be more than welcome then.
Really, thank you for everything.
Please take care...
Catherine-san, uh...
About Otose-san...
The train on Platform 2
will be departing momentarily.
I'll be going then.
Suejiro-san is waiting for me.
Please wait, Catherine-san!
Please take care of...
...Otose-san for me.
Snack Otose
Didn't you read the sign?
We're closed today.
Really?
Guess you don't have a choice
without your poster girl around.
Don't worry.
I'm not here for a drink.
I'm here to do the pouring.
I never knew.
When I first met her,
she was just a dirty thief.
I felt so bad for her
that I let her stay at my bar.
But she kept wandering off.
Couldn't really blame her
since she was a stray at heart,
but lately, she's settled down
and been working hard.
I never knew she actually
had a plan for her future...
You didn't like the guy?
I should be grateful
that anyone was willing to take her.
I understand that she
can't exactly be choosy.
Still, as a parent...
Your daughter can bring
home the perfect man
and you'll still be able
to find something wrong.
I can't just smile and send her off,
when I know she's going to suffer.
That was the best I could manage.
I feel bad.
So this is how it ends.
If you feel bad, don't
talk like it's over.
Once she's opened a bar
that's as good as this one,
you should go have a drink.
Catherine, find your happiness.
The last train is departing.
Today's service has concluded.
Please exit the station
in a swift manner.
Suemoto?
Nope, never heard of him.
I don't think there's anybody
by that name in this area.
A bar?
No, no.
They're going to open a drugstore here.
Greater Edo Bank
Please wait.
Your balance is 0 yen.
Would you like a receipt?
Please remove your card.
Are you new here?
I don't know what you've been through,
but it's a harsh world out there.
If you need anything, let me know.
They call me the lord of this park.
I'll do anything for a little alcohol...
Bacchus
W-Wait!
Wh-Where did you get this stuff?!
Don't touch that!
L-Lady, that's incredible stuff!
Bacchus wine from Planet Bacchus,
only made once every hundred years!
Legendary stuff that
will net hundreds from any collector!
H-How did you get your hands on this?!
You can display it in your bar.
The perfect place to display
a cheap bottle of alcohol.
Otose-san...
You were giving me a push in the back...
I'm so sorry, Otose-san...
I have no place to display
this wonderful bottle...
Wait, I didn't drink any!
I didn't even take a sip!
I just touched the bottle!
I'm sorry! Really sorry!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Okay?
So yeah.
She wouldn't tell me
what happened when I asked.
She kept saying that she
couldn't go back because she promised.
I guess she got sick
of me asking questions,
since she just ran off.
Do you know anything, Gin-san?
Hasegawa-san...
Were your parents happy
when you got married?
Where did that come from?
I married into money.
So my whole family was thrilled.
I see...
That's what matters in the end.
Hey, it's starting, Gin-san!
Whoa, wait!
Wh-What?!
Man, that's nasty!
Gin-san!
Look at that!
What?
Huh?
Easy Financing
Evil Loans
You actually got the money.
I knew you could do it.
You just have to trick a few women
and you can pay back
your loan in no time.
Evil 4 Lyfe
What was your opinion of this target,
as a former gigolo.
Quite frankly, she was so easy
that I was bored to death.
I just used her dream of opening a bar,
and she completely fell for it.
Stupid woman.
Why would I waste my
time on that old lady?
I could barely stand
walking next to her.
I don't know how you
came up with the idea
of pretending to go broke
after you were a couple.
Most women will do anything for money.
But there are a few exceptions
who have a weakness for the penniless.
You're starting to look
pretty evil yourself.
At this rate, you'll pay
off the rest in no...
Wh-What's that?!
B-Bro!
We're under attack!
Wh-What?!
Which gang is it?!
It's not a gang!
There's only one...
Evil 4 Lyfe
You're the man who was at Otose's bar!
Don't worry.
You guys aren't evil.
You just stole money from a woman
who was saving up for her dream...
You fooled her into thinking you
wanted to marry her so you
could take her money...
That doesn't make you evil.
I'll show you what true evil looks like.
Do you have a moment?
I feel like having a drink.
Are you open?
That's a relief.
I didn't think anyone
would be open with the snow and all.
Just give me one shot
of your cheapest booze.
This is a nice place.
You can watch the moon, watch the snow,
and have a drink.
But I have one complaint.
Nobody cries while pouring a drink.
You have to have a smile
on your face at all times.
Even if the customer is crying.
You still have much to learn, Catherine.
Well, let's go have a drink.
Gin-san.
I brought a little present...
The drinks...
...are on me.
Catherine
Greater Edo Bank
Next Episode
It's like a dream come true!
I'll pretend like these
glasses are Gin-san
and never let them go!
Next time:
Glasses Are Part of the Soul
Glasses are part of the soul!