Hado Number 91: Senjukotentaiho!
Wh-What the hell...is that?!
Here I go.
This time, I'm not holding back.
Bankai...
Kamishininoyari.
What's wrong?
You're getting slower.
Are you already at your limit?
Yes, it seems like it.
I've reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul Reaper, that is.
You stopped that well.
That's pretty good for sheer luck.
Who are you calling
lucky, stupid?!
Sorry, Captain Aizen.
Did I interrupt your conversation?
It's all right.
I just finished talking.
Honestly...
The Hogyoku is very
aptly named!
It has the power to
destroy the wall
that separates those
who are gods
from those who aren't!
So you've come...
Kisuke Urahara!
Urahara...
It's been a while, Aizen.
Yes, around a hundred years.
In the time I haven't seen you...
You've taken up some
interesting fashion.
Everything in the process
of evolving looks ugly.
Who said anything about "ugly"?
You fused yourself with the
Hogyoku, haven't you?
Not "fused."
I'd rather you said "subjugated."
The Hogyoku you
could not control.
You're right, I couldn't control it.
At that time.
"At that time"?
That is some excuse you have.
Though whether you're trying
to make an excuse
or not means nothing to me.
Because...
Urahara!
You have already lost your chance
to control the Hogyoku.
Rikujokoro!
Come to think of it,
Yammy's battle records
did list such an item.
I'll tell you!
That was called a Bala!
We solidify our Spiritual Pressure
and hit the enemy with it!
It's not as strong as a Cero...
But it's twenty times faster!
"Lord Aizen's going
to be furious!"
You bastard! Why?
Why am I still alive?
The answer is...this.
Wha--
It's a portable gigai!
I let my guard down,
figuring you'd never
resort to such trickery.
So, what do you plan to
do now after tying me
up with such a weak Bakudo?
Such a weak Bakudo?
Then let's see how many
you can take.
Bakudo Number 63...
Sajosabaku!
Bakudo Number 79...
Kuyoshibari!
Beyond the end of
a thousand hands.
The hand of darkness
out of reach.
The archer in heaven
that goes unseen.
Road that lights the way.
Wind that ignites the embers.
Gather without hesitation.
Look where I point.
Bullets of light, bodies of eight,
rays of nine, paths of heaven,
treasures of speed, wheels of immensity,
and cannons of grey.
From a distance, the bow is
drawn and fades in light.
Do you think I'd let you
use such a Kido?
I can easily break free of...
Too late!
Hado Number 91: Senjukotentaiho!
Incredible...
Aizen...
It would appear you really did
lower your guard when you
embedded the Hogyoku.
Exactly.
Too slow.
I did lower my guard.
There is no longer any
need to be on guard.
I can feel it.
Even when I was in
the Soul Society,
no one could compare
to my powers.
But now that I have subjugated
the Hogyoku,
my body has surpassed
even that.
There is no longer
any need to dodge
a Kido at the nineties level.
You've got it wrong.
Not dodging my Kido isn't what I meant
when I said you let your guard down.
The old you would never
have attempted
to attack me twice
without thinking.
This is...
It's a seal.
I've sealed the outlets
for Spiritual Pressure
that are on the wrists
of every Soul Reaper.
You will be incinerated
from the inside by your
own Spiritual Pressure.
Urahara!
It's not over yet.
Huh?
It would be child's play if that
were all it took to finish him.
We could laugh him off
as a mere monster.
He'll be coming out in no time.
Wh-What the hell...is that?!
You used a nineties-level
Kido as a decoy
to lure me into attacking,
and you used a spell you developed
to incinerate me from the inside.
If I hadn't been your opponent...
No, if it hadn't been me who
subjugated the Hogyoku,
the battle would probably
have been over.
But unfortunately,
the Hogyoku you created exceeds
your ability to understand it.
Even this technique you created
in anticipation of battling me,
has no effect on me.
Your spell didn't work, so now you're
coming at me with your sword?
As you wish.
What nonsense is this?
Do you really think...
You're...
Yoruichi?!
Well? Did that work?
Yoruichi, get out of the way!
Tsk!
What's the matter?
You're not done already,
are you?
You'd better make your
next move quickly.
I will crush them one at a time,
down to your last remaining one.
The number of methods you
contrived to defeat me
is proof of your effort
and strength.
At the same time,
it represents the number
of hopes you hold.
If that is so, then what I must do
is to crush each one of them.
Now, come at me with
your next attack.
Kisuke Urahara.
Yoruichi Shihoin.
And...
Isshin Kurosaki.
Well, this is a problem.
That was specially made iron
armor for use against Hierro.
I didn't think it'd be destroyed
so easily.
Huh?
What? You make it sound
like it was my fault.
No, I didn't mean it that way.
Oh yes you did!
You're trying to say it's my fault
for letting my guard down!
Aren't you?!
Well listen up. You didn't put in enough
effort when you made these!
Which means it's all your fault for being
lazy during their construction!
Okay, okay, I get it!
I see.
The fact that your leg still
remains intact after being
hit by me proves
they are special.
You mean my legs?
What's with that look?!
My nose hurts!
There's no need to
make a scene.
It's meaningless to argue
what is special.
If a single swing makes
one disappear,
then three more swings will make
that specialness disappear.
Here he comes.
I know.
Are you good to go?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
All I have to do is hit him with something
other than my left leg.
Yoruichi!
Pay attention.
Your back is wide open.
Psych! Just messing with you.
How about we take a
break for a second?
W-What're you talking about?
Oh, come on. Let's watch the show.
It's useless.
I'm telling you, it's useless.
It's useless now.
I've been with Captain
Aizen a long time,
but I've never seen
anything like this.
Well, he fused with the Hogyoku
without my knowing,
so maybe that's to be expected.
Don't you get it?
There's nothing you can do.
He's going to kill all of you.
It's all over.
I'm not letting that happen.
Yeah, that's what I
thought you'd say.
And there's no telling what Aizen
would do to you,
now that he's like that!
Oh my, now I wasn't expecting
you to say that.
The way you said it...
Sounds like you said it
assuming you'd die.
Maybe somewhere inside of you,
you've already given
up on this fight.
That's not...
My, my...
How pathetic.
I was hoping you'd
be better than that,
but I guess you really
are just a kid.
You're weak inside.
I couldn't possibly let Captain Aizen
fight a coward like you.
What is that stance?!
Kamishininoyari... Buto.
It's already back in place?!
Kamishininoyari Butorenjin.
Captain...Ichimaru...
Matsumoto?
Gin...
Way too soft.
I'll be the one...
who'll stop you!
We'll have to resort
to our final plan!
You still had one left?
Off with all the armors!
Huh?
And last goes the clothes.
I call it, "Operation: Sex Appeal"!
Put your clothes back on!
What's this? Looks like it had
an effect on my ally instead.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
What is this old album?
Memory Album
It was left in the captains'
meeting room earlier.
Let's have a look.
This is...
Hey, this brings back memories.
This is about a century ago.
Everyone was so young.
Old Man Yama hasn't
changed much.
This one's back when we
were in the Academy.
How many centuries
ago was that?
Sensei was young back then.
He looks exactly the same!
How long has he been like that?!