Nel's true identity is
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck, a former Espada.
Having once again regained her powers,
Nelliel releases her Zanpakuto.
She takes on her Resurrección form
and overwhelms Nnoitora.
Lanzador Verde.
Relax… I will not take your life.
What? Why did Nel…
It's over, Nelliel!
Nel!
It's over for all of you here!
Tesla, I'll let you take over.
This guy has nothing left.
Kurosaki…
What is this?
You look like you're
about to die, Ichigo!
Kenpachi?!
Are you really…Kenpachi?!
Of course I am.
Did getting beaten to a pulp
screw up your head as well?
Who are you?
You don't feel like answering, eh?
Then be gone!
You stupid fool!
Get away, Tesla!
Master Nnoitora…
Next.
Come on.
You're next, right?
K-Kenpachi…
Why are you here?
I thought the Soul Society
pulled out of this fight.
K-Kurosaki?!
Move, you're in my way.
Damn!
Oh, so you're okay.
I'm not okay!
You kicked me in the gut
with all you've got!
How'd you get here, anyway?
Kisuke Urahara.
That guy was given a bunch
of orders from the old man
when the showdown was
set for winter.
One of those orders
was to stabilize
some sort of underground
cavern called a Garganta,
and once it was totally secure,
make it possible
for captain-level personnel to
pass over to Hueco Mundo.
The guy said it would take
only one month to finish
what was believed to
take three months.
But before he could do it,
that woman there was snatched away.
And so that cavern
was finally fortified.
That's why Kenny came here!
Yachiru! You stay out of this!
Who are you?
I regret that I cannot tell you my name,
but that is also fate.
Pass on, Soul Reaper.
For crying out loud…
I said I could handle this by myself.
No one listens!
Who are you?
Squad 4 Captain of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
Retsu Unohana.
Likewise, Lieutenant Isane Kotetsu.
That coat… I take it you are
of captain standing.
I am Espada Number 7,
Septima Espada, Zommari Rureaux.
Now identify yourself, intruder.
Who am I, you ask?
Is there some meaning in
answering that?
What?!
There's no need for an answer.
Our identities are one.
We are your enemies.
I see.
We have only come to
heal everyone's wounds.
We have no intention of
fighting with you.
As long you do not interfere in our efforts,
we have no intention of interfering with you.
Arrancar… Arrancar… Arrancar…
Espada!
Fascinating, indeed!
Hueco Mundo is quite
a treasure trove of riches!
I, too, wish to ask a question.
Are you the one
who fought with her?
It was not me.
However, I was about to
administer the finishing blow.
I see.
So you finally attacked.
I was waiting for this.
Come at me like your life
is at stake!
Damn you, Kenpachi!
You must not act on
your own like this!
Injured people keep out of this!
What?! I can still…
No, you don't, Itchy!
Y-Yachiru! Don't!
You're killing Kurosaki!
Oh no… His head just drooped!
Kurosaki! Don't pass out!
Seems like I saw this just
a while ago.
Itchy, you have to
stay out of this! Because…
Kenny has that look on his face.
It's okay now, Kenny!
Yachiru, stay right there.
Okay!
Are you mocking me?
I've got no intention of joining
your circus!
Hey, is that all you've got?
Looks like we can have some fun.
What's your name, Soul Reaper?
Squad 11 Captain,
Kenpachi Zaraki!
I'm Quinto Espada,
Nnoitora Gilga!
It would seem a very sensible captain
has appeared before us.
We're leaving.
– Wait!
– Isane.
Our role is not to spill blood,
but to stop it from being spilled.
We will not pursue those
who choose to run away.
Come, we must heal them.
Sado, and that Arrancar.
C-Captain Kurotsuchi?!
W-Why…are you here?!
So, is this man someone
you know, Quincy?
Know? Hardly.
I don't know such inferior beings.
What?!
Quincy…
Aside from the fact that there
aren't very many of them,
they are of no value or
interest to me now.
Why you…
You came all the way here
to insult us?!
– Ta-da!
– Two out of Three
– Great Desert Brothers, are back!
– Brothers of the Burning Sands, are back!
You guys! What were you fighting
about while we were gone?!
And, you're not very convincing
when you try to act strong
in that beat-up condition,
Ichigo…I mean, Uryu!
Quit screwing with me already!
You're all messed up, yourself!
What did you say?!
Unlike you, it's not my body
that's messed up!
I'm psychologically messed up
because Cero Sincretico didn't work!
Got that, Uryu?
That's even worse!
Stop fighting amongst yourselves.
It's unsightly.
Now, let me ask you again.
Who on earth are you?
On second thought,
I won't ask your name.
I will, after all,
just eliminate you.
It would be a waste of time
to ask your name.
You think so?
On the other hand, it would be a problem
if I don't hear your name.
Why is that?
Why? Are you an idiot?
That should be obvious.
So when I stuff you in a jar,
I can write your name on it.
Is something the matter?
Aren't you going to come
at me, intruder?
Just so you know,
if you intend to rescue that collapsed
Soul Reaper there, it's no use.
Don't try it.
I don't get it.
What do you mean by,
"it's no use"?
This is what I mean.
Just as I would expect of a captain.
Your speed is outstanding.
And your reactions are superb.
However, that is,
for a Soul Reaper's level, of course.
What do you mean by that?
Inoue!
Hey Inoue! Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
What about you, Kurosaki?
I'm okay, but…
That damn Kenpachi.
How long is he
going to go all-out?!
That was pretty good.
Looks like we could have
an interesting duel.
So let me enjoy this a little longer!
Same here!
Put me in a jar?
He's laughing.
What just happened?
I don't get what was
so funny at all!
There's no way I could've
missed that guy's joke.
No, that wasn't a joke that he told.
What?!
Then are you saying that guy made
Szayelaporro laugh without telling a joke?!
What sort of miracle is that?!
Who is that guy?!
Just what sort of trick did he use?!
Oh, shut up, already!
Keep quiet, you guys!
Oh, come on.
You're as cold as a woman
who has absolutely no interest in the man she left!
You annoy me!
Shouldn't overdo it, Uryu.
You're all messed up.
Messed up. Messed up!
He's right!
Okay then!
We're cheering on the warriors!
That's right!
Gemelos Sonido.
Among the Espada,
my Sonido is the fastest.
And by a adding a small step,
I've completed something
resembling a pseudo clone.
You might say
it's like playing with magic.
Magic is used to astound
one's audience,
so there's no need to
be ashamed if you are astounded
because you cannot follow it
with your eyes.
I see.
However, you should be ashamed.
You've already shown
your cards to me.
Too bad.
Gemelos Sonido isn't
limited to two bodies.
I suppose it isn't.
Hado 4: Byakurai.
I grow weary of this.
K-Kenpachi!
Earlier, I said it would be
a waste of time to ask your name.
However, you said something
quite intriguing to me,
so as a show of respect to you
I think I will ask you your name
so that you can become
my marionette.
This is bad! Those feathers are…
Captain Kurotsuchi!
Gemelos Sonido has a maximum of…
five bodies.
What's the matter?
Don't tell you're shocked
just by this level?
At this rate, I'll be far from satisfied.
I'm waiting for you!
Come at me like your life
is at stake!
Damn it!
It's what happened to us
all over again!
You might be a captain,
or whatever,
but you coming here isn't going
to change anything greatly.
I'm afraid your expectations
are about to go up in smoke.
I sympathize with
your meaningless end.
Oh, do you?
Farewell, captain whose name
I don't even know.
The reason for your defeat is the arrogance
of not even stating your name.
Stealth Hoho,
Shiho Number 3: Utsusemi.
I wish I didn't have to use
a technique I learned from her.
What?!
This is what I've been waiting for!
This feeling that sends tingles
through my body!
From here on, it's kill or be killed!
No more feeling each other out!
It is I who sympathizes with you.
Because starting now,
you are about to experience a world
your comprehension cannot keep up with.
You are the arrogant one, Espada.
But do not fret.
The reason you will lose is not
because of your arrogance.
It is simply a difference in skill.
What did that Nnoitora do
by sticking his finger in the ground?
That is how he measures
Spiritual Pressure.
You! I thought Kenpachi killed you!
If I don't explain it, who will?
Master Nnoitora is not that nice.
So true.
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia
Today, I'll tell you about Zommari.
Zommari's skilled technique
is called "Gemelos Sonido."
By adding steps to his Sonido,
he creates clones to dazzle his opponents.
My Sonido is the fastest
among the Espada.
As I said, you're being arrogant.
What?
Hey! How far are you guys going?