Speaking of Crossovers,
Don't Forget About Alien vs. Predator
Hey, listen up, guys.
We have a special treat this week
Odd Jobs Gin-chan
to commemorate the 26th
episode of the new season.
A special treat?
Wait, 26 is kind of a random number.
Basically, we were told to do
a crossover with Sket Dance,
since the anime started at
the same time as ours.
Really, Gin-san?
They're finally letting us do that too?
I figured that Jump and TV
Tokyo hated our guts by now.
Since we keep causing problems.
But now I'm nervous,
since I'm actually a pretty shy guy.
What is there to be scared about?
We've done plenty of crossovers.
Have you forgotten when
we shared the screen
with Dragonball, One Piece,
Bleach, and other classics?
Uh, those were just parodies
we did without permission.
That would be one of the reasons
I figured that everybody hated us.
Hey, don't get too excited.
This might be a crossover,
but our goal isn't to
have a happy pow-wow.
Huh?
Check out the data I've collected.
Pay attention now.
Sket Dance is a comedy
manga with a school setting
that began running in Jump in 2007.
The anime began airing in 2011 at the
same time the new Gintama began airing.
The Sket Dan is a school club that
does odd jobs with three members:
The leader, Bossun.
The brains, Switch.
The straight man/muscle, Himeko.
The manga's pretty episodic with
plenty of laughter and tears.
Hold on, Gin-chan!
Look at their time slot!
It's 6:00 PM on Thursday!
Huh? Isn't that the old Gintama slot?!
Exactly.
In 2006, after it only took six months
for us to be booted from prime time,
we spent the next 177 episodes
defending that fortress,
and they just snatched it away from us.
Snatched it away from us?
It wasn't their decision.
There were obviously extenuating
circumstances involved.
Well, as I'm sure you can see even
from my vague explanation,
these guys...
...are clearly trying to supplant us!
Uh, why are you trying to twist
everything before the crossover's even started?
Clearly trying to overtake us!
Why are you repeating yourself?
Don't make false accusations.
It's pretty common to find a story
about people doing odd jobs.
And there are lots of examples
of series with a trio.
Like this.
And this.
They're all the same.
Uh, did you really
need to bring that up?
Yeah, that's right.
It's not the same.
After all, one of them
uses a computer to talk.
Their characters have more personality.
Compared to that, just look at you, Shinpachi.
Why do you talk normally?
You want me to kill you?
Kagura, why haven't you learned any
genuine Kansai-style witty retorts?
Why haven't your boobs
gotten any bigger?
Why are they shrinking?
What was that?!
You're the one who started
off wearing goggles
before they disappeared for no reason!
Why don't you learn how to Connect?!
Why don't you get yourself
a twin brother?!
Shut up!
I'm not gonna wear those
things around every episode!
Don't you realize the limitations
of the author's drawing ability?!
That's why the goggles were removed
from the beginning of the anime!
You should be grateful you even get any
screen time in the opening sequences,
you worthless goggles!
Uh, are you talking to your goggles?
Besides, in Jump,
characters with goggles
are sidekicks like Usopp
and kid Konohamaru!
Er, Naruto was wearing
goggles in volume 1.
And compared to the One Piece
x Toriko crossover last spring,
Gintama and Sket Dance
just lacks pizazz.
It's a boring crossover.
That's not true!
And don't blame them!
Why did Jump bother with
this boring crossover?
I guarantee that they're not
trying to get us all buddy-buddy.
Then what's the point of this crossover?
That should be obvious.
Wh-Who is it?!
You don't need two Jump shows
about people doing odd jobs
at 6 PM on TV Tokyo.
They're pitting us against one another
because of our similar settings.
To see whether the Sket Dan or you guys
are more worthy as Jump's odd jobbers!
Bastards!
I think it's amusing.
Let's go along with
Jump's little scheme.
We had to settle this sooner or later.
Stop that, Bossun. Show some respect.
They've been in Jump
longer than we have.
Sorry about that. He
usually isn't so rude.
He's a nice boy deep down.
Stop acting like my mom!
Bossun, that should be,
"Stop acting like my ma!"
You rock, Switch!
You already know how
to fit in this world!
I mean, ya already know
how to fit in this world!
Don't just barge in here
and start making fun of us!
Pisses me off!
You're destroying our characters!
You're clearly set on crushing us!
Hey, Himeko. Have they really
been around longer than us?
They seem really worried.
Bossun, that's the secret
to their success.
They've spent years pretending
to be the weak link
so they can bash other series
without any repercussions.
Stop spilling the beans,
four-eyed computer boy!
Want me to nail down your enter key?!
Spilling the beans?
Why are you talking to yourself
anyway? The hell is this?
What was that?! You wanna know how
it feels to talk to yourself?!
Shinpachi, let him have it!
What? Me?
Fine then.
H-Hold on...
Recite the 12th clause of the
Tsuu Terakado Fanclub creed!
Taka-chin!
E-Er, I'm not Taka-chin.
You can't fool me,
your childhood friend.
I mean, look.
What's up, Shin-chan?
I'm Taka-chin.
You can't fool me!
Then I'll send in Teppei.
Bossun, where are we?
This makes it harder for me!
Now, now. Stop fighting.
Okay, Runny Diarrhea.
R-Runny...
Teach, Bossun-kun and Pachi-boy-kun
made Himeko-san cry!
I'm not crying!
D-Does this mean...
It can't mean that...
I was cast as...
Jugem Jugem Shit-Tossing the Life of
Shin-chan's Two-Day-Old Underwear
Balmung Fezalion Issac Schneider
1/3 True Love 2/3 Hangnail Anxiety
Betrayal Knows My Name Or Does It Really
Ignore Calls Squid Dogfish
Halibut Trout-Cod Dogfish...
This Is a Different Dogfish,
I'm Talking About The Dogfish Shark
Kaluga Angler Ray
Yuuteimiyaoukimukou
Pepepepepepepepepepepepe
Runny Diarrhea
...just for this?!
Yes, just so we could do that.
That's despicable!
We get in the first word since our
side of the crossover airs earlier.
Now even in the parts of the manga
where we parodied other works,
people will think that
you're copying us.
Man, Gintama's desperate.
I'm kinda creeped out.
They aren't aware that
in most decisive battles,
the one who attacks first usually loses.
Fine then!
Let's make it clear which team has the
pizazz to be worthy of Jump.
This is supposed to be a crossover.
Let's all get along.
Hah, we'll show you that flashy battles
and special attacks aren't everything.
I doubt the viewers are
going to appreciate this.
Yeah, equally boring anime
shows should get along.
We should be glad that
we're still on air.
Shut up! This isn't just about our position.
Our pride as odd-jobbing Jumpers,
and our very existence, is on the line!
You mob characters should just
shut up and follow your leader!
That's right!
C'mon down! I got everything set up!
Impact
Amethystyx (Pachimon type) Capture Level -26
Gin-chan, where are we?
The Gintama world was already a stretch,
and now we're in a place
that's even weirder, Bossun.
Okay, quiet down.
Listen up.
We're going to have a little
scavenger hunt on this island.
Why are you talking like a teacher?
We're on Treasure Island, an island where
shiny gems grow on everything.
This sounds awfully familiar.
There is a legend that every hundred
years, the gems bear a very special fruit.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
Yes! One of the famous Devil Fruit!
The Pizazz-Pizazz Fruit!
Hold it right there!
This is supposed to be a Sket
Dance x Gintama crossover!
But now we're in the Toriko
x One Piece crossover!
We might be boring, but
that doesn't make it okay
to steal ideas from series
that have more pizazz!
Toriko and One Piece?
What are they babbling about?
You must have had some of
that Dream-Dream Fruit.
They're starting to piss me off.
Hopeless fools.
They must have eaten
the Argh-Argh Fruit.
As you may have guessed,
the Pizazz-Pizazz fruit can
give the dullest people pizazz!
Whoever finds it first,
will be declared the winner of the contest
with the flashiness worthy of Jump!
I thought we were fighting over who
had the pizazz worthy of Jump.
But now we've given up?
We're going to rely on outside help?
I have a question.
Does this Devil Fruit
have any side effects,
such as turning one
into a hammer in water?
It's fine. You won't lose
the ability to swim.
I see. So you've changed
the setting a little.
Only your crotch turns into a hammer.
I see, that's good.
Huh?
What did you just say?
Well, it's only your crotch
that turns into a hammer,
so you don't need to worry.
I'm worried!
Why is there a hammer down there?!
Stop that, seriously.
We're supposed to be innocent,
unlike you people.
We don't do dirty jokes!
Himeko-san, I'll handle this.
As the straight man, I'm used
to this, so leave it to me!
The hammer's upside down!
It should be like this!
Who cares?!
Aren't you supposed to be
the Gintama straight man?!
Why are you acting like the funny man?!
I'm not going to last long if I
have to respond to both sides!
I'm sorry, I thought I
could let you handle it.
Right. So who cares if
it's upside down or not.
If I have a hammer on my
crotch, I can't get married.
Are you going to take responsibility?
Isn't that right, Kagura-chan?
Why? What's the problem?
A hammer makes a better
weapon than a hockey stick.
I asked the wrong person!
No, no! Think this through!
You can't survive in this wacky manga
when you have a hammer on your crotch!
You don't need to worry.
If you grow a hammer down there,
Bossun will boss into a nail for you.
What the hell?
What's that mean?
Why would I boss into a nail?
Hey, bitch. Enough already.
Did you call me a bitch?!
You aren't in your puny
little school anymore.
In this world, your crotch
can grow into a screwdriver
or your balls can get
crushed at any time.
What kind of world is this?
If you want to do odd jobs,
you gotta be ready for your
crotch to do odd jobs.
That's not how it's supposed to work!
Oh, really?
You're picking a fight with us when you
aren't ready to get down and dirty?
You shouldn't be so happy just because
AKB did your theme song.
It's not AKB anymore!
Are you jealous?
Say that you're jealous that we got AKB!
Your token glasses character
must be jealous!
Not really!
Fine then!
I'll be the one to turn
my crotch into a hammer!
Uh, wrong objective, Bossun!
No good. Bossun has lost his head.
Your leader doesn't like to lose either.
I want nothing to do with this.
Don't come to me when you lose viewers
because your crotch is a hammer.
We'll just have to stand by and watch.
Bossun has always had a complex
about how he's too boring
to be a main character.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Gin-san always complains about how
he should have a special attack.
That's why it's so hard to make games.
That's why Bandai Namco gave up on us.
Oh, we're going to have that problem.
There's always Hyperion and Genesis.
Those are crap.
We need something like Bankai or Stands.
Oh, I've seen Gin-chan
secretly practicing
his Kamehameha two or three times.
Ouch. Just ouch.
Right. Bossun has that Connecting
special power when he wears his goggles.
But really, it just looks
like he put on his goggles.
Does he yell, "Goggles on!"
He did at first.
Kind of like how your guy
wore goggles at first.
They should stick to it.
To be honest, I don't think
it's about special attacks.
Between his silver hair and that hat,
he's tried a lot of things to stand out,
but people with pizazz
just have it already.
Yeah.
You can't be a main character
when you complain to your buddies
about not standing out.
Luffy would never say
anything like that.
You're never going to hear him say, "I
will become a main character with pizazz!"
Yeah?
That's why these guys just fail.
If they're going to bother competing,
they should set their sights higher.
Really, does it matter who wins?
They're in the same boat anyway.
Indeed, their weak will is
embodied by their weak goals.
They don't have any goals like becoming
the Pirate King or becoming the Hokage.
I'm getting worried about
throwing my lot in with him.
He's too wishy-washy.
I should have gone with a reliable
main character like Luffy.
I want Aya Tojo!
I prefer Nishino.
I prefer Raoh!
Uh, none of those are main characters.
Huh? They disappeared.
Oh, they fell down.
Hey, are you okay? Gin-san? Bo-san?
I'm already...
...sick of this.
They said something.
But I can't hear them.
I'm already...
...sick of this.
They're the ones who
ran off by themselves.
What? You're giving up on
finding the Devil Fruit?
Let's go home then.
We need to wrap up this episode.
They really want attention.
They're the ones who dragged us into this...
what are they trying to do?
Just ignore them and go back.
I agree.
I must return to my enjoyment
of To Love-Ru Darkness.
Uh, Himeko-san.
Sorry about the Runny Diarrhea thing.
Nah, it's okay.
This crossover was new and fun.
Like...
Like, you guys don't
understand how we feel.
Uh oh, he's going to
start monologuing again.
It's not that we want pizazz,
or that we want to stand out.
That's not what drives us.
We're doing this for
the sake of our teams,
but none of you even care.
Yeah, yeah. Forget it.
There's no point in trying
to explain to them.
Wait, I'm really upset about this.
Don't you feel the same way, Sakata-san?
He just called him Sakata-san.
Forget it. Just forget it.
Stop talking.
I know how you feel.
It's not easy being the leader.
They're buddies now.
Uh, sorry.
Could you leave?
Feel free to go join Luffy or Raoh or whoever.
We leaders are going to
do this by ourselves.
This is bad. They heard
what we were saying.
Hey. Pull yourself together, Bossun.
Can you stand?
Uh, Gin-san. We're sorry.
You've got it wrong! You've
got it wrong, Bossun!
We were just joking!
We just wanted to give
you a little push.
It's not like you need
to apologize or anything.
Everything you said
was absolutely right.
An apology won't heal Bossun
and Gin-san's wounded hearts!
What's going on?
I can't tell if they want
us to apologize or not.
They left. Should we just ignore them?
They got mad when we tried to apologize.
Those leaders are too hard to deal with.
How naive can they be?
Hmm? They're not moving forward.
They're walking in place.
They're waiting for us to say something.
What a pain!
What are they trying to do?!
Hang in there!
Now they're acting.
Where did Bossun injure
himself?! His head?!
Hey, this isn't good.
They're not chasing after us.
They've given up on us.
Why?! Aren't they worried about me?
They don't care about their leader?!
At this rate, we'll lose
our status as leaders.
We have to find the Pizazz-Pizazz
Fruit to regain their trust.
H-Hey, look there!
There it is!
What? They just took off.
Did they find the Devil Fruit?
Pathetic.
They've revealed their true
colors and started to fight.
Let go! I'm going to get pizazz!
I'll become a brutal
genius with an IQ of 300
whose hair turns silver
when my powers awaken!
Over my dead body!
The pizazz is mine!
I'll become a space pirate
who's lost his memories with
a Psycho-gun on my right arm and
travel around space with hot women!
Almost there!
So close to the pizazz!
Who is that guy?
That's a dangerous place to stand.
Honey, forgive me for going on ahead.
I can't do any carpentry
when my hand's like this.
Can't even hold a hammer...
Damn it.
But I'm healthy down there.
If my crotch became a hammer,
I could use my rapid hip
movements to hammer nails.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hold on, gramps!
Gramps! Your request...
...has been accepted!
So in the end, neither
of them got any pizazz.
But there's nothing
wrong with being boring.
Yeah, that's right.
They're great odd jobbers.
They're great leaders.
Hey, why are you so blue?
Cheer up, guys.
You looked good back
there. I'm impressed.
Let's call this a draw.
Next time, we won't lose.
Fine by me.
Next time, we'll wreck you!
To finish, you twist the story into
something resembling a good ending.
That's as Gintama as you get.
Exactly.
This way, you have a
sense of completion.
Uh, can you stop that?
The episode's over.
Were you really that
desperate for some pizazz?
It's okay.
No, that's not it...
When we threw the Pizazz-Pizazz
Fruit at the old man,
some of the juice sprayed out.
Everyone, tune in next
week for Carpenter Dance
and Gin-Balls.
Next Episode Preview
Notice: This footage isn't real.
Next time on Gintama,
Odd Jobs suddenly appears
in the Sket Dan clubroom.
Wait, isn't this the preview
for our episode this week?!
Why are you showing a
preview for our show?!
And why are you showing fake footage?!
Well, it just happened as I was
following the original.
What's that mean?!
Is this really okay?
Episode 26
Next time: Spirit Dance!
We're the academy support group!
Carpenter Dance!