Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Central 46.
It consists of forty sages and
six judges gathered
from across the Soul Society.
It is the Soul Society's
highest judicial system.
Any crime committed by a Soul Reaper
is judged here
regardless of whether it happened
in the Soul Society
or in the World of the Living.
If they decide that military force
is necessary to carry out a verdict,
they give out orders to various forces
such as the Stealth Force, the Kido expert,
and the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
And once a verdict is declared,
no one, not even a captain,
can appeal the decision.
That is what Central 46 is.
Wh-What is this?
What's going on?!
The blood is dry…
It's blackened and even beginning
to crack…
Which means that they weren't killed
today or yesterday…
When were they killed?!
After Abarai was defeated and
martial law was declared,
this central underground assembly hall
was locked down
and no one was allowed
to enter.
And its defense system was engaged
until we forced our way in just now.
There was no sign of a forced entry.
Which means that
they were killed before then!
And all the decisions given to us
from Central 46
since then have been…
all fake…
Who did it? Ichimaru?
Something this big by himself?
Or are there others who helped him?
I thought you'd come,
Captain Hitsugaya.
Kira--!
Are you the one who did this?!
After him, Matsumoto!
Yes!
Wait! Kira!
Answer my question!
Are you the one who did that
to Central 46?!
No. I was just let in to
the underground assembly hall
before you arrived.
They opened the lock
from the inside.
Who let you in?!
Why, Central 46, of course.
Are you making fun of me?!
What about the seal?!
Never mind all that,
Captain Hitsugaya.
Instead of chasing me…
shouldn’t you be concerned
about protecting Hinamori?
What are you talking about?
Hinamori is…
She's not in Squad 10 barracks
anymore.
Captain Hitsugaya,
you put up a barrier
around the room that Hinamori
was sleeping in, didn't you?
You used Kyomon,
a high-level barrier that reflects
all attacks from the outside.
That's why you left her there
thinking she’d be safe.
But that barrier can be easily broken
from the inside.
Hinamori is a master of Kido.
It's easy for her to break
your barrier from the inside
or move while completely hiding
her Spiritual Pressure…
You didn’t notice?
Hinamori was following you
the entire time.
Matsumoto!
Can I leave him to you?
Go ahead!
What? You’re not running away anymore?
You didn't know,
did you, Matsumoto?
About what?
About my Zanpakuto's ability…
You don’t tell anyone about things
like that.
That's not true.
I think my classmates,
Hinamori and Abarai, know…
But that's okay.
I'll tell you, too…
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
You…
You have good reflexes.
Who do you think you are?!
There's something wrong
with you!
Kira!
I don't know what Gin told you, but…
How many times have
you blocked my sword?
It doubles the weight
of whatever it strikes.
If I strike twice,
the weight doubles.
If I strike three times,
the weight doubles again.
Until finally…
the defender can no longer
bear the weight
and grovel on the ground,
head bowed down as if in penitence.
Thus the name, Wabisuke,
“the penitence one.”
If you weren’t counting,
I'll tell you.
If a sword is 0.8 kilograms,
that multiplied by
two to the seventh power
would make
your sword 102.4 kilograms.
That's not something
you can run with.
So what?
If I can't run with it,
then I just don't carry it.
Gin…What do you want to do
with him?
Roar, Haineko.
And what do you want with me…?
Just where do you want to go…?
What…is this?
Everyone in Central 46…
is dead.
Everyone…
Hitsugaya…was surprised…
there was Kira…
Hitsugaya followed him…
What's going on?
If Hitsugaya is the one
who killed Captain Aizen,
then he must be the one
who did this as well, but…
So…that means…
the one who did this…is Kira?
Then…
What about Hitsugaya…?
Is Captain Aizen…?
Welcome, Hinamori.
Captain…Ichimaru?
Come this way.
Hinamori!
This is…Seijoto Kyorin,
Immaculate Tower Grove.
The living quarters of Central 46…
Why would you bring me here?
Captain Ichimaru…
How many times have
you been here, Hinamori?
No way…
This area is completely off limits.
This is the first time I've seen it.
There’s someone
I want you to meet…
Want me to meet?
That's right.
But…
Take a look.
Behind you.
Behind…me?
Captain…Aizen…
It's been a while, Hinamori.
Is it really you, Captain Aizen?
I thought you were dead…
I'm alive, as you can see.
C-Captain Aizen…
Captain Aizen…
I…
I’m sorry. You must’ve been worried.
Oh… It’s Captain Aizen's hand…
It's so warm…and big…
Talk as much as you like
until you calm down.
I don't mind.
Stay as long as you like.
The same scent of Captain Aizen
that cleanses my soul…
It really is…Captain Aizen…
I thought there was no hope…
I thought I couldn't go on…
but I was wrong…
That was a lie. A lie.
Yes, I knew…
Captain Aizen wouldn't die.
I knew he wouldn't die
and leave me behind…
You've become a bit thin…
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry for hurting you so much…
But you understand, right?
It had to be you.
There was something
I had to do.
I had to fake my own death and…
It's all right…
It's all right now.
I can't wish for anything more
as long as you're alive…
Thank you, Hinamori.
I'm really glad I had you
as a subordinate.
Thank you, Hinamori…
Thank you very much…
Goodbye.
What is…this?
What…?
Let's go, Gin.
Yes, Captain Aizen.
Hello, Hitsugaya.
Ai…zen?!
But how…
Is it really you?
Of course. As you can see,
I'm the real one.
But…
Captain Hitsugaya returned
a lot faster than expected.
Sorry. Izuru must’ve failed
to keep him.
What…What are you talking about?
What are we talking about?
Just strategy.
Dividing an enemy’s fighting power
is the basics in strategy.
Enemy!?
Where is Hinamori?!
I wonder…
Hina…mori?
How unfortunate.
You found her.
I’m sorry.
I didn't mean to surprise you.
Maybe I should’ve chopped her
into little pieces
so you couldn't find her.
Aizen… Ichimaru…
When did you team up?
Since before
you faked your death?
From the beginning, of course.
Since I became a captain.
I never considered anyone other
than Gin as my lieutenant.
Then…all this time…
Hinamori…
Me…
Your subordinates,
all the other Soul Reapers…
Everyone…
You've been deceiving us all?!
I never thought of it that way.
It’s just none of you understood…
my true identity.
Didn't understand?
Hinamori…
She looked up to you…
She joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
so she could be closer to you.
She worked so hard to become
your lieutenant, to serve you…
And she finally made it!
I know.
That’s why she was
so easy to manipulate.
That's why I requested her
to be my subordinate.
Wha--?
This is a good opportunity.
Remember this, Hitsugaya.
Admiration is the state furthest
from understanding.
Bankai.
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Oh!
Aizen…
I'm going to kill you.
Don't use such strong words.
It’ll make you look weak.
What?!
This can't be…happening…
What a beautiful sight.
Ice is not in season,
but it's not so bad to see it
at this time of the year.
Captain Aizen.
No, we probably shouldn't call you
captain any longer…
You’re just Sosuke Aizen,
the traitor.
Hello, Captain Unohana.
I thought you'd have shown up by now.
Did you immediately figure out
that I would be here?
Seijoto Kyorin is the only place
within the Seireitei
that is absolutely off limits.
This is the only place to hide
in the Seireitei
for someone who’s gone so far
as to fake his own death
with such an elaborate corpse doll.
Close.
Your insight is good,
but you made two mistakes.
First of all,
I didn't come here to hide.
And second…
This is not a corpse doll.
Wh-When did he…
When?
I've been holding it all this time.
But…
I just wasn't letting
you see it until now.
Wh-What do you…
You'll understand soon enough.
I’ll release it now.
Shatter, Kyokasuigetsu.
This is my Zanpakuto,
Kyokasuigetsu.
Its ability is perfect hypnosis.
Perfect…hypnosis?
But Kyokasuigetsu is supposed to be
a running-water-type Zanpakuto…
That it uses diffused reflection
of running water and mist
to confuse enemies into
attacking each other!
Captain Aizen,
that’s what you told us!
You gathered all the lieutenants
and showed it to us!
I see…
So that was actually
the hypnosis ritual.
Correct.
Perfect hypnosis controls
all five senses
and can cause every dimension
of a target,
including its form, shape,
mass, feel, and smell,
to replicate that of an enemy.
In other words, it can make
a fly appear to be a dragon
or a marsh a flowerbed.
And all I need to do to activate it
is to show my enemies
the release of Kyokasuigetsu.
Whoever lays eyes on it,
even once,
will be hypnotized into
doing my bidding
whenever I release
my Kyokasuigetsu.
Whoever lays eyes on it…
even once…
It seems you figured it out.
Yes. Whoever lays their eyes
on it falls under my spell.
Which means that those
who can't see will not be affected.
In other words…
Kaname Tosen was my subordinate
from the beginning.
C-Captain Tosen?!
Why are you here?
Wh-What is this?!
Before I go,
I'd like to commend you for
sensing something suspicious
about my dead body,
Captain Unohana.
You had the chance to examine
my body the longest,
but you were still
under perfect hypnosis.
Goodbye. I doubt I will
ever see any of you again.
Wait!
What the hell was that all about…?
This is the Sokyoku hill?
Welcome…
Abarai.
Captain Aizen?
It can't be…
Ichimaru…
What’s going on?
Leave Rukia Kuchiki here
and back away.
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
In the next episode,
I plan to divulge my true intentions
with a dinner show.
There're still
some tickets available,
but it's first come first served.
I'm making
a special guest appearance.
Look forward to it.
There's no such show!
And you're no star!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden!
Why is my sexy body being unreasonably
strapped to that kid?
Damn it…
I'm going to get it back!
Take this, Jinta Dribble!
I'll turn anyone who gets in
my way into minced meat!
Kill
What's he doing?!
That was a foul, a foul!
What? It's okay?!
Since when did you
become the referee?!
When are we going to do
the Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers?!
Tune in again!