Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What the hell happened
to Muramasa?!
My body…hot…
Settle down!
Koga…
Koga!
Getsugatensho!
Why're Hollows coming out
of Muramasa's body?!
It's likely that he's no longer
able to suppress
the Spiritual Pressure
of the Hollows,
that he had somehow absorbed…
He gave up everything
for Koga's sake…
He even exceeded
his own limitations—
it's as though he's only existed
until now through sheer will power…
Ko…ga…
What's that?!
They're…
This is bad!
It looks like Muramasa's
Spiritual Pressure
is attracting Hollows
in the vicinity!
Then I'll take them on
all at once!
Damn!
Huh?
Ishida!
Against these numbers,
it looks like my bow
is more appropriate
than your sword that's huge
but nothing more.
You're so nice to have around—
like bug spray.
Shut up!
Kurosaki! Kuchiki!
Chad! Inoue!
Santenkesshun!
Nice, Inoue.
Damn…
What's going to happen
to Muramasa?!
This…can't be…
Not yet…
I still have…
Come to me…Muramasa…
What's the matter?
Muramasa…
Why won't you respond?
I'm calling for you!
Mura…ma…
I'm all right now.
Koga…
If he hadn't possessed
such power,
he would not have
had such delusions…
It was the fate of
a weak-hearted man
consumed and controlled by power…
He was the exact opposite of you,
who willingly allowed himself
to be branded a traitor,
in order to stick to your beliefs.
Now you can finally
return to where you belong.
You talk too much,
Senbonzakura.
What is that?!
Are the Hollows being
sucked toward him?
Is that…Muramasa?!
It looks almost like an Arrancar!
A Zanpakuto is of one mind and
one body with
its Soul Reaper master…
It attaches itself to the soul of
its master and coexists with him…
Are you saying that in order
to maintain his physical form,
he needed a source of energy
to replace his Soul Reaper master?
He probably had to take in Hollows
in order to maintain his body…
Then the energy that
deflected my power was…
It goes to show
how deep his feeling
and obsession
towards Koga was.
But for it to end in such a way…
W-Why?
You have become nothing
but a hindrance to me.
I don't need to use
an unstable sword like you—
my powers alone are enough.
A Zanpakuto is merely a tool.
Damn…
If we don't do something,
his Spiritual Pressure might
envelop all of Karakura Town…
We have to stop him
before that happens!
Right!
He's coming!
He's fast!
Those eyes…
It looks so lonely…
He so desperately
sought after his master,
only to be abandoned…
It's too cruel.
Brother!
You're all right.
Byakuya! Did you defeat Koga?
Did you think I would lose?
Yeah, right.
You look pretty beat up.
Brother, we need to
treat your injuries…
Never mind that…
Right now,
he is our main concern…
I never expected him
to unleash a Sero…
He's completely
become a Hollow…
I won't give in…
Not to the power of Hollows…
What?
Is he…
fighting the Hollows he absorbed?
This is all wrong…
Inoue!
Stop! Don't fight anymore!
The person you were looking
for no longer exists!
It's no use, Inoue!
The way he is now,
he can't listen to reason…
No… He hasn't completely
been possessed by Hollows yet…
In the depths of despair,
he's still fighting desperately
to maintain his identity…
What?!
I won't give in…
I won't…give in…
Koga…
Is he still seeking Koga,
even though he's become like that?
What tenacity…
It's meaningless to do this…
You'll only cause yourself
more suffering…
So…let's stop this.
I won't give in…I won't…give…
Inoue, get away from him!
Why you—!
Are you okay, Inoue?
Yes…it's nothing.
Can't we save him
from his sadness?
Getsugatensho!
Huh?
Stop it!
Damn! The Hollows
are swarming again!
Sado, we'll split up
and take care of them!
El Directo!
Hado 33, Sokatsui!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Muramasa!
Getsugatensho!
I won't…give…in…
What the—?!
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
No… Kurosaki's
Spiritual Pressure is…
It can't be…
What is this?
The Spiritual Pressure
of the Hollows
that Muramasa took in
induced this…
Inoue?
I have to go and save
Kurosaki and Muramasa…
It's dangerous! Stay back!
But…
This isn't good!
Garganta is opening up…
And we're in a bad situation…
Scatter, Senbonzakura!
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Sodeno…shirayuki…
I'm sorry it took so long.
Sodenoshirayuki…
why are you here?
It's not just me.
Hey.
There are others who've
come to help, as well!
Wow! Zanpakuto are incredible!
There are so many
different types!
There's a cat, a snake…
And a dog, too.
You're right! It's so cute!
If it were a bit smaller,
I'd want to keep it as a pet.
Come here, boy!
That's actually…
Captain Komamura.
The Arrancar Encyclopedia
That's odd…
What's the matter?
You look like there's a problem…
There is a sudden decrease in
the number of Menos recently.
Huh?
Could someone be
poaching Menos?
Hold on a second, Tosen…
Don't tell me you were also
managing the Menos?
Why of course.
Checking their health condition,
knowing what foods they're eating…
Keeping watch over each individual
is the way to raise the best Menos.
So where exactly are you
going to sell them off to?