Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
This is no good.
Hey, Karin! Wait!
There've been so many incidents
like this lately.
Sightings of UFOs, poltergeists…
It's probably because of them.
Is something there?
It's better you can't see them.
They'll only make you sick.
Huh? What was that?
A cat…?!
W-What?!
– What is that?! It's coming this way!
– Get it off me, Karin!
I'm not sure what's happening,
but I won't lose!
That'll teach them!
That was scary!
Karin, look!
Doesn't it look like brother?
Huh? It's Ichigo!
Hey…isn't there something wrong
with this cat?
Uh…hmmm…
I have this strange feeling…
like I've seen it somewhere before.
Right?
Huh? Meow?
Oh, I see.
What'd it say?
It's hungry.
Are you serious?
Yup, I'm not positive,
but it's a woman's intuition.
Hmm? And do you remember
where you saw this cat before?
Nope, not at all.
– Oh…
– Cat food! Let's go buy cat food.
All right.
Man, this is so annoying.
It's useless cleaning up.
No one's gonna come to
a store like this.
I don't think that's true.
Tell me how many customers
we had this month.
Well…
Not one!
That hurts, Jinta!
Shut up!
Hollow spotted!
Disposal complete.
Ever since Carrot-top left,
they've increased.
I know!
I think I'm not getting enough
exercise lately.
I think I've gained weight.
I have something to take care of that.
I bought this on the
Grasshopper Shopping Channel.
It's the original weight-loss remedy,
Karugaru-kun.
– Wow. Sounds questionable…
– Huh?
I mean I just don't believe
in such products.
Well, I tried it myself and
the results were quite amazing.
Is something wrong?
– Something's growling.
– Jinta?
– Awright!
It’s time!
For the sake of the town,
it's time to exterminate Hollows!
"We'll get scolded if
we don't clean up."
I can't understand
what you're saying!
I think there's something wrong
with this cat, after all.
Huh? Why?
Hmm… Just a feeling.
There's nothing wrong
with you, right, Raku?
What's “Raku”?
Its name. That's what I named it.
Raku as in "rakuda" or camel, because it's
the color of my camel-colored underpants.
Camel-colored underpants?
Huh?!
What's this car parked
in front of our house? It's so huge.
It's obstructing our business!
W-What?!
You there, cute ladies…
Spirits are always with you!
Ah! It's Don Kanonji!
A-Are you all right?
Sorry. Maybe I startled you.
Are you the boy's family?
Huh? Boy?
Of course! My #1 pupil, Ichigo!
Huh? Brother's your #1 pupil?!
Of course!
Wow! Wonderful! Really?!
– Brother is your #1 pupil! Wow!
– I have a rare day off today,
so I came here incognito
to play with him, but…
Where is the boy?
Incognito? And making such
a big scene?
Brother isn't home.
Oh…my…God!
If you're done here, go home.
That's…!
Why you bad spirits!
You stay there!
Mr. Kanonji!
Karin, what's that?
Huh? You can see that?
Oh. Now that you mention it…
I see. I see.
You are able to see them now, too.
Sorry, but I'm going straight
to the finish!
Golden Cannonball!
Carelessness is
the greatest enemy!
Agh! They have no mercy!
Mr. Kanonji!
– Huh?
– What?
The legendary Red Bat!
Mission complete!
Hey!
Mr. Kanonji!
Are you all right?
Are you hurt, little girl?
I-I'm okay.
– Huh? Is he for real?!
– That's Don Kanonji!
Hey! Yuzu! Karin!
Did Mr. Kanonji save you?
I'm so jealous!
Mission complete! Bohahahaha!
Mr. Kanonji,
won't you join us for tea?
– You two come with me, too!
– If I may say so myself…
it’s pretty good tea.
– Kanonji! Kanonji! Kanonji!
– Hey! Where're you going?!
By the way, who are you two?
I'm the one who'll be clean-up batter
in the Majors someday, Jinta.
I'm Ururu.
I'm Yuzu Kurosaki.
Kurosaki?
So you know Carrot-top?
You know our brother?
In a way…
That cat…
It seems the Hollows are appearing,
lured by its spiritual power.
Hollow? Those things just now?
Yup. We should probably let that
cat's spirit pass over peacefully.
Huh? Raku isn't a ghost.
Huh? What're you saying?
That's a spirit.
Is not! Don't say such things!
I-It's true! That cat's already dead!
It's not dead! Cut it out already!
Hey! You're Carrot-top's sisters,
and you can't even figure that out?!
Wonderful and great!
Isn't it amazing?!
Although you pale in comparison to me,
imagine kids with such talent
gathering here!
You will all be my disciples!
Not interested!
I like you more and more,
boys and girls.
I've been seeking your type,
those with youthful power!
Now come with me!
Hey! Come! Come!
Mister, want another one?
How unfortunate…
The power hidden within you…
I will acknowledge that.
However, that's a little short!
All right! I shall take a
good look at your powers!
I don't understand all this,
but it's my chance to show
you my true power!
Well, sorry…
I still haven't gotten serious either.
– Such energetic children!
– I'm taller than you!
– Now come with me!
– Height has nothing to do with it!
Of course, it does!
Come, young ones!
The future is in your hands!
That cat… Left like that,
it'll be attacked again.
No way…and Mr. Kanonji is gone.
What'll I do?
I'll ask the boss.
Huh?
Lunch Time
Sorry…
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
What'll you do?
If this man, Kisuke,
can do something, I'll wait.
There's nothing else we can do.
Uh-huh…
Thank you, Ururu.
Hollows approaching!
Over here!
Escape out the back!
Ururu!
It's all right. I'll protect you.
Dammit! How long is he
gonna make us wait?
Sorry to keep you waiting,
boys and girls.
The charismatic medium of
the new century, Don Kanonji,
at your service!
All right! I'll show you what I've got!
Me, too!
Hold it!
I am not your opponent.
Huh?!
Think about it.
Why should heroes fight each other?
Huh?
Actually, I have been thinking
about starting a special troop
with kind-hearted kids
who share my vision
to protect the peace of the town!
And they would be called
Karakura Super Heroes!
These days in the entertainment world,
it's natural for grade school kids
who’ve undergone rigid auditions
to take active parts.
Right? And you two have potential!
Well, how about it?
Will you form a unit under me…
– So long-winded.
– and protect…
– This is stupid.
– Karakura City?
And on top of that,
since you are the first two I've scouted…
Guess what? The Red position is open…
– Red?!
RED = THE LEADER
Oh, and I forgot to mention that
I intend to turn this
into a segment of my
"Spontaneous Trips" television show.
Television?!
– I'm in!
– I guess I have no choice.
Since it's to protect the peace
in Karakura Town.
Okay! I accept your enthusiasm!
Okay, I'll be Red. It’s decided.
Hey! You can't just decide
like that! I'm Red! Me!
Shut up! No girl can be Red!
What?! You looking for a fight?
What a pain!
I refuse to let you be Red!
Huh? This is…
Bad spirits are after your sister!
It's dangerous!
Get ready for our first job!
I can't understand what
he's saying at all.
Raku?
Raku? Huh?!
Smells like bad spirits!
I don’t think so!
Raku?!
Raku…
SPIRIT DRINK
FROM PIERRE CORP.
Sorry to keep you waiting, little girl.
Don't worry because we're here!
Karakura Red, Karin Kurosaki!
And the real Karakura Red,
Jinta Harakari!
Hey, hold it! Didn't you hear me?
I'm Red!
Shut up! It's decided! I'm Red!
No way! Red is definitely me!
Okay! We'll decide who Red will be
based on your performance today!
– Yeah!
– I'll show you!
Mr. Kanonji… Karin…
Secret Attack! Ultra Spirit Javelin!
EASILY ATTACHABLE SAW
GRIPS WELL TOO
With this amazing device,
EVEN HIGH BRANCHES.
SO EASY TO MANEUVER!
you can reach any Bad Spirit,
EASILY EXTENDABLE
PRUNING SHEARS
no matter how high.
It extends…
What're you doing?! You coward!
You're too slow!
Scatter! Scatter!
Wonderful, boy's sister!
I shall entrust the
Spirit Javelin to you!
Hah! The lead is mine!
Clean-up batter, Jinta Hanakari!
Jersey number 55!
Very good swing!
You are the superstar that
will linger in memory!
It's only natural, 'cuz I'm Red!
Karin…
Yuzu, get away!
Okay!
Hey! Hold it!
Hey!
Yuzu!
Huh?!
Ururu!
W-What's this?
Another new generation?!
Wonderful! So many Red candidates!
Ururu! Showing up
out of the blue!
You're not taking the
Red title from me!
I keep telling you,
you're not Red, either!
Number One…
Only the one who gives
a Number One performance
deserves the Red title.
I won't lose!
I'll show you!
Magnificent!
Karakura Superheroes is born!
Aren't you going to fight,
Mr. Kanonji?
Hey you!
That kind of fighting
won't make you Red!
Useless!
There's a soccer ball!
There! Did you see the power of Red?!
Like I said, I'm RED!
What's that?!
So you've finally appeared…
Bad Spirit King!
It's coming this way!
Let's do it now!
This is a job for the Karakura Superheroes!
– Right!
But before that, let's plan strategy.
– We don't have time!
Yuzu!
Raku…
What's that?
An ally?
It's…a miracle!
Our unified desire for justice
called forth a miracle!
That is the Hero Robot
sent to us by the gods!
Karakura Lion Jet!
– Ohh!
– Wow!
Let's join the Lion Jet, too!
Let's go!
Now! Karakura Attack Formation!
– Right!
Kirukiruaunan…kirukiruaunan
Take this! Secret Attack of Justice!
Golden Cannonball!
Jinta…
Homerun!
Karin-style…Death Shot!
It's coming! Ururu!
Okay!
Karakura Superheroes!
Mission complete! Bohahahaha!
Did that thing really work?
Of course! It was the finishing blow!
No way, not at all.
Oh, I remember.
I did meet Raku before. Right?
Here…
Bye bye…
If I hadn't come by,
Raku wouldn't have had to die.
I thought maybe you’d hold
a grudge against me.
But…
Raku…
Yuzu!
Karin…!
Thank goodness!
I…
The legendary Karakura Lion Jet,
which was summoned from
our power of justice, saved you.
Huh?
Right! We summoned
this amazing thing!
Hey, where'd it go?
That's right.
But it was amazing!
Secret?
All right. It'll be our secret.
What?!
Wha--?!
I'm glad. I think it was
able to pass over.
Huh? Then that cat was
really a ghost?
Probably, it was able to come
to terms with whatever regrets it had.
I-I wasn't able to do …
anything for Raku…
H-Hey…
He said, "thank you," to you just now.
Really?
I'm not sure,
but a man senses these things.
Really? Really?
It's all right…
Raku…thank you.
Karakura Pink,
Ururu Tsumugiya.
Karakura Red,
Karin Kurosaki!
Jinta Hanakari!
I said I'm Red!
Shut up! I'm Red!
You are not fit to be Red!
You're more like Yellow!
And…the leader/producer,
Karakura Gold,
is as you know…
the natural-born hero Don Kanonji!
– Leader?!
– Karakura Gold?!
– What's that?!
Now everyone,
follow your leader/producer!
– We quit!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Oh, that was a nice story.
Everyone, do your best!
Not! What about everyone's idol, Kon?!
Whoever's responsible, come out!
No one cares about your existence.
I got new stuffing, and was waiting!