In my right hand,
the stone that connects the worlds.
In my left hand,
the blade that binds existence.
The black-haired shepherd.
The chair of the noose.
I strike the ibis
when the clouds gather.
This hole that the Arrancar
come and go through
is called a Garganta.
Inside, there is no path,
and there are wild reishi currents
swirling around.
Move through it by making
footing out of reishi.
If you move towards the darkness,
you should reach Hueco Mundo.
Let's go!
Now then.
I guess I should do my job.
In order to let Ichigo and
his friends rescue Orihime Inoue,
Urahara opened a Garganta,
the opening that connects
the World of the Living
with Hueco Mundo.
However, there were still things
he needed to do.
This is the story of what occurred
during Ichigo and his friends' battle
in Hueco Mundo.
KONSO COP KARAKURIZER
EPISODE 1
A HERO FOR JUSTICE IS BORN
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Sis…
Bonjour!
And that is how Kurosaki and
the others left for Hueco Mundo.
However, just because Kurosaki
is no longer here,
does not mean the Hollows have
stopped appearing in Karakura town!
Something needs to be done,
but unfortunately,
I have other matters to attend to.
So, I slept on it a night and
this is what I came up with!
Protect Karakura Town!
A "Konso Cop Karakurizer"
transformation wristwatch!
Huh? That's a very
unhappy-looking face.
It's your chance to appear
in the show.
Of course, I'm unhappy.
Just when I was sleeping and
feeling so good dreaming about Sis.
You wake me up like that.
Bonjour.
What? Wasn't that an elegant way
to wake up?
Elegant my foot!
Don't think everything's elegant
just because you say it in French!
Now, now, don't be like that!
Here, put this on.
Let go of me!
I've got better things to do
than that!
Bug someone else!
Why're you so reluctant?
Who wouldn't be?!
Nothing good happens
when you're around!
That's a mean thing to say.
If a stranger heard that,
they might get
the wrong impression.
It's the truth!
Don't be like that.
Come on!
Put this on,
just for the heck of it!
I told you,
I'm not going to do it!
You won't do it, after all, huh?
Even though it was your chance
to be popular with the girls.
Well, if you absolutely refuse,
then I'm not going to force you.
W-Wait!
Is something wrong?
N-Nothing, I just…
You did, after all, insist.
I'm willing to at least listen.
Okay, then… Let's get started!
W-Wait! I only said I'd listen.
Don't you want to be popular
with the girls?
And what's more, I think that
with Kurosaki not here,
you can use this to preserve
the peace in Karakura Town
and even earn praise from
your beloved Kuchiki!
Sis?
Way to go, Kon!
I see you differently now!
Sis!
Feel like doing it, now?
When you put it that way,
I'll go along with this,
but just for a little while!
Okay, then I'll get right into
teaching you how this works!
Click the button on the side.
It's really cool!
Huh? This one? Transfer…
Wait! Use "Career Change"
as the activation code.
Huh?!
It's set up so that any other
activation code will shock you to death.
Shock me to death?!
What is that? A cat?
It's the alarm!
A Hollow has appeared!
Go, Kon.
I mean Konso Cop Karakurizer!
No, "Kon" is fine.
But I just put this wristwatch
on a minute ago.
Do I have go on a mission already?!
You'll be fine!
You're already invincible!
No, that's not what I meant.
Tessai!
Karakurizer is about to take off!
Roger that, Owner!
Whoa!
Mr. Karakurizer, here we go!
Hey you, what're you going to do?!
Hey!
He's all yours, Tessai.
I understand!
Let me go!
Karakurizer, away!
LARGE SIZE HOLLOW
ZONZAIN
Ouch!
You're safe now.
Leave this place to him and
let's get out of here quickly!
What? But…
Come on, quickly!
We'll leave the rest to you!
Ow ow ow…
Who the hell are you?!
Umm… You see…
I'm… That's… Umm…
Kon, please hurry and transform
into Karakurizer!
Oh, that's right. Umm…
If you don't transform within
five seconds,
you'll be shocked to death.
C-Career Change!
I'm beginning to see it.
The new hero who will
protect Karakura Town.
It exploded!
Huh?
Nice entry scene!
This is why I said not to…
Besides,
This is too lame!
I asked Ishida to design the outfit!
You deliberately chose
the wrong person!
Why'd you let
that four-eyes do it?!
If you had asked me,
I could've come up with
a much sharper design.
Huh?
Ready, set…
Pound!
What's the big idea?!
You talk too much!
Shut up!
In situations like this,
you normally hold off on your attack!
Who cares?
But never mind that,
who are you?!
I am the hero of justice
who has come to defeat you!
Konso Cop…
Karakurizer!
KONSO COP
KARAKURAISER
Oh!
Ururu, good timing on
the character insertion.
Kon's a lot more into it,
than I expected.
So, are you surprised?!
Not really.
Just carried away
by your intensity.
What?!
Besides, what kind of pose is that?!
It sucks!
Sh-Shut up!
The protagonist's duty is to strike
a pose when he appears!
Once you've transformed,
strike a pose in the shape of
the letter "K" with your entire body.
If you don't, you'll explode!
I'm going to kill
that bastard one day!
Ready, set, pound!
I said to wait!
Who cares?
You're wide open!
You're nothing but a minor Hollow
that I can finish with a single blow!
Don't think your life will last
through the commercial break!
Give it your best shot!
You'll regret talking to me
like that after you're dead!
How's that? Surprised?!
Everybody might have
completely forgotten,
but I was originally an
enhanced-leg-strength-model Mod Soul!
When the power of the suit
is added to my original strength,
my leaping ability is doubled
even further!
And that means my kicks
are doubled, as well!
There's no such feature.
What?!
Your leg strength is
already strong enough,
so I didn't think I needed
to go through the trouble
of putting in
a body-strengthening feature.
"Didn't think"?!
Now's my chance!
Oww!
Ouch! That really hurts!
Oww…oww.
That bastard!
He kept that attack hidden.
Hey, you sinister shopkeeper!
Does this thing have anything
I can shoot with?!
Oh yes, yes.
It has a Rizer Beam!
Want to use it?
I'll use it! I want to use it!
Okay, then use your body to
spell out "Rizer Beam,"
then cross your arms
and thrust them out.
Why does it take such
a roundabout method?
Because if you don't,
not only will the beam not fire,
but you'll be shocked to death as well!
I get it!
Don't forget to call it out!
Here goes! Special Technique!
Ri…z…er…
Beam!
Stop!
Awesome.
You did it, Kon.
I mean, Karakurizer!
I told you, "Kon" is fine.
If you're so particular about
making a hero look good,
shouldn't I do some sort
of victory pose?
You're exactly right,
but I never imagined you'd win,
so I hadn't thought that far ahead!
What's that mean?!
I'm sorry.
I'll think of one now,
so get back here.
I'm reading a new Hollow!
It's right nearby!
Hey, is that what I think that is?
Yes, it is.
A new Hollow has appeared.
I knew it.
You'll be able to see it
with your own eyes soon.
Do your best to defeat it, okay?
Don't make it sound so simple!
Guess I don't have a choice.
I'll use the Riser Beam again and…
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
The Rizer Beam uses
a lot of energy,
so you can only fire it once
per transformation!
What?!
What's that?!
Why're there so many?!
Powerful Hollows appearing one after
another in such a short period of time.
As I suspected,
the time seems to be approaching.
Damn! That sinister shopkeeper…
Putting nothing but useless techniques
in this thing.
However, the enemy is a flying Hollow.
This suit has just the perfect thing
for such an opponent!
Here goes!
Special Technique! Rizer Cape!
Allow me to explain!
The Rizer Cape has 1.5 times
the normal number of pleats!
Oh! So I can use the 1.5 times
the normal number of pleats to…
Huh? Did you say pleats?
Right! 1.5 times!
Is that all it is?
Of course!
I can't fly?
You can't fly.
What?!
Hey! Sinister shopkeeper!
What's the meaning of this?!
It's totally useless!
Huh?
Stop! Hey!
You! Let go! Hey!
D-Damn it… It's strong.
At this rate…
Stop! That hurts! Not the butt!
Hold it!
W-What's that?!
– Karakurizer!
Ready, and…
Are you all right, Karakurizer?
We've come to help you!
That's…
I am the new emissary of justice,
Karakurizer Spirit!
Don Kanonji?
You're Don Kanonji, aren't you?!
No!
I am your ally, Karakurizer Spirit!
Liar! The only thing we have
in common is the letter "k"!
You talk too much,
Ichigo wannabe!
What?! Ichigo wannabe?
Wait, aren't you?!
Karakurizer Beast!
You're Arisawa from Ichigo's class.
No.
We're comrades who share
a common goal.
I am Karakurizer Erotic!
I will suck off the peace
from Karakura Town!
Hey, watch what you say, you!
W-W-Why me, too?
Umm…
If you don't strike a pose,
you'll be shocked to death.
Okay, all right.
Karakurizer Delicate.
Huh?
And lastly,
I am Karakurizer Tiny Devil.
Pleased to meet you.
What's up with these guys?
They're your team.
Please work together with them
and do battle.
Team?
That's right…
down Shinjuku Boulevard.
You and we are a team!
Let's go, everyone!
Let's go!
Aye aye, sir!
You should hurry up
and get going, too.
What? We're really going to fight?
Rizer Cannonball! Fire!
Rizer Deadly Magnum!
Doing good!
Hang in there, everybody!
Help!
A-Awesome.
But why did Urahara seriously
put together a group like this?
Mission complete.
They weren't tough at all!
Aw… Is it over already?
Will somebody tell me
what's going on?
Karakurizer,
Huh?
We are the chosen team.
The brave who will protect
Karakura Town.
From here on, let's work
hand-in-hand and fight together.
Y-Yeah.
Afro?!
He's the Soul Reaper in
charge of this town!
Afro!
Afro! What happened to you?
You're hurt.
They're…
They're coming.
They?
What's that?
There's no need for Aizen
himself to go to battle.
What the heck is going on?
A huge Hollow fortress
suddenly appears!
Karakura Town is threatened
with destruction.
How will Karakurizer face them with
a cape that won't let him fly?
It's your fault!
Next time on Konso Cop Karakurizer:
"Cape at Work"
Stay tuned!
No, they won't!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today's topic is about Garganta.
Garganta is the way we
enter into Hueco Mundo
and Urahara Kisuke is the only Shinigami
who's managed to figure out how it works.
That is a rather insulting statement.
Huh? Why's the 12th Squad's Captain here?
I've been using this segment to aid
in my research on Arrancar.
Since this is called an encyclopedia,
why don't you show a diagram
of an Arrancar's innards?
I'd be more than happy
to help you dissect them!
You're so excited, I can't keep up!