Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
This guy…
Ordinary means won't
work against him…
Not bad.
I'm not here to play with you.
If you have true power,
hurry up and show it to me.
Sounds like fun…
Damn…
What the hell are they
up to inside me?
Destruction of our Zanpakuto?
Yes, that's right.
Even if our Zanpakuto breaks,
it returns to normal along
with our recovery.
Now, however, our Zanpakuto
have abandoned our bodies
and operate as separate entities.
We may be jumping to
conclusions if we believe that
these Zanpakuto are
no different from before.
So you're saying that our killing
these Zanpakuto manifestations
is the same as killing
our Zanpakuto?
I suppose that is possible…
but I think that's
jumping to conclusions.
I agree.
However…
If we must ultimately
confront the Zanpakuto,
can we fight rationally?
Too easy, Renji.
Man, I thought he'd be
much better than that, Monkey.
Do not belittle him.
We can't have him
giving up so soon.
Look! He's up! He stood up!
Imbecile! Stop getting excited
over something like that!
Oww! You don't have to hit me,
you big ass!
Shut it! You perverted brat!
Let go!
That's enough, you two!
Don't quibble like that.
Wasn't I your opponent?
You don't understand anything,
do you?
What?
Didn't I tell you?
We don't have time
for weaklings like you.
Yup, you did!
The big-assed broad said it!
I said to stop it!
You keep calling me names
like weakling and whatever.
But what does that
have to do with this?
A lot.
It is our true instinct.
And just what the hell is that?
We don't want to be weak.
We do not wish to be weak.
In other words,
we want to be strong.
We're fed up with your weakness
and wish to leave you.
That is all.
You sure put it bluntly!
Roar! Zabimaru!
How do you intend to fight?
Renji?
So running away is
all that's left for you!
Damn! He anticipates nearly
every move I make.
Is it wise to rest leisurely
in a spot like that?!
You disappear from
my range of vision
to attack with
projectile weapons…
You're as rotten as you look!
Rotten? What of it?
Does it have anything to do
with life and death?
It's not compatible
with my way of fighting.
Like I care.
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to take lives.
I have no interest in
how my master fights.
I always thought that
the relationship between
a Zanpakuto and a Soul Reaper
was one of communication and synergy.
I don't know about
other Zanpakuto!
I'm me. I cut down lives!
I thought that was our sole
agreement between you and me.
I see. Then it's easy.
If you die and my Zanpakuto
disappears, so be it.
I don't like you.
I just realized that.
Fine with me.
Because the feeling is mutual.
This speed…
This power…
This feels so good.
It feels as though
it's been a while
since I unleashed my power
without holding back.
And his raw nature…
He's…on the offensive.
Come on out, Zanpakuto!
I know there's more to you.
I'm surprised…that I'm being
pressured to this extent.
You must be a Hollow.
When Ichigo Kurosaki released
himself from Zangetsu,
you could run free inside him.
Isn't that the reason for
Ichigo Kurosaki's strange
transformation at that time?
Am I wrong?
And if I say you're right?
I have nothing to say.
Just that if that was the trick,
it wasn't worth my effort.
The relationship between
a Zanpakuto and a Soul Reaper
is communication and synergy.
However, I know now that
there are exceptions like you
who are kept reined in.
It's very interesting.
Hey, I let you talk and
you put me down like that?
He's been keeping me reined in?
Am I wrong?
Dead wrong!
Then what?
It's none of your business!
Besides, why are you so
interested in Ichigo…in us?
What's your aim?
You will know in time.
Yeah?
I don't know what you're up to,
but I won't let you have your way!
I'll devour Ichigo and then
take control of this body!
That's my true instinct!
I see. So you intend
to stand in my way.
Then I have no choice.
I will extinguish you.
Nice try!
Roar!
Hey coward.
Weakling, coward…
You sure like to call people names!
Because you are a coward.
There's no other
description for you.
Sheesh… I quit.
Hey!
Get more serious!
But!
Even after all we've done to him,
he won't get serious!
It's not fun at all!
We know everything about you.
Like the time you gave up
something very dear to you.
And that you tried
desperately to get it back.
And…that still, you don't
have confidence in yourself.
If we beat that precious girl to
a bloody pulp
and hold up her head,
will you get serious?
Why you!
We know.
The reason why you cannot kill us.
It's called weakness.
I think you went and did it.
It doesn't matter.
He wasn't the man
we were seeking.
That's all.
Hold it. Where do you think
you're going?
You intend to continue?
If you're leaving,
do so after you beat me.
Forget it.
You have no will to fight.
Or did you think we didn't know?
You fight us. You defeat us.
That means…you would be
destroying your own power, right?
You cannot attack us
because you fear that.
Unfortunately, I don't know either.
We have left our master already.
It would not be strange if,
like Soul Reapers,
death awaits us too.
Renji…
You cannot destroy your Zanpakuto
with your own hands.
In other words, you cannot
come to terms with erasing us.
Am I right?
So how can you reproach me
for calling you weak?!
The ability to fight is not
the only criteria for strength!
What's the matter?
Is that all you have?
Don't think you can get me
with your low level of speed.
Rest assured. I don't.
I don't know what you have
up your sleeve, but…
What is this?!
M-My body…
What's the matter?
Is that all you have?
Damn it! Shut up…
It's just like what
happened to me…
What is that?
Is that his?
You are just a Hollow.
Not a power that I seek.
So you can disappear.
The pain…
What am I gonna do?
Am I weak?
Am I hopeless, after all?
– Just what have I been doing?
– Say something!
I've been forsaken
by my own Zanpakuto…
What have I been
doing all this time?
It hurts…
This pain… It hurts.
But it's not my body that's
being hit that hurts…
It's my life force.
Monkey… What should we do?
Fine… Finish him.
Am I still just…me?
I said I was going to
become strong.
But did I just fight blindly
and rush forward senselessly?
Ichigo…said he fights
in order to protect.
Is that his strength?
What do I have?
And why do I fight?
Damn you…
I can't let you have
your way any further.
He escaped my spell
in such a short time…
Just who is this man?
You're protecting me?
What's the meaning of this?
It means nothing.
I'm just being me.
And you're a part of me.
That's all.
There you go spouting out
nice words again.
Now that Old Man Zangetsu is gone,
I don't know what
you plan to do to me.
And I don't know what
I want to do with myself.
But there's one thing to do.
You know that, don't you?
You're so irritating.
Such a strange scene.
You, protecting a Hollow's power.
Sure, he may have
been a Hollow once.
But he's a part of me now.
What I do with him is my business
and I'm fine with it.
But I don't intend to let
a perfect stranger have his way!
Ichigo Kurosaki, just what are you?
Your speech and conduct
surely are not those of
a Soul Reaper towards a Hollow.
Your name is Muramasa, right?
Well, you're wrong
about one thing.
I've said it many times,
but I'm not a Soul Reaper.
I'm human!
You intend to thrust me out
with your own will?!
Ichigo Kurosaki… You are
an interesting fellow indeed.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You may be right that I'm weak.
I had forgotten.
But I don't have time to
ramble on about such rubbish.
Rubbish?
I want to become strong.
That's all.
I will take myself back.
The only way to do that is to
get Old Man Zangetsu back.
Even if it means destroying him…
There's someone
I must win against.
So I have to become strong,
whatever the cost!
You two made me remember that.
That is how I truly feel.
In order to do that,
whatever happens…
– I cannot lose!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Here I come!
What do you want?!
You said to "Roar, Zabimaru."
Right, Snake?
Yeah, so I roared.
Shall I roar again?
No!
Shut up!
Quincy Encyclopedia.
My kids are cute too.
See? See? See?
Don't get jealous
just because he's at that
rebellious adolescent stage!
Although,
my girls aren't rebellious.
It's all your son's fault.
I don't pay attention to my son.
Silence!
Parents are responsible
for their child's actions!