Success!
We did it, Karin!
My name is Franken Ichigo.
I was on the brink of death
after battling Hollows,
but I have been brought back
to life as an android.
I wandered aimlessly about,
and as I emerged from the dark forest,
there was a castle.
Where…is this place?
What the heck is this?
Not again.
Ichigo!
Oh, Rukiruki!
Huh?
One night, I had a dream.
I awoke in a desert to find I had
become an Arabian thief and…
Ah, forget it.
The point is that this whole
thing is a dream.
Are you daydreaming
or something?
What’re you talking about?
What difference does it make when
I’m already inside a dream?
Ouch!
Hey, that hurt!
You’re not dreaming!
It was time for our meeting,
but you never showed up,
so I came to get you!
Meeting?
You fool!
Ouch!
Have you forgotten about
that too, you moron?!
Ow ow ow!
Hey, cut that out!
Come on, we’re going
back to the castle!
Okay!
I get it, so stop that!
Rukiruki!
It’s not Rukiruki!
I’m Rukia!
Stop… Ow!
We’re back!
Rangiku, Toshiro, Ishida,
Inoue and…
Who are you?
Wait… Relax, relax.
This is a dream. A dream.
What’re you mumbling
to yourself about?
Hurry up and take your seat!
Oh. Right, right.
Ishida, what’s that
you’re drinking?
Can’t you tell? It’s milk.
Why aren’t you drinking blood?!
Aren’t you Dracula?!
What’re you talking about?
Blood is the same color as a Soul Reaper’s
Spirit Ribbon. I would never drink that.
But, why milk?
As both Dracula and a Quincy,
it is only natural that I take
pride in the color white!
Hey, what’s wrong, Ishida?!
The truth is, I’m a bit anemic
because I can’t drink blood.
Mind not getting me
so worked up?
Is this guy okay?
He’s fine. It happens
all the time, right?
Right.
Rangiku is a witch,
and Inoue is a…
Is that a pumpkin?
A pumpkin ghost?
Kurosaki, you’re all patched together!
So weird!
You’re the weird one, Inoue.
Sorry about that, Inoue.
He’s been acting strange
since I brought him here.
I’m fine!
By the way, what kind of monster are
you supposed to be dressed up as?
What? Can’t you tell?
I’m a succubus.
Huh? What’s a succubus?
Allow me to explain!
Succubi are generally known
as “dream demons.”
They are a kind of demon
that ruin men,
appearing as lovely women with
bat wings on their backs.
They attack men in their sleep, seduce them,
and suck them of their life energy.
Hey Rukia.
You’ve been jabbing at me with
that fork this whole time.
Don’t tell me you’re…
Fool!
Why would I seduce you?!
I display my skills as a seductress only
to those who are noble and beautiful.
For example…
Someone like my older brother.
Jeez… Enough with all of this!
Uh…
That voice… Is that you, Renji?
I couldn’t tell who you were
with that mummy outfit.
Wrong.
Huh?
I’m not a mummy. I’m a pirate.
What?
I was once a pirate who
sailed the seven seas.
Back then, I was afraid of nothing.
I believed the world
was my oyster.
But my arch enemy,
Team Seaweed, stood before me.
Get them!
Pine!
Go, seaweeds!
Seaweed, seaweed!
A fierce cannon fight ensued
between our two pirate ships.
And finally…
Shall I tell you the difference
between you and I?
It’s class.
The wounds from that day
made me end up like this.
Wait.
So you’re not a monster?
And Team Seaweed?
What the hell?
Hey, you guys!
Weren’t we here to
have a meeting?!
Meeting?
What are you talking about, Toshiro?
I’m not Toshiro! I’m Wolfman Hitsugaya!
We couldn’t start the meeting
because you didn’t come!
Oh, that’s all right, Captain.
We haven’t all introduced
ourselves yet,
and the meeting is only about
the hunters anyway, right?
Hunters?
All we have to do is get rid
of the hunters quickly.
Don’t get so stressed out.
Your fur will start falling
out again, Captain.
Matsumoto!
Don’t get angry!
Here, use this to ease
your stress!
Fetch!
Wow, Captain!
Good boy, good boy!
I’m not a dog!
Shake!
Good job!
I said I’m not a dog!
Here, one more time!
Fetch!
So what’s the deal with this
meeting and the “hunters”?
If you insist…
I guess I’ll have to explain.
So we’re back to you again?
We received information
that recently,
mysterious monster hunters have
been showing up in this area.
For reasons unknown,
the two of them are not killing monsters but
they are looking for a certain secret treasure.
Secret treasure?
That’s right. The secret treasure
they are searching for is
a legendary jewel that will force us monsters
to turn back into human beings, the Snow Crystal!
Wait just a minute…
I recognize that shape!
Yes.
They plan to use the Snow Crystal to cleanse
the world of every last monster.
That is their objective.
Question!
Where is that whatever-you-called-it crystal?
It is kept under lock and key here
in the top floor of this castle.
So by using that, we all turn
back into human beings?
That is correct.
That is why we absolutely must protect
the Snow Crystal from them.
Stop!
Where are you going, Kurosaki?
Where? To the top floor.
Hey, Kurosaki! Surely you’re
not planning to…
Damn right!
I’m using that jewel to return
to being a human being!
Then I should be able to
wake up from this dream!
What kind of nonsense is that?!
Come to your senses!
Blood…not enough blood.
Once you wake up from this dream,
your anemia will be gone too!
See you!
- Everyone! We have a situation!
- Ouch!
Look! The sky is…
That’s…
- Dad?
- Ryuken!
Ah!
Dad!
Ryuken!
Kurosaki, you first.
No, you go ahead first.
Fine, then...
Ahem.
Ryuken!
Calling your father
by his first name…
You haven’t changed at all.
Why do you have the powers
of a monster hunter?
You are such a fool.
Ryuken Ishida…
Whether I like it or not,
I am the only man who is
allowed to call himself
the last monster hunter.
Um… There’s also
me, you know.
Just shut up and get going!
Now then! Prepare
yourself, Uryu!
You leave me no choice
but to fight you.
Kuchiki, Inoue, Hinamori,
return to the castle and protect the crystal!
Right!
The rest of us will stop
the hunters here!
Huh?
Where’s Kurosaki?
Oh, crap!
Like I would waste my
time fighting hunters!
I’m going to get the Snow Crystal
and wake up from this dream!
Dad…
So you’ve come, Son.
I’m not letting you
go a step further!
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Didn’t you guys come to steal
the Snow Crystal from us?!
Never mind the details!
What is this?!
You’re not making any sense!
I’ll defeat you and
return to reality!
It’s useless to resist, Uryu.
I know you don’t have the energy
to shoot a volley of arrows.
D-Damn it!
If only I had drunk blood
like I should have.
And also, you probably think that
the maximum number of Spirit Arrows
I can shoot in a volley is 1200, but…
Actually,
it’s twelve hundred…and one!
What?!
Extend, Zabiobi!
Hey!
Let me help you out, Ishida!
Damn! All I want is to wake
up from this dream!
Why do I have to fight you, Dad?!
Sour grapes? You’re being
a poor sport, Ichigo!
As the saying goes,
“The lion, the King of Beasts,
shoves its cubs off the highest cliff
to test their worthiness.”
Now, Ichigo!
Crawl back up and prove that
you’ve surpassed me!
Like I said, stop talking nonsense!
That’s no reason to fight, is it?!
Found you, Kurosaki!
Bastard! How dare you betray us!
You deceived us and planned to
snatch the crystal, didn’t you?!
What?
No, wait, you don’t understand!
I mean, look! I’m fighting
a hunter right now!
Huh?
Oh, so you’re having
a family squabble?
Abarai! Ishida!
My, my… You guys are all
talk and no substance.
Damn! We can’t do
a thing against him!
If you absolutely refuse to tell me where the crystal is,
then you leave me no choice.
I’ll get rid of you first,
then take my time looking for it.
Hey, Ishida!
Isn’t there anything we can do?
Now!
Huh?
Huh? What?!
Wh-What is this?
Hikotsu Houtai!
Hey, what’s the big idea? Stop it!
Panpuru, Pinpuru, Hainekkon!
Ban…
kai!
Daiurufu Hyorinmaru!
I placed Sprenger inside the courtyard
for such a situation. Guess it paid off.
It’s over, monster hunters.
And as for you, Kurosaki…
Your noble sacrifice allowed
us to earn a victory.
Rest in peace.
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Are you all right, Kurosaki?!
Man, that was close.
If I didn’t have this mask,
I’d have been a goner along with the hunters.
Hey, Ishida! What was up
with that land mine?!
What’re you talking about?
I told everyone about
it earlier today.
It’s your fault for not
being there on time.
What? Is that so?
That’s right!
You’re so forgetful, Ichigo!
Oh, I see! Sorry!
Joke's over!
Wh-What?!
Now you’ve done it.
Brats!
You won’t get away with this!
Pumpkin. Pumpkin.
Pumpkin.
Will this do, Inoue?
Yes.
The barrier appears to have
become much stronger now.
What’re we going to do?
There’s nowhere else to run!
Damn! Guess we’ll have
to fight them again.
Fight? But we didn’t
stand a chance!
We have no choice.
It’s not worth everyone’s lives.
It’s regrettable, but we’ll have to
hand the crystal over to them.
Inoue!
Where is the crystal?
It’s right over there!
Okay!
Huh?
Hey, Ichigo!
It’s no use. I can’t hold
them back any longer!
This is as far as you go,
you pathetic monsters.
Where’d you hide the crystal?
It would seem there’s a
petty thief among you.
Which one of you is it?
It wasn’t me!
I wouldn’t do such a thing!
Kurosaki!
It wasn’t me, either!
Or me!
Looks like you have your answer.
Nobody knows!
Maybe such a thing never
existed to begin with!
What?!
These guys might be monsters,
but it doesn’t change the fact that
they’re my precious friends!
I will protect them!
Fool! Do you think
you can beat us?
I’m not going to fight you
just thinking I can win.
But I can’t have you hurt
my friends any further!
I have to win!
Jeez… Reckless as always,
aren’t you?
Ishida!
Don’t get the wrong idea.
I’m not helping you.
This is my fight too, you know.
That’s good enough reason
to join forces.
Let’s do it!
Wh-What is this?!
Beating scum like you isn’t going
to amount to much money.
That’s how it is.
Huh? What’s that supposed
to mean?
See you.
Hey you guys!
Hurray!
We won!
Hey!
Friends, he said. How impudent.
Aren’t you glad? You got to see how
much your precious son matured.
Whatever!
You just won’t admit it, will you?
Hey, wait up!
What the hell was that all about?
But where is the Snow Crystal?
That’s right! Without
that, I can’t go back!
Go back to what?
I’m out!
Hey!
Rukia?! You hid it?!
What’re you talking about?
A succubus is a demon
that shows you dreams.
In other words,
I am the Snow Crystal!
I don’t get it.
And besides,
this isn’t your dream.
Then whose is it?
Ouch! What was that for?!
Kurosaki?!
What’s this?
Fur?!
Farewell, Ichigo.
Beast!
A dream?
That was scary.
Oh, wait! It was my face!
What a good episode to celebrate
the series’ 10-year anniversary.
We got to see our son’s mature.
No it wasn’t. Look at this outfit.
I wore it thinking it was my son’s design,
but he hasn’t improved at all!
Oh, I designed that.
I’m going to go change.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
We’re not done yet?
It’s to celebrate the
10-year anniversary.
We have to go all the way.
Whoa!
Why the surprise?
You’re a monster, right?
Ishida, you bastard!
Wait, that’s…
Nothing happened.
Actually, it looks like
we’re falling yet again.
Ah! There’s more of this?!