The Final Getsugatensho is...
me...
becoming Getsuga itself.
Mugetsu.
Repair work complete!
Check!
Number 1097, okay!
Numbers 1098, 1099 and 1100, okay!
We've secured every member
of the World of the Living
within the boundaries of the Tenkaiketchu.
Activating Tenkaiketchu!
J-Just a minute, Captain!
There are still squad members
left inside the town premises.
Transporting them to the World of the Living
without the use of a Senkaimon is dangerous!
I guess I have no choice.
I'll count to ten slowly.
Honestly, my indulgence makes me sick!
Hurry it up, or else you'll get killed!
Ten...
W-Wait for us!
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Captain!
We need to confirm the safety
of the World of Living side as well!
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Don't do it, sir!
What're you people doing?!
Captain...
Please be patient just a little longer.
I don't give a damn
about the slowpokes over there!
Enough! I'm activating it now!
Captain!
That should do it for the time being.
For the time being?
You mean she might not make it?
Kido's limitations are no
different than medical treatment.
We've completely healed the body.
From here on, as long as she doesn't
give up her will to live,
she'll eventually regain consciousness.
Whether she will give up or not
is something you'd know better than me.
Thank you, Unohana.
Why are you thanking me?
A thank you isn't necessary
for saving a friend.
We're not friends, you idiot.
Well, that's what Hiyori
would probably say.
Thank you, Unohana.
Everyone!
Y-You must get away from here quickly!
Captain Kurotsuchi is going to
activate the Tenkaiketchu any minute now!
It's dangerous here!
Let go of me!
If you don't let go right now,
I'll use you as guinea pigs and
put you through the worst kind of horrors!
Are you trying to make a fool of me?!
Hurry up and hand over the
real activation switch!
Please wait a little longer.
Just a little longer!
Captain Zaraki!
Captain Kuchiki!
Welcome back!
I'm here too!
Welcome back, Lieutenant Kusajishi.
A job well done, sir!
Med crew, stat!
They're walking normally,
but they're badly injured!
Welcome back, sir!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry for coming back!
Lieutenant Kotetsu!
Seventh Seat Yamada!
A job well done, sir!
Huh?
You may have been in a support role,
but you stormed into Hueco Mundo.
I was impressed!
A job well done, sir!
Actually, I got knocked out as soon as
I got there and didn't do much.
Captain!
How did the battle go?
Captain?
Yeah...
Why're you following me?
Dumb dog.
It was a lousy battle.
Kurosaki.
Mr. Urahara... Where is everyone?
I sent them all home.
They all seemed to want
to talk to you, Kurosaki,
but they seemed just as
hesitant to approach you.
You didn't erase their memories, did you?
No.
Not this time.
I see. That's good.
I was tired of hiding things from them.
When I get back, I'll
personally explain it to them.
Aizen's Cross Seal was
taken to the Seireitei.
Central 46 will soon make a decision
on how to handle him.
I see.
Why the solemn look?
I don't know.
I don't really know myself.
You saved everyone's life
and this world because
you risked your life to
battle Aizen and defeat him.
I know that.
You did the right thing.
There's no reason at
all to look so solemn.
Kurosaki.
Say, Mr. Urahara...
Was Aizen...
Was Aizen really...
...rejected by the Hogyoku?
My old man told me that
the Hogyoku's power
is to take in the heart surrounding itself,
and manifesting it's desires.
If that's the case, could it be that
Aizen lost his powers of his own will?
After I attained enough power to battle
Aizen on even terms,
I was finally able to feel his sword.
There was nothing but
loneliness in his sword.
If his powers were superior
from the time he was born,
perhaps he was searching all this time
for someone he could regard as his equal.
Then, ever since the moment
he gave up thinking he'd
ever find such a rival,
he's been wishing
somewhere in his heart that he could
become a mere Soul Reaper.
K-Kurosaki?
Inoue...Ishida...Rukia...Chad...Renji...
What's up with you guys?
Is it okay for you to be up already?!
Don't put me in the same league as you.
Yeah...
It's not an issue.
What about you? What is that?
It...
It is you, after all.
Your hair is long,
so I thought maybe it wasn't you.
I'm glad...I'm so glad.
What's with that look, Inoue?
Well I guess my hair is a mess...
-Ichigo! -Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
Ichigo?!
Hey, Ichigo?!
K-Kurosaki?
We will now pass judgment!
Former Squad 5 Captain, Sosuke Aizen.
We sentence you to the
lowest level of the
Underground Prison 8: Muken,
where you will remain for 18,800 years!
I see.
The likes of you, passing judgment on me?
It strikes me as a bit comical.
Traitor!
Pushing your luck just
because you're immortal!
Restrain his eye and mouth
as well immediately!
Increase his sentence to 20,000 years!
Yes, yes!
Idiots!
You lost your Captain's Coat?!
Tearing it is one thing, but losing it?!
How can you look so nonchalant about it?!
Head Captain.
Do not worry.
It was just a cheap coat,
so I will pay for it.
That's not what I'm concerned about!
And it wasn't cheap, you idiot!
Listen!
Battles aren't just about winning!
What do you people think
the Captain's Coat is anyway?!
A nuisance.
Cheap.
Fashion?
You're all idiots!
The Head Captain seems
to be in good spirits.
Yeah.
Listen carefully now!
It's been ten days since the battle.
A Captain's Coat is a symbol of
He lost his left arm,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
but his strength seems to
be back, so I'm relieved.
And of all the things, you lose it!
There's still no Soul
Reaper in the Soul Society
who can take his place.
Captain!
Captain Kurotsuchi, where are you?!
If you're looking for the
captain, he's not here.
He went to Hueco Mundo to
do research or something.
What?! Again?!
What'll I do?
Lieutenant Hinamori's been left in
our care to heal her internal organs, right?
Lieutenant Matsumoto is here
to pay her a visit, and...
Lieutenant Hinamori is not
allowed any visitors.
Besides, we cannot allow outsiders into
the research facility when
Captain Kurotsuchi isn't here.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Matsumoto.
I don't see her.
Huh?!
This isn't good enough.
At this rate...
At this rate, I'll...
never become able to protect Hinamori!
I have to...
become more adept at using...
Hyorinmaru's Bankai.
You've gone away, but you didn't leave
behind even a keepsake to remember you by.
That's what I didn't like about you.
They're moving on.
Neither Shuhei nor Renji
were at the barracks.
They must be somewhere
brushing up on their skills and strength.
I need to as well.
You're right.
If you had left behind a keepsake,
it would have probably kept
me from moving forward.
You must have certainly
seen that weakness in me.
Thank you, Gin.
That's what I...
...loved about you.
Kurosaki!
Where am I?
My home.
Huh?
You guys! What happened to your injuries?!
We healed up a long time ago.
A long time ago?
Ten days have already passed, you know.
Ten days?
My powers...
Don't worry.
They haven't disappeared yet.
You know?
Yes, I heard from Urahara.
I see.
Kurosaki.
Ten days ago, you collapsed
the moment we were reunited.
-Ichigo! -Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
Kurosaki! Kurosaki!
Ichigo! Hey, pull yourself together!
Mr. Urahara... What happened to Kurosaki?
Tell us, Urahara.
What happened?
According to Urahara,
there are several stages in the
course of losing your Spiritual Pressure.
Stages?
Yes.
First, you lose consciousness and the time
that your body spent inside the
Precipice World flows in reverse.
See how your hair is shorter?
Your height has returned
to what it used to be,
and your Spiritual Pressure is stable now.
And of course, you still retain
your Soul Reaper powers.
Eventually, however,
it will move to the next stage.
When that happens, he
will black out once more,
accompanied by intense pain.
When he regains consciousness the next time,
he will lose all Soul Reaper powers.
It could occur tomorrow, the day after that,
or maybe even a year later.
Even I don't know how
long his current state of
unstable Spiritual Pressure will continue.
Well, when that time comes, it comes.
Kurosaki.
Don't worry, Inoue.
More importantly, I'm
glad all of you are okay.
But...
What're you talking about?!
All okay, you say?!
You know you're going to
lose your Spirit Energy!
Ishida...
I did what I did knowing
all of the consequences.
I have no regrets.
I see.
Anyway, now that we're all healed up,
there's no need for us to stay here, right?
Let's hurry and get back to Karakura Town.
Everyone's waiting for us.
Head Captain...
What is it?
As apology, I prepared you a new coat.
You still don't get it, do you?!
I had it crafted by the finest craftsman
using the finest material.
V-Very well, I shall keep it then.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
All right guys, let's go home.
Sorry Kurosaki.
I promised Kuchiki and Rangiku
that we'd go eat sweets together.
Could you wait for a moment?
O-Oh, sure thing.
I also made a promise to Hisagi
to teach him how to play the guitar.
O-Okay.
H-Hey, Ishi-
Members from Squad 4 have asked
me to make some clothes for them.
Be seeing you!
Hey!
Take care of your business
beforehand, will you?