Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Ishida!
Ishida, that bastard.
He's just acting tough!
I hope he's not thinking that
he doesn't want to be a burden!
Throwing away his own friends…
That's harsh.
I won't let him do that!
That's right! It's not even trash day!
Y-You're mad? That's unusual…
Of course! I'm going to find him
and treat his wounds!
Earlier…
If I had used the last of
my strength, maybe…
Just maybe…
I could have thrown her off my trail.
But I didn't do that.
Why?
Why did I save you?
Is that what you want to know?
It's because you had lonely eyes…
Is that a good enough answer?
You're being targeted by the Bounts.
You'd be putting your friends
in danger if you stayed with them.
That's why you ran away.
What a sad story…
No one's happy.
So you felt sorry for me?
You don't seem like the type
who would be sentimental like that.
I was once like that…
There was a time when
I saw sweet sentimental dreams.
Those feeling have just become cold…
because of the mind-numbing
passage of time.
That's some noise…
I can feel it echoing
through my body.
That's because you're not used to it.
I'm used to hearing it,
so I no longer feel anything.
The sound of the bells
or the passing of time…
Is that how you've watched
this town all this time?
Uninvolved with anyone and all alone…
Strangely…
There's a lack of reality when…
I watch those people restlessly
living from here.
I don't feel loneliness.
You're one of the Bounts.
Don't you even live with them?
There was a time when I did.
That was a long time ago…
A long time…
For a time so long that it numbs the mind,
we've lived in the shadow of history.
During that time…
countless numbers of us
have endured harsh experiences
and borne indescribable treatment.
With that behind us,
the time when we Bounts can
be released from the darkness…
is finally approaching.
This long time…
may be what plants fleeting dreams
and foolish ambition in us Bounts.
Everything…because of time…
How strange…
You hate time so much…
And yet, you live next to this clock.
Could it be that you're still
expecting something?
You want to live rather
than observe the passage of time.
Is that what you're thinking?
If it's possible…
I suppose I'd like to die.
Die?
When you have eternal life,
you feel like you can do anything.
You begin to think that
you've become a god.
Isn't that foolish?
Now then…
Kariya could you tell us?
Why have you gathered us here?
A Quincy has been found.
Oh… That's interesting.
I want you to help me!
We chosen Bounts
must catch this Quincy!
To gain greater absolute power…
and for our shining era!
What?!
Maki Ichinose's Spiritual Pressure?
Yes. It has been undeniably
confirmed to be in the World of the Living.
Right, Aramaki?
Huh? Yes…
We've never been able to find him,
no matter how hard we looked.
We were suddenly able to
track his Spiritual Pressure.
I overheard Captain Hitsugaya and
Captain Ukitake talking about it earlier.
Then, then, Maki-maki…
Is Maki in
the World of the Living right now?
It seems so.
Is that so, Maki-maki?!
Maki is alive, Maki-maki!
E-Excuse me,
but that's confusing,
so could you not repeat my name?
What? Why?
You're Maki-maki and Maki is Maki!
They're completely different!
I'm saying that it's confusing!
Isn’t the nickname Maki-maki…
kind of weird?
Yes… I mean, don't ask me that!
What is he doing?
Who knows…
What should we do?
Leave him alone!
But I feel a bit responsible…
Ken-chan, don't you feel it too?
I don't care.
Wait!
Zaraki… You…
How dare you do this to the Captain!
I won't accept this!
Huh?
What's with you?
Please stop, Ichinose!
Let me go!
Under the attendance
of 200 squad members,
the winner of this match and
the new captain of Squad Eleventh is…
Kenpachi Zaraki!
You aren't allowed to draw
your sword here!
How boring…
Listen up, all of you!
I'm going to do things my way!
I won't chase those who leave!
Do as you like!
Eleven
Maki?!
Are you really going to leave?
I'm very sorry.
You’re still holding
a grudge against Ken-chan…?
No… That was an official
one-on-one match.
Captain Zaraki did nothing wrong.
Then why?
I really can’t find
a reason to remain here.
Also…
My captain will always…
be our former captain.
Do as you like.
Thank goodness he's still alive.
Back then, he looked
as if he would just die.
He's probably being forced to live…
But I don't know who’d do that…
Mr. Ichinose, what do you suppose
Kariya's real objective is?
What does he plan to do when
he catches the Quincy?
Who knows? I do not question.
I simply obey Master Kariya.
Because it's easier that way…
If you always completely
agree or disagree…
there's no reason to think.
What are you thinking?
Who knows…
I'm still thinking.
Ishida!
Hmm?
Oh…
Sorry…
Damn…
Where in the world did you go?!
Ishida!
It sure is miserable here.
You should put…
I try not to own things.
It's easier that way.
It's too much of a burden
to own things.
That may be true.
There are times when the things
you should be thankful for…
feel like a burden.
Another day is about to end…
When I look down at humans
from here, I think…
we live for hundreds of years.
Humans are so short-sighted
compared to us.
But that short-sightedness…
It's because people only
have a few decades
in which they can try hard…
That's why they're happy.
Long ago…
when I was still a child…
I came to have this odd feeling that
I was not like normal people…
Since then, I've kept that fact a secret.
I was desperate to keep that…
a secret even from
my friends…
But then I realized…
that it was impossible for them
not to notice.
Everyone around me
was aging like they should.
People…and history…
It seemed like only
I was left behind…
Never changing.
Unable to change…
I was at such a loss…
Time had passed.
I was forever left behind
by the times…
Find her! Find her!
She's a witch!
She's got to be a witch!
Kill her! Kill her!
I had tired of living…
Day by day I thought only
of ways to die…
And when I decided to
end my own life…
He appeared.
There's no need to be afraid…
I'm like you.
Kariya, huh?
He told me to live with him.
He said there were reasons
for Bounts like us to live.
I'll tell you my reason for living.
It's you.
Remember this…
A Bount's love is deep, long…
limitless, and continues eternally.
God has given Bounts
our time of bliss…
Eternal love…
There was a time when
I truly believed that.
But not now.
I've realized that
the word “eternal”
exists for humans who
have limited life spans…
It's something that has
no meaning to us Bounts.
In other words…
does that mean that
your love for him…Kariya…
came to an end?
There may not have been
any love to begin with…
The light of hope
I saw was an illusion.
An illusion?
He tricked my eyes with
a bright veil of light…
only to hide his ambition
in its shadow.
Ambition?
The Power Hold…
Kariya has gathered
the few Bounts that are left…
and is probably trying
to go to Hueco Mundo…
He's trying to gain
limitless power there.
In order to make the Bounts…
no, himself an ultimate god!
That's crazy!
If he does that,
he'll deviate from the principal rules
which we must uphold!
God has no rules to follow…
Rules are for God to decide.
Even so!
That's why I've brought you here.
To keep Kariya from doing that!
Umm… Do you…
still love him?
Stop!
I can't forgive him…
In order for me to remain human,
however little that may be…
I can't forgive him for losing
his human heart.
What do you mean?
He took a living person's soul…
with the same mouth with
which he told me he loved me…
I couldn't forgive Kariya for that…
but I couldn't forgive myself even more
for being unable to stop him…
How ironic.
He gave me the hope to live,
but by his betrayal, I awakened to…
the little that remained of my heart
as a human which slept within me…
What do you plan to do now?
I'm going to defeat Kariya.
How?!
I'd help you if I could but,
I no longer can…
You sure are kind
to want to help me…
But I don’t intend to rely
on you any longer.
I'll deal with him myself.
You should just stay in this room
until your wounds heal.
Do you have any hope of winning?
Of course.
If it's possible, I'd like to die…
That's a lie!
A lie?
Why do you think that?
W-Well…
Please.
Try not to be captured
by Kariya's men.
I don't know why,
but you're a key person
in Kariya's goal.
But I no longer have any powers…
You can't be sure of that.
Am I wrong?
I have the feeling that
the Quincy power still lies within you.
Live…
Wait!
Umm…
There's one thing
I realized earlier…
I could have run away from you
if I had wanted to…
But I didn't…
Now I finally know why.
Why?
Your eyes.
I may have seen a small ray of hope
from your lonesome eyes…
You haven't fallen completely
into despair.
You have a beautiful light
that seeks hope…
Well… If it's possible,
I'd like to help you…
I don't know what I can do
in this condition, but…
Even so…
Even so, I'll go with you!
You sure are good-natured
despite your looks.
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
There's a Soul Reaper
among the enemy.
He's probably a good-for-nothing…
Probably a dangerous battle maniac
or a crazy-eyed modification maniac.
Oh? Who might that be?
I'd like to hear more.
I'm sorry!
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Health Land
Why do we have to go to Health Land
to do our remaining business?
Why not?! Let's meet in the rest space
and work after a bath!
We'll be more productive!
Hey!
I'm very sorry. Children must stay
with their guardians.
Child… Child…
Oh! Then let's go
in the women's bath together!
Matsumoto!
Tune in again!