Ichigo and his friends have set out for
Aizen's headquarters, Las Noches.
But they are dragged into
the Forest of Menos
by Runuganga,
the Guardian of the White Sand.
In the forest, Rukia is separated
from Ichigo and his friends.
She is saved by Ashido,
a mysterious Soul Reaper.
Long ago, Ashido followed Hollows
into the Forest of Menos.
He fought Hollows by himself
for many years.
Save your...friend!
Ashido!
Ichigo and his friends are able to make it
back to the surface with Ashido's help,
and they finally make it
to Las Noches.
Your friends have
entered Hueco Mundo.
Why?
“Why,” you ask?
They've come to save you.
Aside from that...
They have no other reasons.
They came to save me?
That's right.
But that no longer
has any meaning for you.
By wearing that, it means you are
one of us in body and soul.
That’s the reality, Orihime Inoue.
Yes.
Tell me. Who does
your body and soul belong to?
Yes.
Lord Aizen and his desires.
Did we break through it?
It looks like it…
Wind is passing through.
Wh-What are you doing?!
The entrance is just
a three-day walk in that direction!
Idiot… This isn't a friend's house.
We can't go in through the front.
We don't have the time
to walk for three days either.
Nel.
Thank you for bringing us this far.
But if you involve yourselves
with us any more,
you'll wind up being
treated as traitors.
So this is farewell.
Later!
W-Wait, Ichigo!
Ichigo!
We were traitors from the moment
that Lord Runuganga saw us together!
No… It may have
been far before then.
Lord Aizen may have already known!
Lord Aizen will never forgive us for that!
Even if Lord Aizen forgives us,
the Espada won't!
Nel is not saying that Nel
wants you to take us with you!
Nel is just telling you this
so you don't get worried about us!
What is she saying?
I think she wants him
to be worried about her.
Nel is not saying that Nel
wants you to take us with you!
Nel’s not saying that!
– Nel’s not saying that!
– Aww… Jeez. All right…
What?
Her voice is getting fainter.
It seems that
she fell underground.
Fell? What do you mean?!
Oh! Wait, Ichigo!
Nel!
Ow ow…
That hurts!
That’s my line!
What are you fools doing?!
Oh yeah! Where's Nel?
We just came here after Nel.
Yeah.
Huh? Then where is she?
Ichigo! Look!
What is this?
The floor fell through?
No… It's probably some airshaft
or something that was in the walls.
It looks like she fell through here.
She sure is a lot of trouble.
Hueco Mundo sure
has a lot of holes.
Nel!
Are you all right?!
What should we do?
Well, we can't leave her alone.
Jeez. What troublesome guys!
Good grief…
Let's go!
Ichigo, you idiot! Baldy!
Piece of crap! Good-for-nothing!
Who's a good-for-nothing?!
Wh-Why did you come?!
Nel doesn't really want you
to take me with you.
Aw… I'm getting kind of annoyed…
I'll really leave you!
You pretended to come and save Nel,
but you just came to pick on Nel!
All right! I get it. Don't cry!
I'll take you with me,
so give me a break!
Good?
Ichi...go!
Ichigo!
You ended up crying again?
What are they doing?
They're doing a stand-up routine.
What's that?
I hear it coming from above us!
Yeah.
Everyone, jump!
Here… Blow your nose
and wipe away your tears.
Kurosaki, run!
Hey, guys…
Ah! Nel, you're safe!
Yeah.
Let me play too!
Get off me!
You did it to me yet again.
Whoa.
That was close.
Ichigo, are you all right?!
You guys…
Anyway, let's get out of here.
Yeah…
Let's see if there are other stairs.
Hey, you guys! Hey!
It sure is dark here.
For times like this,
just leave it to me!
What is it? Can you do
something about it?
When tweaked a bit,
kido can be used like this!
Shakkaho!
Oh? That's a pretty small light.
I didn't think that
you were so reserved.
Fool! This happened because
he tried to look cool
by using an Eishohaki
even though he's not good at it.
Well, don't worry about it.
We can follow the brightness
of your red hair!
There's even a song about it.
A reindeer with a bright red nose
becomes useful to Santa…
Shut up!
What's with this place?
Say… Did this place exist
before Aizen came?
Hmm…
Lord Aizen built the building above,
but I don't know about the basement.
This area was probably
the old building.
It's probably not used now.
Well… I don't care either way.
Let's go upstairs
as soon as possible!
Something just shined!
Huh? I didn't see anything.
– I'm going to go check!
– All right!
Oh! Hey, wait!
What's this?
What is it?
This has got to be the exit!
Indeed… The materials
used to make it are different.
Everything from this point on
must be the newly constructed building.
In other words, it's not
abandoned like this area is.
It's being used now.
We should be cautious
from this point on.
– We don't know what--
– Ishida!
Move aside for a moment!
Ah! There are stairs!
Another door.
Kurosaki, you should
be a little more--
We just have to smash through
and move on!
We finally came to
a decent-looking place!
A crossroad, huh?
What a troublesome
place to come to.
Nel…
Sorry…
It looks like we'll have to
part ways here after all.
Huh?
It doesn't seem like you guys
will be able to withstand
the Spiritual Pressure
from this point on!
I can't even imagine what
might happen from here on.
There are five paths.
We've got to check each one,
starting from the ones on the ends!
No…
Let's go down separate paths
at the same time.
What are you saying?!
We're talking about Espada!
It would be better
if we move together!
If we become separated…
Stop.
It's insulting for a warrior to be concerned
about his life while in the battlefield.
Ichigo… You say that because
you are worried about me,
but it is not like you
to say something like that.
I told you that you
don't need to worry about me.
I didn't come here so
you would be worried about me!
All right…
Let's go down separate paths.
All right!
Then, before we leave,
let's chant a charm!
A charm?
Yeah… It's a traditional Thirteen
Court Guard Squads ritual of sorts
that’s done before big battles.
It's fallen out of use. There aren't
many squads that do it now.
But I figure it's something
to do at times like this.
Come on!
Place your hands together!
Don't look so unenthusiastic!
I don't really want to do it either!
We're going into battle now!
Believe...that our blades
cannot be broken!
Believe...that our hearts
will not yield!
Even if we lose our way,
our iron will is one!
Vow...that even if the earth splits,
we will come back to this place alive!
They left…
What should we do?
Hmm…
If we turn back now,
it'll still be dangerous.
Oh!
Where are you going, Nel?
Ichigo… Nel is going after Ichigo!
Going after him?
Nel had…
Nel had fun!
Nel had lots and lots of fun!
Nel still…
Nel still want to stay with
Ichigo and the others!
– Nel!
– What?
All right! We're…
We’re going too!
Which way did Nel go?
Lord Aizen and his desires.
She only hesitated
for an instant.
She didn't flinch at my question.
She's a tough woman.
Hey…
How is our pet doing?
Nnoitora…
I know that Lord Aizen has left you
in charge of that woman.
How wonderful…
So? How far have
you disciplined her?
How vulgar.
Don't get too crabby…
I'm just asking you
if things are going well.
Come on.
You're curious?
That's such a trifling matter.
Huh?
Don't worry…
That woman was under
Lord Aizen’s spell
before she came
to Hueco Mundo.
His Kyokasuigetsu, huh?
Of course not. There's no need for him
to use it for something like this.
He placed her in several psychological
cages when he brought her here.
He ordered her to surrender
and made her unable to refuse
by using her friends' lives.
Afterwards, he gave her
a 12-hour reprieve
and allowed her to say good-bye
to one of her friends
on the condition that
no one else could notice her.
You call that a cage?
By giving her a reprieve,
and allowing her to say good-bye
to a friend in such a tense situation,
she'll mistakenly believe that
we've shown her sympathy
and her feelings will
waver a little.
But her friends' lives were not actually
at risk during that 12-hour reprieve.
Furthermore, even though
she was forced to surrender…
By allowing her to choose
someone to say good-bye to,
she'd get the idea that
she had done so by choice.
Afterwards, by making her
come to a specified place
before taking her
to Hueco Mundo
that idea would be etched
even deeper into her mind.
She'd gradually lose
the will to run away.
Furthermore…
The fact that we allowed her to
say good-bye to only one person
without anyone else noticing
means that she'd leave evidence of
having said good-bye to only one person.
What of it?
We've failed if
you let her do that.
Quite the opposite…
The evidence of having said good-bye
becomes undeniable proof
that she was free to do
what she wanted until she surrendered.
In other words…
The stronger the evidence,
the more her friends would think
that she willfully betrayed them.
That last part wasn't
a complete success.
But it's safe to say that Soul Society
isn't getting involved.
That sure was well thought out.
I guess that's to be
expected of Lord Aizen.
Well thought out?
This is a game to Lord Aizen.
It would have been fine whether
she played into it or not.
Whatever the case…
Right now, that woman has
no strength to run away from here.
She doesn't have the will
or strength to defy us either.
I'm glad you've come…
Orihime.
I'm sorry I called you here
on such short notice.
There's something
I want to show you.
Loly, Menoly, leave us.
Huh?
B-But we cannot leave someone
like her alone with you.
– E-Excuse us!
What's with that woman?!
Now then…
Could you take a look at this,
Orihime?
What is this sensation?
Could this be...?
It seems you can tell…
This is the Hogyoku.
It's a little weak from repetitive
instantaneous awakenings,
but it's definitely becoming
fully awake.
Without the Hogyoku,
it is impossible to either
transform Hollows into Arrancars,
or create the Ouken.
Consider the fact that I showed this
to you as proof that I trust you.
You have the power of
phenomenon rejection.
You can negate things
that have happened
and wipe out the events entirely.
It's an incredible power.
I need your power…
Orihime.
You'll use your power for me,
won't you?
I don't think he showed me
the Hogyoku because he trusts me.
But I at least know
where the Hogyoku is.
And about my power…
I can negate things that have happened
and wipe out the events entirely.
Thank you for coming
to save me Kurosaki.
But I know what
I have to do here.
It's probably something
that only I can do.
I have to use my power to
return the Hogyoku
back to the state it was in
before it existed!
Renji, have you ever
done that cheer before?
No. I've suggested it to
my captain several times,
but for some reason
he always ignores me.
Rukia, ask him to do it for me.
Well…
Do you think that
Byakuya would do that?
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today I shall reveal my secrets!
First, my Dondochakka Eyes!
They're sharp eyes that can find
my targets in games of eternal pursuit!
My Dondochakka Innards!
I have a wonderful stomach
that can digest anything.
Shoot 'im dead, Shinso!
I'm sorry!
Jeez…
You took over my segment.
But this is pretty amusing.
Maybe next time
I'll try this with someone.