I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Say…
If you really want to fight me,
bring a better weapon now, won’t you?
You're naive…
You…brat!
You should have just died…
I told you…
I will put an end to
this meaningless battle…
You're getting cocky.
Do you think you can beat us
with that rickety bow?
I am somehow getting used
to controlling this power.
All that's left is my aim…
My aim is still off…
Damn! This time,
my power has dropped…
You said that this battle
is meaningless,
but I never wanted battles
to mean anything to begin with!
What?!
Then why do you fight?!
What is your goal?!
Kariya said that
he was going to exterminate
the Soul Reapers of Seireitei…
But…
I don't care about that.
I just wanted to run amok…
Long ago, it was great.
I risked my life in battle
to get what I wanted…
I was satisfied.
But the world changed…
What's wrong with
the strong killing the weak?!
I've been thirsty for a long time!
I was so thirsty that
nothing could help me!
But here, I can proudly display
the heads I've taken
without reservation!
I'm surprised you can stand.
That's good…
You're making me excited…
Now then, I'm going to finish you off.
There are an increasing number
of injured among the Squads…
How are the captain of Squad 2
and the Punishment Force?
Yes. They are recovering,
but most are exhausted and
are in no condition to be moved.
Hmm… That can't be helped…
Squad 8 Captain Shunsui Kyoraku.
Yes…
How much have we confirmed
from Squad 12’s report?
It's troublesome…
We have confirmed
an enormous sealed facility…
deep in the basement of
the Department of Research
and Development.
What?
It's something I cannot overlook.
The Jokai Crest,
a sealed-away power
that we never knew existed
was stolen from us and has fallen
into the hands of the Ryoka…
According to Soul Reaper substitute,
Ichigo Kurosaki,
who battled at the scene…
the Jokai Crest was used as
the source of power for
past soul experiments.
If it accidentally goes off,
it can instantaneously
turn Seireitei into ashes.
But the Jokai Crest was
sealed away far before…
the formation of the Department
of Research and Development.
Even the part about Rantao,
the one labeled as the great sinner…
We don't know how much of it
is true with just this information…
Indeed… But whatever the reason,
it's also true that
Central 46 of that time…
completely sealed it away and
had its existence erased
from the records.
I can't say that the immense power
that the Ryoka spoke of was fake.
Whatever the case,
I want to tell everyone to do
their best to track the Ryoka.
Yes!
Jokai Crest?
That's right.
I never thought that such
a thing existed…
Yeah…
Now we can blow away Seireitei.
Everything will be decided
after one day!
It feels good.
Kariya, you don't have
to go that far!
Are you worried about me?
It's all right.
I won't die that easily.
No! I'm saying that this
is outrageous!
Several of our comrades'
Spiritual Pressures
have already disappeared…
It's enough, isn't it?!
If you have that much power,
you should use it to make
the Soul Reapers kneel before you…
It's no good!
Why?! Our goal is revenge.
But even so, what good will
it do if everyone's dead?!
What's the point in that?
That’s the way it should be.
Kariya, you can't mean…
I've been thinking about this
since the first time we met…
You're a blade that
cannot be controlled…
The Bounts went through hardships
and got carried away
with your spirit…
That's why I was following you
until today, but…
If you're going to use
the Jokai Crest,
then that changes things…
If it is the source of
our tribe's power, as you say,
then we shouldn't use it
as a weapon.
I like that serious side
of you, Koga…
Kariya, don't do it…
That's like spitting
on the heavens!
I've been with you
for a long time.
I'm really grateful to you.
Ka…ri…ya…
Oh my. I thought you were
just a regular kid, but…
You have a pretty
determined look…
A Quincy's arrow is only released
in the name of Justice.
Justice…
Justice, that is, for those
you've sworn to protect…
There's nothing difficult aside from
the basics I have just taught you.
Everything, from there on…
depends on your heart.
Heart…
Quincies release arrows
with their hearts…
in the name of Justice.
Master…
I'll give it a try…
I'll release an arrow with
my heart…
In the name of Justice.
That's pretty impressive…
To think you’re powers would
increase at this point…
But it seems that
you're reaching your limit…
Please…
Hold up!
It's my turn!
What?!
Yes!
What's wrong?
What are you doing?!
Oh my. It’s because you carelessly
returned me!
It's not my fault!
What was that just now?
Could it be?
It seems like you didn't do
that on purpose…
It went off by accident?
In that case…
Please…hold up!
You're already at your limit!
Don't you understand that
my defense is impregnable?!
This is the end…
Why?!
Those dolls make
their own decisions
while you're fused with them.
That's why you had
superhuman abilities.
But it's different when
you undo your transformation.
You can't attack when
you're defending.
You can't defend when
you're attacking.
That's why…
whenever you change forms,
you have to change back
to your original form
with your own will.
When my Kojaku accidentally
went off,
you were sure you had won
and carelessly undid your fusion.
You couldn't react at all to
the second arrow that appeared.
In other words,
a small time lag is created there.
That's your only and
greatest weakness.
But how did you fire
that second shot?
My master told me…
“An arrow is not fired,
it is released…”
And a Quincy's arrow is released
with the heart…
I lose… It was fun…
SEIREITEI LIBRARY
My, my…
Someone who's faking sickness
shouldn't be coughing for real…
Did you discover anything?
A little…
But the data is vast…
So what did the enemy say?
He's given us
a day's grace period.
Come tomorrow… Boom!
I see…
Take a look at this…
It's a summary of the Jokai Crest.
Its author is Rantao…
Why is something
like this here?
The person called Rantao
is incredibly clever.
People want to know secrets…
They especially want to enter places
where the secret might be located…
The most targeted places
in those cases
are official information
storage facilities.
But it's pretty difficult to find
if it's turned into a document
and hidden amongst
lots of other documents…
Oh?
I once confirmed with
Captain Hitsugaya
that the Bount data
disappeared from here.
I thought that there might be
something important here.
It seems that the person
who erased the data
didn't notice the documents
on the Jokai Crest…
And…?
I found the Jokai Crest document
by accident…
But I think there's something else…
Something else?
The important part
isn't written here.
The writer divided the information
among several books
and scattered them throughout
these numerous books…
Whoa… Are we going to
search through all of them?
We still have time until tomorrow.
Uh…um…
Thanks…
You came to help me, didn't you?
My, my…
You're welcome…
Master…
You've done your best, Uryu…
Why?
You've fought enough…
You released a wonderful arrow
on your pride as a Quincy…
No way… I still…
People have limits at times.
You fought to that limit for now.
It's enough.
Rest well from now on…
I can't do that!
I…I still…
A heart of vengeance makes
a person's heart tough.
But at times your obstinacy
can dull your blade…
Take the time to think about that…
Master…
Ishida!
Ishida, did you fight a Bount?
Yeah… I was able to defeat her…
What about you?
Kariya… That bastard said that
he was going to blow away
Seireitei by tomorrow.
What?!
Don't push yourself…
You're going to stop Kariya,
aren't you?
I'm going, too!
I know…
But first we have to tend
to your wounds.
Kariya…don't be reckless…
There's no need to
destroy Seireitei…
Don't affect the youths
of the future…Kariya…
There's one!
Take your positions!
Out of the way!
I have somewhere to go…
We've tracked a Ryoka!
We will begin our attack!
A different team has found a ryoka!
Tell them not to lay a hand on him!
Wait until we join them!
Everyone…
Zeig Dih, Dalk!
It's okay to get them, right?
It can't be helped.
What happened? Answer me!
The responses suddenly stopped
after the screaming!
Damn!
At any rate, let's go after them!
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
A request has come from
Squad 10 for help.
What?!
All right… Let's give it our best!
It seems that one of us will do.
Then I, the most worthy, will…
What are you talking about?!
It'll be me!
No me!
Me!
It doesn't matter who goes.
Just come quickly!
Me! Me! Me!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
We shall begin our regular meeting of
the Female Soul Reapers Association…
Oh… is it only you,
Third Seat Kotetsu?
Yes.
Captain Soi Fon and
Lieutenant Kurotsuchi
are absent due to injuries.
Big Sister is their nurse.
I've received a call from
Lt. Matsumoto that she's working.
How unusual…
Umm… “Whereabouts unknown…”
Oh! Speaking of
unknown whereabouts,
Captain Ukitake
has gone somewhere…
Come to think of it,
my captain is gone, too…
Master…