Ichigo and his friends
undergo intense training
in preparation for
the showdown in the winter.
Aizen suddenly sends an elite group
of Arrancars before them.
But the Arrancars suddenly
retreat in the midsts of battle.
Aizen was after Orihime and
the Espada's attack was a diversion.
Orihime is captured by Ulquiorra
and taken to Hueco Mundo.
Ichigo and his friends
realize Orihime's disappearance
and try to go to save her,
but Genryusai forbids them
from taking action.
You mustn't!
We need your help in this battle...
I won't allow you to plot your own
course of action and die for nothing!
Meanwhile, Tatsuki realizes that Orihime
is gone and presses Ichigo about it.
You know where Orihime went,
don't you?
That's enough...
Tell me everything you're hiding.
This doesn't concern you.
Ichigo decides to go to
Hueco Mundo by himself
and visits Urahara's Shop
for help.
Welcome...
I thought that it was
about time you came.
Waiting there for him
were Ishida and Sado.
Do you still think that
I'm not strong enough?
Believe in us.
Chad...
Don't take this on by yourself...
This is what friends are for!
All right! Is everyone ready?
It seems like you're
finally prepared.
URAHARA'S SHOP
That was Ichigo...wasn't it?
Yeah...
Wh-What is he doing here?
We came here to find out,
didn't we?!
Well, that's true.
Honestly...
Ichigo sure is hopeless.
It's completely obvious that
he's hiding something!
He's practically telling us that
he's going to do something.
That's because he's an idiot.
Arisawa, I don't think you can really talk
about his ridiculous straightforwardness.
And don't bother with me.
Just what does Ichigo
think I am?!
This isn't like you...
Don't you want to know
where Ichigo's going?
Well...
In that case...
"In that case"?
Well?
"Well"?
You're the one who
brought this up.
What are you saying?
We followed Ichigo all the way here...
What should we do, Arisawa?
What should we do?
What will we do?
What should we do at a time like this?!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Shut up!
No, Arisawa!
Don't get mad for real!
We're going to go, of course.
You're finally acting
more like yourself, Arisawa.
Shut up...
All right. Let's go!
Ichigo...
Now then, I shall now open
the path to Hueco Mundo!
Lirin and you others, it's dangerous,
so stand back a little! Stand back!
What?! This doesn't happen often,
so I wanted to see it up close!
That's right!
It's rare to get such good seats!
No problem.
I can't let you do that!
What?!
Hey, hey! What are you doing?!
I can walk on my own.
We're being left out. It's not fair!
Storeowner!
Things are okay over here!
All right!
Well then...
In my right hand,
the stone that connects the worlds.
In my left hand,
the blade that binds existence.
The black-haired shepherd.
The chair of the noose.
I strike the ibis
when the clouds gather.
This hole that the Arrancars come
and go through it is called a Garganta.
Inside, there is no path, and there are
wild reishi currents swirling around.
Move through it by making
footing out of reishi.
If you move towards the darkness,
you should reach Hueco Mundo.
All right.
Mr. Urahara...
Can you take care of
everyone at home for me?
I want you to tell them
not to worry about me.
All right...
What about your friends?
I'll apologize to them
when I get back.
All right.
Well, go give it your best!
Be careful.
Yeah...
Let's go!
So that's it.
Why don't you
come out about now?
Umm... When did you notice us?
Since before you came here.
I knew that you were following Kurosaki,
so I left the store unlocked.
My, my...
Kurosaki has been naïve,
as usual.
He thinks that he's cut his ties
just by being a little cold.
Now then...
I guess I should do my job.
Welcome to our castle,
Las Noches.
Orihime Inoue...was it?
Yes...
Sorry this is so sudden, but Orihime,
could you show me your power?
Yes...
What was that just now?
It felt as if my strength was
being sucked out of my body.
It seems like
there are some people
who don't like the fact
that I brought you here.
Isn't that right, Luppi?
Of course...
Our entire battle was a diversion so that
we could bring this woman here?!
I can't agree to that.
Sorry...
I didn't expect you
to get so beaten up.
Ah, I know...
Orihime, in order to clearly
show off your power...
I want you to heal
Grimmjow's left arm.
Impossible!
That's crazy, Lord Aizen!
Grimmjow?!
Director General Tosen
turned his arm to ashes!
How is she going to heal something
that's been wiped out?!
She's not a god!
Sotenkishun.
I...reject.
Hey! Are you listening, woman?!
If you're just putting on an act so
you can save yourself, then cut it out!
If you can't do it, I'll kill you!
If your power isn't real,
then there's no reason
to keep someone like you al...ive...
H-How?!
This is beyond
the level of healing.
What did you do, woman?!
Don't you understand?
Ulquiorra thinks it's time regression
or space regression.
Yes.
Impossible... There's no way a human
has such advanced power!
That's right. It's neither.
This is a rejection
of phenomenon.
Her power limits, rejects, and negates
events that happen to an object.
She has the power
to return things
to their state before
things happened to them.
It's above time regression
and space regression...
It easily overcomes the limits of
God's established phenomena.
It is a power that encroaches
on the realm of the gods.
Hey, woman.
Fix one more part of me.
What are you doing, Grimmjow?
Huh?
Wha-?!
G-Grimmjow...you bastard...
That's how it is...
So long...former Number Six.
It's back!
My power's back!
I'm Seis!
Seis Espada, Grimmjow!
Beyond this point
is Hueco Mundo?
Crap!
He talked about making footing
with reishi as if it was easy!
I'm really terrible
at little things like this!
Are you all right, Chad?!
Not a problem.
Sorry!
My, my...
That's pathetic... Can't you make
your footing a little better?
Shut up!
I told you I'm not good
at things like this!
Anyway, what is
that thing you have?!
You're cheating, aren't you?!
It's a variation of the Hirenkyaku...
This is nothing.
Make one for me, too!
Sorry...
Your inability to control Spiritual Pressure
means that you couldn't use this.
What? You talk as if
I don't have any powers!
Am I wrong?
You can't even make
your own footing properly.
I'm going to kill you!
I'll go on ahead of you.
Ishida...
I heard from Mr. Urahara that you
made an agreement with your father.
In exchange for his training,
you wouldn't involve yourself with
Soul Reapers or their associates.
So why are you here?
What's that?! I never heard
about that before, Ishida!
Is that true?
Training, huh?
Yeah, That's right.
Hello... Sorry to disturb you
at this hour.
Well, it's still evening, though.
M-Mr. Urahara?!
Oh? Your father isn't here...
This is lucky!
What do you want with me?
Oh, that's it!
What's it?!
Inoue was abducted
by the Arrancars?!
More accurately, the Arrancars did it
on Sosuke Aizen's command.
Kurosaki is probably going to go
and save her by himself.
He's probably going to come to me for
a way to get into Hueco Mundo tonight.
Please leave.
Huh?
You're trying to tell me to go with
Kurosaki to Hueco Mundo, right?
But right now,
I can't involve myself with Soul Reapers.
Please leave!
I'll save Inoue by myself
if I have to...
By himself?
Mr. Urahara,
what did you just say?
Kurosaki's by himself?
Yes.
Soul Society isn't
touching this incident.
Kurosaki decided to head into
enemy territory by himself.
Is that so?
Then that changes things.
Why?
Even though Soul Society
isn't touching this,
that doesn't change the fact
that I'm a Soul Reaper!
No.
You're a Substitute Soul Reaper.
Furthermore,
Soul Society has abandoned you.
In other words...
Right now, you're not a Soul Reaper
or one of their associates.
Hence even if I associate
myself with you,
it doesn't go against
my contract.
That's a forced argument.
I'd like to think of it as finding
a hole in my contract.
That's called a forced argument!
Shut up! Whose side are you on?
Your enemy's!
How typical of Ishida...
Hey!
It looks like Ishida ran away.
How did you get in?
Kurosaki...
Oh?!
What's this?
That's the first time
you ever called me that.
Why the change in attitude?
Answer my question...
I'm asking you how you got in.
That attire...
You got your powers back?
Pretty much!
I look good, don't I?
It makes me want to throw up.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to
read the letter?
How silly... I know what it says
without having to read it.
You let him go on purpose,
didn't you?
It's none of your concern.
I brought back his Quincy powers.
Whether he makes use of it
or suppresses it is up to him.
Whether he lives or dies
is of no concern.
What a horrible father you are.
I think I'm much better than you.
Yeah. I know.
I was told to stay quiet here,
but there's nothing for me to do.
I'm hungry...
I wonder if it was really a good idea
for me to come here.
I wonder if the battle got worse
because I healed those people.
No...
But, right now,
I have to make them think that
I'm of use to them, no matter what.
At least until everyone's
prepared for battle.
They've come.
I wanted to go to
Hueco Mundo, too.
It can't be helped. Our gigai were
broken in the previous battle.
What a waste.
Then let's get new ones made.
This time, I want a sexy one.
I want a handsome one.
Know your place.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Hey Ishida, you still smoke?
You already quit, didn't you?
Yeah...
I don't smoke unless
it's a memorial day.
Huh? Come to think of it,
this is a hospital...
NO SMOKING
INSIDE HOSPITAL
That's not a problem.
No... Do you really think that
saying that makes things any better?