Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Bount.
Bount?
This reishi is probably from a Bount…
So what's a Bount?
When I was in the Department of Research
and Development,
I saw residue that looked
a lot like this.
It's a mysterious reishi that reacts
with special components of human souls…
Upon investigation,
I found a tribe called the Bount.
A tribe?
They are few in number,
but the Bount are humans
who have special powers…
like the Quincy.
Quincies, having the power
to destroy Hollows,
brought disaster
upon themselves, but…
Bounts absorb human souls
as nourishment.
Also, Quincies are born human
and die human, but…
By absorbing human souls,
Bounts can live forever.
That's all I found out,
but I have never been able
to see one myself.
Live forever--?
Yes…
Bounts gain eternal life
by absorbing human souls for food.
That's the kind of tribe they are.
It seems that depending
on the era and place,
they were also called vampires…
The way Bounts usually do things is
to come and steal
the soul of a human who died
while konso is being performed on it…
But this time…
Don't stop a man and a woman
from having a good time together.
You were trying to
suck out his soul.
Who are you?!
You'll find out in time!
The Bount I saw was trying to
absorb the soul of a living person…
What happens to people
if their souls are sucked out?
The same thing as when
their lives are taken.
The result is, in other words…
death.
Death…?
We're still not sure
if it's a Bount.
Do you suppose that it could be
a subspecies of Bount?
Well, who knows…
Why are you crossing your arms
and thinking so hard!
At this rate, there may be more victims!
All right!
Just as I expected of you, Kurosaki!
You sure have a strong sense
of justice!
Cut the sarcasm…
So anyway…
– Lirin.
– Huh?
Go to Kurosaki's place.
What? No way!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Kurosaki, Inoue, and Sado
will act as support.
Support?
These three mod souls have
reishi sensor functions attached.
Sensors?
They can detect reishi waves.
In other words, the enemy
is targeting living humans.
All of you have exceptionally
high abilities for humans.
You would be tempting prey for them.
We're not sure if they'll notice you.
We have to find the location
of the enemy quickly.
Hmm… I see…
What? Huh? Then what about me?
Oh… It's as I just said…
You don't have any abilities!
That's right…isn't it?
Now then…
So Kurodo will go to Inoue's place.
Well, I guess it can't be helped…
You're leering. You're leering…
It can't be helped…
Noba, go to Sado's place.
What's the point in closing
your mask?
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
But…don't give me too much trouble!
Wh-What did you say?!
You're causing me trouble!
Oh? I forget, who couldn't
defend against my attack?
Come on, say it.
You never shut up!
Also, you may already know,
I want you to hide yourselves
in stuffed animals.
Stuffed animals?
Are you serious?
Then take care!
Detect reishi waves…huh--?
When did you add that sort
of search function?
Oh, that--?
You know what they say,
“A stitch in time saves nine!”
You act as if you knew that
the Bounts would come…
You're just thinking too hard.
Seireitei Library
Captain! Captain Kyoraku!
There is a message from
Captain Ukitake saying
that he wants you to hurry
to the Central Library.
Captain?! You're awake, aren't you?!
Why do you speak in such
an unrefined voice…
It's a waste of your beauty.
Were you listening to
what I was saying?
I was listening…
It's probably some crude work, isn't it?
It seems that the material concerning
the item we're investigating has been lost.
Hey!
Why are you both so quiet?!
Someone might think it's some sort
of broadcasting accident!
Don't look at me like
you've seen something unusual!
The three of us are here,
so shall we form a trio? Huh?
Did something happen?
Will you listen?
Kurosaki Clinic
No way!
No, no, no!
Even if you say so…
The only stuffed animals remaining
in this house are the really old ones
that Yuzu and Karin had
when they were really young…
– No!
– Oww!
What are you doing, you…!
At any rate,
I can't believe that
you're trying to force me
into these ratty and ugly things!
I'm going to tell Kisuke if
you don't take this seriously!
All right… Then what kind of
stuffed animal would you like?
Tell me. If I know what it is,
I'll look for one…
Well…
Definitely…something that's smart
and moves quickly…
Something that reveals a glimpse
of cuteness within its beauty…
A bit gothic, but…
– not too formal…
– This is a pain!
– yet not too cheap…
– This is good enough!
Huh?
What is this--?!
What is it? Probably a bird…
Hold on! What are you doing?!
I can't change bodies
once I've gone into one!
– Is that so? How nice.
– I'll be like this all my life!
Huh? Who is this?
What? Could it be, Lirin?
You've been making fun of me,
but that's just the sad nature
of being a mod soul!
You're a talking stuffed animal like me!
Watch how you talk…
I'm in a really bad mood right now!
Y-Yes…
Since then, she's gotten carried away
and bosses me around…
Isn't it horrible--?
I'm still sort of her elder!
Here you go…
Oh!
Seniority is important, isn't it?!
I'm an elder of mod souls!
There's a proper order for things!
But I wanted to go to
Inoue's place if anything…
I want to be held in that large chest…
But that damned old man!
I'm so jealous!
Having such a stuffy old man
pushed on to her probably upset Inoue!
Say, say, don't you think
we should see what the situation
is at Inoue's house?
No… not particu--
Right?! Inoue is definitely troubled!
We're not men if we don't go!
What was that voice?!
Could it be…
Could it be that Inoue is in…
This kind of…
or that kind of…
situation, is she?!
What is it?!
Peeping isn't good.
I'm not peeping! I'm just keeping
watch to protect Inoue!
Oh dear!
Oh, I can't leave this alone!
Here I go!
Huh?
It's as I thought!
You're really cute!
Well, it can be cute depending
on how you look at it.
It is cute. I'm not saying anything
about your aesthetics.
But I'm the one inside of this, so…
I think you match it very well,
Mr. Kurodo…
It's…what would you call it?
Mismatched? Like that?
But…
Kurodo!
Did you feel that?!
What's with this serious atmosphere?!
A Bount.
What?!
They've come!
A Bount?
It's all right. They're far from here.
That's a good girl…
What are you doing?
A Soul Reaper?
I'm just a substitute…
What business does
a Soul Reaper Substitute have with me--?
I can't let you eat the souls
of living people!
Please, don't interfere!
I can't do that!
Where is she?!
Over there, you slow poke!
B-But…
It's all right.
She's just unconscious.
Wait!
She's not as vicious
as we expected.
But you shouldn't let your guard down.
I know.
What is this? How far
do you plan on going?
We're almost there.
We're getting closer.
Turn right at the next corner.
Tell me what you're planning…
My plan?
There's no way that your mind
would be able to comprehend
even if I told you…
What a bothersome kid.
Even if it is a bother,
I'm not letting you go
until I'm satisfied!
I don't want to fight…
Zeig dih! Goethe!
Fire?
Be careful! That's no ordinary fire!
What is he?
How do you like my doll?
Doll?
Yoshino… Did you call me?
Goethe, please help me.
He's being persistent.
He's…being persistent, huh?!
Ichigo!
I know!
– Don't let go!
– Okay!
He turned back to normal!
That's right.
He'll turn back to normal
no matter how many times you cut him.
You…have no chance of winning.
There's…a Bount here?
Be careful! He should be nearby!
I-I want to go home already.
Noba?!
Noba?
There's a person…
It seems we were too late…
I never thought a person could
disappear without a trace like this…
I've failed to greet you…
Pleased to meet you.
Is this your doing?!
My doing--?
Oh, I just finished a bit of a meal.
A meal--?! Stop joking!
Joking--? Me--?
I wouldn't do something rude
like that.
I'm always deeply grateful to
my food and pay my respects.
Food…
You all seem very delicious…
Too bad… I'm already full for today.
So maybe some time later…
Wait!
Who is he?
The Bount Yoruichi saw was a woman…
It means that it was a different one.
Damn it… Where should I cut?
It's useless to cut anywhere.
That can't be true!
There's got to be away I can cut him!
Why you--!
She’s told you it's useless…
What about it?
Do you have a better idea?
Did you forget what Kisuke
told you?
Stay calm in battle…
Observe your opponent
and find a weakness!
Stay calm…
That's right…
Observe well…
Find…a weakness…
There!
Huh?! Hold on…
All right!
His weak spot was his heart!
I did it, Lirin! Look!
In front of you! Look in front of you!
I told you…
Goethe, finish him!
Finish him? I understand.
Ichigo!
Are you all right? Can you move?!
Yeah! I'm fine!
There's no need for that! Look!
Quickly!
Huh? Whoa! What the--?!
What are you doing?!
I can't get out.
You idiot!
What are you doing, fool?!
Rukia!
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
I'm Rukia Kuchiki,
the transfer student.
Let's get back to our school life
with spirit once more!
Rukia, what are you doing?
The Karakura High School arc starts
from the next episode of Bleach!
Tune in to our bittersweet
youth-filled heartfelt story!
That’s not what it's about!
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Captain Hitsugaya,
I'm sorry it was a waste of time
even though you came out
of your way to help me.
There's no need to worry…
This may be linked to
that bastard, Aizen.
As a token of my apology
how about an assortment
of snacks?
Huh?!
They're a bit out of season, but look!
Hey… Why do you always give
this stuff to me--?
Because we're both “Shiros”!
Huh? Is that all?
JyuSHIRO Ukitake     ToSHIRO Hitsugaya
Do you need more?
Tune in again!