Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
You can't move yet!
You're…
I'm almost finished.
This power… Who are you?
Are you one of the Substitute
Soul Reaper's friends?
Huh?
Why did you save me?
Why? I can't ignore
an injured person.
Besides… You looked like
you were in so much pain.
Ridiculous…
What is this?
This ominous Spiritual Pressure
is like that of an Arrancar…
Ishida! Sado!
Come on, make your next move!
Kenny…
Come on!
Kenny!
Don't make a fuss, Yachiru.
You're pretty good.
This is the way…
battles should be!
That's a good attack.
But it's still not enough!
I'm not done yet!
You're not getting away!
Growl!
Shunko!
Where is she?
Behind you!
What?!
Why you!
You're full of openings.
You pay too much attention
to men and clothes.
I can see you don't spend
enough time training.
Shut up, you monster cat!
Oh, dear…
I was giving you a piece
of advice as a fellow cat.
You're not getting away!
Cut it out.
I've been called
the Flash Master.
You girls could never catch me
in a hundred years!
But we can't afford to lose.
Why don't you realize
that Muramasa tricked you?
He tricked us?!
That's right.
Your friends Katenkyokotsu
and Sogyonokotowari
were broken by
Muramasa's betrayal.
Don't lie!
I guess I have no choice.
I'm going to use
some rough tactics.
Well, we should try to
get Ryujinjakka back again.
Yeah.
But these flames…
He won't be easy to deal with.
My master, Toshiro Hitsugaya…
We're fighting the most powerful
fire-type Zanpakuto.
He is a satisfying opponent.
I shall lend you all of my power.
What is it?
There's no need to be so formal.
I'm telling you to just act normal.
There are four captains with you.
Winning will be no problem.
Captain Hitsugaya is right.
Let's settle this and
catch up with Ichigo.
That's right.
Let's go.
Ishida, Sado…
Inoue, are you all right?
Oh, yeah… I'm all right.
This Spiritual Pressure…
He's not a Soul Reaper
or an Arrancar…
Who is he?
Don't move!
And who might you be?
Are you friends of
the Soul Reapers?
I'm not a Soul Reaper.
I'm a Quincy.
A Quincy?
I don't know what that is.
Sado!
Sado?!
I don't have time…
to be fighting you here!
What?!
Ishida!
These guys…
I'm so close…
Sado, you go at him
from the other side!
Got it!
I've got you!
Wha—?!
That's Byakuya Kuchiki's
Senbonzakura…
I won't let you.
Muramasa, leave this to me.
The Zanpakuto rebellion…
This is…
Scatter!
Ishida!
Now's not the time to be
worrying about other people.
This is…
Abuelo…
You certainly aren't
a Soul Reaper, are you?
That was easy.
You can still move?
Just die already!
Sado!
Sado! Sado!
It's useless, woman.
He cannot fight anymore.
No way…
Ishida!
I'm not done yet!
Where are you aiming?!
Bankai!
Ishida!
Santenkesshun!
What?!
Why are you doing this?
You are burdened with
a deep sadness.
That's what I saw in your eyes.
Why would you do this?
Inoue…
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Don't act as if
you understand, woman!
What do you know?!
My name is Muramasa!
My power will change this world!
Hado 33!
Sokatsui!
Kuchiki!
Are you all right, Inoue, Ishida?
Somewhat.
But Sado is…
Sado…
Rukia Kuchiki…
Why are you here?
I just followed my brother's
Spiritual Pressure.
Followed his Spiritual Pressure?
What do you mean, Kuchiki?
I'll explain later.
Anyway, be careful.
This man is the person who
manifested the Zanpakuto
and threw Seireitei into chaos.
What?!
Why is he in
the World of the Living?
Where's Kurosaki?!
He should be burning in
Ryujinjakka's flames right now.
Ryujinjakka…
Did you gain control of
the Head Captain's Zanpakuto too?
That's exactly what I did.
You're wrong!
Kurosaki will come back!
He…
Muramasa…
I'm all right.
But I don't have time.
What?
A Hollow?
That Spiritual Pressure earlier…
I knew it.
Why are Hollows here?
Aren't you a Zanpakuto?
What are you trying to do here?!
I am a genuine Zanpakuto!
A Zanpakuto with the power
to change the world.
And I am trying to release myself
from this long,
lonesome battle!
Take care of things here.
You're not getting away!
I'm not letting you pass!
Kuchiki!
Inoue!
Take Sado somewhere safe!
Okay!
Hado 33! Sokatsui!
Soon… Soon…
Koga…
I've finally come this far…
Gather around the supreme one
who was purified with a dark soul
and place a blood pact
upon the altar.
Kuchiki! I can handle this. Go!
But…
That Muramasa is overwhelmed
by a deep sadness about something.
At this rate…
They're coming!
Kuchiki!
Oh, no!
Sado!
Sado, are you all right?!
This is nothing.
Go, Kuchiki!
All right.
Please do something, Kuchiki.
Why you…
What?
A cherished offering
from the dark heavens.
Offer the holy grail to
the vengeful spirit
who has been sealed away
while holding the six keys
which have been passed down
through the ages.
Damn it!
I've got to do something fast.
You don't have time
to be getting distracted!
What?
Open now…forgotten coffin!
That was…a barrier?
I never knew that
Quincies used swords.
But you can't win with
weapons you aren't used to!
It's over, Quincy!
What?!
Seeleschneider isn't a sword.
It weakens the bonds between reishi
so that they are easier to steal.
It can't be!
Too slow!
Ah… I've finally come this far…
Hado 33!
Sokatsui!
Don't interfere!
Kuchiki!
I won't let you!
What is that?!
What are you trying to do?!
My master is in this coffin.
He once tried to take
control of Soul Society.
Koga, the most powerful
Soul Reaper rests here!
What?
My wish is to revive Koga.
Everything I've done
is for this moment!
My master…
Hold it right there!
Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
You bastard…
Rukia… Sorry I'm late.
You fool.
How did you escape
Ryujinjakka's blockade?
Who knows?
But I'm not going to let you
do whatever you want!
I see.
But that's too bad,
because you're a little too late.
The wish I've had for many years
has finally been granted.
Damn it…
Are you guys all right?
Who are you?
– Huh?
I… Huh?
A friend who goes off to
Soul Society without telling us
– is no friend of ours!
– Uh, umm…
Huh? Huh?
Sorry about that.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Ryujinjakka!
You have always helped me out.
Ryujinjakka…
When I cooked rice…
When I was cold…
When I baked potatoes…
You always help me out!
Now I shall undo
your brainwashing!
Perhaps he was sick of
doing household chores.