Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
So running away is
all that's left for you!
You disappear from
my range of vision
to attack with projectile weapons…
You're as rotten as you look!
Like I care.
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to take lives.
I have no interest in
how my master fights.
I don't like you.
I just realized that.
Fine with me.
Because the feeling is mutual.
So you shifted your body
to avoid a direct hit…
What an idiot.
You wouldn't be in any pain
if you had died.
Oh, well… It's over now!
Who the hell are you?
A Zanpakuto killing his owner…
I find that to be
quite a sick joke.
K-Kira…
You continue to amuse me,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I never expected to become so
interested in a single Soul Reaper.
And you're incredibly talkative.
You keep droning on and on.
I'm done talking.
Let's settle this!
So it comes to this,
Old Man Zangetsu!
I'm going to fight to get you back.
Even if I have to fight you.
My feelings won't change.
What about you?!
I want to know.
You or I…
Which one of us is
truly the strongest…
If I can find that out, I will
gladly cross blades with you.
Without Zangetsu's power
within your Zanpakuto,
you can't fight like
you normally do.
I will lend you my power for now.
In exchange, you won’t be able to
use the power of your mask.
Remember that.
Bankai!
Watch out, Snake.
I know that.
Did something about him change?
Looks like it.
Sorry, but I'm going to
put an end to this!
Zanpakuto should stick to
being used by their owners.
The way it should be.
What did you say?!
What kind of arrogant
nonsense is that?
Wait.
That's quite an impressive
thing to say.
It looks like you finally
have the will to fight us.
I don't just have the will.
I'm going to thrash you head on!
Don't get ideas, Renji.
That's right! Don't get cocky!
Huh?
Do you think you can beat us
if you have the will to fight?
No matter what you do,
we're stronger!
Want a taste of it?
Taste of what?
Your blade.
Kira… Why…?
Hisagi… You shouldn't move.
Your wounds are pretty deep.
Even so…
I can't leave you with
the task of disposing him.
I don’t want to do this either.
But having a lieutenant die
before we can
find a way to resolve
this problem is far worse.
I'm not just here to help you.
Our mission is to put down
the Zanpakuto rebellion!
Kira…
Another idiot has come along, eh?
That’s fine by me.
I don’t care which
one of you dies first.
After all, my desire is to hunt
down as many lives as possible.
You're a Zanpakuto
with pleasant interests.
And you're a stupidly
honest Soul Reaper!
Too slow.
I was waiting for that.
Bakudo 37, Tsuriboshi!
Damn it…
What the hell is this?!
Here I come, Ichigo.
Getsugatensho!
Crap!
Such power… That was close.
Was I always using
power like that?
Get up, Ichigo.
I'm not finished.
All right.
If that's what you want…
Bankai!
Too bad, Ichigo.
Without my power,
you can't use your Bankai.
What?!
Getsugatensho.
Can I take him on
without using my Bankai?
I will lend you my power.
In exchange, you won’t be able to
use the power of your mask.
Getsugatensho!
Not bad!
I never expected you to
be able to use us this well.
You idiot!
I've been training
every day for decades!
I guess we have no choice.
Shall we do it?
Bankai!
You look quite surprised, Renji.
We're Zanpakuto, you know.
I'm sure you figured
we could do this.
Go!
Hikotsu Taiho!
Old Man Zangetsu…
You mentioned that you wanted to
see which one of us was stronger…
Why do you want to do that?
Why do you ask?
If that's the case, you don't
really want to leave me.
I wanted to make you stronger.
That was my only desire.
And now, I have nothing
left to teach you.
Whether you can surpass me
is all up to you.
Even if you were to
fall by my blade,
I would be content with that.
Is that all?
Yes.
All right…
That means,
in order to get you back,
I've got to hit you with
everything I've got
and show you how strong I am.
That's right.
Come at me with
everything you've got, Ichigo!
I'm difficult to handle.
All right, let's go!
Our Bankai is not like
your shoddy one.
We have no blind spots!
This match is over.
Your Shikai is no match
for my Bankai!
Now you understand.
You cannot defeat us.
Sh-Shut up!
Damn it…
It's true that my Shikai is
no match for her Bankai…
Furthermore,
she's reading my attacks.
She knows my usual attack pattern,
so I guess it makes sense.
What should I do?
You don't have brains, so thinking
about this is pointless.
Of all your weaknesses,
your intelligence is
the weakest, Renji.
My weakness…
I'll give it a try…
What should we do, Monkey?
He probably realizes that
fighting any longer is pointless.
Bakudo 4: Hainawa!
It's not over yet!
You never learn.
This is pathetic, Renji.
I'm bad at Kido, so they'd
never expect me to use it.
Hado 31! Shakkaho!
How interesting.
Were you aiming for this?
But with your level of Kido…
I'm not done yet!
You idiot!
Your Kido is dangerous to everyone,
including yourself!
So you’re trying to fight
in a different style?
But you can't beat us
with your level of Kido!
I've got it!
It appears your sword
is worthless now!
It's over!
Not yet!
Shakkaho!
Knock it off!
What?!
What happened?!
Higazekko!
Not yet.
I told you, Ichigo…
Hit me with
everything you've got!
Otherwise, you can't beat me!
I know that.
I'm starting to understand
how to handle you!
Keeping this up is a waste of time.
Let's end this, Ichigo.
Yeah. Let's do that.
Take this.
Getsuga…
…tensho!
Getsugatensho!
I can’t let my host die,
now can I?
Impossible!
He isn't even using his Bankai.
This is…
You're next to go down,
Muramasa!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Didn't you have any misgivings
about destroying your Zanpakuto?
Nope.
What?
Old Man Zangetsu is a part of me.
He'd definitely take in my power.
When I think of that…
There's no way I can cower from
battle and turn my back on him!
This is our bond!
I see…
You…
Your bond is your strength…
How interesting…
It seems I've played
with you for too long.
I'm going to retreat.
Hey! Wait!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I'll remember you.
Old Man! Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm all right now.
I am free of his mind control.
Mind control?
I may be weak…
But as long as I have
the desire for strength,
I can become stronger.
No, I will become stronger!
Stop showing off!
That last one hit the spot,
didn't it, Snake?
You're not bad, Renji!
You guys…
We've come to our senses.
We won't continue
this silly battle anymore.
What's going on?
Muramasa…
It appears he was
controlling us Zanpakuto
by awakening our urges
and inciting them.
Are you saying that all the other
Zanpakuto are under his control?
It's very likely.
Ichigo… You saved me this time.
My other self helped too.
What are you going to do now?
It's obvious.
I'm going after Muramasa.
That's all.
I see.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
He might be the one…
It’s all thanks to me
that you won this battle!
So hear out my request!
What is it?
I demand a house
with a garden and
a garage built inside
your inner world!
I'd like a dog or a cat too.
A pure-bred at that!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
KUCHIKI MANSION
Let me know right away
if anyone is injured!
What's wrong?!
Hurry up and save him!
Are you all right?!
Hang in there!
Are you with me?
Get some warm water right away!