Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
This is revenge.
The Bounts were created by…
Soul Society!
What was that just now?!
It sounded like it came from the back?
Do you suppose it's Ichigo
and the others?
Judging from the volume,
it sounds like a fierce battle.
I can't stay here. I've got to go on.
Kuchiki, you shouldn't
push yourself yet!
But…
What's wrong, Sado?
You…
What did you say?!
Long ago, Soul Society performed
a certain experiment.
We're not sure what its purpose was…
But it's clear that at the time
they only thought of humans
as test subjects.
The name of the one who was responsible
for this great crime is in the records.
Anyway, "that" began
because of his madness.
There was a sudden, giant explosion.
Something created by that
unexpected phenomenon
mutated certain souls
in the cycle of rebirth.
And those with different abilities
began to appear
in the World of the Living during a certain
time period all over the world.
Those are the Bounts.
At first, we worried
about our differences.
Everyday we worried that
those around us would notice.
But it was not something we could hide.
Though we were human, we were called
demons and monsters.
We were forced to live
in a world of darkness.
And when Soul Society learned
of our existence
they kindly gave us a hand.
But that was just a part of their plan.
Without that knowledge, many of us
tried to live with the Soul Reapers.
This tunnel is a capital
where our many comrades lived
in secrecy to escape persecution.
It's pretty big, isn't it?
That's how many of us there were.
But now there are only a few.
You understand, don't you?
They used dirty tricks
to try to erase us from history.
We will never ever
forgive them… Soul Society…
The Bounts wish for the annihilation
of Soul Society!
This is the truth.
I don't understand.
Soul Society did something to you…
But…
No matter what horrible things
happened to you,
you shouldn't take the lives
of your fellow…
Humans!
I can't forgive you!
Getsugatensho!
You had this much power left?
But this is it…
What?!
Bastard!
It's useless.
You don't have the power to defeat me.
Living souls have given me
even greater power.
We Bounts can keep growing stronger.
Soul Society's Soul Reapers
are insignificant!
They'll soon kneel before us!
Damn!
Is this it?
No…
I…
didn't come all this way…
by myself.
I won't…
let it end in a place like this!
Zangetsu…
Zangetsu? Is that the name
of the zanpakuto?
Heh… Shut up…
What…are you doing?
I hear that a Soul Reaper's zanpakuto
is like the alter ego of that Soul Reaper.
Would you consider it a partner?
How about being killed by that partner?
Bastard…
I'm going to finish you off
with this blade.
Say…
Zangetsu…
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Show yourself…
What…are you doing?!
Zangetsu!
Old Man…
Are you prepared?
I really might have been
relying on you too much.
I've had my Bankai if things got bad.
I've even been told that by Urahara,
so I must have thought that
somewhere within my heart.
A Bankai is…
the extreme readiness
that involves blades and pain.
Don't be afraid, Ichigo!
Your blade will dim
if you have hesitations.
You once gained power
with an unwavering heart.
I will ask you once more…
What are you preparing to do?
Why are you fighting?
For whom do you want the power?
I remembered…
I wanted to become a Soul Reaper in
order to protect those important to me.
I was able to get a hold of my Bankai
by swearing on my soul…
That I was prepared to shorten my life.
Zangetsu…lend me your power!
The power to protect everyone!
I am your power…
Trust your own power!
Yeah…
You! What did you do?!
Here I go! This is
what I'm prepared to do!
Bankai!
Tensa Zangetsu!
A…Bankai?!
Master Kariya!
Don't make a fuss, Ichinose!
Concentrate on controlling
the Senkaimon!
He'll come soon!
I understand.
Stand!
I can see you…
It's past here!
Yes. Let's hurry!
Don't rush in!
You dodged that well.
Hmm…
Indeed, it's worth being
boastful about.
Let's end this now.
Fine…
What the--?!
Ishida…
– Kurosaki!
– Ichigo, are you all right?!
Inoue! Chad! Rukia!
But…
Ishida… that look…
I can't remain a burden to you forever.
Your Quincy powers have returned?
Not completely.
I've heard that…
this is a battle accessory which was
passed down between some Quincies
several hundred years ago.
It has the power to control reishi!
Oh?
Don't miss this time, Quincy!
I didn't miss that earlier shot.
Ishida…
Hirenkyaku…
It seems your power has really returned.
Ichinose! Are you prepared yet?!
Yes…
Here you go…
"Mache sogleich das tor,
fur unsere bount auf!"
– What do you plan to do?!
– Don't move, Kurosaki!
What are you going to do?!
It's opened, Ishida!
No…it hasn't opened yet.
So what are you going to do, Quincy?
Are you all right, Inoue?
Th-Thank you, Sado.
Oh? What is Ishida going to do?
I wonder if Ishida is going to
destroy that gate.
– Ah! It's as I expected of him!
– That's a good idea!
– Give it your best! I'm with you!
– Ishida, do it!
What's with…this odd feeling?
Ishida, you…
Sorry, Kurosaki…
Let me do what I want to.
I thank you, Quincy boy.
Now we can finally go.
Wh-What are you talking about--?!
It means that the path to Soul Society
has just opened.
What?!
– So you did know…Quincy.
– Yeah…
The Soul Reaper who gave me
this Quincy power told me.
Also about why you were persistently
chasing after me.
I see…
A Bount who gains concentrated souls
can open spaces to different dimensions.
But one must convert their body to
Reishi in order to go to Soul Society.
Unfortunately, we don't have that power.
But there are a few among the Quincies
who can freely control reishi.
If we use the arrow of the person
who has that power as a conductor…
Reishi conversion is possible.
Then…that thing earlier was…
Yeah. The Kojaku arrow I released
earlier passed through the Senkaimon
to make it into a reishi conversion gate
that would convert them into souls.
Ishida! Why are you helping them?!
I believed that you would come…
Like the Bounts, Soul Society is
an enemy to the Quincies.
But I was really disappointed
when I learned
that you had lost your powers.
But Yoshino supported you
in a good way.
I'm grateful to her.
She not only got us Bitto, but was able
to lead your Quincy powers back to me.
And you've regained
your Quincy powers.
Now let's walk together,
the Last Quincy.
Don't get the wrong idea, Kariya!
I'm letting you go to Soul Society
so I can settle this with you there!
So you're avenging Yoshino?
How silly…
Can't you see the bigger picture?
I'm going to defeat you!
On my pride as a Quincy!
Well…that's fine too.
Master Kariya!
It seems it's time…
Quincy! Soul Reaper Boy!
Follow us if you want to!
We'll be waiting on the other side!
Ishida!
What do you think you're doing?!
Ichigo! Ishida!
Yoruichi…
I was too late…
– Kurosaki!
– Ishida!
What in the world happened?!
Ishida…you've done
a troublesome thing.
Why? Why did you do it?
Kurosaki…
Indeed, you've regained
your Bankai power
but would we have been able to
defeat him if we continued fighting?
Wha--?! Well…
We don't know that unless we try!
It would have probably been difficult!
Yoruichi…
This…
This is all I have…
to defeat him!
Indeed… This is a Quincy's power.
But I cannot defeat him…Kariya,
with this level of power.
That tool forcefully gathers the reishi
that exists in the air and forces it out.
Since there's little reishi
in the World of the Living,
this is probably
the best you can do.
But what would happen in Soul Society
where everything is made of reishi?
I knew what was going to happen
if I tried to settle this here.
But if we go to Soul Society…
Like I said earlier,
that kind of thinking is shallow!
Quincies and Soul Reapers
aren't the only things
that become more powerful
in Soul Society!
Bounts also get stronger!
What do you mean, Yoruichi?!
If they go to Soul Society,
where all matter is made of reishi…
they can absorb all the reishi
they want!
What?!
– This is awful…
– And Ishida,
do you know what kind of thing
that Quincy tool is?
Yes. It forcefully brings out
a Quincy's power.
Its power isn't stable.
I don't know when it'll stop working.
But…
Even so, I need this power!
What you did may lead to
the destruction of the world!
What are you doing, Kurosaki?!
Ishida, why are you taking your time?!
Let's go to Soul Society!
Kurosaki…
You should do what you wanted to do!
We'll cover the rest for you!
Jeez. You're all so hopeless.
Thank you…
You all…
Well, we've come this far.
It can't be helped.
We have to finish this by mobilizing
all of Soul Society's Soul Reapers.
That may be the best thing to do.
Soul Society was the one
who created the Bounts.
Soul Society
needs to take responsibility,
even if it has to see blood
or become wounded.
Hey!
– Renji!
– You're safe!
Of course I am!
Don't just kill me off!
Where are the Bounts?
You're too late.
We've failed our mission…
What an unbeautiful end.
Damn it…
We can pay them back in Soul Society!
Let's go!
But how? Sado and I…
Don't worry. There's the Senkaimon
that the Bounts left.
We can probably use it
if we adjust it a little.
Oh! I see…
Hold on a second.
Hello, Captain? It's me!
How are you?
What's going on?!
Hold just one second!
We're going, too!
There aren't Bount sensors there,
are there?
You're right…we'll be counting on you!
I-I guess I'll go back home.
It doesn't matter,
but you'll be home alone!
Home alone?
No!
Sister! Please take me!
Oh, I've asked captain,
so it's all right to go!
Please don't leave me alone!
All right! Let's go to Soul Society!
I see… This is reishi air.
It's better than I had imagined.
Now let's begin our revenge!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather
trust and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won’t get started if you don’t act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
We're about to charge into Soul Society!
I wonder if I can become friends with
some cute Soul Reaper girl.
Oh, I know! I've got to pay my respects
to Sister Rukia's family!
– Kon, I don't think you should.
– Why?
She has a big brother
who can't take jokes.
No…!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden After These Messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
– Hello?
– Hello, Captain?
It's me! How are you?
Matsumoto, huh? What is it?
I'm sorry!
We cornered the Bounts, but…
– They escaped to Soul Society!
– What?!
I'm taking Ichigo and the others back
with me. Could you file for permission?!
– Yeah…all ri--
– Oh! Also…
don't use your new teacup!
Matsumoto!
Shake My Hand in Soul Society!