Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Jeez…
The basis of the Zaraki Squad is
one-on-one battles.
Yumichika said that and
just left right away. Him aside…
Why would Shuhei and Kira also
go off as soon as we arrived?!
This trip to the World of the Living is
an order from my captain!
Doesn't that make me the leader?
I'm going to complain about them
to the Captain when I get back!
Isn't…
That's…
It sure is nice…to be young.
I think I'll take my time and have
a taste for the first time in a while.
Why do you suck the souls of
living people?
Who knows?
Stop attacking people!
I…want more power.
What do you plan to do
when you gain power?
What I'll do…?
I can't tell you…
Hey there!
It's been a while!
How have you been, Chad?
Rangiku… Why are you here?
Well… I'm really glad I met you!
It's seems that you're having
a bit of trouble here.
My captain suddenly told me
to come to the World of the Living.
I just arrived.
You know how Lieutenants like me can't
come to the World of the Living too often…
It's been so long, I don't know
what's going on at all.
But the World of the Living sure is great…
There are so many
interesting things going on.
Umm… Rangiku.
What? Oh. Are those two
friends of yours?
It seems like they're looking at me.
I'm Ururu.
Noba…
I'm Rangiku Matsumoto.
Lieutenant of Tenth Squad.
Pleased to meet you!
Pleased to meet you.
A pleasure.
So what are you all doing here?
A Bount.
A Bount?
Yeah…
That old man?
No mistake.
It's true, Soul Reaper Lady.
Really?
Oh, well.
I guess I'll show you…some proof.
Baura, let's go!
Is that your doll?
That's right.
What kind of joke is this?
His Spiritual Pressure…disappeared?
Noba… Do you sense anything?
Jump!
What…was that?
Whale?
A shark?
It looks like a rockfish.
It doesn't matter
what kind of fish it is!
There's no response!
Behind you!
Rangiku!
Noba!
Ow…ow…ow…
Thank you!
What's with that?!
I'm thanking you!
Look this way…
Hey, you!
He's bashful.
You've escaped death.
Let me introduce him.
This is my doll, Baura.
You called me out on a nice night.
It feels good.
It talked?
Dolls have their own minds.
Humph…I see.
Baura can control space.
He can create
special alternate dimensional spaces
and swim freely within them.
It seems that boy over there
has a similar ability.
Even so. His power is outclassed.
Are you sure about that?
What an arrogant boy!
Shall we show him
our difference in power,
Baura?
We're the ones who are going to
show you our difference in power!
Growl! Haineko!
Baura!
Okay, Boss.
Come back!
Rangiku… Why?
That Soul Reaper's judgment
was correct.
If she didn't return that ash,
Baura would have eaten it all.
She would have lost her Zanpakuto.
What?!
It seems his mouth is also connected
to an alternate dimensional space.
Just when I thought I was going to get
a Soul Reaper's Zanpakuto.
Yes, Ms Rangiku Matsumoto.
What can I do for you?
Freeze the space up to 300 meters
around me!
And soul protection!
Understood.
Help Kira and Shuhei in the same way!
Yes! But we have a report that
Lieutenant Abarai charged into battle
without soul protection
and was injured while protecting
a human.
Renji?!
What's wrong?
It seems that everyone is
having a difficult time.
The space around here has been
protected by the power of Soul Society.
Now we can let loose!
I see…
All right!
Hado 4! Byakurai!
It's pointless to attack him
while he's in a dimensional space!
He went your way!
You're being pesky!
That girl's pretty good!
This way!
He sucked in the attack.
It's useless from the front.
What should we do?
Noba, I've been wondering,
you know when he's going to attack?
He creates ripples in space,
when he surfaces from
the alternate dimensional space.
Can you predict in advance?
I only sense him
right before he appears.
Which means we can only manage
to just barely dodge.
How does he know where we are?
He is probably utilizing something
like sonar radar.
Sonar radar?
I sense a subtle wave of spiritual
pressure from within the ground.
Then can't we trace that
to find where he is?
It's too weak.
We can't do anything?
He chases us by swimming
through the ground.
It seems all right
if we're in a high place.
Let's think of a plan in the meanwhile.
Yes!
Ururu!
Ururu!!
I'm so glad that you're safe.
Ururu!
Chad!
This way!
Where is he?
He's not behind us.
What's with him?
Does that mean that it doesn't matter
if it's high or low, but it works, as
long as there's a wide surface?
That's right.
One down.
The little lady is safe.
Baura's belly is connected to
an alternate dimensional space.
I'm having her stay there for a while.
But…
she can't live there
for long periods of time.
What?
Bounts usually only eat souls.
But only Baura and I can
engulf, dissolve and absorb
an entire human body.
You bastard…
Give Ururu back!
You're next!
I'm going to devour you
into Baura's space one by one.
Go, Baura!
Okay.
I won't let you!
Roar, Haineko!!
It doesn't matter! Just swallow them!
What?!
Diving into the ground was
your specialty, wasn't it?
Y-You bastard!
And…
you should watch your head!
What?!
Blasted Soul Reaper.
She's making a fool of me!
They haven't gone that far.
We're going after them, Baura!
Okay.
Is it really safe here?
It should be safe.
He can't make any exits in space if
he doesn't have a space wide enough.
Is that so?
I sense enormous energy
when he moves through space.
He can't physically open it up
in cramped spaces.
Chad!
I won't tell you not to worry,
but this is not your fault.
My power is…
It should be the power
to protect someone.
At this rate…
Find out why you have those…
big strong fists.
I'll hit him for you.
I'll risk my life to protect it if it's
something you'd risk your life to do.
At this rate…there's no meaning to it.
Chad…you…
Now let's go save Ururu.
Calm down.
What were you planning to do?
Do you have some sort of plan?
I would take her place.
Out of the question!
There's no way that he'd release
Ururu because of that!
They only think of humans as food!
We've got to think of a plan.
Umm…
What?
I can suck him into my space.
Tell me more!
He has an alternate dimensional space
within his body.
I'll extinguish his energy by
surrounding him with my power.
If I do that, I should be able to move
everything he's swallowed through space.
Is that possible?
It should work in the same way
that alternate dimensional spaces
are created by spiritual energy.
It's possible.
Hmm… That's the only method, huh?
All right. What should we do?
I want you to lure him in front of me
without him noticing.
All right. I'll be the decoy.
Wait!
I'll be the decoy!
Support me from the back!
But…
Then you'll be in danger!
Chad!
Who do you think you're talking to?
A-All right…
All right! Then, let's go!
Come on! Both of you, stop wasting time.
Come on all ready!
Hey, Gramps!
You're nearby, aren't you?!
Come out already!
I'm right here!
Your attacks are predictable!
Hold on, Chad! Stop!
I can't tell where he is!
Wh-What's wrong, Baura?!
What?!
You fell for it!
Boy!
Curse you youngsters!
Do you know how many souls I've sucked
in order to gain this power?!
I won't lose to the likes of you!
What?!
Noba!
No problem.
Thank goodness…
Are you all right?
Where's Ururu?
Yeah… Immediately.
What's wrong, Noba?!
Noba?!
Noba!
Don't come near me…
Could it be?!
What?!
Noba--!
Get a hold of yourself!
Noba…
You've been quite entertaining,
but you're 100 years too early
to be sealing us away.
Shall we put an end to this already?
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
I'm hungry…
Why don't we all go out to eat
after we defeat those Bounts?
I want to eat a sashimi meal.
I'll have a fried fish meal.
I want something refined,
like boiled fish and a drink!
How can you eat fish
after fighting someone like that?
No problem.
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers after these messages!!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
We've received a report from
the Seventh Seat, Yamada.
I see. So what does it say?
Yes! Well, that bastard… Oh, I mean,
Yamada is blathering on… I mean,
he says that he's got a part time job
in the World of the Living and that
every day is fun.
Really… I'm envious.
I mean, he's slacking off
while we have to handle strenuous tasks
like this everyday. Yes!
I see. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Really. I can't believe him--!
He seems to be enjoying himself…
Tune in again!