I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Rioters have gathered at
Hakuto Gate
and Kokuryo Gate.
Hurry to your defense positions.
I repeat…
Rioters have gathered at
Hakuto Gate and
Kokuryo Gate.
Hurry to your defense positions.
Are you ready you bastards--?!
All right, don't let up!
We did it! We did it, Kariya!
Yes…you did…
All right, all of you!
Riot away as you please
in Seireitei!
Stop right there!
You're not passing this point!
Who's the Ryoka?!
There're Soul Reapers!
What?!
H-Halt! We're not letting you in!
Don't move!
Get him!
Kariya, that's an amazing technique!
Good work.
Huh?
Unfortunately, this is where
we part ways.
Wait! What kind of joke is that?
We were going to…
I said that your role is over.
What are you talking about?!
Weren't we going to
crush Seireitei together?!
You're just a pawn.
Or, to put it another way,
you're just a means to open this gate.
Seireiheki shuts out
all spiritual power.
In other words,
it is impossible to destroy it
or pass through it
using spiritual power.
You bastard!
You were using us!
I'm just saying that
you're of no use now.
From this point on,
it's my tribe's battle.
You're just in the way
if you linger around.
What do you mean?!
No way!
We've been tricked!
You bastard!
We can't back down now!
Let's go, everyone!
I told you that you're in the way.
Let's go.
Jidanbo!
The gate is open?!
What is that device?
Kariya!
The gate!
Damn! We let him get away!
They call themselves Soul Reapers?
They're pathetic.
The real battle is about to begin.
Don't underestimate the captains.
I told Mabashi and Yoshi
to create diversions.
You two crush each squad captain
one by one
while Mabashi and Yoshi
are causing riots.
What about you?
Our final goal is to completely
destroy Seireitei. Instantaneously.
They created us,
and yet they tried to wipe away
our existence.
Judgment must be passed
upon the Seireitei for their actions.
But we need something in
order to do that.
I'm going to go and get that.
Are you saying that
there's something
with that kind of destructive force
in Soul Society?
There is.
Where is it?
At the Department of Research
and Development.
What is it?
You'll soon find out…
Our final meeting place
is the Sokyoku Hill. Got it?
What is it? If you have something
to say, then say it.
No… Good luck…
Go.
Jidanbo… Get ahold of yourself…
Thank goodness!
Ah…you're…
It's been a while.
What's this?
You saved me again?
It was nothing… Does it still hurt?
No, everything's all right!
Ichigo!
It's no good…
As expected, it'll take time for
the seireiheki to be fully open.
I see…
Oh well… Jidanbo!
Sorry that you're injured,
but could you open the gate?!
Ah! Of course!
Wait a second!
Thanks, Jidanbo!
Let's go!
Hey! Are you all right?!
I'm all right! Go quickly!
His wounds have opened…
Let's go, everyone!
He's trying his best in spite
of his wounds!
Don't let his efforts go to waste!
Thanks, Jidanbo!
Inoue, quickly!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Kurosaki! I'm staying back!
I have to heal Jidanbo!
Orihime!
Well, what kind consideration…
Kurodo, go with everyone else!
What?!
No way…
Inoue, is that all right?
Yeah! I'm all right!
Leave it to me!
Jidanbo, you can let go now.
Thanks…
Take care of him, Inoue!
Yeah!
Orihime!
Orihime! How could you?!
Inoue stayed back
because she wanted to.
Take her feelings into consideration…
But…
Besides, there's a reason
she left you with us.
What?
Lirin, how are the Spiritual Pressure
of the Bounts?
Hmm… I don't sense any right now.
I wonder if they're hiding it.
I see… But they've come
this far with a goal.
They can't hide their
Spiritual Pressure forever.
You're the ones who can sense
the Bounts the best.
Well, that's right, but…
We need your help!
Kurodo, we're counting on you!
Hmm… I understand!
If that's the case,
then I'll trust Orihime and
give it my all to search for the Bounts…
I will find them…
Man, once his mouth opens…
…and crush
he just doesn’t stop.
their plan.
Yeah…
In Soul Society…
Split up! Right now,
we have to track the Bounts!
All right!
We will, too…
Yes!
Captain…
A hell butterfly--?
Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
In accordance with
special order level one,
all captains are
urgently summoned.
We will hold a captains' meeting.
I repeat…
Thirteen Court Guard Squads…
In accordance with
special order level one,
all captains are
urgently summoned.
We will hold a captains' meeting.
At a time like this!
Continue dispatching to
the assigned areas!
We can only keep searching
until we find them!
When you do find them,
don't approach them immediately!
Contact other groups and wait for help!
That's all!
Yes!
Aw man! I'm not
getting any hits at all!
Just keep searching!
Damn… Where did Kariya go?!
Ichigo, you're so hyped up!
What good is it not to be hyped
at a time like this?!
No! Calm down a bit!
Huh? Why--?
My sensors don't work properly with
someone who's worked up next to me!
Is that so?
Yes!
All right!
How is it?
Not yet.
Really! You run a lot more
roughly than Orihime. Jeez!
Stop complaining!
Hey… You're the Punishment Force,
aren't you?
Are you a Ryoka?
A Ryoka?
Who knows?
Forget that, I heard you guys
are strong…
Oh? You want to fight, huh?
Zeige Dich, Ritze.
Ritze, go!
Understood!
Damn!
Don't let him get away!
Where is Captain Jushiro Ukitake
of Squad 13?
He's sleeping. It seems that
he's not feeling well again…
I see… Squad 2 Captain.
Yes!
Tell me the status of
the Punishment Force…
I have already positioned groups
throughout Seireitei.
Very good… A very quick response.
Yes!
So what has the captain of
Squad 10 done in comparison
to the Punishment Force?
I heard that he was the commander
for the annihilation of the Ryoka…
But it seems that he allowed them
to invade Seireitei.
He has some nerve,
calling himself a commander…
I won't make excuses.
It is all my fault.
Now, now. It can't be helped
that they got in.
We've got to think of what to do next.
Captain Kuchiki. It seems that
you fought the man called Kariya…
I heard that he's their boss.
I want you to reveal what
you know to everyone.
He can control wind.
Wind?
Furthermore, he can control reishi
and has a powerful regenerative ability.
Don't change the topic!
I was saying that we should
question the responsibility
of the captain of Squad 10.
I've heard about it…
About what?
About a Quincy tool…
They were able to come here because
someone gave them a Quincy tool
that was in the Department of Research
and Development…
That was probably all a set up…
What are you trying to say?
No, I was just thinking that
you're good at ignoring
your own shortcomings.
Think about other peoples'
feelings a little.
I am also irritated right now!
And I know how to
take responsibility.
That aside, where did you
hear about that?!
I have sharp ears…
This is not the time
to be quarreling!
This is an order!
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are to spread out within Seireitei…
and destroy the Ryoka when
they find them!
It is best if we deal with
the Ryoka as soon as possible.
Therefore, from now on,
each squad will take their own actions.
The Squad 10 captain will be relieved
of his duties as temporary commander.
Reports are to be done quickly
and immediately. That is all.
Master Mayuri, are you
going out in person?
Of course! I hate being made fun
of more than anything!
Jeez. Time was wasted on
that unnecessary captains' meeting!
Don't think this is over, Bounts!
I'm leaving you in charge!
Do what needs to be done!
Yes, Master Mayuri.
What's wrong?!
I sense a Bount!
What?! Where?!
Now it disappeared!
You're not just
saying things, are you?
How rude! I was positive!
Damn! Curse those Bounts
for sneaking around!
Guerrilla warfare is most effective
when taking on an army
with a few people.
It's reasonable.
The enemy is pretty good…
What good will it do
to praise them?
Excuse me…
Anyway, let's hurry to the place
where you sensed them!
Which way is it?!
Yes, yes! Turn right at that corner!
Aw, man! It's appearing and
disappearing like an old flashlight!
This is so annoying!
You're pretty hyped up despite telling
me to calm down!
It's fine if it's me!
It doesn't matter if
I'm the one that's hyped up!
Jeez. That's so selfish…
Did you say something?
Nothing!
How is it?
I sense them.
Which way?
It disappeared…
I sense them.
Which way?
It disappeared…
Hey!
Yo..!
You're a Ryoka, aren't you?
What's with the scary faces?
You bastard!
Ritze!
I'm coming!
What's this?!
We're moving on, Ritze!
Understood!
Mabashi is doing well.
Now then, I should go as well.
Reporting! It appears that group two
and group three have met the Ryoka!
Did they get them?
The information is complicated.
The result is unknown.
How irritating…
I'm very sorry.
Go ahead of me! Gather all groups
at Seireitei's northern streets!
I will follow shortly!
Yes!
Group two and group three,
give me your reports…
Group two reporting!
The Ryoka we apprehended
got away.
Group three reporting!
We encountered a Ryoka at
Western Street Number Five.
We were unable to
apprehend him…
What are you doing?!
A level one guard position
has been ordered out!
What good will it do us if
the Punishment Force isn't
functioning properly?!
Ritze… It's about time…
Rearrange battle positions!
Groups one and two are to spread out
along the western streets!
Groups three and four are to make
a detour eastward
and head for the main road!
Yes!
Do it!
Captain!
Who did that?!
What's going on?
Hold him down!
You bastard!
Captain!
What's this?
What did you do?!
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Captain Komamura,
isn't it inconvenient
to have your lieutenant
out of commission?
It can't be helped. It's not as
if Tetsuzaemon wanted to be injured.
Shuhei isn't doing anything right now.
Do you want to hire him temporarily?
That would be helpful.
What about what he wants?
That's all right.
There are no rights for a lieutenant
in middle management.
Woah…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Damn! Where are those Ryoka!
I haven't had any appearances lately.
And now look at what happened!
Damn it! It's hot!
I'm going to be burned to ashes
by these flames!
Where are you, Ryoka! Come out!
I, Ikkaku Madarame, will take you on!
It's hot… It's hot, man…!
LET’S HAVE COMPASSION