Okay, see you tomorrow.
Careful on your way home,
Inoue.
Ichigo!
Yeah? Is it near?
Guess I'll have to…
Wait!
It's gone…
Huh?
Man, so many false alarms…
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Hey, Ichigo!
Ikkaku!
Stay here?!
What is this about?
Well, simply put,
we're on special assignment.
Special assignment?!
The other day,
Hollows used for
experiments got away
while being transported
under escort.
One of them seems to have
snuck into the World of the Living.
Oh, really? And?
We were given
the special assignment
of finding and
capturing the Hollow.
Why didn't they leave
that to us here?
Well, it's a Hollow
undergoing experiments,
so the higher ups ordered us to
capture it unharmed, if possible.
So that's the story.
We'll be counting on
your help for a while, Ichigo!
Huh? …How so?
Well, you know…
put us up for about a week.
Just a minute!
Who do you guys think you are,
dropping in out of the blue?
Don't decide on things yourself
when I'm not here!
Who do you think you are,
dropping in out of the blue?!
You have the gall
to talk like that!
This is now Sis and my love nest!
Get lost!
Um, Sis?
– Can you manage, Ichigo?
– Just so you know,
I'm kind of squished here.
I'm sorry,
but my place doesn't have
the room to put the two of you up.
In the first place,
you once said you
"had no intention of
asking me any favors."
So what's with the sudden
change of heart?
Well, that's…
Anyhow, you can't stay here!
OUT INDEFINITELY
THE OWNER
Looks like no one's in…
For crying out loud,
where'd he go?
Do you have anyone else
you can ask?
It's not that we don't, right?
No, we don't!
But in this case,
do we have a choice?
And that's the story.
Could you put up
these two again?
Okay, look after them.
W-W-W-Wait!
Come on, Ichigo!
What's with this, nonchalant, "Can
you pass the soy sauce" attitude?!
Well, you looked after
these two before, right?
You'll manage somehow!
Somehow?!
You talk as if it's
not your business!
That's how it is.
Be good to us.
Long time no see, eh?
Looks like you'll
get along just fine.
See ya!
How is this "getting along"?!
That was a threat no matter
how you look at it!
The baldhead itself is a threat!
I'm not bald, remember?
Oh yes, that's right…Sorry…
Hey! Keigo! What're you doing?
You're making too much noise!
You'll annoy the neighbors if you
make a ruckus by the front door…
Welcome home…Darling!
Did you just say
"welcome home"?!
Why're you treating him
like family?!
I left the front door open
all this time waiting for you.
How can you lie like that
without a second thought?!
Why're you playing
the devoted wife?!
Keep quiet, you.
Mind not interrupting
our fateful reunion?
I want to interrupt!
In fact, I want to
break up that fate!
How can you
accept him so easily?!
It's all right…
No matter what fate awaits us,
I will accept this hurt and lost
man without asking for a reason…
That's the kind of woman
I want to be.
And I don't care
a rat's ass about it.
It doesn't matter what type of
woman you want to become!
Besides, you already said that
to him before, remember?
Yeah, but I love shaved heads.
That's all it is!
He's not shaven,
he's bald, I'm telling you!
I keep telling you, I'm not bald!
Got that?
Yes, that's right. I'm sorry…
I'm getting tired of that banter…
Man…
They sure are a loud bunch…
That's why I didn't
want to come here.
Well, it's all right.
We'll be out most of the time,
and though this is
a special assignment,
we'll finish in about a week,
I'm sure…
Well, yeah…
The last time, he went
back home before I knew it…
This time I have to
capture his heart for sure
while he's still at our place…
To do that, I…
This is delicious!
I made it just for you…
Your wallet, cell phone,
handkerchief,
keys and your train pass.
Thank you.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Will you have a bath first,
or dinner?
I have both ready.
You are such a thoughtful woman…
I couldn't live without you…
Darling…
I call it my "Operation: Thoughtful
Woman Turns Her Man into Putty."
Flawless! It's Flawless, Mizuho!
Good morning, Darling!
Eat a good breakfast!
Yakiniku in the morning?
I can't eat this in the morning!
Is that so?
WHOLE SHARK'S FIN
Then would you like this?
What is that?!
Then how about this?
TENGU POWER
What are you trying to engage
in this early in the morning?!
Excellent Collagen!
Don't eat so willingly!
These trotters are
pretty good, too!
Who cares!
Oh, by the way,
where'd our clothes go?
The clothes you
had on yesterday?
I took those to the cleaners…
What?!
You're good to go!
It's not good!
Looks good on you, Ikkaku.
Shut up!
How come you're liking this?!
Don't hold it against me…
Just because I look great
in anything…
That's not what I'm talking about!
I have these, as well.
I ain't wearing any of those!
Man, this is really messing me up…
Well, as long as
we're staying there,
we'll have to put up with it.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Not really…
Anyway, let's get this
over with quickly
and return to the Soul Society!
What is it?
I think it's telling us the time…
Darling!
It's time for lunch!
How far are you going to
keep following me!
Man…
What's with that woman?!
I'll wash your back for you.
Huh?
Don't come inside!
What is it with you?!
Just mind your own business!
Listen!
If you do anything crazy again,
I'll kick your butt!
That…
That might be nice…
Wh-What the hell are you?!
If that woman's behavior
escalates any further,
we'll have no choice
but to leave here.
Do you have somewhere to go?
I don't want to be without
a place to stay.
At the very least,
we'll have to think of some
sort of countermeasure…
At this rate, the mission
is the least of our worries.
I know. I have an idea.
How's that?
What is this about? I don't get it!
Okay, look…
Yeah, but I love shaved heads.
In other words, if you wear a wig,
her interest in you will go away.
I can't wear something like this!
Oh?
You never know till you try.
It might work.
Looks great on you…
Dammit you are enjoying this!
N-No…not at all…
I'm doing it for your sake, Ikkaku…
I'll kill you!
Now, now…
I think that looks about right,
don't you think?
On second thought,
no way I'm wearing this thing…
I can't get it off?!
What's going on?
If it comes off easily,
it'll give it away.
Huh?
SUPER EXTRA STRENGTH GLUE
So I glued it on!
Damn you, Yumichika!
What're you gonna
do about this?!
Come back here!
Looks good on you, Ikkaku!
Are you all right?
Dammit, watch where
you're going!
Where the hell were you looking!
Oh, it's you, Ichigo…
Who're you?
What are you laughing at,
dammit…
You're laughing too much,
bastard!
No, what should I say,
it's just that…
Sorry…
I think it looks unexpectedly
good on you…
That's not convincing!
By the way,
how's your mission going?
Nothing so far…
We're looking for
its Spiritual Pressure,
but we haven't found a trace …
Man, don't you have it easy?
You asking for a fight?
No, not at all, but…
I can't waste my time
talking to you guys! Let's go.
See you.
Oh! So that was Ikkaku?
She only realized that now?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Darling, you must be hungry…
Who are you?
Can't you tell?
Huh?
Not "Huh?"!
It's me. Me!
What is this?!
You'd better take it off right now!
Stop it!
This can't be…
You have hair…why?
That's for me to decide!
Let's go, Yumichika.
What is this treatment?
Aren't you being mean,
treating me the same way?!
Be that as it may.
– It ain't right!
– It's not right!
More importantly…
how long are you people staying?
I want you out of here quickly.
It really was effective!
It's beyond effective!
Why does it turn out like this?!
It's too troublesome to explain…
I think it means she has absolutely
no interest in you with hair.
You mean the meaning
of my existence
is in my shaven head?!
Only that.
Fine! I'll leave!
I decline this place from my side!
I'd be glad if you did that.
I'm never taking off the wig
when I'm in front of you!
Remember that!
Remember a man who'd
grow out his hair,
even if it meant breaking
a woman's heart?
Forget it!
Sis…are you sure about this?
It's okay…
I told you…
I love shaved heads…
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy some juice.
Aah…we're sleeping outside,
after all…
That's okay.
This way is less stressful
from the start.
Sis?
I felt like getting
some juice, too.
Sis, you really ought to
be more honest with yourself.
I said I just wanted juice!
Y-Yes, ma'am…
Come on, let's go!
S-Sis…
What is it?
M-M-Monster!
Huh? Rain?
Sis, look out!
What're you doing, Keigo?!
Looks like it's the one
we're looking for.
Yeah!
Huh?
Somebody!
Somebody…
Hey! What's the matter?!
Sis is…
Something weird
attacked Sis…
Please save her!
What?!
Let's hurry.
What're you waiting for?
We have a mission to do, Ikkaku!
Guess I'll have to…
Why can't I come out?!
Huh?
This glue says it adheres the Gigai
and Konpaku to each other!
What the hell?!
Shit!
Then I'll just have to
will my way out!
What is this?
What's going on?
Was it a dream?
Thanks for letting us stay.
Darling!
If you come this way again,
you can stay at my place!
Oh, alright…
Guess I will then …
In exchange…
Just do something
about that hair, okay?
Quit nagging me…
What?
Why're you all laughing,
dammit! Hey!
If it rusts, you can never
stab with it again.
Grasp it incorrectly,
and it will rip you apart.
For you see,
pride resembles a blade.
In today's segment, we'll cover
Mayuri Kurotsuchi's Ashisogijizo.
Claw out, Ashisogijizo.
Ashisogijizo has the power
to take away the movement
of the four limbs of
the adversary it slashes.
Unlike paralysis, the feeling
of pain remains the same.
Its Bankai form is
Konjiki Ashisogijizo.
This scatters a lethal poison
over a wide area.
Hmm…that's a fine explanation.
I'll give you candy as a reward.
Stop treating me like a child!
It's apple-flavored poison candy.
Don't want any!