With the disappearance of
the Spiritual Pressures of
Squad 9 Captain Kensei Muguruma
and his lieutenant, Mashiro Kuna,
the vanishing konpaku case,
wherein Rukon district residents
vanished leaving only their clothes behind,
became a major case involving
even the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
When Hirako and his group of five
who headed to the scene arrived,
they saw the figures of
Kensei and Mashiro,
who had transformed
into Hollow-like forms.
Kensei, who lost himself, attacks.
Hirako and the others fight back.
Suddenly however, Hiyori, too,
changes form.
You're…
Tosen!
Why did you do that to Kensei?
You betrayed him…
Your own captain?!
He didn't betray him.
He is loyal.
He just…
loyally followed my orders, that's all.
Please don't hold it against him,
Captain Hirako.
Ai…zen.
Aizen!
Damn it! You're doing this to me too?
In the end, remember one thing.
Betrayal you can see is trivial.
What is truly frightening is betrayal
you cannot see, Captain Hirako.
Goodbye.
You people were wonderful
test subjects.
Damn it!
Well…
What an interesting guest.
What brings you here?
Captain Urahara,
Kido Commander Tsukabishi?
This is bad. They found us.
I will kill them.
No, that won't be necessary.
But…
Kaname,
I said that won't be necessary.
Y-Yes, sir!
Please forgive my impudence.
K-Kisuke…
Why'd you come, you idiot?
What's with that vulgar mask?
That's right, say what you want.
Lieutenant Aizen.
Yes?
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
As you can see,
I just happened to find
the members of the investigation unit
in charge of the vanishing soul case
who were injured in battle,
and I was attempting to rescue them.
You bastard!
How can you lie
so shamelessly?
Why are you lying?
Lying?
Is there a problem with
a lieutenant helping his captain?
It's not that.
That's not what's bothering me.
Injured in battle?
You call these injuries?
You mustn't lie.
This is a Hollowfication.
The vanishing soul case…
Squad members disappearing
one after another as if erased.
And now, it's come to this.
Those were probably…
Hollowfication experiments.
By someone, you see.
But given the situation,
there might not be any need
to bewilder things by saying
"someone."
I see.
You are indeed
the man I thought you were.
I'm glad you came here tonight.
Gin, Kaname…
We've fulfilled our objective.
Let's go.
Wait, Aizen!
I'm not done talking to you.
Stand clear, Urahara!
Hado 88…
Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
Bakudo 81…
Danku.
That's impossible.
A lieutenant stopped my Kido
using Danku without an incantation?!
Forgive me!
It seems I let him get away.
Tessai…
What in the world is he?
Hirako!
Let's deal with Aizen and
the others later, Urahara!
Right now, we need to treat
Hirako and his group!
But…
With the Hollowfication
so far advanced,
we can't treat him here.
Urahara, it seems you know
something about this matter,
which you described with
the unfamiliar term "Hollowfication."
If that's so,
can I assume that you know
how to deal with this as well?
I do know.
Although the method
is a gamble.
Understood! Even so,
it's better than nothing!
We'll bring all eight of them
back to Squad 12's barracks
in their present condition.
With the facilities in the barracks,
we can save their lives.
In this condition?!
But how are you going to do that?
By using Time Stop
and Teleport.
What?
Both are forbidden techniques.
Their use is strictly banned.
That is why I'd like you to close
your eyes and ears for a moment.
Hollowfication is one of the outcomes
I arrived at
as I studied how to strengthen
the souls of Soul Reapers.
In the process,
I created a material
that instantaneously destroys and
then creates the boundary
between Hollows and Soul Reapers.
I will use that to treat
Hirako and the others.
What is that material?
I call it the Hogyoku.
Hogyoku.
What is this sensation of pressure?
Is it Spiritual Pressure?
No, it's not the same.
It is "presence."
The presence this stone possesses
is trying to push away my presence.
What on earth is this?
What has Urahara created?
Can Hirako and the others
really be saved using this?
No.
I've already told you.
The method is a gamble.
The likelihood that Hirako and the others
will return to the way they were
by using Hogyoku is,
even by a generous estimation,
about 20 percent, I'd say.
Twenty percent?!
If the series of
vanishing soul cases
was Lieutenant Aizen's doing,
then I'd assume that he never
even considered
the possibility of a treatment
for Hollowfication.
There is no other way,
but this.
Urahara.
I'm sorry, Tessai.
It failed.
I need to go outside to
get some fresh air.
What's going on?
Captain of Squad 12,
Kisuke Urahara!
And Kido Commander of
the Kido Corps,
Tessai Tsukabishi!
A warrant for your arrest
has been issued by Central 46!
Come with us!
What is the meaning of this?
I don't recall giving you
permission to speak.
You have been summoned here
for an inquest.
You are not to speak other
than in response to a question.
Is that understood,
captain of Squad 12?
Inquest?
Am I being suspected
of something?
I apologize.
Where were you last night
shortly after midnight?
In the forest of District 6
in West Fugai district.
Were you there conducting
Hollowfication experiments?
Just a minute!
Who told you such a thing?
You tested Hollowfication,
the results of your evil research,
on the captain of Squad 5,
as well as
seven other captain-class members
in the Fugai district.
So it is true?
You are indeed the man
I thought you were.
Who was it?
You do not have the right
to ask questions.
Was it Lieutenant Aizen?
That makes twice,
captain of Squad 12.
The next time,
we will add to the charges.
That was all his doing!
We went there to rescue
Hirako and the others!
When your lies go that far,
they become comical.
The lieutenant of Squad 5 never
left the Seireitei last night.
What?!
We have the statements of
124 squad members
and one captain.
That leaves no room for any doubt.
That can't be.
I have information to report!
Numerous traces of Hollowfication
experiments were found
in the research wing of
Squad 12's barracks!
That settles it.
I will pass sentence!
Kido Commader
Tessai Tsukabishi!
For the crime of using
a forbidden technique,
you are sentenced to imprisonment
in Underground Prison 3: Shugo.
Captain of Squad 12,
Kisuke Urahara!
For the crime of conducting research on
and applying taboo phenomena
to deceive and cause serious injury
to your fellow squad members,
you are sentenced to eternal banishment
to the World of the Living
after you have been stripped
of all Spiritual Power!
Furthermore,
the pitiful captain of Squad 5
along with the other seven
captain-class members,
who became the victims of
your heinous experiments
will be dealt with severely
as Hollows!
But that's…
Just a minute!
Who are you?!
Who gave you permission
to enter the conference room
while proceedings are in progress?!
Leave this place immediately,
lowly oaf!
C-Capture them!
Intruder!
Someone!
Isn't anyone there?!
Somebody!
Th-Thank you.
Yoruichi.
You don't need to thank me.
I'll even save the swift kick
I was going to give you
for not saying a word to me
last night for later.
I brought all eight of them here.
And the new Gigai prototype
you were working on as well.
Get started on it.
From the moment you heard about
this incident from Hirako,
you envisioned
the worst-case scenario.
And you also came up with
the best solution to counter that.
You saw through everything, I see.
You are a nasty one.
Look who's talking.
Tessai, put a Time Stop
on Hirako and the others.
Then place a double and
triple barrier around this place.
Starting now, for the next 20 hours,
you and I will build
a total of ten Gigai built
with Spiritual Pressure masking function
for the two of us,
and Hirako and the others.
What about you, Yoruichi?
Don't worry about me.
I can always manage to get away.
We'll lay low
in the World of the Living
and take our time to
solve the mystery.
We will, without fail,
find a way to undo
this Hollowfication.
Kisuke did say,
"there were no miscalculations."
That was the biggest
miscalculation of all.
As expected, everything turned out
in the worst possible way.
Man, we sure owe Kisuke…
and Aizen too.
Let's go.
When evil intentions pervade society,
a warrior for hope who operates
above the law appears without fail.
His cape fluttering in the wind
is a symbol of justice.
Career Change!
Go, Konso Cop Karakuriser!
Next time: "I'm reluctant, but I will
protect the peace in Karakura Town!"
Watch for it!
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
Substitute Soul Reapers sometimes
hold on to things for Soul Reapers.
I came to pick up my Gigai.
Why'd you leave them
at my place?
Because if I left them at
Mr. Urahara place,
he'd make me work for free as
payment for holding on to them.
What in the world?!
The truth is…
The other day, I spilled curry in
the closet and made a mess.
So I asked Ishida to fix it up.
Why is it a dress?!