Naturally, your only option is
to approach from that side.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Kick about, Los Lobos!
You dodged it...
Your release isn't just
for show, I see.
Why, thank you.
I went through the trouble
of doing a sword release.
You will show me your "Bankai."
Cero Metralleta...
Running away is no
use, you know.
Wait! Wait a minute!
I won't wait.
A Cero should be effective
if I shoot it like this.
Don't you agree?
Isn't that cheating?
No it's not.
Oh, have you had enough?
How about doing your
"Bankai," Captain?
At this rate...
Damn...
I took too much damage.
Are you all right, Captain?!
I don't need your help.
Good grief...
You should just humbly accept
your subordinate's kindness.
Did you say something?
No! Nothing...
But I must say...
That guy was scary,
wouldn't you say, Captain?
Captain?
It's all in the past now.
Sogyonokotowari.
Ukitake...
Did he fire a Cero just now?
That was definitely a Cero...
Ukitake...
No arguments.
It's like there are two
of them anyways.
So it won't be cowardly
if I assist.
And I get the sense you have
no intention of using Bankai.
Actually, I was about to...
No, you'd better not.
Your Bankai shouldn't be used
in a place like this,
where people might see it.
Besides, against an enemy like this...
My abilities would be more effective.
Hey, you...
Not you.
The captain with the white hair.
Me?
That's right.
How did you shoot that
Cero just now?
Gosh, I wonder how...
If you shoot again, maybe
you'll find out?
I see.
You have a point.
Don't you get it?
It's a trap, Stark.
This is a...
Stark! Are you listening?! Stark!
Shut up.
You see!
He shot back, just like I said!
That's why I told you! Are you
listening to me, Stark?
I see.
Your ability is to absorb
an enemy's attack
and return it directly
to the attacker.
But that's not all.
Those five charms hanging
from the cord can
adjust the speed and pressure
of the returning technique
to throw off the opponent.
Just enough that the opponent
can't time when to dodge.
It's a much more malicious ability
than it looks, Captain.
Amazing!
I never thought you'd figure out that
much from just three attempts!
Why thank you...
But I'm glad
that your power wasn't just
some ability that reflected
an attack back without
any rhyme or reason.
If you're sending attacks back
after absorbing them first,
there has to be a limit to
what you can absorb.
If I instantaneously fired
a thousand shots at you,
you probably couldn't
return them.
I told you not to act
uncharacteristically, Captain!
I don't appreciate you telling me
what's characteristic, Mr. Espada.
And if you're going to talk
about characteristic,
then my "characteristic" is
being uncharacteristic.
And here I thought you
and I were alike.
There!
Wrong.
So your plan is to stay close
so I can't fire repeatedly.
In that case...
Now you can't get near...
Naturally, your only option is
to approach from that side.
You're good, all right...
I thought it was odd of you
to get cornered so easily.
So that was your plan, huh?
Did anyone say he
was fighting alone?
How's your body holding
up, Ukitake?
Couldn't be better!
You bastards!
Two on one is unfair!
Come one at a time!
What are you talking about?!
There are two of you, too!
There is nothing unfair about it.
But never mind that and
stop fighting this instant!
You're still saying that?!
Oh, I've had it! I hate this guy!
Stark, let's kill this
guy right now!
Okay, okay. I do want to get
it over with quickly, but...
This time, I'll see to it
from the start
that he can't get near us.
Ukitake...
Yeah.
Wh-What?
What is that huge Garganta?!
It can't be...
At a time like this?
A Garganta!
Enemy reinforcements?!
You mean there are more
of them who can come
to the aid of the three Espada?
That's not a pleasant thought.
Who the hell is that?
That's one creepy fellow...
Wonderweiss...
Something else is coming out!
C-Captain!
What?
N-No way...
That eye...
It's the one from back then.
Let's get out of here, Captain!
Quiet.
What is that?!
Sorry.
The fact that this guy appeared
means that Lord Aizen
can't wait any longer.
Shunsui! Jushiro!
That can't be...
C-Captain...
Captain Komamura...
We're good here... Please go.
Kira.
Please go!
Your presence here is keeping
us safe, Captain Komamura.
But our survival means
nothing...
if the rest of the squad
is wiped out!
A foul stench, as always.
Agreed.
This must be what people
call "the stench of death."
It's perfect.
The stench of death is fitting...
for what's happening before us.
We're finished...
We're really finished!
Hold it.
Rose!
I know!
You're mine now!
Bakudo Number Ninety Nine!
Restrict!
Shin...ji...
Let...
go of...
me!
You're...
Tosen!
He is loyal.
He just
loyally...
followed my orders, that's all.
Please don't hold it against
him, Captain Hirako.
Ai...zen...
Aizen!
Damn it! You're doing
this to me, too?
Aizen!
What is this?!
Maybe you should be
apologizing to your friends.
Because I chose you,
your friends ended up down
there on the ground with you.
As we thought,
it looks like an agitated state
accelerates the Hollowfication.
Hollowfication?!
What is that supposed to mean?
You don't need to know.
Let's end this...
Captain Hirako.
Here are my last words to you.
Betrayal you can see is trivial.
What is truly frightening
is betrayal you cannot see,
Captain Hirako.
Good-bye.
You were all wonderful
test subjects.
Damn it!
It's been awhile.
Aizen.
He's still screaming...
Sorry Kira, I can no longer
hold back my urges!
Captain Komamura?
Shut up!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Hmm... This is supposed
to be the place.
No one's here.
Ukitake said to meet up
here for our trip home.
Maybe that's them!
Excuse me!
S-Sorry...
What are you doing?
You didn't know what to
do so I tried to help!
Oh no, our plane's
about to depart.
"New Ending song starting
new week!"