Where were you, Gin?!
I'm going to become a Soul Reaper.
In that case...
I'll handle killing those kids.
Gin.
Kill'em, Kamishininoyari.
Gin... Damn you!
Gin...
It's over.
It's over now.
W-What is that?!
How would I know?!
I win, Gin.
Even without being inside of me, that Hogyoku you took...
...belongs to me.
What...the hell?!
If you were to turn into a snake tomorrow,
and began devouring humans,
and from the same mouth you devoured humans,
you cried out to me, "I love you!"
Would I still be able to say "I love you,"
the same way I do today?
This sensation...is Hakufuku.
Gin!
Yes...
I had already come across the answer known as the Hogyoku.
Even before Kisuke Urahara did.
However, it failed.
In order to complete the Hogyoku,
I gouged out the souls of hundreds of Soul Reapers
and hundreds of residents of the Rukon District
who possessed latent Soul Reaper powers
and gave them to the Hogyoku.
Yet even that did not satisfy the Hogyoku.
But judging from the results of his experiments,
Kisuke Urahara's Hogyoku was not complete either.
That being so, I decide to steal his Hogyoku and give it to mine.
By doing so...
Evolution requires fear.
The fear that, in your current state,
you could die and disappear at any moment.
Thank you, Gin.
Thanks to you, I have finally become a being
that transcends both Soul Reapers and Hollows.
W-What happened?
Maybe they had a falling out
and took each other down or something?
W-What is that?!
A-Arisawa? Kanonji!
Gin!
Where were you, Gin?!
Is that a Soul Reaper uniform?
Where did you get that?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to become a Soul Reaper.
I'm going to become a Soul Reaper and change things.
I'll fix it...
so you won't have to cry anymore, Rangiku.
Gin!
But I failed.
In the end...
I couldn't retrieve what was taken from you, Rangiku.
I'm glad.
Goodbye, Rangiku.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad I apologized.
Thanks...
Dad.
I-Is that...Ichigo?
It's Ichigo, right?
Why is his hair long?
Maybe it's because of the hair...
But...does he look a bit taller than before?
Good.
Yuzu and Karin seem to be okay.
Tatsuki. Keigo.
Mizuiro.
Honsho.
Kanonji.
Imoyama.
Who?!
I'm Kurumadani!
Zennosuke Kurumadani!
If you can't remember, at least be honest about it!
Don't name people based on your perceptions!
Everyone, stay where you are.
Stay still, right where you are.
W-What do you mean?
Ichigo...
I don't feel anything.
This isn't right.
I can feel his overwhelming power from the other guy.
But from Ichigo...I don't feel anything.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Are you really...
Ichigo Kurosaki?
What do you mean?
If you really are Ichigo Kurosaki...
then you're a disappointment.
I don't feel any Spiritual Pressure from you now.
Even if you're suppressing your Spiritual Pressure,
there's no way that I wouldn't notice it at all.
You failed to evolve.
You let the final chance that I gave you slip away.
For your own good... Get out of here.
You don't want to die yet, do you?
Ah...
Your eyes have more power in them.
That's good.
You are at a level now...
where I can die and leave the rest to you.
It's unfortunate, Kurosaki.
Aizen.
Let's do this elsewhere.
I don't want to fight here.
A meaningless suggestion.
Those are words only someone who has the
power to give me a challenge has the right to say.
There's no need to worry.
There will be no need to destroy Karakura Town. You will...
What?!
Impossible.
There's no way he could force me like this.
Let's do this, Aizen.
I'll end all of this
in an instant.
Let's do this, Aizen.
I'll end all of this in an instant.
End it in an instant?
I see.
I understand now, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Why you lost your Spiritual Pressure.
You didn't lose your Spiritual Pressure.
You discarded it.
I don't know how you did it,
but you converted all of your
Spiritual Pressure into your body's physical strength.
Arm strength, leg strength, grip, throwing, running...
In exchange for drastically improving
every one of your physical abilities,
you have discarded your Spiritual Pressure.
All because you gave up fighting me,
Spiritual Pressure versus Spiritual Pressure.
But...do despair.
I will teach you...
that the physical strength you were counting on
is incomparable to my own power.
What's that?
You parried that well.
How shocked you must be though.
The landscape changes with a single swing of my sword.
That is how powerful I am now.
To be honest, I didn't think my abilities had improved to this extent.
I'm happy, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Thanks to you,
I can test these powers that transcend those
of Hollows and Soul Reapers to my heart's content.
I'm not done yet, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Did you really think I couldn't follow your moves?
By some odd coincidence,
we seem to have arrived at a similar evolved form
where our right arms are combined with our Zanpakuto.
Perhaps this is the true form of the Zanpakuto.
What's so funny?
I realized it during our clash just now.
As I suspected, your evolution and mine are on different levels.
If I so wish...
I can shatter your Zanpakuto with a single swing!
Impossible!
He caught it?!
Dodging it, I could understand.
Though he shouldn't even be able to dodge at that speed to begin with.
Even so, dodging it, I could understand.
But...he caught it?!
He caught my blow?
Why so surprised?
Is it so unbelievable that I caught your sword?
What?
Does it scare you?
That something you can't
comprehend happened right  before your eyes?
Interesting, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Something I can't comprehend, you say?
Don't talk as though you've won.
It was simply a case of your physical strength momentarily exceeding mine.
Miracles like that happen from time to time.
But I am a being who surpasses even that.
In that case, I will see to it that miracles like that
never happen again by crushing you to pieces with Kido!
The oozing crest of corruption!
The arrogant vessel of madness!
Deny the seething urge...
Stun and flicker...
Disrupt the sleep!
The crawling queen of iron!
The eternally self-destructing doll of mud!
Unite! Repulse!
Fill the earth, and know your own powerlessness!
Hado Number 90: Kurohitsugi!
Now that I transcend both Hollows and Soul Reapers,
this is Kurohitsugi with a full incantation!
It unleashes enough gravity to warp time and space!
The likes of you could never comprehend it,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You don't seem to realize, do you?
My power is greater than the power you have right now.
The force that erased that mountain...
...was my sword.
Here I come, Aizen.
All Humans are an imitation of apes.
All Gods are an imitation of Humans.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
What's up! It's me, the Great Kon!
You're wondering why a
super star like me is lying on the ground like this?
When I woke up, I realized something strange happening to the town.
Not sure if it was safe to get up,
I decided to stay down and see how things go.
Huh? Looks like someone's coming.
I hope it's a cute girl. Oh, with big...
What is this?!
His eyeball is way too close. It's freaky!
What's going on?!
Someone help!