Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
I found you, Ishida!
I won't be satisfied until
I beat the hell outta you!
Right! You get it.
This is a fight between
you and me!
So quit harping on about
whoever kills the most Hollows!
Let's settle this between
you and me!
Say something, Ishida!
Hey Ichigo!
What is it?! I'm--!
The sky is…
What is that?!
Hollows are coming together.
Wait! There're so many!
You scared, Kurosaki?
Huh?
If you're scared, stay and watch.
I'm the victor of this match!
Over here, Hollows!
I, Uryu Ishida, the last Quincy,
will take you on!
The last Quincy?
The Quincy became extinct
200 years ago.
No, that’s not quite right.
To be exact…
the Quincy were destroyed
by the Soul Reapers.
This was a very difficult choice
for the Soul Reapers.
The Soul Reapers had to
destroy the Quincy…
in order to prevent the
destruction of this world.
In the Soul Society,
Soul Reapers were commonly
called Balancers, or regulators.
Regulators?
The sum of all the souls
in the Soul Society and the human
world does not change much.
And souls can travel between
the two worlds.
It is the job of Soul Reapers
to regulate that.
However, one day, the Quincy appeared.
The Quincy totally destroy Hollows.
This means that any soul
who left the Soul Society
for the human world would
never return.
If it were left as is,
the balance between
the two worlds would collapse!
And the two worlds would end.
There were many meetings between
the Quincy and Soul Reapers…
But the Quincy refused to
heed our pleas.
And the order was given
to annihilate the Quincy.
Do you think that this resulted from
the arrogance of Soul Reapers?
Damn! Their numbers aren't
going down.
Sensei…!
Ishida…!
H-He's so rash!
I heard… The reason why you fight!
I don't know who was right…
the Quincy or Soul Reapers.
And I don't intend to tell you!
But, one thing I do know!
Your ways are…
That story's old.
Huh?
I don't care about the
slaughter of 200 years ago.
I only heard it from
my teacher myself.
Furthermore, when I heard that story,
I sort of sided with the Soul Reapers.
That is, until my Sensei died…
Huh?!
I felt that the Quincy were at fault
for refusing to listen at all
to the Soul Reapers.
But why?!
It was the Quincy who were
annihilated.
You are right.
So many died.
And as long as there were casualties,
thinking about who was right or
who was wrong is meaningless.
What we must think about is
how we can prevent this from
ever happening again. That is all.
It's hard to see the sadness
in the faces of humans and Soul Reapers.
He was a kind, gentle man who
never hated or resented anyone!
As the last Quincy, Sensei was
under strict watch by the Soul Reapers.
And yet, Sensei kept telling
the Soul Reapers
to join forces and fight together.
But the answer was always the same:
"Do not interfere with our work."
Then...
on that day...
five huge Hollows appeared…
and it was obvious that he
couldn't take them on
without the help of Soul Reapers.
Soul Reapers only appeared two hours
after Sensei had begun to fight.
If they had listened to Sensei,
if they had acknowledged
his strengths, and his thoughts…
They would have come
to the rescue much sooner.
And Sensei wouldn't have had to die!
Can you understand,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
I must prove to the Soul Reapers,
the strength of the Quincy!
I realize that our ways of
thinking are at opposite poles.
If you think my way is wrong,
stay there and watch…
My true strength…
You talk too much!
What're you doing?!
I just don't get it!
Your teacher's hope wasn't
to prove the power
of the Quincy to the Soul Reapers…
It was to join forces with
the Soul Reapers to fight, right?!
Well then… Just when will you
be able to do that, if not now?!
Opposite poles? Fine!
When you have many opponents,
the best way to fight is back-to-back!
Good!
Don't get me wrong.
Unless I shot, I'd have been killed.
That’s fine!
Kill or be killed.
But it's too hard by yourself.
So it can't be helped.
Isn't that enough…
of a reason to join forces?
I just want to destroy Hollows.
Why?
My mother…
was killed by a Hollow.
Is that the reason why
I want to destroy Hollows?
If you ask that,
of course, it is. But…
I just don't want others
to go through what I did.
After my mother was killed,
my dad and my sisters went through a lot.
I just don't want any more of that.
I don't wanna see that anymore.
That's how I feel.
It's hard to see the
sadness in the faces…
I can't say bold things like
I'll protect all the people of the world…
But I don't want to just protect
those I can carry in my arms...
I want to protect lots
and lots of people!
Your way of doing this would
end up involving too many people!
No way!
But this is no time to be saying that.
We can only join together!
What do you say?!
Geez… you talk too much, too.
But I understand.
Unless we survive,
we won't have
a sparring partner for later.
Fine!
Kurosaki!
Huh?
The sky…
Sky?
What…is that?!
Huh?!
That's…!
W-What is that?
It's huge…
That bait can't have
this kind of result…
It's too late now!
Dammit!
H-Hello…
Jinta home run!
Kurosaki, we came to help you.
Hat-and-Clogs!
We'll take care of the small fry.
So that you, Kurosaki,
can concentrate on fighting that one.
Oops, you don't have time
to listen to my rambling.
It's Menos…
Menos?
A gigantic Hollow borne from
hundreds of Hollows mixed
and folded together…
But I've only seen such a thing
in illustrations in school books.
"Menos Grande."
I can't believe it!
That such a thing would come out…
This is the jurisdiction of
the Royal Special Task Force.
It's not something just
one Soul Reaper can take on!
Look at the size of that thing!
No sense in thinking about
how to fight such a giant.
What?
A thing like that…
has to be cut and cut again,
with all your strength!
There's no other way!
Let's do it, Ishida!
Hold it, Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Stop! He's not an opponent
you can take on!
Urahara! Do you
intend to kill Ichigo?!
Not at all. But just watch.
This battle…is necessary.
This is…a Binding Spell.
For you and him.
Kurosaki!
I told you so…
Dammit!
Kurosaki, can you stand?
Yeah, I'm sort of okay.
What were you thinking?!
Just how did you plan on
destroying that thing like that?
Well...
I figured if I kept cutting
him from the feet up,
the head would fall eventually.
This isn't “Pull the Blocks Out”!
Geez!
I can't believe the way you think!
Now stand…
and think up a new strategy.
What is…?!
It's flowing in…
Is this from Kurosaki's power?
A new strategy, huh?
Kurosaki!
Huh? Aghh!
W-What's with that arrow?!
How'd it get so big?!
Just listen!
We may be able to beat that thing.
Huh?!
Can you see Ishida…
and Ichigo, who's next to him?
Yes.
He asked that
we watch from here…
Does he mean watch,
and then choose…the path we walk?
Actually…Actually, I haven't
forgotten a single thing.
I could only doubt
my own memories.
Chad…
Hmm?
What are we supposed to do?
All right, now we can fight!
Hey, are you crazy?
What?!
Quit babbling!
In this situation, if you release
all your spiritual energy in this form,
I'll be able to shoot
an enormous arrow!
We can't waste all
that spiritual energy!
Don't say "waste."
Come on! Control your spiritual energy
and release it all at once!
How?
What? Can't you do that?
Then how did you fight
Hollows until now?
I just went with the flow.
The flow?! That's crazy!
I don't understand stuff like that!
If my spiritual energy is high,
isn't it always at maximum level?
Sero? Does he intend
to release Sero here?!
Run! Hurry!
If you get hit,
there'll be nothing left of you!
There's no other way!
Kurosaki, grab that
sword again and…
Kurosaki! What're you doing?!
What?!
What is this terrible Spirit Pressure?
Kurosaki's power
is increasing!
Isn't it always at maximum level?!
That's right, there's no way
that can be.
No matter how high
your spiritual energy,
if it's always at maximum…
the energy will burn out in no time!
If he can't control
his spiritual energy,
it means he always has
more than enough spiritual energy.
If you turn on a faucet and
a large amount of water flows out…
most people will quickly
turn it off.
If he's like that…
If his usual spiritual energy…
is always held back like that…
And if through some incident,
it gets turned on…
It's almost time, I think.
What?!
Menos is...
...turning back!
I win!
What the hell is he?!
Impressive! I can see why
the Boss had his eyes on him.
Yo!
What? At least say thanks.
I just saved your butt.
The least you can say is thanks.
I don't have any more strength…
W-Whaa--!
What's going on?!
The shape of the Zampakuto
is deteriorating!
It's because he released
his energy so suddenly!
At this rate,
his body won't hold up!
I must do something! I know!
This should do it…
If I release the spiritual energy
which Kurosaki is unable to control…
W-What're you doing?!
Shut up!
Your hand…it's tearing apart!
I told you, didn't I?
If we both don't survive,
I'll lose my sparring partner!
Stay alive, so that I can beat
the hell outta you!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
And you can do the same to me!
Forgive me, Sensei!
I tried to look away…
by hating Soul Reapers.
I didn't want to look at myself…
Because I couldn't save you.
Today, I will save a Soul Reaper.
Can you forgive me?
I couldn't give my life for you…
I'm a weak apprentice…
Please… can you forgive me?
Grandfather?
Sheesh…
How am I supposed to beat
a guy who looks like that?
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
Hey, how are you all?
I'm Kon, the superstar
of the world of Bleach!
After this comes
my own new corner!
Even the Soul Society is shocked!
Mr. Kon's Soul Reaper Dictionary
is about to start!
Stay tuned to this channel!
I never heard of such a thing!
It's for real this time!