Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
There!
Yay! Caught the cicada!
Done!
Bostov! Here, you have a new outfit!
See, isn’t it cute?! And on this…
I’ll stitch some embroidery,
with a pretty colored thread…
Huh…?
With a refreshing colored thread…
A kind and warm…
No, I don’t have the embroidery threads
that I want!
Wait just a while, okay, Bostov?
I’m going to go buy it right now!
Kon here.
It’s been a while since I’ve become
a stuffed animal in this house.
But…to have to wear that thing…
And on top of that,
to be forced to play house
with other stuffed animals…
Oh, I can’t take this anymore!
I’m going to run…
I’ve been made chummy with these guys!
And with red thread,
as if we are destined to be together!
What the heck is this?!
You’ve got to be kidding!
I can’t take this anymore!
BLEACH 50
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Spirits are al--!
You shouldn’t lick the sweet-sour liquid
that comes out of the cicada’s butt…
But I did it anyway.
Don’t link up with my line!
Once again, Spiri--!
You’ve got your car parked
in front of my house again;
you better not obstruct our business!
Oh, it’s been a while, Karakura Red!
Never mind that already…
What do you want, old man?
How cold.
We are comrades who protect
this world’s love and peace,
luv-pea for short, aren’t we?
It’s the middle of the day…
Aren’t you supposed to be working?
Uh-oh!
That’s a good question.
You see, TV shows are taped weeks
in advance of the broadcast.
Moreover, they’re off during
the Bon Festival season!
So, I’m off too!
You say so, but your show is over…
Uh-oh…
Could it be that it didn’t
make the ratings…?
Once again, uh-oh!
Wh-What are you saying,
Karakura Red?!
Never mind that…
Today, I have come to insist that
you participate in a special training session!
Special…training?
Yes! We need to train like hell to protect
this happy town from the bad spirits.
Whoa! That was close…
Well, let’s enjoy the special
training together!
Bohahahahaha!
Are you trying to hide something?
Uh-oh!
POPULARITY GRAPH
It’s something I don’t want
to acknowledge, but…
It’s true that lately, I, Don Kanonji,
have suffered plummeting popularity…
However, this will not be
the end of me!
No matter what it takes,
I’ll make a comeback!
In order to do that,
I must appeal to the hearts
of the masses…
by featuring the heartfelt performances
of my Kiddy Heroes!
For that, I must reunite
the Karakura Superheroes!
Isn’t that a waste of time?
You think so too?! Ah, no wait…
Nooo! Don’t go!
I’m begging you, Karakura Red!
Please, don’t forsake me!
Please help me!
Internal Medicine - Pediatrics
KUROSAKI CLINIC
The wings of freedom
are now in my hands…
Huh? They’re heavy…
Ouch… Oh, never mind!
Once I’m out,
I can do as I please!
I should skip out of this house now
while I can…
He saw me!
Good evening.
I am a robot…
Ah! Found a 100-yen coin!
Eh?! Where, where?!
You… You’re no ordinary
stuffed animal, are you?
N-No, it’s not like that…
See, see look! I'm completely
an ordinary stuffed animal.
You… Are you a bad spirit?!
Oh no!
I’m a pretty sailor stuffed animal, Bostov!
And here are my pals,
Buri and Puri!
So, anyway…
Good-bye!
Wait up!
I said good-bye!
I got you, bad spirit.
What are you doing?!
Stop sniffing me!
Don’t breathe down on me.
Strange smell!
But not a bad smell.
I got it!
You may be weird,
but not a bad spirit, correct?
Of course I’m not!
Don’t go confusing me with a Hollow!
When it comes to forming
a group of superheroes,
a mascot is a necessity!
If this stuffed animal joins us…
Catch me if you can!
The future of the Karakura Superheroes
is bright!
What? Don’t decide everything!
I was thinking out loud again!
Oh no, it must be
because of my age,
my brain must have gone weak…
What the heck are you
talking about?
Wait! How would you like
to become a hero of justice?
A hero? What?
Yes…! A Hero of Justice!
A Hero of Justice, huh?
Sir Kon, you’re so cool!
Hero of Justice!
I’m being squeezed by
so many lovely marshmallows!
So? What do you say?
Won’t you join
the Karakura Superheroes
and fight for justice?!
My name is Kon…
Also known as…the Karakura King!
Oh--!
Welcome, new member!
Mr. Don Kanonji! Bohahahaha!
Bohahahaha! All together now!
Bohahahaha!
It’s been awhile, Ichigo’s sister!
What brings you here today?
Another “Spirit Hunter” episode?
Non, non. I’m about to
embark upon a new mission
with my new member!
New member?
Let me introduce you.
This is our newest member,
Karakura King!
Huh? This stuffed animal…
Oh no, oh no, oh no…
It looks like my Bostov…
Nice to meet you!
N-Nice to meet you, too!
Wow, it can talk!
So kind of you to say that…
Karakura Yellow… Of course,
you’ll participate too, right?
Roger, yes sir, affirmative!
Oh, that’s right!
I made this for Bostov’s groom
to wear but…
Here! For you, Karakura King…
What’s this outfit?
Oh, I see…
since she thought I was a girl,
she’s been dressing me
in those frilly clothing only, but…
She can make these kinds
of stuff too, huh?
Wow!
Oh!
H-How do I look?
Great! It fits perfectly, Karakura King!
What're you doing?! Hey!
I got one member!
Now all I have to do is pull
the rest of ‘em out of the ground
just like a bunch of taters!
What’s a bunch of taters?
O-Oh, nothing! Absolutely nothing!
Everything’s okay! Bohahahaha!
There!
So Karin turned you down?
Oh, it’s all right.
Turn left up here.
Right.
Did she finally figure out?
Of course, my face being
exactly the same and all.
It’s a miracle if she didn’t…
Karakura King can walk?
Uh-huh! He’s a Hero of Justice!
Amazing!
I can jump rope double-dutch too!
Even more amazing!
My Bostov just sits and sleeps.
But I do know what
she’s thinking about.
She thinks about having a boyfriend
or pretty girls’ clothes.
No, I’m not thinking that! Not at all!
He who believes shall be saved!
Believing is such a beautiful thing!
What are you talking about!
JUNK WE DON'T NEED
Wh-What the heck?!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Was that all the trash…
Oops, I didn’t know somebody
was down there.
Th-This place…
Training?
That’s right! Join us!
Join us! Oops!
The last time I helped you guys,
I got a huge scolding
afterwards, you know!
Jinta…
W-Well, it wasn’t your fault but…
Old man! I’m not taking
any more orders from you!
No?
Nope!
I swear, darn it!
Boy, oh boy…
Karakura Red, once again!
But if we goof off again,
Mr. Tessai would…
Th-That’s right…
That was hell…
Let’s do this together, Jinta!
It’s a good thing to keep
the peace of the town! Right?!
All right, I’ll do it, I’ll do it,
I’ll do it!
Ururu! You come too!
Then we’re both guilty!
We’ll each get half the punishment!
Well…
Come on, let’s do this, Ururu! Okay?
Okay…!
This is a nightmare…
Hey, looks pretty good on you.
The dude with glasses.
The violent kid.
The space cadet.
And my nemesis…
No! It’s hot!
You’ve got to be kidding me!
I wasn’t told about this.
I can’t handle this.
And where do you think you’re going?
Where are you going?
Come on, Karakura King!
Let’s begin training!
Father, Mother,
the tempura was very delicious…
To be continued!
It’s time to begin
our first training session!
Karakura King, are you all ready?
Never mind the preparations,
what the heck is this supposed to be?
10… 9…
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1! Fire!
First training session, all done!
All done!
What’s next!
Incredible!
What’s the point of this…?!
You’re so cool.
Cool!
That’s not what I’m talking about!
Wonderful! Beautiful! Cool!
Stop it! Stop that creepy dance!
What’s this string?
You shouldn’t pull on that yet…
You should have told me
that before I pulled on it!
You shouldn’t have pulled
on it before I told you that…
Agh! Why me?!
Marvelous!
It was a failure.
What do you mean a failure!
It would have been prettier
at night.
That’s not the problem!
I can’t put up with this training!
No! Wait!
No, I won’t!
Ow…
Ow, it hurts…
I wonder if it’s going to rain.
Yuzu… Huh?
She's not here.
Oww…
Sis Rukia…
Hurry and come back!
Come back and hold me tenderly
in your modest bosom!
Sis Rukia… Huh?
Wh-Wh-What?!
Karakura King!
Karakura…King?
He’s not here…
Pinch! Crisis! And suspense!
Things were coming along just fine,
but without our mascot here,
this is the end of my perfect plan!
Mr. Kanonji…
He sure talks a lot to himself…
Uh-huh…
A-Anyhow, we mustn’t give up!
But you know,
we checked this whole area…
And he doesn’t seem to be around…
Help me!
Wh-What?!
That is a bad spirit!
It’s a Hollow, a Hollow!
That’s amazing, Karakura King!
Help! Save me!
Girl, what are you talking about?
The Karakura King can
fly in the sky too! Right?
Oh right. You can’t see them, can you?
Rescue me! Anyone--!
At any rate! The escalating screams!
The signs of terror!
The gathering dark clouds!
This is indeed where I come in!
Don Kanonji is… awesome, awesome!
All right! This is the new
Karakura Superheroes’ first mission!
Save the Karakura King!
Eh? Yes, sir!
Right!
Mommy!
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?!
Y-You want to eat me?
I probably won’t have any taste…
I’m cotton inside, cotton!
Oh no, I’m not going to eat you.
Oh? Y-You c-can t-talk?
Of course.
Then what are you
planning to do with me?
I’m going to take you
home with me
and give you good lovin’!
In a way, that’s worse
than being eaten!
So, let’s go home now,
my flat-faced lion!
N-No! Let me go!
You don’t have to hate me so…
I’m a professional, you know…
Am I going to be
taken away like this?
Good-bye, Sis…
Good-bye, Orihime…
Good-bye… to all the beautiful ladies
I have yet to meet…
Please be gentle…
Hold it right there!
What?
You’ve come to rescue me!
Karakura Red, at your service!
You're in good hands now.
There’s no coordination…
Spirits…are always…with…you!
The burning heart
is the flame of justice!
Burning Fire! Karakura Red!
Umm… I’m Pink…
Nice to meet you.
What? What’s wrong?
Oh, Karakura King!
Shouldn’t you know better
than to interfere
with our time of love and healing?
Little flat-face is mine now!
It’s even changed
my name already…
Anyone who messes with my love life…
gets sliced!
Eh? What’s happening?
Oh no, Yuzu!
She can’t see it…
Then one more time…
Wh-What?
My claws…
Run!
…will tear your flesh!
Yuzu!
Karakura Yellow!
Karin…?!
I swear…
No wonder my head hurts so bad.
Karakura Red!
So you came, after all.
Wait a minute,
I’m Karakura Red!
Karakura Red…?
You guys still doing that stuff?
Only because I was asked to!
And it’s for good cause!
Oh yeah, Karakura King!
Not a sound…stealthy step at a time.
Is that Bostov?
It’s the Karakura King!
Looks like Karakura King’s in trouble.
Help him, Karin!
But…
My fluffy-boy, wait for me!
My sweetheart!
Enough! I’ll go already.
You guys stay back.
Hey, you! Wait!
Karin!
Why are you following me?
I don’t know,
but I can’t leave this up to you.
Don’t mock me!
You’re the one who
put Yuzu in danger!
Unforgivable!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
You’re just a girl!
Say what?!
Wait--!
Wait, wait a minute…!
The brown one is mine!
Don’t come, don’t come,
don’t come, don’t come…
I got you!
Don’t interrupt!
Oww..ouch..
I told you to stay out of this!
Stay out of this!
What did you say, you hissy-fit?!
What, billboard face?!
Don’t call me billboard face,
you ugly!
Twerp!
Scary Hair!
Stupid!
You’re stupid for calling me stupid!
You’re stupid for calling me
stupid for calling you stupid.
Well, you’re stupid for
calling me stupid--!
You guys…
I can't stand it anymore!
Enough is enough!
I’m spinning my twister!
What?
Typhoon!
Poor me--!
Hey! Are you all right?!
Yuzu--!
The center of the rotation…
I’m spinning! I’m turning!
I’m drawing an arc!
Oh! I stopped…
But what are you doing?
It’s over there… As I thought…
I must throw a powerful attack…
Umm? What?
Come, Ururu!
Huh? What are you going to do?
Karakura Storm! There!
Let’s go, Karin!
Jinta…Homerun!
Leave it to me!
Go…fly!
I’m flying!
Th-This technique…
It’s the legendary Karakura
Ultimate Buster--!
Oh… I can see.
I can see…eternity…
To think that it would end this way…!
Where’s everyone?
There!
Bohahahaha! Bohahahaha!
Hey, what are you doing, hey!
Let go, you pervert!
Huh?
Is this…heaven?
Dear angel…
…or not!
Are you all right, Karakura King?
It seems… I’m still alive…
Thank goodness!
I thought you sacrificed
yourself to save everyone else…
No, actually,
I had no choice in the matter…
This is the result of the training!
Magnificent, Karakura King!
Bohahahaha!
Special Edition! Investigative Report
Spirits…are always…with…you!
I…followed the legendary heroes
of the Karakura Town…
and trekked into
the uninhabited mountains!
And what we witnessed
there was truly…!
Shock and suspense!
Hey… Isn’t this you, Karin? See, see!
Eh?
Hey, what’s this?
When did he tape this?
Maybe this is…
one of those restless…
sad spirits!
I wonder how
Karakura King’s doing…Oh!
I haven’t forgotten about you, Bostov!
I’m making you a brand new outfit now.
So look forward to it!
Please give me a break…
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
Bohahahaha!
For all of you in our nation plagued
by bad spirits!
We, the Karakura Superheroes, can take
care of your problems right away!
Call now to take advantage of
our no-interest, no-handling-fee offer!
Now, everyone together…
Next episode, we’re getting back
to our main story.