In order to prevent Aizen from
wiping out Karakura Town,
an Enriched Spirit Zone,
the Soul Reapers evacuated
the people of Karakura Town
by using four pillars to relocate
the entire town to the Rukon district.
Ikkaku Madarame, Izuru Kira,
Yumichika Ayasegawa
and Shuhei Hisagi
were assigned to defend the pillars.
The four faced the Fracciones
sent by Barragan.
The battle between
Charlotte Chuhlhourne and Yumichika
escalated into
a battle over beauty.
Yumichika struggled against
Chuhlhourne's Resurreccion,
Reinas de Rosas,
but emerged victorious
by using Ruriirokujaku,
his Zanpakuto's genuine form.
At the same time, Kira faced off
against Abirama Redder.
Against the Devorar Pluma
attacks by
Abirama's Resurreccion, Aguila,
Kira was forced on the defensive.
However,
Kira was waiting for his adversary
to make a direct attack.
Then, by using
the power of his Wabisuke
to make Aguila's wings of steel heavier,
he finally brought Abirama
down to the ground.
What?!
Were your legs crushed because
you couldn't get away in time?
I didn't think I used
that great a speed, though!
You saved me the trouble.
For what?
Your long-distance attacks
were tough to deal with.
All this time,
I was thinking of a way
to make you attack me directly.
You see,
there's no point in cutting objects
separated from its target with my sword.
What the hell is this?!
Damn it!
What's happening?!
My wings are suddenly…
It makes what it cuts weigh double.
If I cut twice,
it will weigh double again.
Cut a third time,
and it will weigh double again.
That is the power of
my Zanpakuto, Wabisuke.
Earlier, you asked,
"What in the world was I going to cut with that
oddly shaped sword," didn't you?
Wait… Please wait a minute!
A warrior shouldn't
beg for his life.
I don't get it.
Don't get what?
A while ago,
you said you'd fight with
strength equal to a Lieutenant.
Even giving you
the benefit of the doubt,
your strength right now
was about fifth seat.
What's up with that?
Exacta.
That is correct.
Correct, you say?
My strength right now
is indeed
at the level of a fifth seat in
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
It pleases me that you made
the correct assumption.
Just what I would
expect of a Lieutenant.
You pass.
What?
This is a test.
A test to check to see if you could
accurately measure my strength.
Unless I did that,
you wouldn't realize it
even if I fought at
lieutenant-level strength, right?
My current strength
is that of a fifth seat.
And…
The impact of his sword
is greater?!
This is fourth seat!
Third seat!
Quit fooling around!
Am I getting closer?
And…
This is lieutenant level!
Can you feel it?
This is a lieutenant's
Spiritual Pressure,
and this is
a lieutenant's power!
And, this is a lieutenant's…
sword!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
What's the matter?
C'mon! C'mon!
It's useless!
I wonder how long you can last.
How was that?
That was a lieutenant-level
Spiritual Pressure, Cero and Bala!
So then, Lieutenant…
How do you feel?
You appear quite exhausted.
Don't you think it's about time for
you to get serious, Lieutenant?!
This is a lieutenant speed.
What's the matter, Lieutenant?!
You seem quite worn-down?
In a battle between lieutenants,
would only one side
be worn-down like this?!
I wonder what this could mean.
You're fighting me,
who is at lieutenant-level ability,
but you're the only one
getting worn-down.
What do you think is happening?
You're an annoying bastard.
Are you trying to tell me that
I don't have the strength
of a lieutenant?
Exacta!
Just what I would
expect of a lieutenant!
If I haven't misjudged the strength
of you Court Guard Squads,
then that is precisely
what it means!
Don't call me "Lieutenant."
It's Shuhei Hisagi!
I told you my name at the start,
remember?
How rude of me.
It slipped my mind.
It was a breach of
etiquette for me
to allow only you
to identify yourself.
I'll tell you my name.
I am Findorr Calius,
a Fraccion of His Majesty Barragan.
Well then, now that I've complied
with your etiquette,
it's about time I put
an end to the battle…
in a manner that follows
your methods.
In other words, this will end
with me slashing you to death!
Shuhei Hisagi!
Carve upon the Water…
Pinza Aguda!
Is that what you call
an Arrancar's Resurreccion?
Exacta!
That is correct. Very good.
You're badly mistaken
if you think
you're the only ones with
information on your opponents.
No, I never thought that way.
Exacta!
I give you credit for following
the speed of my Sonido with your eyes!
Correct this, correct that…
You're one annoying bastard!
Seems you still have
a lot of fight left.
To live is to face one difficult
problem after another.
The ones who survive
are the ones
who choose the correct answer
just a few more times!
Therefore,
anyone would want to possess even
a few more correct answers!
Am I wrong?!
Is that why you're giving me
the correct answers?
Such grand talk.
Bakudo 62: Hyapporankan!
You're finished!
Motormouth!
Don't underestimate me!
Soul Reaper!
A high-pressure water stream?!
Exacta!
It's not a good idea to turn
your eyes away from your enemy.
No es exacto!
Wrong answer!
Too bad, Soul Reaper!
You think you've escaped me?!
It's over!
Reap...
Kazeshini!
Hisagi…
Finally.
I see.
So that's your Zanpakuto,
Shuhei Hisagi.
Yeah…
This is my Zanpakuto, Kazeshini.
I'm not very fond of it, though.
What do you mean?
Just that…
I don't like the shape
of this thing.
Look at its shape.
See how it takes the form of
something that reaps lives?
Damn it!
You're not getting away!
Hard to predict
the trajectory of this thing,
isn't it?
Afraid?
Who's afraid?!
I see.
I'm afraid.
Afraid?
Afraid that your own power
is too huge?!
What cheap narcissism!
Keep dreaming, Soul Reaper!
In fact, allow me to wake you up!
Right now!
It's over!
When I strip off 90 percent
of my mask,
my strength becomes
equal to that of a captain!
You, a lieutenant,
have no chance of winning!
You're not afraid of
your own strength…
or the enemy's?
You're not much.
A person who isn't afraid…
A person who isn't afraid
of the sword he holds…
is not qualified to hold a sword.
That is what I was taught.
Are you feeling afraid now?
You're equal with me at last.
Damn you!
Take this!
Equal to a captain, you say?
You are so far off.
The pillar is…
destroyed?!
Destroyed?! By whom?!
Ik…
Ikkaku!
Madarame was…
defeated?!
Madarame was defeated?
We have to hurry and help him!
Leave that to me!
After all, this arc is about
helping us, the unfortunate lieutenants
who don't get enough screen time.
I see!
Iba, don't say "unfortunate"
and things like that.
And Hisagi,
don't sympathize with him.
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
SUBSTITUTE SOUL REAPER
WORK JOURNAL
Please have a look.
I see…
Well done, Kuchiki.
Nice work.
Yes, sir.
Are you serious?
Also, about the illustration…
Yes, I have it right here.
What?!
Why is an illustration necessary?
Isn't that a report?!
Report? Hardly.
This is the manuscript that we'll be
publishing in the Seireitei Bulletin.
What?!