Ichigo Kurosaki…
So you’re coming to
the Soul Society, eh?
Your second entry will be far
riskier than your first.
Mr. Urahara did warn me.
But I have to get to the
Soul Society quickly!
Gokei, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
There is one thing I share with you.
I will use any means
to protect my pride.
I knew we would face one another
in battle sooner or later.
You’re wounded.
Not an issue.
I suppose not.
I would never run,
no matter what my situation.
I’m going on ahead.
I cannot allow that.
- There can only be one Byakuya Kuchiki!
Kenny, maybe you should’ve
rested a bit longer.
You’re tottering.
Don’t be silly.
I feel awesome right now.
Kenny, she’s probably a…
I know.
It doesn’t matter.
I know what you’re about to do.
When the leader of the Punishment
Force draws her sword,
an execution battle is imminent, right?
I hope you guys are
going to make this fun!
Kill him!
Battles...have begun everywhere.
Darn children!
We must apprehend Kageroza quickly.
Huh?
Shiro…
Hinamori?
Well, Mr. Urahara?
The captains
haven’t made it to
Kageroza’s location yet.
What about Kurosaki?
He appears to be making good time
toward the Soul Society.
I’m glad.
No… It’s going too smoothly.
Kageroza couldn’t
possibly have missed him.
Why’re you giving her the eye?!
Stop stripping her with
your eyes, you pervert!
I’m not you!
What?
Come with me.
Hey, let go of me!
You’re practically kidnapping me!
No, he’s taking me away!
So, what is it?
There’s something I want to ask you.
Nozomi Kujo…
Did you notice anything about her
during the time you were together?
What do you mean?
Kageroza is after her.
When I have retrieved Nozomi,
I will be able to show
you my true power.
Then, not only the Soul Society,
but the World of the Living
will also be under my control.
That’s why we…
In all likelihood,
that girl holds some huge secret.
For example,
he may have hidden something
inside that girl’s body.
That’s the conclusion we came to.
But what I still don’t
understand is…
What is it that’s hidden within her?
What is the secret that Kageroza needs
that can control both
the World of the Living
and the Soul Society?
Do you have any idea?
A secret in her body, you say?
I mean, I didn’t mean
to see her naked.
It’s the truth!
Besides, it’s just coincidence
that we were together.
I wasn’t like, worried
about her or anything!
Anyhow, if she doesn’t
want to tell us, so what?
Well it’s obvious that you like her.
Wh-What’re you talking about?!
You’ve got to be kidding!
There’s no way I would like such a
violent, smart-ass chick!
Don’t talk nonsense!
I don’t have any feelings for her,
and I don’t know anything!
I mean it!
I really don’t have
any feelings for her!
W-Why?
Just because.
What’s that?
Looks like Kurosaki made
it to the Soul Society.
Huh?
This is way off the mark.
Did Mr. Urahara make a mistake
in his calculations?
I summoned you here.
Kageroza!
I tweaked the Precipice World a bit.
Why?
You said you would control
the Soul Society and the
World of the Living.
What are you up to?!
Why are you after Nozomi?!
What did you
hide in Nozomi?!
My, my, so many questions.
Let me answer just the first one.
Why did I summon you here?
Very simple.
To erase your existence.
Shiro…
Hinamori?
What are you doing here?
Well…
When I woke up
the people from Squad 12
who were looking after me
were all gone.
Where did everyone go?
You still don’t look well.
I think you should rest.
No, I’m all right.
No.
Multiple battles are
going on right now.
We might find ourselves
in a battle as well.
You’d better go somewhere safe.
Thank you.
But really, I’m all right.
You’re tottering.
Don’t strain yourself.
You need to rest right now.
I’m sorry…Shiro.
I’m so sorry.
It’s no use.
You can’t kill me.
But can you kill me, Shiro?
Are you going to try and kill me…
again?
I’m really sorry.
It’s not my fault.
It’s Kageroza’s fault for
coming up with this idea.
Awesome! Awesome!
Not yet.
He… I…was strong!
I fought my strong self…and I won!
My body is still tingling.
More… I want to fight more!
You don’t know when to
give up, Kenpachi Zaraki.
Whatever you’re feeling,
you should barely be
standing after a battle like that.
What would you know?
They’re planning to
attack all at once.
What’ll you do?
Then I’ll just have to
take them all out together!
Yachiru…
Dodge.
Okay.
Wha—?!
He took our attack and
emerged unscathed.
What Spiritual Pressure!
Are you okay, Yachiru?
Yup. How about you, Kenny?
Nothing wrong at all.
These guys are no challenge.
I’m totally unsatisfied.
Are you going to make this fun for me?!
Soi Fon!
Kenny!
Sajin Komamura…
So you’re alive?
Sorry I’m late. Allow
me to assist you.
Assist?
Don’t even think about it!
She’s mine.
Don’t interfere.
Don’t worry about me!
It took some time to get
through the Precipice World,
but my body is tough.
Who’s worried about you?!
I’m telling you to stay out of my—
Captain Soi Fon!
I’ll be your opponent.
Hey! Did you hear me?!
Go for it, Bow-wow!
You took the fun right out of it.
I’m going on ahead after Kageroza.
Bye bye!
Forgive me, Shiro.
Snap…Tobiume.
Snap, Tobiume!
Shiro!
Is that me?
You hurt Shiro, didn’t you?!
Unforgivable!
I…didn’t do it because I wanted to!
Shiro!
Help me!
Bakudo 4: Hainawa!
Help me, Shiro!
Don’t let her trick you!
She’s an imposter!
No! I’m not an imposter!
Quiet! Imposter!
Believe me, Shiro!
Stop it!
I’m sorry.
- Snap…Tobiume!
We’re so sorry.
This is Kageroza’s strategy.
We’re weaker than you, Shiro.
He said if we made you
drop your guard…
Then we could defeat you.
Because you could never
attack us, Shiro.
We’re so sorry.
Please don’t hate us for this.
So you’re both Reigai?
That’s good.
What?
Good?
Why do you say that?
It’s not good. We tricked you.
That’s all right.
Because I didn’t have to get the
real Hinamori involved in this mess.
I don’t ever want to hurt her again.
I see.
Then we’ll make this quick.
Shunko!
We were so close.
But I’m glad.
I wish…I was the original.
You’re way too naïve.
You were here in the Soul
Society the whole time?
Yeah.
I had business to take care of.
And you?
I still have unfinished business too.
Hey!
Don’t overdo it.
I’ll join you shortly.
Erase my existence?
Why me?
Answer me!
What?!
You shouldn’t exist.
You’re not human.
You’re not a pure
Soul Reaper or Hollow.
You’re an anomaly.
I am unable to create a
Reigai of you from Reishi.
You are the unaccountable variable.
Quite frankly, you are
a thorn in my plans.
Goodbye, Ichigo Kurosaki.
What the—?
Is this…the Precipice World?
What’s wrong?
Kurosaki’s Spiritual Pressure just…
completely disappeared!
- What?!
Listen, Four-Eyes.
When you like someone,
your heart starts to pound,
and you also feel some pain.
What?! You had an experience
like that before?
Of course!
I've had my share of
romance once or twice.
That’s terrible! You’re not well.
We must take you to
the hospital quickly!
That’s not what I meant! Hey!