Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo,
the world of the Hollows.
They crush the Arrancars
standing in their way and
finally make their way to Las Noches,
Aizen's headquarters.
Upon breaking into the palace,
the group decides to split up
and go down separate paths.
Blocking the path that Ichigo and Nel
choose is Privaron Espada Dordoni.
Ichigo underestimates Dordoni's power
and is hit with an unexpected attack.
Whirl! Giralda!
Sorry to keep you waiting,
old man.
This is my Bankai!
I see… I've been
waiting for this, niño.
But you have a stronger form,
don't you?
I know about
your Hollowfication.
Use it!
I'll use…
any means, niño!
Don't you have any shame?!
I do!
I am ashamed…that I cannot
fight you when you're serious!
All right.
Sorry, but I can only show it
to you for an instant.
Wh-What?
I told you…
It was only an instant.
Dordoni accepted his defeat to Ichigo,
who used his Hollowfication.
But while having his wounds treated,
Dordoni attacks once again.
The fact that you healed the wounds
of an enemy that you don't know,
means that you were prepared
for a counterattack!
Stop!
You haven't recovered
enough to move!
Wounds are made
to one's spirit, niño.
As long as my will to fight recovers,
my physical wounds mean nothing.
That's why I say you're
like chocolate…niño!
Ichi…go…
Welcome, Exequias.
We've been ordered to hunt down
and kill the wounded intruders.
By whom?
I cannot say.
Do you want to pass?
Your sword is broken and you cannot
maintain your sword release.
I don't think that you can
fight us in that state!
Strong words, jovenzuelo!
I'm really glad that I made it, niño.
If I hadn't attacked you again
at that time, you'd still be here.
Niño…my powers
have weakened.
You probably could have defeated me
without transforming into a Hollow.
But you did that for me
even though you knew that
it would quickly exhaust you.
I thank you.
This is the least I can do
to thank you.
The residents beyond this point
aren't as lenient as I am.
Don't hesitate to kill your enemy.
Don't waver when
you finish them off.
Above all, healing their wounds
is out of the question, niño.
Leave your chocolate here!
Become a demon, niño.
Become as strong as a demon.
Become as crafty as a demon.
In order to withstand
others' ruthlessness,
you need to learn that
you have no choice
but to become ruthless yourself.
If not, niño…
Damn!
Reporting!
I've just received
information that
Arrancar Number 103, Privaron Espada,
Lord Dordoni Alessandro Del Socaccio
was defeated by
one of the intruders!
I see.
It seems he took longer
than I had expected.
I thought that he could take care of
someone like Dordoni a little quicker.
Oh well…
Anyway, there's something you're
not reporting to me, isn't there?
Who…sent the Exequias after him?
W-Well…
What's wrong?
Was that a difficult question?
It was I, Lord Aizen.
Szayelaporro, huh?
I'm very sorry!
I figured that if we wanted to
wipe out the intruder
we shouldn't miss a chance
to get them while they're injured.
I ordered them to go
at my own discretion!
Even though I thought that
it would be beneficial to you,
it was an action that
you had not ordered me to do.
I am prepared to
take any punishment!
No, there's no need.
It's fine as long as
you have a reason.
There's no need to
punish you for anything.
Th-Thank you very much!
Excuse me!
But…
I would like your reports to be
a little more accurate.
Szayelaporro.
Are the Spiritual Pressure records
you got from Dordoni about the intruder
of any use in your research?
Yes.
I see… That's good.
What's this?
You look quite amused
despite the fact
that one of your subordinates
was just killed.
Do I look that way?
Am I wrong?
You look like you're
amused by the fact
that those kids are
winning their way here.
That's the sort of
expression you have.
Amused, huh? I wonder why.
Indeed, I feel something
similar to that.
Don't you think it's strange, Gin?
Not at all.
Oddly enough,
I also feel the same way.
It's useless to hide!
Wh-Why am I doing this?
Why are you doing this?
That's what I'd like to ask you, idiot!
You said that you sensed
Nel's Spiritual Pressure,
got excited, then suddenly
picked me up and took me here!
Are you making fun of me?!
W-Well, I got excited when
I sensed Nel's Spiritual Pressure!
I know!
I just said that!
I can't help it!
Of course you can!
Are you making fun of me?!
Come on stand up!
You're going to look for
that kid Nel, aren't you?!
Th-That hurts.
Don't kick me.
What you did to me
hurt a lot more!
Pe…
What? What's wrong?
Where's Pesche?!
Pesche's suddenly gone, too!
Pesche?!
That skinny skeleton-like guy?!
He wasn't with us from the start!
F-From the start?!
U-Umm… From the start?
Does that mean that the Pesche
that was living with us was an illusion?
Not that start!
Aw man, what is this?!
This guy is so annoying!
P-P-Pesche!
How many times do I have to tell you
to make you understand?!
You can't run away from me.
You can't run away.
Don't attack me while
I'm still talking.
You've got no tact.
Honestly…
Are all male humans like this?
Don't run away, funny clothes!
You of all people shouldn't talk!
I keep telling you it's useless!
Even though she's an Arrancar,
as a woman, her attacks are light.
I can repel her attacks
in response.
In that case, I've got to persist and
wait for a chance to get a clean hit.
You're being a pest,
funny clothes!
Curve!
Go!
All right… I can do this!
What a bad personality!
Her weapon attacks
in a straight line.
When it's released.
And when it's drawn back.
In that case,
I've got to dodge all of those attacks
and release arrows from directions
that she won't expect.
Then…
Stupid!
What are you shooting at?!
What?!
Then I just have to control it by
controlling my Spiritual Pressure.
Why you…
Hey, don't keep moving around!
Now!
Now might be a good time.
It curved?!
Are you stupid?!
This is what you would call
"digging your own grave"!
I tricked you into smashing
all of the pillars
so you could make
an opening for me!
There were so many of them that it was
a bother to destroy all of them by myself.
Look! Now I can curve it
any which way!
Oh no.
Look, look!
Curve, curve!
What's wrong?
Are you giving up already?!
Damn!
That's not a shield.
Don't be reckless!
Damn.
Ishida and Sado's Spiritual Pressures
have been fluctuating.
Have they encountered enemies?
No.
I don't need to worry about them.
Anyway, I've got to get to Inoue
as quickly as possible.
This is…
What is this?! Blue skies?!
Why is there a sky here
beyond these walls?!
Also…
Shall I tell you?
Follow me.
Wait!
I can finally relax now.
Sorry.
I can't seem to stand sunlight.
The sun doesn't get
inside of the palace.
I'll remove my mask
and introduce myself.
My name is Aaroniero.
Espada Number 9…
Aaroniero Arruruerie.
S…
Sir…Kaien…
I've received
Lord Aizen's permission!
Now I can rampantly
carry out experiments!
Now then, who should I
collect samples from first?
Is it all right to leave
Szayelaporro alone like that?
It seems amusing,
so let him do what he wants.
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
What?!
Squad 8 isn't coming?!
They had a huge
drinking party last night
to celebrate their first-class mission,
and they all got smashed.
CELEBRATING BEING ASSIGNED
IN THE OUKEN TRANSPORT
GUARD MISSION
They had a little too much fun.
So we'll be the only ones
doing this.
Ukitake!
Sorry… It seems like
I'm no good today.
Take care of the rest.
Captain…
We're the only squad left.