You're really annoying!
What?!
Ichigo!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Curse you, ant!
Defying a god...
Unforgivable, unforgivable!
This is unforgivable, you ants!
That's my line.
Why do I have to fight
someone so strong?
Lord... Aizen?
I'm done with you.
I didn't expect this outcome.
I went through a lot of trouble
to gather you Espada.
I never expected your combined
strength to be inferior to that of mine.
Now, shall we begin?
Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
and you failed mock Arrancars.
Whoa... The last Espada
got beaten up.
Ah...
Mashiro!
Ah!
I know!
Mashiro!
When you fight against guys at this
level, you get exhausted quickly!
Remove your mask and put it back
on before you reach your limit!
Humph! You're so
stupid, Kensei!
How long do you think I can normally
maintain a Hollowfication?!
Fifteen hours! That's
fifteen hours!
I can go on like this right
through the night!
Mashiro...
Behind you!
I told you...I already know that!
How's that?!
Hey!
How dare you rip my scarf!
Take this!
Mashiro...Super...Cero!
So what if you could
cancel that!
Here I go! Mashiro...
Oops... I'm out of time?
Sorry...
I'm not mature enough to
hold back against a kid!
Get some sleep. I'm going
to clobber him.
Kensei...
Are you avenging me?
What's with that happy look?
Stupid.
This all happened because you
didn't heed my warnings.
I would never avenge
such an idiot.
I'm just going to pummel a
kid who's getting cocky.
Kensei...
That's not going to hit me!
This is how you throw a punch!
Are you ready?!
Bankai!
Tekken Tachikaze!
Aizen...Let's settle our score
from a hundred years ago!
You know, I really liked those
days back in the Soul Society!
Soul Reapers are always in death's way
because of their existence
and line of work.
We may die the next day.
We may be talking at one moment
and be dead in the next.
No one talks about it,
but everyone has that thought
in the corner of their minds.
We saw death up close.
We felt death up close.
That's why we were able
to cherish each day.
Death will eventually come to us all.
But that's what made us united.
That's what I believed.
But you...
Ai...zen...
Aizen!
Good-bye.
You were all wonderful
test subjects.
Damn it!
Aizen... I don't hate you because
you betrayed us.
I hate you because you made
me hurt my friends!
You used me...
and trampled on our bonds
and our feelings!
Aizen!
I'm seething with an anger that's
been boiling for a hundred years!
I won't go back to the way
I was until I kill you!
Don't approach him carelessly.
Aizen's got that power.
If you approach him
recklessly, it's over.
I know that.
You idiot. I'm talking to you!
Relax, Hiyori.
How typical.
You have such caring words,
Captain Hirako.
But it's so silly to say that it'll be over
if you approach me recklessly.
Even if you approach me
recklessly or carefully,
or even if you don't
approach me at all,
the end result will be the same.
I'm not talking about
things to come.
Your end is inescapable.
It's an event of the past.
He's taunting us! Don't fall for it!
What do you have to fear?
All of you already
died on that night
a hundred years ago.
Hiyori!
One down.
Hiyori...
S-Sorry, Shinji.
Don't speak.
I...I couldn't hold back.
Hachi!
Use your Kido to heal Hiyori's...
Hiyori... What should I do?
How can I help Hiyori?!
That's right...
Orihime...
Orihime's power can
still heal her!
Ichigo!
Isn't Ichigo here yet?!
Kurosaki...
Go on ahead.
I'll be all right.
There are people waiting below.
Ishida...
Go.
But...
Kurosaki!
If you have something
you want to say,
I'll listen to you after
this is all over.
Right now, you have something
else you have to do, don't you?
All right.
Inoue, take care of Ishida.
Okay. Leave him to me.
Yeah.
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
No matter how many times
you try, it's useless!
This is lame...
What?!
Now! Rukia! Sado!
Right!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
Tsuginomai...
Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del Gigante.
Don't get carried away!
That can't be... He's not
even scratched?!
That's why I said it was useless!
That toughness and power...
What should we do?
There's nothing to discuss.
We've got to do this.
You're right.
What are you talking
about, you trash!
Let's go!
Hm? Where did you go?
Are you there?!
You keep moving around!
This is such a pain!
This is so annoying!
I knew it.
He can't keep up
with our speed!
We'll confuse him
with our speed.
And then...
Where are you?
Where are you?!
There you are!
Hikotsu Taiho!
You're really annoying!
What?!
That's one down.
Now then...
That's two.
All that's left is...
Hey, where did you go?
Oh? Oh...
Do you think you can get away
from me by doing that?!
This is bad!
I caught you!
You're the last one.
You're so small, I had a
tough time catching you.
You're not getting away!
Don't struggle.
It's pretty difficult to hold on
to you without crushing you.
Now then...
How should I kill you?
Let's see...
Crushing you like this
wouldn't be amusing at all.
I've got to think of the method
that's the most fun.
Hey, how do you want
me to kill you?
I'll do it however you like.
I may look frightening, but I'm quite
generous towards weaklings.
Sokatsui!
That hurts! That hurts!
That really hurt!
That was really painful!
He isn't affected at all.
That was so painful
it made me lose my grip
on you!
What incredible power...
I can't regain my posture because
of the wind pressure!
Rukia!
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
- Go, Kensei!
- Oraoraora!
Looking good Kensei,
go get'em!
Hey, Mashiro.
If you have the energy to root for me,
then give me a hand.
What? No way...
I'm mature enough to
hold back on a kid!
You brat!
The Seven Wonders
of Karakura Town!
Rumors about a moving mannequin...
That's impossible.
Huh?
It can't be...
Why, if it isn't Ichigo.
I was right!
If you leave your Gigai here,
people will put cute
clothes on it for you!
The others have their
Gigai here too.
Why?
Why is mine dressed like this?!