I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Are you better now?
Renji…
Yeah… Inoue completely fixed me up.
Well, you don't seem like you'd die
even if you were killed.
Shut up.
Inoue healed Rukia as well, right?
She's taking pretty long to recover…
Idiot… Did you forget?
Her current injuries aren't the only
reason why she's been weakened.
Rukia didn't have enough time to
recover her spiritual power
when the Bount mayhem occurred,
and she was sent to
the World of the Living.
She needs time to recover.
I see…
So are you finished cleaning up?
Yeah… Damaged buildings need
to be repaired
and the wounded need to be healed.
There is still damage,
but it looks like
we're pretty much finished.
It seems that Seireitei has officially
acknowledged the Bounts’ existence
and the reason for their creation.
Yeah…
That bastard, Kariya, wanted to
erase the Bounts' existence,
but instead, he left a big impression.
As usual, you talk as if
you know everything…
What?!
Come on…
This happened because
you sent the Bounts here!
What?! You were with us, too!
I…
I defeated Gesell, remember?!
Zabimaru is still damaged
because of that!
Isn't that because you're weak?
What…did you say?!
Don't get so mad!
I just let the truth slip!
You just let what slip?!
Don't get cocky just because
you got a little better!
Besides, you're just a substitute.
You're not like a real Soul Reaper!
Don't get carried away!
Got it?!
I said I'm sorry!
No! I can't forgive you!
Shut up! I'm worn out!
Your strange meekness is
even more unforgivable!
What are you doing?
– Umm…
You're pretty noisy.
You haven't forgotten
where you are, have you?
Sorry…
Ichigo Kurosaki.
If your business here is done,
go back to the World of
the Living immediately.
You do not belong here.
I got scolded because of you!
Did he come out after he was done
eavesdropping on our conversation?
Shut up…
You fools!
Hey, you're up?
Of course! I can't get any sleep
with you guys raising a ruckus!
You two don’t think of me
as an injured patient, do you?!
How peaceful.
Yeah…
But man… I never thought that
I would come to this world twice.
You meddle too much!
Yeah. Probably…
What's this? Say something!
There aren't any Bounts left…
It was a battle that left
such unimaginable suffering.
Yeah…
Kariya…
was too hung up about
the Bounts' past.
He probably couldn't stand
things repeating themselves
over and over again.
Repeating?
Yeah… It's not easy living forever…
He saw the state of the Bounts
get worse countless times
over a thousand years.
To him, history wasn't a line
that stretched forward.
It was something that revolved
around and around in a circle.
He wanted to break that cycle.
Revolving, huh?
It’s revolving.
I'm being transferred?
No, no!
We're not transferring you
or anything extreme like that!
You're being stationed
in the World of the Living!
You went there to support me
when you joined long ago!
Over there!
Umm…
Look, she doesn't remember!
She erased it from her memory
because it was such
a bad experience!
Right, Kuchiki?!
Umm…
Huh?! Shut up!
Go bury yourself in the yard!
What?! I'm not some potted plant!
Umm…
You're being stationed
within a four-kilometer radius
around Karakura Town.
With your skills, this mission
shouldn't be difficult.
Captain Ukitake!
C-Captain!
That's no good.
You've got to get some rest!
No… I'm feeling good today.
Even though it's only a month,
I thought you might be anxious being
stationed by yourself for the first time.
I came to see you off.
Thank you very much!
Don't. That sounds so stiff.
Have you informed Byakuya?
Oh! No… Not yet…
Oh… No…
Captain Kuchiki would probably
tell me not to inform him
about every little thing…
So I was going to leave
without informing him…
I see…
All right.
That's fine if you think so.
I'll tell Byakuya.
Go with peace of mind!
Yes!
That's right…
That was the beginning
of everything.
Until I met Ichigo,
I thought that the future was
a line that stretched on forever.
I still believe that.
I hereby appoint Squad 11
Sixth Seat Renji Abarai
to the position of Squad 6 lieutenant.
Congratulations, Abarai!
Y-Yeah!
Oh, no…
I humbly accept this appointment,
Lieutenant Hinamori!
You don't have to do that.
That sounds so rigid…
Anyway…aren't you glad?
You've gotten one step closer
to Byakuya Kuchiki.
Ikkaku…
Isn't it about time
you talk to Rukia?
Even if she's become an aristocrat,
you're a lieutenant.
You're more than equals.
You held out for 40 years.
It's about time you restore
your relationship with her.
Before, you used to run around
the Rukon District together.
In that case…
You should hurry.
Kuchiki is supposed to be stationed
in the World of the Living
for a month.
Oh no! Abarai, hurry!
No…
I'll be officially promoted
at the appointment ceremony
a month from now.
When she comes back,
I'll surprise her by telling her that
I'm a lieutenant.
It’s revolving.
If fate is a cog,
then all we can do is believe
that whatever is turning it
is flawless,
as we move ahead…
in the direction of
the force of the fixed cogs.
Then…a blade is swung.
And so fell the sword of fate…
Where am I?
You've regained consciousness.
You're…Yoshino?!
She's not Yoshino…
She's Rantao…
Rantao…
This is Rantao's hideout.
Why am I here?
I carried you here,
so the Soul Reapers
wouldn't find you.
Weren't you with Ichigo Kurosaki
and the others?
Why did you help me?
Who knows…?
What about Kariya?
He died.
I see.
The Jokai Crest is backed
by all of the Bounts!
Can you withstand it,
Ichigo Kurosaki?!
People hate those
who are superior to themselves.
Your friends aren't any different!
I protect them because I want to!
I'd risk my soul!
Kariya!
If the fate of the Bounts
is to die out…
then I just have to accept that.
I see.
Anyway, you should stay here
until your wounds heal.
Rantao…
I no longer have anything to do…
I don't plan on returning to Seireitei
after all this time.
I want to listen to the story
of the last Bount…
Well then, I'm returning to
the World of the Living.
I've left the rest to Ukitake.
There's no need to worry.
Sorry, but…
What is it?
Thank Ichigo Kurosaki for me
for stopping Kariya.
All right.
I'll tell him…
Huh?
All right! No one's noticed me!
Here I go!
What are you doing?
O-Oh. It's just you!
Don't surprise me, you bastard!
You bastard… You were trying to
sneak into Rukia's room.
What's wrong with me wanting
to be with her?!
She and I are of one mind and body!
I've devoted myself to her!
Just what in the world
are you talking about?
You'll be sliced up by Byakuya's
Senbonzakura if you go in there.
Shut up!
Besides, you guys neglect me
way too much!
By the time I finally
caught up to you,
everything was over
and I lost my chance
to play an active role!
An active role?
You wanted to be useful?
Why do you think
I came to this world?!
All right… I understand. Let's go!
The Senkaimon is just about ready.
What?! What about Sister?
She's injured, so she has to
stay here to recover, of course.
What?! Then I'm going to stay
by her side!
Let go of me, Ichigo!
There's no point in leaving you here!
Crap!
If only I were more powerful…
I could pound the Bounts and
the Soul Reapers…
and make Sister adore me.
Power, huh?
He gained that power and
was swung around by it.
In the end, he had to destroy himself.
Kariya wanted the power
to change fate.
What I wanted was…
Revolving…
Ichigo!
Did you see?!
Did you see this?!
It's the new Bad Shield Series!
Bad… What is that?
What?! Hey, hey, hey!
You said before that
you enjoyed watching the DVD
of the TV version!
I forgot.
What?!
I like this series!
Shut up! I wasn't talking to you, Mizuiro!
It's cool, isn't it?!
I like Stanley Ashford…
– It doesn't just revolve.
– …the guy who plays Ricky!
– It revolves…and whenever…
– Julian, who plays Mille…
– the sun touches the moon…
– is a much better actor.
– It seems that Mille dies in “2.”
– Really?!
…the world changes itself
into something new.
Umm…
Then what's your favorite snack?
Gotsubukko.
No way! Then you like
baumkuchen as well, don't you?
Oh, yeah, I do!
Okay! Here's what your fortune says…!
You're a perfect match…
for me--!
You're leading her on
with those questions!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Huh?!
Later, Tatsuki!
Oh! I'm going home soon, too.
Sorry, I have somewhere I need to go!
I see… Then see you tomorrow!
If there is something that
doesn't change…
I'm sure it would be my helplessness.
Ah… So, boy, you really came…
Sorry… She disappeared.
Yeah.
I can see spirits. I can touch them.
I can talk to them.
But that's it.
That airplane…
It's gone to waste.
That's all right…
It was just something in my closet.
Sometimes they just disappear
like this.
I don't know why
they disappear.
Sometimes they leave
behind bloodstains
that only I can see and
somewhat painful feelings.
No matter how much I train my body,
I can't protect them.
Whenever I think about it,
my heart feels like a blade.
It’s revolving.
Oh! Mister!
Over here!
Sorry! I'm late…
Three dogs and six cats
passed me by today!
I see… Did they say anything?
The brown dog was really cheeky!
He kept peeing on the telephone pole,
no matter how many times
I told him not to!
Look! I brought you flowers!
Wow! They're beautiful!
There we go!
Huh? What's wrong?
Will you come back tomorrow?
It’s revolving…
Yeah, all right!
– If fate is a cog wheel…
– I'll come back tomorrow!
– We are…
– Thank you…mister…
grains of sand crushed
between those cogs.
It's all right. Don't cry anymore!
– There is nothing we can do.
– Got it?!
We just want power.
If it’s something we can’t easily protect,
we want to grab a sword beforehand.
The power to crush fate surely
resembles a swinging blade.
Is my strength the power
to crush fate?
Or will I be consumed
by my power like Kariya was?
There's no point in thinking about it…
This power is for protecting everyone!
That's fine, isn't it?
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Ukitake…
Why are you spacing out?
Well, I was thinking about
why Kariya wanted to gain power.
Kariya probably thought of history
as a circle.
He was probably trying
to sever it with force…
I don't know if that's
right or wrong…
But…even if things
repeated themselves…
It wouldn't be that bad if
you had friends there…right?
It's not something that can
be answered so easily.
Is history something that revolves
or stretches ahead of us?
Even if it's something that revolves,
should we try to break that loop…?
Or be content with it?
Ichigo, everyone's here!
Kurosaki-kun!
Ichigo!
We came all this way
to this unknown world, Soul Society…
It truly is sad,
but it's almost time to part.
You can stay if you want to.
You're being mean again!
It's almost time.
Let’s go home, Ichigo.
Yeah…
Revolving, huh?
Thank you, Ichigo.
Let's meet again…
We tremble in awe of that
which cannot be seen
What's this?
Such a cruddy little town.
And so fell
the sword of fate once again
in the name of a mask
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Hey, how've you all been! It's Kon!
I didn't appear much in Soul Society,
but I'll play a big part
when we get back to
the World of the Living.
Sorry. But with the new main character
of Bleach, me,
appearing in the next episode,
you don’t have any appearances.
Who the hell are you?!
My name is… Oh!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I'm back…
Hey! We just got back!
You sure are late, Captain.
Yeah, we got lost in Kusajishi…
It was really fun!
So where are the Bounts?
Ichigo defeated them.
I see… All right!
I guess I'll fight Ichigo now!
Captain…
He already returned to
the World of the Living.
What?!
That bastard…
When I see him again,
I'll kill him without even
greeting him!
Ichigo… You were right not to
see him before you left.
Don't spy on others!