may be inferior compared to yours.
Ichigo and Rukia continue to
search for Rurichiyo
after they disrupt
her marriage ceremony.
The search for Rurichiyo goes on with
Shu's help and the support of Amagai.
Meanwhile, Kira tracks down Kibune,
who had been acting suspiciously,
and he comes across Rurichiyo
in a Squad 3 facility.
However, due to Kibune's interruption,
he fails to rescue her.
In the past, Kibune was not
recognized as a Soul Reaper.
Out of frustration,
he reached out to the Kasumiohji Clan
and acquired their Bakkouto.
Kira confronts Kibune about this.
I need even greater power!
With that power, I will make
every Soul Reaper recognize me!
Izuru Kira!
Guys like you, who have no talent,
yet get promoted to lieutenant…
I will sweep all of you away!
Weakness is a crime.
Someone like you doesn't
deserve to be where you are.
When the previous captain
went out of control,
you couldn't even stop him!
Powerless people like you don't
deserve to stand above me!
It's useless!
The killing blow.
You bastard, just die already!
You think you've dodged it?
How unsightly you are.
Why do you continue to resist?
What was your purpose
in coming to Squad 3?
If it was only to become the strongest
Soul Reaper, there are other ways.
To show off one's power,
one must attain a position that is fitting.
I see.
But, that's not possible.
Captain Amagai knows what
you've been doing up until now.
Even if you kill me,
you have no future!
So what?
What?!
The Kasumiohji Clan is planning to use
the Bakkouto to create a new world.
For example, with this Bakkouto,
I can annihilate all of Squad 3.
Is that the goal for you
and the Kasumiohji Clan?
There is no need to know,
as you are about to die!
You…
I won't let you do it.
Just what do you take
your colleagues for?!
Those guys? Colleagues?
Like I said again and again.
Weakness is a crime.
Never once have I thought of
anyone as a colleague!
I see.
Then I can't forgive you.
You ridicule the weak,
and deceived your colleagues,
only seeing them as someone
to use for your own ambitions!
So what of it?
For me,
the most important thing is
having squad members
working together based on trust!
And you violated that trust!
Listen to you!
You're exhausted,
Lieutenant Kira.
I'm surprised your body
is still holding up.
You can never become
the strongest Soul Reaper!
Shut up!
Over here!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Why?
You don't seem to have noticed.
Since you entered that state,
you were being spun around
by the power of that sword.
What…did you say?
What you attained
is not real power.
I couldn't stop Captain Ichimaru.
I am powerless!
But I have a responsibility!
To Squad 3…
I have a responsibility to
protect my colleagues!
I can't afford to lose!
Are you saying it's a difference
between our resolve?
That is not enough to make up for
the difference in our strength!
You can't beat me
with force alone!
What's that?!
The Bakkouto!
I see.
Your Bakkouto is that thing
covering the Zanpakuto.
And…
It is what negated
the effects of my Wabisuke.
It appears your strength was
nothing but a fraud after all.
True, my Wabisuke's attack power
may be inferior compared to yours.
But that is not the only thing
that constitutes our strength.
"Zan Ken So Ki!"
Only through that, and possessing a heart,
can it really be considered true power!
I will not… Not here…
Kibune!
I won't lose…
to the likes of you!
I won't lose!
Has he become completely
consumed by the sword.
W-What's going on?
Hey, wake up!
Wha—?!
Lieutenant! Third Seat Kibune!
What is this?!
Kibune…
As the Squad 3 Lieutenant…
I'm going to stop you!
Lieutenant Kira!
Everyone…
Are you all right, sir?!
Somewhat.
Kibune…
Lieutenant!
Tell Captain Amagai…
Coordination between each squad
appears to be going smoothly.
I understand.
Return to your post.
Yes, ma'am!
Shusuke Amagai…
His defecting could
prove to be troublesome.
And…
the Substitute Soul Reaper…
I apologize.
Please move out of the way.
What are they trying to do?
You haven't changed, Soi Fon.
Lady Yoruichi!
You seem confused.
Uh… It's…
How about listening to
what I have to say?
Huh?
Hold it!
Hold it, damn it!
Let me handle this!
End of the line!
Let Rurichiyo go!
Wha—?
Is she all right?
It's a doll.
Ichigo!
How's Ruricchi?
It was fake.
Oh no…
Then the real one is…
Yeah. By now, she has most likely
been taken to another location.
What?! At the arena?!
I see. Thanks.
So this Kibune guy and
the Kasumiohji Clan really were…
I can't believe it.
Since when?
I never imagined the Kasumiohji Clan
was rooted this deeply.
In any case,
you guys take Kira to Squad 4!
Yes, sir.
You can count on us.
What are you going to do?
Well…
This is no longer a matter
regarding the succession rites.
One of my own subordinates became
infatuated with the Bakkouto.
This is serious.
What's serious?
Renji!
How did you get here?
It was faint, but I sensed
the Spiritual Pressure of Kira fighting.
So I came here,
and I was right.
Never mind that,
why didn't you contact me sooner, huh?
Very impressive,
Lieutenant Abarai.
And? What do you plan to do
now that you've found us?
Wait a minute, Captain Amagai!
I'm friends with these guys!
So, what's this about
things being serious?
And it looks like
Kira got hurt as well.
The Third Seat from Squad 3 was
connected to the Kasumiohji Clan.
Lieutenant Kira uncovered that,
and defeated him.
We don't have time
to explain details.
But it's a fact that
something bad is going on.
Looks like you've got yourselves
in a sticky situation. I knew it.
Lieutenant Abarai…
If you say you're going to be on our side,
can you lend us a hand?
This is our proof of
the Kasumiohji Clan's treason.
We want you to deliver this to
Head Captain Yamamoto
and explain the situation.
This?
But I'm in no position to…
It would be better suited if you go,
Captain Amagai.
No. I'm going with Kurosaki
to the Kasumiohji mansion.
This is just my thinking…
There's a high probability
that Princess Rurichiyo
is inside the Kasumiohji mansion.
Why do you think so?
Now that their hiding place
has been discovered,
there is no other location for
a cornered person to run.
Anyway, as a captain among
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
I must uncover their objective.
Besides…
If Kibune was their trump card…
Then it means Rurichiyo's life
is in danger unless we hurry.
I understand.
If that's the case, I will definitely
deliver this to the Head Captain.
I'm counting on you, Renji!
Okay, leave it to me!
Captain, preparations are
ready for us to deploy!
Just wait a little longer.
But, Captain, we have been receiving
orders to deploy for a while now.
We can't wait any longer.
I know. However…
Yoruichi Shihoin!
You haven't changed at all.
I have something to tell you.
Well? Won't you hear me out?
Once the Head Captain
gives the order to go,
there is no changing of plans!
I know that!
I'm not asking you for
an answer right now!
Then, what do you
want me to do?
I want to show this to the Head Captain
and have him hear what I have to say!
In that case,
give us some time!
I don't have time!
What's the commotion?
Damn.
Another troublesome character.
What'll we do?
What do you mean?
Ichigo Kurosaki!
I know that you're there.
Come out!
Toshiro…
I knew you'd come here.
Captain Hitsugaya!
Listen to what we have to say!
All right. In that case,
we'll hear it when we arrive
before the Head Captain.
Amagai… You!
Go, Kurosaki!
Leave this place to me!
Captain Amagai!
Thanks!
Let's go, Shu!
– Damn!
– Get them!
We can't have that.
Lieutenant Matsumoto!
Rangiku!
I don't have time to explain!
Please!
I want to let you go…
but it's an order.
Wait, Ichigo!
I'll go!
Rukia!
Go, Ichigo!
Right!
Stand down, Amagai!
Sorry, I can't do that.
It doesn't look like there's
any room for discretion.
In that case…
Reign over the frosted heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Sever, Raika!
Now the real battle begins!
Notice!
It has come to light
that there were
suspicious acts of high treason
found against the Kasumiohji Clan.
All squads of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
will enter the Kasumiohji mansion
immediately and secure this evidence!
You ruffian!
Sorry!
Shu… Do you know
where Rurichiyo is?
There are lots of rooms like that.
Maybe…the one in the back.
Kumoi didn't allow us
to go near there!
Okay, which way?
That way!
Ruricchi…
Rurichiyo, where are you?
Kira! Are you okay?!
Abarai… Why are you here?
My friend got hurt!
It's natural to come visit!
It's really because
you fell behind
and missed the deployment
of your squad, isn't it?
Oh… That's why, huh?
Shh!
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today we'll be talking about
the blue skies inside Las Noches.
Lord Aizen built this space in
Hueco Mundo to replicate the sun.
But I think he only
built this on a whim.
Why are you talking about this?
Looks like the story is
about to take place here,
so I thought I'd help
build up the excitement.
Isn't it because you just
want to appear more often?
You want to appear more often,
don't you, Tosen?
This is unpleasant.