Ichigo and his group had been
defeated by the formidable Espada
when the captains of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads arrived.
Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto
had ordered them
to go to Hueco Mundo.
And each challenged
the Espada to a battle.
Byakuya and Mayuri
had won their battles,
but Kenpachi was still locked in
a fierce match against Nnoitora.
Nnoitora's Hierro was considered
the hardest among the Espada,
and Kenpachi was facing
an uphill battle,
as he was unable to
cut through it.
However, upon seeing
Nnoitora dodge an attack,
Kenpachi realized that he can
be killed and relishes the fight.
Nnoitora overreacts and attacks
Kenpachi with his full force,
and cut off his eye patch.
Fool…
You ripped off my eye patch,
so I wasn't able to hold back.
Are you alive?
Or is it just that
you haven't died yet?
I…
I'm not going to die!
Pray, Santa Teresa!
What?
Is that all you've got?
What's the matter?
You've had enough already?
Damn…
Six…arms!
It's over…Soul Reaper.
Kenpachi!
You can't!
He said so.
This is Kenny's fight.
You heard him, Itchy!
You can't interfere.
Kurosaki!
Isn't this great?!
This is awesome!
This is how it should be!
It's over, you say?!
I've finally gotten a hole myself
and now I'm even with you!
All right, let's get started…
Espada!
What is this?!
I'm the one cutting him!
He's the one who is bleeding!
And yet, he's…
No matter how much I cut him…
He keeps coming back!
I'm the strongest!
The strongest!
You're an eyesore!
Just hurry up and die!
Kenpachi!
At this rate…
I will really die, huh?
Kenny…
I don't enjoy…dying.
Cripes… I have no choice.
It's been awhile, but I guess…
I'll try some Kendo.
What did you say?
When I first joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
the old man pigeon-holed me
and made me do it.
No good! No good!
It just wasn't for me.
Kendo, the way of the sword.
It sounded so smug,
I didn't like it and didn't use it.
But there was one thing
I did like about it.
Did you know?
They say the sword is mightier
when swung with both hands
rather than one.
Huh?
What the hell are you saying?
Isn't that…pretty obvious?!
Nope, it's not.
Come at me!
You don't know, do you?
Just how much…
stronger…
it is.
Has he given up?
He's just standing there like that!
I'm the strongest!
I am the strongest!
Has he given up?
He's just standing there like that!
I'm the strongest!
I am the strongest!
You're still alive?
Unbelievable.
You're one strong dude.
Damn…
See ya.
W-Wait!
What? Stop bugging me.
Where are you going?!
It's not over yet!
Are you stupid?
It ended, just now.
I'm under no obligation to finish off
a guy who can no longer fight.
Is that so?
Then all the more reason.
It's not over yet.
Because I…can still fight!
What's the matter?
Say…
something…
You scared?!
Answer me!
Are you scared of me,
Soul Reaper?!
What a pain.
Oh well…
Come at me!
Why?
The annihilation of this colony
was not part of your orders.
Why did you massacre them?
Shut up.
No one told me
not to kill them either.
Lord Aizen's orders were
to find the Vasto Lordes.
Mass killing goes
against his orders.
Not everyone approves
of Lord Aizen.
The ones coming at us are
elements of the rebellion.
Killing them benefits Lord Aizen,
don't you think?
Was it really for
the sake of Lord Aizen?
Didn't it seem that way to you?
Besides,
if I could kill them off,
they couldn't have
been Vasto Lordes.
I think that goes along
with following orders.
You're just overreacting because
one or two hundred
Hollows were killed.
Think hard before you speak,
Nnoitora.
Of those Hollows,
we just happened to be
fortunate enough to
evolve past that stage.
You still disapprove?
Then come at me.
If you think you can beat me.
You amaze me.
You're still a child.
Even after becoming an Espada.
What?!
Wait! You…
I won't lose!
There's no way I can lose!
I…
Why?
Why did you save me?
I didn't save you.
I simply stopped you from
your suicidal actions to
prevent a shortage of Espada.
Nelliel… I don't like you.
You should know that too.
So why do you follow me around?
Because…
you are weaker than me.
Quit joking around.
Every one feels sorry for me.
Don't they realize that only
rubs salt in my wound?!
I'll show no mercy!
Whether someone is strong,
or whether they're weak.
Whether someone is
a mere child, or a beast.
I'll kill them in one blow!
So that they'll never have
the strength to stand up again.
I'm…
Nnoi…tora?
I was born to fight.
Being pitied by others is
a sign of weakness!
Nelliel, I'm stronger
than you in every way!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
We're talking about Nnoitora today.
The secret to Nnoitora's
strength lies in his Hierro,
said to be the hardest in
the history of all Espada.
With it, he can defend himself
against powerful attacks.
His Resurrección is called
"Santa Teresa."
SANTA TERESA
It seems he can produce
a sickle from his arm.
How about a corkscrew or
a bottle opener, I wonder.
Wouldn't that be convenient?!
Do you wanna get killed?!