Now, my Raiku
has the powers of both Head
Captain Yamamoto’s Ryujinjakka
and the Substitute Soul
Reaper’s Getsugatensho!
As strong as you are, Head Captain…
You cannot remain unscathed after
an attack with such power!
The time has come!
This ends right now!
Oh no!
Head Captain!
Young lady?!
This…can’t be!
Nozomi!
Stop! It’s too much for you!
This young lady…
Is she trying to protect me?
You can’t absorb any more!
Get away, Nozomi!
Please stop!
You’ll die!
Out of the way!
Nozomi…
Head Captain!
Old geezer!
Get a hold of yourself, Head Captain!
Nozomi!
Totally ignored me.
Why?
Why what?
Why did you protect a Mod Soul like me?
Don’t get the wrong idea you fool!
It’ll take more than a thousand years
before I need to be protected by you!
Besides…
You may be a Mod Soul,
but you’re just a young girl.
Be a bit more honest with her!
Old geezer!
Head Captain!
Hey! Old geezer!
Are you all right?!
Head Captain…
Already?!
Rukia! He’s coming!
Right!
Where’s Kageroza?
Ichigo…
Over there.
Kageroza…
The bastard won’t stay down.
Nozomi, you’re okay.
Thank goodness.
It won’t do any good, Nozomi.
You can’t fight with that Zanpakuto.
Substitute Soul Reaper…
Why do you try to stop me?
Because Nozomi doesn’t
want to go with you.
That’s why!
Doesn’t want to go?
Why?
Why do you say that?
What?
What the hell is with you?!
Of course she doesn’t
want to go with you!
Nozomi’s creator…
In other words, Nozomi’s father.
The research is about to be complete.
Complete?
You mean taking over
the World of the Living
and the Soul Society?!
We won’t allow that!
That wouldn’t make Nozomi happy!
Won’t it?
It would make me happy.
So Nozomi should be happy, as well.
Stop spouting nonsense!
Nozomi’s not like you!
Forgive me.
What’s so funny?!
You.
You talk as though you
understand Nozomi.
Unfortunately for you,
no one understands Nozomi
better than I do.
Huh?!
What’re you talking about?
It’s simple, really.
Simply put, Nozomi and I
were born from the Reishi
of a single Soul Reaper.
W-What’s that mean?!
Exactly what it sounded like.
Hey, Nozomi!
What the hell is he talking about?!
I don’t get it!
At least say something!
Come on, Nozomi!
Hey! Answer me!
It seems you haven’t forgotten.
Hey!
Quit laughing at every little thing!
You see…
Nozomi always knew.
If she was captured,
we would become one.
That she would become your enemy.
That’s why she tried
to keep her distance.
You tried to push everyone away.
Didn’t you, Nozomi?
But then, you began to feel
an attachment to these people
who tried to protect you.
What’s your name?
Where are you from?
I won’t tell you.
Go away! Pervert!
Keep your hands off me, pervert!
Not my concern.
Don’t worry, Nozomi.
From here on, we’ll protect you.
That won’t be necessary.
I’ll fix things so he
won’t have to protect me.
If I enter here and close the gateway,
no one will find me.
Ichigo and the others, all of
us, said we’d protect you!
Is this what you really want?
Lots of good things will happen
if you keep on living!
You guys are all alike.
You’re all lousy perverts.
Don’t go putting me with him!
At any rate, I don’t know
why I want to protect you.
But I heard it…
a voice telling me I
have to protect you.
You are an idiot, after all.
I’m a burden.
Everyone tries to protect me…
But I don’t have the power
to do the same for them.
But when I thought of
wanting to protect you…
I had a sword.
That’s why she couldn’t
tell you anything!
You nerdy bastard!
Quit mouthing off like
you know everything!
Don’t go telling
Nozomi how she feels!
Mod Soul…
Nozomi is me, and I am Nozomi.
Ask Nozomi herself if what
I am saying is true.
Nozomi…
You bastard!
I said not to laugh!
Ichigo…
Kageroza!
You don’t understand anything!
Ichigo!
You idiot!
You plan on fighting
me in that condition?
However…
It’s futile in your
current condition!
Damn it!
Nozomi…
Come, we’re going back
to where we belong!
To how we should be!
Come on, let’s go.
No.
I don’t want to go!
I see. How unfortunate.
In that case, I’ll take you by force!
Damn it!
You bastard!
Stupid bastard!
Come!
-You…
-No!
-Damn it!
No…
Take this, you!
Nozomi!
What?!
Now’s your chance! Run!
What?
Get away, you!
What’re you waiting for?! Run!
Get away, Nozomi!
Damn you!
You’re a Mod Soul,
but you’re a total failure!
I’ll eliminate you
completely from both
the World of the Living
and the Soul Society!
You pathetic fool!
Tenran!
Kon!
Nozomi!
What?!
Genryusai Yamamoto!
Sorry, I don’t have
time for you now.
Come back here!
You saved my life!
Thank you!
I was so scared!
Even now, you still have your guard up.
Behind you!
How foolish.
What’s the matter?
You…get away now.
What’re you saying?
We’re going together!
I can’t run anymore.
But you can make it alone.
I’m not going without you!
Come on! Get up!
Run!
Come on, hurry!
Get up!
Come on!
Man, you’re heavy! Come on!
Kon…
Huh?
You told me once before…to live.
Now it’s my turn.
Live.
What about you?!
No! We’re going together!
I’ll be okay. I promise.
I won’t die.
But…
No! We’re not doing it that way!
I’m getting away together with you!
You’re such a stupid pervert.
Nozomi…
Shitotsusansen.
Huh?!
Why?
Hey, Nozomi!
Why’re you doing this to me?!
That’s…
My Spiritual Pressure’s…
Hang in there for just one more attack.
Nozomi, I have you now!
Nozomi!
Get down, Nozomi!
It’s gone!
Please… Just one is enough.
Getsugatensho!
Ichigo…
I’m okay.
Let’s go back…
To where we belong.
Impossible.
How did you…
I took out a little insurance.
Back when I slipped near the slopes.
My Raiku is even capable
of replicating myself!
What?
The me you defeated was
nothing more than a replica.
Goodbye.
Ichigo!
Nozomi… Let’s go back…
to where we belong.
Nozomi!
Nozomi…
Why do that for me?!
Why do I always end
up getting protected,
and not able to do anything?!
There’s no point for
me to live like that!
Damn it!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Boss!
We’ve completed freezed the space.
All right, then let’s go and help
rescue Kurosaki and the others.
Just a minute!
Zaraki and Madarame’s Spiritual
Pressures have produced a fissure!
That’s not good!
We’ll need to deal with that first!
Whoa!
Now the protective barrier was destroyed
due to Miss Nozomi’s technique!
What?!
The Head Captain and Kurosaki’s
combined techniques
opened a huge hole in space!
I didn’t make it in time.