Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Take her!
Don’t just stand there!
Take her already!
That’s your job!
Don’t let her go even if it kills you!
Renji!
A-Abarai.
Don’t just stand there, you fools!
After them! All lieutenants, go!
Yes, sir.
Go ahead.
Now run! Itegumo!
Bite! Gonryomaru!
Crush him! Gegetsuburi!
Impossible…!
He’s not even using his zanpakuto…
I told you, I could see your moves…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Why?
Why do you keep trying
to save Rukia over and over again?
Let me ask you instead.
Aren’t you Rukia’s brother?
How come you don’t try
to rescue Rukia?
Such a foolish question…
Even if you learned why,
someone like you wouldn’t understand.
It seems talking serves no purpose.
Here I come.
There is only one path left for me.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
I will kill you.
And once again,
I will capture Rukia and
execute her myself this time.
I won’t let you do that.
That’s why I’m here.
Let me go! Please let me go, Renji!
I must help Ichigo!
Will you just shut up?!
We’re running away so stay quiet!
What if someone hears us?!
Your voice is louder than mine.
That guy…
Ichigo said he owed you a favor.
Me? A favor?
Yeah…
Rukia saved my life.
Rukia changed my destiny.
I became a Soul Reaper
after meeting Rukia.
That’s why I’m able to protect everyone
and fight like this.
Because of me, Ichigo’s fate
has been changed…
and I hurt him terribly.
Nothing I do can
make amends for that.
You always think too much.
You’ve always been like that.
You’re not as bad as you think.
So stop blaming yourself
for everything.
You’re not strong enough to
carry it all on your shoulders.
Share it.
Put some of your burdens on my shoulders,
and Ichigo’s shoulders.
Share it a little and
stand up slowly.
That’s the reason
why we became strong.
Have faith in him, Rukia.
I’m sorry, Renji.
Fool. No need to apologize.
Thank you.
Fool. No need to say thanks either.
Sis…
Sis!
Wait Kiyone, hey!
Huh?!
Hold it, Soi Fon!
Do not move!
Sir Genryusai!
It was a lieutenant that took off
with the criminal.
We can always find
a replacement.
We can take our time capturing him.
However…
I cannot forgive you two!
As captains, you have done something
you must not have done.
I’m sure you both understand
what that is.
Captain Ukitake…
Captain, you’re in danger!
Stay back, Kiyone!
Well, we’ve got no choice!
Guess we should make
a run for it, Ukitake!
Wha--?!
Shunsui!
Wait, Kyoraku!
My subordinates are still…!
Calm down!
Try fighting the old man there,
and everyone will end up dead.
It’s gonna be okay with
the both of us.
Can’t you feel it?
There’s someone on
our side getting closer.
Prepare! We’re almost to the ground!
Captain…
Can’t stand just being a bystander.
Lowly scum!
What you all have done was
a shameless act of betrayal
as officers of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
But rest assured…
I will kill you so that you will not
bring any more shame.
Let go of me! Who are you?!
Don’t make such a fuss.
Short-tempered, as always.
You are…?!
You are…
Yoruichi…!
It’s been a long time, Soi Fon.
Have you regained consciousness, Isane?
Captain Unohana!
I…
Stay quiet. It seems you received
the lightest blow,
but still you should not
move around too much.
Take us down, Minazuki.
Are you hurt, Captain Unohana?
Lieutenant Kotetsu!
No.
Release the others and return, Minazuki.
Their wounds are not serious.
Being in Minazuki’s belly should have
helped them recover.
Lay them down in the Relief Station
until they wake up.
Yes.
Such Spiritual Pressure.
Is someone still there?
Captain Kuchiki is still battling the Ryoka.
The other captains have
gone elsewhere to fight.
We will not be able to
stop them ourselves.
Follow me, Isane.
There is a certain place
that I would like to go.
We’ve come quite far.
Yes. This will be far enough to
put everyone else out of harm’s way.
Nanao… you’re the last!
You two are too fast.
I must say, you got here fast.
No brats have ever been successful
escaping from me.
Now come, you greenhorns!
But just my fists won’t do any longer.
Head Captain Shigekuni
Genryusai Yamamoto
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
His Spiritual Pressure is enormous.
Even two captains together
might not be enough to win.
There’s only one thing I can do…
Leave!
I don't have the patience…
to teach a mere infant like you
how to breathe.
It’s all right, Nanao. Hang in there.
Sorry.
I shouldn’t have brought you with me.
I can’t believe it.
He crushed my whole being
just by looking at me.
“Even two captains together might
not be enough to win”?
No, I was so naive.
This is no good.
No, Captain Kyoraku…
Your Flash Step is impressive.
Now you’re able to cover
so much ground.
Thanks.
Looking back, the two of you
had exceptional strength.
You weren’t good with the girls
and your behavior was wild…
But you were intelligent and
your ability to see the truth
far outshone the others, Shunsui.
And you, Jushiro,
you had a weak constitution,
but were daring and popular.
Everyone looked up to you.
And when it came time to battle,
you defied the imagination.
No one could hold a candle
to either one of you.
You were both strong-willed.
You never let up on training
and honed your strength.
You were the first captains
from the academy that I created.
You were my pride and joy,
like my own sons.
I believed in you!
That although we had different thoughts,
we walked the same path.
I am deeply regretful.
Master Genryusai…
Do not say anything.
Words have no use any longer.
Draw your swords!
What is the meaning of this, you two?
You intend to fight me without
releasing your zanpakuto?
Do we really have to fight,
Old Man Yama?
Silence!
I have taught you that I will not
forgive anyone who defies justice.
You’re the one who also taught us
to carry out our own justice,
Old Man Yama.
You also taught us to become
strong for that, Master!
Such foolish talk!
You cannot defy the justice of the world
to push through your own justice!
Then what is the justice of the world?
Master Genryusai!
Did you not hear me?
As I said…
the time for words has passed!
All things in the universe turn to ashes.
Ryujinjakka.
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Master Genryusai, what would I have to do
to maintain a muscular body like yours?
It is truly magnificent.
Well, you train each and every day.
But you weren’t able to maintain your hair.
I’m deeply regretful!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
– Golden!
Take this! Golden Cannon Ball!
Jinta homerun!
Let’s go! Karakura King!
When did you…?!
Karin Death Dodge!
Not again!
Go-Go-Golden!
Mission complete!
We did it! Perfect!
What’re you looking at?!
Hey, I thought this was
the Guide to Soul Reapers.
Tune in again!