Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
Rukia!
Hang in there!
What's wrong?!
You're injured.
That you, Ichigo…?
Don't worry.
How can I not worry?!
What happened?!
This Spiritual Pressure…
She's not a Hollow?
She doesn't have
a mask or a hole.
Are you this town's Soul Reaper?
Who are you?!
Hand her over.
What?
I don't know who you are,
but I'm not giving you Rukia!
I see…
So you’re
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
How do you know about me?!
Somenomai…
Tsukishiro.
That was…!
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren.
Damn you…
Getsugatensho!
Who the hell are you?
Both Tsukishiro and Hakuren
are Rukia's techniques!
Yes. That's why they
are my techniques.
What?!
Wait!
Damn it!
Rukia!
Hang in there! Who is she?!
She's…Sodenoshirayuki…
My Zanpakuto…
What?!
Rukia! Rukia!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Here you go.
Down I go.
I hope Sister is okay.
Orihime is with her,
so there's no need to worry.
No problem.
Continuing on…
Kuchiki said that the woman
was Sodenoshirayuki, right?
Yeah.
But I never imagined
a Zanpakuto
would take physical form
and attack its owner.
For now…
I’m having Yoruichi check out
the Soul Society.
We should wait for
Kuchiki to recover first.
Rukia regained consciousness!
Sister!
Don't worry, Kon. I'm all right.
But, but…
Jeez… She said she's all right!
Why don't you trust in
Orihime's powers?!
So Kuchiki, what happened
on the other side?
It was a nightmare…
My name is Muramasa.
Tonight marks the end of
the Soul Reapers reign
over the Zanpakuto.
From here on,
the Zanpakuto
will rule over the Soul Reapers.
The Zanpakuto will
rule the Soul Reapers?
What do you mean?
It's exactly what it sounds like.
I told you.
Your Zanpakuto have already
been freed from your control.
Roar, Zabimaru!
This stuff about Zanpakuto
is important, but…
Where is Old Man Yama?
I believe he's the one
who called us here.
Could you tell us?
Genryusai Yamamoto
has been sealed away.
His Zanpakuto, Ryujinjakka,
refused to work with us.
Therefore, your Zanpakuto,
Katenkyokotsu, Sogyonokotowari,
and Minazuki,
combined their Spiritual Pressures
to seal his power away.
What?!
Captain…
Ridiculous… Is it even possible
to seal away the Head Captain?
This is truly interesting.
Do you think we believe that?
Whether you believe me or not,
it's the truth.
Ikkaku!
Captain Kyoraku,
Captain Ukitake!
It's pointless talking
to him any longer!
Kyoraku!
I guess I have no choice…
Captain!
Isane, get Lieutenant Sasakibe!
Yes, ma'am!
Captain!
I'll help you out!
Kyoraku! Let's retreat for now!
That seems like a good idea.
Oh?
It looks like it's
going to spit poison.
Everyone, run!
You can't escape.
What's going on?!
Where did the captains
run off to?!
I want to take them on!
There's nowhere to run,
Soul Reapers.
Damn it!
They're just doing
whatever they want!
Do you suppose everyone
is all right?
Yeah! We shouldn't have to
worry about the captains!
How's your Zanpakuto, Rukia?
It's no good.
I can't use my Shikai.
I see…
Here they come!
What?!
Rukia…
Bakudo Number Sixty One…
Rikujokoro.
Brother!
Rukia!
Are you all right?
Captain!
Don't let your guard down.
I see…
The captains are
truly impressive.
They certainly have the strength
to control powerful Zanpakuto.
Brother!
My name is Senbonzakura.
Go.
But…
I will not repeat myself.
You should know better than anyone
about how hopeless it is
to challenge my thousand blades
with a single sword.
Not good enough.
It's useless!
Brother!
Wait, Rukia!
Let go of me, Renji!
Captain Kuchiki is all right.
Anyway, look around you!
Could that be…?
Tsuginomai, Hakuren.
I got separated from Renji.
I managed to get to
the World of the Living
through a Senkaimon while
fighting Sodenoshirayuki.
Zanpakuto resisting the will
of their Soul Reapers
and attacking them…
I've never heard of such a thing.
Anyway, a Zanpakuto's
true body exists
within their Soul Reaper's
inner world.
What is a Zanpakuto's true body?
A Zanpakuto has a consciousness
that controls its power—
its true body.
A Soul Reaper can draw power
from a Zanpakuto
by conversing with its true body.
Does Zangetsu have a true body?
Yeah.
Naturally, my Benihime
has one too.
The Seireitei…
Is everyone all right?
They're all right.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
still haven't been destroyed.
Yoruichi! Back already?
Lady Yoruichi,
how is the Soul Society?!
My brother…
What about my brother?!
Don't panic.
I'm going to tell you.
The Seireitei was
in a terrible state.
The battle appeared
to have ended,
but buildings were in ruin
and many were injured.
I looked for someone
who could talk to me.
I ended up going to
Squad Four's relief center.
I met Captain Unohana there,
as well as Captain Ukitake
and other members
who had been staying in
Squad Four's barracks.
So those bandits wreaked havoc
and then suddenly disappeared?
That's right.
There are many
injured in Seireitei.
Several buildings burned
to the ground,
starting with
Squad One's barracks.
The damage is extensive.
Luckily, the relief center
was all right.
Squad Two and Twelve's buildings
were also intact.
Captain Soi Fon and
the rest of the Stealth Force
are already going
after the Zanpakuto.
And I hear Captain Kurotsuchi
has begun to look into
this phenomenon as well.
For now, let's use
Squad Four's barracks
as an information center.
We need to find skilled
Soul Reapers among the uninjured
and use them to
boost our security.
Please take care of it.
With the Head Captain missing,
we need to pull together.
Yes.
I guess I have no choice.
I'm going to go back to
the World of the Living.
I have to ask Kisuke's opinion
about this phenomenon of
Zanpakuto rebelling
against its owner.
You mean, you’re going to have him
look into it as well, correct?
That sounds about right.
Well, that's great news.
The captains are all right.
But that doesn't
change the fact that
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are in terrible shape.
Depressing…
Lots of problems.
Even more depressing…
Kurosaki, has anything changed
with your Zanpakuto?
Not really.
I see.
To tell you the truth,
there had been reports recently
in the Soul Society
of Soul Reapers having trouble
with their Zanpakuto.
For the record, I had no
problems with my Benihime.
In other words, the enemy's
control over Zanpakuto
only stretches as far
as the Soul Society
and has no effect on Zanpakuto
in the World of the Living.
Is the enemy's power unable to
reach the World of the Living
or is there some other
reason for this?
I guess we won't find out
until we look into this.
When dawn breaks, I'll return to
the Soul Society once more.
Please do.
Yoruichi…
What about my brother?
I’m told they have confirmed
the whereabouts of
the other captains, lieutenants,
and high-ranking officers.
But Byakuya is
the only one still missing.
Brother…
It's all right.
Byakuya would never die.
You know, better than anyone,
how strong he is.
Yes.
Good evening!
Bad news, Ichigo!
What do you want at this hour?!
We've got an emergency!
Big problem.
Rukia disappeared!
What?!
Sister!
There is evidence that
a Senkaimon has been opened.
It seems she went back
to the Soul Society.
What is Rukia doing?!
Her wounds haven't
even healed yet.
She must have been quite
worried about Byakuya.
I understand.
Urahara, open up a Senkaimon.
I'm going after Rukia.
Wait a second, Kurosaki!
It's dangerous to go to the other
side in our current situation.
We need to gather
more information first.
But we can't ignore Rukia!
Still…
Let him go, Kisuke.
I was planning to go in
the morning anyway.
I might be able to work faster
if someone comes with me.
Yoruichi…
Please, Urahara!
Good grief…
It looks like I can't stop you.
I have no choice.
I will make preparations
to assist you.
Try not to rush into things.
Okay.
Let's go, Ichigo.
Wait up, Rukia.
Don't do anything rash.
Sister! I'm coming right away!
I see you're ready to go.
Yeah!
You're going to have to fight lots
of Zanpakuto in that form.
Yeah…
You're going to have to fight
swords with your bare hands.
Sister, forgive my cowardice.
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today, I'm going to be
showing all of the names
of the Resurrección
that I haven't featured.
Mamut, Tigre Estoque, Cierva,
Leona, Anaconda…
This is how they're written.
Why are you showing them
at this point?
I thought we still had
time to introduce them.
But then this all happened.
If we don't do this now, they won't
be able to rest in peace.
This segment is pretty
difficult to host, you know.
How's it difficult?
Why don't you give it a try then?
Huh?