Liquor and Gasoline, Smiles and Tears
You people throw the word
brother around too much!
Neither Gin-san nor I am interested
in being brothers, you fool!
Shinpa—
Why would you come here
when it's already too late?!
Gin-san!
Gin-san, hang in there!
Idiot...
Why did you come?
Yamazaki-san told me everything.
That you guys were here...
That he wouldn't be returning...
Don't say that.
Who went and decided that it was over?
Stay out of this.
Th-That guy will be back.
I swear I'll bring him back to you.
So can you wait just a little longer?
It won't take much longer.
Really.
Please. I promise, okay?
Damn...
It's okay.
You've done enough.
So Gin-san, don't disappear on us.
Even if Hajime-nii returns
and Earth is saved,
we won't be smiling if
you're not with us.
It's okay if you don't
act like a big brother.
It's okay if you're the total
opposite of a role model.
It's okay if you aren't
showing us the way to go.
As long as you're with us
when we've lost our way...
As long as you're by our side,
sharing the pain and sorrow...
As long as everybody's by
our side, we'll be smiling.
No matter how difficult it may be.
Shinpachi...
So can you let us take it from here?
Don't worry.
I'm no longer the crybaby
little brother of Obi Hajime,
nor am I a student of the
School of Beam Saber.
I am the successor of the
School of Tendo Mushin
and Odd Jobs' Shimura Shinpachi.
Wait, Shin—
Gin-chan!
Hold on, Gin-chan!
Kagura-chan...
Take care of Gin-san for me.
Didn't you hear me tell you to wait?
Are you insane?
You want to fight a man who completely
destroyed your big brother?
You seem to be mistaken.
Gin-san didn't come here to kill you.
He came to save you.
If Gin-san had come to kill you,
you wouldn't be standing
before me right now.
But it doesn't matter now.
I'll get Hajime-nii back
even if I have to kill you,
no matter how much
pain it may cause me.
If you go through life with the blood
of your benefactor on your hands,
you won't be the only one
who suffers as a result.
I, Shimura Tae, will be the
witness for this battle.
The School of Tendo Mushin
and the School of Beam Saber
in a no-holds-barred duel.
Fight as true warriors to the very end.
Boss lady...
Please watch us, Obi-one-niisama.
The crybaby who always
followed you around
and all of us who always
admired your strength
have become much stronger
after meeting you and everyone else.
Strong enough to stop you.
Begin now!
Hajime-nii!
Come, Shin-bo!
I have seen the future of
the School of Tendo Mushin.
You've become so strong,
Shin-bo, Otae-chan...
Point.
We've lost contact with Kenofi?
Impossible, he's the
Galaxy Sword Master.
Curses!
Do you have any idea how much money
we poured into making that thing?!
It was a mistake to rely on a native
monkey to carry out this mission!
How dare he die before
he could be of any use?!
No matter what you spend on it, junk is—
Shut up.
Keep that filthy mouth of yours shut.
He's not a piece of junk.
And he's not a weapon.
At long last, he's finally made it home.
The samurai is back in the
country of the samurai.
No more will you toy with
human lives and emotions!
We will make you pay!
Apprehend them!
What?!
Too bad for you, monkeys.
That was an excellent strike.
Shin-bo, you've come a long way.
I'm very happy.
You've always been a liar.
And that hasn't changed.
You always gave in to my persistence,
and let me win once while
saying that I'd gotten stronger.
You were always joking around.
I was serious this time.
Your voices pierced through
this cold metal body.
Your voice,
Otae-chan's voice,
Instructor Sakata's voice...
Your voices summoned my soul
from this lump of metal.
Which is why I was able to beat
my other half at the very end.
I couldn't match up to the rest of you,
but for a moment, I think I
knew what true strength was.
I can finally come home
without feeling ashamed.
Truly, thank you very hamnida.
You shouldn't leave, then.
Stay here forever.
We can all play with beam
sabers together again.
I'll do a better job of preparing
your bath this time.
So...
Don't talk like this is the end.
Don't leave Shinpachi and
the boss lady alone.
Don't worry.
I just left something up in space.
Did you think that we wouldn't
be prepared for such an event?
Even if Kenofi is disabled, the energy
that's accumulated inside won't vanish.
At the moment, he's an unexploded bomb
that can destroy an entire planet.
Do you know what will happen if
we give him a little stimulation?
You bastard!
Huh?
Don't touch me!
What?
Are you guys okay?!
Toshi!
Stop them!
They're going to
discharge the energy in Obi Hajime
and obliterate Earth!
So once I've picked up
what I left behind,
I'll come back.
In the meantime,
Instructor Sakata, look
after everyone for me.
Let's go, guys.
Didn't you hear me?
You didn't forget the teachings of the
School of Beam Saber again, did you?
It's okay.
Don't worry, Obi-one-niisama.
We won't cry anymore.
So just promise... Just promise us...
Yeah...
I promise that we'll meet again.
Fire!
Shoot that thing down!
It's too late!
Beam cannon energy fully charged!
We're locked onto Kenofi's coordinates!
What?! Impossible!
Kenofi has...
That man is pointing
his beam cannon at us!
It means nothing! Open fire!
Listen up, you two.
Tears are handy for washing away
troubling and sad feelings.
But when you grow up, you'll learn
that there are things so sad, they
can never be washed away by tears.
That there are painful memories
that should never be washed away.
So people who are truly strong
laugh when they want to cry.
They endure all of the pain and sorrow
while laughing with everybody else.
You can cry all you want right now.
But one day, you must become
samurai strong enough not to cry.
Kabuki First District
Why don't you drop by, big guy?
Snack Smile
We've got a bunch of cute girls!
How about it, gentlemen?
Is that true?
We can choose anyone we want?
Yup, you can choose anyone,
and they're all babes.
Really, then...
We'll take the babe named Otae.
Oh, it's you guys again.
You keep coming back every day.
I told you that you're wasting your time.
We haven't heard anything from Otae-chan
since she went on leave a month back,
and we have no idea
when she's returning.
We're struggling right now after
losing our top attraction,
so could you not disrupt our business?
It's been a month already.
That man saved our planet,
but we weren't able to save anything.
I heard that Shinpachi-kun hasn't
been down to Odd Jobs since.
This is when they really need
other people by their sides,
but the person they truly want
by their sides is no longer here.
If we go visit, we'll only
put more stress on them.
I don't believe I can make
them smile right now.
All we can do now is
wait and have faith
that the two of them
will be able to overcome
their sorrow and move forward.
Our job is to smile and welcome
them back when the time comes.
For now, we wait.
But when the time comes...
Yes, I'm sure they'll smile again.
Man, that was so much fun.
Yes, it's been so long since the two of us
were able to have some fun together.
But I wanted to stay a little longer.
That was long enough.
We don't want to trouble
everyone any longer.
Oh, it's Kondo-san and Kyubei-san.
Haven't seen you in a while.
The Shimura siblings
are back from Waiiha!
Here, we brought chocolate covered
macadamia nuts as a souvenir.
Vacation?
Yes, we went to Planet Waiiha,
where it's always summer.
You know, with all these new long arcs,
we haven't had a chance to take a break.
So we decided to use the paid
vacation days we've accumulated
and take some time off together.
So, Planet Waiiha was awesome!
You're probably thinking that
vacationing in Waiiha is too cliche.
But there's a reason it's considered cliche.
Ah, I understand what you mean.
Waiiha is the best!
How am I supposed to understand?!
Why would you choose this
timing to go on vacation?!
I thought that you were both
moping around inside your house,
but you're completely tanned!
Dark as chocolate covered
macadamia nuts!
Can't you tell, Kondo?
They're pushing themselves.
This wasn't an ordinary vacation.
They left Edo so we wouldn't
have to see them suffer.
And they're acting cheerful
so we don't notice that fact.
Don't say anything that'll
dig the wound open again.
Well, I'm glad that you
enjoyed yourselves.
But it must have cost
a lot to go to Waiiha.
You must have had a lot saved up.
Oh, we paid for it with money
we received from Obi-one-niisama's
life insurance.
What wound? They dug up a
whole new grave on their own!
I can see him! I can see
Obi-one-niisama rolling in the grave!
Obi-one-niisama made arrangements for
the money to be given to this
dojo if anything happened to him,
so the money was meant
to be used for the dojo.
Really? So you went on vacation?
That's why...
You used that money to go on vacation?
We were happy to use it
for macadamia nuts.
You used the money for macadamia nuts?!
Wait!
You spent the money from
his life on nuts?!
It wasn't much money.
He's gotta be mad!
He's going to shoot
beams down from heaven!
Wait, Kyubei-kun!
These siblings are a lot
stronger than I expected!
They've overcome their brother's death
and started trampling all over it!
You must understand, Kondo.
They're trying to say goodbye
to their memory of Obi Hajime.
So they exchanged his life for
chocolate covered macadamia nuts
so the memories will
melt like chocolate.
No, that can't be it.
Don't you understand, Kondo?
Macadamia nuts are really good.
You just want to eat macadamia nuts!
Please help yourself, Kondo-san.
Please enjoy the fruits of the legacy
left behind by Obi-one-niisama's life.
I can't eat that!
I've never eaten chocolate
that was so meaningful!
Hajime-nii...
We won't let your wishes go to waste.
We will restore this dojo
and make it as busy as it
was when you were here
with these macadamia nuts.
Uh, I'm pretty sure
you wasted the money!
Why would you need macadamia nuts?!
Hello!
Look, Shin-chan.
They're here already.
Excuse me.
Is this the dojo that's
looking for students?
We've been expecting you!
Welcome to Kodokan!
Is it true that you'll give us
macadamia nuts if we train in the sword?
You're just using the nuts as bait!
Shinpachi-kun! They're not
looking for a home dojo!
They're just plain homeless!
And what happened to your tan?!
It's okay.
We can start with macadamia nuts
and hope they learn to love the sword.
If that's what it takes to
protect the sword he loved...
To protect this samurai country...
Hey, who cares about swords?
Give us the macadamia nuts already!
You should be looking for work
instead of begging for nuts.
Shut up!
Don't be in such a rush.
No need to worry.
You'll get all the nuts you want,
if you can land a clean hit on Sakata
Gintoki, substitute instructor
for the School of Tendo
Mushin Macadamia.
You guys...
I promise you this.
By the time you get to eat your nuts,
you'll all be functional
members of society again.
Wait, this is turning into
a different kind of school!
So promise me something.
No matter how difficult the training may be
or what kinds of hardships you face in life,
never stop smiling.
That's the one and only rule in
the School of Tendo Mushin Macadamia.
Eternal Instructor
Obi Hajime
Isn't that right,
Instructor Obi-one?
That's fine!
Gang up on him!
Give us the macadamia nuts!
Okay, next!
Hold on!
What happened to the swords?! This
is turning into a kung fu dojo!
Is this a dojo where we get beat
up in return for macadamia nuts?!
Stop worrying about the
details and just smile!
How can I do that?!
Kondo, do you understand?
I sure do.
Hey, they won't help you
become decent samurai.
I'll take you on!
Bring it!
Nonsense.
The macadamia nuts will be mine!
That's not the point here!
Well, let's get going,
Shinpachi.
Shin-bo.
Yes!
Obi-one-niisama, I'm sorry.
We can't use the money that
you left for our dojo.
There hasn't been time for a
proper burial, but I promise to
put you in a grave next to our father.
So don't worry about us.
The two of you can enjoy your
liquor and gasoline together.
It's okay.
Shin-chan and I
and our wonderful friends
are doing just fine.
Announcement
Three years after Benizakura
Arc the New Translation,
we now have a completely original
story by the author Sorachi Hideaki,
which delves into the past.
Gintama the Movie: The Final Act!
Odd Jobs Forever!
Watch as the Gintama
anime comes to an end!
In theaters July 6th
Wait, what's this about?!
Hold on a sec!
Where did they get that idea?!
What's this Final Act business?!
What? The manga isn't over yet!
Is this just the usual
fooling around again?!
Gin-san and the Yaksha know nothing!
Dog Food Doesn't
Taste Like You Think
Next time: Dog Food Doesn't
Nobody said anything to me about this!
Gintama as usual.
Odd Jobs as usual.
Hey, can you hear me?!
Hey, Fujita!
Hey, Shinji!
The trio plus one animal,
forever...
Hey...
Are you listening to me?!