I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Did you do it again, Ikkaku?
Sooner or later, there won't be
anyone for you to fight here.
Then we'll just have to go
to the next area.
Why don't you wipe your face?
That's not very beautiful.
Impatience, a short temper,
irritability...
At the time...
I was filled with
those tendencies.
I didn't belong in Soul Society...
I didn't belong anywhere.
Battles and pain...
Those were the only things
that felt real to me.
Isn't there anyone strong?!
I want to fight!
Isn't there even just one or
two people who want to die?!
Who's that?!
Wha-?!
You should leave.
Kenny is in high spirits today.
He's going to pummel you!
He's going to pummel me
because he's in a good mood?
I don't know what that's
supposed to mean...
You sure are stupid.
When he's in a good mood,
he can't hold back!
He ends up having fun!
What?!
Wait!
Don't lay a hand on her.
Aren't you going to run away?
Tough luck...
I'm also in high spirits!
Ikkaku...
Don't help me.
I know.
You seem strong.
Yeah...
I'm strong, too.
I'm looking forward to it.
Here I go.
It's heavy!
Wh-Who is this guy?!
Not only do his blows
land heavily,
but he's incredibly fast too.
This is a first.
Huh?
Ever since I came here,
I've never had this much fun!
That's good.
What is this?
I can't see most of their hits...
Kenny is smiling!
That's too bad...
It's going to end soon.
Wha-?!
That was fun.
It's been a while since
I enjoyed myself.
Wait!
What's this? You're still alive?
What are you thinking?!
Why won't you finish me off?!
You win!
Sorry...
I'm not interested in guys
who've become unable to fight.
Anyway, I've got no obligation
to finish you off.
You've got to be kidding!
Are you mocking me?!
Kill me!
If you like to fight,
then don't tell me to kill you!
Don't accept a loss
and wish for death!
Accept that you've lost
when you die!
If you've lost and
you manage to live,
that just means that you're lucky.
When that happens,
just think about surviving!
What?
Survive and think about
killing the guy
who almost killed you!
I didn't hold back when
I fought you...
You managed to live
because you were lucky.
Live.
Live, and try to kill me again!
W-Wait!
You... Tell me your name!
Kenpachi!
Kenpachi of Zaraki!
Kenpachi...of Zaraki...
When my wounds had healed,
I looked everywhere for him
so I could fight him once more.
But I couldn't find him anywhere...
It's been a while...
How are you?
Yumichika, huh? I'm okay...
So, what did you come
to tell me today?
I've heard something interesting.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads?!
From this day forward...
As a member of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads,
be aware of your duties...
- and devote yourselves to them.
- I heard that he defeated
- That is all!
- the former captain one-on-one and
- Break up into your squads!
- immediately became the new captain.
Being a captain is probably
the best way
for him to fight as much
as he likes.
He's going to protect
this disgusting world?
Him?
No... He's not that sort of guy.
Want to take a look?
Of course! I'll track him
down anywhere,
even if he's in hell!
I knew you'd say that.
Hmm...
So that's what we can
expect this time...
Why is there a child here?!
Go away!
I'm Lieutenant Yachiru Kusajishi.
Huh?!
Kenny!
I'm Squad 11 Captain,
Kenpachi Zaraki!
Listen up! I won't ask you
where you're from,
what your age is or what
your personal history is like!
I won't restrict any viewpoints here,
nor will I sanction any of them!
There's just one thing I want!
What I want out of you...
is strength!
I like strong guys...
Guys who can fight!
I feel the same way.
I've come just as you told me to!
It's a team of caterpillars!
Lieutenant!
He's already slaughtered
fifteen Soul Reapers!
You mustn't underestimate him!
But...
All right! I'll go!
Wait.
Captain...
Get the guys who went first to pull out.
They're in the way.
Kenny!
Go, go, Kenny!
4...5...
6...7...
You did it, Kenny!
This is bad...
This is perfect...
I was feeling unsatisfied...
Hold on!
That's really bad, Captain.
Yeah. You're trying to keep
all the fun for yourself...
What are you doing?
I told you to pull back.
A contest!
Hey, Kenny, it's a contest!
It's a contest to see who can
slice off the most tails!
A contest, a contest!
Oh well... I'll join you!
But if you get in my way,
I'll slice you first!
All right!
Good morning,
Third Seat Madarame!
Hey!
You're...
Renji Abarai!
Oh yeah... You came from
Captain Aizen's squad.
As soon as you joined,
you got into a huge fight
and got thrown in
the punishment cell.
So what do you want?
Please! Teach me how to fight!
Please!
Seven... eight...
Ten... You would have died
ten times by now.
Once more please!
Why do you want to become
strong so badly?
Why?
There's someone I want to surpass.
This will be our last day.
Wha-?!
I don't have anything else
to teach you...
But I still...
You figure out the rest yourself!
Unless you want people to say that
you're a copy of me
for the rest of your life...
I wanted to see your Bankai.
Bankai?
You can do it, right?
Why don't you use it?
Are you hiding it?
It's my style.
Your style? Such a foolish style!
I'm also chasing someone...
I'm desperate.
I'll tell you my name.
Ikkaku Madarame!
Remember that!
Huh?
The next time we fight,
it'll be to the death.
It'll also be your final battle.
Telling your name to
the one you plan to defeat
is a sign of respect.
Someone who assumes
he's going to die in battle...
should at least want to know
who defeated him
before he dies.
Thank you very much.
Is it true?
Captain Aizen joined
the Hollows?
You saw those Menos Grande, too,
didn't you?
But...there hasn't been
any formal explanation yet...
- I refuse.
- Huh?
Sorry... Ask someone else.
H-Hold on a second, Ikkaku!
You're the only person
who can do this!
Aside from you...
There isn't any lieutenant
who can do a Bankai!
E-Even if there was one...
I know it's presumptuous!
I think that you're the only one
who can do it!
It could be Squad 3, 5 or 9!
You're the only one who
can fill the space
that Aizen and the others left!
You should be the next captain!
Ikkaku!
You idiot...
I don't plan on telling anyone aside
from you and Yumichika
about my Bankai.
If it went public,
guys like you would begin to
tell me to become a captain.
So what of it?
This is the time when
we need to find a new captain
as soon as possible.
It's neither this time nor that.
I have no plans on becoming
a captain.
Becoming a captain means that
I can't fight under Captain Zaraki.
Your wish is to surpass
Byakuya Kuchiki...
I have one wish...
To fight under him...and die.
That's all...
If you understand,
then don't bring it up again.
Crap...
Ikkaku...Madarame...
I'm glad I asked for your name...
I thought so...
I knew you were alive, Ikkaku.
Of course.
I'm really lucky today!
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
Oh no!
I can't cancel the Squad Funeral
for Ikkaku!
What?
The Lieutenant really got
into preparing it,
and she doesn't want to cancel it!
Baldy, which picture do you want
to use for your funeral?
I'm going to make it a fun one!
Give me a break, Lieutenant...
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Yeah! Today, I'm finally going to
put my plan into action!
Umm... What would that be, Kon...
First, I take his gigai...
EXTRACTION PRINCESS
Then I use this
Gikon Self Removal Pad...
"Extraction Princess," and...
All right! I've got a body!
With these stupid-but-popular-
with-the-ladies looks...
My manly, erotic conquest
of Soul Society
will begin in the next episode!