Hi, Ichigo.
It’s been a while.
Tsukishima!
You bastard!
What’re you doing here?!
Brother?!
Brother Ichi!
Stop it, Brother!
What’re you doing?!
What’s wrong with you, Brother Ichi?!
You’re hurting Shu!
Answer me!
Shu, we’re here!
Huh?
Oh, Ichigo’s here, too.
You’re right.
Hey Ichigo!
We hear you’ve been staying
out late these days?!
You should come home earlier!
You’re making Yuzu
and Karin feel lonely!
That’s okay. We’re not lonely!
I asked them to come.
Oh Karin!
Hi, Shu!
I wanted to see everyone since
it’s been such a long time.
It’s been a while, hasn’t it?
Don’t give me that scary look.
I’m sorry about calling
everyone so late at night,
but tomorrow’s Sunday,
so it’s okay, right?
You know…
maybe I’ll call Chad and Orihime, too.
What the?!
Mr. Tsukishima!!
Tell me, Tsukishima…
What did you do to everyone?!
Tsukishima!
Ichigo!
What’re you doing?!
Never mind! Apologize!!
You don’t understand…
Tsukishima is…
Apologize to Mr. Tsukishima!
Ichigo…
Hey Ichigo, what’s gotten into you?
You’re nuts.
Yeah, what happened?
Brother Ichi…
Brother…?
What happened to you?
What’s gotten into you, Brother Ichi?
You should apologize.
Hey!
You’re acting strange, Brother.
Ichigo. Hey, are you okay, Ichigo?
What are you doing?
Ichigo.
You’re to blame, Brother.
Brother Ichi.
You…
What is this?!
What the hell’s going on?!
Anybody!
Isn’t there
anybody left who's still sane?!
Ichigo!
Ginjo!
He got them!
Riruka…
And Kutsuzawa…
And Yukio…
And Jackie…
Tsukishima got them all!
We should be safe here for a while...
I kept this place in the
event Tsukishima found
all of our safe houses.
Not even Riruka and Kutsuzawa know
of this place, much less Tsukishima.
Damn it...
Why the hell did this happen?!
Why?!
Ichigo...
It’s your fault, Ginjo!
This all happened because
you dragged me into this!
Yeah…you’re right.
I’m sorry.
Damn it!
I know!
You guys were only trying to help!
It’s not your fault!
It’s nobody’s fault.
Don’t go blaming yourself.
Before they attacked me,
Yukio and the others said…
We finally remembered.
About what?
Guys?!
Remember?
What’d he mean by that?
From what Chad said,
I thought Tsukishima’s
power was the ability
to disrupt memories…
But rather than their
memories being disrupted,
they actually sounded more like
things became clear
after they remembered.
I’m thinking Tsukishima’s power…
is not a disruption of memory,
but a manipulation of the past.
Tsukishima’s “Book of the End”
is a Fullbring that uses a bookmark.
This is purely speculation,
but if a new power arose
from “Book of the End,"
it coincides with its original
form as a bookmark.
Tsukishima places his presence
in the pasts of the people he cuts down.
Is that even possible?!
I don’t know.
But you heard what the guys that
were stolen by Tsukishima said.
It’s far beyond a matter of trusting
or not trusting Tsukishima.
To them, Tsukishima is someone who was
always there in their past
as a family member,
a friend,
a lover,
someone deeply connected to them.
Otherwise, there’s no way they’d
speak of their memories of him
in the ways that they did.
They weren’t confused
and they didn’t lose their memories.
He is already a fact of their pasts.
Shedding tears won’t
miraculously bring
back their memories like
it does in fairy tales.
To all of them…
The two of us who
don’t know Tsukishima
are the crazy ones!
Would…
killing Tsukishima
return them to normal?!
I’ll be honest with you.
Even if we kill Tsukishima,
there’s no guarantee
they’ll return to normal.
We might be despised by our
families and friends as
nothing but murderers
and they might continue to think of us
as having gone crazy.
But regardless of whether
we can or cannot undo the effects,
the only way to sever their bond
with Tsukishima is to kill him!
Can you do it?
Can you really kill Tsukishima,
when there’s no guarantee
it’ll undo everything?
Oh, boy… You guys are having a
pretty disturbing conversation.
So this is where you were.
Ginjo!
I thought you said you were the
only one who knew about that place?!
Yeah…
Then how?!
Damn!
Making our escape comes first.
You can’t get away.
That was dangerous, Kugo.
Wasn’t that your precious hideaway?
How’d you know I’d be there?
How?
What’re you talking about?
How I always do, of course.
Whenever we’re separated,
we always make sure to know
where each of us are, remember?
Something really is
wrong with you, Kugo.
C’mon, let’s go back.
Don’t worry.
Neither Mr. Tsukishima nor I,
or anybody, is angry with you two.
In fact, we feel sorry for you.
It’s okay.
We’ll bring you back to
your senses right away.
All right.
Ichigo!
He’s offering to take
us to Tsukishima.
It’s just what we need.
You…
I’ve made up my mind.
We’re here.
So this is the place.
Hey.
Tsukishima!
Wait!
Ginjo?!
Don’t charge blindly.
If his powers are what
I think they are…
One slash and it’s all over!
Knock it off. I’m unarmed.
I don’t want to fight you two.
Let’s go inside and talk.
You really think
we’d walk into a house
full of potential traps?
Are you kidding me?
If I were going to set a trap,
I’d have set it in the
forest on your way here.
You heard him.
Now, come on inside.
Welcome back!
What took you, Ichigo?
You’re late!
What’re you just standing there for?
Yeah, come on!
Come on and join us!
Hey, Ichigo!
Ichigo!
Brother!
Welcome back, Ichigo!
Ichigo!
Brother Ichi!
Brother!
It’s all right, Ichigo.
These people consider Tsukishima
to be their friend,
but they consider you
a friend, as well.
They won’t attack
you without warning.
Stay calm…
I’m so happy!
Shu said he’s not
angry at all, Brother!
That’s right!
You’re lucky, Ichigo!
Shu’s such a nice guy!
You should apologize while you can!
He’s right. You should
apologize properly.
Ichigo, apologize.
Apologize, Ichigo.
Apologize!
Please apologize.
Apologize.
Tsukishima…
-Hey!
-Ichigo!
Brother!
Damn it!
He couldn’t bear it.
Damn!
I want to kill Tsukishima right now.
But I couldn’t fight him in there.
If I fought him back there,
I would’ve dragged
everyone into the fight!
Everyone…
Yuzu…Karin…Tatsuki…
Keigo…Mizuiro…Ms. Ikumi…
Everyone!
Oh, good.
You seem to be doing well.
Yeah.
Looks like he’s brimming with energy.
I’m glad.
Oh?
I thought you didn’t
like me, but maybe not.
You voluntarily got
yourself surrounded.
Now then…
I destroyed the stairway.
Yukio’s about the only person
that can possibly come up here.
Now…
There’s nothing to hold you back.
Fight with everything you’ve got!
Ichigo!
Damn you!
No you don’t!
You’re not getting away!
So that’s your Fullbring.
You’ve come a long
way in a short time.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
Say it while you still can.
I came here to kill you.
Chad…Inoue…
Sotenkishun!
I reject.
Don’t…
Don’t do this, Inoue…
Don’t heal his arm!
He’s!
I’m impressed.
You heal amazingly as usual.
Thank you!
Chad…
Are you two also like the others?
I don’t know what you mean by that…
I’m actually confused because
you’re different...
Ichigo…
Why are you doing this?
Kurosaki…
Have you forgotten how Mr.
Tsukishima has always helped us?
We were able to save Kuchiki.
And bring Inoue back from Hueco Mundo.
And were able to defeat Aizen.
It was all thanks to Mr. Tsukishima!
Even when we first
awakened to our powers.
And when Inoue went
alone to Hueco Mundo.
Mr. Tsukishima was…
always there for us.
We were able to come this
far all because Mr. Tsukishima
was there for us!
Do you understand what’s going on.
Ichigo?
Guys! Snap out of it!
Look! Mr. Tsukishima bought
me this new game console.
Huh?
He also renovated my bar.
What?!
Join this side, Kugo, and something
good will happen to you too.
I won’t fall for that! I won’t!
I think…
Xcution Dictionary!
Today I will explain my power,
“Book of the End.”
Mr. Tsukishima!
WASABI PASTE
Look!
FRESH WASABI ROOT
CHOCOLATE AND WASABI MOUSSE
I made this wasabi-chocolate
parfait from
the recipe you taught me!
Please have some!
Mr. Tsukishima.
Do you remember this?
Back when I was feeling depressed,
SNUGGLE SNUGGLE
you dressed in this and
let me snuggle you.
Thank you so much!
Maybe I inserted the wrong
kind of memories…