O-Otose!
Why are you here?!
Madame Otose...
Stop this silly fighting.
Let's make peace and
celebrate at my bar.
H-Huh?!
Pirako, you're coming too.
Since you made a real mess of things
you'll have to make up for it
with one hell of a show.
Otose...
Whatcha babbling about, old lady?
We don't have time for that!
Finish up your business then.
How long are you guys going to lie there?
This old lady came out here
despite being seriously injured.
Enough of your petty bickering.
There's a serious fight in the
works, with Edo on the line.
If you don't protect
this town, who will?
We may be moving in
different directions,
but we all started in the same place.
The yakuza, trannies, cabaret girls...
We all love this town.
That's all there is to it.
Otose-san! Look out!
Hey, if you wanna snuff
one of the Four Devas while I'm around,
come back in a hundred years!
B-Bro!
What are you fools doing?!
You always return the
favor, seven for three!
Well, Gran?
Show them our...
No, show them the Kabuki
District's might.
'Tis An Honor!
Wh-Who's there?
A bandit who's opened
the door to paradise...
Catherine the lock picker!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Why did you shut the door
without saying anything?!
Do you realize how hard it
was for me to get here?!
They found me!
Hey! Open the door!
Help!
Stay away!
Don't come any closer!
Wh-Who's there?
You scared him because of your
funny clothes, Catherine.
That's right.
Don't worry!
The Kabuki Cats are here now!
B-Bro!
What are you fools doing?!
You're gonna stand around while
the Amanto take over our town?!
Ka-Katsuo...
Young lady, we were the
castoffs of society
until the boss took us in.
We're prepared to throw away
our worthless lives for the
boss, and for his daughter.
However...
We aren't gonna abandon
the town our boss
has dedicated his life to protecting.
We have a duty to protect
the Kabuki District!
Take a good, hard look!
This is the town your old
man has been protecting!
Let's do this!
The whole universe will learn
to fear the Jirocho Gang!
The Kabuki District belongs to us!
Heh...
They're the ones who made
a mess of this town.
That's why I can't stand yakuza.
The Kabuki District belongs to you?
No.
It belongs to us trannies!
It's finally time for us to go crazy!
Show them the true power of a tranny!
Loud and clear, everyone.
This is the Kabuki District!
Fr-Freaks...
Kill them in the name of the Harusame!
Finish them!
Pops,
we promise to protect everything
which was dear to you.
Jirocho...
Take care of her... Take
care of our town...
They did it!
There were only two of them.
My elite soldiers lost
to these base monkeys.
This can't be... This can't be...
That's...
Otose!
I never expected this filthy
town to be home to such heroes.
Mark my words, Jirocho...
The Harusame will return this favor!
W-Wait...
All this effort to chase
a vixen out of town.
I don't want to get any older.
But you young'ns are disappointing.
When I was a young lad...
The elderly always let nostalgia
cloud their memory.
I don't want to get any older.
Hey, kid.
Is that his jutte?
Why do you have it?
I made a one-sided promise,
and then I swiped it.
Heh.
Same here.
Whenever I smoke, the
memories come back.
I would watch from behind
as he walked around, toying with his jutte
while smoking with his left.
It was rather striking to see him
with the Kabuki District as a backdrop.
He loved this town,
and I'm sure that this town loved him.
We can smoke and fiddle with a jutte,
but we can never be like him?
He died the way he lived.
Like a man,
who sacrificed his life
for someone like me
while leaving loved ones behind.
I killed him.
So I had to give up on being
a man, on being human,
in order to protect what he left behind.
Even if the town hated me for it...
Damn...
So you weren't trying to kill Gran.
She's always been a pain in the ass.
Squawking in my ear whenever
I did something...
My resolve would waver when I saw her.
When I watched you guys,
I would get the urge to go
back to being the old Jirocho.
You're getting in my way, Tatsugoro.
Let's settle this once and for all.
We'll see who's worthy of
inheriting his pipe and jutte.
I'm not interested in any inheritances.
I just wanted to keep
my promise this time.
It's obvious that neither of
us is going to cave or give in.
In that case...
...there's only one way
for us to move forward.
I will keep my promise and survive.
In return...
...you will keep your promise...
...and die.
Both of you are chained to
this town by the same thing.
A promise made to a certain man.
An iron vow of your own choosing.
The chains of a warrior.
Old man!
Your promise was broken.
I win.
Bastard...
Why didn't you cut me down?
Like I said...
I'm going to keep my promise this time.
Pops,
we promise to protect
everything which was dear to you.
Quit smoking, old timer.
I'd appreciate it if you
never woke up again.
Usually, you wouldn't put
a guy in the same room
as the person he stabbed.
This can't be a hospital.
Must be some kind of haunted house.
What was that, Seirogan?!
Looks like everyone managed
to survive somehow.
Had nothing to do with us.
Our lives were saved.
Your daughter spent
three days taking care
of you without any sleep.
And your daughter kept an eye on me
to make sure I didn't run off
again and exacerbate my injuries.
A futile effort.
We can stab you, tie you up,
and you'll still get back up.
You're one to talk, stubborn mule.
I know that I'm stubborn,
but you make me look like
a reasonable fellow.
Everybody turned out to
be as twisted as he was.
Actually, you're worse
than Tatsugoro was,
since you beat me in a battle of wills.
You look pretty happy for
someone who was beaten.
Yeah...
It's been so long since
I've had a real fight.
A real fight between men and warriors.
I can only laugh after losing
in such a satisfying way.
I've given up so much to be
able to keep my promise...
But he managed to save everything
to keep his promise,
including me.
No, I was just running away...
I was scared of losing
anyone else dear again...
He shattered the ungainly
chains around my neck.
They made it clear that they could
protect this town without me.
Twenty years...
I spend twenty years keeping my promise,
and this is how it ends.
In the end,
I just made everyone around me unhappy,
while failing to keep my promise.
Otose...
You've done a lot for me.
But I kept running in circles.
I was never able to return the favor.
Sorry I couldn't make you happy.
Jirocho, I'm...
Damn! What are people doing?!
It was about to get good!
I told you to stop pushing!
It's your fault for bringing
such a big camera!
Shut up!
How often are we gonna get to see
the boss in a romantic scene?!
Men are so hopeless.
The sensitivity of a brick.
What's that in your hand?!
Please stop this, everyone.
Recording mode off.
I just heard something!
You were recording!
You were recording the entire time!
What are you people doing here so late?!
Wait, that's alcohol!
Don't you realize what
kind of place this is?!
This is ours!
Do you realize how much
effort it took to get
the old lady on top of the roof?!
Jirocho...
You and Gintoki will never change.
You're both selfish jerks.
The difference is that he had
people to help him realize
that other people needed
him the way he needed them.
Now, you can see that
there's no need to worry.
There are plenty of fools
in the Kabuki District
to carry on the spirit
of you and Tatsugoro.
You did a fine job of
protecting this town
until the next generation
could take over.
You kept your promise.
So you can let go now.
You have other promises to keep.
I'm very happy right now, Jirocho.
I met Tatsugoro here
in the Kabuki District.
And I met them.
And I met our beloved Jirocho again.
Thanks for everything, Jirocho.
This isn't good.
My eyesight's starting to fail me.
First, I can't control my bowels,
now I'm leaking up here.
Greater Edo Hospital
I don't want to get any older.
We cannot allow them
to get away with this.
Just you wait, Devas.
I can no longer turn back.
I will do anything to obtain
the Kabuki District.
I've been waiting for you, Lady Kada.
You're...!
Sorry, but could you not interfere?
I finally get to see my old man look...
Silence!
Don't you understand that you're
the one who's interfering?!
I do.
My interference is over.
But I'm taking you with me!
You're the only one who's leaving!
Br-Bro!
Sacrificing yourself
to take out the enemy...
won't be enough to make up
for everything you've done, bitch!
There you have it.
Whatcha gonna do now, Pirako-chan?
My job is finished.
You can have your way with me.
Sad.
Don't you need to settle
things with your old man?
I have.
You took all the glory though.
You're the one who saved my old man.
I didn't expect you to protect him...
No, it wasn't just you.
This town has
wonderful people who help one another
despite their differences.
They do more than take away...
If I could be like them...
But it's okay now.
The father I wanted to see...
The father who Mom and I were waiting for...
...is back.
Bro... Everyone...
I can't apologize for what I've done,
but let me say this.
Thank you for letting me see my
father one last time!
I couldn't be my father's
daughter or the Bro's underling,
but I was very happy to be
a resident of this town,
if only for a moment.
Please let me take responsibility
for what I've done...
Sorry, but I'm not
sadistic enough to beat
up a crying little girl.
Besides, I'm tired.
Go wait at the place listed there.
I'll deal with you once I'm healed up.
You better be done crying by then.
Let's try that place next time.
Sure.
Bar Chono
What?
You want to know who the strongest
man in the Kabuki District is?
You must be new in town.
Won't last long with that attitude.
Forget it.
This town is on a whole different level.
It's too dangerous.
With the fall of the Deva Kada
and the retirement of the Deva Jirocho,
the fragile balance of power
is beginning to crumble.
The town's never been this tense before.
Is that you, Bro?
'Tis an honor.
I was born and raised in
the Kabuki District of Edo,
where I lived as a ruffian
in a town of ruffians,
always surrounded by steel.
I am ashamed to admit
that I have walked astray
and was guided by my brothers
to embark on a journey of redemption
to regain that which I have lost.
I have been called boss,
warrior, and many other names,
but I have given them up.
I am the father of Pirako Chin,
Jirocho.
It's rude, but may I ask who you are?
I-I am the newest member
of the Odd Jobs family
in the Kabuki District of Edo...
On a journey to find my missing father...
I was guided here by the
kindness of my brothers.
I am the daughter of Jirocho,
Pirako Chin!
We must have been brought
together by fate.
Would you mind
if I accompanied you on your journey?
I'm home.
Next Episode: Odd or Even
Next time:
Odd
Or even?