Let's cut loose!
Let's do this, Stark.
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
nando demo umarekawaru no
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
You will regret your insolence
towards the emperor...
and turn to dust!
I am the emperor,
Barragan Ruizenban!
I am the god of Hueco Mundo!
The only thing that is absolute
in this world is my power!
I hold supreme power. The world
should be under my control!
Wh-What is this?
You said it yourself.
It's your power, the only thing
that is absolute in this world.
Where's your right arm?
What is the meaning of this?
I've given it to you.
Curse you, ant!
Defying a god...
Unforgivable, unforgivable!
This is unforgivable, you ants!
King of Hueco Mundo...
Even you were but
just a tiny life
who feared death and
tried to avoid aging.
Oh my. It looks like they
really defeated him.
Where are you looking?
I'm your opponent.
Don't be so hasty.
Let's take our time, okay?
Number Two is dead and
no one says anything.
How sad.
Hey! Come out, Rose!
Hachi did it!
Tsk! How annoying.
Quit stalling and come on out.
You're going to make
me go bald!
There's a certain art to
climbing out of rubble!
Is that so?
Then make it an art to avoid
being buried in rubble.
So Hachi did it...
His opponent seemed
pretty powerful too.
Yeah. I would have liked it if
we had settled things earlier.
Why's that?
Can't you tell?
Once a comrade falls, a battle
becomes one of revenge.
You sure?
He doesn't seem like
the type to me.
That's what makes him scary.
There isn't anyone who would be unaffected
by the death of a comrade.
If he's shaken up by the death of his comrade,
we can strike when his guard is down.
If he's angered by the death of his comrade,
we can attack him before he snaps.
You mean they become stronger
as their numbers dwindle?
There are two of us. So we should
just fight accordingly.
Well, whatever the case...
Whoever strikes first wins!
Slam!
Tengumaru!
That's not going to work!
You're not getting away!
He's moving slower
than before.
Which means he's the
type that gets shaken up.
Ouch...
Stark! Stark!
Why are you zoning out?!
I thought you were going to
avenge Barragan's death?!
You're pathetic!
I told you, it's not my thing.
I've had enough.
And it looks like Lord Aizen has
no intention of helping us either.
They're strong...
I get that. I've had enough.
If we continue to fight, someone's
going to die.
I get that. Let's go home
and go back to sleep.
Stark!
What are you, stupid?!
You're Number One!
You need to realize that!
All you've been doing
is trying to act cool.
You haven't been fighting
them seriously at all!
Did you forget why Lord Aizen appointed
you as Number One?!
It's because he believes
in your power!
If you don't want your comrades
to die off, you've got to fight!
Fine! Do whatever you want.
I'll do my own thing!
Did you get him?
Hardly.
He's just not moving.
He's planning something,
or watching us.
Whatever the case, we can't make
a move until the dust clears.
Losing your chance to attack because
of your previous attack.
You're unbelievable...
Shut up!
I still haven't lost
my chance yet.
There he is!
All right!
Jeez! Where is he aiming?!
Hey! Don't fire on your own!
He's coming, Stark!
That's because you
taunted him!
You kept me waiting
quite a while.
We didn't mean to
keep you waiting!
Huh?
You made it difficult for us to attack
or come at you, you dunce!
Huh?!
A talking pistol? How unusual.
What of it?!
That shaggy head of yours
is far more unusual!
Quiet down, Lilinette!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm doing things on my own!
Hey!
The intervals between his shots
are very different from before.
Does that mean he's
not the one shooting?
Stop it, Lilinette!
I told you, I won't!
All right!
I knew it. You weren't the
one calling the shots.
So what of it?
Why won't you come at me?
Are you grieving?
Something like that.
You idiot!
Your opponent is reading
your emotions!
That's pathetic!
Shut up!
How unexpected!
I didn't think that you
Hollows had hearts!
You're one to talk.
You're like Hollows too.
You had a mask on earlier.
By mask...
Do you mean this?
Let's cut loose!
Hey! Why are you silent?!
Jeez!
What are you doing?!
Go after him!
He's taunting us.
So what?!
There's no way that you'd lose!
I guess I have no choice...
Here he comes!
Now!
Right...
Play...Kinshara!
You're late!
If we don't get our timing right, there's
no point in fighting him two on one!
Sorry. As I told you, there's an art to making
an appearance in any situation.
I don't care!
He looks a bit motivated now.
I'm not so sure about that.
Fighting cowards
is not my style.
Otherwise, I won't be able to shine
during our moment of victory!
Dodge it, Stark!
I know.
That doesn't count as a dodge!
That's not enough to knock
down my Kinshara.
What?!
Nice, Rose!
Here we go, Tengumaru...
It's going to get a little
hot, but bear with it.
Hifuki no Kozuchi!
She's gone?!
Not!
You're over here!
Do you think that's enough
to fool me?!
You idiot!
What are you doing?!
What am I doing?!
What do you think you're
doing, you idiot?!
I've been charging at her since the
beginning to try to lure her in!
You've got some real
nerve, baldy!
And what you do think
you're doing?!
Save your lovers' quarrel for later,
after we're finished with this battle.
Who's doing what?!
What's wrong?
Do you think you can take
me on by yourself?
Of course not.
Don't tell me you're thinking of a
plan to fight me three on one.
Of course not.
Aww, this is annoying!
I'm ready, Lisa!
That's enough!
I know that's enough.
I'm just making sure.
What do you mean by "I'm ready"
and "that's enough"?
It has nothing to do with you.
It does.
You two may be used
to fighting together,
but this is my first time joining
either one of you.
If the three of us are going
to fight together,
I need to know your
fighting styles.
What are you talking
about, baldy?!
We don't always fight together.
Our personalities and preferences
are completely different.
But there's one thing
that we do share.
The time in which we can
seriously fight is limited.
We just needed to find out what
our opponent was like first.
You mentioned the three of
us fighting together, right?
That's incorrect.
It's the two of us, and one
of you. Remember that!
How amusing.
Are you all right?
Of course not.
They really are strong.
You're whining again!
I can't help it.
Whenever they put
on those masks,
their Spiritual Pressure
skyrockets in intensity.
On top of that, there
are two of them.
I'm by myself.
You're not by yourself.
You were able to get this far because
you weren't by yourself.
Long ago, you were by yourself.
But ever since that time, we've
always been together.
If we fight together, we'll be able
to handle two opponents.
All right.
I get it.
Stark...
I guess I have no choice.
There's a slight change in
his Spiritual Pressure.
Where is he?
Above us, Love!
What is that?
What in the world's going on?!
Love...
Huh?
Is he...?
I know. He's unarmed.
Where's his pistol?
Who knows? He's
making fun of us.
Is he implying that he doesn't
need a weapon?!
Let's do this, Stark.
He's coming!
I know that!
Slam!
Tengumaru!
Play...
Kinshara!
They're like flames!
There's no end to them!
How troublesome!
I hate peculiar magic-like
techniques like this
the most!
Kinshara Sokyoku Number 11...
Izayoi Bara.
Your technique is even
more magic-like!
Surely you jest! Mine is an art!
Magic and art are similar
but different.
You keep moving about!
I'm going to crush you!
Rose! Rose!
Can you hear me?!
What is it?
I figured it out!
They're not flames!
They're Cero!
Those wolves came out from the
magazine of that Espada's gun!
Each one of them
is a Cero he fired!
They're dangerous when they
explode in close combat!
Damn it...
They're not Cero.
Regular Cero don't have the power to
mortally wound strong guys like you.
I split and rip my own soul into
pieces and make those pieces
follow and obey me like comrades
and I use them as weapons.
These wolf-shaped warheads
are both Stark and Lilinette.
That is the power of Espada Number 1,
Coyote Stark and Lilinette Gingerback.
Stark...
What is it?
They aren't able to
handle it at all.
Yeah. Looks like it.
Let's finish this all at once!
Yeah.
I know.
Let's go...
It's game over.
If you run, I'll let you go.
Don't underestimate us.
I see...
I guess I have no choice.
I don't like the term
"finishing blow."
But here comes my
finishing blow.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
I'm not alone.
I'm not alone anymore.
"Footsteps can be heard inside an abandoned
building said to be a passageway for spirits."
I don't sense anything.
Is it really here?
It's been a while since I've been
to the World of the Living!
I'm looking forward to shopping!
Ikkaku... There's a cafe
I want to go to.
Could you go there with me?
He can't!
He's got to help me
carry things first!
Why won't they notice me?