I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
A level-one guard position
has been ordered out!
What good will it do us
if the Punishment Force isn't
functioning properly?!
Ritze… Do it…
Captain!
Who did that?!
What's going on?
Hold him down!
Why you…!
What's this…?
What did you do…?!
Is this…a Bount’s…poison?
Hey… What's wrong?!
He's dead?!
Really?!
It can't be!
What's going on?
Captain!
Don't make a fuss!
If I recall…
There was a Bount who could
control a person like a puppet…
There's a high possibility that
the Bount took control
when he came into contact with him…
If that's the case,
there may be others…
Is there anyone else
who encountered the Bount?
Yes! We were around
East Street Two…
What are you doing?!
Hold him down!
Protect the Captain!
Captain, we'll take care of this!
Captain, take care of your wounds!
How many of them are there?!
What's going on?!
The Bounts' Spiritual Pressure
keeps appearing and disappearing!
They're up to something.
What should we do, Ichigo?
Damn! Curse those Bounts…
Woah!
What?!
What are…you doing?!
Ichigo… These people…
They smell like Bounts.
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You're going to die!
A doll, huh?
The doll that that Bount, Mabashi, uses…
These guys are being controlled.
Cut it out!
This is just like the time
Rukia was being controlled!
Damn!
That's good, Ritze…
That's the spirit!
Keep that up!
This strong Spiritual Pressure…and…
What?
Yes. A number of Soul Reapers
have fallen into the hands of the Ryoka
and are attacking their allies.
What's the meaning of this?
They are being controlled
by a Bount's doll…
It is the work of a Bount
whom I met in the World of the Living.
Is there a way to regain control?
It’s inside their bodies,
so it's difficult to defeat
only the doll…
The puppets should be brought
under control
if the one who's controlling them
is defeated…
At any rate, I must get that Bount…
Who’s there?!
A Bount!
I came to take a look when
I sensed a strong Spiritual Pressure…
You're a captain, aren't you?
Plus, you've also been injected
with the Bitto's poison, haven’t you?
So this is your doing…?
If I condense a living soul
and leave it alone…
It'll rot.
What?!
You're going to die soon.
Don't look at me like that.
There's no way to counteract
the poison, you see…
Just as I’d expect from you, but
the poison will work faster
if you move.
It's disadvantageous for me
to drag this out…
In that case…
Kill all enemy with your venom!
Suzumebachi!
You're not getting away!
Why you…!
So this is the Homonka…
I know about it.
I’m supposed to die if I get hit
in the same place twice, right?
But…is time almost up?
You're going to die soon!
I'm going to hide and
take my time watching you until then.
Why you…!
Just die, you idiot!
Wait!
Hisagi!
Yes.
It's as you say. The puppet seems to be
completely fused within the body…
Yes…
They'll probably go out of control
once they regain consciousness…
Let's move them to
the Squad 4 barracks.
Huh?
I want Captain Unohana's opinion.
There’s no one else who can do
anything for them in this condition.
Yes!
Move these people to
the relief station!
Yes!
This is a request from
Squad 7’s Captain Komamura, isn't it?
Yes! They've been knocked
unconscious for the time being…
But we don't know how many people
have been contaminated.
We'd like you to tell us…
how to deal with this.
This is…
What's wrong?
His mind and body are
being strongly controlled.
Extraction on the scene
is probably impossible.
So what should we do?
At any rate, bring in those who
are being controlled by the doll.
Let's stop their movement.
Yes!
It's an unreliable method,
but the only thing we can do
is to give it our best.
Make preparations.
Yes!
Damn… It's painful…
I can't see…in front of me.
What in the world should I do?
I never thought that…
I was so helpless…
What should I do…Madam Yoruichi?
That's it…that's it!
Captain!
Don't bother with me!
Defeat your own enemies!
Come on!
Put the next one in this bed!
Hey! That patient goes in that room!
Look sharp!
Captain…
I can't send orders to
some of the Ritzes? Why?
Curse those Soul Reapers.
Are they knocking out those
who Ritze is attached to?
It's pointless…
With my increased power…
I can multiply Ritze as much as I want!
Go, Ritze!
Understood!
This is simple…
Come to think of it,
it's almost that Soul Reaper’s time…
It might be good to make her
feel a little more despair…
Go somewhere else!
Bakudo Number One!
Sai!
Renji, that's wonderful!
You can even fight with Kido!
Yeah. I'm using this because
I can't use Zabimaru…
Wait a sec…
You were subtly making fun of me,
weren't you?
About what?
Is it really so unusual that
I can fight with Kido?!
I am a Lieutenant!
Yes!
I found you.
Hey… So this is where you were…
Are you still alive?
You're almost dead, aren't you…?
I was thinking of hiding until you died, but…
Then…why did you come out?
I sensed that the Soul Reapers were
sealing away my Ritzes one-by-one…
So I was thinking of hitting them
with someone strong.
Are you thinking of using me?
I can't stand Ritze being harmed.
What are you looking at?
Are you thinking of hitting
this spot once more?
Do you want to kill me?
It's impossible!
Wait!
The Punishment Force?!
Captain!
Are you all right?!
Oh? There're still a few left?
This is unforgivable!
You desperately rushed here
when your captain was in danger?
How touching…
Captain! We'll take you to
the relief station at once!
But I wonder if they're really your allies…
What?!
Ritze!
Yes!
Too bad… All of your henchmen
already belong to Ritze!
Get her!
What's wrong with all of you?!
How does it feel to be held back
by your own subordinates?
You scum!
You're sure good at talking
despite not being able to move.
I'm going to take your body.
I'm going to enslave it with
Ritze's power until you die!
Why you…!
It's useless…
Ritze!
Yes!
Too bad.
Good bye, Captain.
I'm going now!
What?!
Homonka: Second Strike!
Why you…?
How are you able to move?!
Who do you think I am?
I detoxified your poison already.
That's…
I was trained to be in
the Punishment Force since I was young.
So I am already able to
resist most poisons.
And I also know a way to build
resistance to a new poison.
Fight poison with poison…
using Suzumebachi.
Then why did you act as
if you couldn't move?
It was all or nothing.
There was no chance I could return
my subordinates back to normal
if you didn't come after me.
My precious subordinates!
This is it.
Don't underestimate me…Ritze!
Understood!
I still have Ritze…
If I kill you, this poison…
What's wrong?
Are you shaking so much
that you can't move? Huh?
How foolish…
Damn you!
Ritze, get her!
Yes, yes!
What's this?!
Hey, Ritze, stop that! Not me!
That woman! Kill that woman!
Understood!
Ritze! Why?!
Your doll’s power
is a double-edged sword…
I hear that it rebounds back
to the controller if his power weakens.
Ritze, stop! Stop!
It's useless… Suzumebachi's poison
is already affecting your body.
Wh-What's this?
What's going on?
The doll's presence has
suddenly disappeared!
Astounding!
What's the meaning of this?!
It seems that someone has
defeated the controller…
It's all right now.
Mabashi's Spiritual Pressure
disappeared…
In the end, you were just too naive.
How pathetic.
So it was Mabashi's Spiritual Pressure
that disappeared…
The enemy is pretty good…
Now then, that person hiding over there.
Isn't it about time you came out?
Oh? How did you know?
I tried to copy you and hide
my Spiritual Pressure…
Even if you hide
your Spiritual Pressure,
anyone could find you
if you're that bloodthirsty.
Sorry…
I was searching for Ichinose…
Where is he?
Who knows? His Spiritual Pressure
disappeared long ago…
Do you suppose one
of your allies did it?
Hmm… What a waste…
It can't be helped, then.
I'll settle for you.
I'm going to make you pay
for embarrassing me.
Well, well…
You underestimate me…
Well, fine…
It's my job…to erase Captains…
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Baura, the alternate dimensional monster,
has suddenly appeared!
Konjiki Ashisogijizo,
the guardian beast, fights back!
Two giant monsters clash!
“Giant Monsters, Soul Society Showdown!”
Coming soon!
How rude!
My zanpakuto is not a monster!
It's close enough…
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden!
There's no one here…
It's really empty!
Kenny, aren't you going
to search for the Bounts?
No…
I've never found anyone I chased…
Besides, the one I want to cut is Ichigo!
What's with this chill?!
MADAM YORUICHI!