Kumoi, the provisional administrator
of the Kasumiohji Clan,
is after Rurichiyo’s life.
He gives his follower Hanza,
the leader of the assassination squad,
the Bakkouto
and sends him off.
Nukui overcomes his limits
to merge with the Bakkouto
and he leads new assassins who
possess powerful Spiritual Pressure
in a new attack against
Ichigo and his friends.
So here you are,
Substitute Soul Reaper!
Ichigo!
Stay back, Rukia.
For some reason,
this guy wants to challenge me.
Let’s change locations.
Fine.
Let’s go!
You’re a friend of the Substitute
Soul Reaper, aren’t you?
Ichigo…
Who’s there?!
You are Rurichiyo Kasumiohji?
You… Are you with
that attacker from earlier?
Hand over Rurichiyo Kasumiohji.
What is this ominous
Spiritual Pressure?
And his appearance…
Is this foe different
from the others?
What’s the matter?
I refuse!
What?
I said I refuse!
Dance Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai Tsukishiro!
Miss Kuchiki!
I went easy on him.
He’s not dead, but he can’t move.
He is a valuable witness.
If we use him, the truth of the plot…
I wonder about that.
What?!
Was that the power
of the Zanpakuto
which is said to be
the most beautiful in Soul Society?
You’re…
Well then,
proper etiquette requires me
to show you my power!
The power of this Bakkouto, Retsurai.
Bakkouto?
W-What is this?!
Amazing… I feel power overflowing!
Here I come!
Take that!
Miss Kuchiki!
Is it over?
Do you want to end up like that?
Be silent!
Bloom in glory…
Benishidare!
Now’s your chance!
Kenryu!
Such a childish trick!
Damn it!
You can’t get away.
Hado 33:
Sokatsui!
Miss Kuchiki!
I am your opponent!
Just what I’d expect from a Soul Reaper
of the Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
You know? Looks like you're
going to make this fun!
I, Jinnai Douko, find you
worthy to be my opponent!
W-What the…
Amazing!
I can feel the power
building inside me!
This is the power of the Bakkouto?!
You’re a human,
but you are able to use the Flash Step?
It’s not the Flash Step.
It’s called Hirenkyaku.
Hirenkyaku?
Yes. A Quincy technique.
I see.
So you are the rumored last Quincy.
You’re aware of that?
Well, yes.
Tell me your name, Quincy.
Uryu Ishida.
And you?
I am Kuzuryu.
What’s the matter?
Well…
Just that it’s an unusual Zanpakuto.
That appearance…
Am I correct to assume that
it’s in a Shikai state?
What’s so funny?
This sword is not a Zanpakuto.
It is a Bakkouto.
How different is that from
a Soul Reaper’s Zanpakuto?
Everything about it is different.
Bakkouto do not have concepts
like Shikai and Bankai.
This encompasses its appearance.
And depending on
the wielder’s Spiritual Pressure,
it can unleash enormous power.
Isn’t that exactly what
the Zanpakuto does?
No.
A Soul Reaper
and his Zanpakuto
enhance each other and
mutually increase power.
But this sword takes its wielder’s
Spiritual Pressure and nothing else,
and transforms it into power!
I see.
But I find it hard to believe
that it’s stronger than a Zanpakuto.
Bend!
What?!
Did I get him?
What is this Spiritual Pressure?
What’s with that appearance?
This is the true form of my Shiragiri.
What?!
Arrows of reishi won’t work on me.
Why you…
Shiragiri, Mugen Kairou!
This is…
There!
What?!
Over here.
An illusion?
Where is he?
Which is the real body?
It’s useless looking
for Spiritual Pressure.
You cannot discern my form.
There!
I said it’s useless.
Strange. There’s no way
this location is so huge.
Is my perception off?
Or…
How long can you keep running?
Kurosaki… Kuchiki…
Ishida…
I can feel all their
Spiritual Pressures.
I must hurry!
Sado!
How far do you intend to run
before you’re satisfied?
I have no intention of running.
I just don’t like fighting in town.
Oh?
Listen, I’m sorry but can you
forget fighting and leave?
What?!
I know nothing about
the nobility in Soul Society.
But even I know that nobles
have a certain responsibility
regarding the power that
they’ve been entrusted with.
Just like Byakuya Kuchiki.
Just what is it you want to say?
Rurichiyo is still young.
But I believe she is prepared to
take on her role as an aristocrat.
When the time comes,
Rurichiyo will return to Soul Society
with Kenryu and Enryu.
In order to confront her destiny
and forge her own path.
So?
When that time comes,
she will have to settle things
whether she wants to or not.
I want you to leave her
alone until then.
What’s so funny?
I wondered what
you were gonna say.
Impossible!
Then, I’ll force you to leave!
Save your words until after you’ve
fought with me on equal terms!
Smash, Kakuyoku!
This is…
It’s the same Zanpakuto as
the assassin Ichigo defeated.
What’s going on?
It’s not the same!
This is its true power!
This is the Bakkouto, Kakuyoku!
Last time, the small fry
could barely make a wall.
But it’s different with
my Spiritual Pressure!
So you can use it even if
the wielder changes?
Exactly!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don’t think you can
dodge this forever!
Prepare to die!
Oh?
Not even close.
Huh?
It seems your big body
isn’t just for show.
You seem to be pretty tough.
Then…
It’s useless, useless, useless!
What?!
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante.
Is that your true strength?
Your attacks won’t work anymore.
Interesting!
Then I’ll use all my strength
to destroy you!
What’s the matter?
Are you done?
That’s my line.
You’re breathing awfully hard.
Doesn’t bother me.
Don’t think you can resist forever!
Too slow!
You really are one tough fellow!
That technique of yours…
It eats away your life
each time you use it.
I’m amazed by your toughness,
but how long do you think
you can keep up that attack?
I could ask the same of you.
That sword is exhausting
your Spiritual Pressure.
At that rate…
your sword will consume you.
My Spiritual Pressure is limitless.
This is nothing!
I’ll show you…
the true power of my Kakuyoku!
Do you think you’ve shut off
any escape by creating a wall?
There’s no sign…of his presence.
You’re mine!
Kuchiki, I heard an enemy that
can eat swords came to you.
The enemy who appeared before me
can create mist.
My opponent can create walls.
I get it!
So they build stages,
then create smoke for effects,
and do a magic show!
Inoue, I think you’ve got it wrong.
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today, let’s talk about
Yasutora Sado’s technique.
THE RIGHT ARM OF THE GIANT
His right arm has
enormous defensive power
THE RIGHT ARM OF THE GIANT
BRAZO DERECHO DEL GIGANTE
known as
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante.
His left arm has
attack power
THE LEFT ARM OF THE DEVIL
BRAZO IZQUIERO DEL DIABLO
known as
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo.
You can’t understand its meaning
without seeing the word.
Why am I featured in this corner?
You said so yourself.
Your power is close to a Hollow’s.
That’s true.
HOLLOW
But I have really
mixed feelings about it.