Ichigo defeats Espada
Number 6, Grimmjow,
in a deadly battle and
rescues Orihime.
But shortly afterwards, Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora, appears and challenges him.
Unable to tend to the injuries
sustained from his previous battle,
a wounded Ichigo is
forced to fight back.
As a result, his mobility
is greatly affected.
Well, Iet me show you.
This is my rank. Get it now?
That piece of trash you barely
managed to defeat back there…
Well, I rank higher than him.
It's over for you.
Sorry, I forgot your name.
Why are we running away? Why?!
– Meanwhile,
– Isn't it obvious?
– Ishida, Renji,
– Our goal is to rescue Inoue!
– Pesche and Dondochakka
– Not to defeat the Espada.
– escape from Szayelaporro's palace
– We're not under any obligation
– and are running deep into Las Noches.
–  to wait for him in a room
– However…
– where we can't use our powers!
I agree!
And now, it looks like we'll have to save
Rukia and Sado as well as Inoue!
It appears so.
W-What?!
This is…
Welcome back.
Now then…
Shall we start Act Two?
– This is terrible!
– Hey, hey! Move! Let me see too!
– I thought we had gotten outside!
– Hey, I said move it! Damn you're huge!
– That's what we thought, and yet…
– Let me see!
I said to move! I can't see!
Let me be surprised
in real time too!
How could this be?!
Damn it! Let me see too!
Kick!
Oh no!
Well? How did you like my palace?
I don't think an explanation is necessary,
but I'll tell you anyway.
The inside of this palace is
like being inside of my body.
It does what I tell it to.
You remember, don't you?
The first time you stepped
inside this place.
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
You can't use your Bankai
in this room.
I have complete information
on your Bankai.
From its form, abilities,
and Spiritual Pressure,
to even its reishi composition.
I used that information to seal away
your Bankai within this palace.
Naturally, I checked into
your Spiritual Pressure as well.
Quincy!
What?
You fool! Did you think that
your arrow went through me?!
That it pierced me and
went through me?!
Is that what you thought?
I am invincible inside this palace.
However, under the circumstances,
I do give you credit for
what you were able to do.
You managed to tatter my clothes.
But you'll hurt a little if you
get hit at point-blank range.
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Damn!
How impudent of you,
Soul Reaper!
It's exactly as we had planned.
Hasta aquí…
It's over, Szayelaporro Grantz.
Damn!
Wha—?!
B-Bastard!
Wait! Where are you going?!
Where am I going?
I had no choice
but to change my clothes.
However, even during that time,
I kept watch over you people.
There are hidden cameras
in every wall of this palace.
And I can rearrange the corridors
in any way I desire.
If I leave you behind in a room,
it's only natural for you to try and escape,
like a fly trying to escape
from a dragon's open mouth.
All I did was make you run around
from corridor to corridor,
only to return to the same place.
So will you stop looking like that?
Like you want to say,
"We ran around a long corridor."
"And we ran up and down
long stairways."
"And we ended up in the same room.
Like it was a bad joke."
Rather than something so trivial…
The fact that such lowly fellows like you
dare to irritate me to this extent,
and are forcing me to fight
with my full power…
To me, that is a much worse joke.
Sip… La Lujuriosa.
Wha—?
What is…
What's this?!
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Now the curtain shall rise
on the long-awaited Act Two.
Oh no…
Sorry, I take that back.
To be more accurate,
it is the end of Act Two.
What is that?!
I don't know!
Dodge it!
I don't know what it is,
but dodge all of it!
Even if you say that…
This is impossible!
I-I'm coming out?!
Wha—?!
Damn!
What the hell are you doing?!
Yikes! No fair, guys!
Me too, me too!
Pesche!
Yahoo! There's more of me!
What're you doing?!
You were dodging them
until now!
Huh?!
But, I didn't want to be
the only one left out!
It's lonely!
It's better in this situation!
Don't get so upset.
Don't expose me!
Hey! Cut out the comedy!
Now then, the characters
are all together.
Let's start.
As you can see, your enemies possess
the same power and abilities as you do.
Fighting haphazardly
only invites death.
Yikes!
However, be happy.
I have one piece of
good news for you.
I lifted the trap that sealed off
your powers in this room.
And so, you can fight to
your heart's content
against your alter egos
and kill yourselves off.
Damn it!
So before fighting the enemy,
we must fight ourselves, huh?
It's like a Zen riddle.
Indeed… This is a bad joke.
Your moves are quite impressive.
Is this the first time you're fighting
against a long-range weapon?
This is the second time!
Is that so?!
Kurosaki!
Stop this!
Kurosaki is hurt!
Shut up! Are you stupid?
So what if he's injured?!
This is a battle!
It's supposed to be unfair!
A battle is a monster from which
inequality and intolerance are born!
"I don't like him."
"I can beat him."
"I can't forgive him."
For various reasons,
one makes an enemy
and at that moment,
everything pulses towards a battle.
After raising hell right in the center
of your enemy's fortress,
it's pretty lame if you think no one's
gonna come after you, Soul Reaper!
So come on.
Of course, I watched you fight against
Grimmjow from the beginning.
So I already know your every move.
This is bad. This is bad, Uryu!
It's kinda late to say that.
No, this is really bad.
With another handsome guy like that,
the girls will switch allegiance!
What a bad joke!
Don't give him the time of day!
It's irritating!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Quit talking nonsense
and start fighting!
Let's go!
Roar, Zabimaru!
All right!
I guess we have no choice.
Let's get down to business!
Let's go!
Why avoid it?
I thought I'd increase
your handsome self in numbers.
Oh, it's all right.
There's more!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm so sorry!
Kurosaki…
Too slow!
What?
Does this just look sharp?
I shouldn't have bothered dodging it.
Kurosaki!
Don't think that you can beat me
with your level of power.
Your power is tremendous…
But the manifested reishi
called "Rikka,"
which configures your power,
is very fragile.
Even I could easily destroy them.
The only reason
I don't do so is
because your power belongs
to Lord Aizen.
Lord Aizen's order is
"as long as you are not attacked,
do not destroy Rikka."
If you do attack, I shall destroy it.
Please do not resist.
Kurosaki…
Wait a minute.
I don't see Nel!
Is something wrong?
Oh no!
Oh, I-It's nothing.
That's right.
The Arrancar who was
with you at the start.
I don't see her.
There.
Nel!
Ichi…
Are you…
Nel?
I thought so. That estigma…
You've become quite shabby, eh?
Well?
Does a cracked mask throb? Hey!
What's going on, bastard?
You know Nel?!
I'm scared!
Please help me, Uryu!
How mean of you to dodge me!
I'm trying to grab you
because I'm scared!
I want you to accept me!
Stop your nonsense!
You grabbing me only seems
like an attack to me!
Damn! You managed to dodge
our Dondochakka Press Attack!
See, what did I tell you?!
It is an attack!
I can't take anymore!
There's no time for this!
What are you talking about?
We must look for Nel!
I know that! We'll look for Nel!
As soon as we get away from here!
No. We must find her right away!
I sensed it a while ago.
Nel is frightened.
We can't let Nel get any closer
to Las Noches.
What's this?
I wondered what
she was doing here.
You brought her?
Well, judging from your face,
you've been dragging her around
without knowing who she is, eh?
What do you mean?
Well, if you don't know, I'll tell you.
This kid is Nel…
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck.
A former Espada.
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck
can't be Nel's real name.
There's no way Nel could
pronounce such a name.
Inoue, even Nel can say
her own name.
Right?
I can't say for sure.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
What am I doing in
a place like this again?!
Huh?
I came to eat snacks!
Just a little now.
Yay!
What?!
Thanks for the food!
Come again.
You can eat this?