Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
It turned out that the three mod souls
were created by Mr. Urahara
in an effort to get us to reflect
on our own strengths.
Meanwhile, a mysterious group
called “Bounts,”
who suck out the Souls of
living people, appeared.
Lirin, Kurodo and Noba hid themselves
inside stuffed toys
in order to give us their support.
With their investigative skills,
they discovered the Bounts.
Damn it… Where should I cut?
Goethe, finish him!
Huh?!
What are you doing, fool!
Have you gotten rusty, Ichigo?
Rukia!
More, Goethe! Destroy them!
Destroy them? All right.
What kind of power is this?!
No…  It’s too big!
Ryo!
Ms. Yoshino…
Roaming around without permission?
Are you a Bount, too?!
What was that all about?
A noisy one, aren’t you?
Ichigo! Be careful!
You know, food doesn’t talk.
Huh…? What do you mean?!
Now, let’s go home.
I guess I have no choice…
Friede!
You will not disobey…
You’d better not fight it.
My doll, Friede,
is a bit short-tempered, you see.
H-Hey! Weren’t you two
on the same side?
I said you’re too noisy…
I’m getting a headache!
Soul Reaper, noisy!
What’s going on?
What are the Bount’s capabilities?
If you will excuse us now.
After all, nobility and pigs
never share the same table.
Friede!
Wait!
What was that?
I have no clue.
– Huh?
– Oh?!
Orihime! And Chad…!
Ichigo, that guy…
You know him?
Just a while ago…
he made someone…
Rukia…!
Oh… The never-before explored
great 180-degree great cliff,
that I have but dreamed of,
is right before my eyes…
This is my first climb…
What do you mean, “great cliff”?!
Rukia!
Welcome back!
Um… Yeah…
I didn’t think I’d be able
to see you so soon…
Yeah…
Hey! That dress looks really good
on you!
Ishida’s love…oops…
No, no… Let’s see… Oh, yes!
“Umeya” near the school has started
serving green tea spaghetti!
Let’s all go there to
celebrate your return!
What do you say, Rukia?
Uh…sure!
I’d be delighted to join you.
Yes, that’s the spirit!
And then…their deluxe curry frappe
is pretty good, too.
If you pour it over shaved ice,
it’s out of this world.
I suddenly received orders
to rid this town of Hollows again.
I really preferred to spend
more time in training,
but I couldn’t disobey my orders.
Oh, man…
So I’m stuck with you yet again?
That’s my line.
Ichigo, who the hell is this?!
Wh-What’s with that
ugly stuffed toy?!
It’s not my fault!
I don’t look like this because
I wanted to!
I have to provide support for Ichigo,
so I had no choice!
Support…?
Yeah. Mr. Urahara gave her to me,
saying we had to watch out for
those guys we just ran into.
I don’t understand.
If you judge things by
their appearance, you’ll be sorry!
Lirin… I think Miss Rukia
is speaking of the Bounts.
Huh?
Hm… Are they allies, or enemies?
Really, those guys are difficult
to read.
I don’t even know their objective.
I don’t know, I don’t know,
I don’t know…
Hello…young lady…
What…is this?
Huh? This is Kurodo.
He’s supporting me.
And this is Noba,
who’s with Chad.
Hello…
Oh?
What? What…?!
Yes?
He’s so cute!
He looks exactly like Chappy!
J-Just a minute, Rukia!
Wasn’t I the one you loved best?!
I like you and all, Rukia,
but I can’t give you Kurodo…
Oh! Are we rivals in love?
In short, “lovals.”
Hey! What about me?!
Here I was thinking I was accepted
as the fluffy, healing character…
Have I fallen by the wayside?
Been given the hook?
Been waylaid?
Made the bad guy?
Nooo…way!
Come in…
Beautiful, isn’t it?
But, this view can only be seen
because we are surrounded by darkness.
Jin…
We could never become brilliant lights.
Did you eat a proper meal?
How could you have any strength,
if not?
And this bruise…
Did you cause
Udagawa trouble again?
Did something happen
that upset you?
Perhaps Yoshino doesn’t
understand her position here.
I find it difficult watching her actions.
My position? What do you mean?
I think you ought to think that over.
Never mind, Udagawa.
Don’t be so cruel to Yoshino.
Yes, sir. Forgive me.
Even so, Yoshino.
I cannot forgive you completely.
There’s nothing for which
I need your forgiveness.
Oh?
I won’t be ordered around by anyone!
That’s fine…
But I worry about you.
You are much too weak and foolish.
So much so, that I have
no choice but to protect you.
Don’t do it.
I don’t want to hurt you
any further.
Kurosaki Clinic
Excuse us for visiting
at such an hour.
We have decided to spend the night
studying for tomorrow’s test,
as young people tend to do…
Welcome. Please make yourself
at home.
Thank you!
Don’t you dare try to come in!
I won’t let you in
even if you try to bring us juice
or cake, or anything!
Take that!
Ouch…!
– There’s no pain!
– Ichigo, are you all right?
This is a dream, after all!
Dad, what's the big--?!
That’s right…
No way could this really
be happening.
Ichigo would never bring
two beauties home.
It’s like Bon, New Year’s and
Christmas all came together…
Shut up and get real!
Rukia…don’t…
What’s with him?
No cares in the world.
Yes, well, what do we do now?
Even if these things are able
to sniff those creatures out,
I doubt they’ll be willing
to talk to us.
And whether we can capture them…
Uh-huh.
The problem with them
is their trickery.
Like us, our enemies’ powers
seem to be
various and unique to each of them.
What a headache…!
True. When I attacked that monster
with my zanpakuto,
I caused it no harm at all.
And I’m not sure what sort
of power that other guy has.
But if we don’t do something,
someone else might get
his soul sucked out.
We’ll have to find some way
to fight them.
– Uh-huh.
– Yeah.
Doesn’t Soul Society know anything
about the Bounts?
Huh?
Judging from the timing,
isn’t this why you were sent here?
Unfortunately, I wasn’t told anything.
That encounter was the first
I’d ever heard of Bounts.
It was a surprise.
Oh, well…then…
Oh…!
Yes?
Rukia?! Is that really you, Rukia?
I just got a message from the Captain!
You really are here?
I’m coming right over!
Right over…? Renji!
Who the hell are you?! Huh?!
Dad…
Get off me…
Rukia!
Don’t, I said…
Uh… How far did I get?
Um… There are these Bounts…
It is a mystery what they are
and what their objectives and powers are,
but there’s no doubt
they are dangerous, I would say.
Are you an idiot?
What do you mean,
“I would say”?
Anybody who learns nothing
after battling someone
can only be an idiot!
Listen, I don’t want to hear
that from some fool
who’d break someone’s window
to come in!
Quit trying to dodge the subject!
I’m not dodging anything!
Yes, you’re dodging it.
– Indeed, it is odd…
– No, I'm not.
– What is?
– Idiot Ichigo!
Normally, one Soul Reaper is sent out
for every 50,000 humans.
But, including the Substitute,
there are three of us.
I think we should consider
our being sent here
as a response to this problem.
Oh, yeah…
Hey, what will we do tomorrow?
If that’s the case,
we have no other choice…
Hello, everyone…!
Good morning, Rukia!
You look as pretty as ever.
Good morning, my honey…!
What do you mean, “honey”?!
I see them every day,
but I’ve missed Rukia’s serenity.
My heart goes out to you.
I don’t know what
you’re talking about,
but I will take them as words of praise.
Huh?
J-Just a minute!
What did you do?
That…?
Why are you acting like
we just parted yesterday
and are meeting again today?
It’s because we parted yesterday
and met again this morning.
Look at this! It’s a Kikanshinki Delux.
It’s an amazing gadget that
allows me to freely change memories!
So, in their memories,
I am Rukia Kuchiki,
a student who transferred here
not long ago,
and has started to
get used to her class.
So anything goes now…?
What are you doing here, Rukia?
What’s the matter, Ishida?
N-Nothing…
Uh-oh… I forgot to tell him.
For lunch today,
we have French riceballs!
I wrapped some custard in rice!
There’s enough for Tatsuki
and everyone!
Okay, okay.
I’m on a diet, so no thanks.
Oh, this is delicious.
The custard that squishes out
between the grains of chewy rice is superb.
Don Kan’onji’s new
“Feeling Spirits 5 vs. 5”?
The shoot is open to the public?
I’ll go!
That’s great. I can’t go
because I have a date.
You’re going, right, Chad?
We’ll be two guys having a blast!
It’s like…
Soul Society didn’t exist at all…
Don’t be ridiculous! It’s here!
– Huh?
Ichigo…?
I forgot something. I’ll be back.
Huh? Huh? What is this?
Chad I can understand,
but Orihime and Rukia, too?
Don’t tell me…
Ishida, don’t exert yourself!
Well, good-bye, everyone…
No! Why have we been left out?
Probably because of
the way you are, Mr. Asano.
“Mr. Asano”?
Why the formality, all of a sudden?
Orihime…
Which way?
That way!
And which is it?
The man.
Don’t they become active
only after nightfall?
I guess not.
After all, our detection ability
is very accurate.
What’s this?!
Huh? It’s money…
This won’t do?
Are you trying to make
a fool of me?
You think you can use money
like this? Get out!
Ouch… How mean…
He’s like the men in the Squad 11.
– Huh?
– Hurry!
Oh…hey!
That face seemed somehow familiar…
Pay attention, will you?!
I know!
Don’t worry…
Your body will feel no pain.
Hold it…!
Damn you!
How rude…
There’s something I want to ask you.
What is it?
First, you’re a Bount, aren’t you?
Yes…
What happened to the girl,
yesterday?
No comment.
What is your objective?
Does that mean you have
a scheme you can’t talk about?
No comment on that, either.
Now, can I ask you a question?
A Soul Reaper’s soul and
a human’s soul–
which tastes better?
Zeig Dih Friede!
So your ability
is in that strange whip?
This is just a start.
Oh, Friede, are you ready so soon?
Yes. It was easy.
Then, go and show them
your strength.
All right.
Watch your step!
Ishida…!
When…?
His direct attack on you was a trick.
He made it seem like
he was chasing you,
and had laid a trap around you.
I guess it changes everything
it touches into snakes.
It’s not a matter of touching
or not touching.
Anything that Ryo can imagine
will turn into a snake.
For example…
Oh!
Oh-oh-oh… What’s going on?!
All of a sudden
there are snakes everywhere?!
Stop it! Stop! I can’t stand snakes--!
Quit babbling! Just get out of here!
I hate snakes…!
Santenkesshun!
I…reject!
Can’t you do anything?
I see… This is interesting.
To think I’d run into you here…
Leave Ishida alone!
That is impossible.
What?!
He is the most defenseless
and weak among you.
Taking advantage of another’s weakness
is an established tactic, isn’t it?
Besides…
I wonder what
a Quincy’s soul tastes like…
I’d like to find out.
Where does she think she’s going?
How naïve.
This town is truly, more beautiful
when it is cloaked in darkness.
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Kon’s pearls of wisdom.
The doll used by a Bount is like
the Zanpakuto of a Soul Reaper.
Their abilities seem to differ
depending on which Bount
uses them.
The doll is a stuffed animal, right?
There are all sorts of stuffed animals,
but none worth anything
on our side, I’d say.
What?!
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
This is Hanataro Yamada. Let’s see…
The reason I’m applying here is…
Uh, what company is this now…?
Unsatisfactory
I'm very good at…
at vanishing without a trace…
Unacceptable
Hanataro is an easy name
to remember…
Reject
Why won’t anyone hire me?
After all, Captain Unohana
sent me here
to have a look at this world… Ohh…
What’s this…?
Tune in again!