Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Byakuya…
Brother…
A silvery-white
windflower silk scarf…
And a kenseikan…
You're…from the Kuchiki Clan,
aren't you?
Byakuya Kuchiki, 28th generation
head of the Kuchiki Clan.
28th generation head… I see…
A great deal of time
appears to have passed
since I was sealed away.
So, did Ginrei kick the bucket?
Don't talk about
my Grandfather so familiarly.
You soiled the honor
of the Kuchiki Clan.
You have no right to speak
of my grandfather's name.
Bastard…
Brother… What…
…is going on here?!
I thought you were on their side…
Watch quietly.
This is a fight with
the Kuchiki Clan's honor at stake.
What?
You… Weren't you under
Muramasa's mind control?
Yes…
It's true that at one point, I fell
under Muramasa's mind control.
However…
Master…
You've returned to your senses,
Senbonzakura?
What happened?
I don't know…
A sudden voice rang
within my chest.
It told me to release my heart
and follow as I desired…
I see… I thought so.
Byakuya, having been told
by his grandfather, Ginrei,
was aware of the Zanpakuto,
Muramasa, and its master, Koga.
Know this.
If by chance the seal is broken,
it will be your duty as head of
the Kuchiki Clan to slay that man.
The world must never be exposed
to that warped evil power ever again.
I swear on my honor as
head of the Kuchiki Clan…
Byakuya went to the archives
in search of clues to Koga.
But…
as he feared,
there was no record.
All he came away with
was the further realization
that he could not make
the incident public.
That Soul Reaper named Koga…
He was connected
with the Kuchiki Clan?!
But that's no reason for him to
keep it all hidden from us as well!
It was all for the sake of
determining where Koga
was sealed away!
Merely killing Muramasa
is meaningless…
The real person who must be
defeated is Koga alone!
So, I acted as though
I had been brainwashed.
But it wasn't easy to
identify the location
where Koga had
been sealed away.
That's why Byakuya
stayed by Muramasa…
Even if that meant giving
his friends the wrong idea…
Why did he go through all that?
Because it is his duty as
head of the Kuchiki Clan.
Brother…
Head of the Kuchiki Clan…
Are you planning to
seal me away, too?
No, I can't allow you to
remain alive any longer.
You soiled the honor
of the Kuchiki Clan…
I will kill you.
Spoken with the true arrogance
of the Kuchiki Clan…
Fine…
If you're the head
of the Kuchiki Clan,
I have ample reason
to fight, as well.
Koga…use me…
My power belongs to you…
W-Why?
You have become nothing
but a hindrance to me.
I don't need to use
an unstable sword like you—
my powers alone are enough.
Damn you!
What do you take
your Zanpakuto for?!
A Zanpakuto is merely a tool.
There are any number
of replacements.
Muramasa!
Did his despair trigger
an inability to control
his Spiritual Pressure?
Ko…ga…
What the hell?!
I don't believe it…
He collected Menos inside of him?
This is a waste of time…
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Byakuya…
You were willing to
pretend to betray us
to be true to your own pride!
In that case,
let us take care of this.
You defeat Koga!
Brother!
Let's do it, Ichigo!
Right!
Getsugatensho!
Soren Sokatsui!
Senbozakura.
Let's go.
Yes, Master.
What's that supposed to be?
You mean this?
Didn't I tell you?
Any weapon will do.
Come! Kuchiki Clan head!
You do indeed seem to
possess the skills
to call yourself head of the clan.
Let's see how you do with Kido!
Kongobaku!
Hado 33, Sokatsui!
Gakirekko!
Hado 4, Byakurai!
Hyogaseiran!
Bakudo 81, Danku.
Byakuya!
Oh?
Against my Senbonzakura,
your Kido is mere child's play.
Don't get cocky, youngster!
I've captured your image.
You're no longer able to
move even a single finger!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
This ends here.
You left yourself wide open,
Kuchiki Clan head.
You're not getting away!
What have you done?
Muramasa can control
Zanpakuto…
That ability came from my powers.
By sending Spiritual Pressure
into my adversary,
I am able to confuse
his five senses.
Already, your body's senses
are in the palm of my hand.
You can't even tell
for sure if that is me
standing right before your eyes.
An illusion?
It isn't anything so simplistic!
In your present state,
even the distance you see
with your eyes and
the distance you swing your sword
no longer match.
You can no longer
fight effectively.
Of course…
if you had challenged me
with your heart closed
the way Ginrei and Genryusai did,
I wouldn't have been able
to use this technique.
It appears you let your guard down
when I snapped Muramasa.
You're wrong.
What?
I challenged you without closing my heart
in order to kill you.
If I closed my heart, I may have
been able to seal you away,
but I wouldn't be able to kill you.
You have the gall to talk
like that in your situation…
No you don't!
What?!
Hyogaseiran!
Danku.
Which way are you facing?
You're a sorry sight.
Without your Zanpakuto,
you're powerless, kid!
The enemy's skill is irrelevant…
Everyone falls to
their knees before me!
That's right!
It's all because of my power!
Even without a Zanpakuto…
I am the strongest there is!
Let's put an end to this…
Kuchiki Clan head of today!
What the—?!
That's impossible!
It did Shikai by itself?!
Senbonzakura…
Master…
If your senses have been shut down,
I will fight as
your eyes and limbs.
Then I'll control the senses of
that sword and you together!
I won't allow it.
Bankai.
Senkei, Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
This is the true form
of Senbonzakura.
It is a specialized form
that discards defense
for the sole purpose of
defeating an enemy.
Within my space,
confused senses mean nothing.
Wherever you are, this blade
will find you without fail.
Wherever I am, you say?
That goes for me, as well!
Damn you!
How is it that you possess
so much power?
It is because we fight together.
A Soul Reaper and Zanpakuto
together make one.
We display our true powers
only when
our respective souls
are in harmony.
You, who have abandoned everything
for the sake of silly pride,
cannot defeat us.
Shut up!
You're the ones who don't
understand anything!
Despite all of my achievements,
no one recognized what I did.
They branded me a traitor
and tried to put me away!
If that's the case, then I decided
to create a place for myself!
Power is order!
I'm going to become
king of a new world!
Such foolishness…
What?!
The real tragedy is that
you failed to recognize
the true nature of power.
The power you needed…
was the power to relate with
others and with your Zanpakuto.
Relate with?
I don't need that kind of power!
My power is like no other!
Absolute power that has no equal!
Then I won't say any more…
You can blame
your own immaturity
for not being able to recognize
your confidence as arrogance.
Koga…
l will now complete the duty
I inherited from
my grandfather, Ginrei,
as head of the Kuchiki Clan.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi…
Shukei Hakuteiken.
You're more than I expected.
Even among the long line
of Kuchiki Clan heads,
few are as powerful as you.
You were once a member
of the Kuchiki Clan.
By using this technique,
I pay my final respects.
Then I will defeat you and
blow away my Kuchiki Clan curse
once and for all!
I was strict with Koga,
but that backfired.
I let Byakuya have his way,
but he grew up obstinate.
Raising children is difficult.
The World of the Living
has lots of how-to books.
Don't give my grandfather
any ideas!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Zanpakuto manifestation…
Sado!
There is no need for you to worry!
I'm sure you can talk
with yours too!
Take me, for example!
Oh, Uryu!
Because you listened to me,
I'm able to speak like this!
You see?
Uryu, you have another weapon,
don't you?
He wants to talk to you, too.
You don't mean…
Seeleschneider?
No way.