Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Over here!
This one comes first.
Hurry!
How's that side?!
Brother?
Rukia!
– I was worried about you!
It's really you, right, Rukia?
– Where've you been all this time?!
– Renji, stop.
I said, "Ow!"
Cut it out!
My wound hasn't
completely healed yet!
G-Got it…
But I'm so glad that you're okay.
What about my brother…
I mean, Captain Kuchiki?
Right, there's a search party out,
but…
No word yet…
Hey, don't worry.
There's no way the captain would
get killed by something this petty.
You're right.
Tonight marks the end of the Soul
Reapers reign over the Zanpakuto.
From here on, the Zanpakuto
will rule over the Soul Reapers.
Brother!
Go.
I will not repeat myself.
Brother!
Brother…
Everyone…
Stop it!
Stop this, Sodenoshirayuki!
Rukia Kuchiki…
I will not tolerate your
ordering me around.
What?
Don't forget.
Kisuke said so too, but
recklessness is absolutely taboo.
Right…
If you sense any change in
Zangetsu, retreat immediately.
Zangetsu will be fine.
It's true that Zangetsu is special…
To you…
Yeah…
But it's the same for all of us.
We all think of
our Zanpakuto as special.
I am going to check how
the Stealth Force is faring.
Be careful.
I know.
Until later!
I am no longer under
your restraint.
I am free.
Whatever I do, you no longer
have the right to stop me.
I see.
But why injure those
who are innocent?
I just act as I see fit.
I will not spare anyone
who gets in my way.
To be honest,
I do not wish to fight you.
However…
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki!
So it's true…
I really can't use my Shikai.
Of course you can't.
I no longer exist in your sword.
Until now, you freely used
my power as a Zanpakuto.
I allowed you to do so…
Because us Zanpakuto had
no other alternative.
No other alternative?
However, it will be
different from now on.
I shall use my power for my sake,
in any way I choose.
You always thought everything
came from your own power.
But you are mistaken.
In actuality, you can do nothing.
I never thought that
it was all my power…
Somenomai, Tsukishiro!
Impossible!
Tsukishiro's freezing range…
"Should only be within the realm,"
"both earth and sky,
of the circle drawn by its blade…"
Is that what you thought?
Wait, Sodenoshirayuki!
Are you saying that…
without you, I can do nothing?!
All creation,
flap of wings.
The one who carries
the title of human!
In the name of truth
and temperance,
dig your claws into
the wall of sinless dreams!
Hado Number 33!
Sokatsui!
Impossible!
Sodenoshirayuki…
You extinguished Sokatsui?!
Are you shocked?
You certainly underrated me.
I see.
Let me clear up
your misunderstanding.
My sword…
So beautiful…
Truly the finest beauty in
all of the Soul Society…
And yet, why?
It's as though you harbor
a hatred towards me.
You are I. And I am you.
Didn't we always exist together?
Is what you said true?
Have I monopolized your power
and made you suffer?
Did you know?
Whenever you reflect on the past,
just as you're doing now,
an opening is created in
your Spiritual Pressure.
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren!
Ichigo?
Why have you come?!
It's dangerous for you to come here
when we still haven't uncovered
why the Zanpakuto
are rebelling against us!
Shut up!
How can I just sit back
and watch?
It's okay.
If we don't know the reason,
let's just find it.
Ichigo…
Welcome, Substitute Soul Reaper.
What?!
Be careful. She's tough.
I know.
I mean, after all,
she is your Zanpakuto!
What are you waiting for?
I see…
The thought that I am
Rukia Kuchiki's Zanpakuto
makes you want to
go easy on me.
Interesting.
You will soon regret it.
Somenomai, Tsukishiro.
What?
Get away from there…Ichigo!
Damn it!
Ichigo!
Does it hurt?
Substitute Soul Reaper…
You would come all the way
to the Soul Society
to protect Rukia Kuchiki?
So what if I did?
How foolish…
Oh yeah?
What can you possibly do
with that frozen arm
when you're still
hesitant to kill me?
Shut up!
Then I shall teach you
that such vacillation
will only result in death.
Rukia!
Hey!
Stay out of this!
What is the meaning of this?
Sodenoshirayuki…
If you feel hatred,
direct it at me!
You are right.
I do hate you.
That is why…
In order to make you truly suffer…
I shall take everything
that is dear to you.
Your family and your friends,
your pride as a Soul Reaper…
All you have to do is watch.
I see…
You truly are my Zanpakuto.
You know so well how to hurt me.
You are beautiful…
I was so proud to have
such a beautiful Zanpakuto
like you for my sword.
I am not one of your belongings.
You're right.
You are free.
Rukia?
I release you.
Huh?
So quell your anger.
I am grateful for the time
we had together.
You will go on living without me?
Yes.
Even if I lose everything and
end up crawling on the earth…
Even if I must return to
the Rukon District…
Mask of the flesh and blood…
Universal soar…
– You seriously intend to destroy me?
– The one crowned with man's name…
Carriage of Thunder…
Gap of the spinning wheel…
– Divide into six with light…
– Don't you fear losing me?!
On the wall of blue flame,
inscribe a twin lotus.
– What?
– In the abyss of conflagration,
wait at the far heavens!
Bakudo 61, Rikujokoro!
I…will not forgive
anyone or anything
that tries to destroy
what I must protect.
I am about to lose everything…
What are you doing?
I shall let go of everything.
My anger…my hatred…
My sadness…
You are not me…
You are no longer a part of me.
Stop!
I shall release you.
Sodenoshirayuki,
you who were once a part of me…
Your beauty…
The Soul Reaper power
which you gave me…
Everything that happened
in the past…
I will let go of it all.
All of it…which was
a burden to me…and to you.
Stop!
Sodenoshirayuki…
You will now be free.
Hado 73: Sorensokatsui!
Rukia!
How could you do this?
I never expected you
would let go of me…
A Soul Reaper cannot go into battle
fearing of what they could lose.
Even if that means
losing one's Zanpakuto,
the life of a Soul Reaper.
Rukia Kuchiki…
Farewell…my…self.
Rukia Kuchiki!
Do you intend to
die here like this?
Rukia!
Are you okay?!
That was some show.
I didn't anticipate her
going this far.
But this proved to be useful
for future reference.
Who the hell are you?!
Muramasa.
Muramasa?
Who are you?
I've never seen you around!
Are you a Soul Reaper?
I am…
a Zanpakuto.
I thought Zanpakuto
manifest into
the same appearance
as their masters.
But Sodenoshirayuki is
completely different.
How rude!
What about yours?
He's an old man.
The two of you got it easy.
Mine are a monkey and a snake!
I'm getting depressed
just thinking about
what appearance
they're going to take!
– Oh…
The Arrancar Encyclopedia.
THE ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
T-Today, w-we have
the Espadas as o-our guests.
Let's see…
U-Um, about your numbers…
Mr. Stark, you're number one,
Mr. Barragan is two,
and Miss Halibel is three, right?
Umm…
See? Didn't I tell you
it would be difficult?
This is difficult on
a whole different level!