Getsuga...Tensho!
That woman is already one of us.
That's not for you to decide!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
I shall eliminate you with my sword.
That was unexpected.
I didn't think you would
draw your sword first.
I came here thinking
that I'd have to start
by making you draw your sword.
Can I take it you consider me
an equal opponent?
At the very least,
I consider you
worthy of destroying.
That's good enough for me.
Kurosaki!
New ones keep coming...
Don't just stand there!
Let's go!
Sado!
Watch it, will you?!
Sorry... They attacked you
from behind, so I tried to help...
If you're going to help,
then warn me first!
Otherwise I'll get
caught in the mess!
Wh-What? You got
a problem with that?
I said, warn me!
Sorry.
Good grief!
I knew for quite
some time now, but-
you really don't
say much, do you?
Really?
Yeah really! You never
noticed it all this time?!
Well?
Your subordinates have all fallen.
Grow, Arbol.
My subordinates have fallen.
So what of it?
You will soon know...
that by defeating my subordinates,
victory shall not come to you.
Ichigo...
Getsuga...Tensho!
Sorry! You okay?!
I'm okay...
That was, you know...
Because you weren't paying attention.
No problem.
Man... He's hard to work with...
We may have trained together before,
but we never did fight together.
So I guess it can't be helped.
Well, against an adversary like this,
there should be no problem, though...
What?!
Doesn't that kind of
look familiar to you...?
It sort of does...
Ah, that's what it looks like.
As I recall... It's weak
against water attacks?
Hey, Rukia!
She's not here.
Sado...you can't do
a water attack, can you?
Of course not...
Gah, screw this!
Then we'll beat it down!
We just have to beat it down!
What the--?!
I can't pull it out?!
In fact, I'm being sucked in!
Thanks...
When it opens its mouth,
I thought it would
shoot something out...
If you knew that,
give me a heads up!
You pulled out the sword
I was about to eat...
So it talks...
My body is heavily
armored with sand.
I can easily swallow
a sword like that!
What?!
Just as I thought...
I suspected as much, given its size.
I keep telling you to
tell me sooner!
Damn! What should we do?
You withstood my Cero without
taking out that mask.
You've gotten stronger.
Is it because you defeated Grimmjow?
Or is it because of your friends
who continue to fight
under this tower?
Or is it...
because of that woman?
That woman is already one of us.
Even if you rescue her from here,
it doesn't change that fact.
What?!
Were you relieved that
she appeared to be unharmed?
You don't even know what
happened to her on the inside!
Rescuing her...is meaningless.
That's not for you to decide!
You're right.
It's for Lord Aizen to decide.
Did we kill it?!
Sorry.
Sorry isn't gonna cut it!
Up! Look up!
I feel twice as drained when
fighting alongside with you.
Sorry...
Man...
It's hard enough
fighting this thing,
but it sucks when our attacks
don't have any effect at all.
Guess I don't have a choice.
I didn't want to use it
against an opponent
like this, but...
Bankai!
Shut up, mutt!
All right, then. Let's go.
What a hassle.
Not done yet...
I can do this.
I can see his moves and react.
He hasn't become
a different style of fighter
just because he drew his sword.
It just means his attack range
has extended.
Watch closely...
Watch closely!
Watch!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
That was a pain in the ass.
What?!
Are you...serious?
That was a bit of a surprise.
But you mustn't compare my strength
with the likes of Runuganga.
Are you all right?
Yeah...
That Cero...
I think we'd better assume
it's closer to an Arrancar
than the guardian we faced previously.
It doesn't look different from
an ordinary Hollow, though.
It's getting on my nerves.
Abarai, what did you just say?
That it's getting on my nerves?
No, before that.
What did I say?
Something about it not looking different
from an ordinary Hollow...
If you were listening,
just say so from the start!
So what about it?
My attacks put everything in
a single strike.
I'm always looking for
an opponent's weak spot.
I've been thinking all this time
about where its weak spot is...
And...?
Its abilities may be
nearly Arrancar-level,
but if it looks like an ordinary Hollow.
If we cut off its head in
the same way, we can defeat it?
In that case...
That'll make things faster!
Wait, I'm not certain yet.
Watch me! I'm taking it
down right now!
What?
What are you laughing at?
N-No...it's nothing...
Here I go!
Hikotsu Taiho!
Tsk!
I hardly cut you.
Must be that Hierro of yours.
It sure is tough.
But I get the feeling I'm able
to read your movements
better than I could before.
What?
The last time we fought,
I couldn't read
your movements at all...
Not your attacks, defenses,
reactions, speed,
or which way they were
coming from...
I couldn't read where or
what was coming at all.
I felt like I was fighting
a machine or a stone statue.
Is the reason why I've become
able to read your movements
because I've become
more Hollow-like?
Or...maybe it's because you've
become more human like me.
Sado!
What the hell?!
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo
El Muerte!
Gotcha!
- Thanks.
- Don't mention it.
I'm used to it.
But...what's with that arm of yours?
This?
I guess it's the first time
I've shown it to you.
It's my new power.
I see...
With that thing's power,
you could've put a crack that
reached nearly to the face.
That was close...
But...it's time I put you away.
- It's coming!
- Oh no, you don't!
Go, Sado!
Leave the Cero to me!
Give it another taste of
what you did earlier!
El Muerte!
Did you think I couldn't
see that coming?!
No, it's not me.
What?!
You thought we didn't
see that coming?!
Bastard!
You weren't the decoy?!
We did it!
Sorry about using you as
a decoy without telling you.
Forget it. I figured
you'd do as much.
You kind of resemble Ichigo.
You didn't have to say that.
It isn't over yet!
Let's go!
Did you say...
I've become more human?
I see...
You must feel really good being
able to keep up just at this level.
No, you don't.
We forgot to get
the name of that big guy.
It was Batticaloa.
Huh?! When did you
get that out of him?
When it first came out.
That was just a grunt!
I'm used to talking
with cats and dogs.
That thing's the same as
a cat and dog to you?!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Today, we'll cover
Rudobon's sword release.
ARBOL
Rudobon's sword release
is called Arbol.
Today, I'll talk about its powers a bit earlier
than its formal appearance in the story.
Never mind that!
Did you see me in action today?!
Explain my Sodenoshirayuki
in more detail
in preparation for the upcoming battles!
And the power of
my El Muerte, as well...
Um, guys... Don't you want
to hear the power
of the enemies
you're currently fighting?
- Shut up!