I apologize for the wait, everyone.
I’ll be done with the
adjustments in a minute.
So we’ll have to pass through
the Precipice World, after all?
Isn’t the Precipice World
completely under Kageroza’s control?
I wouldn’t say completely.
What do you mean?
It appears Kageroza’s
control doesn’t extend to the Cleaner.
You might be wondering,
“How did the Cleaner appear
so often when it should
only have appeared
once every seven days?”
I came up with a hypothesis.
Never mind the lengthy explanation.
What you’re saying is that
he set the time axis of
the Cleaner’s appearances
to coincide with when
we enter the Precipice World.
Exactly.
Astute as always, Squad 6 Captain.
However, that suggests
there are limits to his control of time.
Otherwise, why waste the time between
your entry into the Precipice World
and the Cleaner’s appearance?
So, what do you want us to do?
I’ve reserved a space behind
the Cleaner that is not
controlled by Kageroza.
It’s a short time axis when you can
move inside the Precipice World.
You will be passing through there.
I said “reserved,” but it’s
at most thirty seconds or so.
If your timing is off
and you enter too soon,
you’ll become the Cleaner’s prey.
On the other hand, if you
leave the reserved space,
you’ll fall into
Kageroza’s territory.
You might never be able to leave
the Precipice World again.
Kurosaki!
Are you all right?
Oh, Inoue! Just barely.
What about the others?
We brought them all here.
We’re treating them now.
I see. That’s good.
Can you take a look at her too?
See if she’s hurt or anything.
Sure.
What’s the matter, Nozomi?
Are you okay?
Pervert!
It’s good to know you’re
fine and kicking.
What are you doing?
You guys are all alike.
You’re all lousy perverts.
Don’t go putting me with him!
Back at you!
At least I’m not afraid to admit to
being a pervert, unlike
like you, Ichigo!
Why you…
Kurosaki, are you all right?
Y-Yeah…
I’ll treat you right now.
It’s nothing!
Really?
Huh?
Kurosaki!
Is he dead?
A tiny kick sends you flying?
“Nothing,” my ass!
You kicked me off guard from behind!
Anyone would go flying!
Anyway, I thought you went
to the Soul Society!
I’m leaving right now.
Then I’ll go with you.
Forget it!
In your current condition,
you’ll just end up dead.
Shut up!
Try not to get yourself killed, okay?
He’ll be fine!
There’s no way Kenny’s
getting killed!
Keep out of this, Yachiru.
Oh come on! Right, Itchy?
Relax.
Until you and I fight again,
I don’t plan on dying
even if I get killed!
I get it, I get it.
Hurry up and go!
Later, Ichigo.
Bye bye!
You’re late!
We were about to leave without you.
You’re just in time.
But before you go, I
should warn you that…
Don’t need any.
Let’s get this show on the road.
Aren’t we running out of time?
You’re right.
Okay, watch yourselves.
Here we go!
It appears the captains
have entered the Precipice World.
Doesn’t that mean
that your attempt at
invading the World of the
Living ended in failure?
You’re a smart scientist.
If they return to the Soul Society,
it’s only a matter of time
before they shut down your plans.
I think you understand that.
Captain Unohana…
You sound almost like a teacher
scolding her student.
But you’re mistaken about one thing.
Do you think I’d simply wait
for them to come without doing anything?
What’s the matter?
Something isn’t right.
The Restrictive Current!
Keeping up behind the Cleaner
is not all that difficult by itself.
The problem is your powerful
Spiritual Pressure.
The walls of the Precipice
World react to Reishi.
In other words, the higher
their Spiritual Pressure,
the faster the Restrictive
Current becomes.
Is that what you’re saying?
Yes, but they probably counted on that.
But that’s not all it is.
Very astute.
I am unable to control
the Restrictive Current.
But I am able to manipulate
time around it.
That bastard Kageroza…
He set a trap, after all.
So what? We’ll just
force our way through.
What’re you going to do, Komamura?!
Leave this to me!
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
You fool!
You’ll be swallowed up!
Go!
Komamura!
There!
That Komamura…
Let it go.
We can’t go back for him now.
Besides, he’s not going to let
something like that kill him.
We can’t waste time by stopping.
I’ve picked up the Spiritual Pressure
of Captains Kuchiki,
Hitsugaya and Zaraki.
But not Captain Komamura.
Only a single sacrifice?
My science is still far from perfect.
I have much to learn.
Don’t move!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
There’s no hurry,
Lieutenant Kotetsu.
Takaoni!
Is that all you’ve got?
Sogyonokotowari.
Thanks, Ukitake.
It’s so funny…
What is, Old Man Yama?
The two of you talk
like the real things,
act like the real things, and
fight like the real things.
But the reality is, you’re Reigai.
Your intentions are not your own.
Don’t say that, Old Man Yama.
Master Genryusai…
As you say, everything we are
comes from the originals.
But that doesn’t mean we’ve
lost what’s important.
Oh?
We have our pride.
Then show it to me.
That “pride” of yours!
A shadow?!
Kageoni.
They’re coming.
This is going to be good.
What? You’re stopping me?
No, that would be useless.
Besides, their purpose is to defeat us.
We’ll have to fight them regardless.
But our target is only Kageroza Inaba.
We’ll split up here
and head for Squad 12’s
barracks individually.
Fine. I’ll drop by along the way.
No objections.
Kenny, it’s that way!
I know that.
I’m going this way.
We’ll meet up where Kageroza is.
The Spiritual Pressure in Zaraki’s
direction…that’s…
Kenny.
Yeah.
Hey.
I’ve been waiting for you.
Got to hand it to you,
it’s as though you could read my mind.
I can’t.
Then why are you here?
I only wanted to find
out how strong I am.
You can read my mind!
Try to get me from the start.
I don’t mind losing as long as…
As long as you’re stronger than me!
Yachiru.
Right.
Make this fun.
They’re both like the real Kenny.
Better go full force.
Or else…
You’ll die!
You mean you will!
What’s wrong?
I was told a Reigai is stronger
than the real thing.
Don’t disappoint me.
Relax.
Huh?
I’m pretty strong, eh?
Nice try.
I take back what I said about
not caring if I lose.
I don’t want to lose
to the likes of you.
Wait, Isane!
Kageroza Inaba…
Don’t let this madness
go any further.
Oh?
You might think everything
is going according to plan,
but killing Head Captain
Yamamoto is impossible.
No…
Not just Head Captain Yamamoto.
You seem to underestimate our powers.
What’s so funny?
This is so much fun.
I haven’t laughed like this in ages!
Reigai, you have the same
memories I do, right?
It’s just like that other time.
It’s so much fun, I
can’t help myself!
Too bad, Reigai.
If you really are stronger than me,
then I’m the one who
gets to enjoy this fight!
Don’t you dare say
it’s over, you hear?
Not when things are just
starting to get fun.
Damn right I won’t.
I’m finally starting
to enjoy myself too!
The same thing works
only so many times.
Iro Oni… White!
Not good enough!
Kyoraku!
Man, this is not easy.
The objective of these
Reigai is to stop me.
But they must realize that even
a draw might be difficult.
And yet they’re fighting as though
they’re willing to fall right here.
Like they’re on a suicide mission.
What does it mean?
Kenny!
You done?
I never thought…
I’d be killed by myself.
Well, it’s survival of the fittest.
I have no regrets.
Kenny!
What is it, Yachiru?
You’re right.
I totally forgot about that.
We’ve been together all this time.
So I’m not supposed to die.
What are you talking about?
I’m also going to take
back what I said earlier.
About not minding if I lose…
Well, all I want to do is win!
Even if it’s against
an imposter like you!
You make me laugh.
Kenny.
You just want to win, you say?
Now I get…it…
Kenny!
You’re not dead, are you?
Of course not.
I underestimate your powers, you say?
Don’t you think so?
I was never interested
in what others did,
so it’s hard to say I
understand all of you.
But, Captain Unohana…
Don’t you think the same
could be said of you?
What do you mean?
You’ll see.
Captain Unohana…forgive me.
I wouldn’t face a
captain of your caliber
without a plan now, would I?
You already know that many lieutenants
passed through the Precipice World
to the World of the Living to work
on cleansing within
the Tenkaiketchu zone.
During that time,
I made a few changes to the Senkaimon
leading to the Soul Society.
I collected a tiny amount of
Reishi from the Soul Reapers who passed
through that Senkaimon.
From that,
I created Mod Souls
indistinguishable from the
originals and placed them inside Reigai.
That is how I built my invading force.
The Senkaimon…
Do you get it now?
I’ve already collected your Reishi.
Thanks to Lieutenant Kotetsu
of my invasion force.
What will you do now?
Let’s make sure to take out
the enemy before us, Kuchiki.
I will be the first one to
arrive at Kageroza’s.
Slow down. First, we must
focus on the enemy before us.
I will be the first one to arrive.
Umm…
Fine, already.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Isane.
Yes?
Do you think I’ll lose?
N-No, I would never…
Then come over here.
If you come here now,
I won’t hurt you, even
though you are a Reigai.
Isane.
Y-Yes!
No!