I want to live in a world of peace
Without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
Where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Who are you?
Maki Ichinose.
Are you the Soul Reaper
who's helping the Bounts?
I am no longer a Soul Reaper…
I am a comrade of
the great Master Kariya!
Where are the Bounts?!
I don't need to answer you.
Then I'll force an answer out of you!
Why do you help the Bounts
when you have this much skill?
I saw Master Kariya's goal
as justice.
There is no longer any justice
in Soul Society.
Master Kariya will purge you!
You bastard!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Why, it's Toshiro!
Matsumoto! Abarai!
There really are too few thugs
gathered in the forest.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Oh! Kurosaki!
Why are you here?
We came with Ganju and the others
to stop the people gathering
in the forest.
For some reason,
there seems to be only a few people!
What's the meaning of this?!
It's too late!
I'm not going to
let you get to Master Kariya.
Not letting us get to Kariya, you say?
How can you be so confident
when you're against this many of us?
Matsumoto, I’ll be fine here…
Go on ahead!
Captain!
I don't think that Seireitei
will fall so easily.
But the Bounts have raised their power
abnormally by absorbing reishi.
Understood.
Let's go, Renji!
Roger!
I thought I told you
I'm not letting you go!
Flash and Burst, Nijigasumi!
What is this all of a sudden?
Isn't it a bit early for mid-day sun?
It's so bright!
What?!
This is…
Ichinose!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Abarai!
Why are you here?
That's what I want to ask…
I thought that Ichinose swung at me,
but it turned out to be you.
What?
What in the world is going on?!
Don't move recklessly!
We'll end up attacking each other!
What, what?
Seems it'll be dangerous to move.
This is…Ichinose's zanpakuto's power?
That's right.
My Nijigasumi is a zanpakuto
of light…
The light that Nijigasumi releases…
reflects and refracts the air
around you and creates this space.
An illusion created by light reflections.
But…he's a Soul Reaper…
He's different from the Bounts.
Even if we can't see him…
I can't even sense
his Spiritual Pressure?!
Can he travel through space
like Noba?
No, it's different…
I never sensed him opening up space.
Could it be that he erased
his Spiritual Pressure?
That's…
The cave that the Bounts
were hiding in had a special mineral
that shut out all Spiritual Pressure.
Huh?
Is he using that…?
Damn! At this rate…
Matsumoto!
He’ll keep attacking us
if we don't move!
You're going to die here.
Everyone, be careful!
It's useless…
Wha--?!
What happened?!
You!
Hey. It's been a while, Ichinose.
Zaraki.
Itchy, we found you!
Yachiru!
Jiggly, it's been a while!
How are you?
I'm great! What about you?
Ichigo… When you come here,
Yeah. I'm great!
visit my Squad first.
We'll give you a warm reception.
Oh, no, well, next time…
Zaraki!
Hey…
It seems like something interesting
is happening.
He blew away his Spiritual Pressure
with his enormous Spiritual Pressure?
That's crazy…
Captain Zaraki!
The Bounts are headed to Seireitei.
We were stopped by him, and…
Oh?
Kenpachi Zaraki!
Ichinose…
You're with
the Bounts now, right?
What's wrong with that?!
The head of the Bounts.
Was he called Kariya?
That's none of your business!
Heh! You're the same as usual…
So, what are you going to do?
You've got to stop
these guys, don't you?
I won't interfere if that's
what you're going to do.
What?! Zaraki, you bastard!
But if you're going to remain here,
I'll fight you if you want me to.
Indeed…If I really care
about Master Kariya,
then I should help the charge
on Seireitei by…
drawing in as many Soul Reapers
as I can.
But…
Oh?
Master Kariya… I'm very sorry!
You look a little more determined
than when I last saw you.
Kenpachi Zaraki!
I will cut you down!
All right…
I was just getting bored.
I'll take you on.
Show me how much you've improved.
Wow! Kenny and Maki,
give it your best!
Shut up! You're making me
lose my concentration.
Step aside for a moment!
Okay!
Hey!
Say…
Let this be between
Kenny and Maki, okay?
Is it all right?
Yeah.
I think that Maki would like it that way...
All right!
Let's go!
Yes!
We'll leave this to you!
Now then. Shall we begin?
Come on. Attack me!
Don't underestimate me!
Hey, hey, hey!
Did you think that you could
cut me at this level?
What's wrong? Is that it?
I'm not finished yet!
What's this?
Heh! How silly!
Don't fight blandly!
This is the end!
Zaraki!
Hm?
Flash and Burst! Nijigasumi!
My Nijigasumi makes all things
invisible when it shines.
There are no shadows to hide
in wherever it shines!
So nothing's changed at all.
He repelled it with
his Spiritual Pressure?!
Did you think that you could
defeat me at this level?
Didn't you improve your skills
by leaving Soul Society?!
You're not a challenge…
I'm going to finish this!
Maki's Spiritual Pressure changed…
You're still hiding something?
Don't hold back. Show it to me!
Kenpachi Zaraki…
This is where the real fight begins!
Flash and Burst! Saigyoku Nijigasumi!
Kenpachi Zaraki…
This is where the real fight begins!
Flash and Burst! Saigyoku Nijigasumi!
Oh? What's with
that Spiritual Pressure?
How interesting!
A good reaction!
You've gotten a little better!
So you can do it if you try.
You bastard!
Your attitude hasn't changed at all!
Why did the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads allow
someone like you to be a captain?!
As its name indicates…
aren't the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads…
supposed to defend those
they've sworn to protect?!
Why do you fight?!
Where do your loyalties lie?!
This again, huh? Why do I fight?
Because it's amusing, of course!
I don't need a reason!
You really don't have any right
to call yourself
a captain of the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads!
I have a problem with
the way Soul Society thinks.
And I've returned with Master Kariya,
who also feels the same way.
I'll risk everything for Master Kariya!
I’ve gained this power
solely for that purpose!
Stop rambling! Take me down
with force if you don't like me!
What?!
What's this?
This is Nijigasumi's true power.
Saigyoku Nijigasumi!
Disappear… Kenpachi Zaraki!
Kenpachi Zaraki is dead.
Nijigasumi receives
my Spiritual Pressure
and creates limitless beams of light.
Those beams erase and
engulf all shadows.
Kenny isn't dead.
Indeed. He seems to be breathing still…
The light that engulfed Kenpachi Zaraki
will soon be compressed into
a high-density beam and he will perish.
There is no way to escape.
Kenny won't lose.
How pitiful…
Now, the compression has started.
Where am I?
I don't know why,
but it's hard to move…
I don't have enough…
Spiritual Pressure…eh?
Where are you going?
I'm going to Master Kariya.
What about your showdown
with Kenny?
He won't return.
Kenny is alive.
He's dead! I'll cut you down, too,
if you interfere!
Don't just write me off!
It can't be!
This is impossible!
What?!
How did…you…?
Well, I just released
the Spiritual Pressure
I was holding back for a bit.
Impossible… Are you saying that
you suppressed…
the Spiritual Pressure of Nijigasumi
with even greater Spiritual Pressure?
That's a Kido-type zanpakuto, isn't it?
What…about it?
It's just like you.
Well, I commend you for making me
use even just a bit of my full power.
Even if it was a makeshift technique…
A light that erases and
engulfs all shadows?
You idiot…
The idea of shining light on everything
is impossible to begin with.
You'll always create shadows
wherever you shine light.
How can someone like you…
someone who has no noble goals…
have so much power?!
As opposed to my captain who
gave everything for justice!
Why you--?!
Don't you understand that there is
nothing in Soul Society we can trust?!
We've come to serve justice.
Why do you stand before us?!
It's because of people like you that…
People like…
How stupid!
Noble my ass!
Is that really your goal?
Doesn’t someone else
give you everything?
Don't talk as if you understand!
That's why I say that
you're no good.
Relying on people and loyalty
are different things.
It's no fun fighting guys
who don't have their own goals.
Then…then why did you fight me?!
Was it to have fun making me
a laughingstock?!
Heh! If you wanted to achieve
that Kariya guy’s goals…
then weren't you supposed to
stop Ichigo and the others first?
But you chose to face me.
Wasn't that your own choice?
Your power is the power you gained
through hatred in order to kill me…
Hit me with all of that hatred.
This man… Could it be…?
Kenny… Maki…
Did you make up your mind?
Master Kariya… I'm sorry…
I, Maki Ichinose, may not be
of any use in the very end…
Even so…forgive me…
Come on!
Kenpachi Zaraki!
Captain…
It still wasn't enough, huh?
Kenny…
I went all out…
Let's go home!
Yeah…
You always lament on
how boring this town is
…Searching for a place in the sun
The melody you hum is that
rusty, same old song
…Rejecting any new song
You're anxious because somewhere
in your heart, you believe in the future.
Baby, it's you;
That pain will eventually become
a memory
You're the only one.
Don't think, just feel,
let your whole body tremble;
future is you!!
Baby, it's me;
You're never alone, I'm right here
We should be as one;
Even if you stumble, I don’t mind
I want to tell you now
about the thing called love
Kenny, shouldn't you return
to Seireitei?
Yeah. There's no need to hurry.
Ichigo will become stronger
if he fights the Bounts.
I'll defeat him when he does.
That's so smart!
Well, if that's the case…
Good luck, Ichigo.
My stomach is suddenly sore!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Welcome!
Yamada, Seventh Seat,
about this document…
Yes. It's a plan to build
a convenience store.
Are you serious?
It's all right. I had training
in the World of the Living.
No, not that…
Aw… Really, Captain,
please talk some sense into him!
Yamada, Seventh Seat.
Yes?
Be sure to carry some cosmetics, too.
Yes!
Captain…
Enjoy next week's episode!