What?!
Where are they?!
Did we get them?!
You did it.
Nozomi, that was awesome!
-Yeah.
-Nozomi!
Brother!
Did you think…
I’d be defeated by
a technique like that?
Hado Number 73: Soren Sokatsui!
Now I’ll finish you off!
What…the hell?
Old Man!
Old Man.
Is she the one in the report?
Yes. She is Nozomi Kujo.
The name doesn’t matter.
She’s just a mere Mod Soul.
Hey, where are your manners?!
Didn’t you ever learn the
importance of a proper greeting?!
Head Captain!
This girl can help us!
Her Zanpakuto has the ability to
absorb an enemy’s Spiritual Pressure.
We don’t need a Mod Soul’s help!
Look, you old geezer!
She might be a Mod Soul,
but she’s still a young girl!
How about being a little nicer…
Keep quiet!
Hey!
Now come on, Old Man!
Yes, Nozomi’s a Mod Soul.
So what?
We’ll discuss that later.
Listen!
Nozomi is one of us…
I said later!
More of them?
Ishida! Chad!
Take the injured to Inoue!
Right!
Okay, let’s go rumble some more.
Renji!
Rukia, Renji!
You two stay back as well!
But…
Stay back.
In your condition, you’ll
only get in the way.
Yes, sir.
You two again?
Master Genryusai…
Oh boy, it’s Old Man Yama again.
That sucks.
But we must fight him.
You’re right.
All waves become my shield!
All lightning become my blade!
Sogyonokotowari!
Flower wind stirs and flower god roar!
Heavenly wind stir
and heavenly demon laugh!
Katenkyokotsu!
You guys certainly look convincing…
For imposters.
Why thank you.
Your praise honors us.
Nevertheless, you’re still both brats.
You need to be taught a painful lesson.
Render all things in
the universe to ashes!
Ryujinjakka!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Yes?
You people stay back as well.
I’m fighting with you!
Stay back!
I can’t guarantee you won’t
get caught in the crossfire!
What?!
Nozomi?!
I will end this myself!
The young lady says she’s
going to take us on.
We better make sure we capture
her without hurting her.
Yeah.
You know what her
Zanpakuto can do, right?
Of course.
We can’t be careless when
we cross swords with her.
She’ll suck away our
Spiritual Pressure.
Damn it!
Nozomi, stay back!
I’ll end this!
You’re scary.
Darn kids. Who told you to…
Bakudo 61: Rikujokoro!
Bakudo 62: Hyapporankan!
Bakudo 63: Sajosabaku!
Bakudo 75: Gochu Tekkan!
Seems they distracted you.
You left yourself wide open.
That’s not like you.
What’s the matter?
Your Spiritual Pressure
seems awfully low.
Shut up!
Ichigo…
He’s not doing so well.
Damn it!
Where’d he go?
From my shadow?!
Correct.
It’s called “Kageoni.”
I see.
You’re a quick thinker.
That’s right.
I can’t use Kageoni
unless there’s a shadow.
But you see…
Katenkyokotsu knows a
lot of other fun games.
For example…
This one, where the one who’s
higher up is stronger, known as…
Takaoni!
But this is not the time for games.
If our swords touch, my Spiritual
Pressure will be sucked away.
Oops… Did I kick too hard?
That’s a relief.
If I injure you, I’ll
get scolded later.
What should I do?
Should I use Bankai and
use Getsugatensho?
Are you debating whether
to use Bankai or not?
From what I can tell,
even if you did use Bankai,
you couldn’t maintain it for long.
I’m guessing you can only unleash
Getsugatensho two, maybe
three, more times at most.
Damn you!
Iro Oni…
Black!
Nozomi!
I have no time to hesitate!
Bankai!
Getsugatensho!
When you fight,
you need to understand
your opponent’s powers.
You don’t want to waste a good attack.
Your Spiritual Pressure
dropped again it would seem.
This is bad…real bad!
Calm down!
How can I stay calm!
Both Ichigo and Nozomi are in trouble!
I can’t do anything to help them.
I’ll go.
Me too.
You can’t!
You can’t do anything
in your condition!
Just keep still!
Shut up!
Your attack, Sis, is as crisp as ever.
But you still can’t go.
You heard the old geezer!
You’ll only get in the way!
But sometimes you still have to go.
Rukia’s right.
If we can get in even a single strike…
What the—?!
What’s the matter?!
This Spiritual Pressure…
What?!
This can’t be!
Didn’t you already know?
A Bakudo like that would do nothing
more than stall him for a moment.
You’re…
Surely you didn’t
misjudge the power of Genryusai Yamamoto,
who has served for a millennium
as Head Captain of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads, did you?
Crap! Get down!
Ichigo! Nozomi!
Hey… Damn you!
What was that for, old geezer?!
Where’s Ichigo?!
Did he get caught in that blast?!
Over there!
That was close.
Too close for comfort.
Hey, old geezer!
Stop that!
But Sis…
The existence of Mod Souls is
a bitter legacy in the
Soul Society’s past.
His intention may have been
to eliminate Nozomi along with Kageroza.
What kind of an excuse is that?!
He wouldn’t…
Perhaps eliminating me
is an effective way to
stop Kageroza’s plans.
That’s not true.
Yes, it is.
But…I’m not going to die!
You’re damn right.
Let go already.
I’m fine.
Oh, sorry.
Old Man Yama…
Master…
You may be imposters,
but you wield the powers
of my students well.
I didn’t think you’d
still be standing.
That will be enough.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
Now please step back.
I will do the rest.
You’re…
Kageroza Inaba!
You are everything I expected,
Head Captain Yamamoto.
Even the power of the captains
together could not hold you down.
Still, everything is going as planned.
I will take Nozomi now.
I need her to fulfill my wish.
Old Man!
You can’t attack that guy recklessly.
Who do you think you’re
talking to, kid?
You think I don’t know
what his abilities are?
Umm… If you know, then the more
reason you should be careful.
Yes, it certainly would be a
problem if he copies my techniques.
Then what will you do?
Attack in a way that won’t
allow him to do that, I suppose.
Yeah,
but…
I’ll be your decoy.
Are you crazy?!
It’s okay.
It’s the least I can do.
But…
I want to do it. Please.
Nozomi…
Old Man?
Fine.
Nozomi?!
What’s she up to?
I can’t see her coming to
allow herself to be captured.
You want to cross swords
so you can absorb my Spiritual Pressure?
Sorry, I won’t fall for that.
It’s futile.
When did you…
But this won’t be enough!
It’s futile!
Negate!
With every last ounce of
my Spiritual Pressure!
Substitute Soul Reaper!
Getsuga…tensho!
Ichigo!
He did it!
Did I…get him?
Ichigo!
That nearly…got me.
Why?!
I-Ichigo!
It means that…
my judgment won!
Ryujinjakka is certainly
a frightening power.
But at that very moment
I transferred Nozomi’s
abilities to myself…
and absorbed both your powers.
Now, my Raiku
has the powers of both Head
Captain Yamamoto’s Ryujinjakka
and the Substitute Soul
Reaper’s Getsugatensho!
As strong as you are, Head Captain…
You cannot remain unscathed
after an attack with such power!
The time has come!
This ends right now!
Oh no!
Head Captain!
Young lady?!
This…can’t be!
That man, Kageroza…
His mysterious nature scares me.
Sis!
They say embracing something
soft in your arms
will help ease your worries!
Something like me!
Now come on!
Phew… I feel much better now!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Inoue!
Look after their wounds!
I’ll go and get the
last injured person.
Huh? Isn’t this everyone?
No, I’m certain there was one more.
No, we have everyone.
I’m positive!