Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
URAHARA'S SHOP
Trouble! Trouble!
Trouble!
Ichigo… Ichigo is in danger!
I rushed here as fast as possible
to tell you,
but this idiot, Kon, got lost.
It took an incredibly long time
to get here.
Ichigo is… Ichigo is…
Lirin, calm down.
Kurosaki is fine.
Lirin, sorry!
I was so desperate to save Keigo,
I left you behind.
Ichigo, you idiot!
It seems I've upset you…
N-No way!
Who would be concerned about you?!
Sorry…
But thanks.
Y-Yeah…
Ichigo, you idiot--!
There there.
Good work, Lirin.
Shut up!
Are you going to cry, or be angry?
Hanataro, how's Keigo?
He's better already.
I was able to share your reishi
with him.
I've replaced his memories.
He can return home after he rests for
a while. It's as if nothing has happened.
I see… Thank goodness.
Everyone…
has returned.
Everyone, are you all--
Rukia, what happened?
Fool… This is nothing
to be worried about.
I am deeply ashamed of myself.
Despite me being there to protect her…
Kurosaki, I'm going to tend
to Kuchiki's wounds.
It's all right, Inoue.
What you did earlier was enough.
Besides, you should tend
to your own wounds.
You're covered in scratches.
I'm fine…
Well, anyway, come in.
It looks like you've found the Bounts.
It seems that Ayasegawa was
searching for the Bounts' hideout by
himself while we were fighting.
What about Ichigo and the others?
They're safe. Everyone has gathered
at Urahara's Shop.
All right. We're going to settle this!
That's what we came here to do!
I made a mistake…
Well, I don't mind.
You were able to display your powers…
after absorbing a small amount
of living souls.
That's not bad.
It's not enough… It's still not enough.
Mabashi, don't become addicted.
You'll regret it.
No, you did well.
Don't worry about one loss.
I didn't lose…
I haven't lost!
I would have finished them off!
But…
He…
You would have turned to sand
if you had fought any longer.
That's not true!
That's not…
They're coming.
Don't panic.
All of you continue absorbing souls
from the Bitto.
Ugaki!
It's about time for me
to make an appearance.
Before that…
What is it--?
What is the Quincy boy doing?
He's struggling.
It seems he still hasn't
regained his power yet.
I see… Go!
Of course!
Now, now, I have no intention
of leaving everyone bored!
This shall be a magnificent
public performance!
Watch carefully. Now then…
Ichinose.
Yes!
What about the matter in question?
Yes. They'll be making a move soon.
I see…
URAHARA'S SHOP
Is that true?
That's impossible!
Renji! What are you doing?!
Stop, Renji!
Shut up! The injured
should stay out of this!
I can't sleep if a fool like you
is around! Calm down!
Hanataro, what is it?
This boy…
His injuries are greater than Keigo's.
I've tried my best, but…
Huh?!
You can't mean…
His soul is getting progressively
weaker.
No way…
Use my soul!
I don't have any serious injuries.
Do the same treatment
that Ichigo did for Keigo.
It's already…past that stage.
We can only trust in his own life force.
It's my fault…
If I had handled the situation better…
He…
He wouldn't be like this!
Calm down, Renji.
Shut up!
It seems Lieutenant Matsumoto and
the others are going to confront the Bounts.
I understand your feelings.
Things won't go well if we charge into
this with personal emotions in the way.
Damn!
He'll be saved.
It's all right.
Ichigo…
Hanataro saved me in Soul Society…
when I thought I couldn't
go on any longer.
Let's trust him.
We're going to focus on fighting.
We can't continue to let the Bounts
do whatever they want!
I've gotten pretty soft
if you're lecturing me!
Hey! What did you say?!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Kurosaki, can I talk to you
for a moment?
The Bounts are stronger
than anticipated.
Yeah… I know.
Can you win without using your Bankai?
Well…
I can't use my Bankai yet, but…
How should I put it…?
It feels like…
I can almost do it.
I'll manage.
I see.
I understand.
I'll leave it to you.
What are you doing
in front of the enemy's hideout?
What were you going to do
if they found you?!
It's all right.
They already have.
It's frustrating, but the Bounts
seem pretty formidable.
Let's go!
I'm not very good at working in groups.
I see… But…
It's hard to believe, but it's true.
I wouldn't call you here
if that wasn't the case.
Captain Kurotsuchi can't fool me.
No matter how hard he tries to hide it…
A blatantly destructive movement
is in the works.
Just like last night's ruckus.
There is a traitor…
among us Soul Reapers.
Could it be…
Aizen?
I can't say that there isn't
a possibility,
but I don't think he'd help the Bounts.
Then…
We know how many
Soul Reapers have left us.
We'll soon finish investigating them.
That aside…
I have a favor I want to ask of you.
I know that of the four great
noble families…
the one in charge of compiling
Soul Society's history is
the Kuchiki family.
Records of the Bounts…
Do any exist?
Sorry, but could you check?
All right.
Kon, are you coming, too?
Shut up! Sister is going to
kick some butt!
Whoop. Naturally I, Kon,
am going to go to protect her!
Don't underestimate me!
He might make a good shield.
Argh!
Lirin, Kurodo, Noba,
take care of this.
Of course!
Leave it to me!
No problem.
Hey, freeloader!
Huh?
What's this?
They're rice balls!
You're…always in a bad mood
when you're hungry, aren't you?
Eat them along the way--!
Mr. Freeloader, Jinta made those.
He said that it was because
he couldn't always get you seconds.
Shut up! Don't say unnecessary things!
Thank you…
Hanataro.
Yes?
Take care of that kid.
I'll do my best.
Now then… Let's go!
Is it all right not to help them?
There are some challenges
like that from time to time.
Now then…
I guess I'll begin.
Zeig dih, Gesell!
What's this?
I don't have a very good
feeling about this…
Let's go!
What's that?
A party of four Soul Reapers…
Being led on a journey to their deaths.
I'm going to test them first.
Why is this thing here?
It's a horrible construction.
It's not beautiful.
Take a look.
There's another one here, too.
It's probably just decoration.
You're right.
Let's continue onwards.
Everyone--
We let our guard down too much!
Yumichika!
Where did that come from?!
We're surrounded. Let's split up!
Yes, that would be better!
Let's go!
That's what I wanted…
Roar!
Haineko!
There's nothing there?
One down.
This way!
This is bad! It's a dead end!
The shadow is smaller than his hand…
Could it be that he can't come out--?!
Hado 4! Byakurai!
Then what about this?
Just one more…
These sure are ugly.
They're not pleasant at all.
I don't like things like that.
Bloom! Fujikujaku!
Gesell!
Show your true form
for just a moment!
What the…?!
It seems like it's already begun.
Let's go!
Don't squeeze too tight…
Pull straight back and
release with my heart.
Master… I…
You're…
It's been a while.
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather trust
and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won't get started
if you don't act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Hey! How's everyone doing?!
Today, we're going to go over
the remaining Bounts!
Gorilla Man, Scary Old Lady, Gross Guy,
Fish Using Grandpa,
Old Man With Glasses…
And the Big Shot!
All together that's…five!
That's six. What are you? Stupid?!
I'm getting even more confused
by your explanation.
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden After These Messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Let's go!
Hold on a second!
What is it, Renji?
Well, I have to eat something
before I fight!
Ah! The packed lunch
you received earlier!
Jeez. There's no time for this--!
Shut up! I don't have any energy
if I don't eat!
Whoa--! Hot!
What's this?
Water! Water!
There are extra spicy
chili peppers in it!
So, it's this sort of thing
until the very end, huh?
Tune in again!