I…chi…
Morning, Keigo!
How did you…
I hadn't even said anything yet.
Yo, Mizuiro!
Good morning, Ichigo!
A pretty quiet morning, isn't it?
I guess.
Stop!
Did you see
what just happened?!
Why are you ignoring it?
Why won't you mention it?!
Come to think of it, there was
someone here to see you, Ichigo.
Someone to see me?
It has been a while, Ichigo!
Things are nice and easy
over here as always.
No one is around to scold you
even if you play kemari.
A far cry from life at the mansion.
I envy you.
Did something happen to you?
Huh?
Why are you here?
And all alone.
It is up to me where I go.
And if something did happen,
you would help me, Ichigo.
Stop assuming
things on your own.
I have things to do here,
myself.
Where are Kenryu and Enryu?
Aren't they with you?
I do not know about Kenryu!
I came here on my own!
Huh?!
Didn't you…become the head
of the Kasumiohji Clan?
Be more conscious of that.
I am well aware of that!
Listen to me!
There is a good reason for this.
I have class, so I'm going!
Hey! Wait I say!
What's the big idea?!
That hurt!
I said listen to
what I have to say!
Cool your head a bit.
Ichigo, you jerk!
Yes!
It's lunchtime!
Ichigo!
What could today's
main dish be?!
If you're looking for Ichigo,
he already left.
What?!
That was way too fast!
This has gone way past
just blowing me off!
By herself?!
Yeah… Looks like neither Kenryu
nor Enryu came with her.
Then why did she come here?
I'm guessing she got sick of living
at the mansion and ran away,
maybe.
So, where's Rurichiyo now?
Beats me.
That hurt.
You fool!
Although the trouble
in her clan is over,
she's still the princess
of a noble family!
What if something unexpected
happens to her?!
Something unexpected?
An inner tube!
What we need is an inner tube!
How did you come to the conclusion
of needing an inner tube?
Well… Out of frustration,
Rurichiyo arrives at a certain pier
and jumps into the world
of the fisherman…
Inoue!
Sounds like it'll take a long time
to explain, so stop.
Oh, okay.
At any rate,
let's split up and find her
before anything terrible happens.
– Right!
Guess I don't have a choice.
Did you find her?
Man…
Even though she became
head of the clan,
her knack for causing alarm
hasn't changed.
True.
But…
She may have become
head of the clan,
but she's still very young.
We can't even imagine how heavy
a responsibility that must be.
It's enough to make her seek
relief in the World of the Living.
We must not waste any time.
Let's look for her again!
– Right!
What's going on?
Ishida!
Rurichiyo's nowhere to be found!
Any idea where she might be?
An idea?
My, my, my, my.
I was wondering when you would
come to pick her up, Kurosaki!
I had a feeling you
would surely come soon,
so I didn't contact you,
but what took you so long?
Umm… No, I…
We…umm…just came to…
Why didn't you think
of this place first?
Come on, let's go!
I do not want to!
I am staying here!
I do not want to go with
that orange-headed man!
You're still saying that?!
If you keep on being
unreasonable, you'll…
I am telling you to leave me alone!
You know that's not possible.
Why not?!
I'm saying you're causing everyone
trouble by coming here on a whim!
You're the head of a noble clan,
you know!
Yes, I am a selfish
head of a clan
who knows nothing
of the world!
What's gotten into you?!
Be quiet!
I do not need your…
What's that?!
You're in a bad mood
because you're hungry.
That was not me!
I assure you, I am not hungry.
Sorry…
You heard that?
So it was Inoue?
That was superb timing.
I'm hungry.
Want to go and eat something?
That one…was me.
That was delicious.
You cannot get meals like this
unless you are in this world.
Is my after-dinner tea
not here yet?
You there, waiter!
Bring me my tea!
Rurichiyo!
You don't have to yell.
She's sound asleep.
If only she were this quiet
when she was awake as well.
Sorry for being so loud.
You were awake?!
Well…things must be
tough for you too.
I do not particularly
need your sympathy.
Sorry I left you alone.
Who's there?!
– Kenryu?!
Lady Rurichiyo!
Leaving the clan and
coming to the World of the Living
is an outrage!
What were you thinking?!
Now wait…
Give her a chance to explain.
Was my scolding you
about the kemari
so hard for you to take?!
No, that's not what it was…
She…
That is right!
Huh?
What about kemari is so wrong?!
As I said!
We have a mountain of things
we should do before playing kemari!
That is for me to decide!
Just a minute!
Is the reason you came here…
– Kemari!
– It's kemari!
That is why I keep telling you!
Right now, having a pastime
like kemari is important!
I have told you repeatedly,
until I turned blue in the face…
With the people alienating
themselves from us now,
our priority is to repair relations
with the leaders of
other noble families!
I do not know about such things!
I am the head now!
I will do what I believe in!
That will not do!
Just a minute!
Just this once, calm down!
How can I calm down?!
Ichigo, do something about
this pigheaded guy!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You understand how I feel,
don't you?!
Well, Ichigo?!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Oh for crying out loud!
Suit yourselves.
Then are you saying that
you oppose what I say
no matter how many times
I tell you, Kenryu?!
Of course!
We are about
the only ones who can
persuade that stubborn
head of yours!
Did you just call me stubborn?!
However, this is my duty!
This resolve will not change,
even if it means I incur
your anger or your distaste in me!
I never liked you from the start!
In fact, I hate you!
I hated you from way, way back!
If you cannot obey me, then leave!
Very well.
Excuse me.
Kenryu!
Hey!
Hey, wait!
Rurichiyo!
I do not care.
What?!
Now it's Kenryu who's missing.
People connected with
the Kasumiohji Clan
appear to enjoy
causing a commotion.
But Rurichiyo didn't seem
much different from her usual self.
– Over here.
– Pass, pass, come on!
They are pretty bad.
Found you!
What're you doing here?
Oh dear…
Sorry about that.
That hurt.
She's good!
My skill is awesome, is it not?
Yeah…
I mean that's not it!
Doing this isn't going
to solve anything!
That incident is at
the root of everything.
Ever since that incident,
the domain of the Kasumiohji Clan
has been unsettled,
and public safety is
steadily growing worse.
The people have lost
their energy and spirit
because of anxiety and distrust.
We are responsible for all of this.
That is when I came up with
the idea of a kemari festival!
I recalled seeing something similar
in the World of the Living.
I thought we could make
the people happy with this.
So, together with Shu,
I worked out a plan, but…
What are you saying,
Lady Rurichiyo?
We are telling you this
for the good of
you and the Kasumiohji Clan!
I am the head of this clan!
Let me do as I wish!
That will not do!
I will keep on saying it
until you understand!
That Kenryu would not
listen to my plan at all!
I thought the head of a clan should
do what she believes is right,
but it is a bit tiresome.
So you see, Rurichiyo
has her reasons.
If we explain to Kenryu,
wouldn't he listen to
what we have to say?
But the way Kenryu looked,
just trying to tell him is
going to be a lot of trouble.
First of all, there's no way
we can tell Kenryu
if we don't know where he went.
Well, yeah, you're right.
Where in the world could he be?
– Ichigo…
– Huh?
I see.
Lady Rurichiyo said that?
Yeah, well…
Rurichiyo wasn't really serious
when she told you to leave.
Can't you accept what she's saying?
It's difficult.
It's true that right now,
Lady Rurichiyo is focused
on the people.
Regaining the trust of the people
and rebuilding the House is important too.
But I believe that in order to
restore the Kasumiohji Clan,
we need first to mend our relations
with other noble families
and people with power,
and work in tandem
with them to govern.
It's a matter of priorities!
One day,
we will be able to have
the type of government that
Lady Rurichiyo is seeking.
But right now,
we don't have the luxury!
We must do what we must do!
That, above all,
is for the good of the people.
It sounds like…
neither of your views are wrong.
What're we going to do about this?
You're asking me?
What to do?
It's entirely my fault that I have not been able
to convince Lady Rurichiyo.
Since it's come to this,
I will offer my life in exchange.
Just a minute! Just a minute!
Don't stop me, Ichigo Kurosaki!
I must take responsibility!
Never mind! Don't rush things!
Calm down for a minute!
Don't stop me!
I said stop!
Kurosaki, let him go.
What? Ishida?!
It's what you would call
compassion towards a warrior.
We'll watch him end his life
and report it to Rurichiyo.
What?
B-But…
Kenryu, go right ahead.
I will assist if you wish.
Only, I will be using an arrow
rather than a sword.
Very well.
Excuse me.
Rurichiyo!
Here you are!
What is wrong?
You look pale.
It's Kenryu!
Did you find him?
Where was he?!
He…says he's going to
commit suicide!
What?!
So what?
What?
Kenryu already left!
It is not my concern
what happens to him!
Is it all right to say
such a thing?!
You made him protect you
in every way,
but you won't consider
protecting him?!
Fine!
A-Are you all right?!
Thank you, Ken…I mean Enryu!
Thank you.
Kenryu!
Do you think it will work?
What are you talking about?!
Wasn't this the plan
you came up with?
Yes it is, but…
Kenryu, go right ahead.
I shall assist if you wish.
What am I to do?
Good grief, how melodramatic
can you get?
I'm not being melodramatic.
If Lady Rurichiyo still
does not change her mind,
it is my duty to stop her,
even if it means taking my life.
I found you people as I was
considering that thought
and wandering about the town.
So you weren't just
nearby by chance.
I'm begging you, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Help me out!
Well, this might be the best way
to persuade his master.
You think so?
Oh, here she comes!
Quickly!
Okay!
Everything ready?
Rurichiyo!
– Over here! Over here!
– Don't do it!
– Hurry!
– Kenryu! Don't be a fool!
Don't be hasty!
Let go of me!
Let go of me, you guys!
Are you telling me to live
with this shame?
I would rather die!
You moron!
L-Lady Rurichiyo…
You really are a moron!
Do you really think doing that is
going to make me happy?!
B-But…
Protecting my retainers
is my responsibility.
I cannot let you die!
Is that understood?
Then, Lady Rurichiyo…
They sure are a handful.
You're telling me.
My, my… I guess I will have to
give in just this once.
I am so happy that you understand.
I won't have to lose my life for
something as silly as kemari.
As silly as kemari?
What do you mean by
"as silly as"?
Are you finding fault in my idea?!
No…I…you know…
a mere pastime like kemari is…
A mere pastime?!
Umm…no, I mean…
I have decided not to
give in after all!
What?!
You just said you would
agree with my view.
And who is the one who
stepped all over those feelings?
This is hopeless.
And everything was going so well
with everyone's cooperation.
What?! Cooperation?
– Oh man…
So all this talk about committing
suicide was to deceive me?!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
It can't be helped
now that you know!
At any rate, kemari is out!
You don't understand because
you have never done it!
I have, that's why I'm saying this!
I can do something like that
better than you, Lady Rurichiyo!
If you are going to talk like that,
let us have a kemari competition!
We shall settle it with this!
Let us say the loser never
says anything again!
I wouldn't have it any other way!
How do things get this way?!
Lady Kuchiki, please accept this
as a small token of goodwill
from one noble family to another.
Pardon me, but I cannot.
W-What?!
This is the elusive golden Chappy!
I went through great pains for it.
Thank you.
So what is your request?
I will hear you out.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Let me tell you about
this place, Ichigo.
This is my favorite optician.
Huh?
GINTONBO
Glasses by Gin…
You can't read it?
I thought you said Japanese
was your best subject.
Wait…I'll have it in a second…
The radical for "insect,"
so it's the name of a bug, right?
Want a hint?
It's a bug that conjures
an image of glasses!
Oh!
Gin…Namekuji as in slug!
Slugs don't make you
think of glasses!
SLUG