Trouble arises over
succession rights
in one of Soul Society’s high-ranking
aristocratic families, the Kasumiohji Clan.
Their princess, Rurichiyo Kasumiohji,
traveled to the World of the Living.
Ichigo reluctantly agrees
to become her bodyguard.
Rurichiyo, who is unaware that
her life is being targeted,
turns Ichigo’s life upside down
with her naive behavior.
One day she runs away
from the house
over a trivial argument with
her stewards, Kenryu and Enryu,
and encounters
an enemy assassin in town.
Orihime, who happened to be near,
makes an attempt to fight him alone.
But Orihime and Rurichiyo are in
great danger against this assassin,
who has a strange Zanpakuto.
Then Ichigo appears
just in time to save them.
Ichigo Kurosaki!
What is it,
so early in the morning?
Huh?
W-What are you doing?!
That doesn’t matter!
Lady Rurichiyo has
disappeared again!
What is it?
Is someone returning from
the World of the Living?
There’s no one here.
A malfunction?
Princess…
Oh, it’s you, Kumoi.
Princess!
Oh! It’s the princess!
I’m glad to see you are well.
Princess…
Where have you been all this time,
without telling me?
I was with Kenryu and Enryu.
I do not need your permission
for everything I do.
I beg to differ.
If anything should happen to you,
you are not the one
who will be put to shame.
The shame will be on
the Kasumiohji Clan.
Namely, your late
mother and father.
I know that without you telling me.
Then you must behave like
a princess of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Do you understand?
O-Oh yes, prepare my palanquin.
And where are you off to this time?
A tea ceremony!
Are you there, Hanza?
Yes, Sir Kumoi.
For some unknown reason,
she has returned from
the World of the Living.
Furthermore,
without Kenryu or Enryu.
Do not let this opportunity pass.
Understood.
Not again!
Be prepared.
What?!
What’s going on?!
What is this? Stand back!
– Yes sir!
You should be aware
that this Senkaimon
is used only by the princess
or the inspectors.
B-But Sir Kenryu…
The gate opened earlier
and no one was there.
So she went back after all.
I’m sorry. We can’t go to
Soul Society through this gate.
There’s also a chance
that Miss Kasumiohji
will return here before you.
So we’ll keep a tight watch
on this side.
Right. Thanks.
I’m counting on you.
We’ll be off.
Let’s hurry.
She probably snuck in
while the gatekeepers
weren’t paying attention.
Yeah.
You guys painstakingly find refuge
in the World of the Living
and she comes right back.
All your troubles were for nothing.
Cripes…
That’s what you get for being
caretakers of a spoiled princess.
W-What was that for?!
Talk!
To be blunt,
it is not the place of a low-life like you
to criticize the princess.
But it’s true that she’s spoiled.
What if she’s discovered by
that guy named Kumoi,
the very one
who’s after her life?
You won’t get me a second time!
What did you do that for?!
You’re at fault for carelessly
saying the name of the enemy.
It’s her fault for wandering
around carelessly!
But, it stands that Lady Rurichiyo
is still a young child.
It can’t be helped.
Let’s split up and search for her.
We will search inside the mansion.
Damn. Where did Rurichiyo go?
She’ll get it when I find her.
Yo!
Why are you in a hurry?
Long time no see!
Captain Zaraki…
and Lieutenant Kusajishi!
What’re you doing here?
Oh. That’s true.
Weren’t you in
the World of the Living?
Uh…
Um…
Err…
Is Ichigo here too?
Um…uh…
So he’s here.
Yup, he’s here!
And he’s pretty worked up
about something.
Yup! He seems worked up.
N-No… That’s…
He’s here and hasn’t
come to greet me?
Oh well. I’ll go to him then.
C-Captain Zaraki!
This is bad. This thing
about Ririchiyo is a secret.
If I allow Ichigo and
Captain Zaraki to meet,
things can get out of hand.
She’s not on
the castle grounds anymore.
What’s the matter, Enryu?
That’s…
It belongs to the princess!
The door closed by itself!
Enryu, where are you?!
It’s too dark to see!
Huh?! What?!
Something just touched me!
Stay there for a while.
Just until I get rid of the princess.
Princess, we have arrived.
Lady Rurichiyo Kasumiohji
has arrived.
I thank you for your invitation today.
Thank you for coming so far.
You wait here.
Yes!
That’s…
Why you…
You may leave us.
– Yes sir!
Ruricchi…
Sacchi…
– It’s been so long!
Come on.
Everyone is already here!
It really has been so long.
Yeah.
Everyone, Ruricchi is here!
– Ruricchi, it’s been so long!
– How have you been?
Fine. And how have you all been?
Hey, Ruricchi…
Okay!
I’m so glad that you remembered.
How could I forget?
It is proof of our friendship.
There! Just a bit more, Enryu!
Good! We’re almost there!
We won’t let Kumoi have his way!
Hey! We can get through!
We did it, Enryu!
We’ll be right there,
Lady Rurichiyo!
I think she went in here.
Who are you?!
Hey wait! I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Rurichiyo went in there
just a while ago, didn’t she?
Substitute Soul Reaper?
How dare you address
Lady Rurichiyo so casually!
You’re suspicious!
W-Wait! I’m a Substitute Soul Reaper
who was asked by Kenryu…
You dare mention
Sir Kenryu’s name too?!
I’ve never heard of
a Substitute Soul Reaper!
He disappeared?!
Where’d he go?
I guess “Substitute” Soul Reaper
ain’t gonna work.
There he is! Above the wall!
Oops!
Ruricchi…
This was made with the year’s
first batch of tea leaves.
Thank you.
What the heck?
How filthy!
I-Ichigo!
What are you doing here?
That’s my line!
Coming here on a whim…
Come on, let’s go back.
Everyone’s waiting.
You shouldn’t have
followed me here!
This is an important tea ceremony!
Rurichiyo, quit acting so spoiled.
Huh? What’s this?
What’s going on?!
I beg your pardon, Princess.
A message was brought by
a vassal of the Kasumiohji Clan
that a robber had
infiltrated the grounds.
W-Wait! I’m not a suspicious guy!
Rurichiyo!
I don’t know this man.
Ruricchi! Wait!
Rurichiyo!
Damn it!
– He disappeared!
– Where’d he go?!
Find him!
That way!
I’m in no mood to enjoy the tea ceremony
now that Ichigo appeared.
What’s wrong?
Are you the child of
one of the servants?
Did your mother scold you?
Now come.
Is there something over there?
What about this place?
Die!
Ichigo!
Rurichiyo! Are you all right?!
Rather… Who is she?!
Over there!
There he is!
Lady Rurichiyo is in danger!
How dare you point your blade
at a helpless child!
No, wait!
This is…
Get him!
Hold on, you see…
Wait a minute!
That kid is the…
Princess Rurichiyo, are you hurt?
That’s wrong!
Damn it!
Kenpachi?!
So, Ichigo…
You’re here, after all.
Yoo-hoo! Itchy!
C-Captain Zaraki of Squad 11!
Captain Zaraki!
Ichigo… What are you doing?
Now then, Lady Rurichiyo,
please get in.
Please don’t scold Rurichiyo.
Umm…I’m going to
be wed shortly.
Oh, that’s great news.
No!
She doesn’t even love him.
She’s being forced to marry
someone she’s never met!
It’s a marriage that was sealed
between two noble families
since they were children.
Don’t look like that.
I plan to accept it as part of my fate.
So this is my final tea ceremony.
Ruricchi knew that,
so she went through great pains
to come and see me.
Because we may never
be able to meet again.
You must be marrying
into a very strict family.
Yes.
Oh my… How strange.
It’s not as though I’m sad.
Sacchi…
I guess aristocratic families
have no freedom.
Without a doubt,
it’s a totally different place
from the World of the Living.
Captain Zaraki…
Due to certain circumstances,
we are working under secrecy.
May I ask you to keep this incident
to yourself for now?
I don’t know what your reason is,
and besides,
I’m too busy to remember
what’s what.
Kenny, you’re not too smart.
Thank you very much.
I was amused today.
Bring Ichigo back again.
I’ll wear him ragged.
Ragged, you know!
Ragged?
See ya.
Jeez…
We’re going back as well.
Yeah.
What’re you doing?
Yeah…
He didn’t even quiver when
he felt my Spiritual Pressure.
Seems like an interesting fellow.
That Kenpachi…
I wonder if he’s really gonna
keep the secret about us.
Don’t worry.
Kenny always says
it’s too much of a bother
and he never reports a thing.
Huh? Then who’s been preparing
the Squad 11 reports?
I dunno.
Is that okay?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
What are you doing?
Baldy made this scooter
for my birthday!
Why are you in my mansion?
Because it’s so big!
I guess it's useless
to tell her to stop.
Madam Chairman,
it’s time for tea.
Oh, what’s the snack today?
The Madam Chairman
has confetti candy.
Yay!