The Meaning of a Main Character
Lady?
Boss?
Sarutobi-dono?
You're siding with him?
You're going to betray
your friends, betray me,
for a man who attacked your friends?
What do you think you're doing?
If you do this...
Field Trip Groups
Boys
Sakata
Stop it, boys!
Let Sakata-kun join in!
Are you okay, Sakata-kun?
Teacher, can we let
Sakata-kun join our group?
...I'll feel like that pathetic
left-out boy who
ends up in a group of girls
out of sympathy!
Kintoki, we trusted you.
That's why we're here.
So trust us.
This man isn't what you think he is.
The Kin-san I know would back off.
If you consider us friends...
I see.
I suppose you're representing
the Yagyu and Hyakka.
Get out of this town
with Gintoki.
Kintoki-dono?!
If you're taking that man's side,
you're an enemy of this town,
an enemy of the Kabuki district!
I see.
Is that your answer?
In that case...
We also have our answer.
What do you think you're doing?
Women are quick to betray you,
but men are supposed to have honor.
Aren't we frien—
We're friends.
No doubt about it.
Kintoki, I once made a
promise with a friend.
Never change.
If you ever change, I'll
be there to cut you down.
Kin-san, a buddy of mine
used to smack me around.
Fool! Don't blame everything
on your sunglasses!
That's who we are.
When we believe you're
taking the right path,
we stick with you,
no matter how hard it is.
But if you're taking the wrong path,
we'll stop you, even if it turns
the whole world against us.
That friend is...
That man is...
That idiot is...
That lazy ass is...
That sadist is...
Our friend, Sakata Gintoki.
Huh?
I-I kind of went with the flow,
but I can't remember a thing.
Y-You guys are...
Middle School Class Reunion
Yo, it's been forever.
You been doing okay?
You still look like a
loser. Have a drink.
...acting all friendly and mature
at our class reunion as though
you never shunned me
when we were kids.
Screw you!
Bastard!
Impressive, brother.
So this is the power of
a bond forged through
60 volumes of DVDs?
But it's no use.
You can try to win them back,
but I can undo your work
with a wave of my hand.
Want to know why?
It's because the main
character in this anime...
...is Kin-san.
You thought I couldn't
brainwash people anymore.
Tama threw away her life for nothing.
Come on, let's protect our town.
This sideshow continues to defy
the main character and his friends.
Send him packing!
Go ahead and try!
But we hold inside us
ironclad memories of the
battles we fought together!
A silver sword lies inside our souls!
If you think you can
break those swords,
break them!
My hypnotism isn't working!
Crush them! Beat them down!
Go!
Gintoki!
Yeah, I'll let you watch my back!
While...
I handle being the main character!
I'll obliterate you.
Erase your memories, your
friends, your very being...
You're the one who's
getting obliterated.
Let's see if your memory
bank is fried first,
or if my soul burns out first.
Let's finish this.
Whether gold or silver wins
this battle for existence,
you will be the one who disappears.
I installed a special program
in myself that will activate
when certain conditions are met.
This program will cause
a hypnotic explosion
that will blanket the
entire Kabuki district
and reset everyone's memory.
There are two conditions.
The first is when my core is broken.
The second
is about to happen.
Shin-chan! Kagura-chan!
What are you doing here?!
Come on! Pull yourself together!
Sis...
We remembered everything.
Who Sakata Kintoki really is,
who Sakata Gintoki really is...
The person who altered our
memories just restored them.
After that, we lost consciousness.
Boss lady, we did terrible
things to Gin-chan.
How do we say we're sorry?
How can we make up?
Stand up, you two.
Let's go back to our leader.
The second is when the four people
who started this all appear before me.
Understand?
If you defeat me or
recover your friends,
everything will end.
That was my true objective.
You thought I wanted to take
over this lousy anime?
Sorry, but I'm not going
to be satisfied with
your sloppy seconds.
I take everything from you
and become the worst
enemy you've ever faced.
But still, you're able to recover
your friends singlehandedly
and work together to defeat me.
Yes, that is what I was hoping
to see in this final battle.
I wanted to give this
show its last episode
so I could return as the main character
of a show that was neither
Gintama nor Kintama.
Sakata Gintoki, this anime returned
as a tombstone to mark an end
to your pathetic existence,
to this joke of an anime.
Well done.
You and your friends have
made the atmosphere perfect
for a final episode.
Don't worry about me.
I've backed up my data
and prepared a new body.
Rest easy.
The finale will be very soon.
That's it?
Is that all you have to say?
Sorry, you took so long that I
missed half of what you said.
Y-You'll pay for ignoring my warning!
If you kill me...
You're finished, right?
B-Bastard...
You think you can end this yourself?
Without recovering
everything you've lost?
Nothing's going to end.
Except for
you and me, brother.
Seppuku?!
You'll lose more than your memories!
You're going to cripple yourself!
That's just fine.
Everyone else forgot about me.
It's my turn to forget.
Fool!
Have you forgotten that I've
made a copy of myself?!
I have my own copies.
They don't listen to a word I say,
but they share the same soul.
Listen up, Kintoki.
The main character in Gintama
is every last idiot alive in this show!
Gin-chan!
Can I hold him back by myself?!
Sorry, everyone.
You finally remembered me,
but I doubt we'll be
seeing each other again.
I was hoping to see your
stupid faces one last ti—
Sorry, Gin-san. We kept you waiting.
We won't let you go off
by yourself, Gin-chan.
We'll always be together.
Don't worry.
We won't forget you this time.
If you forget about me, I'll punch you.
Fools...
Now that you're here, this
anime is really going to end!
And it just started again!
That's not true.
You'll be there.
We'll all be there
to save the day.
So it doesn't matter how
many times we forget,
how many times we're separated.
Isn't that right, Gin-chan?
Yeah...
I'll find you.
We'll see each other again.
A sword isn't meant to be
sheathed in underwear.
It belongs in a scabbard.
I don't think I can be
your scabbard anymore,
but I'm sure there's a girl out there
who's worthy of being your scabbard,
so you must find her
so you can be happy.
I don't wanna.
I want Tokiko-chan.
Geez, you're so stupid.
Will you make me a promise then?
If I'm reincarnated,
I'll find you again.
So promise you'll also find me.
Uh-huh, I promise.
I'll find my precious scabbard.
Mantama
aren't cute at all.
Sponsors
Oedo Expendables
Matsuo & Kiyo Drugstore
*Not real sponsors. We made them up.
Gold and silver
The new show Mantama
begins now.
Sponsors
Andromeda Sweets Shop
*Not real sponsors. We made them up.
Episode 1: A Man's Sword
Love Country.
Be sure to watch Mantama in a well-lit room
and sit some distance from the TV!
There was a time, long ago, when our
country was called by that name.
20 Years Ago
Twenty years ago, a mysterious
building appeared out of nowhere
and spread a mysterious virus
that caused every man's
pride to rot and fall off.
Where men and women once talked of love,
we now had trannies and women bitching.
Where men and women once spoke of love...
Fantabulosa!
...was all that remained.
However, there was one last samurai
with a resistance to the virus,
whose sword of steel remained strong.
Sakata Kintoki.
Yes, he was the last hope for mankind.
The man who had the right to
claim every woman on the planet,
but instead continued to search
for a single scabbard.
That man was me.
Good morning, Sakata-kun!
Let's go to school together!
I made an extra lunch today.
Would you like it?
Sakata-kun promised to
have lunch with me!
What are you talking about?
He promised me, too.
Sorry, but I don't remember making
any promises to you girls.
My promise is to someone else.
A promise that was made
long before you were born.
Huh? What does that mean?
How much time has passed
since I started looking for you?
To keep my promise to you,
I changed my sword, my body, into metal,
so I could remain a man, even
if I was no longer human.
Eventually, the human race will
die and I'll be left alone.
But my sword will never break.
Even if you're reincarnated
as a cockroach,
you will still be my precious partner.
Oh no!
I'm late on my first day
at my new school!
Wham!
Are you okay, Sakata-kun?
Ow...
Ouch.
Oops, I screwed up!
Could it be...
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
Is it truly...
...her reincarnation?
Um, excuse me.
That's my plastic bottle.
Sh-Shit!
A plastic bottle is stuck on
the only sword left in the entire world!
What's all this fuss about?
Ms. Goriko!
It's terrible!
Look at Sakata-kun's crotch!
This is...
Don't touch it!
If the main character of
this anime loses his crotch,
his only unique feature,
Sakata-kun will no longer be
qualified to be the main character!
Teach!
Don't make it sound like my
crotch is all there is to me!
For now, let's carefully carry
him to the nurse's office.
Here we go!
Teach! Could you be any less careful?!
Look out! There's a
ball coming your way!
Teach! Please go to
the nurse's office!
Thanks, Teach!
Hold on!
You've got two balls and
a bat in your mitt now!
Okay, here I go!
Wait!
Those are my balls and bat!
Kick off!
Aren't you playing baseball?!
She hit the school!
My sword!
What's going on?
This came flying into the art room.
Is it okay?!
Yes, there was a broken
screw in the bottle,
so I repaired it.
Bon voyage!
Sakata-kun's crotch
has gone bon voyage!
Okay, let's take attendance!
It's over...
I finally found someone who
appeared to be her reincarnation,
but my scabbard is a plastic bottle,
and my sword has set
sail for a new world.
I can no longer...
Excuse me!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
You're late on your first day.
I-I'm sorry.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a new transfer student.
Sorry about being late.
I was looking for something.
It took forever,
but I was finally able to find it.
Find you...
Sorry it took so long.
Tokiko-chan!
You don't need to cry.
Didn't we promise
that we would meet again?
Sakata Gintoki
Let's start over.
I'm the new transfer
student, Sakata Gintoki.
Hey, what's with the look on your face?
Did you forget the promise we made?
Of course not.
It doesn't matter how
many times we forget...
How many times we're separated.
We'll find you.
Right, Gin-san?
There you go, brother.
Sorry to ruin your main
character gig, but Mantama
was created to be your tombstone.
Did you enjoy your brief
experience as a main character?
Did you enjoy having
everything important
to you taken away?
That's what you were doing.
I see...
So that world was a virtual
one that you created.
When I was repairing you,
I added a few safety measures.
That's why they still
have their memories
after being hit by the
hypnotic explosion?
Heh, they didn't need my help.
Kintoki, the bond people share
goes deeper than the memory.
Tama, I've settled my score with him.
He's all yours now.
Boil him, fry him,
do whatever you want.
Please wait, Tama-san!
Can you spare him?!
We were the ones who
asked you to make him!
He was just trying to take
Gin-chan's place as our leader!
He just went too far!
We'll join him in begging
everyone for forgiveness!
Please!
Did you hear that?
You people are too soft.
Gintoki, this is the reality
of what you've achieved.
See how your friends are too
weak to finish off your enemy.
See how you were too powerless
to do anything alone.
Your imperfect character was
destined to fail, even
without my intervention.
You're absolutely right.
I can't do anything alone.
Everyone here has their
flaws and imperfections.
But that's what drives
us to work together
to make up for those flaws.
Together, we make the
perfect main character.
If you don't believe me,
you can come back.
We'll take you on again.
See ya, imperfect plastic model.
Wait! Did you say I was imperfect?!
Take that back!
No, you are certainly imperfect.
You were so focused on altering
other people's memories,
you didn't realize that other
people were altering your soul.
You should treasure the
life your friends spared.
Gramps...
Can you polish me up?
No idea. I can start by
making you shiny gold.
No, shiny gold won't do.
Gin-san!
Gintama
Welcome back!
Let's try making you
Gintama Episode 256
shiny silver.
We're Back