I'm curious to see
your Bankai now.
Bushogoma!
Kick about, Los Lobos!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Thanks for watching on Crunchyroll.com!
Hyoten Hyakkaso!
Hirvi-
Anything that comes in
contact with that snow
freezes instantaneously
into a flower-like shape.
By the time the flowers blossom
in the hundreds...
your life will have faded.
All right, bring it on!
What's the matter?
Worried about that child?
It's not that...
Don't worry.
Ukitake won't do anything
funny with that child.
You should concentrate
on our battle.
I said that's not what it is!
I just don't get it...
You're working hard at running
away, you mound of flesh!
Th-This isn't going to work!
It's obviously not going to work!
I'm really going to get killed!
Help!
Time to finish it.
What the heck is that?!
Gran Caida...
A guillotine that's
too good for you.
Rot away...and die!
Ban...kai!
What?!
Jakuho Raikoben!
Is that what a Bankai looks like?
C-Captain!
That's the first time I've seen it.
So that's Captain Soi Fon's Bankai!
What's with that shape?!
How is she supposed
to fight with that?!
That's a ginjotan!
The steel sash you
wear under armor!
Why does she have such a heavy
thing wrapped around her body?!
With that wrapped around her,
even Captain Soi Fon's
mobility would be limited.
If possible, I wanted to end this
without using this Bankai.
This Bankai goes against my pride
as a member of the Stealth Force.
It is too huge.
I cannot hide with it,
and it is too heavy to
move freely with it.
And its attack...
It's too flashy to be called
"assassination"!
Captain Komamura!
D-Dammit...
D-Did I get him?
C-Captain...
Captain...
That you, Omaeda?
Yes... But never mind me.
Can you see that?
You did it.
Captain!
Get your hands off of me...
You're grossing me out.
I'm your opponent.
You should be paying attention.
You know?
Is something wrong?
You look distracted...
Aren't you Arrancar Number 1?
Are you worried about
your comrades?
What is it?
Comrades, huh?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Say...
Are all you Captains'
Bankai that powerful?
Huh?
I'm asking if they're all
about that powerful.
Well, yeah... A Bankai
is our secret weapon.
I think they're all
pretty powerful.
I see...
Then, between that ice guy's
Bankai and yours, which is...
more powerful, for example?
Who knows...?
Captain Hitsugaya is a prodigy.
I think he'll surpass me in another
hundred years or so.
I see...
Which means...
Right now, you're still stronger.
Ukitake!
Kyoraku!
Can you hold this for a bit?
This guy's finally serious.
Yeah.
I'm curious to see
your Bankai now.
He sheathed his sword?
Lilinette!
Come!
Don't shout! You startled me!
Why did you call that child?
The two of us together are one.
An Arrancar's Zanpakuto is the nucleus
of each Arrancar's power
sealed in the form of a sword.
A sword release means
releasing each Arrancar's
true power and form.
In the process of evolution,
other Arrancars crammed
their Hollow powers
into their swords.
But ours is a bit different.
When the others evolved
from Hollow to Arrancar,
they divided their Hollow powers
into a body and sword.
We, however, divided
it into two bodies.
When we return to being one,
our powers are released.
Kick about, Los Lobos!
Katenkyokotsu.
Okay. I'm ready.
Let's do it, Lilinette.
These Spiritual Pressures...
It seems everyone went
into Resurrección.
The Soul Reapers are all putting
up quite a fight as well,
wouldn't you say,
Captain Aizen?
It must be quite a spectacle.
I wish we could see it directly.
Isn't there something we can
do about this wall of flames?
Ichimaru...
Yes?
Wait just a bit longer.
The time will come soon.
All right...
Let's do it, Lilinette.
Lilinette.
Lilinette?
Lilinette!
Don't ignore me!
That hurt!
Did the pistol just speak?
What if you cracked my
skull, stupid Stark!
Shut up!
It's your fault for being
uncooperative!
Besides, I have no idea where your
head is when you're in that form!
The tip end is my head.
I've told you so many times...
That hurt!
Ouch! Ouch! That's my butt!
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch. Ouch. Ouch.
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch. Ou...
You bastard!
You're doing that on
purpose, aren't you?
Okay! Okay, already! I'm sorry!
Attack in the middle
of a conversation?
That's a very...
Bushogoma!
Takaoni.
Let me finish my sentence.
That's a very desperate act.
It's not like you, Captain.
Actually, I was hoping to get
you with that first blow.
But you dodged it...
Your release isn't just
for show, I see.
And the counter attack
you performed...
I'm impressed.
Why, thank you.
And on a side note...
Those pistols in your hands
shoot Ceros, don't they?
That's correct.
Can I assume that they also
shoot something else?
They don't.
You're a bad liar.
What good is it going to do
to hide it at this point?
That's my line.
I went through the trouble
of doing a sword release.
You will show me your Bankai.
Stark, you suck!
You haven't hit him at all!
Just shut up and keep shooting!
Don't you know...?
It's surprisingly hard to shoot
a moving target with a pistol.
Yeah, I know.
Then...
Maybe you shouldn't be
wasting those shots.
Stark!
I've figured out the pattern
of your actions.
You parried that well.
I think I'll have to change
how I read your actions.
Bushogoma!
You're wasting your time.
I won't let you do that.
I know your right pistol
can't shoot anymore!
I'm surprised.
Your right pistol has power,
but requires recharging in the
holster after each shot.
Your left pistol is weaker in power,
but it can fire repeatedly.
I was so sure that was
how it seemed...
No one said such a thing.
That's certainly true.
So, what will you do?
Nothing at all.
As for the reason...
You know that best.
You've been firing only Cero.
I've memorized their power.
What of it?
Dealing with your random firing
is troublesome, I admit.
But a Cero is not
enough to kill me.
Even if you are more powerful from
going into your released state.
Eventually...
Cero Metralleta
Running away is no
use, you know.
Wait! Wait a minute!
I won't wait.
A Cero should be effective if I shoot
it like this. Don't you agree?
Isn't that cheating?
No, it's not.
Oh, have you had enough?
How about doing your
Bankai, Captain?
At this rate...
Sogyonokotowari.
Ukitake...
Did he fire a Cero just now?
Captain Ukitake fired a Cero?!
What's bothering
Izuru this time?
No, there's no way Captain
Ukitake would betray us!
Hey, he's starting
to think positively.
No, wait! Captain Ukitake
is white-haired!
Which means he's going to betray us,
just like Captain Ichimaru.
Never mind, he's
still the same...
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Stark!
Our only option now
is to do "that."
I suppose we'll have to.
Tararararara?
And the finale.
There, you've lost
your will to fight.