Your pale broken wings...
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Loneliness still continues to stalk me
A candle lit within
The party is lively;
the chandeliers are gorgeous, and yet...
How do I fill the hole left behind
by those lacking words?
I don't even know anymore
If I can at least swim freely
in my dreams,
I wouldn't need a sky like that
I can face tomorrow without painting
over all the things up to yesterday
Your pale broken wings
Are just a bit tired from
that clear blue sky
You don't need to force
your smiles for someone
It's okay now... to smile for yourself.
Soul Reapers...
They are the spiritual guardians
of the World of the Living.
They are the balancers
who keep a close eye
on the countless souls,
good and evil,
that fill this world.
Ichigo and his friends manage
to defeat the Arrancar
who come to Karakura Town,
but they suffer a lot of damage.
I haven't been able to protect anyone.
I haven't even been able
to bring down
the one who hurt my friends.
I lost.
I'm surprised you knew
where we were, Ichigo.
Ichigo visited the Visoreds
in order to learn how to suppress
his inner Hollow.
You pass!
We're going to pound knowledge
of how to suppress your Hollow
all the way into the heart
of your soul!
It's been a while... King...
Where is old man Zangetsu?
I don't understand.
When you talk about Zangetsu,
are you talking about
the one that you're holding?
Or is it the one...
I'm holding?
I'm Lisa Yadomaru.
Pleased to meet you.
Ban...
- ...kai!
It's begun.
You bastard... When did you learn
how to use a Bankai?!
It's obvious!
The same moment that you did!
This is Soul Society...
What in the...?
What?!
Scatter...Senbonzakura.
What's going on?!
Byakuya!
How ridiculous.
What?!
Is that your power now?
What are you saying?!
What in the world is happening?!
Answer me!
Where am I?!
Why have you shown up?!
You've become rather pathetic,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Wha...?!
Bankai...
Wait!
Scatter!
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi!
Damn it!
Stop!
I don't have time to
be fighting you!
Damn it!
You haven't even acknowledged
the confusion in your heart.
What?!
What exactly did I do?!
Stand up...Ichigo Kurosaki.
In that case...
Byakuya!
You bastard...
You're being stubborn!
What do you want?
Ichigo Kurosaki...
It seems that it is impossible
for you to obtain a true Bankai.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm in the state of Bankai
right now!
You bastard!
Stop talking nonsense!
Those who have no will to
fight cannot stop my sword.
It's over.
Don't get so annoyed!
Let's have fun!
Shut up!
What was that just now?
Why did Byakuya appear?!
Damn... What's going on?
Don't get careless at a time like this!
I'm not getting careless!
With a look like that on your face,
how can you say that
you're not getting careless?!
I said that I'm not getting careless!
Getsugatensho!
He stopped it with one hand!
2...1...
That makes ten minutes.
Hachi!
Time to switch!
Open it up!
All right.
It's time! Trade off!
I'm Kensei Muguruma.
I'm going to crush you.
Don't waste your time, Ichigo.
If you don't hurry,
he'll really have to kill you...
I told you that
you're really bad at this, Ichigo.
Did you forget?
I'm the one who used
the Getsugatensho in Bankai first.
You just copied the way I fight.
You're just an incompetent brat.
Ichigo.
Give up.
I'm telling you
that you really can't use...Bankai!
You're really quite pathetic, boy.
Huh?
Kariya...
How long do I have to rest?
There are eight of us in all,
and we're rotating,
so ten minutes times eight
is 80 minutes!
It isn't "times eight," baldy!
If you exclude her, it's seven!
Ten minutes times seven
is 70 minutes then!
My job is to set the barrier,
but I'm still included...
He was strong! Far more than
I thought he would be...
Be careful, Kensei...
If you don't...
Instant Regeneration!
What's this? He's pretty serious.
You understand the
situation best, don't you?
Wha...?!
What?!
Tsk!
His Hollow transformation
is unexpectedly fast.
The maximum amount of time
he can take in his Visored Training
to control his Hollow transformation
is about one hour.
Excluding Hachigen,
ten minutes times six is 60 minutes.
That means that when
my turn comes around again...
It's over.
Kariya...
This is a hallucination...
This is a hallucination!
It might be... But...
What is it?
The mind sees hallucinations...
Since your mind created me,
it means that you're concerned
about the fact that you defeated me.
You always look back whenever
you finish a battle...
You look at the foe you defeated
and the friends
you couldn't protect.
Are you that afraid to move
forward through battle?
Are you afraid to walk
the same path as me?
No! I'm not like you!
You're pretty confident...
What happened to your Zangetsu?
Do you think that you can defeat me
with your bare hands?
You've lost your Zangetsu...
Do you know how helpless you are?
You're as defenseless as
a scared baby!
Damn it!
Do you want a weapon that badly?!
Then I'll give you one!
This is...
Old man Zangetsu!
Sorry... It's me...
You want a weapon, don't you?
Choose whichever one you like...
No!
Zangetsu isn't here!
Remember!
Zangetsu is...
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to take a weapon?
How are you going to repel this?!
It's within me...
Zangetsu!
Now you can't say whatever you like!
Getting a weapon has
made you confident...
You're really pathetic.
Shut up!
Then cut me down with that!
Wha...?!
You cannot cut me...
...with that blade that regrets
cutting me down.
I'll tell you the truth...
The truth about battle...
Battles go on forever...
Even if you defeat one person,
another strong person will appear.
And even if you defeat him,
an even stronger person will appear.
If you don't have the determination
to withstand that everlasting struggle,
you will lose someday.
But it doesn't end there...
Someone else will repeat the battles.
It's a cycle of rebirth!
It's not limited to the life
and death of people!
Battle has its own cycle of rebirth!
As long as peoples' souls exist,
conflicts will be born and
battles will begin.
Battles will repeat themselves
throughout eternity!
That's not true!
That's why you're foolish!
Those with power will always
be drawn into battle.
It was the same for us Bounts...
The ones who are first to
lose their lives...
are idealists like you!
Damn it!
You're still fighting with
a weak blade like this one?
Don't you have any pride?
How boring...
Z-Zangetsu is...
It's not Zangetsu...
I told you that I'm Zangetsu.
As usual, you're amazingly stupid!
You've lost your weapon.
Why are you just standing there?
Ichigo!
What's the difference between
a king and his horse?
What?
I don't mean, "one's a person
and the other's a horse,"
or "one has two legs and
the other has four."
I'm not giving you a kid's riddle!
Form, abilities, and power!
Even if the two were
exactly the same,
one would be the king
who controls the battle,
and the other would be the horse
that lends its power to the king.
I'm asking you what the difference
is between them!
There's only one answer...
It's instinct!
It's the thing that someone
with equal power needs
in order to gain even greater power!
What someone needs to
become the king is...
The desire to engage in battle,
and to obtain power.
And the desire to mercilessly crush
and trample your enemies.
The absolute desire to
engage in battle!
Our sharp, murderous instincts
are etched deep
in the core of our bodies!
You have no raw instinct!
You fight with reason.
You try to defeat your foes with reason!
Who can you cut with
a sheathed sword?!
That's why you're weaker
than I am, Ichigo!
I don't want that, Ichigo...
I don't know about Zangetsu,
but I don't want a king
who's weaker than I am
to ride around on me and
get us both killed!
You're weak, so I'll crush you...
Then I'll become the king.
Instinct?
To desire to engage in battle...
Sword...
I won't give it to him...
SWORD
Sword...
Instinct...
I dressed up my five fingers
with a manicure
And then what's glowing
was me instead
Inspiration is like a goldfish
Or perhaps a voice
There's no sound that
doesn't bounce back
Those lines stretching parallel
to each other
They say one line turns beautiful,
then deteriorate repeatedly
I'm standing right there,
but the way is locked
The distance grows,
but it's within reach
And even today
I trace your gibberish roman letters
over and over with my left hand
The one you see the moment
you open your eyes
What color will
he paint your nails?
Ichigo seems like he's having fun
in his internal battle.
Do you suppose
he's having a really good dream?
Men always have perverted dreams.
What?! When we're trying really hard
to help him! Tthat perverted baldy!
Perverted baldy?! Perverted...
Perverted baldy?!
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Lieutenant Kusajishi!
What is this?
Oh!
Something amusing will happen
if you put that in the mouth
of a stuffed animal!
Yay!
All right! I'm back!
Huh?!
A dog manju!
Huh? "Dog manju"?
THE END
It's over?!