I want to live in a world of peace
without conflict, like the one I dreamed of.
I can't be patient any longer
There are things I must say
At the evening bus stop
on the way home
I Wave to those sunken shoulders,
Bye Bye Bye
Got to show your Fighting Pose, Oh! Oh!
That world I dreamed of
Is peaceful every day, without any conflict.
But in reality,
there are troubles every day
And sometimes I regret,
these Rolling days
Lies probably have little meaning
~All my loving
Otherwise, how can I go on?
A Sweet Love I dreamed of
where lovers search for a hideaway
But in reality,
the days we can't meet
Go on; but we still believe,
these Rolling days
We may stumble, but Way to go!!
Yeah!! Yeah!!
A mud-caked Rolling star!!
Ichigo...Kurosaki...
Good morning, Ichigo!
Hey, Mizuiro!
I...
Chi...
Go!
Hey.
I told you not to do that.
Next time for sure...
Jeez...
You're hopeless as usual...
Good morning, Ichigo!
Nice to see that your hair's
as messy as usual.
Shut up!
What, what, what, what is this?
You're all together again?!
Chad...
And for some reason Inoue...
And Ishida?!
You've all been acting weird
since summer break...
But ever since you all took that
vacation at the same time,
your buddy-buddy level has
increased even more!
What happened?! Tell me already!
Tell me! Tell me!
- Tell me!
- Nothing happened!
I get it!
I can tell that you're leaving me
out of something big!
It's finally begun!
I'm being left out of the circle!
Pretty much. Now that you understand,
go over there.
Can't you tell that he's just teasing you?
You stupid blue skies!
Good...
'Morning, Hime!
As usual, an impressive retort...
That wasn't a retort!
I keep telling you that it's a kick!
Jeez!
It's already autumn
and you're still in heat!
Hey, Tatsuki!
Hey! Ichigo, how's your paper going?
Paper?
The assignment you were given
while you were all on break.
I told you about it, remember?!
Oh, I forgot about it...
Seriously, are you okay?
Don't blame me if
you don't finish it in time!
I know.
Well, that's fine. Anyway, things will get
troublesome afterwards
if you take too many breaks.
- What's that?
- Huh?
PROTECTION
Oh, this charm is...
KUROSAKI CLINIC
Pop!
Sorry... I forgot to return this to you!
PROTECTION
Anyway, I don't even know
why I still have it...
I don't need it!
Huh?!
I don't need it anymore...
So I'm giving it to you!
Hey! H-Hold on a second!
Hey, why are you sewing it
onto my uniform?! Hey!
And that's what my stupid pop did...
I knew that without even asking.
How did you know?
It's obvious!
Who else besides your father
would do such a thing?
Anyway, that's not what
I was talking about.
I was asking about that skull!
Oh, this? This is... Umm...
A Soul Re- No...
I bought this last time...
Tatsuki... You can see this?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Hey!
Oh, the teacher's here.
Hey! Get to your seats, men!
Okay...
All right! Everyone's all here today!
Oshima and Sorimachi are never here,
but they're delinquents, so it's fine!
They're probably all right!
All right, I have
a wonderful announcement for you all!
Today I'm going to introduce you
to a transfer student!
Wow...
This is a stronger tool than it looks.
It's dangerous for someone other
than a Soul Reaper to use this.
That's why it has
a visual barrier built into it
to keep normal humans from seeing it.
Wasn't that the case? Or is it broken?
Hey!
A Hollow...
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Oh...No...My stomach hurts a little...
Who screams out loud when
they have a stomach ache?
All right, come in...
Huh? Where did he go?
Hey!
Hey! Kurosaki!
I'm going to the restroom!
The restroom? Oh come on...
Hey! Sado! And Inoue too?!
We're going to the restroom!
Liars!
And besides, Inoue!
Girls are supposed to
hold in stuff like that
until they start getting
a stomach ache!
It hurts! And I've got to pee real bad!
All right! Just go already!
Teacher! I also have to go!
Not you, Asano!
What?!
That's favoritism!
You're favoring Ichigo
and the others! Favoritism!
Favoritism! Favoritism!
- Stop it already, Keigo...
- Favoritism! Favoritism! Favoritism!
Favoritism! Favoritism! Favoritism!
I'm going to sue.
Beef...
Pork!
Rare, rare, rare!
There are still Hollows?
Yeah. Hollows will
probably continue to exist
as long as there are humans...
Beef!
Pork!
Beef or pork? Which is it?!
Medium?
Pork!
Come to think of it...
Wasn't it all right for me to
take out the usual Hollows by myself?
You didn't have to cut
class as well...
Yeah!
To be honest, I've always wanted
to try cutting class
by pretending to go
to the bathroom!
It's good that you're not
making any excuses,
but that's way too honest, Inoue.
Come to think of it,
Ishida didn't come...
It can't be helped...
He doesn't have
any spiritual power now.
But it's been two weeks
since we've come back...
Don't worry...
He'll figure something out.
He fought pretty hard even
without his power returning...
Let's believe in Ishida.
You're right...
Ichigo...Kurosaki, huh?
URAHARA'S SHOP
Well now...
We're finished unpacking.
Good work...
You guys actually had
things to unpack?
I did. I received a number
of parting gifts from Orihime.
Are you sure she didn't just
push useless garbage on you?
How rude, Lirin!
Ah, what delicious tea.
Anyway, seems you've been making
yourself quite comfortable
inside that stuffed animal.
Once you get used to it, this is easier.
Why don't you two change as well?
True... We'll be freeloading here at
Urahara's Shop from now on.
We shouldn't take up too much space
and cause trouble.
Why did you decide to live with us?
We are Bount sensors.
Now that the Bounts are gone,
our role is done.
Also, Ichigo and the others are
at school throughout the day.
It's too much of a bother to live
in secret during that time.
It's easier to just live here!
We can see everyone at any time.
I see...
- Why are you asking the obvious?!
- That hurts! That hurts!
They're mod souls that the boss created.
They should help out around
here from now on.
- Now, now...
- I'm sorry...
- So why don't we just get along...?
Oh... Shut up, shut up...
KARAKURA HIGH SCHOOL
Listen up, everyone!
The transfer student I was talking
about this morning has come.
I'll introduce him to you!
All right! Introduce yourself!
"Shin" from "genuine sadist" with
"Ko" from "karashi mentaiko"
and "Hira" from "lecherous" with
"Ko" from "Ono no Imoko" makes...
OKARIH IJNIHS
Shinji Hirako! Pleased to meet you--!
Hey!
Hirako, Hirako, it's the other way around!
Pretty good, isn't it?
I'm good at writing things backwards!
Oh, so that's it!
ell, you'll be sitting... Umm...
Oh, Teacher...
I'd like to sit next to a cute girl...
Ishida...
A cute girl?
-I thought
- Yeah.
- you'd recover immediately...
- Then sit next to me.
- What?
- But I guess your powers
- That's not what I want.
- won't come back so easily.
- I see.
- Yeah.
- All right! Then sit behind there!
All righty!
So you're my neighbor.
Let's be friends...Kurosaki.
Y-Yeah! Pleased to meet you!
PHYSICIAN - PEDIATRICS
KUROSAKI CLINIC
No!
I don't want to live like this anymore!
I want to go outside--!
I want to get friendly with busty girls!
Shut up! Stop making a fuss!
Yuzu and the others will hear you.
How can I not make a fuss?!
If you're going to keep me locked up,
I'm going to have to file a suit against you
for infringement of stuffed animal rights!
I'll take everything you've got,
even the fuzz off your butt!
Ah...I want to go into your body.
It's been a while...
Even if I go peeping or flip skirts,
it'll only ruin your reputation...
It would be so much easier...
You bastard... You're joking, right?
Don't tell me that you've been engaging
in those illegal acts all this time.
It was so easy to be locked away
when sister was here!
- Sister, come back!
- You're being a pest!
Shut up and go to sleep!
Hollow! Hollow!
- Oh, again?
- Hollow! Hollow!
Hollow!
Oh well... I'll stick you in!
Take care until I come back!
Don't make a ruckus! Got it?!
Right! Take your time!
Ah... It's been a while since
I've been in his body!
Now then...
Guess I'll go out to do a little
of this and that!
That's it!
How disappointing.
I guess it's to be expected.
Wh-Who are you?!
Dressing up like a Soul Reaper
and acting so suspicious?!
Who are you?
Huh? Me?
My name is Zennosuke Kurumadani!
Ms. Rukia Kuchiki was
dragged away for some crime,
so I was placed in charge of
this area instead.
I'm an elite Soul Reaper!
What do you think? Surprised?!
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki!
I'm a Substitute Soul Reaper!
Here's my combat pass!
What?!
What is that? A combat pass?!
I've never seen or heard
of such a thing.
What's with this thing?
It isn't any help at all...
What's wrong?! Say something!
If you want to apologize,
now's your chance!
You're...
Hirako?!
Is that...a zanpakuto?!
Who the hell are you?!
Don't make too much noise,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Guys with Spiritual Pressure like
you shouldn't make such a fuss.
The world will tremble
and they'll notice you.
They'll notice? Who will?
"Who"?
Must I tell you everything
before you understand?
You fool.
Wh-What's that noise? It scared me...
I thought that Ichigo found me...
Now then...
It's night, but it's the first time
I've been outside in a while!
I'm going to enjoy my brief,
youthful escapades!
I won't do anything illegal, of course!
I'm going to be good and
keep my promise!
Ichigo...Kurosaki!
A Hollow!
It got here by ripping
a hole through space?!
Is it a Menos Grande?!
Wh-What?!
What's going on?! Damn it!
Everything's getting in my way...
Don't tell me that you've forgotten me...
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Y-You're...
Grand Fisher!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Wh-What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
They're monsters...
They've come.
Hirako... Who are you?!
See? I told you.
This is all because you were
releasing your Spiritual Pressure.
I was asking you who you are!
You sure are difficult.
Are you really that concerned
with who I am?
I guess it can't be helped!
Take a good look.
What is this?
A Hollow mask--!
That's right...
A zanpakuto and a Hollow mask...
Now do you understand?
I'm a Soul Reaper who's stepped
into the domain of the Hollows.
I told you..."Let's be friends."
Let's be friends!
Y-Yeah!
I'm a Visored.
You're the same as me.
Come with us...Ichigo.
You shouldn't be on that side.
What incredible
Spiritual Pressure he has...
Is he really a Menos Grande?!
But that's no problem!
Even with what remains of
my Spiritual Energy...
I still have a way to fight!
Renze Forumeru Venti Gral!
Haizen!
Those were Ginto that I charged
with Spirit Energy
during the battle in Soul Society.
It may not be enough to defeat him,
but it'll help me put up a fight
at the very least.
Instant Regeneration!
His upper body disappeared?!
He split?!
No... Were there two of them
from the beginning?!
My, my...
Wha--?
How pathetic of you...
Uryu.
You're...
Ryuken.
Addressing your father by his name
without any sign of respect?
You're the same as always,
aren't you, Uryu?
I met you at age 16
and we had
an eternal love
Beneath
cherry blossoms petals
gently fluttering downward
That steep and sunny hill
where I ran up to see you,
...And our shadows at
the corner of the park,
they are still unchanged
even today
You, me,
and cherry blossom days,
we dance
and sway in the wind
Holding in our heart
the unseen future,
we look up at the pink sky
I didn't know that Ishida's father
was a Quincy.
Does that mean that his father
has those clothes as well?
Of course. Those clothes are
the traditional Quincy attire.
You and your father are both Quincies?
That's awful...
You can't say that you're any different.
Why?
It's a secret.
- Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
- Hello?!
What in the world is going on
in this town?!
There are all sorts of weird folks
all gathered here.
There are humans who can see me here.
Even a Substitute Soul Reaper
shows up...
I'm sorry.
Due to the disruption in Seireitei,
we got behind on informing you.
You got behind?!
Kurumadani, please continue to
destroy petty Hollows.
Petty?!
But try not to interfere with
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
Oh, hello?
Wasn't I one of the elite?