Other than being
able to see Spirits,
I, Ichigo Kurosaki, was a very
ordinary high school student.
When I met Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki,
I obtained Soul Reaper powers
that allowed me to protect people.
As I began my work as
a Substitute Soul Reaper,
I was sucked into
a maelstrom of battle.
Orihime Inoue was taken away
by the treacherous
Soul Reaper, Aizen.
Together with Chad and Ishida,
I headed into Hueco Mundo
to rescue Inoue
and began my battles against
the enemy, the powerful Arrancar.
In order to stop Aizen, who invaded
the World of the Living,
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
moved into action.
An all-out war was about to begin.
In order to prevent Aizen from
wiping out Karakura Town,
the Soul Reapers used four pillars
to move Karakura Town
to safety in the Rukon district.
Kira, Yumichika and Hisagi,
who defended the pillars,
faced Fracciones sent by Barragan,
with each emerging victorious.
The final pillar, though,
was destroyed in the battle
between Ikkaku and Poww.
However, Iba managed to prevent
the return of Karakura Town
by using emergency stakes,
and Komamura,
who rushed to the scene,
defeated Poww,
putting an end to the battle.
Okay, shall we get on
with the real battle?
Don't let a single ant
escape alive.
There's no place for you
to return as losers.
Don't disappoint me.
Kill them.
Everyone!
Put your entire spirit on the line
and crush them here!
Even if your flesh
is torn from you,
use pieces of your bone
to form an ironclad wall!
We mustn't let them step even
one foot into the Soul Society!
Attack!
This is a joke!
Huh?!
Aren't you worried?
Your second-in-command is
getting his butt kicked.
I don't care.
He's a fool who only
thinks about
money, food,
and the family business.
That's pretty cold of you.
Is that how things work
between you two?
I don't like a cozy atmosphere
within my squad.
Yeah?
Damn it!
Bakudo 30…
Shitotsusansen.
It's over, Arrancar.
I didn't even have time
to ask your name.
Kill all enemy with your venom,
Suzumebachi.
Nigeki Kessatsu…
That is the power of
my Suzumebachi.
What do you mean?
Are you saying if it stings twice,
I'm done for?
Get stung, and you'll know.
Cero.
Sonido!
You're awfully soft!
If that is truly a weapon that
kills an enemy in two strikes,
if you had used Flash Step
to approach me
at the moment you stopped me,
the contest would have been over.
That's what I would have done.
He's fast!
One more!
You're completely on
the defensive now!
What's the matter?
No way to attack?
You sure talk a lot…
What, are you tired?
Huh?
It'll only take me one strike
to finish you off.
I recommend you hurry up
and use your killer or
best move before that.
What?!
What the hell are
you talking about?!
Let me tell you!
I'll settle this contest
without even using Shikai
or my killer move!
I'm getting tired of this.
You're still alive?
Oh…boy……
You know…
Truth is, I wanted to fight
that blonde chick…
I have absolutely no interest
in a lumbering fatso like you.
Fatso?!
What're you talking about?
Is something wrong
with your eyes?
Or is it…
I know.
It's jealousy, isn't it?!
Certainly, you are fat,
and you look bad!
And there's no denying
you look shabby.
But that's not my fault!
Don't take it out on me!
What?
Look, you!
No matter what someone
who looks bad
says to someone
who looks good,
no matter how much
someone with no money
complains to someone
who does,
it just sounds like
an inferiority complex.
Hey.
Who is this guy who
looks good and has money?
Are you an idiot on top of
being ugly and fat?
An idiot?
Who are you speaking
with right now?
There's nobody else here
besides you and me.
In other words…
it's me, of course!
My looks leave nothing
to be desired!
And what's more,
I am a man of enviable wealth!
And look at this sense of style!
I talk a lot?
Yeah.
Do all Arrancar talk that much
during a fight?
I have a tendency
to become talkative
when the battle
looks so easy.
I see.
Then to make you talk less,
I just have to make it
difficult for you?
Unfortunately, my second in command
is quite annoying.
I'm afraid I have
all the talk I need.
What?!
All I'm saying is to
be quiet for a while.
I'll fix that wise-ass mouth
of yours so you can't talk!
I don't think so.
I have him!
You think I can't keep up
with that level of speed?!
Sorry, but I'm still talking!
Looking at your uniform,
you're the captain of Squad 2,
aren't you?
What they call the Stealth Force.
I heard the Stealth Force was
comprised of assassins,
but your way of fighting
is awfully soft.
Or is this level of fighting
what the Soul Society
considers an assassination?
Which reminds me,
earlier you said you didn't
have time to ask my name?
Lucky you.
Now you have time to hear it.
I am His Majesty
Barragan's Fracciones, Ggio Vega.
And while I'm at it, I'll tell you
the other name, as well.
Bite Off, Tigre Estoque!
A good-looking man
is bred from
good lineage and
a good environment.
It polishes the senses.
Oh, a pauper wouldn't understand
the sense of a hot man like me!
I got it, I got it.
Shut up already, fatso.
I don't want to be called "fatso"
by a fatso!
And besides, I'm not fat!
I'm full-bodied!
A symbol of abundance!
It's different from how a pauper
like you bloats up for no reason!
So there!
Man, you are such a pain.
A real pain in the ass.
Moron! I think you're
a real pain too, you know!
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to put an end
to this right now.
What is that now?
In the first place, those clothes
you're wearing aren't cool!
Huh?
Stomp Down…
Mamut!
Damn it!
These guys use
sneaky transformations!
Becoming huge like that!
I'm only fighting with my sword!
Huh?
In my Resurreccion, my movements
become slower the bigger I get,
but for a fatso like you,
it's just right, isn't it?
How's that?!
Once more!
Hey, fatso!
If you can't keep up
with this movement,
you really are a slowpoke!
I'm not fat!
I'm "full-bodied," I said,
you're the real fatso, you!
You're not exactly
fleet of foot either!
This coming from a guy
who's running away?!
Even being rich doesn't
make you a fast guy.
Right?!
Like hell I'm going to
fight you head on!
What?!
Moron!
In a street battle,
legs aren't important, savvy is!
With that body, going down is easy,
but climbing is tough!
If you can follow me
to this height…
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Okay…here I come!
His attacks are sharper!
Hey, how long do you plan on
analyzing my moves like that?
The same could be said for you.
No doubt.
But don't think you'll have
that sort of leeway forever!
He's increased his
destructive power, as well!
There's no time to rest!
Oh…not bad!
Then, how about this?!
I see…
Resurreccionn increased his
attacking power by several levels!
Take this!
And his speed has increased!
However…
That's not enough to kill me!
Now that's more like it…
N-N-No fair, you!
You can't have awesome jumping
ability with that size of yours!
How strong are your legs, anyway?!
Don't you know?
It's not good to judge a person
by appearances.
Take this!
Running away
isn't getting us anywhere!
You can't keep running
with that huge body.
If you had the choice,
maybe you should've spent
your money on becoming more agile?
You're mine!
I'm not just running away, am I?
How did you?!
Who do you think I am?
What?
I am lieutenant of Squad 2,
and concurrently leader of
the Stealth Force Second Unit,
"Patrol Troops," Marechiyo Omaeda!
That's the "Stealth Force."
There's no way I'd be slow.
You were putting on an act?
You mocked me!
Smash 'em,
Gegetsuburi!
Let this be a lesson.
It's wrong to judge others
by appearances.
The same technique again…
Well, it looks like the attacks
are starting to have an effect.
I fully understood that you were
not attacking me all that time,
watching how I would
make the first move.
I knew, too,
that you were doing that
because you felt inside
that you still
had the leeway to
field my attacks.
But unfortunately, this is still
not everything that I have.
I think it's to your benefit
to discard that sense of having
leeway as soon as possible.
Interesting.
All right!
You fool! I won!
Serves you right!
Talk smack to me, will you?!
Look at you now, pauper!
Hopping like a bunny with
that huge body of yours!
You've got no substance!
You've got a face like
a vacuum cleaner, you bastard!
Shall I tear off this
funny nose of yours?!
Well?!
Oh?
I…uh…
Sorry…I was so obsessed
with this nose that I…
I've always admired a long,
good-looking nose like this,
you know…
Is that so?
Then I will extend your nose, too?
Uh, no, I'm sorry!
I was just kidding! Just kidding!
I said just kidding!
Let go!
You're going to stretch it!
Like this?
Uh…come on!
Give me a break!
Oh… Ow ow ow!
My nose is still here, right?
What?! What just happened?!
What the…
C-Captain?!
An Arrancar's Resurrecion form
sure is difficult to pronounce.
– Tigr…
– That's Tigre Estoque!
Written with the Chinese characters
for tiger, fang, swift, wind
and read Tigre Estoque!
Save stuff like that for
the Arrancar Encyclopedia.
Shut the hell up!
The powers that be won't let me!
Today's Zanpakuto is
my younger sister, Rukia Kuchiki's
"Sodenoshirayuki."
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki.
It is a snow and
ice type Zanpakuto.
Sodenoshirayuki's blade, guard
and hilt are all pristine white.
It is said to be
the most beautiful Zanpakuto
in the Soul Society today.
DEEPLY TOUCHED
My Zanpakuto, the most beautiful…
I don't deserve such praise!
I'm just stating the facts.