Brother...
I'm sure that Brother
is somewhere, doing...
Crap!
Oh no!
Is this yours?
Oh... Yeah...
It's dangerous!
Be careful!
That's good!
Huh?
There!
Take a shot!
That's good!
They're still playing.
It looks like they're
middle school students.
Excuse me!
It's our time to use the field.
- Huh?
Huh?
Who are you?
We've reserved this time slot.
Huh? Oh, you're a bunch of brats!
Sorry, but we're using this field!
What? No way...
You can use that empty area
on the side!
No way! It's our time to use it!
Follow the rules!
What a bother...
You don't even need a field.
We don't get much time to use the field
because you brats reserve it.
What do you mean
we don't need the field?!
We've got practice, too!
That's right!
Yeah!
What?!
What's going on?!
You've got some nerve!
You're just grade schoolers!
Kurosaki, this is bad...
So what if we're just grade schoolers!
Follow the rules!
What?!
What of it?!
An empty lot is good enough for kids!
You're not even serious about practicing!
We are serious!
we're far more serious than you.
You can't even follow the rules!
I'm saying that poor players shouldn't
even bother making reservations!
Are you really better than we are?!
Y-You brat!
Now, wait...
If you're so confident,
shall we play a game?
A game?
We'll play a game of soccer!
If you're not playing around,
then show us your skill!
What should we do?
But that's so sudden...
It's impossible...
Fine!
- What?!
- Kurosaki, what are you saying?!
It's fine! Let's accept!
Then it's decided!
We'll play here next Saturday evening!
If you lose, we're going to make you
eat spaghetti through your noses!
What?! That's...
All right!
Don't you back out on us either!
Kurosaki, what are we going to do?
That's quite an agreement.
We just have to win!
If we lose, we have to eat spaghetti
through our noses.
What are you saying?!
We just have to win!
If we can...
Anyway, let's show some spirit!
Is showing spirit enough?!
We've got to come up
with some sort of strategy.
That's it!
How about we ask
your brother to help us?!
What?!
Your brother seems like
he's good at sports!
I see! Our opponents
are middle school students.
It's all right if we get help from
a high school student, right?!
Sorry... My brother can't do it.
He's on a trip right now.
What?!
I see...
I'll look for someone else
who's good at soccer!
Someone else? Who is there?
There's probably someone...
He's that guy from this morning.
Hey!
You picked up my ball, right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Say, what school do you go to?
Huh?
I don't go to any school!
I'm busy! Go away!
You can play soccer, right?
Who knows?
We've got a soccer match!
want to play with us?
What?!
Hold on...
What're you doing?!
Never mind that, Kurosaki.
Take a look at him...
He's got silver hair...
He probably colored it!
And he looks fierce.
He's probably a delinquent.
Don't bring a guy like that
on to our team!
Besides, is that little guy
really good at soccer?
What?!
Who're you calling a midget?!
We never went as far
as to call you that...
Hey!
Wait!
In that case...
All right!
- Amazing!
Amazing!
- That's amazing!
- That's so cool!
Where are you from?
What's your name?
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
Toshiro, huh? What a cool name.
Did you color your hair, Toshiro?
Your hairstyle is pretty neat, Toshiro!
Please! You're our only hope!
Uh... I told you, I'm...
It's just a regular Hollow.
It's that sensation again...
I'm the only one nearby!
Oh! Toshiro! Where're you going?!
I've got urgent business!
What?!
Sorry! I can't help you!
We'll be practicing every day
at the park on the hill.
Be sure to come tomorrow!
We really can't get
much practice here.
In the end, Toshiro didn't come...
I thought that we'd
gotten a strong ally.
I suppose we should practice
eating spaghetti through our noses.
I'm going to look for Toshiro!
Oh! Wait, Kurosaki!
You guys keep practicing!
I knew he'd be here...
Toshiro!
You again?
Why didn't you come to practice?!
I never said that I'd help you.
Besides, I don't have the time!
You're a grade schooler.
What are you so busy doing?!
Shut up!
Say, why do you come here?
Do you live nearby?
Not really...
Are you listening, Toshiro?!
It's cause I can see the sky
the best from here.
Come on!
I told you to stop calling me "Toshiro"!
I'll call you by your last name
when you've been admitted
into the same place that I have!
No way!
Who'd go there?!
It brings back memories...
Hmm?
Brings back memories?
How old are you?
That doesn't concern you!
Don't go there!
Huh?
Oh... No... How should I put this?
I sense something bad
in that direction.
Could it be that she...
Someone defeated it...
Toshiro, is something the matter?
No...
It's nothing.
Say... You'll come tomorrow, right?!
Who knows?
Captain!
Are you stalking someone?
No!
There's just something
I'm curious about.
What?! Captain...
You're interested in a girl
from the World of the Living?!
I told you that's not it!
Come now...
You don't need to be bashful!
Ugh... That's enough!
Oh, Captain! Wait!
In the end, Toshiro never came...
Nobody could get anyone
to help us, either.
What'll we do?
Maybe we should have practiced
eating spaghetti through our noses.
Maybe we should just apologize?
Shut up!
We've come this far.
We've got to do this!
What's wrong with you all!
Come on. Let's go!
All right!
- All right...
That's good, Kurosaki!
Keep on going!
Kurosaki!
Are you all right?!
Those bastards!
They're terrible!
What, are you finished?
Shut up!
This is nothing!
Come on. Let's go!
- O-Okay!
All right!
Middle school students
sure are strong...
We'll lose at this rate.
Why're you getting timid?!
Because your leg...
I-I told you that I'm all right!
See?!
I-I'm all right.
Maybe it's no good...
Oh! Everyone, look at that!
Toshiro!
Time out!
You're late!
I never made any promises.
Who's he?
We're going make
our counterattack now!
They're getting someone
to help them now?
Everyone, we're going to
make a comeback!
- All right!
Hey, wait!
I didn't come here to play soccer...
Are you hurt?
This is nothing!
What's wrong?
Oh well...
We just have to win, right?
Yeah!
Changing players!
I'm not letting you do that!
All right!
What?!
Crap!
He did it!
Amazing!
- Go!
- Toshiro!
Crap!
We did it!
- Yeah!
Put it in!
This is your team...
You do it!
All right!
No way...
- We did it!
- We did it! We did it!
We did it!
We won!
It's all thanks to you, Toshiro!
You made the winning goal...
Anyway, I have to
ask you something.
Wh-What is it?
Earlier, you...
It's appeared again!
This is a Huge Hollow...
No, is it a Menos?
Everyone!
Wait! Don't go.
Huh?
Toshiro, you can see that thing?
I'll explain later. Anyway, run away.
I can't!
I can't just stand by
while this happens to my friends!
H-Hey!
It doesn't affect him?!
The same black kimono
that Brother has...
A Soul Reaper...
Frost unto the Heavens...
Hyorinmaru!
Too bad for you.
I'm in the World of the Living.
You can't do anything.
A Cero.
Too slow!
Amazing...
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Oh! How is everyone?!
They're all right.
- Thank goodness.
- Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- What happened?
- What's going on?
That freaked me out.
Toshiro, that uniform...
It seems that you have
strong spiritual power...
But I never expected that
you could see me in this form.
Say, do you know
where my brother is?
Judging from the way you're dressed,
you're a Soul Reaper, right?
How do you know
about Soul Reapers?
My brother is also a Soul Reaper...
His name is Ichigo Kurosaki!
Kurosaki?!
I see. You're Ichigo Kurosaki's
younger sister... That makes sense.
Sorry, but I don't know where he is.
I see...
But...
Kurosaki is trying to become stronger.
Just like you.
No matter what,
he doesn't give up until the end.
That's the sort of person he is.
Don't worry. He's your brother right?
You're right.
Captain! I'm glad you're safe.
Is she a Soul Reaper, too?
Yeah. She's my subordinate.
Oh? You have subordinates?
Yeah.
You're late, Matsumoto!
I'm sorry.
Huh? Captain, this girl...
She's Ichigo Kurosaki's sister.
Ichigo's?!
Pleased to meet you...
I'm Rangiku Matsumoto.
I'm Captain Hitsugaya's Lieutenant.
Wow. You really are a Captain!
You sure are cool, Toshiro...
Even though you're
a grade schooler.
A grade schooler?
What?
It's too much for me!
How many times must you
make the same mistake?!
I'm not a grade schooler!
Captain, good work helping out
those grade schoolers!
Shut up!
There's no need to get so mad.
Oh. Come to think of it, we're helping out
high school students next!
What do you mean "next"?
All right, let's give it our best!
Listen to me!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
We're having okonomiyaki
for dinner tonight!
It'll all be gone if you don't hurry!
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Aren't you going to eat?
Well... How should I put this?
I wanted to eat rice today.
I cooked some rice! Here!
Huh? Why? We're having
okonomiyaki today, right?!
What are you talking about?
You eat the okonomiyaki with rice!
Huh? But...it's a carbohydrate
with a carbohydrate.
It's essential!
Huh? What?!