Ichigo and his friends are suddenly
attacked by an elite group of Arrancars.
During the battle,
Orihime is taken to Hueco Mundo.
Ichigo and his friends realize Orihime's
disappearance and try to go to save her,
but Genryusai forbids them
from taking action.
Furthermore, Genryusai determines that
the Arrancars are prepared for battle.
He orders Rukia and Hitsugaya's
advance troops to return to Soul Society.
Ichigo is left alone in
the World of the Living.
He ignores Genryusai's orders
and decides to go
to Hueco Mundo by himself.
Ichigo goes to Urahara's Shop for
a way to get into Hueco Mundo.
Waiting there for him
were Ishida and Sado.
They too are prepared
to go to Hueco Mundo.
Believe in us.
It seems like you're finally prepared.
Let's go!
I wonder if it was really a good idea
for me to come here.
I wonder if the battle got worse
because I healed those people.
No... But, right now,
I have to make them think that
I'm of use to them, no matter what.
At least until everyone's
prepared for battle.
Huh?!
What's this?
We arrived inside
a pretty well-made building.
I imaged Hueco Mundo to be
a little more disorganized.
Keep your voice down, Kurosaki!
Someone should have noticed us
after the noise we made coming in!
Is this really Hueco Mundo?
Are you listening, Kurosaki?!
I'm listening!
Anyway, you're talking
louder than I am!
Oh. Sorry...
Well, this will be a lot quicker
if they notice we're here.
We can just catch the first guy
who comes out
and make him tell
us where Inoue is.
Hey! If anyone's here, come out!
Kurosaki?!
Stop standing around
and look for someone!
Hey!
You're right...
Hey, Sado, too?!
Hey, wait!
All right. It looks safe.
Hey! Is anyone here!
Kurosaki!
What? It looks safe, right?
Then there's no problem...
As I keep saying,
don't you have any sense of caution?!
Aw...Shut up...
Ishida, calm down.
I am calm!
Run!
Ishida! How could you do that?!
It's your fault to begin with!
Hey! Are you trying to
blame this on me?!
Now's not the time to argue.
- I know!
It's a side path!
What should we do?
Anything's fine! Let's go!
Sado!
Ishida!
Thanks... You saved me.
Jeez... What an old-fashioned trap.
And who's the one who
fell for that old-fashioned trap?!
I'm sorry about that...
Well, as long as you understand!
Let's hurry ahead.
Anyway, this path looks safe.
How long does
this hallway continue?
Don't ask me.
We've gone in pretty far...
We should find something
sooner or later.
Still...
There's no sign of anyone at all.
Did we wander into
somewhere strange?
Don't let your guard down,
Kurosaki.
I know!
I'm being careful...
Huh?
This is...the same thing
that happened earlier.
Kurosaki, what do you
think that sound is?
I don't want to imagine what it is.
I thought so!
Jeez. What truly basic traps!
Now's not the time
to be impressed!
I'm not impressed!
Chad?!
Leave this to me!
Chad!
Nice, Chad!
It's not nice!
I told you to not let
your guard down!
All right, all right!
I was at fault this time!
Wait, Kurosaki!
I'm not finished talking to you!
Who are you?
Ah!
They've shown up!
Wh-Why are we running away?!
We finally encountered an enemy!
It's the perfect chance
to get information!
Are you stupid?!
If we fight in this narrow place,
what'll we do if the building collapses?
We won't do anything!
It's not a problem if it collapses!
You really are stupid!
Didn't you notice while
we were walking around?!
There aren't any windows
in this long corridor!
So?
We're underground!
Is there any other reason why
there wouldn't be any windows?!
So what if it's underground?!
Fighting here is
not our best option!
We've got to wait until
we come to a wide area.
Let's go through, Ishida!
A hall?
All right! You don't have any complaints
about this place do you, Ishida?!
Stairs!
It might connect to the outside!
I'll go check!
Oh! Hey!
Where are you intruders going?
Another one!
I guess there wouldn't be
only one in a place this wide.
It seems they've
trapped us in between.
Don't say that, idiot!
Are they Arrancars, too?
They seem more like Hollows
than the ones that came
to the World of the Living.
Well, that's all right.
Anyway...Chad, Ishida,
you two should stand ba--
Wh-What are you doing, Chad?!
You're the one who's
going to stand back, Ichigo.
We're going to...
...handle this.
What are you saying?
Save your stamina
until we find Inoue.
Mr. Urahara gave me information
about the Arrancars.
The guys that the Arrancar
named Grimmjow brought with him
were a mixed team of
Gillians and Adjuchas.
Menos Grande usually
turn into humanoids
when they become Arrancars.
But it seems that only the Vasto Lordes,
the highest ranking Hollows,
become humanoids
100% of the time.
As for the other two ranks,
even if they become Arrancars,
many don't become
completely humanoid.
Also...
The lower their intelligence,
the closer to Hollows they become.
Ishida!
I can't ignore that.
Demora is one thing...
But I, Iceringer,
have low intelligence?
I can't ignore that at all.
Ice!
Don't talk as if I'm
the only one who's stupid!
Don't run away!
We can't become humanoid?!
We discarded our human forms
so that we could gain enormous power!
Don't underestimate me, humans.
Ishida! Chad!
Shut up!
Shut up and watch, Kurosaki!
You bastard!
I'm your opponent!
Ishida! What are you doing?!
I told you, you're in the way!
What?!
Chad! You, too?!
Get out of the way.
You don't have time to be
concerned about others!
Chad!
Ichigo!
Kurosaki, keep out of this!
You two...
This guy...
I thought that it was
just a regular slap,
but he's surrounding his hand
with reishi when he attacks!
It's a more troublesome attack
than it looks.
I can't construct my spirit weapon
with the reishi disturbance.
If I could only gain
a little distance...
Sado!
A slow attack...
He can't keep up
with my Sonido.
I've already measured
your fighting power.
One has power,
but is slow.
The other is fast,
but lacks power!
Here I go!
Now!
What?
Why is he just standing there?
Have you given up, you fool?!
Wait, Demora!
My, my...
Compatibility is important.
I've been fighting
the same enemy for a while,
so I forgot the most basic thing.
We're fighting two-on-two...
If we have difficulty
fighting one enemy,
we just have to trade off and
fight the one that's easier to fight.
Power against power.
Speed against speed.
Now then...
Let's retaliate.
Wh-What is that?
Ishida?! Is that a bow?
Is it a bow, you ask?
Of course...
What weapon would I
use besides a bow?
This is my new spirit bow...
Ginreikojaku.
I shouldn't have
destroyed your mask.
You looked more pleasant
when you had it on.
What's wrong? Aren't you going to
show off your strength?
Is that all you've got?
Crap... You damn human!
Is that a Sonido?
As expected, you're fast.
Impossible!
There's no way that a human can
keep up with the speed of a Sonido.
Sorry...
Unfortunately,
I'm no ordinary human.
I'm a Quincy.
This is called a Hirenkyaku.
It's a Quincy high-speed
maneuvering technique.
Personally, I think it's better than
the Soul Reaper's flash step.
A Quincy?!
An advanced class human?!
I don't know anything about that!
You don't know? I see...
You're embarrassingly ignorant,
aren't you?
Shut up!
Even if you can keep up with
my Sonido, nothing changes.
As long as your bow cannot
guard against my Uña Tirotea!
Oh?! Are you going to shoot down
all of my Uña Tirotea?!
What a simple solution!
You're like a child, Quincy!
Try your best!
But I'll tell you one thing!
My Uña Tirotea fires
108 shots in a row.
I'm going to see how long
you can keep this up...
I see.
Then let me tell you one thing.
My Ginrei Kojaku fires...
1200 shots in a row.
Wha--?
Crap! Crap!
I can't lose to a small guy like you!
That's impossible!
Is that it?
The fact that you used that at this stage
means that was your final attack.
Now it's my turn to attack.
Sorry...
I really don't like finishing off enemies
who don't have any will to fight.
But it seems that this time...
I can't be so soft.
El...Directo.
It looks like all of the Espada
will finally appear.
New guys are going to appear?
Soul Reaper captains,
Visoreds, the Espada...
With this many people,
someone's probably going to disappear.
Be careful, Kurosaki. In your case,
you can't let your guard down.
Again?!
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Today, I, Marechiyo Omaeda,
am going to introduce my family.
MARECHIYO OMAEDA
FATHER . MARENOSHIN
My father, Marenoshin.
All right! All right!
MOTHER . MAREKA
My mother, Mareka.
Hello.
My older sister, Maremi.
OLDER SISTER . MAREMI
Oh my...
My younger brother,
Marejirosaburo.
YOUNGER BROTHER .
MAREJIROSABURO
Hello.
And my unbecoming
younger sister, Mareyo.
YOUNGER SISTER . MAREYO
Please look after my older brother.
She's the only one
who's unseemly.
There's something wrong
with this family.