One hundred ten years ago…
As a result of high turnover
among the captains of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
a new generation was
about to take over.
As part of the changeover,
Kisuke Urahara,
filled the empty post of
Squad 12 captain
at the recommendation of
Yoruichi Shihoin,
who at the time,
was captain of Squad 2.
However, Hiyori Sarugaki,
lieutenant of Squad 12,
had a strained relationship
with Urahara,
due to the dislike of
his history
in the Stealth Force and
his laid-back personality.
W-What the hell is all of this?!
Just where do you
think this is, you?!
This is the captain's room!
The captain's room!
You can't just go and
do your own renovations!
It's okay.
I mean, it's my room.
What?!
Besides, it's not a renovation.
I just did a little rearranging.
How is this "rearranging"?!
There's absolutely nothing
of the old room left!
Oh yes…
I have a favor to
ask of you, Hiyori.
W-What is it?
I want you to come with me
right now to the Maggot's Nest.
Maggot's Nest?!
Okay, we're here.
This is the place.
Huh?
Kisuke's here?
Yes! He said he already had
your permission, Lady Yoruichi.
What was it now?
What should we do?
If you do not recall,
shall I have him leave?
No, that won't be necessary.
Take him wherever
he wants to go.
Did you remember?
Not at all.
Lady Yoruichi!
What now Soi Fon?
Don't be so noisy.
But…
No need to worry.
Knowing Kisuke,
he came here for a reason.
Oh… It opened, it opened.
Shall we go in?
I don't want to!
Now, now, don't be like that.
Come on, let's go.
I said I don't want to!
– Now, now…
– Let go of me!
When you go in, who knows,
you might think,
– "Wow, it's wonderful!"
– I said let go!
I thought we were going
to some creepy place
called the "Maggot's Nest."
We're inside
the Squad 2 Barrack grounds!
You've heard of the Stealth Force,
haven't you, Hiyori?
Stealth Force?
Well of course I have.
It's your old unit, idiot!
Stop changing the subject!
STEALTH FORCE
Stealth Force.
It is an organization whose
origins are separate
from the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads.
As one of the four
great noble clans
who possess incredible
Soul Reaper powers,
the Shihoin Clan serves as
the supreme commander
to this force.
And whenever the head
of the Shihoin Clan
becomes a captain of
a Thirteen Court Guard Squad,
the squad they lead
has a tendency to
become closely associated
with the Stealth Force.
So that means, what?
Yoruichi,
the current supreme commander,
concurrently serves as
captain of Squad 2.
That means the current Stealth Force
becomes much like an organization
under the direct control
of Squad 2.
The Stealth Force is
divided into five units,
and each unit leader is also
a Seat Officer of Squad 2.
I was the leader of Unit Three,
"Confinement Troops."
Then you were a yard hack?
No…I was a prison guard.
My main duties were to imprison
and watch over those who
committed crimes inside the Seireitei.
So that made you
a yard hack, right?
I was a guard.
Same thing!
Your job was to swagger about
in front of the criminals, right?!
The Confinement Troops
had another duty
as Special Confinement officers.
Huh? Special Confinement officer?
Our job was to
investigate, apprehend and
keep under surveillance
Soul Reapers joining
the Court Guard Squads
whose ideas and
actions would
either put other
Soul Reapers at risk,
or posed a threat by
obstructing the squad's duties.
I don't understand what you said!
You have a confusing
way of saying things!
Say it in simple terms.
Simple terms!
In other words, my job was to catch
and lock up dangerous elements
within the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads.
That facility is located here,
in Squad 2's barracks.
The facility is on the northwest
side of these grounds,
beyond the huge
54-meter-wide moat.
The Underground Special
Confinement Station.
Also known as
the Maggot's Nest.
What is this?
The inside is nothing
but a huge cave.
Did you really keep
people locked up in here?
In this underground prison?
It does sound cruel, doesn't it?
But it isn't really
an underground prison.
See?
They are not allowed
to leave this place.
However, their activities within
the facility are not restricted.
Please be careful.
Sometimes someone
will attack all of a sudden.
What on earth did these people do?
Nothing.
As I told you…
These people haven't
done anything wrong.
They are people who
were determined to be
"dangerous elements" according
to the criteria of the Seireitei.
They've committed no crime,
so we cannot try them.
However, left free,
they may be dangerous.
That is why we keep them
confined in here.
What's that about?!
I don't get it!
They haven't done anything,
and yet you…
Hiyori…
Up until now, have there
been any among your peers
who resigned from
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads?
Huh?
There's been a couple, but…
what about them?
The truth is, there is no system
that allows members to "resign."
Those who have no choice
but to leave the squad
for personal reasons are
on Squad Leave.
If it does not seem likely that
they will be able to
return to the squad
for an extended period of time,
it is considered an "Expulsion."
We do not recognize leaving
the squad by one's own choice.
What?
"Resigning" means they are
placed under "special confinement."
Squad members who
are reported to have resigned
are all sent here for confinement.
Why go through all that trouble?
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
is a noble organization.
It must never produce
any unsuitable members
from among those who were once
accepted into the organization.
That is the philosophy of
Central 46 that rules the Seireitei.
That is why "unsuitables" who might
become "dangerous elements"
are dealt with in utmost secrecy
as deserters.
Hiyori…
Something has
been on my mind
ever since I was assigned
here as unit leader.
Yes, the people here
are all dangerous people.
But I was thinking there
are many people here
whose risk could be
turned to a huge good
if we could only
provide them an environment
where they could put
their abilities to use.
Which is it?!
You're keeping them confined because
they're dangerous elements, right?
But now, you're talking about
putting their ability to use.
Hiyori?!
Is that you, Hiyori?!
Big Mouth?!
He's one of my peers
whom I thought had deserted.
He always used to talk big and boast
about things he couldn't even do,
like one day being
in charge of the Seireitei,
so everyone called him
"Big Mouth."
Hiyori!
Help me!
You've got to help me!
We were classmates, right?
I want to go home!
I want to go home, you know!
Shoot! I left my sword
in the barracks.
I'm sorry.
I knew you forgot your sword,
but I kept quiet.
Bringing weapons into the Special
Confinement Station is forbidden.
That's why it is an absolute
requirement that leaders of
the Confinement Troops be able
to subdue everyone unarmed.
How sad.
Have you forgotten my face
after just two or three days?
After I took such
good care of you.
Damn it!
Get them!
Seems you all
have really forgotten me.
How cruel.
Don't move!
Listen! I want you to get me
out of here right now!
If you don't, I'll…
Big Mouth.
You've taken the wrong person
as a hostage.
Don't mess with me, idiot!
His big mouth
just got a lot bigger.
Good grief…
Shall we go, Hiyori?
What sort of environment
are you talking about
that'll make
these guys useful?!
They're really dangerous elements!
If you bring these guys outside,
you'll just increase your problems!
Now, now…
In any case, let's get going.
Take a look.
Beyond here is the only
dangerous element
in this place in
solitary confinement.
You mean someone
even more violent?!
What business could he have
with someone like that?
Is that you, Kisuke Urahara?
What brings you to
a place like this?
I came because I needed to see you.
Kurotsuchi Mayuri.
Won't you leave here with me?
Who…is this dude?
Oh…
You called someone you met
for the first time "dude."
Quite a disrespectful boy,
I must say.
Boy?!
Who are you calling a boy?!
I'm a girl!
You want me to
show you my boobs?!
Freak! You look like
a weird boiled dumpling!
– Please forgive her foul mouth.
– See?!
She is my squad's…
Come on and take
a good look at these!
Lieutenant.
– Lieutenant…
– You see that?!
– You were promoted?
– Hey!
I'm telling you to look at these,
you idiot!
– Congratulations.
– Hello?!
Thanks.
Getting back to the subject,
can I have your answer?
You mean to your hare-brained idea
of leaving here with you?
Yes.
No thanks.
Okay then! Let's go back!
If this dude doesn't want to leave,
we'd just be wasting our time
by staying here, right?
Why not?
I am satisfied with my life here.
I have no need to leave.
That couldn't possibly be true.
Not in this place where
there's nothing to do.
Then let me ask you…
Why do you want to
get me out of here?
Because I need your help.
Let's dispense with
the frivolous lies.
I could see through
that one like an X-ray.
You got me there.
I am making you
overly cautious, aren't I?
I cannot figure you out.
You are an unpleasant fellow.
I believe in your skills.
That is the truth.
I am considering creating
an organization
under the control of Squad 12
unlike anything ever seen
in the Soul Society.
I'm calling it the "Department
of Research and Development."
I want you to assume the seat
of deputy department head.
What?!
You want me to work under you?
That's correct.
It's not a bad offer, right?
You'd be second
in command to me.
In other words…
If I die, you would
have total control.
You certainly are
an unpleasant fellow.
Oh, impressive,
very impressive.
Practicing hard, I see,
Byakuya.
Grandfather!
You have returned to the mansion.
Did you come to rest here today
rather than at the barracks?
Yes.
I'm glad you did.
It's been a long time since
I've been able to talk with you.
It makes me very happy.
Yes.
So, what do you say, Byakuya?
Why don't you call it a day
for practice today.
I brought someone
here to see you.
Here to see me?
You've appeared, cat monster!
"Cat Monster"?!
Is that what I get for coming
to see you, Byakuya-boy?
And to think I came
all this way to visit!
Quiet! When did I ever say
I wanted you to come and visit me?!
As the next head
of the Kuchiki Clan,
I don't need fun and games!
Oh, is that so?
You!
It may be just fun and games,
but I worry about the future of
the Kuchiki Clan if its next head
of the House has his topknot tie
easily taken away by a girl!
Stay right where you are,
Yoruichi Shihoin.
With my Flash Step, I'll…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
I have beaten you!
I see.
Seems you really
want to make me angry.
Fine.
Then you'll find out for yourself!
That my Flash Step
has far surpassed yours!
Oh good grief…
Byakuya would reach
a whole new level
if he could only get rid
of his quick temper.
Now then, maybe
I'll have some tea.
Thank you.
That smile of yours is
as powerful as always.
Oh, hot!
So about the…
I'll say it again,
I won't be your lieutenant.
Don't say it again.
You'll hurt my feelings even more.
There are lots of others who deserve
to become captain-level before me.
Are you saying that
out of obligation?
Well, that's so you.
By the way, have you heard?
About what?
I'm told there's a prodigy,
the first one since you,
among this year's recruits.
I'm no prodigy.
This child…
He graduated from Soul Reaper
Academy in just one year.
One year?!
That's impressive.
Don't you agree?!
I think…
Captain Kuchiki's grandson
Byakuya is about that age.
Oh, that cocky one.
Yes, that one.
I think the kid's about the
same age or slightly younger.
I hear a Seat Officer's position
will be readied for him when he enters the squad.
That right?
Looks like we've got ourselves
someone with quite a future.
That'll make my chances
for a lieutenant position
even more distant.
Don't sound so happy about it.
So, who is it?
Who gets that new recruit?
Well…I believe…
He'll be joining Squad 5.
Nice.
Your skill is even better
than I had heard.
Tell me your name again.
Gin…
Gin Ichimaru.
How was our Third Seat?
Awful. No competition at all.
I see.
Glad to hear it.
After swinging toward the past
and giving a flash glimpse in time,
several more years pass as we move
toward the crux of the incident.
ONE HUNDRED ONE YEARS AGO
I want you to be my lieutenant.
What it means is that if I die,
you will have complete control.
What's this about, out of the blue?
I wanted to imitate Kisuke Urahara.
How'd I do?
It's not even funny.
Please stop it.
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
INTERACTING WITH REGIONAL HEADS
Interacting with Soul Reapers
who are the regional heads
is also an important duty of
the Substitute Soul Reaper.
You bastard!
You're taking my work again!
Oh…umm…you are…
Did you forget, Ichigo?
He was put in charge of
Karakura Town after me.
SOUL REAPER IN CHARGE
OF KARAKURA TOWN
Kurumada…do…de…
Sir Kurumatta.
Now you, too?!
Then we'll call him Kurumaebi!
What do you mean,
"then we'll call him"?!
– This is too much trouble.
– Kuruma…Kuruma…Kuruma…
We'll just leave it at Kuruma!
INTERACTING WITH REGIONAL HEADS