KENDO TEAM
Hey! Guys...
Where'd you get those injuries?!
Well... How should I put this?
We kinda got ambushed...
Ambushed?
That's right...
Who are you?!
We're the Kotei Academy
Kendo Team!
We'll be victorious at
the regional tournament!
That's an ambush?
They told you who they were...
It's an ambush.
That's ridiculous!
Sorry! This is all because
I ran away too slowly.
It's not your fault...
It's because they're ridiculous!
But with us starters like this,
we'll have to pull out of next month's
regional tournament.
No!
We can't pull out because of
something as silly as this!
I, the student body president, will arrange
a friendly match with Kotei Academy!
- Huh?
You were ambushed...
So pulling out of the competition
is what they want! Aren't you mad?!
Get your revenge at this match
and gain some momentum
for the regional tournament!
That's crazy...
We just got ambushed yesterday!
You first-years look like
you're in good health...
Huh? We can't take on Kotei!
Don't be pathetic!
You're men, aren't you?!
You're going to avenge
your upperclassmen
no matter what it takes!
Got it?!
She's crazy...
Sis, I brought Ikkaku and Yumichika,
just as you ordered me to do, but...
Who are they?
We're the first-years of Karakura
First High School's kendo team.
Pleased to meet you!
So what do you want with us?
You suddenly made me
put on this outfit...
You're not all that dissatisfied.
It really does look good
on you, darling!
You look like a man among men!
This is bad, Ikkaku!
Granted, I'm the one
who brought you here,
but my sister's request probably
won't do you any good!
You stay quiet!
Actually, darling...
We're having a friendly match
between our kendo team
and Kotei Academy's kendo team
this weekend.
I want you to prepare them
for the event!
Huh?
These weaklings?
That's right!
I want you to somehow
make them into real men!
U-Umm...
Please make me a real man!
It won't happen!
There's no way that Ikkaku would
participate in youthful club activities!
Right, Ikkaku?!
Fine... I'll do it...
Really?!
I am indebted to this strange woman
for giving me food and shelter.
Thank you, darling!
I'm not getting involved.
Hey! Wait, Yumichika!
What an unmanly guy!
Anyway, take care of it, darling!
We're counting on you!
Yes!
All right!
My training is tough!
- Darling, you're so wonderful!
- He is so into doing this...
Come on, come on, come on!
Pull, pull! Don't be a wimp!
Y-Yes, I'll do my best!
Come on, come on, come on!
Don't take a rest!
Why carts?!
And that sword is real...
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Climb on up already!
Hopping up the stairs from
a squatting position in this day and age?!
Isn't that bad for your back?
61...62...63...
What is this?
This is beyond heavy!
I must endure...
That's right! Real men endure pain!
Beyond that is victory!
I must endure!
Why pickling stones?
They're doing it!
Things are looking good!
How is this good?!
It has nothing to do with kendo!
Huh?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, sis!
But don't you think that
this training is going a little too far?
Don't worry. He won't kill them...
My darling has his own ideas!
He does?!
You haven't given up already,
have you?
It's no good.
My body...
Tsk! How pathetic...
I can still go on!
I thought that you would go down first,
but you've got spirit!
Come on!
Is that all the spirit you've got?
I've got to become stronger for
the upperclassmen that protected me.
Crap!
You're too direct!
Look for your enemy's openings!
You have no openings!
Shut up! We're going to continue
until you find one!
Come on, come on, come on!
Bring it on!
Umm... Incidentally, I must ask...
Why are you working so hard for this?
Well...
Because it's fun.
Ah, I see.
It's fun...
What?!
You're doing this because it's fun?
Because it's been a while
since I've seen that...
The look of desperation that comes
from one's desire to get stronger.
He's really enjoying his youth.
What's wrong with you?!
Sorry...
We're at our limit!
Umm...
They've got worse injuries
than the upperclassmen.
I got a little carried away...
Hey! Is it true that all
the team members are injured?!
Sis!
No way!
What'll we do, darling?!
I didn't think that they'd
break just from this.
- Sorry...
But this is problematic.
Everyone, can you win
the match with those injuries?
No. It's impossible!
What?!
What are we going to do
about our match?!
Sis...
We should just forfeit.
No way!
I, the student body president,
never change my schedule!
I always win matches
I've decided I'll win!
Besides...we requested the match.
we'll look stupid if we forfeit.
But didn't you request the match
so you could get revenge?
Huh?
I didn't say anything.
Don't you agree, darling?!
Oh well...
You just have to win, right?
In that case...
My friends and I could just enter it.
Your friends?!
I've got some skilled companions.
You're so wonderful!
I knew I could count on you, darling!
Ikkaku... Could it be that you wanted
to enter from the beginning?
Did you say something?
I-I-I didn't say anything...
I'm going to ask Yumichika
and the others to help us out.
Do any of you have
the guts to participate?
I-I'll enter!
Please let me enter!
Well said.
We just need three more.
I-Ikkaku!
You only have two friends?!
We're short three people!
What are we going to do?!
Shut up!
Anyway, I'm going to
ask them for help!
So...
What do you want us
to help you with?
I have an idea of what it is...
Then that makes things simpler!
I want you to participate
in the match this weekend.
- We're not participating!
What?!
Of course I'm not!
That's right. There's no way!
I'm begging you to help me!
I know, but...
We're probably the only ones
you can ask, too...
So why can't you participate?!
- 'Cause the protective gear stinks...
What?!
- 'Cause the protective gear stinks!
Huh?!
I'm stumped...
What do you suppose we should do?
The match is tomorrow...
I wonder if we can make
any strong friends by then.
Sorry...
If only I had run away faster.
You would have been all right
if you could run away as fast as I can.
You idiot!
What's the point in running away?!
Just get stronger!
That's all you need to do!
And you, stop laughing foolishly!
Take a good look at
where your bruises are!
Those are all bruises of someone
who's running away!
Men don't care if they get bruised
when they tackle things head on!
But don't worry about
the unfilled spots...
Are you going to make
some friends right now?
You idiot!
KARAKURA HIGH SCHOOL
VS KOTEI ACADEMY KENDO CLUB
FRIENDLY MATCH EVENT HALL
I wonder if we've got all of
our participating members...
So...
Why do I have to participate
in this match?
Sorry, Captain Hitsugaya!
Please accept this!
Don't bribe me with sweets!
You say that, but you're already
wearing the protective gear!
That's because you
made a big fuss
and told me to put it on
without any explanations.
I'm very sorry!
This is a token of my regret!
You bastard...
I'm really glad that
my younger brother in grade school
had protective gear
that fits you perfectly!
Grade schooler?
Madarame... You bastard...
I really want to win this match.
I warned you not to get involved
in the lives of humans!
Sorry...
That's right, Ikkaku!
We're busy with training.
It's a real inconvenience!
You too, Abarai?
Well...
Mr. Urahara kept
pestering me to come.
Abarai! Sado!
We're going to finish
training for today.
I want you to go to the school...
- Huh?
Well...
Something troublesome
has come up.
All the other Soul Reapers
will be there.
Did a Hollow appear?
You'll know when you get there.
When I got here, this was it!
Sorry for taking up your time.
Jeez! Did you give Urahara
a box of sweets to get him to do this?
Bribes are always necessary
for things like this.
So where's Sado?
He's not coming!
He said that he
doesn't accept bribes...
What?!
Those sweets were expensive!
I don't care if they were!
What should we do?
It's almost time.
Say, Matsumoto...
Please!
I won't do it!
I don't want my hair to stink!
Oh well...
In that case...
Huh?
We don't have enough people...
You enter!
No, no!
I've never even held
a bamboo sword!
You just have to run away!
Only three out of five of us
need to win!
The match between
Karakura First High School
and Kotei Academy will now begin!
Because we're having
a friendly match today,
the person who gets the first point
will win the round.
I'm fighting in the semi-finals?!
Don't worry!
I'll win even if you lose!
We'll still win!
But is that really all right with you?
Begin!
Take that!
Splendid!
And you kept saying
that you didn't want to...
Both of you, shut up!
Second round participants,
come forward!
Yes!
Begin!
I can run away really fast!
Just look at this
God-given foot work!
That's pathetic!
What are you, a crab?
Jeez! What is that idiot doing?!
You there, take a stance!
No way! I don't want to get hurt!
Head!
A Hollow...
Begin!
Madarame, don't be late!
Sorry! I've got to
go out for a moment!
Huh?
I told you that if you lose, I'll win!
But you're the one
who wants to win the most!
So go and become a real man!
Huh?
Huh?!
What?!
He transformed?!
Where's he going?!
I'm scared, uho!
I'm going to lie on my side until
my master gets back, nya.
Don't look at me! I'll kill you,
thank you very much!
I'll just stay put...
There's so many men, beshi!
Did everyone's personalities change?!
Semi-final participants, come forward!
Yes!
Indeed, even if I lose,
Ikkaku will avenge us...
But...
Begin!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Growl! Haineko!
Extend!
Hozukimaru!
Even though Aizen is using
the Hogyoku to create Arrancars,
only small fries have been appearing!
Whoops! Now's not the time for this!
Run away, run away!
Run away and lose at a suitable time!
Don't push yourself, Shinji!
Don't be stupid!
We're going give Kotei Academy
some divine retribution!
Even if he loses, Ikkaku will win!
Shut up!
I can't do that! There'd be
no point to it unless I win!
Shinji, you don't have to push yourself!
That's right. Don't push yourself!
Upperclassmen...
I'm going to do this!
I'm going to beat this guy
and become a real man!
You really are annoying!
Wait up, Shinji!
Don't lose before I arrive!
This wouldn't have happened
if your team members were
better at running away!
That's all it took to do you in.
I guess there was
no need to ambush you!
Crap!
This is for the upperclassmen!
Shinji!
We won, we won!
R-Really?!
The match between Karakura
First High School and Kotei Academy...
Karakura First High School
wins three to one!
Wait, wait!
What about my turn?!
Huh?
We've already won!
We won without you
going through any trouble!
I will never forget your words!
Thank you very much!
Okay! That's great!
So when's my turn?!
Karakura First High School
won three to one!
Therefore, you don't have a turn!
What?!
Where's their captain?!
I'll kill him!
There he is!
That's Igarashi, their captain!
Sis?
He's a bad man who
dumped me long ago!
What?!
This is your own grudge?!
This is your own revenge!
Ikkaku?!
What the hell are you doing
to our captain's toupee?!
Come on!
I'll defeat you all!
Darling!
Stop! Stop!
- Because of the unruly actions of
- I'll help you, Ikkaku!
- Karakura First High School's captain,
- Ikkaku!
- this match is...
- What are you doing?!
- Stop it!
- How stupid. I'm leaving...
Cut it out!
I've taken down their captain!
Darling, you're amazing!
You really were the man
I thought you were!
I'm Rin Tsubokura of the Department
of Research and Development.
I'm Hanataro of Squad 4.
You two seem very much alike.
Are you siblings?
- No! We're not that alike!
You're in perfect harmony
with each other!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Then let's begin!
Yes.
I'm scared, uho!
I'm going to lie on my side, nya...
I'll kill him, thank you very much!
I'll just stay put...
This is the result of the special
soul candy that we've prepared.
It's a great success!
We'll definitely make a lot of money!
Thank you,
Substitute Vice-Chairman!
It was no problem at all, Chairman!
What's the matter?
VICE-CHAIRMAN