Orihime has been abducted
by the Arrancars.
In order to save her,
Ichigo, Ishida, Sado, Rukia, and Renji
have marched into Hueco Mundo,
the world of the Hollows.
They crush the Arrancars
standing in their way and
finally make their way to Las Noches,
Aizen's headquarters.
Awaiting Ichigo and his friends
in Las Noches
was a path that split five ways
and disturbing Spiritual Pressures.
We're going into battle now!
Believe...that our blades
cannot be broken!
Believe...that our hearts
will not yield!
Even if we lose our way,
our iron will is one!
Vow...that even if the earth splits,
we will come back to this place alive!
Waiting down the path that Ichigo chose
was Arrancar Ciento Tres, Dordoni.
Ichigo is baffled by
the strange actions and words
of this Arrancar
with a triple-digit number.
But when he decides
to fight him seriously,
Dordoni's moves suddenly change.
My, my…
Don't judge people
by their appearances, niño.
We're known as
the Privaron Espada.
All those who have triple-digit numbers,
including me, were once Espada.
Whirl! Giralda!
Is that all you've got, niño?!
This Spiritual Pressure…
It's Ichigo.
Crap!
I sense a terrible presence
all around.
Wh-What?
What's this Spiritual Pressure?!
S-So it was you!
Don't surprise me!
What are you doing here?!
Ne… Ne…
“Ne”?!
What about “Ne”? Tell me!
Nel!
I'm looking for Nel!
Then why did you come to me?!
I know! You're lost!
You got lost, didn't you?!
Where is Nel?!
I don't know!
You really are lost!
I thought it was strange!
You had no reason in
choosing to come to me!
Nel…
Nel went after Ichigo.
It'll be terrible if we don't hurry!
Shut up!
She's safe if she's with Ichigo!
Don't cry. It's scary!
Th-That's not it.
If we…If we don't find Nel quickly…
If we don't find Nel and stop her…
Nel will…
He's running away!
Why are you running away?!
It's a reflex!
It's because you're
chasing after me!
Your face is… How should I put this?
It's thoroughly terrifying!
Please, stop!
I'm getting to the good part
of the story!
You stop, first!
Anyway, you have to
search for Nel, right?!
Turn back!
Nel!
Ichigo!
Come on! Come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
Use your Bankai, niño!
Otherwise you’ll die!
Saving your spiritual power
against an opponent like me…
That's about as sweet
as chocolate.
Why don't you understand?!
You're being unreasonable, niño.
Use your Bankai…
I want to see you at full power.
Getsuga…
tensho!
Oh?
Ichigo!
Are you all right, Ichigo?!
Oh? I commend you
on your actions just now.
But now you understand, right?
At this rate, you don't
have a chance at winning.
Don't assume that.
I'm not making assumptions.
I'm merely stating the truth!
Getsugatensho!
Not falling for that again!
I'll use it again.
I'll keep using it until
you change your mind.
It's difficult for me too.
Or I should say it's
a little troublesome?
I want to see your Bankai.
But if I don't continue
to hold back…
You'll…die…right?!
This would be all for nothing
if that happened!
Ichigo!
Ichigo, this is bad!
You're really going to die, Ichigo!
Ichigo!
That bebé is worried
about you, too.
Come on, niño, use your Bankai!
Wha—?!
Getsuga--!
I told you not to
underestimate me, niño!
Crap!
Kids who don't listen…
need to be punished.
Cero.
N-Nel?!
She stopped...my Cero?!
Sh-She swallowed it?!
H-Hey, Nel, are you all right?
D-Don't be…mean to…Ichigo.
Nel!
I don't know who you are, bebé.
But you are impressive.
I never expected you to deflect my Cero
while I was in my released form.
But…
Don't you think you're
getting a little too unruly?
Get lost!
If you want to see it that badly…
Then I'll show it to you!
Sorry to keep you waiting,
old man.
This is my Bankai!
I see… I've been
waiting for this, niño.
I-Ichigo…
Sorry, Nel.
You got hurt because I was being
stubborn over something silly.
I came here and decided that in order
to fight on the same level as the Espada,
I shouldn't use my Bankai
against anyone else.
How silly!
You think so?
It's important for those who want
strength to restrain themselves.
I think it's wonderful.
It's not a reason worth upholding
just to let my friends get hurt.
Does that mean that
you're not after strength?
Are you saying that you
want to protect your friends
and that strength is only
a method to achieve that?
You're very kind, niño.
You're like a saint.
But you have a stronger form,
don't you?
I know about
your Hollowfication.
We've received the records
of all the battles
that have happened
in your World of the Living.
You have a technique that makes you
more like a Hollow
and massively increases
your battle power.
Use it!
I see! What impressive
Spiritual Pressure!
But…
I thought I said…
I want to see you at full power!
I'll use…
any means, niño!
You bastard!
What's wrong?
Are you mad, niño?
What are you mad about?
If your goal is to
protect your friends,
then my goal is to defeat you
when you're at full strength.
In order to do that,
I will go after that bebé instead of you.
That's all.
Don't you…
have any shame?!
I do!
I am ashamed…that I cannot
fight you when you're serious!
Any other shameful thing is
nothing compared to that, niño!
All right.
Nel, stand back for a moment.
There's fine.
It's all right…
I won't let the slightest bit of
Spiritual Pressure get past me.
Ichigo…
Oh?
Sorry, but I can only show it
to you for an instant.
That's more than enough.
I see.
That's…good.
Wonderful! What a wonderful
Spiritual Pressure!
I'm deeply moved
by the fact that
I can fight such
a wonderful enemy, niño!
Come on! This time…
Let's trade blows
at full strength, niño!
Wh-What?
I told you…
It was only an instant.
What a shame…
I knew that once
we got the Hogyoku,
the former Espada
would become useless.
I stayed with Lord Aizen
even with knowledge of that fact.
But…
What?!
What are you doing?!
I'm drooling on you.
I can see that!
I'm asking you why
you're drooling on me!
Shut up…
What are you making
a fuss about, Don Panini?
It's Dordoni!
PANINI
What kind of delicious-sounding
name is that?!
She says her saliva has
weak healing properties.
Right, Nel?
Yes! So if Nel does this…
Wh-What are you doing?!
It's saliva!
That's not saliva! It's vomit!
If Nel squeezes Nel’s uvula,
then a lot of saliva comes out!
And I’m telling you it’s vomit!
Anyway, a lady shouldn't talk about
that kind of thing!
It’s saliva…
It’s vomit.
I lose.
It feels good…
My body was full of power and my heart
was filled with the desire to win.
I was confident that I could block
your attack whenever you struck,
and strike back at you.
I didn't let down my guard.
But…
I couldn't see it.
You're strong, niño.
That's not true.
I wanted to become
an Espada again.
The Espada are Lord Aizen's
faithful servants.
But Lord Aizen probably
only thinks of the Espada
as nothing more
than tools to fight.
I know that…but…
Those who have stood at the top
never forget the view from there.
It was incredibly pleasant there.
I thought that if I defeated you
when you were at full strength,
Lord Aizen would acknowledge
my strength once again.
And I could return to the Espada.
That's why I urged you
to transform into a Hollow.
And my feelings…
still have not changed!
You bastard…
Why are you surprised?
The fact that you healed the wounds
of an enemy that you don't know,
means that you were prepared
for a counterattack!
Am I wrong?
Stop!
You haven't recovered
enough to move!
Wounds are made
to one's spirit, niño.
As long as my will to fight recovers,
my physical wounds mean nothing.
That's why I say you're
like chocolate…niño!
There's a stage show
that involves whips
prepared for the Quincy boy
in the next episode.
I guess I'll watch it
over a cup of tea.
Take that, and that,
and that, and that!
I don't approve of
a stage show like this!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
MISSION TO GUARD THE ROYAL
SEAL AS IT'S BEING TRANSFERRED
This time,
we have a joint mission!
Why these members?
1 4
Squad 1 and Squad 4
are excluded.
Squads 3, 5, and 9
are out of the question.
3 ABSENT
ABSENT
9 ABSENT
Do you think that Squads 11 and 12
can work as bodyguards?
11 12
That's impossible.
2 7
It's not a top secret mission,
so Captain Soi Fon won't come,
and Captain Komamura
doesn't want to appear before people.
What about Squad 6?
It seems that he can't come
because he had to take care
of the carp at his house.
He ran away…