So, so...
Who is this guy, this man
with blond straight hair?
Who is Sakata Kintoki?!
Why was the main character's throne
changed from silver to gold?!
Sakata Gintoki's accomplishments
and history
have been stolen by Sakata Kintoki!
In that case, you should stand
up and take this sword.
We're taking back our color.
We're taking down this world of gold!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was washing my head.
Yes, Sakata Kintoki was created
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
Snack Otose
at the request of Shinpachi-sama
and Kagura-sama.
The Perfect Super Golden Alloy,
Sakata Gintoki Unit 02.
Or Kin-san, for short.
A perfect Sakata Gintoki who
had overcome his weaknesses...
Wait? What?
Are you saying that...
What are you saying?
He's a plastic model.
Ah, he's a plastic model.
How am I supposed to
believe that, fool?!
That's too simple!
How about some details?!
How can he be a plastic model?!
You must be lying!
Tell me you're lying!
The newer plastic models come
with detail before assembly.
That's not what I meant!
Why does this even exist?!
Why has it taken over this anime?!
As I explained earlier...
Doll House
I can't believe our leader
ditched us at such a busy time.
No kidding.
We need every hand we can get.
I can't offer any hands,
but I can provide help.
Huh?
I've been working on this
useless toy for a while.
Gengai-sama first built the
robot to serve as an assistant.
But then they decided to
use it as a substitute leader
since you were gone all the time.
Yes...
That was...
Perfect Gintoki Unit 01.
Yes! This is great!
Is that what the leader is used for?
You feel better now, right?
In the beginning, it still
resembled Master Gintoki.
I thought his hair was more wavy.
But then they began
making improvements
to make it more
like the Odd Jobs leader.
No, that's the wrong leader!
He leads a different trio!
This was a better leader.
This was the leader they wanted.
At some point, they began customizing
the robot into their ideal leader.
How's this?
Looks good.
Okay, I'm up next then.
Die, Gintoki!
Give me more screen time!
It was no longer Master Gintoki.
Hey, freaks.
What's so fun about beating
up a helpless man?
And you're supposed to
be Odd Jobs members?
They had created their ideal leader.
A perfect leader that
surpassed the original.
If you're going to do
dirty business, quit now.
Covering silver...
Stand up. Come with me.
Today is the birthday
of the New Odd Jobs!
...with brilliant gold.
Things took off from there.
He led Odd Jobs on a
campaign of good deeds.
Word spread and Odd Jobs quickly became
accepted as heroes by the town.
However, he didn't stop after taking
over as the new face of Odd Jobs.
In order to fulfill his one and only
duty, to replace Master Gintoki,
he made every person in this town forget
the real Odd Jobs leader, you.
He used special hypnotic waves
to manipulate their brains
so they would replace you
with him in their memories.
Sadaharu-sama and I are the
only ones who weren't affected
because his hypnosis didn't
work on machines or animals.
Do you understand now, Master Gintoki?
His goal...
Kintoki's goal...
...is to completely replace
the original Odd Jobs leader.
In other words, to become
the real Odd Jobs leader.
The hell?!
Why did you just sneak in the
episode title Bleach style?!
This is turning into a different anime!
This is how we roll!
Kintoki and Gintoki
That's wrong too.
Anyway, one day is all it
should take for you to
understand what's happened.
One day was all it took for them
to switch from silver to gold.
Why am I letting a plastic
model dictate my life?!
I'm not Kyoshiro!
You people need to take responsibility
for creating the monster!
Unfortunately, Gengai-sama
was also brainwashed.
The creature is out of
the creator's control.
If you intend to take him on,
you'll be going up against
all of your friends.
First, we must help
everyone remember you.
Is that possible?!
While your past accomplishments
have been overwritten,
the only difference is straight
hair instead of wavy,
and nothing you did was changed.
In other words, there
is a disconnect because
perfect Kintoki behaved
like a buffoon in the past.
Wait, what's that supposed to mean?
If we bring out that disconnect,
their memories may return.
We'll need their help to defeat Kintoki.
You must take back your friends.
Tenny's
Help them remember the man
called Sakata Gintoki.
Snack Smile
Oh, I'm very worried.
Do you know where
Tama-san and Sadaharu-kun
may have gone?
We searched the whole town with Gran,
but we couldn't find them.
Oh, no...
What if Sadaharu and
Tama don't come back?
I'll... I'll...
Don't worry.
You couldn't kill them if you tried.
Kin-chan...
I'll find them. Promise.
So don't look so sad.
We came here to cheer you up.
What's that, Kin-san?
I thought you came here to see me.
Oh, sorry about that.
Hey, can you bring
every table a bottle?
Guys, I'm buying!
Drink as much as you want.
In return, let us know if you see them!
Kin-san does it again!
You can count on us!
We'd do anything for you!
It looks like Kin-san has
everything under control.
Yep.
Uh, please wait.
We don't allow animals inside.
As far as I'm concerned,
humans are all animals.
Besides, he's a member
of Odd Jobs Sepia.
Isn't that right, Master Gintoki?
What are you people doing?!
Sadaharu! And Tama!
You're okay?!
But why are you dressed like that?!
We are not Tama and Sadaharu.
We are Tamagura and Sadahachi
of Odd Jobs Sepia.
What's the idea, Tama-san?!
What are you talking about?!
Hey! Are you the one who made
Tama and Sadaharu sepia?!
Excuse me, Otae-san.
I heard you had work for Odd Jobs.
Huh? You mean the request to
repair the karaoke machine?
But Kin-san's group is on it.
You should try us instead
of those slackers.
I promise that we'll be more useful.
Hey! First you copy us, and
now you're stealing our work?!
Oh, it's over here!
Ah! H-Hold on!
Understood?
We must steal their glory
and draw attention
to help them remember you.
Yeah, I know. I got this, Matagura.
It's Tamagura.
Okay, this is it?
This is a new model with all
the parts to TRA-BRYU's "Road"?
Yes, that and 300,000 other songs.
Okay, I got it.
There isn't enough room here
so I'll move it over there. Upsie...
Oh, sorry!
The 300,000 parts to "Road" are
so heavy that I lost my grip!
Master Gintoki!
Calm down! It's not the
time to unleash your rage!
"Road," Part One!
"Road," Part Two!
"Road," Part Three!
Boo!
Why are you talking like it's a haunted house?!
Cut it out!
Why do you keep doing this?!
Shit, I lost control!
You've completely destroyed
the karaoke machine!
It's fine. He was simply preparing
this machine for me to dive inside.
Right, she can communicate with
broken machines and repair them.
Fresh Oil
Want a drink?
So what's wrong? You look blue.
You still can't forget
about Mr. Steamer?
There we go! Machines on
their afternoon break!
I told you to give up on him.
He's not going to leave his wife.
Plus, he's been cooking it up every
night with Telly the receptionist.
He's always ready to move
on to his next target.
If you let that man play you,
it won't be long before
you're fizzled out.
Oh, there's a mixer with Dyson
from Foreign Capital tonight.
Dyson
Go, Tama!
Show them the true power of Odd Jobs!
Wait.
Mr. Steamer wants to talk.
H-He can also communicate?!
Mr. Steamer was turned
off a long time ago.
Ever since he returned
from a business trip
Healsio
to find his wife cooking
it up with Healsio.
After that...
He turned to you and
Telly out of loneliness.
But you should know well that
he can no longer cook anyone.
You mean that Karaoky and
Mr. Steamer had a platonic relationship?
When you went to the karaoke bar,
he felt himself get a little warm,
even though he wasn't turned on.
He's lying! Don't be fooled!
Mr. Steamer would never say that!
Could you play that song for him again?
Don't, Karaoky!
And cry on your own...
Then you'll shine bright,
Ultra Soul!
Hey!
Way to go, Kin-san!
You always come through!
I'm up next!
Let me sing!
As you can see, after
I gave him a scolding,
he's refusing to come down.
I'm not sure what to do,
so I went to you.
Okay, okay. I got this one.
Rise of the Planet of the Apes, right?
We can handle this.
Hey!
Cut it out already!
Can you stop butting in?!
Damn! This time, I'm
going to steal the show!
Sadahachi's on the move!
Translation: So what's wrong? You look blue.
Can he communicate with other animals?!
Nope, it didn't work!
Dogs and monkeys just don't get along!
That's enough.
I don't know what you were
saying, but I can say this.
I understand you.
Wow, Kin-chan! You were instantly
able to understand him!
Hold on!
That's not Kin-san!
That's not the Odd Jobs leader!
Look closely! That's a different leader!
Everybody together now...
Then you'll shine bright,
Ultra Soul!
Hey!
Why do you have to end everything
with a performance of Ultra Soul?!
And Tama!
Why are you guys over there?!
Stop! Come down!
Stay away! I'm going to jump!
Apparently, her favorite customer
was stolen by a harlot.
I'll never understand romantic
affairs. It's beyond me.
I'm feeling blue.
I'd like to be alone,
so can you go away?
There's someone who's completely blue!
Green Tea
Calm down.
Care to join me for a
drink before you die?
Kin-san's also up there!
Master Gintoki, this is
a direct showdown!
You can't lose!
Stay back! Leave me alone!
If you wanted to be left alone, you
wouldn't try to die in public.
She just wanted to see the
gloomy sky one last time.
Gloomy as I feel inside.
The other guy's not even
trying to persuade her!
He might jump first!
Let it out.
It's easier to talk to
strangers sometimes.
You can't help me...
He's not talking to you!
Then I'll hear you out!
Start talking!
You're not part of this either!
Um, this may sound
strange coming from me,
but I believe you should let
everything out before you die.
You too?!
Yeah, bro! Tell us what's
wrong! Cheer up!
Don't give up!
Wait!
Hey, who's helping who here?!
Shut up! Don't be nice to me!
I'm gonna cry!
I'm glad I met some total strangers who
actually cared about a loser like me.
Wait, bro!
No.
Jumpers are usually so worked
up about their own problems
that they don't pay
attention to other people.
But if they see someone more
unfortunate than themselves,
they will hesitate.
He's faking it!
Silver can decipher
human emotion in a way
that the golden machine cannot!
Oh, sorry!
My heart's so heavy that
I slipped and fell!
Stop!
What are you doing to Kin-san?!
I-It's you?!
I just wanted Kin-san to
give me some attention!
Sa—
Gintoki, you're finished now—
Master Gintoki!
That was crazy!
It wasn't crazy.
I knew you'd be there for me.
Odd Jobs Kin-chan
Snack Otose
Sugar Content
What exactly happened?
When I saw him falling,
my body moved by itself.
Master Gintoki! Sa-chan-sama!
Are you hurt?
Yeah, her head's a little funny,
but it always has been.
We're fine.
Shinpachi-sama, Kagura-sama.
Thank you very much.
You've finally remembered Master Gintoki.
Huh?
What do you mean?
It's okay, Tama.
That's how they are.
It doesn't matter who I am.
They'll move without thinking
to save someone in trouble.
They can't stand around when
something bad is going down.
They move without considering
the consequences.
Those are the kind of
fools who join Odd Jobs.
They haven't forgotten that.
That's all I needed to know.
As long as they've got that,
it doesn't matter who the leader is.
Master Gintoki!
You saved my life, kids.
Well, yeah...
I guess.
Thanks for everything.
Take care, Odd Jobs.
Why did he look so sad?
Why do we feel so unhappy?
It's like we've forgotten
something important.
Like we threw away an ice cream carton
lid without licking it first.
Kagura-chan...
Wouldn't that just be garbage?
That's right, and then he used
the karaoke machine to hit
Kin-san in the head.
Oh, so he was acting the
same when you saw him.
He's such a strange person.
Yes.
Oddly enough, this seems so familiar.
Didn't we used to laugh like this before?
Don't we laugh all the time?
I'm having fun now, too.
But something seems different.
It feels like something's missing.
What's that?
I don't know...
But if I had to describe this feeling,
it's like I've dropped a glove
in the middle of the road.
Hinoya Tea
Fool.
What are you doing?
You should take better
care of yourself.
I wasn't planning on dying!
Besides, Tsu-ki, this
wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't put moves on Kin-san!
When have I ever put moves on him?!
That would be you!
Honestly, what would have
happened if that guy wasn't there?
In any case, he was crazy.
That was beyond reckless.
Tsu-ki, something's wrong with me.
Yes, I know.
No, that's not what I meant.
I wanted to thank him,
but my chest started to
hurt and I couldn't speak.
This feeling couldn't be...
I'm not cheating on Kin-san, right?
I'm okay, right?
No, you're not okay.
Seriously, that's not what I meant.
I was wondering why I would
be attracted to this loser.
Yes, you're guilty.
Can you drop it already, bitch!
That means you're attracted
to men who fail.
You're in for a hard life.
You're in no position to talk!
But I understand what you're saying.
Kin-san is a wonderful person,
but he used to be more...
What? You've made me curious.
Then you have to promise
to keep this a secret.
He used to be more complex,
with a peculiar charisma.
What's that mean, Hinowa?
Kind of like...
Jump
A copy of Jump on Thursday that
everybody's already flipped through.
Did that really happen?
No, nothing happened.
I haven't gotten any screen time.
At least nothing happened!
This seems so familiar.
Didn't we used to laugh like this before?
No, we barely ever talk.
But it feels like something's missing.
I feel like there was
someone always with us.
Are you talking about Elizabeth?
No, when I was out of work,
I killed time by partying
with that really fun guy.
Huh? Who are you talking about?
You know?
We went to an island together.
Can't remember his name...
Oh, him!
I can picture his face, but
I can't put a name to it!
It's, uh...
Are you talking about me?
Yes! Big Dadd—
Big Daddy
You're not thinking of doing something
foolish, are you, Master Gintoki?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
You think I'm going to ditch
all of this and leave?
Want me to be honest?
The hard feelings are gone.
He did a pretty good job
after stealing my place.
He cares about his friends
and does good work.
He kept everyone safe while I was gone.
His past is a lie, but his present is real.
If that's the ideal leader you wanted,
is it worth taking all of that away
for me to return?
I have to wonder.
Master Gintoki...
That's why I've made up my mind.
I want you to promise me something.
No matter what happens to me,
even if I fall,
you won't lay a hand on them.
In return, I'll also make a promise.
Even if my friends want my head,
even if I have no home,
I will take them back.
The truth may be harsh,
but that's the world we've built.
Tama, don't insult me.
You stayed on my side through it all.
You think I'm going to
run away and let you
live in this strange world alone?
I'm not going to ditch anyone.
Master Gintoki...
Then let's call it a day.
I need a pillow to charge, so
I'll be heading back to the bar.
You'll have to find a place
to sleep by yourself.
You're ditching me?!
Hey! Kintoki knows that
you're on my side!
Be careful!
Master Gintoki, I've realized that
you will always be yourself.
Did you think I would be angry
if you wanted to run away?
I wouldn't be angry.
Not if you took me with you.
Hey, where did you learn that act?
From the K-drama
Catherine-sama is watching.
Okay, I'll add it to my data
for when I pick up girls.
I must...
I must do something,
or Master Gintoki and
Shinpachi-sama's crew will
end up fighting each other.
However, he hasn't given up yet.
Even though he's alone,
he shows concern for us.
I must find a way to restore
everyone's memory.
There must be a way.
Having trouble?
Want me to lend you a hand?
Leave it to Odd Jobs Kin-san
and he'll save the day.
To be continued...
Kin-san's Kintama
Next time on Kintama:
Kin-san's Kintama.