Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade in a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
My love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
My body feels heavy…
My legs…
I can’t raise my arm either…
Damn, I guess…
the end is nearing for my time
as a Quincy…
That’s right!
If I’m the first one here,
I could rescue Rukia myself.
I bet Ichigo wants to
save her himself.
If I did that, he’d be ticked off.
I bear no ill feelings.
However, for the sake of the peace,
I’ve no choice but to eliminate you.
Cry, Suzumushi.
Forgive me, Ryoka.
This is the end of
a senseless battle.
Sleep. Your battle will soon be over.
To advance from “Shikai” to “Bankai”
typically requires well over
ten years of training,
even for those with talent.
However, you must achieve
the “Bankai” in three days.
Wh-What is that strange doll?
Tenshintai.
It is one of the Stealth Squad’s
most important specialized spirit tools.
It forcibly draws out the zanpaku-to’s
true form and materializes it.
Uh? I don’t quite get it.
How’s that thing necessary
for the Bankai training?
What is necessary for the Shikai
is a dialogue
and harmony with the zanpaku-to.
In other words,
instead of us entering
the world of the zanpaku-to,
what is necessary for the “Bankai”
is the “materialization”
and “submission” of the zanpaku-to.
“Materialization” refers to
summoning the zanpaku-to into our world.
Normally, several years of training
are required for this,
but you, even though
it ended in a draw,
fought on equal footing
with Kenpachi Zaraki.
So in actuality, you may have
already reached the "materialization"
or a comparable level as I see it.
Do you want to fight?
It seems you recall an instance…
If you stab this with Zangetsu,
it can forcibly bring it into
the “materialized” state.
In other words, we can bring
the zanpaku-to into this world.
However…
Using this method, the “materialization”
is limited to three days!
During that period, you must defeat
the “materialized” Zangetsu
and force him into submission.
If you cannot…
I won’t ask about that.
If this is the only way…
Then I’ve got to do it!
Seems you have recovered
quite a bit, Ichigo.
Dude!
You heard our conversation?
Of course.
I’ll leave the fighting methods to you.
Can you start right away?
Yeah…
Wh-What the heck?!
Among these, only one…
is the true me.
That is the only one
that can defeat me.
If you wish to force me
into submission,
find it before I kill you!
And…
Slay me if you can!
FOUR
Greetings, everyone.
It is I, Squad Four, Third Seat,
Yasochika Iemura.
What? You don’t know me?!
You may have seen me here,
or over there.
Since it seems some of you
are not familiar with me,
as an introduction,
I wish to disclose my medical journal
that chronicles our Squad Four’s
strenuous activities.
– Hey, hurry it up!
– Reporting!
Lately, due to the recent
Ryoka disturbance,
our Squad Four station
is in daily chaos!
Especially, with the large number of
those louts from Squad 11 hospitalized.
No! I mean, those gentlemen…
it has kept us very busy.
On top of that, yesterday evening,
both the Squad 13 and 8 captains
requested to have a Ryoka admitted
so we were forced to implement
the three-shift emergency protocol.
Things are busy enough as is,
and on top of this, being asked
to admit the Ryoka is just…
Really, enough is enough!
Why these defeated Ryoka
should be purposely hospitalized
and treated in the first place
is completely beyond me!
I mean, the Squad 13’s
Captain Ukitake is one thing,
but Captain Kyoraku of Squad Eight
is always goofing off
and chasing after girls’ behinds
and with that gaudy attire,
always snoozing when
something comes up.
How can someone like that
become a captain, while I…!
What is it?
Just now, we received a request
from Captain Tosen of Squad Nine
to admit one Ryoka.
I see.
And…
You were thinking out loud.
However, I have the deepest respect
for Captain Kyoraku.
In light of these points!
He who was held by the Ryoka…!
was physically and mentally subjugated
by those Ryoka
and had no choice but to obey.
That is my opinion!
Therefore! I sincerely request that
Captain Unohana of Squad Four
judge the matter kindly!
This concludes the arrest report
from Captain Ukitake of Squad 13!
I understand.
However, the damage caused
by these Ryoka,
whom you have aided,
is substantial.
In light of your rank
and responsibilities,
I cannot condone your actions.
You do understand?
Fourteenth Advanced Relief
Group Leader
and Squad Four,
Seventh Seat, Hanataro Yamada.
What’s the matter, Hanataro?
I wonder if what I did was a mistake.
Did I create more trouble
for Rukia instead?
Who knows…
However, seeing how you act
so true to your feelings,
I’m a bit envious of you.
Lieutenant!
The rest is up to Captain Unohana…
Let’s go, Zabimaru!
I-I drew my sword against
Miss Hinamori.
How could I… Despicable…
I’m…despicable…!
Burst! Tobiume!
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
Wh-Who’s there?!
My…
This is just awful.
Can’t bear to look.
Captain…Ichimaru…!
You look haggard, poor thing.
Want me to help you?
Huh, Izuru?
Stand up, Ichigo!
Three days! Ichigo,
you don’t have time to dawdle!
I’ll say it once more.
Stand up, Ichigo!
Stop stalling!
Are you going to waste time?!
Never mind!
If he cannot stand on his own…
then I’ll drag him to his feet!
ELEVEN
My, was I ever surprised!
To think that Lieutenant Kusajishi
would pick me up at that place!
I, Makizo Aramaki,
am moved beyond words!
Well…I didn’t really care about you.
Let…me…go!
Please let me go!
Oh, no, I can’t!
Why you--!
Sorry about that.
Maybe I should apologize
when she wakes up.
Maki-Maki?
What’s that you’re carrying?
That Spiritual Pressure…
A Ryoka?
No. Well…you see, this, well…
That’s a Ryoka, right?
This is, well, umm…
there were circumstances…
Circumstances? Oh, like what?
Well…that is…
This girl, you see…um…
she suddenly spurted out of this area…
Spurted out?
Yes, yes. Like…bubbling.
Bubbling?
So I thought it was very unusual,
and I wanted to show you.
Really?!
Then let’s take her back with us!
Eh? Well…
I want to see her
doing the bubbling thing!
Well, that’s…
I wonder if Ichi does
the bubbling too?
Hey, Ara… Ara… umm…
Ara…what’s your name again?
Ah! Pardon me!
It’s Maki-Maki! Maki-Maki is fine!
It’s been ten years since you
so kindly took me into your care!
Maki-Maki…
Hah! That’s a weird name!
Wha--?! But that’s the nickname
you gave me!
So, what’s happening, Orihime?
She’s beautiful…
Is Ichigo still alive?
I want him to be alive.
No, I’m sure he’s alive!
Orihime…
He’s alive.
I can tell.
He’s alive and he’s trying
to get stronger still. Interesting!
I’ll lend you a hand, woman.
If I stick with you,
I get the feeling
I’ll see Ichigo again!
– Yep!
– Yes!
Aye, aye, sir!
FOUR
Where is this?
Am I alive?
How?
Are you awake?
Wh-What are you,
who are you?!
Are you a burglar, you jerk?!
Idiot! Why would anyone try to steal
from an injured man in prison?
It’s me, me!
G-Ganju?! You’re alive! Good!
You didn’t seem too strong
so I thought maybe…
That line…
I’ll throw it right back at you.
Still… Why did they treat our injuries?
We’re intruders and also their enemy.
There shouldn’t be any reason
for the Soul Society to treat us.
The situation has changed.
Sado.
I overheard the guard talking
and found out.
Apparently, a Captain was assassinated
within the Seireitei.
The culprit is unknown.
What?
So we’re the prime suspects
in the case.
We’ve been kept alive
for their investigation.
That’s what it means.
If only my Spiritual Pressure
wasn’t sealed with these things.
We could bust right out of here
with my Seppa right away.
I see…
These seal the Spiritual Pressure.
Too strong of a flame,
and you will burn yourself.
Sanreishuto…
you must never remove this glove.
If you remove the glove,
for a moment you will gain
enormous powers, however…
you will surely lose all
your Quincy powers as well.
No. Even without this,
my Spiritual Pressure’s already…
Anyway!
Although we did survive,
we’re stuck in this prison with
our Spiritual Pressure sealed,
and it really sucks!
However, one thing’s for sure.
As long as the enemy has
no intention of killing us,
the rest of the gang is sure
to be alive as well!
Seeing that we are
captured like this,
we can assume that Orihime,
who’s not suited for combat,
is probably detained somewhere
as well.
That leaves just Yoruichi
and Ichigo.
I will wait for Ichigo.
Ichigo will come here
without fail.
What we can do until then
is heal our wounds
and prepare for the next battle.
Let’s wait for Ichigo!
Eighteenth sword…
That’s it!
The real one…
has to be this!
Too weak!
As I’ve said. All these swords
represent a piece of your heart.
The purpose of this trial is
to find the one piece among these
that was forged just
for combat alone.
That one there was your “heart’s frailty”
for trying to depend on me.
Frailty…my being prone
to depending …heart
As long as you cannot
even discern that,
don’t dare mention the word “Bankai!”
So these are all my weaknesses…
Damn it!
Well! Next one, Ichigo!
You don't have time
to be kneeling!
Yeah…
That’s right!
Happy people
Come on, come on, come on
Here we go!
Everybody stand up! Everybody fight!
Within your heart, you may feel uneasy
But keep your head right up!
To the sky!
No matter when (Oh yeah!)
No matter where (Oh yeah!)
Just call me anytime! (Oh yeah!)
I’ll be here for you
Happy people in the house!!!
With a tough smile
Let’s live!
Wow
Happy people in the house
All right
Happy people
The food was bad
in the Squad Six jail.
Squad Three's jail didn't
get any sunlight.
Squad Five's jail had cockroaches!
There's definitely room
for improvement.
You guys don't seem to get
why you were put in jail!
– Why don't you try it, Shiro-chan?
– I will not!