One hundred ten years in
the past, and nine years after
Kisuke Urahara assumed the post
of captain of Squad 12.
In the Rukon district,
the mysterious deaths of residents
who vanished leaving
only their clothes behind
caused quite a stir
among the Soul Society.
Under normal circumstances,
when a person dies and becomes reishi,
their clothing would
also disappear.
This fact made
the whole incident unnatural.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
took this as an abnormal situation
and dispatched Squad 9,
led by Kensei Muguruma
to investigate the incident.
They headed to the plains
that stretched through
the Rukon district.
Blast away!
Tachikaze!
Kensei!
Mashiro… Where the hell did
you go during the battle?
In those bushes!
I found this on the ground!
See? A shihakusho!
Ten…shihakusho?!
It matches the number
in the advance party!
Judging from the number of
shihakusho left behind,
Kensei determined they belonged
to the advance party
sent ahead to investigate.
He had squad members report
back to Central 46
about the first Soul Reaper casualties
connected with this incident.
At the same time, he asked to have
laboratory personnel dispatched
because of the possibility
of an unknown pathogen.
In response,
Urahara sent Hiyori to Kensei.
Then, that same night…
What happened?!
What is this?
You…
Emergency assembly!
All squad captains,
assemble immediately
at Squad 1 barracks!
There is an emergency
with Squad 9!
The Spiritual Pressure readings for
Squad 9 Captain Kensei Muguruma
and Lieutenant Mashiro Kuna
have vanished!
As a result,
an emergency meeting of
squad captains will be convened!
Where's Hiyori?!
Sh-She left a while ago!
– Captain!
– Repeat!
Emergency assembly!
All squad captains,
assemble at Squad 1 barracks!
I should have gone.
Sorry about this.
Hiyori, you're
the only one I can
confidently entrust
a task like this to.
I'm counting on you, Hiyori.
I never thought
this would happen.
I get the feeling I fell
for stupid Kisuke's trick.
I mean, why do I have
to help with the work
of the Department of Research and
Developement in the first place?!
That's something Kisuke and that
baldy Mayuri should do themselves!
But they're making
the entire squad
study how to develop
new technology.
What is that?
We have an emergency!
According to reports
from Squad 9's camp that's now
standing by at the scene,
the Spiritual Pressures of both
Squad 9 Captain Kensei Muguruma
and Lieutenant Mashiro Kuna,
who were out in the field,
have vanished.
The cause is unknown!
We must consider the possibility
that this is a worst-case scenario!
What, until yesterday,
was simply an incident
that occurred in the Rukon district
has now become something
that we must stake the pride of
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads
to resolve!
Therefore,
from this moment,
I will select five people
of captain class
and dispatch them to the scene!
You're late, Kisuke Urahara.
Let me…go there, please!
No.
My second-in-command is
headed there now!
– I must…
– Kisuke!
You're making a scene.
Pull yourself together!
Didn't you make
the choice to send her?!
Can't you see that your panic
is an insult to her?!
Now, don't just stand there.
Line up over here.
I will now continue.
Captain of Squad 3,
Rojuro Ohtoribashi.
Captain of Squad 5,
Shinji Hirako.
Captain of Squad 7,
Love Aikawa.
The three I just named
will head to the site.
Captain of Squad 2,
Yoruichi Shihoin,
will stand by for further orders.
Captain of Squad 6,
Ginrei Kuchiki,
captain of Squad 8,
Shunsui Kyoraku,
and captain of Squad 13,
Jushiro Ukitake.
The three of you
will guard the Seireitei.
Captain of Squad 4,
Retsu Unohana.
You will stand by in
the Medical Treatment Room
to await possible casualties
that come in.
Just a minute, Head Captain.
If your concern is
treating casualties,
shouldn't I head toward the scene?
As long as the situation
remains unclear,
we cannot risk dispatching the head
of the medical treatment unit.
I will send someone else
to the scene.
Enter.
Tessai Tsukabishi.
It's been a long time since
he came out into the open…
This has sure become
a major issue, hasn't it?
You've heard, I assume.
I want the two of you
to head to the scene.
Will do.
Understood.
Hey, Old Man Yama.
Sorry about that.
But you know I was thinking,
without knowing the situation
on the front,
isn't sending both
the Kido Commander
and his lieutenant
a bad idea?
Then what would you do?
I would send my lieutenant
in place of the Kido Commander.
You're going to summon her now?
That's right.
Hey!
Lisa!
What is it?
You see?
Didn't I tell you that you must not
peek into a Captain's Meeting?
I couldn't help it.
It's human nature to want to
see something you keep hidden!
And the details?
I heard.
Can I ask you to do it?
Of course!
Then I'll be counting on you.
Deciding things on
your own like that…
We don't get to see an incident
this big very often.
I'm like a parent who wants
his subordinate to gain experience.
Can't you understand that?
She'll be fine.
My Lisa might not look it,
but she's pretty strong.
That's why,
will you let her do it?
Kido Commander?
It's okay with me.
Then I will take you up on
your offer and sit this one out.
All right, then.
Rojuro Ohtoribashi.
Shinji Hirako.
Love Aikawa.
Hachigen Ushoda.
Lisa Yadomaru.
I am assigning you five as
the investigation unit in charge
of this vanishing soul case!
Dismissed!
She'll be all right.
Hiyori is strong.
Though not as strong
as my Lisa.
Don't look so worried.
It's a captain's job to
have faith and wait.
Damn it.
Shinji!
You idiot.
Why didn't you draw your sword?
Idiot.
How am I supposed to
draw my sword?
Kensei?!
Captain, I will be leaving now.
Oh, okay.
Shinji!
Are you all right, Hiyori?!
K-Kensei!
What's going on with that?
Is that really Kensei?
That mask… That Spiritual Pressure…
It is almost like he's a Hollow!
I'm not sure, either.
Maybe it's Kensei, maybe it's not.
Anyway, what's certain is we'll die
if we don't draw our swords.
What the—?
Love!
I could really feel that one.
Just what I'd expect
of you, Kensei.
No!
Don't you see?!
You're going against Kensei!
This is…
Quiet, Hiyori.
We have to stop him.
If he's Kensei,
then all the more reason.
He's right, Hiyori.
Kensei is important to us,
that's why we have to stop him.
Don't worry.
There is a mountain of ways we
can stop him without killing him.
We'll cut the tendons
in his arms and legs.
You take the right half.
All right!
You're mine now!
Behind you, Rose!
Rose!
Is that you, Mashiro?!
Shinji… Let go of me.
You idiot!
If you talk unnecessarily,
you'll bite your tongue!
Gochu Tekkan.
You guys really run fast.
Hachi!
I'm glad I made it.
Bakudo Number 63:
Sajosabaku.
Shinji!
What in the world is
going on here?!
Why are Kensei and Mashiro…
How could this be?
A sixties-level Bakudo was repelled
with just arm strength.
It's not possible!
That's quite an odd item
you've created.
Creating a coat that completely
shuts out Spiritual Pressure
is no ordinary accomplishment.
Drats… You saw me.
You're going to rescue her,
aren't you?
Your lieutenant.
I had a hunch this was
going to happen from the time
I saw how you were at
the captain's meeting.
Gotta hand it to you.
We both spent our time together
at Lady Yoruichi's mansion.
Did you think I wouldn't catch on
to something like this?
Won't you let me pass?
Don't be unreasonable.
I'm not letting you go alone.
Tonight, I, like you,
felt a fear beyond words!
Come on, let us
rush there together…
to where they are!
Urahara, I can't conceal
my Spiritual Pressure like this!
Then let's share the coat.
What an ingenious idea!
If you don't mind,
then be my guest.
Now let us head out!
– And join them!
The Substitute Soul
Reaper Work Journal!
There are people in the World of
the Living who cooperate with us.
Found it?
No, I lost it.
Where could that Hollow
have gone?
If you're having trouble,
would you like to use
my new Hollow detector?
Thanks for the help!
But, you can't use it for free.
I know.
However, if you rely
too much on them…
Take care of those boxes next!
You'll pay the price later.