Aizen has stolen the Hogyoku,
a material that can remove the barrier
between Soul Reaper and Hollow.
He has gone to Hueco Mundo,
and is raising a powerful army
of Arrancars.
Ichigo and his friends manage to
fight off the first wave of Arrancars,
but they end up taking
a lot of damage.
Aizen's true goal is to kill the Soul King,
Soul Society's king.
Because of that,
Karakura Town and the area around it
is in danger of disappearing.
The Arrancars plan to come to
the World of the Living in the winter.
Ichigo, Sado, Ishida, Rukia and
Orihime all undergo harsh training
during the time that remains
until their showdown.
Furthermore,
Hitsugaya's advance troops,
who have remained in
the World of the Living,
continue to clash
with powerful Hollows
who begin to appear in
the World of the Living.
It's as I expected.
It's here.
What are you doing?
URAHARA'S SHOP
Well, everyone.
Take care while we're away.
Be sure to eat three meals a day.
Don't forget to brush your teeth
after each meal. Okay?
Why are you taking Sado with you?
You're just stocking up, right?
It's to help him unwind.
Sado will burn out if he continues
to focus solely on training.
He needs to get some fresh air
once in a while.
Right, Sado?
I want to keep training,
but I appreciate your consideration.
Hurry and bring him back,
Mr. Urahara.
There are still a lot of things
we have to do.
Abarai, you're as short-tempered
as usual, aren't you?
It's all right.
We're off then.
Later...
I'll be off.
Okay.
Leave the shop to us!
Have a nice trip.
Urahara's really good at this,
isn't he?
Good at what, Lirin?
He says that he wants
Chad to unwind,
but he plans on
making him carry things.
Is that so?
Definitely.
I see.
Well, if Sado is with them,
they'll be able to bring back a lot more
at once than they're usually able to.
Chad...
Anyway, how much do they
plan on buying?
They don't even sell that
much stuff in this store.
Jinta...
Did you say something, Jinta?
I thought so.
Be careful of what you say.
This is not a place
you should be entering
without Lord Aizen's
permission, Patras.
I don't like that.
You always say the same thing.
What's that?
Lord Aizen...
The same goes for the other Espada...
I just don't understand.
It's unpleasant.
He's a Soul Reaper.
Why do we Hollows have to
take orders from a Soul Reaper?
We eat souls and
crush Soul Reapers.
Why do we have to
abandon that way of life?
Why must we have
our freedom taken away?!
All for...
someone like him?!
You should know.
Aizen continuously used
us Hollows in his experiments.
I know.
So what of it?
Ever since he appeared,
this place has changed.
I have no intention of following
a Soul Reaper.
And?
Ulquiorra...
Why don't we use the Hogyoku
and control the world?
Don't bother.
You can't even become an Espada.
What can you do?
I can't get your support, huh?
I guess I have no choice then.
I already have two supporters.
Patras...
You bastard.
How unfortunate.
The Espada sure have fallen.
I didn't really hate you, though.
That was easy.
Yeah.
That was pathetic.
We're going to make Aizen regret
that he strengthened us
with the Hogyoku.
And...
I'm going to become king!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Umm...
Move out of the way.
Oh. Sorry.
I just don't know what to do
when I suddenly have free time.
Umm, move out of the way.
O-Okay.
You idiot. You've got to train
for your final battle, right?
Then go do that.
I know that without
you telling me.
Umm...
Move out of the way.
O-Okay.
You're really useless when
you're not fighting.
What did you say?!
Want to fight?
Ah... The weather
sure is nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
It sure is boring
without Ichigo...
It's fun to tease him.
You were teasing him with
your stream of curses?
Of course. He always reacts
to them seriously, so it's fun.
Oh?
I always thought that
you were having a lovers' quarrel.
No, no.
Honestly.
He should show up
once in a while.
You're really worried about him,
aren't you?
I agree with Kurodo's idea.
It's not like that!
What?!
What is this?
What incredible Spiritual Pressure!
We have a confirmed
Arrancar reading in Karakura Town.
I repeat.
We have a confirmed Arrancar
reading in Karakura Town.
We have confirmed that
the Arrancar reading is
at coordinates 3800.
We know. I request a Gentei Kaijo.
Don't worry!
We have already simplified
the procedures to receive permission.
You should get
permission immediately.
Understood.
It sure has gotten convenient!
Matsumoto! Abarai!
Madarame! Ayasegawa!
Can you hear me?!
Yes! I also have confirmation.
It looks like things will be fun again.
It seems a little troublesome, though.
This is Abarai! I'm the furthest away.
Go on ahead of me.
The Soul Reapers have quickly
sniffed us out and are coming this way.
What a letdown.
They all seem weak.
What should we do, Patras?
I want you to handle
the Soul Reapers.
They don't seem very powerful...
But I don't want them
to interfere with our investigation.
Is it true that there's
someone in this town
that knows how to use the Hogyoku?
That's why we've come here.
We've only obtained it.
But if we don't know how to use it,
then it's just a ball.
Sooner or later someone
from Las Noches will come for us.
That's the real battle.
Act swiftly.
Let's meet up afterwards.
Captain!
Look out. They're close!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Yeah. They're coming!
How cocky.
Oh well.
Stab! Erisuto!
The difference in our power
is self-evident.
There's no need to take you seriously.
Unfortunately, we don't have time.
We need you to die here.
Freeze! Abare!
Yeah!
Jeez. Ever since Sister Rukia
and Inoue went to Soul Society,
I've been so bored.
Is there a paradise-level
goddess anywhere?
Perhaps over there!
Something's there...
Who are you?
K-Kon...
So that's your Zanpakuto release...
That's right!
This is my true form!
I'm going to finish this all at once!
Frost unto the Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Why you...!
It's useless!
Oh?
This is my Zanpakuto release!
Yumichika! This fight is mine!
Don't interfere!
Again, Ikkaku?
Let me fight sometimes.
Sorry.
Extend!
Hozukimaru!
You're taking me on by yourself?
How foolish!
You Arrancar...
As usual, you've got tough skin!
That's...
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
Oh, Renji!
What happened?
Some guy with incredible
Spiritual Pressure suddenly...
It's an Arrancar!
Where did he go?
Th-That way...
Could it be?!
URAHARA'S SHOP
Stop! This is no place for
your kind to come!
Terrible things will happen to you
if you don't stop!
Hey, you!
What should we do?
He's dangerous...
And it's impossible to take
him on in this form.
Indeed...
Retreat!
Hey, wait!
I hear that someone here knows
how to use the Hogyoku.
I'd like to meet him...
He's not here.
So there are others...
Who are you?
Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
Squad 6 Lieutenant, Renji Abarai!
Where is the person who knows
how to use the Hogyoku?
I'm saying that he's gone out!
Then I'll just have to
wait here for his return.
I can't let you do that.
I'm keeping watch over
the shop while he's gone!
Just waiting here is boring.
Very well...
Come on!
Roar! Zabimaru!
What are you doing, freeloader?!
Why you...
Ururu!
Get inside!
It won't matter if you hide.
What are you going to do?
If we fight here, that shack will
immediately be crushed.
You think so?
That store's owner is pretty shrewd.
It shouldn't be that easy!
Besides, that just means I have
to finish this before that happens!
Want to try?
What should we do, Jinta?
What should we do?
We've got to fight!
Ururu, you stay here!
But...
Ahem!
Hey!
We're going out first!
We've got to assist Renji!
As freeloaders,
we shouldn't hide like this!
You all...
Roar! Zabimaru!
Too slow!
Oh? It seems that
you're a little capable.
Not just a little!
Very well...
I wasn't going to show my sword
to the likes of you, but I will!
You're exaggerating!
Come on!
How weak...
I have 20 levels to my sword skill.
That was the lowest. Level one.
It was a gesture of respect...
But you're nothing if you can't
even keep up with this level.
You idiot!
I just let my guard down a little!
Nonsense!
Then take this once more!
How weak...
Things won't be that easy!
Who are you?!
We're also keeping watch
over this place!
You'll pay if you don't
leave right away!
Stop! Don't--
We will do it!
It's the job of a freeloader to defend
the household at times like this.
It's all right...
We won't do anything rash.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Here we go!
What's this?
Where are you looking?!
What?!
We've forced him into the barrier!
Now, Kurodo!
All right!
Team attack, Abarai!
That's creepy!
Don't say that!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Don't underestimate me!
I've got you!
You look like him,
but the difference in
your Spiritual Pressure is obvious!
Kurodo!
Tricking me with
such silly illusions...
Die!
How impertinent!
How long will you last?!
The finishing blow!
I won't let you!
It doesn't seem like you understand
what I mean even when I tell you.
So taste level two!
This is still just the beginning.
We've had quite a lot
of appearances today.
Could it be that when
the spotlight turns to us,
we're going to di-
Kurodo! Don't say any more.
What an ominous thing to say.
We're forever immortal.
That's also doubtful.
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Hurry up.
Today's your turn to go shopping.
Why with you?
- Huh?
A Hollow.
All right, let's go!
Wait, Ichigo.
What is it?!
A lot of your friends can
see Soul Reapers, right?
In order to keep them from
recognizing you...
Wear this.
Oh. Thank you.
Why?!
He's gotten quite good at playing
the straight man.