Damn! Not again!
Damn!
It feels just like Getsugatensho,
but its actual power isn’t even close!
I get it…
I was throwing my attacks too soon
since this thing doesn’t have a blade.
If I charge it more with my
Spiritual Pressure like I did with Getsuga.
I’ll give it a try!
He produced this much destructive power just
by getting a small hang of it.
Amazing.
All right, this time you’ll
be entering this fish tank!
I permit you!
Welcome.
Oh, so it’s you.
Not the plushie this time?
Now that we know you
don’t need them anymore.
I believe I haven’t introduced
myself to you yet.
I’m Jackie Tristan.
It’s nice to meet you.
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Let’s get this thing started!
Nice. I like the look on your face.
“Dirty Boots”!
Wow.
Not bad.
I didn’t think you could dodge that.
I didn’t either.
What’s that supposed to mean?
What about you?
What’s with that outfit?
I didn’t know there was a
Fullbring you could wear.
There are.
That’s why I’m dressed like this.
I see.
So, this “Dirty Boots” of yours.
What’s its ability?
You think I’d tell you?
Good point.
This is a battle, after all.
Guess I’ll have to find out for myself.
Right?!
Hey, where’re you going?
We need you to undo your “Dollhouse”
when they’re done.
Stay here and watch.
No!
Huh?
Can I say something
that’s been on my mind?
No need to say it.
I don’t like that aspect of Riruka.
I said you didn’t have to say it.
What about you, Giriko?
Me?
I don’t really mind.
I don’t want to look
at Jackie’s Fullbring!
Not over yet!
Hmm…
How is Mr. Kurosaki doing?
Hard to say…
One…
Two…
Three!
I see…
Aren’t you going to attack?
Then…
let me attack you!
You’ve been repeating the same routine.
Dodging my attacks, then getting hit.
You’ve got good instincts,
but you sure take your time.
Are you trying to get the
hang of it as you fight?
Not that it matters.
Pretty soon you won’t
have that luxury.
See this?
The soil that was hard before
is soaking up water and turning into mud.
Observe.
My “Dirty Boots” are getting dirty.
It’s begun.
Yeah…
Do you think Mr. Kurosaki will survive?
We can only hope.
Her kick... got stronger?
Get it now?
As the name “Dirty Boots” implies,
the dirtier they get, the stronger I become.
With sand, dirt, mud,
dust…blood, rust, anything!
I was slowly gaining strength until now.
But from here on,
they’ll become stronger
at an accelerated rate!
The dirtier they get, the
stronger she becomes?
What’s with that?! That’s so stupid!
I can’t stand getting dirty!
I’ll never become dirty.
I’ll always be clean and cute.
Even when I die.
Then can you buy me that next time?!
Sure, I’ll buy you anything.
Yay!
Ichigo Kurosaki…
Stop messing around!!
Don’t you understand?!
You’re not a Soul Reaper right now!
You’re fighting with a mortal body!
Did you lose your sense of reality
from fighting so long as a Spiritual Entity?!
You’re mortal!
You can die!
If you continue taking
any more of my attacks
with your mortal body, you’ll
be dead meat in no time!
Is that all you know how to do?!
That technique of yours is full of holes!
It’s useless in real combat!
Haven’t you realized that yet?!
If you haven’t, I’ll show you!
That technique is inconsistent
in its effectiveness!
Depending on your concentration,
the number of blades varies
from three to six!
You keep firing it and the
number of blades will decrease.
At four blades or less, I
can destroy it with a kick!
And!
After three consecutive shots…
“I become most vulnerable.”…is that it?
He did that intentionally?!
He’s gone?
Bringer Light!
The flickering of the Bringer Light
after moving at high speed
using Fullbring is an
indication for the user’s
next high-speed jump…
It’s a sign that he’s
beginning to master Fullbring.
Impressive.
You quickly grasped the flaw
of your newly acquired ability
and took advantage of it.
Who taught you how to fight?
I was taught the basics.
The rest…
I learned as I fought.
I was a Soul Reaper for only a short period.
But in terms of experience,
I got more than you guys.
Experience, eh?
His mind for battle, which had
been unconsciously sharpened
in the battles he’s fought,
is being awakened as he fights
in a state without his powers.
Not bad, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ready?
Bring it!
Hey…
Thank you, Mr. Chad.
Sure…
Where’s Ichigo?
Over there.
I see…
That’s perfect.
Huh?
I wanted to ask you something.
That guy you told me about.
This Tsukishima.
I want to know about his ability.
I see…
Orihime Inoue said that, huh?
I’m positive I was cut.
But when I came to, there was no wound…
and the people who came here were gone…
And then, when you and Kurosaki came…
for a split second, I thought of
that person as a “friend.”
I don’t really understand
what I’m saying either.
I just felt like he was my friend.
It’s not like I mistook
him for someone else
or that I was mistaken.
How should I put it…
It felt like I thought about the past and…
suddenly I remembered who he was.
I’m thinking that’s what
Tsukishima’s ability is.
Ability?
That’s right…
The power of suggestion—interfering with memories.
Did Tsukishima’s Fullbring have
that sort of special ability?
Tell me…
Don’t keep anything from me now.
That’s good.
At this pace…
Ichigo!
What the?!
My Combat Pass…
Don’t hide it.
I’m not hiding anything.
I’m puzzled…
Puzzled?
If Tsukishima possessed
such an ability, I would’ve
definitely told you at the beginning.
Tsukishima’s Fullbring is
called “Book of the End.”
An extremely deadly weapon—literally,
a sword that can cut anything.
But…
That sword possesses no special abilities.
Don’t just stand there…
Let’s continue!
We’re stopping.
What’re you talking about?!
We’re not done!
Your Fullbring is going out of control!
I’ve never seen that happen before!
We pushed the pace of
your training too hard!
We have to stop.
It’s all right!
Let’s keep going!
Riruka!
Undo “Dollhouse.”
I said, let’s keep going!
My Fullbring isn’t out of control!
This is how I’ve always done it…
This is my Combat Pass telling me to
hurry up and regain my powers!
Listen…
I’m telling you it’s dangerous!
Do you need to be crushed to understand?!
Is it possible that his ability changed?
That couldn’t be.
Fullbring powers don't change with growth.
But my ability has gone
through a lot of changes!
No, you’re mistaken.
In your case, you just
weren’t able to find your
Fullbring’s innate ability
in the early stages.
How many years do you think we’ve
lived with our Fullbring?
We’re way past that stage.
Then what happened to Inoue?
That’s why I said I’m puzzled.
As far as I know, that wasn’t the
work of Tsukishima’s ability.
What about Uryu Ishida?
Huh?
He was attacked by Tsukishima, wasn’t he?
Is Uryu Ishida’s memory in disarray?
Fine…
Great, look how dirty they’ve become…
I’ll crush you as you wish!
Good!
We need to make sure…
If Uryu Ishida’s memory is also affected,
that’s something else
we have to worry about…
If his memories haven’t been affected…
Then what?
It means it wasn’t Tsukishima
who stabbed Orihime Inoue.
Are you sure?
Hi. It’s been a long time, Ginjo.
…Tsukishima!
So he’s…
How’ve you all been?
Kutsuzawa, hope you haven’t
been drinking too much.
Yukio…
Looks like you’re still
engrossed with playing games.
That’s not good.
You need to read more books.
Riruka’s not here?
Tsukishima…what did you come here for?
I don’t see Jackie around, either.
Tsukishima!
They in there?
Wait, Tsukishima!
What is this?!
Ichigo.
Hmm…
That you, Riruka?! Listen,
Tsukishima just…
Hey! I bought too much stuff to carry back.
Can you come pick me up in your car?
I don’t have a car! Forget
that, Tsukishima just…
What?! God, you’re so useless!
You’re the one who’s useless!
Xcution Dictionary!
Today, I’ll explain Jackie’s power!
Jackie’s Fullbring is “Dirty Boots.”
The dirtier her boots get, the
stronger Jackie’s kicks become!
If that’s the case, wouldn’t
it be better to keep them dirty?
Look, that’s not how it goes…
What if we gave them that distressed look…
Knock it off!
Huh?!
Now look what you’ve done!
Hey, stop that!
You’re making a hole in the floor!