Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
We Tremble in Awe of
That Which Cannot Be Seen
And We Worship
Yes… I sense a strong Sprit Energy…
What's this…?
You kick Yama down and
now you tell us to get outta your way?!
Uhh…
Say something, damn you…!
Oh, Toshirin's…
This is bad!
He's so unreasonable!
Shut up, will ya?!
Listen, all of you… Look at that!
First question:
What can that be?
You, in the middle!
Huh…? Uh, well…flowers for the kid
who died here the other day?
Absolutely right!
Mit-chan!
Then tell me…
Why is that vase on its side?
Well…we were skateboarding
and knocked…it…over…
If you ever do it again…
I'll make it so someone will have
to offer flowers for your souls, too!
S-Sorry about that!
Whew… If I put that much fear into them
they probably won't be back.
I'll bring you some
fresh flowers tomorrow.
Thank you for getting rid of them.
Now I should be able to rest in peace.
You're welcome.
It's about time you passed over.
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
15, a tenth grader.
My family runs a medical clinic.
We save some, and we lose some.
Maybe it's because of that,
but ever since I can remember,
I've been able to see ghosts.
I'm home…
You're late!
You delinquent!
You know that dinnertime here
is always at 7:00!
You! Is this any way
to treat your son,
who just laid his life on the line
to help a ghost pass over?!
Shut up! I don't care
what your excuse is.
Anyone who disturbs the peace and
happiness in this home will be punished!
Or what?
Are you gloating over the fact that
only you can touch or talk to ghosts?!
Shut up! I didn't ask
to be born like this!
Stop it, will you two?
Dinner's getting cold.
Leave them alone, Yuzu.
More rice please.
But, Karin…
Anyway…
Ordering a healthy male high school student
to come home every night at 7:00 is…
Ichigo, you have a new one on you.
Huh…?
This guy…when did he get here?!
No matter how hard I try to
get rid of them, they just won't go away!
Thanks for dinner.
Poor Ichigo… He's so popular.
But I sort of envy him.
I can sense their presence,
but I rarely see anything.
Well, I don't believe
in ghosts and such.
What? But you see them too,
don't you, Karin?
Dad's the only one
who can't see them.
Whether I see them or not,
if I don't believe in them,
they don't exist.
Ohh…
So cold!
Dinner…
Wide open!
Never mind!
I'm going to bed.
Oh, Ichigo…
It's your fault, Dad.
Why?!
Ichigo is having
a tough time right now.
Now that you mention it,
he said he's seeing more
of them than before.
What?!
You mean he talks to you
about things like that?
He doesn't tell me…
Of course not.
You're over 40, but can only communicate
in this immature way.
Who'd want to tell you anything?
Dear… I don't know if it's because
they're in puberty,
but our daughters have been
so cold towards me!
What should I do…?
First of all, get rid of that
stupid memorial poster.
The incident occurred
one block away from the main street
outside of Karakura Station.
According to local residents,
at about 7:30 AM,
the ground shook with
a loud crash and
the walls of many buildings exploded.
Good morning, Ichigo.
'Morning… Where's Dad?
He has a meeting.
He won't be home tonight.
I see… Huh?
Investigators and explosives experts
are currently working to discover the cause.
What's wrong?
That's near here.
Hey…!
Hm?
What was that sound?
I didn't hear anything…
It's another explosion!
W-What's that…?
Help me!
Run!
What is it?!
I don't know!
Oh. Hey! Hurry!
H-Hey…
Hey, you…?
What was that, anyway?
Another explosion?
What's going on?
I can't figure it out…
Who was that?
Who…are you…?
Who are you?!
What do you want?
Hey!
It's near…
What are you talking about?!
First you scare the living daylights
out of me, then you ignore me?
I'm asking you who you are!
Y-You… You can see me?
But wait…you just kicked me...
Huh? What are you babbling about?
Of course, I can see you.
You were the one
in town earlier, weren't you?
You just noticed?
Strange…
People usually can't see me…
Quit talking nonsense…
Why, you…!
Then, I will tell you.
I am…a Soul Reaper.
Again… Where…?
I see.
So you're a Soul Reaper.
And you've come all the way here
from this Soul Society place
in order to exorcise evil demons.
So that means that
that monster was a demon…
and it attacked that girl.
Okay, I'll believe you…
Idiot! You think I'd believe that?!
You're...You're saying that,
although you see ghosts,
you don't believe in Soul Reapers?
Of course!
Unfortunately, I've never seen
a Soul Reaper before.
I don't believe in anything
that I can't see.
But you're seeing me now.
I'll admit that you're no human.
But quit playing "Soul Reaper"
around here.
Got that? You pipsqueak.
You dare to call me that?!
Bakudo Number One: Sai!
Ouch! What did you do to me?!
You can't move, can you?
This is Kido, a high-level incantation
that only a Soul Reaper can use.
I may not look it, but I have lived nearly
ten times longer than you.
And you called me a "pipsqueak"?!
In any other situation,
I would kill you on the spot,
but I am not permitted to execute anyone
not named in my orders.
Be grateful for that, pipsqueak.
Of all the nerve…!
And so…
Oh…
Y-You're the guy from yesterday…
N-No… I don't want to go
to the Netherworld!
Fear not. Your destination is
not the Netherworld.
It is the Soul Society.
Unlike the Netherworld,
it is a restful place.
What happened…to that guy?
I sent him to the Soul Society.
In your language it's
called "passing over," I guess.
It's one of the jobs of Soul Reapers.
I will explain it simply so that even
an impatient brat like you can be satisfied.
Now listen…
There are two types of spirits
in this world.
The first are normal spirits
called Wholes…
They're the ghosts you usually see.
The second are called Hollows.
They attack people, living or dead,
to devour their souls.
They are evil spirits.
Do you have any questions so far?
Well…Tell me why your drawing
is so bad, why don't you?
Hey!
What the hell did you do?!
I will continue my explanation, Baron.
Baron…?
We Soul Reapers have two jobs.
The first is to lead the Wholes
to the Soul Society
with a sendoff, Konso,
as I just did.
And the second is to cut and
purify the Hollows.
Why was that Hollow going
after that girl?
That I do not know.
We have yet to grasp
everything about them.
I smell it…
It's the smell of
an especially tasty soul.
It's nearby…
along with the smell of a Soul Reaper.
Oh! What was that?!
Whatever the case,
there's another one
wandering around here.
Then, hurry up and get rid of it!
No, well…
For some reason, I haven't been
able to sense its presence at all.
It's as though some strong force
is obstructing my senses.
What are you saying?!
Can't you hear the terrible cries?!
Isn't that the Hollow you're after?
Terrible cries…? I don't…
I heard that!
That is definitely the cry of a Hollow!
See?!
Yuzu!
Hey, wait!
What strong spirit pressure!
How could I not have sensed this?!
I…!
Ichi…go…
Yuzu!
Karin was…
Ichigo…
Please save…Karin…
Hey, you!
Hey!
Damn it!
Stop it! Stop…it!
Stay back!
Karin…!
Damn it…!
He's moving…
after I put that spell on him…!
You'll get in the way!
Stay back!
Shut up!
Karin!
Stop that! No human strength
can break it.
If you try to force it, your soul will…
A human breaking the spell
under his own power?
Wait!
Ichigo…! Run!
Karin!
I found you.
Karin! Hey!
Get a hold of yourself!
That Hollow has not devoured
your sisters' souls yet.
Are you sure?
Yes…
It is seeking a soul with a higher
concentration of spirit energy.
I see. That Hollow this afternoon
wasn't after that girl, either.
What do you mean?
For some reason,
your spirit energy was almost
completely suppressed until just now.
That's why I didn't sense
anything about you,
and you were never attacked
by a Hollow.
It's just conjecture,
but perhaps the spirit energy that
was sealed up within your body…
began to pour out due to
the contact you had
with the ghost
of that young girl.
In other words,
those two Hollows sensed the density
of your soul through that girl.
They are really after you!
They're…after me…
It's here! You stay…
Shut up!
Are you saying that girl was
attacked because of me?
What are you talking about?
It's my fault that Karin and Yuzu's lives
are in danger?!
Please save…
Ichigo… Run!
Hey!
You…! You want my soul, don't you?
In that case, come fight me
one on one!
Soul Reaper!
You fool!
You should have known…
that you were no match for him…!
Or, did you think that everything
would be over
if you gave him your soul?
At this rate, we will all simply
become food for him.
Do you want…to save your family?
Of course! Is there a way?
There's just one way…
You must become a Soul Reaper!
What?!
Run the point of this Zanpakuto
through the center of your being
and I will pour my powers into you.
I don't know if it will work,
but there is nothing else we can do.
Give me that sword, Soul Reaper.
My name is not Soul Reaper.
I am Rukia Kuchiki.
I am…
Ichigo Kurosaki!
How could it be…?
I meant to give him half
of my energy, but he took it all…
Hey…!
Who is he?!
I have never seen a human
with spirit energy enough…
to confuse a Soul Reaper.
I have never seen a human
with strength enough
to break a spell
on his own…
And…I've never seen
a Soul Reaper's Zanpakuto…
become so large!
Now you'll pay for hurting my family!
You fish-face!
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
Hey, how are you all doing?
This is your idol Kon,
who was voted
"the one you'd most want to make
your bride" in the world of Bleach!
It's finally started…
The high school Soul Reaper's
sweet but painful, slightly salty, heartfelt…
No! You don't appear until
later in the story!
Oh, we're out of time…