Why isn't anyone coming…?
Is this…Karakura Town?
Cool, huh?
I chose an environment you’re
used to fighting in.
Aren’t you happy?
You can fight me one-on-one.
Sorry, but it's two against one.
Ishida… What about your injuries?
Kuchiki healed me.
It was just first aid, though.
Kurosaki…
I have to apologize to you.
Right after we returned from saving
Kuchiki in the Soul Society…
You told us about the Combat Pass.
That’s when I got the idea
that a Substitute Soul Reaper
must have existed before you.
And that he probably went missing.
If he was alive, they
should have let you know.
If he was dead, they should
have told you why.
But the fact that they did neither means
that even the Soul Society
probably didn't know.
I should have told you this
when I thought of it.
Ishida…
Take that!
What the hell, Kurosaki?!
Who cares?
Stop dwelling on things that are over!
Idiot!
Like you don’t dwell on things…
Did you say something?
Nope.
Let's do this!
Don't get in my way!
But Kurosaki...
What really worries me is if their
reason was neither of them…
That's…
…impossible…
Aw, man…
Nobody’s out yet?
Taking their sweet time…
I've got nothing to do.
This is boring. I’m going home.
No!
We made a promise that we'd
come together and leave together!
If you leave early,
the grandpa is going to be
angry with you again, Kenny!
That hurts. Don't pull my ear.
I don't know how he did it,
but he used his power to trap
me in some strange place.
Where are you swinging?
Are you really trying
your best to find me?
Or can you not power up
if you don’t hear something like,
“Or the girl dies”?
Looks like I got stuck
with the annoying guy…
Where are you?!
Show yourself!
Damn you!
Don’t…
Don’t think you can…
tempt me with these things!
This is way too easy…
Damn you…
Maybe I should shoot her for real.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
I don't think this is the right
time to be gazing at the moon.
I was thinking that it's a
good thing I'm fighting you.
Why's that?
Ichigo Kurosaki is soft.
He may be consumed by anger,
but I hardly doubt he would be able to
fight you for the sole
purpose of killing you.
Oh?
It sounds like you would
never let me hit you with my sword!
I despise the way you fight.
You don't act on your own.
You torment your foes by stealing bonds.
It is truly despicable.
An audacity punishable only by death.
Come at me.
I shall cut you down before
you take one swing.
Hey! Don't run away, you bastard!
How odd.
-Come on out!
-No matter how I look at it,
that punch shouldn't have been able
knock down such a large tree
It shouldn’t even be able
to break a wooden sword.
-Hey, you’re playing dirty!
-But that kid…
He's been smashing everything
with a single hit.
What's going on?
Do things just work in their favor
because they set up this place?
Hey!
I busted your shoulder, didn't I?!
Looks like you were unlucky!
This bastard!
He popped his shoulder back
in with just his muscles!
What kind of monster is he?!
Huh? What’s wrong?
Are you scared?
I'm not scared, bastard!
Aren't you going to attack me?
I can't attack a woman.
What a gentleman.
But perhaps you have
a narrow world-view?
Have you ever met a woman
stronger than yourself?
It doesn't matter if
they're stronger or not.
I won't attack first.
I see.
Then the only thing
that’s narrow about you
is your outlook on things.
What is that thing that looks
like it came from a motorcycle?
Do you get more powerful
if you make it roar?
This thing?
I'm surprised.
I had no idea that Soul Reapers
knew about motorcycles.
Yeah, kind of.
You're not going to make
the first attack, right?
Then shut up and watch.
But you should at least draw your sword.
If you don't want to regret having
such a narrow outlook in life, that is.
My “Dirty Boots” get
stronger the dirtier they get!
And it's not just my boots…
Any grime on the Fullbring surrounding
my body makes me stronger!
You should draw your sword.
That's a good reaction!
But I'm not done yet!
I got him.
You’re finished!
Impossible…
He was hit hard!
So how is it that he was
barely knocked back?!
All right.
I get it now.
I'll take the next one too.
Come on.
I told you…
you're going to regret that attitude!
I've been training for the past 17 months
so that I can fight against Aizen.
It doesn't matter if
you're a man or a woman.
All of you aren’t good enough for me.
Damn.
I thought I would be able to get
out of here if I defeated her.
It seems like there's no way out.
It's probably because I'm still alive.
You're conscious already?
You're one tough woman.
I'm conscious, but I won't
be able to move for a while.
Now's your chance to finish me off.
Shut up.
What’s that?!
The sky is folding?!
Damn it! Yukio is watching us!
He figured I couldn’t defeat you,
so he’s decided to wipe us
out along with the dimension.
You!
Hurry up and kill me!
If one of our Spiritual Pressures
disappears and we settle this,
this dimension should
automatically open up!
Kill me!
Can’t do that.
Why?!
A man who lays a hand
on a woman is scum.
Living as scum is the
same as being dead.
We're forcing our way out of here.
That’s the logic of a child…
I thought I became cynical enough where
that sort of thing didn’t
sting me anymore.
I wish a guy like you were
the one who saved me.
You…
Huh?
Aww… She died.
Dying to save the enemy. How touching.
Well, I'm not sure if the
enemy survived that, though.
Oh, good job.
You finally came.
I thought you might never find me.
Did you find me because you leveled up
from all the traps I placed?
You don't seem the least bit tired.
How unpleasant.
You sure like to talk a lot.
You sure are violent.
What if I had left a
bomb in the next room?
You and I would have been blown up.
Weren’t you watching?
My Hyorinmaru is a sword of ice.
I would’ve frozen the explosion.
A sword of ice, huh?
That's so cool!
I’m not here to chat with you.
Me neither.
You can fix the broken
walls and rooms, huh?
What a useful ability.
Didn't you see?
This whole dimension is my ability.
In this dimension, I’m god.
I see.
You don't get it, do you?
A god can do anything.
For example…
Something like this…
You truly are a god.
That's impressive.
Why do you...
keep making fun of me?!
You brat!
Don't dodge it!
Are you afraid?!
Don't let me dodge it then.
Are you holding back?
Of course I am!
Shall I show you what'll happen
if I don't hold back?!
You can't escape this room!
The next room and the next room…
the walls, the ceiling, and the
floors are all part of my ability!
They're set to follow you
forever and crush you!
Come at me!
I'll kill you!
Captains are just elites who
were raised in a warm home!
Somebody like that could never beat me!
Oh, I see…
You’re an abandoned child.
No!
I wasn't abandoned!
I abandoned my stupid parents!
I made that choice!
You have no right to
say anything about it!
I transferred all of my
dad's money over to me
and destroyed his company!
If you ignore your children,
they learn all kinds of things!
They're stupid for not realizing that!
That feeling when I saw the news
that they had committed suicide…
You lost focus from being so
busy talking about your story.
Damn it!
What's wrong?
They're set to follow
me until they crush me.
Are you sure you don't
want to shut them down?
Huh?
What's this?
You saved me anyway!
Of course you would!
You took pity…
I didn’t take pity on you.
And I'm not interested in your past.
There's no guarantee that
this dimension and the other
dimensions will disappear if I kill you.
So how about I make you a deal?
H-Hey!
Wait a second!
I won't freeze your head and your arms.
If you shut off your power
within five minutes,
I won't kill you.
Damn it…
Never… Never…
Who the hell are you calling scared?!
What do you think?!
I think you're the one who's afraid!
Damn it! Come down here!
Flying is cheating!
No one told me that Soul
Reapers could fly!
I'm not flying.
I'm standing.
I don't get it!
It’d be unsatisfying if I beat you
without knowing what you can do,
so I thought I’d try to
understand your ability first.
But I quit. It’s a pain in the butt.
Do you want me to slap you like a brat?
Or do you want me to
destroy you like a man?
Choose one.
That's easy!
I want to destroy you like a man!
Well said!
What?
The tendons in my pinky are torn…
But more importantly,
he smashed Hozukimaru…
Well blocked!
If I had hit your head,
I would have split it open and
this would have been over!
You're right. I'm pretty lucky.
Are you stupid?!
You're not lucky!
Your spear broke with a single hit!
I'm the lucky one!
Come at me!
I'm going to steal all of your
luck and leave you with nothing!
I see your luck allows
you to break things.
That means weapons are useless.
Are you going to take
me on with your fists?!
Bring it on!
Here I go!
You're kidding, right?
What's with this guy?
Is he not affected at all?
That's impossible.
I'm hitting him.
Even if I don't break
a bone with each hit,
I should be leaving fractures.
So why…
So why is he attacking me
as if nothing's wrong?!
What was that just now?
I didn't feel anything?!
My…
My chances of hitting the
jackpot are going down?!
My “Jackpot Knuckle” allows
me to make one lucky hit.
I've never used it this
many times in a row,
so I had no idea this would happen!
So the chances of hitting the jackpot
go down when it’s used repeatedly?!
What's this?
It suddenly stopped working.
Are you worn out already?!
D-Damn it!
I'm not worn out!
Damn it!
All right!
Jackpot!
Your punches were pretty powerful…
But luckily, when you hit a vital
spot, you didn't do much damage.
This was a bad matchup for you.
You may be a lucky guy,
but I'm the luckiest guy in
the 13 Court Guard Squads!
What's wrong?
You can't cut me from that distance.
The fact that you're
waiting there means that
coming any closer puts
you within my range.
I need to think of a plan.
I see. You're very cautious.
Did my actions seem meaningful to you?
What about this?
I believe I shouldn’t view
them as meaningless acts.
Scatter…
Senbonzakura…
Rukia. How are things on your end?
Yes, Brother!
Several items ambushed me,
but everything is fine!
And they are all cute… I mean,
they are all works of art!
Rukia…
Y-Yes, sir?!
Bring one back for me.
Xcution Dictionary!
Today, I'm having tea with all
of the members of Xcution!
Ugh… Come on…
Why aren't they coming?!
Since no one's coming,
TO JACKIE
TO YUKIO
I guess this segment is over.