Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Good...
morning, Ichigo!!
You've got some nerve!
Trying to attack your own son
in his sleep!
You're pretty good, my boy.
There's nothing more to teach you.
Huh?!
Hey, what about Karin and
Yuzu's injuries?
Injuries? What're you talking about?
What?
It's a miracle.
A truck crashes into our house,
and no one's hurt.
What's more miraculous is
that no one woke up.
– What's going on? Their wounds...
– And the culprit gone away.
– They're all gone.
– Not to worry!
– He'll probably come to apologize later.
– Everyone thinks it was some truck.
As if!
Is this the work of
a Soul Reaper?
Ichigo, hurry and eat breakfast
or you'll be late.
Oh yeah...
I wonder if she went back
to that place she called
the Soul Society.
Orihime, did you bring lunch today?
Yes. I have taiyaki-style ramen
with wasabi and honey.
Would you like some, Tatsuki?
Err...no thanks.
It's really good.
Oh, it's Inoue.
Huh? I'm sorry!
Ichigo, you bumped into her and
that's all you can say?!
Oh, sorry. Are you all right?
Y-Yes...
Here.
Huh?!
It's all right.
I-I have voby...bolley...volley...
Hey Orihime!
What's with her?
You have such a mean look.
By the way, why're you so late?
It's already lunchtime.
Well... I'll explain later.
Ichigo, I heard a truck crashed
into your house.
Yeah...
Finished cleaning up?
It's not that easy!
Need help?
Huh?
Err...no.
Chad, you'll end up destroying
the place even more.
What's next?
Modern literature.
Oh, are you Kurosaki?
Huh?
I'll be sitting next to you from today.
My name's Kuchiki.
Y-You...!
What's wrong, Ichigo?!
You know each other?
Oh no, this is our first meeting.
Right, Kurosaki?
She's a transfer student, Kuchiki.
Right, Rukia?
Nice to meet you.
Hey you! Just what the hell
are you thinking?!
My, how scary! What is the matter?
You're not going to do
something to me, are you?
First of all, quit talking like that!
Oh, I think this is pretty good
considering I learned it overnight.
Forget it! So why are you here?
Weren't you going back to
that Soul Society or whatever?
Don't be stupid.
Only Soul Reapers can
go back there.
Right now, I don't have that ability.
What?
Last night, most of my powers
as a Soul Reaper were taken by you.
W-What?
I don't know anything
about that.
Thanks to you,
I'm stuck in this gigai form.
What's a "gigai"?
It's a temporary body provided
for use in emergencies.
Soul Reapers who are drastically
weakened inhabit a gigai
until their powers return.
That's why my classmates
could see you.
Precisely. And so...
until my powers return,
you will have to do
the work of a Soul Reaper.
What?
It's only natural.
You have the powers
of a Soul Reaper.
You don't have the right...
– to refuse.
– I refuse!
What?
I don't ever want to fight
such monsters again!
Ridiculous! You did fine yesterday!
That's because my family was
being attacked.
But I'm not about to fight
for complete strangers.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I see... Then it can't be helped.
Hey!
Huh?
Aghh! My body...
What'd you do to me?!
Follow me.
Hey, where are we going?
It's around here.
What is?
An order...
from the Soul Society.
A Whole spirit who lives
in this park will probably be attacked.
Help!
Wait!
What?!
Why are you going to help him?
Isn't he a complete stranger?
So what?
I can't just stand here when
he's being attacked before my very eyes!
Don't be so naive!
Wha--?!
A Soul Reaper must treat
all spirits equally.
Just because they're close by...
just because it's convenient...
it doesn't work like that.
Do not help him!
If you intend to help that boy,
make up your mind
to save all spirits!
You must make the commitment
to go anywhere...
and even be willing to
sacrifice your life!
Are you committed to this, Ichigo?
No!
Who cares about commitment?!
I saved this boy because I wanted to!
What about you?
What?
You risked your life to
save me last night.
Did you think about your duty
as a Soul Reaper when you acted?
When you put yourself at risk,
it doesn't matter!
At the very least...
I...
will be different!
You okay?
Hey kid...
If you don't want another
scary experience like that,
hurry up and pass over.
That was a fine Konso.
I'm leaving!
Huh?!
What are you doing?!
Stop!
W-Where am I?!
W-What do you intend
to do to me?!
Wandering spirit...
Devour it...that man's soul!
Now!
Hear me God... Why was I born?
Please summon me back
to your side! Now!
Shut up!
How dare you?!
I am studying
contemporary language!
It doesn't sound contemporary
at all!
Besides, how long are you
gonna keep following me?!
Until you agree to do
the Soul Reaper's job!
Hah! Whatever!
Hey!
Inoue?!
Huh? Kurosaki!
Did that car just hit you?
Oh... maybe...
Maybe? And you're okay?!
Yes, it was just a little bump.
I'm fine...I really am!
You're fine? And where's the car?
Huh?
It drove away.
Look, you...!
Oh... I'm sorry.
Well, as long as you're okay.
Huh?
Kuchiki?
Who the hell are you?
Idiot! She's in our class!
That's Inoue! Orihime Inoue!
What?
Oh hello, Inoue!
Oh yes, hello.
Have you been out shopping?
Oh yes! Dinner!
My leeks, butter, bananas,
and bean jam...they're fine, too.
What is she gonna make with that?
How did you get that bruise on your leg?
Huh? Did I just get it?
Maybe when the car hit me.
That looks bad, it must hurt.
A little. But I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Umm...
What's the matter, Kuchiki?
You look so serious.
Huh? It's nothing.
Just take care.
Thank you.
Want me to walk you home?
Oh, no... I'm fine, really.
See you!
Cripes! She'd better be careful.
That girl...
Huh? You mean, Inoue?
Are you good friends?
Not really. I've never even
spoken to her much.
She's close to one of my friends
who lives in
the neighborhood.
Just...
Just?
Three years ago...
her brother died at our hospital...
What?
He was her only family.
It was a car accident.
Brother! Brother!
Don't die! Please don't
leave me alone!
I didn't know that
she was the girl who was crying that day...
I just found out recently.
How was your spirit energy
at that time?
Huh? Not as strong as it is now.
It's only recently that I've been able
to see ghosts and talk to them.
Just as I thought...
What is it anyway?
Nothing.
See you.
Huh? Hey!
Where're you going?
Home.
Where to?
Are you interested?
Not really.
Then don't ask.
W-Why that...!
Yes!
Oh Tatsuki!
Mom asked me to give this to you.
It's stewed beef with potatoes.
Oh!
Wow! Home-made stewed beef
and potatoes!
This is so delicious!
You eat such weird stuff
when you're alone.
You think so?
Absolutely...
I mean, what is this stuff?
Hey Brother...
Have you seen my pajamas?
Hey, at least knock!
Boy, you've gotten so mean now
that you're in high school!
Have not.
And I don't know where
your pajamas are.
That's weird. My dress is also missing.
But why do you have to ask
me about everything?!
Good night!
An order?
What? Huh? Huh?
Huh?!
Ichigo!
W-What're you doing there?!
And those pajamas...!
Save it for later. We have an order!
Order?!
It's coming!
W-Wait a minute!
Don't just stand there!
It's coming!
Aim for the head!
Ichigo!
Idiot! Don't just swing
the sword around!
Shut up! As long as I kill it, right?!
You're mine!
Not deep enough!
Huh?!
What--?!
It got away. We're going after it.
What's the matter, Ichigo?
I have a question...
What is it?
That thing's face...
It was Inoue's brother.
What?!
I'll tell you one thing...
Attacking a Hollow from behind
and splitting its head in one blow...
That is the essence of
exterminating a Hollow.
Do not forget.
What do you mean?
This is to minimize your own injuries...
and also so that you never
see the identity of the Hollow.
What do you mean
"identity of the Hollow"?
You saw it, just now.
All Hollows were once
the souls of ordinary humans.
What?!
You never told me that!
Wasn't that just some monster?!
Some monster we needed to kill?!
Yes, now he is just a monster.
And he must be destroyed.
But... he was once human...?
Grudges, regrets...
Souls who still harbor such feelings
are hard to perform Konso on,
and linger on alone.
Then they either become
Hollows themselves,
or are devoured by other Hollows,
and become new Hollows.
That's...!
What? You mean, Ichigo?!
Yes. But they were just
walking together.
What's the matter?
Why that Ichigo!
I didn't realize he was
such a fast worker...!
I mean...
He didn't even walk you home
even though you were hurt!
No, he offered to
walk me home.
But...
Aghh! Watch out! I'm going to win!
I mean, Champ!
What are you imagining?
To the right! Yes, here!
Watch out! It's a gun!
What was that?
Though the voyage must continue on
May seas always be calm
When the cycle of the moon
has renewed may it shine
It's light to guide your boat
I offer this voyage a prayer
With each new day that still awaits
On vividly shining seas
To the end of the journey
I am the charismatic seer
of the new century!
The messenger from
the Netherworld, Don Kanonji!
I journey everywhere
in search of bad spirits!
It's not your cue yet!
We're out of time, again!