Aizen's true objectives
were to create the Ouken
by wiping out the Enriched
Spirit Zone of Karakura Town,
and to take over
the Soul Society by force.
In order to foil his plan,
the Soul Reapers readied for battle
in a fake Karakura Town
that they
had built in
the World of the Living.
The battle between the Espada and
the Soul Reapers had finally begun.
Stand back, everyone.
All things in the universe
turn to ashes.
Ryujinjakka.
Jokakuenjo.
Aizen and the others
won't be able to
get past this wall of flames
for a while.
Now then,
shall we crush them?
In Hueco Mundo, countless Exequias
stood in the way of Ichigo,
who was headed towards
Tower 5 to rescue Orihime.
Ichigo was gradually overwhelmed by
the Exequias' sheer numbers, when…
Coming at you one more time!
Renji!
El Directo!
Chad!
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Rukia!
Idiot!
Save the reunion for later!
Go quickly, Ichigo!
Gotcha.
Jeez… He's so high maintenance.
Meanwhile, in Tower 5,
Ulquiorra and Orihime
faced each other.
Orihime said she was
unafraid of dying alone
because she shared her heart
with her friends.
To which,
Ulquiorra cast his doubts.
Heart, you say?
You humans use
that word so casually,
as though it's in
the palm of your hands.
What is "heart"?
If I rip open your chest,
will I see it inside?
If I split your skull,
Kurosaki.
Step away from Inoue.
I was about to.
My duty is to protect Las Noches
until Lord Aizen returns.
I've received no orders
to take her life.
Until those orders come,
I will let her live.
However,
you are a different matter.
Killing you is synonymous
with protecting Las Noches.
I shall eliminate you
with my sword.
That was unexpected.
I didn't think you would
draw your sword first.
I came here thinking
that I'd have to
start by making you
draw your sword.
Can I take it
you consider me
an equal opponent?
At the very least,
I consider you
worthy of destroying.
That's good enough for me.
Kurosaki.
So, what should we do?
There are hordes of enemies,
while our boss is in that mess.
That's no way to speak
of Lord Aizen, Barragan.
And that's no way
to speak to me, Halibel.
Given that the boss is stuck,
I will give the orders.
I won't hear any complaints.
What're you…
Be quiet, Mila Rose.
Sounds good to me.
Ow!
What was that for, Lilinette?
Ouch!
How can that be good?!
What're you kissing ass for?!
You're always kissing up
– to everyone, everywhere.
– Quit yakking.
Try and look good for a change!
Are you really taking
this battle seriously?!
The Enriched Spirit Zone beneath
our feet is a fake, he said…
He said they
replaced it with
a replica built in
the Soul Society.
Boss said, all we have to do is
invade the Soul Society and
obtain the Enriched Sprit Zone.
Is it really necessary to
go through all that trouble?
From what was said earlier,
I figure it works like this.
He said they erected four pillars
on each side of the town
and used the power of the pillars
to swap the entire town.
In that case, what would happen
if we destroyed those pillars?
Findorr!
Yes, sir.
I know where
the pillars are located.
It's standard practice
to place
things like that at
the four cardinal points.
This is bad! They know!
What're we going to do now?!
If the pillars are destroyed,
the Karakura Town that we sent to
the Soul Society will come back!
The real Karakura Town
will become a battlefield!
Karakura Town will…
Karakura Town will return!
You fool!
What?
Do you think I wouldn't assign
anyone to such important locations?
What?
Extend, Hozukimaru!
Bloom, Fujikujaku.
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
I've stationed capable fighters.
Huh? Huh?
What?!
Madarame!
Ayasegawa!
Kira!
Hisagi!
You mean they weren't holding down
the fort back home?!
They weren't around when
you had us assembled,
so I felt like a winner,
thinking "you are counting
on me instead of them,"
"serves 'em right."
That kind of thing!
What?!
You mean,
you all knew about this?!
Of course.
What?!
Do you mind not speaking of us
like we're you?
What?!
I did tell you.
No doubt you were
gnawing on fried crackers
and missed what I said.
What?!
That's the only explanation!
Stupid Omaeda!
Come on.
It's your fault for gnawing on
fried crackers in a daze!
What?!
Eating fried crackers and being
in a daze aren't connected!
– Oh yes they are!
– Maybe I didn't tell him.
Four soldiers…
So what?
If there are four pillars
guarded by four ants,
then we'll squash them
with four dragons.
Poww.
Chuhlhourne.
Abirama.
Findorr.
Crush them.
– Yes!
– As you command, your Majesty!
Oh?
So here come the new guys.
Aren't you a big fellow?
I pray you're as
imposing as you look.
Pray?
To what?
You Soul Reapers have a god?
Now that you bring it up,
we don't pray to
anything in particular.
All right, I know!
Anything will do!
I'll pray to your god
if you'd like!
I see.
Then there's no problem.
Our god, the king,
understands better than anyone
that you are no match for me.
Oh?
Before we begin,
I'd like to ask,
what seat are you?
Shuhei Hisagi, Squad 9 lieutenant.
I see.
Then I, too,
will fight with the strength
of a lieutenant.
Here, here, here, here, here!
Look at me!
His Majesty,
King Barragan's first Fracciones,
Charlotte Chuhlhourn,
has arrived.
Oh?
My, my, my, my, my?
I have a policy of not
looking at ugly things.
Oh dear.
W-W-W-What'd you do that for,
you bastard?!
That's what I want to ask you!
What's the idea of calling someone
you meet for the first time ugly?!
Ugly?!
See here!
What's really ugly is…
judging someone
on appearances.
That's right,
I'm talking about your heart.
That was a nice line,
if I do say so myself.
Yes, someone with
a heart like mine,
now that's someone
with true beauty.
Absolute beauty that
defies all else.
Can you understand?
I'm saying something worthwhile,
so the least you could do
is look at me, ugly bastard!
I don't need to look at you,
and you're not saying much,
ugly bastard!
I said to just look at me! Look!
Don't want to!
Look!
Look, I said!
Stop it!
Don't bring your ugliness near me!
You said it. You said it again!
You called me ugly!
I'll say it all I want!
Ugly! Ugly! Ugly! Ugly!
Gonna do it! Gonna do it!
Gonna do it!
Who is the bravest of his Majesty
King Barragan's Fracciones?!
Me!
Who is the most trusted of
his Majesty King Barragan's
Fracciones?!
Me!
Who is the strongest of
his Majestiy King Barragan's
Fracciones?!
Me!
Gonna do it! Gonna do it!
Gonna do it!
Hey!
Hey, you there!
Why aren't you doing it
along with me?!
You're a gloomy one, aren't you?
Do what?
You mean that shout-along?
What do you mean,
"shout-along"?!
There's no such thing!
Are you mocking me?!
This is a ritual!
A ritual of battle where
we shout our intent to
kick each other's butt
and incite one another!
Let's go! Let's do it! Ready!
Gonna do it! Gonna do it!
Gonna do it! Gonna…
Do it with me!
I don't want to.
Putting feeling into my desire
to kick your butt.
I have no reason to join in
on such a negative ritual.
I don't need to hear that from
someone who looks so negative
that he's going to die!
Looks like I got stuck
with a gutless one.
Oh well.
I'm King Barragan's Fraccion,
Abirama Redder.
What's your name, Soul Reaper?
Squad 3 lieutenant, Izuru Kira.
Squad 3?
Oh, so you were under Gin Ichimaru?
I see.
I heard he abandoned you
back in the Soul Society,
but it all makes sense now.
Guess he had no choice but to
abandon a gutless guy like you.
Don't toss about
his name so casually
in my presence.
If you are going to die anyway,
wouldn't you prefer to die
with fewer injuries?
What's this?
So you can make that look.
It's been a long time since
I made an appearance.
Hisagi, don't go getting giddy.
I'm not giddy!
I have no notion at all of
showing off my impressiveness
and appealing to the audience!
No one said anything about that.
Substitute Soul Reaper
Work Journal!
Substitute Soul Reapers
lecture Soul Reapers
on information from
the World of the Living.
Eyeglasses?!
Yeah!
I'm thinking of buying
a pair of really cool ones!
Don't come here asking
about everything!
Oh, how about these?!
Sure.
A souvenir from
your business trip?
Yes! I've heard they're popular
in the World of the Living,
so I bought you a pair, too,
Captain.
I don't want them.