Oh Karin!
Hi there.
Impressive!
In just this short time,
you’ve increased your
power tremendously.
I did it to defeat you!
Now, Inoue!
Tsubaki!
Why is this happening?
It’s time to wake up now.
Who am I?
Bastard! What did you do to Inoue?!
What, you say?
The same as what I did to you.
I’m too late.
Inoue and Sado’s
Spiritual Pressures...
It doesn’t look like they’ve
been injured, but...
I sense another Spiritual Pressure?
Okay, break time’s over.
Yeah...
Yukio.
I’m on it.
“Invaders Must Die.”
We’re almost done.
You can all look forward
to getting rid of
our despicable powers.
Yes...
I hope so.
Man, look at the time!
Oh, Ishida.
Are you okay now?
Not yet…
But I had some paperwork at
school to take care of.
Heard you got hurt pretty
bad from falling off a tree,
while trying to save a cat.
That’s not like you.
Hurt trying to save a cat?
That Ryuken…
What sort of explanation
did he give to the school?!
A Spiritual Pressure?!
During my absence,
did you come across anyone suspicious?
Huh?
Nope, if you’re talking about
those punks, they didn’t come.
Besides, Ichigo,
the guy they’re after,
has been playing hooky.
You think he’s doing one
of his part-time jobs?
Maybe I should go check
out his work place again.
You mean, go bother him?
That other Spiritual Pressure
I sensed from where
Inoue and Sado were…
It belongs to him. No doubt about it…
And…
I sensed the same
Spiritual Pressure from
those two, as well…
What’s going on?
Why did he approach
Asano and Kojima, who
don’t possess any powers?
And that odd sensation mixed in with
each of their Spiritual Pressures…
What is he plotting?
Brother Ichi didn’t come
home yesterday, either.
I see…
Has anything…
unusual happened around Kurosaki
or to anyone else in
your family recently?
Huh?
For example…you saw someone
or felt something…
I’m not really sure when
you put it that way…
Besides, Brother Ichi’s pretty numb
when it comes to things like that…
There could be a ghost or monster right
in front of his eyes and he
wouldn’t notice it, I think.
Is that so…
Do you know where he’s
working part-time?
Wait here a sec.
ODD JOBS SERVICE - UNAGIYA
Here you go.
Unagiya?
If Brother Ichi’s there,
tell him he doesn’t need to come home.
What’s wrong?
No, nothing…
See you.
Who was it?
Brother’s friend?
Yeah. Ishida.
That’s the first time
I really spoke to him,
but he’s exactly like
Brother Ichi said.
Okay, that should be enough…
You can stop now.
What’s the matter?
You’re awfully quiet.
Aren’t you going to complain?
Want to do another set?
Just kidding.
By now you must’ve built some stamina.
Stamina?
That’s right.
Fullbring is performed
using your flesh and blood.
To fully control it, you need
a crazy amount of stamina.
I see…
So that’s why you put me
through this crazy training…
You recover fast too. That’s good.
When your Fullbring became complete,
you saw something, didn’t you?
I knew it…
You should’ve seen me
glowing as a Spiritual Pressure
with your smashed eyes.
I made you fight without your
sight to make sure of that.
That’s proof that your Soul Reaper
powers are starting to come back.
After you lost your
Spiritual Pressure…
the remnants of your remaining
Spiritual Pressure
laid dormant, collected in one
location for a long time…
That’s why we used
the Spiritual Pressure
that flowed inside of you from your
Combat Pass via Fullbring
to stimulate the
Spiritual Pressure inside
of you and awaken it.
After that, once you build up your
stamina and learn to
control Fullbring fully,
your Soul Reaper powers will merge
on their own with Fullbring…
giving you powers beyond
that of a Soul Reaper.
Here.
Give it a try.
Your Fullbring should
be fully complete now.
Yukio.
On it.
Ginjo…
Impressive.
It’s like you’re
a totally new person.
You’ll need a name…
For your Fullbring.
UNAGIYA
I don’t see their car…
They must not be home…
Welcome back.
Looks like you managed to complete it.
You were taking so long
that I was beginning to worry when the
battery in this thing
was going to run out.
Yeah, sorry to take up your time.
In any case,
you should go home for
today and see your sisters.
They must be worried…
after not hearing from you.
Yikes!
That’s right! I haven’t
called them at all!
How many days have I
been training here?!
Just about one whole day, maybe?
Huh?
That’s because I fast-forwarded
time while you were inside.
You should thank me.
Now go on home.
I’m sure they’re all
anxiously waiting for you.
Now…I can protect them…
My family…
Everyone.
It’s strange…
I can sense the odd Spiritual Pressure,
but they appear to have
no awareness of it…
And I couldn’t ask them
if they had met him.
Inoue said that she was
attacked by the same
guy who attacked me…
If this is all his power’s doing…
Is it possible?!
That was impressive!
He actually managed to
complete his Fullbring…
Now we can say farewell
to our despicable powers.
The question, though, is
how Tsukishima will act…
What’s wrong, guys?
Aren’t you happy?
We finally remembered.
About what?
What we’re supposed to do.
Don’t tell me?!
“Dirty Boots!!”
They’re still up?
I got them worried…
I’m home…
Welcome home!
Thank goodness!
You’re finally back!
Yeah. I’m sorry I’m so late…
We were waiting for you!
Hey, whose shoes are...
An old friend came to visit today!
An old friend? Who?
Guess.
I don’t know without a hint.
Okay, here’s a hint!
He’s one of our cousins!
A cousin?
That’s right! A cousin!
A cousin…?
What cousin do we know
well enough that he’d drop by…?
Brother came home!
Hi, Ichigo.
It’s been a while.
See?
Aren’t you surprised, Brother?
It’s Shu!
We haven’t seen him since Grandpa
Rin’s memorial service…
How many years has it been?
It’s so good to see him again!
He came this evening and
we had dinner together!
It was so nice to have dinner
with Shu after all these years!
He showed up unannounced.
That part of you hasn’t changed, Shu.
Sorry.
Did I cause you guys trouble?
N-No, of course not…
C’mon, Brother!
Say hi to Shu!
Tsukishima!
You bastard!
What’re you doing here?!
Brother?!
Brother Ichi!
Stop it, Brother!
What’re you doing?!
What’s wrong with you, Brother Ichi?!
You’re hurting Shu!
Let him go!
Are you angry that Shu
dropped by without notice?!
What’s wrong with you, Brother Ichi?!
What did you do to Yuzu and Karin?!
Brother!!
Brother Ichi!
It’s all right, Yuzu, Karin.
Ichigo’s always so serious.
He must be angry with
me for staying so late.
Answer me!!
Yuzu…would you mind?
Okay…
It’s probably Keigo and the others.
Hey, good evening, Yuzu.
Hi!
Here, go ahead and use these slippers!
Oh, thanks!
We’re coming in!
Shu, we’re here…
Huh?
Oh, Ichigo’s here, too.
You’re right.
Hey Ichigo!
We hear you’ve been staying
out late these days?!
You should come home earlier!
You’re making Yuzu
and Karin feel lonely!
That’s okay. We’re not lonely!
I asked them to come.
Hi, Shu!
I wanted to see everyone since
it’s been such a long time.
It’s been a while, hasn’t it?
Don’t give me that scary look.
I’m sorry about calling
everyone so late at night,
but tomorrow’s Sunday,
so it’s okay, right?
You know…
maybe I’ll call Chad and Orihime, too.
Orihime? It’s me.
That’s right. Tsukishima.
Huh? What are you talking about?
We met just the other day.
Actually, I’m at
Ichigo’s place now…
What the?!
Mr. Tsukishima!!
Tell me, Tsukishima…
What did you do to everyone?!
Are you all right, Mr. Tsukishima?
Yeah…I’m okay…
You’re not okay!
You’re bleeding!
Tsukishima!
Ichigo!
What’re you doing?!
I don’t know what
you’re so upset about,
but that’s no way
to treat your relative
who you haven’t seen in years!
Relative?!
No! This guy is…
What about him?!
Never mind! Apologize!!
You don’t understand…
Tsukishima is…
Apologize to Mr. Tsukishima!
Ichigo…
Hey Ichigo, what’s gotten into you?
You’re nuts.
Yeah, what happened?
Brother Ichi…
Brother…?
What happened to you?
What’s gotten into you, Brother Ichi?
You should apologize.
Hey!
You’re acting strange, Brother.
Ichigo. Hey, are you okay, Ichigo?
What are you doing?
Ichigo.
You’re to blame, Brother.
Brother Ichi.
You…
Kurosaki?
What’s happening…?
Is this Tsukishima’s power?!
Oh, if it isn’t Ichigo!
What happened?
Now that I look at you
you’re covered in sweat.
What happened?
UNAGIYA
Here, drink this.
Stay here until you calm down…
If you want to tell me about
what happened, tell me.
Thank you… Ms. Ikumi…
Ms. Ikumi…
Forget it! Just be quiet!
Who could it be at this hour?
Coming.
Tell her what happened?
No…
There’s no way I can tell her.
Ms. Ikumi doesn’t know about
Soul Reapers or Hollows or Fullbring…
Telling her such things out of the blue
would only make her uneasy!
Ichigo!
You’re in luck, Ichigo.
Mr. Tsukishima's here to pick you up!
What is this?!
What the hell’s going on?!
Anybody!
Isn’t there
anybody left who's still sane?!
Ichigo!
Ginjo!
He got them!
Riruka…
And Kutsuzawa…
And Yukio…
And Jackie…
Tsukishima got them all!!
Ichigo, make sure to come up with a name
for your Fullbring by the next episode.
What? I have to think of one?
Let’s see…
You better come up with one soon.
Otherwise, we’ll just give it a name
that sounds really embarrassing.
Oh, I have one!
Now that’s a good one!
Huh? What? Wait, what?!
The Complete Quincy
Looks like he ran away again.
What’re you here for?
There’s somewhere I have to go now…
Why don’t you join me?
No thanks.
Even if I told you
that’s where Uryu is?
It’s none of your business.
But if you so insist then I suppose...