Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
Hey…
How long do we have to
stay in a place like this?
I'm so bored.
I'm going to take a look outside.
Don't.
Everyone is not here yet.
"Everyone," you say?
How many more are coming?
Well, I'm not sure.
Who cares about the numbers?
In fact, I wouldn't mind
doing this all alone.
Shut up.
There's no need to
rush into things.
I'll say.
A man without patience
is so unattractive.
Welcome back.
We have a new friend.
Look after him.
Hey, he's pretty good looking…
Listen, how long are we
gonna hang around here?
Just bear it a little longer.
The rest of our comrades
will awaken shortly.
But!
The age of Soul Reapers
will soon end.
Ichigo…
Can't you hear, Ichigo?
This is…my…
Ichigo!
Can't you hear, Ichigo?
What is it?
Sure, I hear your voice…
Not my voice…
Huh?
I don't hear anything.
What're you talking about?
Then forget it.
No, I won't. Hey, Old Man!
Hey…
Roar, Zabimaru!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Lieutenant!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
– Yeah!
– Lieutenant!
– Way to go!
– You can do it!
You haven't forgotten,
have you?
When Senbonzakura is controlled
directly with my hands,
it doubles in speed.
Your slow Bankai is
no defense against it.
Here I come.
Hear my voice.
Hikotsu Taiho!
You used your Bankai there,
didn't you?
Captain? Is something wrong?
No…
Captain?
Wow, that was a great match.
Lieutenant Abarai,
your skills have improved.
Thank you.
Oh, Captain!
That's all for today.
Ah…yes sir.
Thank you very much.
Byakuya?
If you'll excuse me.
What's wrong with him?
Hyorinmaru!
What's wrong?
What was that just now?
Hyorinmaru…
Just come on out already!
Matsumoto!
Come out, Haineko!
Are you refusing to listen to me?!
What part of me is an old lady?!
You'd better watch your mouth!
– Hey…
– Hey, are you listening?!
You are so fresh!
Lazy! Spoiled! Moody!
I'd like to see
the face of the person
who forged such
a hopeless Zanpakuto!
Matsumoto!
What're you hollering about?
Don't scare me like that.
I was just talking
with my Zanpakuto.
That was talking?!
Excuse me.
Hello, Rangiku, Shiro.
Hinamori. Isane.
Will you stop
addressing me like that…
What brings you two here?
Here…
It's a notice for
a lieutenants meeting.
Thanks!
Something wrong, Shiro?
Are you two doing this
on purpose?!
R-Rangiku!
What do you think
you're doing here?
Oh, that?
I'm communicating
with my Zanpakuto.
Our enemies are becoming
more cunning lately.
So we'd better hone our skills too.
And yet that Haineko!
She refuses to manifest today.
She's so useless.
You shouldn't badmouth
your Zanpakuto like that.
You must be more
magnanimous towards it.
When I was feeling depressed,
Tobiume was so concerned about me.
That's when I thought…
I'm not alone.
You mean, even your Zanpakuto
worry about you?
Umm…
Speaking about Zanpakuto…
My Itegumo has also
been slow to respond
these past two or three days.
Yours too, Isane?
Yes. This has never
happened before.
At least it's your first time.
It's constant with Haineko.
It's the first time,
that's why I'm worried.
Oh, Shiro.
Where are you going?
Stupid, I'm still on duty.
Huh?
But we brought over
some sweet baked beans
that we received from
Captain Unohana.
Let's have a tea break, Captain.
These are your
favorite treats, right?
Captain?
I wonder…
What happened back there?
This is it.
We've reached our destination.
Let's start!
Who is it?
Who's there?!
An urgent summons?
What could it be at this hour?
What the—?
An urgent summons?
Captain!
Ukitake!
Captain Hitsugaya.
What's going on?
Calling us out to
a place like this…
I'm not sure either.
No one had heard
about this meeting.
And…
And?
Hey… Kuchiki!
You were summoned too?
Yes. I don't know why,
but I was called out too.
This certainly is an interesting
group of faces to be here.
Are you two standing in
for Captain Zaraki?
We've never been summoned
as the captain's stand-ins.
But our captain and
lieutenant are away.
So if you tell us to stay and
listen in, we have no choice.
Yeah? Where'd they go?
I'm not sure.
It happens all the time.
Why did the Head Captain
call us out at such an hour?
Damn… This fog is nasty.
Lieutenant Sasakibe.
What's going on?
Where is the Head Captain?
C-Captain?!
Stay alert for
the slightest presence.
He's in cardiac arrest.
He's in danger!
Start resuscitation immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
The Head Captain
isn't coming here.
Who the hell are you?!
You said the Head Captain
isn't coming…
Captain!
What did you do
to Sir Genryusai?!
You refuse to answer?
Well then…
I'll beat the answer
out of your body!
The guy's quite interesting.
Want to go for it, Ikkaku?
Stop. Can't you see my Captain
is fighting right now?
Try to interfere,
and you'll get hurt.
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
You will tell us where
Sir Genryusai is!
Your attack won't reach me.
Don't kid yourself!
Look out!
C-Captain!
What just happened?!
A Zanpakuto attacked
its master?!
No way…
What's going on anyway?!
This is interesting!
Who are you?
Are you…Tenken?
W-What?!
Captain!
Wait!
Let go, Ayasegawa!
Rein over the frosted heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Sting all enemies to death!
Suzumebachi.
Captain!
I can't do Shikai!
Impossible…
Roar, Zabimaru!
Growl, Haineko!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
What's going on?
I don't feel any Spiritual Pressure
in my Zanpakuto!
Why…Tobiume?!
Wabisuke?!
Indeed… The Spiritual Pressure
is definitely gone.
What's the meaning of this?
It's simple.
You are no longer one
with your Zanpakuto.
I freed them from
the Soul Reapers.
Our Zanpakuto?
Is that even possible?
What?!
What did you do?!
It wasn't me.
It's your Zanpakuto who are
doing the destruction.
Impossible!
The Zanpakuto have been released
from the Soul Reaper's spell!
What is it?!
Put out the fire! Quickly!
There's something over there!
Who is it?!
Is it a ryoka?!
What is he?!
So easy!
He's so barbaric.
Hello.
Hurry and make a run for it.
I'm sorry, but I have no time
to play with you all.
Forget it. You guys are
no match for me.
Let us go. We are summoned.
This was just an introduction.
So you would understand
the power of my comrades.
And this is…the true appearance
of the Zanpakuto
which you deluded
yourselves into owning!
The Zanpakuto
manifested themselves?!
That's insane!
Is that possible?
Oh dear…
Out of the way!
You?!
Brother…
Just who are you?
My name is Muramasa.
Tonight marks the end of
the Soul Reapers' reign
over the Zanpakuto.
From here on, the Zanpakuto
will rule over the Soul Reapers.
What are you upset about, Ichigo?
I bet I don't get much screen time
for this new story arc, am I right?
Isn't the next episode where you
get to show off some action?
I doubt it…
Pretty skeptical, aren't you?
You'll end up losing more screen
time with that sort of attitude.
I'm very sorry. I promise to do
my best in the next episode!
Today's segment is on
Ichigo Kurosaki's Zangetsu.
Zangetsu is a type of Zanpakuto
that is always in released form.
Its Bankai is Tensa Zangetsu.
Getsugatensho
unleashes a slashing attack
using ultra-condensed
Spiritual Pressure.
Its manifestation is a man attired
in black from head to toe.
That's today's lesson
on Zanpakuto.
You will find it useful
for this story arc.
Oh… So that's what this is for?