Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
This is the Sokyoku hill?
Welcome, Abarai.
Captain Aizen? It can't be…
What's…
going on?
Leave Rukia Kuchiki here
and back away.
C-Captain Aizen?!
Why are you alive--?
No, never mind that…
What did you say?
How odd.
You must have heard me.
I said, “Leave Rukia Kuchiki here
and back away.”
Abarai.
Hearts of the South,
Eyes of the North,
Fingertips of the West,
Heels of the East…
Gather holding the winds,
scatter sweeping the rains.
Bakudo 58!
Kakushitsuijaku!
31…64…
83…97…
I've pinpointed where they went!
332 East, 1566 North!
It’s the Sokyoku!
Understood.
Now locate every captain
and lieutenant and
report to them everything
we've learned here
about Sosuke Aizen
and where he’s gone to.
Yes.
And…get the message to
those Ryoka as well.
I understand!
I'm counting on you.
I must now try to save the lives
of Captain Hitsugaya and
Lieutenant Hinamori.
Black and white net!
Twenty-second bridge,
Sixty-six crown and cincture!
Footprints! Distant thunder!
Sharp arrow, rotating land,
cover of night!
Sea of clouds, pale soldiers!
Form a circle and
charge through the heavens!
Bakudo 77.
Tenteikura!
Connection…established!
Attention all Thirteen Court
Guard Squads captains,
lieutenants, and seated officers…
And also the Ryoka.
This is Squad 4 Lieutenant,
Isane Kotetsu.
Sis?
This is an emergency.
This is an emergency announcement…
from Squad 4 Captain Retsu Unohana
and me, Isane Kotetsu.
Everything I am about to
tell you is the truth!
I-Impossible!
Aizen did--?
You heard her.
What shall we do,
Old Man Yama?
Don't you think now's not
the best time to be doing this?
I can't believe…
that my Captain lost!
How could he?
He said he wouldn't harm Hinamori…
Central 46 was…annihilated?!
That can't be true…
My Captain betrayed us?!
Tosen!
Did you hear that, Sir Mayuri?
Of course I did.
What shall we do?
Humph! I’m not interested.
You think all this is true?
Hmm… It could also be
the enemy's trap…
No… It seems to be true.
Huh?
Kurosaki, don't you sense
the Spiritual Pressure
that just appeared up above?!
Rukia?!
What?
I said I refuse…
Captain Aizen!
I see.
That won't be necessary, Gin.
You are stubborn, Abarai.
If you don't want to leave Rukia Kuchiki
and back away,
then you leave me no choice.
But I'll take your feelings
into consideration.
She can stay in your arms…
but the rest of you goes.
R-Renji…!
My my…
You've learned to dodge well, Abarai.
I’m happy to see that
you’ve improved.
But I hope you won’t struggle
for too long.
It's difficult to step on
an ant without crushing it.
As your former superior,
I’d prefer not to kill you if I can help it.
Renji!
Shut up, Rukia!
You don’t want to kill me?
Yeah right!
Then why did you kill Hinamori?!
I’d trained her so that
she couldn’t live without me.
So don't you think it was merciful
of me to kill her?
It's also true that
I didn't want to kill her myself.
So I went to all the trouble…
and tried to have her, Kira and
Hitsugaya kill each other.
But that didn't work out.
So I had no choice
but to kill her myself.
I see…
So you were the one pulling the strings
on Kira and Hinamori!
And you too, Abarai.
I get it.
You're not the Captain Aizen
I knew.
I don't know why you want her,
but I'm not handing over Rukia
even if it costs me my life!
Not the Sosuke Aizen
you knew, huh?
Unfortunately,
the Sosuke Aizen you used to know
was just an illusion, Abarai.
He never existed
in the first place.
Roar! Zabimaru!
Shikai, huh?
I guess it can't be helped with
the condition you're in,
but that won't even buy you
any time.
You never know!
What a bothersome kid you are.
He stopped it with
his bare hands?!
You really are the most troublesome
of the three, Abarai.
Renji!
I knew…
I knew that I could use you three
when I first met you.
So when you three joined
the Thirteen Court Guard Squads,
I had you all assigned to
Squad 5 right away.
Then I made the two who
were more useful,
Gin and my subordinates.
I sent you away because
you seemed troublesome.
It seems my instincts were right.
This is the last warning.
Leave Rukia Kuchiki here
and back away.
P-Please wait, Captain Aizen!
I will…
I refuse.
Renji!
Ren…
I won't let you go…
Like I’d ever let you go…
You idiot.
I see.
Too bad.
Hey.
What's wrong,
crouching down like that?
It looks like Rukia is
too heavy for you.
I came to give you a hand, Renji!
Ichigo…
Hey.
You came to help me…
Thank--.
What's this?
All you had to do was carry Rukia
and you’re all beat up!
I guess just running away was still
a too big of a task for you, huh?!
Huh? What was that?!
You look pretty beat up
yourself, too!
What did you say?!
Is that something you say to someone
who just came to save your butt?!
You idiot! I was trying
to thank you earlier!
Hmm?
Oh…
Idiot!
Do you think I'm trying to make
a new world record for holding my breath?!
Talking while pushing me against
your chest like that!
Sorry. I didn't think I should interfere,
so I let the boy pass.
No matter. It's fine.
There’s no difference
whether there’s one piece of dust
to brush off, or two.
That’s Aizen?
Yeah.
Do you still have enough strength left
to get away?
Yeah, but I'm going to stay
and fight.
You know damn well that running away
won’t do, don’t you?
We may not be able
to defeat them,
but let's try to immobilize them
and walk out of here.
Hah! I got no choice.
All right, then!
Let's fight together!
Right!
I can only use this technique once…
But if it hits,
the enemy will be left open.
Strike in that opening.
Got it!
This may hurt a bit
but please hang in there, Zabimaru…
Here we go, Zabimaru!
Higazekko!
Huh?!
Oh?
I thought I cut you in half from
the waist down,
but it seems it was too shallow.
That’s… impossible…
He disappe…
Da…mn…
Ichigo…
Renji…!
I can't…move!
Now stand…
Rukia Kuchiki.
Hm?
Oh, I see.
My Spiritual Pressure has
caused your body to go limp.
Ichigo!
The poor thing.
He’s still conscious.
Having too much life force
without abilities to back it up
may work against you.
Give up already.
You've all been useful enough.
You’ve served your purpose.
Purpose…?
That's right.
I knew that you would enter through
the West Rukon District.
That’s why I had Squads stationed
around the area
so that Gin could be
there if something happened.
The walls of the Seireitei
were lowered,
and there were captains
within the gates,
so the only way to get in
would be with Kukaku Shiba's
Flower-Crane Cannon.
A very flashy entry.
And those intruders were skilled
enough to get past a captain.
As a result,
the eyes of all the Soul Reapers
within Seireitei focused on them.
Your actions after entering the court
were quite impressive indeed.
And thanks to you,
the news of a murdered captain
did not create too much fuss.
It really made it easy to
make my move.
H-Hold on.
How did you know
that we would come in through
the West Rukon District?
What a strange thing to ask.
Where else could it be?
The West Rukon District is
Kisuke Urahara's base of operations.
West Rukon District is the only place
you could’ve entered through
with his Senkaimon.
What's with that face?
You work for him, don’t you?
Didn't you come to retrieve Rukia Kuchiki
under Kisuke Urahara's orders?
Wh-What do you…
I see. It seems you weren't
told anything.
Oh well.
This is the end anyway,
so I’ll tell you.
Did you know that Soul Reapers
have four basic fighting methods?
Zanjutsu, Hakuda, Hoho, and Kido.
Those are the four.
But there is a limit to how strong
you can get in any one of them.
There’s a limit to how much
a soul can take
and that’s where the growth stops.
In other words,
there’s the limit as a Soul Reaper.
Is there any way to get past that
and surpass the limits
of those four abilities
to get stronger then?
Well, there's a way.
That's…
to become a Hollow.
A Soul Reaper to a Hollow,
or a Hollow to a Soul Reaper…
Only by removing the border
between those two opposing existences,
can one become
an even greater existence.
In theory, it was thought
to be plausible.
So I secretly tried to turn
various Hollows
into Soul Reapers.
A Hollow that could hide
its Spiritual Pressure,
or a Hollow that could
destroy Zanpakuto
with a touch and fuse
with Soul Reapers.
But none of them worked out
as well as I had hoped.
In the end,
nobody could find a way.
But Kisuke Urahara made a way.
It was something that
could instantly remove
the border dividing Hollow
and Soul Reaper,
something that defied all logic
within the Soul Society.
It's called Hogyoku.
Dangerous stuff.
He probably felt the same way.
He tried to destroy
the Hogyoku.
But he was unable to find a way
to destroy his own creation.
So he reluctantly resorted
to another method.
That was to create
a shield around the Hogyoku
and hide it somewhere deep
within a Konpaku, soul.
Now do you understand?
The place he chose to hide it
was within you, Rukia Kuchiki.
What…did you say?
But when I found that out,
you had already gone missing
in the World of the Living.
I instinctively knew Kisuke Urahara
had something to do with it.
He was once exiled from
the Soul Society
for creating an untraceable gigai
that contained no Reishi.
There’s no other way a Soul Reaper
in gigai can go missing.
There was another reason
why he was exiled.
That gigai continues to break down
the spirit energy
of the Soul Reaper using it.
Because of that,
the Soul Reaper
never recovers his power.
The connection with
the gigai becomes dim
to the point that all of
his spirit energies are lost.
His Konpaku is reduced to
that of a mere human.
Do you understand now?
He didn't help you.
He was just trying to hide
the location of the Hogyoku
by turning you into a human.
Oh my.
You look like you’re in trouble.
Can I help you?
With a gigai may be?
But luckily, you were found
in the World of the Living
a few months later.
I immediately went to Central 46 and…
Aizen!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Did everyone understand
what I was talking about?
I tried to make it simple enough for
even stupid people to understand.
What did you say?!
We just met! How did you know
that I'm stupid, you jerk!
You don't deny that
you're stupid, huh.
Hey, you're making me blush.
Jinta's Unbeatable Diary!
What's with this guy?
Why is he after me so much?
Hey…
He’s obviously not after the ball…
What is he…?
I get it! It's this!
Bostov
I don’t know why…
but he's after this strap from the goddess.
All right then.
I'll take you on!
Tune in again!