DIALOGUE
If I can't win alone, then I'll win as a group.
I'll defeat you with my next attack!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Smash...
Hagurotonbo!!
Butcher her!
Kubikiriororchi!
Did we get her?
Not yet.
She's so persistent!
Cascada!
Ryusenka!
Lord... Aizen...?
I'm done with you.
It seems you aren't strong enough to fight for me.
I-I don't understand...
Isn't it obvious?
Even if I made any more of you sacrifice yourselves, it would achieve nothing.
That is what I have decided.
No world is without sacrifices.
This is it... There is nowhere for you to run.
The weaker become a part of the stronger.
That is the law of Las Noches.
I'm going to be devoured by this guy...
It looks like you've given up.
Don't worry.
I'll devour your consciousness as well.
Just pray that I'll become an even greater Adjuchas and live on.
Who's there?!
What's this? You're pretty small.
Do you want me to devour you first?!
You...?!  That's not possible...
Who is this?
A female?! But the size of her Spiritual Pressure...
It's not that of an Adjuchas...
Could she be a Vasto Lorde?!
It's no good... I can't move.
Well, I suppose getting devoured by her is much better than some disgusting male Adjuchas...
Come with me.
What did you just say?
I'm telling you to come with me.
Welcome back, ma'am.
Yeah.
Oh, who is that?
A new comrade.
A comrade? Me?
That's right.
What's the meaning of this?!
You may have saved me, but I didn't ask for your help and I'm not grateful to you!
Despite having to be saved, you sure talk big!
What did you say?!
Stop it, both of you.
You're both about equal in your insolence and cockiness.
Huh?!
What gives you the right to look down on us, huh?!
Because I am looking down on you, see?
You bitch!
Stop it... Sun-sun, Mila Rose...
Yes, ma'am...
Sorry about that.
Do you have a name? What is it?
...Apache.
I have no ulterior motive for bringing you here.
We women are easy prey for the males.
I brought you here because I thought that
it would be better if we worked in a group, rather than working alone.
There's no need to chase him down.
Yes, ma'am.
Understood.
Humph!
If he attacks us again, I'll bite off that thing between his legs!
My. Your mouth is filthier than your looks.
Huh?!
You never know when to shut up!
Such attitude! And you call yourself a woman?
Sun-Sun, you bitch!
What's wrong? Can't sleep?
Oh... No, it's just...
Why don't you kill or devour the guys who attack you?
In Hueco Mundo, if you want to protect yourself
you must become stronger.
That's why everyone devours lower ranked Hollows and Adjuchas to make themselves bigger.
So why don't you do this?
I don't want to become stronger through the power I gain by killing and sacrificing another.
If I can't win alone, then I'll win as a group.
That's all there is to it.
No world is without sacrifices.
But if we produce casualties,
we would also sustain casualties of our own.
Oh, no!
Sorry, ma'am.
Don't push yourself.
I want to be like her someday...
Humph! Just to let you know,
if you get in trouble doing something reckless, I won't risk my life to save you!
Well, I won't save you either, stupid!
What?!
It's sweet that you two are getting along, but try not to die together, okay?
What did you say?!
You again? What do you want?
Don't make me repeat myself, Halibel.
It is annoying to see you play around in my sight.
However, it would be a waste to kill someone of your power.
Therefore...
I've come to you today with two choices.
The first one, as I have asked you before,
is to join my army.
And the other one?
Vanish to a place where I cannot see you.
Of course, there is no place in Las Noches that I cannot see!
Halibel! Do you understand?!
You have no choice but to become subservient to Lord Barragan!
Don't touch me.
Stop!
Striking one of my subordinates before my eyes...
How bold of you.
You will regret your decision.
Whoa... There are lots of powerful looking Hollows here.
What's wrong?
Did you find something interesting?
No.
It's nothing of much importance.
That aside, since we're here,
let us pay our respects
to the king of Hueco Mundo.
Humph! They're no match at all!
You've been getting pretty bold lately.
You're right.
Although back when we faced Barragan, you two were trembling in fear.
What did you say?!
That aside, do you know that there are some strange rumors about Barragan recently?
Rumors?
Yes. Something about him having many incredibly powerful soldiers with cracked masks.
Masks... What's that suppose to mean?!
That's none of our concern!
Master Halibel and the three of us can handle them.
Who are you?!
I found you...
His mask is cracked.
Then he's...?!
Master Halibel!
Halibel... Long time no see!
You're...
That's right. You remember now.
You made me look like quite a fool.
What is this sensation?!
This incredible Spiritual Pressure...
No Adjuchas could handle this!
It might even be stronger than a Vasto Lorde like Master Halibel!
What?!
Can't understand what's going on, can you? Of my transformation!!
Master Halibel!
Don't worry.
I won't devour you three.
I'll wipe you all out without a trace!
You still want to fight?
You're not a very smart female!
Master Halibel!
I want all of you to run away!
But...
Just run away!
Yes, ma'am!
It seems like you comprehend the difference in our strength.
No matter.
I just want to kill you.
I don't care about those small fry.
Hey, are we just going to run away?
We have no choice.
Master Halibel told us to run away.
We couldn't have done anything about him.
Lord Barragan told you that you'd regret it!
Hueco Mundo will undergo big changes.
I'll eliminate nuisances like you, and then join the top ranks!
Die!
Sun-sun!
Apache!
Mila Rose!
You bitches!
Listen up! We'd do anything, even sacrifice ourselves, for Master Halibel!
Don't think we'll go down so easily!
Take a listen to the newcomer...
She's so cocky.
But I'm with her.
Same here.
All of you...!
I don't want to become stronger through the power I gain by killing and sacrificing another.
If only I didn't think that way...
Your sacrifices will not go to waste!
What can you do?!
What?!
I'll defeat you with my next attack!
Don't underestimate me.
Your sword cannot penetrate my Hierro!
Not yet... It's not over yet!
I will continue to torment you!
Die!
That power... I suppose it's only natural for an Arrancar.
Wh-Why?! A-Aizen--
With the power of sacrifice
it is possible to do the impossible.
I'm sorry.
I gave him Arrancar powers.
But it looks like I didn't give him the brain to control it.
Who are you?
If you do not want to produce casualties, then gain power.
If the power you seek is your ideal...
I can give it to you.
My ideal?
You want to become stronger
for your comrades, don't you?
If you gain power, you won't produce any more casualties.
That is your ideal.
Don't you want to see what your ideal looks like?
I want you to come with me.
I shall lead you to your ideal.
I won't make you sacrifice yourselves like you did just now.
Even if I made any more of you sacrifice yourselves, it would achieve nothing.
That is what I have decided.
I didn't expect this outcome.
I went through a lot of trouble to gather you Espadas.
I never expected
your gathered strengths to be inferior to that of mine.
Aizen!
How troublesome.
What?!
Don't make me go through the effort
to swing my sword twice on the likes of you.
No world is without sacrifices.
Doesn't he realize it?
This sea of blood covered in ashes...
We refer to this hell
as the world.
Now, shall we begin?
13 Court Guard Squads, and you failed mock Arrancars...
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
Hmph! Finally, I get my chance to show them what I'm made of!
Don't get too excited, Hiyori.
The main protagonist of this show hasn't appeared in a while.
Which means he might show up soon.
Shinji! Make sure you don't call him, no matter what! You hear me?!
Why the hell would I?
I'll make sure to it that this is over before Ichigo gets here!
Monster cats who talk and control people are appearing in large numbers.
I know of one of them...
But a large number of them?
Whoa!
What the hell?!
I'm going to teach you a phrase you can use to control humans.
"I want... tuna!"
I want... tuna!
That's right! I want tuna!
I want tuna!
That's right!
What are you doing?