Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamed D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
Even though it's a bit too late,
they've begun to notice…
What should we do?
This is a good opportunity…
Show them your power.
Kariya, what about you?
Is there a need for me
to do anything?
Ugaki, you give out the orders!
And call back the Bitto.
That should be enough for now…
He's acting every inch the leader.
Don't you think so?
Is there anyone other than
Kariya who's fit to lead?
I don't think it would
be wise to defy him…
I'll obey Kariya.
Agreed. It would be best to obey him
even if we have problems
with him.
Whoops. Not that I have any…
Is it all right to let them go?
It's probably a good chance
for them
to test the power of the living souls
that the Bitto have given them…
I’ll be returning to my room.
Release Mabashi.
Yes!
Renji's Spiritual Pressure is…
What's the meaning of this…?!
Did something happen to Renji…?!
Hey! Pokey head!
It's completed! It's completed!
Urahara's new Bount sensor, huh?!
Yes. Here you go!
Th-This is…
Ooh. It's sure a strange shape…
What is this?
It's all right.
You know what to do!
He said that it's a rush job,
so it's not too good…
He said that there's a fifteen-minute
time limit once it’s switched on!
Oh yeah, and the switch is
the password written over there!
Hey! Why are you hesitating!
Use it already!
Do I have to?
What are you talking about?!
We're racing against the clock!
You screamed that once before!
Good luck!
Here I go…
Feel the power of justice!
Equip! Justice Armor, Justice Bandana!
It really is a switch…
I'm surprised you can say
something so embarrassing…
You told me to say it…
Huh?
What's going on?!
He said that it would lead you
in the direction of the Bounts!
Hey! Can I stop this?
It's impossible.
All right. Ichigo, leave Renji to me.
You go that way!
All right. Take care of it!
Ow…
Come to think of it,
I can't sense the Good-For-Nothing's
Spiritual Pressure anymore.
Did he die?
You shouldn't say that…
Let's take a look!
He's probably that way!
Jinta, are you actually
worried about him?
Ow…!
Don't be silly! Who would worry
about such a big eater!
Your face is red despite saying that.
Shut up! I just want to
see him looking stupid!
Thank you very much.
Why do I feel like eating junk food
as soon as night falls?
It sure is strange!
Huh?
What's that?
Wh-What? Killer bees?
Vampire bats?
CG? Special Effects?
No way!
Help me!
I wonder if I was hallucinating…
I've got to get home
and go to sleep…
Th-This can't be happening…
H-Hold on a second…
This is a pretty realistic…dream, isn't it?
They might be nearby!
Someone’s there!
Keigo!
His soul! They're sucking out his soul!
What?!
Keigo!
Move aside! You're in the way!
Get away, you bastard!
Keigo!
Get a hold of yourself! Hey!
Who is that?!
It's the Bount from before!
I'm Go Koga,
What in the world
did you do to Keigo?
I don't plan on talking…
Sorry, but I'm going to crush you!
Zeig Dih, Dalk!
Hello!
How are you?!
Wonderful! This feeling is enchanting!
Did she always look like that?
Something's a little different about her…
My body's tingling…
I'm flushed! Look at me!
You're my type…
I want to chase you rather
than be chased…
Ichigo!
It's heavy!
Sh-She's…
Oh my. Are your hands numb?
It seems that I've changed…
This body…
I'll let you have a good taste of it.
Ichigo!
Oh my. That bandana matched you.
I'm sorry!
She's faster than before…
Not only that, but she's become
heavier and tougher…
Are you finished testing him, Dalk?
Yes…
You're pretty good!
But I don't have the time to
be fighting with you!
I've got to save Keigo!
Oh, how wonderful! How manly!
I can't feel his
Spiritual Pressure anymore!
What's going on?
He's either fainted or
lost his fighting spirit…
Or…
Or?
Hey!
Inoue!
Kuchiki?!
Where's Renji?
I don't know…
He should be around here…
We suddenly couldn't sense
his Spiritual Pressure, but…
Could it be that Renji is…
Where's Kurosaki?
I had him go in the direction
of the Bounts.
He's using Store Owner's
handmade sensor…
I don't know if he found them…
Lirin went with him.
You should join Ichigo!
What about you?
I'm going to search for Renji.
Something out of the ordinary
must have happened!
All right.
Look out!
What's this?!
Aim a little better!
I'm terrible with details!
Isn't it better to kill two
or three of them at once?
Why not? Whether you slice them
or crush them,
it's the same thing so long
as you defeat them…
You're right…
Leave this to me and go!
But…
Ururu, go to where Sado is!
Jinta, I'll leave Renji to you!
Huh? Me?
You're his friend, after all!
We're not friends!
Here she comes!
Scatter!
Hado 33! Sokatsui!
I'd rather fight a man than
a woman…
It's all the same as long
as you defeat her…
I thought you'd say that.
Inoue?!
Let me help!
Two are better than one!
Ahem!
If I may speak out, make that three.
You two…
You're going to tell us where Kariya is!
And what you plan to do!
I wonder about that…
This feels good!
Sorry. Did I hit you?
Crap!
You have a bad habit of toying
with your prey.
Really?
We're fighting for our lives.
I should let him taste
extreme fear and pain.
It's too tragic not to know
when you'll die.
You guys sure like to talk!
Treating me like some
minor character…
How manly of you!
Well then!
Accept my feelings!
Get out of the way!
More, more!
Oh?
Don't touch Keigo!
Are you all right?!
I'll save you soon. Don't worry!
Ichigo…
You…
He can see Soul Reapers, huh?
That means that quite a bit of his soul
has been sucked out…
He can't be saved.
I'm going to take Keigo with me!
It's pointless.
Even if you returned his soul to him,
his body wouldn't be able
to take the load.
What do you plan to accomplish
by collecting souls
with those strange bugs?
You see it now, don't you?
This is the power that I received from
the souls that the Bitto concentrated…
We plan to absorb more of this
And attain the ultimate power
to achieve our goal.
Ichigo…
Run…away…
Keigo!
Oh my. I guess he didn't
have enough.
Getsugatensho!
Keigo…I’ll…get you right away…
That's pretty good…
But not good enough.
That was a good attack…
But it won't work against us.
I'm enjoying this.
This is fun!
She said to join Kurosaki.
He went to where the Bounts are.
All right.
You children…
Run away quickly!
They won't fall for
my hallucinations forever!
What's wrong?
I have to save Keigo.
No!
His soul was already sucked out!
We can't save him
even if we go…
I can't save anyone if
I can't save Keigo right now.
Not even myself!
That's right.
There is no one who can
save another…
That's either arrogance
or an illusion.
What?!
I won't forgive you if you run away
before I'm finished…
Ichigo!
I'm not letting you
get away anymore!
You're not getting away…
What?!
You fell for it!
Take this, and this!
Oh my… is that it?
Good bye.
What?!
What's this?!
Don't refer to someone
as “this,” you idiot!
Who are you?
Who am I?
Don't ask me stupid things!
I'm me!
I thought you were just
a regular Soul Reaper, but…
Ichigo's the one who's regular!
I'm not soft like he is!
I'd like to say that this
doesn't involve me,
but it would be a problem
if I'm crushed.
I'm going to crush you!
Oh my. Does that mean that
you fight a little better?
Want to test me?
Of course!
Too slow!
Don't treat me like Ichigo!
He doesn't even compare to me!
No…
Y-You…!
Again?! You're going
to interfere with me again?!
You're weak!
If you chase me out right now,
you'll die!
Don't you understand?
Ichigo…
You need strong feelings
in order to use strong power.
What…did you say?
You don't have enough of that.
That's why you cannot
control your power.
Shut up!
Unfortunately, you gained
power imperfectly.
Because of that, you will
destroy yourself in the near future…
Before that happens…
Zeig Dih, Dalk!
Oh my, what happened?
Dalk, this is over.
How boring.
Don't make him suffer too much.
All right!
Hey! Freeloader!
Good-for-nothing!
H-Hey!
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
The flowers glow and fade away.
The sky falls silent,
as a pair of
dreamy fireworks (Hanabi) lit up.
I will sing my piercing love to you.
Can you hear my voice?
Blooming in an instant
are fireworks (Hanabi)
Sky blue dreams shine and flicker,
dancing away into the sky.
Blossom away in full bloom, high above
Protect and keep those feelings thriving
Strongly, at least till the very end.
These flowers will glow and fade away
I'm Kon, the best soothing-type character
of the Bleach world!
Where have my parts gone lately?!
Let me participate!
The next episode
we'll give you three stories:
“Kurodo's Transformation,”
“The Secret of the Birth of Dolls,”
and “A Helper Arrives.”
Tune in!
No we’re not!
The Golden Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
Lieutenant?!
Why “Baldy,” why are you at
a hairdresser's if you're a baldy?
Does it matter?
Say, say, I'm going to draw
a line with a marker
to differentiate your head
from your face, is that…
It's not okay!
This is called a shaved head…
Thank you very much!
Captain Komamura!
I'm going to mark a line
on Komakoma
to differentiate his face
from his head as well!
Wait!
Look at me!