Baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy,
baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy!
Midget!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
...I wanna change.
I wanna chAngE
Let's go.
Kick!
Let's end this, Aizen.
I missed?
Don't be ridiculous.
You hit me.
Komamura...
I'm sorry, Captain Komamura.
Please let me join this battle.
Hisagi...
Mashiro... Super Kick!
Oh dear...
She defeated him quite easily.
I feel sorry for Wonderweiss.
Fura was his favorite.
Mashiro...
Drop Kick!
Whoa, the poor thing.
Yeah! Victory!
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
What is it? Make it short!
And if it's about who we
are, then forget it!
I don't care about that anymore.
I need a favor.
I know I shouldn't be asking
this of strangers like you,
but could you take care
of this Espada?
I...want to fight Aizen.
You're okay with that?
Excuse me?!
What are you, stupid?!
We came here to murder
that baldy Aizen!
Instead, we saw you guys getting
your asses whooped and decided
to save your butts,
albeit reluctantly.
So why the hell should we let
you fight Aizen first, huh?!
Y-You're right... I was
being a bit impatient.
Forget what I just said.
Forget it?! Is that all?!
You should be saying "I'm
sorry" or something!
S-Sorry.
Huh?! I can't hear you!
Sorry!
Look at me!
What kind of apology is that?!
You aren't putting any feeling into it!
I told you, I'm sorry!
Ha! That aside, why's a kid like you
wearing a captain's uniform?!
Are you really a captain?!
I thought you were just pretending
to be a captain!
I told you I was sorry.
I know the truth! I'll tell you!
You think you're hot stuff because you
were able to become a captain,
by doing something sneaky I might
add, even though you're just a kid.
That's why you're able to say
such dumb things like that!
You baldy!
Baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy,
baldy, baldy, baldy, baldy!
Midget!
Midget
You're even shorter than I am!
Just shut up and cooperate,
you midget!
What's the big idea, kid?!
You want to fight?!
If you want a fight,
I'll give it to you!
You're the one who's
trying to pick a fight!
I was trying to apologize, but you
just kept on ragging on me!
Whoa! Now you're
touching me?!
Watch where you touch
a lady, you pervert!
Per...perv...?!
What did you call me?!
Pervert, pervert, pervert, pervert,
pervert, pervert, pervert, pervert!
Shut up! Stop whining, you brat!
Look at that! You touched
me again, you pervert!
That's enough!
It's okay to be interested in
a girl's body. I understand.
You've got it all wrong!
I'm going on ahead of you.
Hey! Wait, Lisa!
You're my first opponent, huh?
I thought I was going to fight
you three against one.
What a coincidence.
I was thinking...
the same thing!
Let's settle this later.
Let's go!
Okay!
It's finally three against one.
That's a good handicap.
Take a look. He looks strong.
Are you sure you want to
remove your masks?
We can only keep them
on for three minutes.
We're heroes, after all.
Now then... Let's begin.
That gun can fire Ceros?!
Hey! Stop dodging!
Ouch! What was
that for, Stark?!
I can't hit things properly
when you come out!
I told you not to touch
my butt, you pervert!
I told you, I can't tell
where your butt is!
Liar! You do it knowingly...
Ow-ow-ow!
Hey...
Who are you?
Who the hell is this unusually
large guy?
On top of that, he's
super strong.
It's been a while...
Soi Fon.
Is he a friend of
yours, Captain?!
You should have told me!
Who is this unusually
large guy?!
Tell me...
I don't know.
I've never seen him before.
I thought you'd say that.
You don't think very
highly of us.
I suppose it's only natural.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter who you are
or what powers you have.
Those things are meaningless to me.
All are equal before my power.
Now then... Turn to
bones and perish.
Respira.
Kido, huh?
I've seen that you have the power
to age the things you touch.
That is why I have come here.
All powers are equal if they
do not make contact.
I have nothing to fear
from your powers.
A-Amazing!
This guy is really extraordinary!
I see...
What do you plan to do?
It's no good!
His barrier...
That's impossible...
Hisagi...
Are his injuries healed?
No... I don't even
need to ask him that.
He's obviously
pushing himself.
It's been a while,
Captain Tosen.
I've come to express
my gratitude.
Interesting choice of words.
Are you being sarcastic?
No. I want to thank you for everything
you've taught me.
I've learned many
things from you.
I'm really grateful.
So now...
I'll use every skill you've taught me
to make you come to your senses.
And I'll bring you back
to the Soul Society!
You? Make me come
to my senses?
You haven't changed.
Suzumushi.
Hisagi, I thought I told you...
"Those who do not know fear
have no right to go into battle."
You haven't changed at all.
Even now, your words don't have
a shred of fear in them.
Behind you, Hisagi!
You do not know true fear...
You cannot defeat me!
Hey, midget! Stop
getting in my way!
Can't you thank me
for saving you?!
Who told you to save me?!
I didn't, baldy!
What?!
Halibel is really going all
out against those three.
Don't you agree?
And here I thought I
could ambush you.
But you already knew...
No matter.
In that case...
Let's fight head on.
Aizen.
Foolish ants...
Did you think that Kido
does not age?
How laughable!
People die, animals die, plants die,
and even Soul Reapers die.
Aging exists in anything
that dies.
The things that people
create die.
The Kido that Soul Reapers
create is no different.
There may be Kido that can
last for a thousand years,
but there is no Kido that
can continue for eternity.
It's only natural!
"Eternity" is a delusion that was
created out of fear of aging!
Let's get out, Captain Soi Fon!
We're no match for him!
Let's swallow our pride and get
help from the other captains.
Shut up and be quiet!
I'm starting to get bored
of playing with ants.
Let's end this.
Now then...
Perish!
I told you that it would rot.
The head, unable to retreat, falls
unto the depths of the sea...
And atones for its sins in bolts
of blue, white, black, and red.
A follow-up incantation...
Chants added to Kido without an incantation
in order to strengthen a barrier.
How clever. But...
You're not going to
make it in time!
Gate of the Dragon Tail!
This completes it!
That's an impressive trick.
Soi Fon!
Please lend me your strength!
From the captain?
I need the power
of your Bankai!
You even know about
my Bankai?
That man...
He never ceases to annoy me.
I can understand you not
wanting to work with us,
who are associated
with Urahara.
But you must also
understand this...
This isn't the time to be
saying things like that!
Very well then.
I'll offer you a deal.
A deal?
How worthless.
Even something as
grand as this
is only good enough to buy
yourself some time.
Rot!
Gate of the Tiger Fang!
Gate of the Turtle Armor!
Gate of the Phoenix Wing!
Shiju Saimon!
How laughable!
Do you think you've
sealed me away?!
How ridiculous!
You really are just trying to
buy yourself some time!
I control aging. Trying to buy yourself
time is like spitting at a god.
Though I suppose I should commend
your pitiful efforts.
That barrier is not meant
to seal you away.
What?
You avoided Captain
Soi Fon's Bankai
by releasing your aging powers
on it to detonate it before it hit,
and directed the blast
away from you.
In that case,
if you were in a place where you couldn't
escape the force of the blast,
and if you were at a distance
at which your aging powers
couldn't work fast enough...
What would happen?
Y-You bastards!
Promise me once more
that tomorrow you'll trap Kisuke Urahara
in one of your barriers for a month.
I promise.
All right.
You puny ants...
Jakuho Raikoben.
Go.
Oh, dear...
It looks like another one of
your allies has gone down.
I give the king of Hueco Mundo
my deepest condolences.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
Echo out from here!
koko kara hibike
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
Decay is my companion.
The world is my servant.
As crows pick away
at this body,
I'll be waiting for you
at the elm mansion.
The Seven Wonders
of Karakura Town!
The Seven Wonders of Karakura Town
Secrets revealed.
Hey, Ichigo, do you know about
this town's seven wonders?
Seven wonders?
Our town has seven
urban legends.
One of them involves
our school.
Late at night when
nobody's around,
you can sometimes hear guitar noises
coming from the music room.
This is some terrible
guitar playing.
Hey!
You there!
I'll perform a Konso on you,
so stop that terrible guitar playing.