Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
Are you surprised?
This is the first time
you're seeing this, isn't it?
This is a fighting technique that
combines Hakuda and Kido.
It's something I created.
You should feel privileged.
This technique has only
been completed recently,
so you're the first person
I'm going to test it on in a real fight.
It doesn't even have a name yet.
No…
It has a name.
What did you say?
It's called, Shunko.
Oh well. I really didn't want to fight
you with this technique…
Be careful, Soi Fon.
Even I can't control
this technique very well.
Do you know…
why I never showed you
this technique until now?
Impossible…
That's because this technique
is too dangerous…
Stop.
It's too early for you
to use this technique.
A Hankisosai…
You cancel the opponent's Kido
by crushing it
with Kido of the same quality
and strength but with opposite spin.
But she did it so quickly and effortlessly
against this much speed
and pressure of my Kido.
Why?!
I'm stronger than you!
I’m supposed to have already…
surpassed you!
A century of isolation should have made
you weaker and me stronger!
Then why are you still standing
in front of me?!
Why are you still dominating me?
Answer me, Yoruichi!
Do you see her, Shaolin?
The one on the palanquin is
the princess of the Shihoin Clan,
the appointed Tenshiheisoban,
Defender of the Realm.
She will one day lead
the Punishment Force.
We the Fon Clan,
devote everything to her.
Everything?
Yes. Everything.
That is our duty and fate,
and yours as well.
From this day on,
your name will be Soi Fon,
and you will live only to serve her.
The first time I met her,
it was like meeting a goddess.
The Fon clan is
a low-ranking noble house.
Throughout the generations, we made
our living as executioners and assassins.
Strength is everything.
Those who cannot even make it
into the Punishment Force
are disowned from the family.
I…
I-I give up.
How dare you stand out like that,
you woman!
I wanted to become stronger.
Stronger than anyone…
Force Leader!
You there, what's your name?
M-My name is Soi Fon.
I see…
I adored her…immensely.
It was beyond adoration.
I worshipped her.
Then, seven years after
I joined the Force came the day
I was named to the Commander’s
Personal Guard Squad.
Soi Fon at your service,
Your Excellency.
Ah, so you've come!
You heard about it already?
Yes! From this day on,
I will sacrifice my body and soul
to protect Your Excelle--
That’s too formal.
Stop with the “Your Excellency” stuff!
You can address me with
something simple, like “Ms. Yoruichi.”
A-Absolutely not!
I could never do that to
Your Excellency…
Th-Then…would it be all right if
I call you Lady Yoruichi?
You are so uptight!
Oh well. Call me whatever you like.
I wanted you here because
I'm confident in your skill.
It doesn't matter what you call me.
I'm expecting you to do well
at your post, Soi Fon!
Y-Yes!
You will live only to serve her…
Yes.
I will live only to serve Lady Yoruichi…
I had no hesitation…
I was happy…
How is it, Soi Fon?
Are you getting used to
the duties in the Force?
Y-Yes, Your Excellency!
Huh? What's that sound?
Buzz buzz.
Buzz buzz buzz--
There it is!
No wonder the noise.
There's a small bee here.
Huh? Wha--?
I thought I told you
to call me "Yoruichi."
B-But…
Hmm?
Lady…Yoruichi…
That's good.
Come.
H-Huh?
Uh…
When I tell you to come, follow me.
Y-Yes!
Yeah.
That's good.
I was happy…
I was happy even in
the middle of battle…
All right, let's pull out!
I'm terribly sorry!
I'm supposed to protect you,
yet I wasn't strong enough…
Is that all?
Don’t worry about it.
But…!
If I say it's okay, then it's okay.
Your Exce--
Hmm?
I mean, thank you very much…
Lady Yoruichi…
Yeah.
Good!
I can't protect Lady Yoruichi
being like this!
Not like this!
Listen up…
Soi Fon, this is how you swing a sword.
Yes. You step in…
Like this.
Don't think too hard.
You're doing fine.
No, I’m not good enough!
In order to protect you, Lady Yoruichi,
I need more power…
No, I'm lacking in everything!
That's enough.
Lady Yoruichi…
You're like me.
I sometimes feel like
you're my little sister.
Someone like me is undeserving
of such words.
I said that's enough.
It's a full moon tonight.
Yes.
I will always be by your side
to protect you…
Forever…
Yeah. It's a promise.
I was happy. Until that day…
It happened so suddenly…
You disappeared without
any words of farewell.
It's a promise.
It was a betrayal of my master
who I adored like a goddess…
Liar…
I was disappointed in you!
I hated you!
And even cursed you!
I vowed that I would become
stronger than you…
and catch you myself!
I will never forgive you!
Yoruichi!
I won't forgive you for betraying
my devotion and trust!
I…
Why?!
Why?
Why did you not take me with you?
Lady Yoruichi…
You've gotten stronger since
the last time I saw you…
That was some wild lightning
just now, wasn’t it?
If we had our swords up in the air,
it would’ve struck us.
Idiot! That's no ordinary lightning.
That's Kido.
It's fired at specific targets.
It won't come this way.
You sure haven’t gotten
any better, huh?
Shut up…
Kido is just not my thing!
I’m not like you.
I'm not a versatile type of person
who’s born with the Zan Ken So Ki.
I wasn't always as versatile.
You’re more likely to be appointed
lieutenant if you're versatile,
rather than excelling in
just one skill.
So I became versatile to
become a lieutenant.
That's all.
That doesn't sound like much fun…
Fool! A man should always strive
to rise through the ranks.
Of course it’s fun!
Don't lie.
It's for your mother, isn't it?
Idiot!
Who’d aim to become a lieutenant
for that old hag?!
Huh? The sake is all gone!
What?! Again?!
You drink too much at once!
Take it easy. It’s only natural
that sake should disappear.
That’s because you drank it all!
Don't make it sound like it
just evaporated!
Oh well. Then let's do the next round!
Fine.
Rock-paper-scissors!
And again! And again!
All right. I win!
I’m taking the high ground!
Again?! That’s not fair!
Idiot! It's your fault that you're weak
at rock-paper-scissors!
I've been wondering…
Who's fighting with Captain Kuchiki
up at the Sokyoku?
I’m not familiar with
that Spiritual Pressure.
It's probably Ichigo.
Ichigo?!
He’s the Ryoka, the Ryoka!
I know because I fought him once!
I see… A Ryoka, eh?
This Ryoka is strong.
Take your stance, Iba.
Let's continue!
All right!
You understand, right?
The loser has to go get more sake!
The winner gets to take a break
in the meanwhile!
If you hold back…
I'll kill you!
I see. You've mastered the Flash Step.
But…
How leisurely. As always.
You seem to be casually
analyzing my powers.
But is that what you should be doing?
I thought you were going to kill me.
You haven't even put
a scratch on me yet.
Or are you telling me that
this is all you’ve got?
Show me your Bankai.
You told me that you were going
to cut me down
and execute Rukia yourself.
What about it?
I don't like that!
I'm going to defeat you…
with everything I have.
I'm going to crush all of your powers
until there's nothing left!
You said you're going to
execute your own sister.
No way!
I don't care about your reasons
or position!
But I will never let you say
such a thing in front of Rukia again!
Release your Bankai.
I'll crush it myself!
A cheap provocation.
You can holler all you want,
but I will not change my mind.
It will not change Rukia’s fate,
nor your own.
Bankai?
Don't get full of yourself, kid.
It's a thousand years too early
for the likes of you to die by my Bankai…
Scatter…
Senbonzakura.
What was that light?
Is this the power of your zanpakuto?
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Yeah.
When I swing my sword,
my zanpakuto absorbs
my Spiritual Pressure.
Then it releases highly concentrated
Spiritual Pressure from its blade.
In other words,
it casts an amplified swing.
That's Zangetsu's ability.
I was never able to aim at anything
with this shot before.
I didn't even know how
to fire it until now.
Kisuke Urahara told me…
“I can only teach you the stances.”
I finally know what he meant.
Zangetsu was the only one who
could teach me about Zangetsu.
At last you are able to fire
a shot at will.
Then I shall tell you, Ichigo.
There is a big difference in its power
when you know its name
than when you don't.
Remember this well, Ichigo.
The name of that attack is…
Getsugatensho.
I'll say it once more.
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Fight me with your Bankai!
I am going to defeat you!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
All right! Now that the fight between
the women is decided,
we'll show you a fight between
some cool guys.
Here I go, Iba!
Yeah!
Sorry to interrupt while
you were getting all excited,
but we don't want to see
your unbearably grungy battle,
so we're moving on to the next one.
What did you say?!
What?!
Yuzu's Super Heartfelt Diary
Big Brother finally came home
from his trip.
But there’s something strange
about him.
He seems afraid of me.
And did he look like that?
Maybe he has something
on his mind.
What’s that?
Bostov!
Tune in again!