Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
What was that light?
Is this the power of
your zanpakuto?
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Yeah…
When I swing my sword, my zanpakuto
absorbs my Spiritual Pressure.
Then it releases highly concentrated
Spiritual Pressure from its blade.
In other words,
it casts an amplified swing.
That's Zangetsu's ability.
At last, you are able to fire
a shot at will.
Then I shall tell you, Ichigo.
There is a big difference in its power
when you know its name
than when you don't.
Remember this well, Ichigo.
The name of that attack is…
Getsugatensho.
I'll say it once more.
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Fight me with your Bankai!
I am going to defeat you!
Tensho, Piercer of Heaven, huh?
What a pretentious name…
Very well…
If you wish for it so strongly,
then feast your eyes on…
my Bankai.
He let go of his sword?
Don't worry.
I won't let you regret it.
You are going to turn to dust
and disappear
before you have the time to regret.
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Not good enough.
I won't make it!
The essence of the Senbonzakura…
lies in its ability to create
a relentless barrage from every direction
by billions of blades
attacking simultaneously.
Your zanpakuto’s abilities
are indeed high.
However…
Attacks that are too broad
and clumsy…
will never be good enough to fend off
the nimble assault of Senbonzakura.
Damn!
I thought I could do a little better.
I guess it was impossible.
Well, of course…
It's foolish of me to think
that I could beat a Bankai while
only using my Shikai!
Watch what you say.
You sound as if you've already
reached Bankai.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
How is she?
She's sleeping.
A Kyomon?
Why a barrier on this room?
I can't predict who is going
to move how.
This is to protect her
from any enemies.
Enemies…
Let's go.
Could that be the Ryoka?
A clash of Spiritual Pressure
like that at the Sokyoku…
Who else could it be?!
Now that the situation has
become this complicated,
we have to try to control
the matter
by making a direct appeal
to our superiors.
Do you mean to tell them about
the incident with Captain Aizen?
Yeah…
Especially about
what really happened…
Let's hurry!
What did you say?
Don't make me repeat myself…
You heard me…
Or may be you just don’t
want to believe it.
I’m not gonna repeat
myself over and over.
You might not believe my words,
but you’ll believe your eyes,
won’t you?
Byakuya Kuchiki!
That's…Kurosaki?
No one fights crazy like
that except him.
Really…
I'm glad I didn't pick
a fight with him!
That's right!
As the old saying goes,
“Even a cat won't eat a childish fight.”
Inoue, it should be
“Even a cat won’t eat a child’s fight.”
Ishida, that's also wrong.
It's not “child's fight.”
It's “a married couple's fight.”
And it isn’t a "cat" that
“won't eat the married couple’s fight,”
it’s a "dog."
Oh, was that it? Sorry, sorry.
I’ve been infected with Inoue speak…
And I was even corrected by Sado!
Excuse me, but now's not
the time to be playing comedy!
I know! Let's hurry!
Really…
Is he smart or dumb?
Be one or the other so I know
what to expect from him.
Ganju, you're going to be left behind!
Huh?! Oh, w-wait for me!
A Bankai? Impossible…
It's the final stage of the zanpakuto.
Only Soul Reapers of
the highest level are able to attain it.
Out of the Four Great Noble Clans,
who are born with far greater
Spiritual Pressure than others…
Only one in several generations has
the ability to reach that level.
And those who have reached
that level…
have all had their name’s etched
into the history of the Soul Society.
That is the Bankai.
But what about him?
He became a Soul Reaper
by absorbing Rukia's power.
He's not a noble.
He wasn’t even born a Soul Reaper.
So how can he talk about Bankai
so casually?
How can he release
such Spiritual Pressure?
This is as if he's…
Yeah…
You're slow.
Even when you are falling.
Brother Byakuya!
Ban…kai.
Tensa Zangetsu.
What is that?
That little thing is your Bankai?
It's just a regular zanpakuto…
I see… First the execution
and now the Bankai…
It seems like you enjoy treading on
the things we hold sacred.
I'll show you then!
I'll show you what happens
when you insult our honor.
“Our honor,” you say?
It seems like your so-called “honor”
has something to do with killing Rukia.
Then I’ll tread on it
just like you said.
This is why I got…this power!
Captain…
What…should I do…?
I have to find out…
There's no one guarding
the front gate?
That's odd…
There's no one here either…
It's closed from the inside.
This is Captain Hitsugaya
of Squad 10!
It’s a matter of an utmost importance!
Requesting permission to
enter the Central 46!
The emergency defense lock
is working…
Yeah.
That's even more strange…
What's going on?
It seems like this is the entrance
to the execution grounds…
Whoa. It’s so high!
We have to climb this?
Kuchiki is up these steps…
Ichigo…
Let's go!
W-Wait just one second!
Doesn’t that Spiritual Pressure
earlier bother you?
Who knows what’ll happen if
we walk into the middle of a fight
where they are fighting with
such monstrous Spiritual Pressure!
I’m telling you! Don't go!
Thank you for worrying about us.
But no… We have to go!
Yeah… We're his friends.
Yeah!
Thank you for coming with us this far.
You don’t have to go any further.
Huh?!
Yeah! I guess this is where
we say goodbye, then.
Umm…Mr. Mini-mustache?
Yeah! See you later,
Mini-mustache!
Sorry for the trouble,
H-Hey…
What's with these guys…?
There's something wrong with them!
I'm not Mini-mustache!
I've been in the Squad 11
for ten years.
My name is Makizo Aramaki!
Damn! And we members of
Squad 11
don't know the meaning
of the word “run away”!
Oh yeah… And try to
remember my name, you guys!
For a moment…
I lost sight of him.
I couldn't react…
Impossible.
You…
Why did you take the point of
your sword away from my throat?
Are you just confident?
Arrogance destroys the footholds
of victory.
I'll say this once more…
That is not a Bankai.
A Bankai can never be
so small and fragile.
And a lowly Ryoka could
never reach Bankai.
You will regret not slitting my throat
when you had the chance.
A miracle only happens once.
There is no second time, boy!
What’s with his speed?
My Senbonzakura can’t keep up?
What's the matter?
Can't keep up?
I can go a little faster, you know.
Don't get too cocky…
Kid!
He got faster?
I'm twice as fast…
if I control it with the palms
of my hands!
There's nothing…
I can't capture!
I've got him!
Impossible!
He knocked them all down?
A miracle only happens once, huh?
Then what do you call it
the second time?
I see…
By compressing all the fighting power
of the Bankai
in that small blade,
that Bankai gives you
maximum fighting power
at unimaginable speeds…
So that's the true power
of your Bankai.
Very well…
Then I shall completely crush
that power!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Did you see that, Byakuya?!
This is my--
Zenkai, full power!
No, Ganju. It's mankai, full bloom!
Oh, sorry.
Umm… Was it genkai, limit?
It's Bankai!
Oh whatever.
You're already at your genkai.
All right! Genkai it is!
Oh, is that so?!
It's all a manzai, comedy, now!
Jinta's Unbeatable Diary!
Hello!
Wha--?!
You again?
Because it's cheap here.
500 yen worth of snacks
as usual, right?
Here!
I've always wondered,
but isn't this a bit too much?
It's just your imagination!
Now get out of here!
I'm busy training for a soccer match.
Wow, that's amazing.
Then…
I'll let you borrow this as
a lucky charm… Bostov!
You dummy!
A man doesn't need a stuffed animal!
Tune in again!