Woke up with yawning,
it's dawning
I'm still alive
Turned on my radio
To start up new day
As goddamned D.J. chattered
How to survive
Amazing news got over
On that air wave
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
She's a shooting star
Good-night, good-night
Good-bye…
Tonight,
Love is rationed
Across the nation
Tonight
Love reflects world wide
Almost another day
See you some other day
We shall now commence
our regular captains' meeting.
We have confirmed
infiltration by ryoka.
Here are my commands…
First, all squads are to take position
in second-class alert.
Next, in light of the seriousness
of this situation,
as a special measure…
Captain Toshiro Hitsugaya of Squad 10
will be responsible
for the ryokas' capture.
Yes! But…
The information is convoluted…
At the moment, there is also a problem
with information leaking
from the Department of Research
and Development.
Put together the correct data
and send it to every squad.
Be thorough.
Yes!
Finally, and this is most important…
Anyone who meets a ryoka is
to kill him without hesitation!
Hey! It's coming this way!
Have any of the squads left yet?
Lieutenant Omaeda of Squad 2
left with some squad members!
Any others?
Squad 7’s Lieutenant Iba
also headed to the Rukon District!
All right! Keep gathering information!
We'll gather all reports from
all the squads!
Don't let any information leak!
Yes!
It sure is quiet…
Well, it'll get loud soon…
There they are!
I'm first!
No, I'm first!
You're taking us on in broad daylight.
You've got some guts…
Kariya, can you leave this to me?
Yeah, this is perfect… Test it out.
Zeig dih, Dalk!
Hi! How are you?!
Oh my. The air here is delicious…
It feels good!
Oh? Bounts sure use
strange techniques…
Humph. You wimp!
Can't you fight with your own power?!
That bastard is absorbing reishi?!
Who are you?!
Don't look at me
as if I'm some monster…
I'm still human.
Just better than your average human.
Get him!
Dalk, crush them!
All right!
I'm feeling really good too!
Hey!
How dare you underestimate us!
Hey! Isn't there anyone else?!
I've become really strong!
Someone, save me!
That's no good…
It's just a waste of your strength…
Omaeda!
I don't like attacking people
who are unarmed,
but I have no choice!
What?!
You call yourself a Soul Reaper?
Know…your place!
How do you feel?
This is great…
There's an unlimited amount of
highly pure reishi here.
I see… Then let's go…
Call the Med Crew!
Yes!
Everyone else,
to defensive positions.
Ascertain the extent of
the damage!
Lieutenant Omaeda!
Get a hold of yourself!
Captain Hitsugaya!
It's Squad 7's Lieutenant Iba!
Is he all right?
Thankfully he's conscious!
Captain!
Sorry I'm late.
I've just returned.
Matsumoto…
I'm very sorry…
I couldn't complete my mission.
I allowed the ryoka
to invade Soul Society…
I'm the one who dispatched you…
I'm responsible.
Don't worry about it…
Yes…
What have you found out?
I don't have anything to report…
But…It is difficult to pinpoint
the location of the Bounts.
Even now, the only Spiritual Pressure
that could be detected
was that of the two Lieutenants…
Tsk--! This is troublesome…
We will continue the investigation!
Yes!
Matsumoto, welcome back
to the squad!
Yes!
We're back again…
Yes…
Did you sense that
Spiritual Pressure earlier?
Yeah, it seemed like some Soul Reaper
was fighting the Bounts.
But you didn't sense
the Bounts' Spiritual Pressure, did you?
It's the same as
the World of the Living, huh?
Why are you in deep thought?
This is an emergency situation…
That's right! That shot of
both of you from behind.
Ugh…how disgusting!
You're not lovers!
What are you talking about, Lirin?!
Humph! I don't know why,
but it feels bad!
Now now, calm down.
We'll lose to the Bounts if we fight!
That's right.
I don't care!
Kurosaki! Kuchiki!
Bad news, bad news!
What's wrong?
She moved.
Huh?
Kukaku loves to move, as usual…
Yoruichi, do you know
where she moved to?
I think I have a feeling
where she might be…
There she is!
We finally found her!
How nostalgic…
You think so?
Yeah…
That's odd…
She always changes its design
when she moves, but…
As usual, she displays her complete
lack of aesthetic vision…
Just like your pictures…
Silence!
Ow! This is usually Kon's role…
Hm? Where did Kon go off to?
Huh?!
Wha-?! Come to think of it,
he isn't here…
That's odd… I was sure he came
with us to this world…
What? Kon is lost?
What should we do?
Should we search for him?
Well, he'll be all right!
He's bursting with energy!
Yes.
That's right.
This voice!
Ichigo--! Sister--!
What is this?!
We came all this way to
the ends of the earth!
Who got lost?!
Me! Crap!
This place has been sealed!
You can't enter!
What's this?
Hello?
What happened?
What's this?!
There's a strange small animal!
Huh?! Huh?!
This has got to be a monster!
Y-You're mistaken! I'm a Mod Soul…
What's that?
That strange small animal
has got to be the one
that destroyed this house!
I-I wouldn't do that!
Or rather, I can't do that!
Catch him!
I won't die here!
I'm going to live! I'm going to live!
I won't lose!
GUY BURSTING WITH ENERGY
You idiot!
It hurts, it hurts!
Yoruichi told me that there was
something strange…
happening in the World of the Living.
So I dispatched you there
because I thought you could
be of some use to her!
It's just like you said!
And you say you forgot
because you were occupied
with your job at the convenience store?
Are you kidding me?!
You're the same as always…
Sorry, I couldn't be of any help…
You know what convenience stores are?
Is that a problem?
Huh?
Bastard… You were making fun of me!
No, I wasn't…
I'm in a really bad mood right now!
Ichigo, don't say unnecessary things!
Wh-What did I say?!
I'm going to straighten you both out!
Get over here!
Kukaku…
Your mouth can get you
into trouble…
And?
The man called Kariya,
the leader of the Bounts…
said that he was going to
have revenge on Soul Society…
The old Department of Research
and Development created them…
Despite that, there is almost no record
of them in Soul Society…
What do you mean?!
“Put a lid on anything that stinks…”
That’s what probably happened…
I don't know how the Bounts are going
to get their revenge…
But you probably already
know that it won't be easy
to get into Seireitei since
it's surrounded by a wall…
So you want to investigate
what they are thinking and
what they're doing?
Yeah.
Sorry… I know that
there are a lot of people,
but for the time being,
could you let us stay here?
The Rukon District is big.
But it'll be somewhat easy to move
if we stay here.
Koganehiko! Shiroganehiko!
Are we good with food?
With our body and soul put into it…!
We can feed up to thirty people!
All right… In a way,
the Bounts were allowed to invade…
because of my stupid younger brother's
mismanagement…
Wh-Why?! Big Sis, I didn't…
Yes… It's all my fault…
It's a cramped house,
but use it as you like!
By the way, how are you going
to find these Bounts?
– Tada!
Leave that to us!
What are these strange things?
They're Mod Souls that
Urahara created
to detect the Bounts' Spiritual Pressure.
Ooh…
Mod Souls, huh?!
I never would have thought
of putting them in a doll…
I expected Urahara to do
something interesting.
No…well…
That's not something to
be surprised about!
One more thing…
I have something to ask of everyone…
What is it?
Could you collect information
on someone called Rantao?
Rantao? Who's that?
Yeah… Ichigo…
Kariya told you about the history
of the Bounts’ appearance, didn't he?
The lead researcher who created
the Bounts long ago.
That's Rantao.
What?!
Are you saying that this person
called Rantao is still alive?!
Yes…
It's been more than 1,000 years
since he was expelled from Seireitei…
But it's been rumored that he lives
in the depths of Rukon District…
All right! Then we may be able to learn
something about the Bounts
if we meet this guy.
Yeah…
All right! Then let's have dinner!
Koganehiko! Shiroganehiko!
You're ready aren't you?!
Yes!
This way to the dining room!
Come to think of it,
I haven't eaten anything for a while.
I'm hungry.
Sorry for the trouble.
Yoruichi…
What is it?
Do you have anything else
to tell me?
About what?
Don't play dumb…
Tell me everything you know.
Why aren’t you going to Seireitei?
It's not just because
it's convenient here, is it?
There's a Soul Reaper
who's aiding the Bounts…
He not only has the ability to
hide his Spiritual Pressure…
But he has the power to turn invisible.
He's already broken into Seireitei.
Oh?
There's no mistake in assuming
that this Soul Reaper, Ichinose,
sealed the database…
of the archives in the Department
of Research and Development.
And he probably manipulated the data…
so Mayuri Kurotsuchi would
become interested in the Bounts…
Kurotsuchi fell for a simple trick…
He prepared the Quincy power and
called the Bounts to Soul Society…
I see… In other words…
You've chosen to hide somewhere
where that guy, Ichinose,
can't predict your movements…
Soi Fon is secretly strengthening
Seireitei's security, but…
Taking into consideration
everything that happened…
It would probably be difficult to
stop him from breaking in.
Probably…
Also, I'm someone who
once left Soul Society…
It's too much of a pain to enter
Seireitei after all this time…
If anything,
I'd say that's the real reason…
I'm just going to do things my way…
Can we win?
I don't know…
Well, that's fine.
I love trouble!
KUKAKU SHIBA
I'll help you out!
Thanks…
We'll split up from here.
Use Lirin, Kurodo, and Noba
to search for the Bounts.
Whoever finds them will inform everyone
with weak Spiritual Pressure.
Is that clear?!
Yes.
Rukia, what are you going to do?
Now that I've returned,
I have to return to my own squad.
I'm quite late, but I'm going now.
I see. All right.
Don't do anything rash, Ichigo…
Yeah…
How silly!
Huh?
I'm going to find the Bounts first!
I'm not going to lose to the likes of…
to the likes of Rukia!
I won't lose!
What's…with her?
This is a form of jealousy…
Yeah…
Jeez, I don't know what she's thinking…
Of who?
No, well…
Hey, Ishida!
There's no time to waste.
I'll search for them by myself.
Leave me alone for a moment…
Ishida!
I'm all right…
All right, Kurodo!
Yes!
Take care of Inoue!
Just leave it to me!
Inoue, don't push yourself too much.
I know.
All right!
Let's go!
The dustiness of Rukon District
hasn't changed at all…
Aw…jeez!
Why am I so pissed off?!
I'm so pissed off
about being pissed! Jeez!
This presence…
They're here!
Hey!
You!
You again…
What a coincidence…
Well, that's fine…
Zeig dih, Nieder!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Lying around, dozing as usual
Flipping through nothing but manga books
My motto: Funny & Easy
I wanna live life carefree
"On the road you need a companion,
in life you need sympathy"
Underneath the sun, smilin' every day
Being kind to others, and also to myself
But I get things done
when I need to (Really?)
Now then, come with me
(Can I trust you?)
Trust me or not, you won't really know
until you give it a try
I mean, wouldn't you rather
trust and laugh together?
(I wanna) Go for walk
Things won’t get started if you don’t act!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Don't wanna lose!
Don't wanna cry!
'Cuz I wanna keep laughing!
MOVIN'! MOVIN'!
Are you in charge of Bount
countermeasures?
Who are you?
I'm Lirin. A Mod Soul.
An expert at tracking Bounts!
– Is that true?
– Unfortunately it's true.
If you want, I'll lend her to Squad 10.
No, I'll pass.
I have a bad feeling about her.
How insulting!
The Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden after these messages!
– Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Hanataro! What happened to that kid?!
Oh, Renji! He's all right!
He's out of danger!
I see. Thank goodness…
Where is everyone?
In Soul Society!
You sure are kind, Renji.
You came all this way
to check on him…
Yeah, that's one thing, but…
I came because I was told
to clean up before I leave…
– What?!
– Quickly…
I won't lose--!