Over by the river, right?
Yes. I’m certain it was the
Spiritual Pressure of
Kuchiki and the others.
Got it!
Wait! I’ll go.
Kurosaki, you look for Nozomi!
Please.
All right.
Chad, go with Inoue!
You can count on me.
Aren’t we there yet?
Cool your jets!
We should see it soon.
There. Isn’t that it?
So, what’s over there?
I brought you here, you know?!
You could at least tell me!
Earlier, you said…
I’ll fix things so he
won’t have to protect me.
What do you mean?
That’s why I came to Karakura Town.
Is that what this is about?
You’re not talking?
Hey! Wait!
Kuchiki!
Wait!
This Spiritual Pressure…
Abarai!
No!
You’re not him.
Nozomi Kujo…
You know, simply looking for her
wouldn’t be much of a work out.
So don’t take this personally.
Inoue… Go.
Sado…
I’ll handle this.
Be careful.
Hey, Sado!
I wasn’t expecting to take you on.
But if we’re going to fight,
I’m not holding back!
Brazo Derecho Del Gigante!
Relax!
It’s me, not some stranger,
who’s going to kick your ass!
Hang on!
Okay then,
let’s see how Old Man Yama’s doing.
Stay sharp.
He may be old,
but nobody can beat Master
Genryusai head on.
I know that.
Isn’t that why we’re going together?
Old Man Yama, it’s
Kyoraku and Ukitake.
May we come in, Master?
We have something we’d
like to tell you.
Enter.
Excuse us.
Master, we’d like to tell you about…
What brings both of you here?
You’ve still got a ways to go.
You allowed your target to
sense your intent to kill.
You’re good, Master.
Damn, so you knew all along?
Now then, young ones…
Tell me what you know.
So the man says.
Guess we have no choice.
We have to do it.
Yeah.
You’re going to fight me?
Fine.
Shigekuni Genryusai Yamamoto
isn’t going to lose to
you youngsters just yet!
What did you find?
The Precipice World traffic record
here does indicate frequent passage
by Substitute Soul Reaper
Kurosaki and Captain Kyoraku.
Could Captain Kyoraku
have altered the record?
He wouldn’t do something so obvious.
I think this is the altered information.
If that’s true,
the only one who could do that is
Captain Kurotsuchi?
No.
It’s too crude of an M.O.
for Captain Kurotsuchi.
Then who?
I wanted to find out,
so I went to the Daireisho
Archive earlier.
The Daireisho Archive?!
In the Underground Assembly Hall?!
Yes.
Records of all Soul Society
events and information
are stored there regardless of
whether you want them to be or not.
I…see…
So, did you learn anything?
I found a Department of
Research & Development
member who is obsessed
with the Precipice World.
This person put together many studies
on the Precipice World all by himself.
And what concerned me the most was
that there was no record of
him prior to a certain time.
What? Even in the Daireisho Archive?!
Yes.
I don’t know the reason,
but it appears he’s no
ordinary squad member.
Am I wrong?
Department of Research & Development,
head of the Precipice
World Research Section…
Seventh Seat, Kageroza Inaba.
Just as I would have expected.
Although I thought it’d take you
a little longer to get this far.
I didn’t count on you entering
the Daireisho Archive.
Isane!
Right!
You’re wasting your time.
It appears you crossed
over both time and space.
Is that the result of your
Precipice World research?
You are astute.
It’s still an incomplete
technology though.
You used the Precipice World to
cut off the Soul Society from
the World of the Living.
For what purpose?
You’ll know soon enough.
El Directo!
You’re good, all right!
Then I’ll get serious as well!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Hikotsu Taiho!
Again! Hikotsu Taiho!
Hey, did I make you wait?
Even though he’s an imposter,
you’re all right to be able
to fight this well against me!
So this is a Reigai?
Interesting.
No matter how high your
Spiritual Pressure is,
I’ll blow you away, imposter!
Come on…
Isn’t it about time you told me?
What is it that’s here?
You’re not talking again?
A Senkaimon.
Oh… I see.
A Senkaimon, huh?
Wait, what do you mean
there’s a Senakimon?!
Isn’t that something
Soul Reapers open?
Studying the Precipice World
led to the discovery
that many previously
unknown Senkaimon exist.
The one up ahead is one of them.
Oh?
And?
What’re you going to do when
you get to the Senkaimon?
Let's go.
Hmm?
There’s a Senkaimon here?
I get it now!
You’re going to open
the Senkaimon and run
away somewhere, right?
Hey!
I’m not running anywhere.
What?
Here.
There’s a wrinkle in space.
What is this?
Doesn’t it look different than usual?
This is a naturally occurring Senkaimon.
There are countless Precipice
Worlds connecting the
Soul Society with the
World of the Living.
Some are dangerous because
they flow too fast.
Some are tiny.
Some are connected to who-knows-where.
This is one of them.
If I enter here and close the gateway,
no one will find me.
Oh…
That would be perfect for hide-and-seek.
So, how long do you
intend to hide there?
Forever.
I see.
Wait! Then, are you…
It can’t be helped.
Closing the gateway means
I won’t return to the
same time and space.
Wait, wait, wait!
Why do you have to do such a thing?!
You don’t have to
go that far, do you?!
Ichigo and others, all of
us, said we’d protect you!
Is this what you really want?
What I want?
Lots of good things will
happen if you keep on living!
Even I was able to
live thanks to Ichigo!
When I have retrieved Nozomi…
Then, not only the Soul Society,
but the World of the Living,
will also be under my control.
But this is the only way to stop him.
You…
Okay, all right!
If you’re that determined,
I’ll go with you!
What?!
Don’t get the wrong idea!
It’s not because I’m
worried about you!
And not because I was worried you’d
be lonely all by yourself either!
It’s just a whim!
Let’s just say that lately
I’ve gotten tired
of this world myself!
It might be nice to spend my life
leisurely in the Precipice World!
Huh?!
You…
What, are you going to kiss me?
You don’t have to thank me.
Hey! What’s the big idea?!
Untie me, you idiot!
I’m going alone, stupid!
Who’re you calling stupid?! Hey!
But I do appreciate…
your feelings.
Huh?
Nozomi!
Come on! Don’t do it!
Hey! You!
Nozomi!
Hi there, Nozomi.
Where were you about to go?
Reigai!
We need you to stop acting on your own.
Are you going to take on all of us?
How did you find me?
How, you ask?
Fool.
Did you think you were
the only one who knew
of the existence of
this Precipice World?
What you know, Kageroza knows, as well.
Let go of me!
Now, come with us.
Hey, you bastards!
Keep your hands off of her!
I’ll take you on! Come at me!
What, are you scared of me?!
C’mon, let’s go!
No! I don’t want to go!
Hey! Don’t ignore me!
I don’t want to go!
Hey, you bastards!
No! I won’t go!
Oh yeah?
So that’s your choice?
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You…
What the hell took you so long?!
They were about to take her away!
Shut up!
And what’s your excuse
for acting on your own?!
If you were with her, you
could’ve at least let me know!
Then give me a cell phone, dummy!
Hand over Nozomi Kujo.
Not happening!
There are six of us, and one of you.
Think you can protect her?
That’s two of us!
I will protect her.
Why?
Because it’s what you want!
Then you leave us no choice.
We can’t back down either.
Let’s get this over with quickly.
Damn it!
Hey, Nozomi!
Aren’t you a Soul Reaper too?!
Don’t you have a
Zanpakuto or something?!
No.
Damn it!
If you had one, we could at
least take out one of them.
Are you worried?
If he were his usual self,
he could probably manage,
but right now…
I mean, it’s natural to
worry about your friends!
Natural…
to worry…
To fight to protect…
your friends…
Damn it!
What’s the matter?
Your Spiritual Pressure’s low.
It’s only a matter of time.
Guess I have no choice.
Here goes!
I-Ichigo!
Your Soul Reaper powers are…
Shut up!
I’ll just have to make do!
Bankai!
Don’t think this is the end of it!
Brazo Izquierdo Del Diablo!
What?!
Way to go, Sado!
Take this!
Hikotsu Taiho!
We won, but I don’t
feel too good about it.
Abarai… What’s this?
Sado, let me have a look at that.
This is no ordinary Gikongan!
Getsuga…tensho!
You…win…
Ichigo!
Your…Spiritual Pressure…
What about it?
N-Nothing!
You fought knowing you might
lose your Soul Reaper powers?
Why?
Because I made a promise.
A promise?
That I’d protect you.
So don’t even think about
disappearing into the Precipice World.
Got that?
Yeah.
Huh?!
What?! No, I mean…
Kon, you’re a mess!
Hah! These battle scars
are my badges of honor!
Wow… They look awful,
not to mention dirty.
You can tell the intense
battle I went through, huh?
It takes courage just to touch you.
Guess I’ll throw you
in a bucket of water.
What am I, a towel?!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Master Genryusai…
It’s over.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
You haven’t been taking your medicine?
Well you see, he’s a Reigai,
so he hasn’t been taking it.
Unacceptable!
It sucks to be identical to
the originals to this extent.