Forcing down a girl against her wishes?
I wouldn’t call that a nice habit.
Oh?
Ishida…
Are you sure about this?
Won’t your master scold you
for doing too much on your own?
It’s not like Ichigo’s my master!
Hado 4: Byakurai.
A Hirenkyaku…
You must be a Quincy.
You seem quite interested in us.
I have no interest in you,
but I don’t want you
bringing trouble to this town.
Leave.
Then I won’t have to take action.
I don’t want this turning into
an incident either, Quincy.
But if you get in our way,
I will be forced to consider
eliminating you as an enemy.
I have no intention of
getting in your way.
Of course…
From my perspective,
I’ve already determined
you to be an enemy.
That’s fine.
I will take responsibility.
What now, Ichigo?!
Isn’t it obvious?
Return to the World of the Living.
Be serious!
This isn’t the Seireitei
as we know it!
As far as we’re concerned,
this is the enemy’s den.
Do you really think you can slip
right through the Senkaimon?
It’s a safe bet that
the Reigai have
blockaded the Senkaimon.
Then what do you suggest I do?
Well…
Don’t worry.
Yoruichi!
What happened to the pursuers?
Do you think their kind could
keep up with me?
About now,
they’re in a fluster because
they lost track of me.
Great work, Yoruichi.
But…
I don’t think the enemy will cease
guarding the Senkaimon.
Neither do I.
Which is why we’ll
break through head on.
Head on?!
They may be fakes,
but didn’t you say they possess
powers equal to or above the captains?!
Breaking through will
be extremely difficult!
We’re going to break through
because they’re fakes.
-Huh?
I see.
Quincy, am I to surmise that
this attack of yours relaxes
the bonds of Reishi and converts
the energy to your own?
You’re very knowledgeable.
And I see that your appearance…
is similar to that of a
scientist that I despise.
Are you referring to Captain Kurotsuchi?
He is my superior officer.
I knew it.
So that’s why you knew
about my Seeleschneider.
No, this is the first
time I’ve seen it.
The first time?
It may have been the first time,
but I am able to analyze that much on the spot.
Unlike that person, I
am a composed scientist.
Regrettably…
That technique tremendously lacks enough
speed to catch me.
I am well aware of that.
It’s elementary.
There was no question that
Ginreikojaku’s speed
could not catch you.
In that case,
all I needed to do
was increase the speed of my Hirenkyaku.
It seems you’re not very
fond of that scientist.
What a shame.
If we weren’t enemies,
I think we could’ve gotten along.
Heavens, no!
What?!
Where’d you go?!
I’m not fond of Captain
Kurotsuchi, you say?
Heaven forbid.
Your wound…
He is a wonderful superior.
He has a few personality
issues, but I respect him.
However, I was superior in all respects.
That’s all there is to it.
W-What do you mean?
Go mad…
Raiku.
That won’t be necessary.
I have no intention of giving
you time to figure it out.
No way… That distance…
I never even…saw you coming.
We’re here.
So they’ve come…
Hey!
There are more of them now.
So they were on to us after all!
They can only hold off
the boundary wall of
the Precipice World for a short time!
We don’t need to attack.
We’ll bust through them and make it
through the Precipice World!
Let’s go!
They’re charging in.
All we need to do is keep them
from going through the Senkaimon.
First, we need to slow them down!
What’s up, Rukia?
Rukia!
Stop looking around!
Damn it!
Hyoryusenbi!
What happened?!
I didn’t do anything!
What just happened?
Getsugatensho!
Moron!
I ended up bursting mine
before it got hit because
you screwed up on the timing!
I can’t help it!
That thing was difficult to operate!
Damn that Kisuke.
I told him to develop something
that anyone could handle.
We’re going to keep going
right through the Senkaimon!
Yoruichi!
Brother!
Did you think I’d be
oblivious to what you were thinking?
Are you sacrificing yourself?!
If I said I was… What of it?
Yoruichi!
What’re you thinking?!
Go!
I’m not going to get killed
by the likes of them!
But…
Go, Ichigo!
Protect the people in
the World of the Living!
Thank you.
Don’t let them go!
I’m not letting you pursue them!
Shunko!
Looks like the situation
is reversed, eh?
You are Reigai originally created
for the purpose of doing battle.
Your personalities and strengths
might be near-perfect copies,
but compared to the originals,
you appear a bit aggressive.
That being the case,
you won’t hesitate to attack
Ichigo, Rukia, or myself.
That is why a single blinding
blow was effective.
If you had hesitated in your attacks
as the originals would have,
it probably wouldn’t
have been as effective.
Now then.
I’m not letting you get beyond here.
Is that so?
Then we’ll just have to eliminate you.
I see.
You may be Reigai,
but your powers are quite impressive.
I apologize for taking so long,
Lieutenant Kira, Lieutenant Ise.
I will handle eliminating the Mod Soul.
I’ll put you out of
your misery quickly.
So you were still alive, huh?
His movements…
It’s not a simple
issue of him being fast.
It was as though the moment he moved
was somehow cut out.
I deeply apologize if it seems like
I’m toying with your life.
I’ll end it now.
Hado 4: Byakurai.
Ishida!
Inoue, heal Ishida’s injuries.
But…
I’ll do what I can to give you time.
Give her time, you say?
You speak as if you own time.
Sado!
Now then, shall we put an end to this?
Let’s end this.
I’ve taken a bit too long.
Kurosaki!
Are you all right, Inoue?
Kuchiki!
Yes.
But Ishida and Sado are…
Ichigo Kurosaki…
You may be Reigai,
but you are still captains.
Is that really the best you
can do against me?
How pathetic.
Do you understand the
situation you’re in?
If you don’t, then let me show you.
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Your denial to admit defeat
is exactly like the real one!
So you made it back?
That was unexpected.
Who are you?
I see.
Was it Yoruichi Shihoin?
Hey! Didn’t you hear me?
Yes.
If you had her help,
I can understand how you could escape.
That is, if she sacrifices her life.
I said, who the hell are you?!
Come now, calm down.
I am Kageroza Inaba.
I study the Precipice World in
the Department of Research
and Development.
You study the Precipice World?!
Then are you the cause of this incident?
And are you in control
of those Reigai there?!
You even know about the Reigai.
Wonderful!
Wonderful, you say?
After all, I am a person
who has done nothing but research work,
so I haven’t paid much
attention to others’ affairs.
It appears you have
reached an understanding
that is much further along
than I had expected.
Never mind all the explanation!
Huh?
I don’t know what
dumb reason you’re doing all this for,
but when you hurt my friends…
I’ll crush you!
That’ll make things quicker.
If you do not need an explanation,
that would suit me just fine.
What’s with his Spiritual Pressure?!
As a show of respect for the
strength that allowed
you to defeat Aizen,
I will not use any petty tricks.
But is this all the power
you possess right now?
What?!
Bring it forth.
You still have a last
resort, don’t you?
Substitute Soul Reaper…
Now you’re suddenly sounding almighty.
I was going to use it
even without you asking!
Wait, Ichigo!
Here goes!
Damn it.
My Spiritual Pressure’s unstable.
I’ve got to settle this in one shot!
Getsuga…
tensho!
What?!
Is this your best?
Ichigo is definitely holding back
his strength because he’s afraid
of losing his Spiritual Power, but…
Even so, to be able to
snuff out a Getsugatensho so easily…
They may be Reigai,
but the fact that
he can command those proud
captains and lieutenants
shows that his powers are greater.
Substitute Soul Reaper,
it would seem I overestimated you.
Or is it that your Spiritual Power
has diminished more than I predicted?
Shut up!
Unfortunately, in your present state,
as a scientist,
I no longer have any interest in you!
Ichigo!
This is perfect.
You two could become a
hindrance to my objective.
Allow me to eliminate you right here.
Hey, Ichigo!
You seem to be having trouble there!
Renji!
What?!
Let the woman go.
Let her go!
One after the other…
Brother!
Byakuya!
Looks like he beat you up
pretty good, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Shut up!
Are you guys the real deal?!
Damn right!
But…how?
It’s not just us.
G-Guys…
The originals?
For a petty underling,
this was some stunt you pulled.
Why Captain Kurotsuchi…
I wasn’t expecting
you to arrive so soon.
Weren’t you tardy
in your report to me?
Because of that,
I ended up helping all these
people I didn’t want to help.
It’s a thankless job.
I’m making you pay for this
a million times over!
Surely you jest.
You seem to think you’ve
won, but you’re mistaken.
But I will retreat for now.
Damn you! Wait!
Ichigo, don’t.
Huh?
The Precipice World
is his territory now.
You have no hope of winning
if you go after him without a plan.
But if you wish to die by
committing such foolishness,
I won’t stop you.
It would be a fitting death for you.
Shut up.
When I have retrieved Nozomi,
I will be able to show
you my true power.
True power?
Then, not only the Soul Society,
but the World of the Living
will also be under my control.
Well then originals, and you,
Substitute Soul Reaper…
We will meet again someday.
We won’t let you take control!
That was interference
we weren’t expecting.
It can’t be helped.
Not everything goes as you
expect. That’s science.
Besides, I knew from the start
that it was impossible to
confine Captain Kurotsuchi
in the Precipice World
for an extended period.
Everyone is here.
We will get Nozomi back…
with our invading army!
Captain Kuchiki, is
there anything you need
during our stay in the
World of the Living?
I will need a place to live.
Yes, sir!
A garden, a lake, and seven rooms
will be the minimal requirement.
C-Captain?
And about five or so servants.
That won’t be possible, sir!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Huh?
I’m saved.
Is everyone okay?!
Are you okay, Sado?!
Hang on, Ishida!
Can you get up?
Yes.
Grab on tight.
Thank you.
Me too, Sis!
We should head back for now.
Got it!
Wounded guy over here!
Right, let’s hurry.
I can’t move anymore!
Let’s go!
-Right!
-Yeah.
Hey, wait!
Carry me back too!
Give me a piggyback!
Don’t leave me behind!