Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
It appears he broke through
the station gate.
Captain Kyoraku!
Huh?
What, he’s here already?
Oh well…
I guess I’d better head out…
Will you really be going?
It’s just one Ryoka…
and as your lieutenant,
I should suffice.
You see, Nanao…
It’s Old Man Yama’s orders,
so it can’t be helped.
He doesn’t want anyone to think
that the Ryokas are giving him
any more trouble.
Oh, don’t look so worried…
It’ll be over soon.
It’s just a little distraction.
Wait!
You’ve come far enough,
you foolish Ryoka!
I am the lieutenant
and third seat of Squad Eight,
Tatsufusa Enjoji!
You have chosen the wrong path!
From the moment I appeared here,
this path came to a dead-end!
Now, now, what’s the matter?!
Can’t make a move?
Nothing to be ashamed of.
That is normal.
After all, this is the technique of
the great swordsman, Tatsufusa Enjoji!
So far, not one has defeated--!
In the beginning,
two blasts a day was my limit.
Now, I don’t tire even after firing
more than five blasts…
I’ll have to thank Yoruichi
for training me.
Whew! Good job!
I’m Squad Eight Captain,
Shunsui Kyoraku.
Pleased to meet you.
Squad Eight… Captain…
Yup, how do you do?
Hey Nanao!
That’s enough flower petals!
Huh? Maybe she didn’t hear me.
Hey, Nanao?
Hey! Enough flower petals!
Cute, cute Nanao!
Lovely, lovely Nanao!
Sorry, but…
I don’t have time for your skit.
Let me pass…
What, can’t you get
in the groove a bit?
Everyone’s so indifferent.
I’m in a hurry,
please move aside from there.
You don’t seem like a bad guy.
If possible…
I don’t want to fight you.
Hmm… You’ve got me there.
Neither one of us wants to fight.
But I can’t let you pass, either.
Isn’t there any way
you could just withdraw?
I can’t do that.
I see. Then you leave me no choice.
Let’s have a friendly drink!
Huh?!
Well, if you can’t withdraw,
I thought maybe you could stop here
for a while at least.
It’s just for a little while…
I cannot!
Aww, come on…
It's the law.
Minors can’t drink alcohol.
Oh, yeah. That’s a problem.
That’s no good, is it?
Never mind then.
The other captains are on the move too.
Soon this battle will be over.
So if you could sit out until…
The other captains?!
So, Ichigo and the others are
being pursued by the captains as well?
The situation’s changed.
Kyoraku, please move out of my way now!
And if I say no?
I won’t let you!
My, oh my…
This sure is becoming cumbersome.
You missed again.
Why… How come…?
He deflected the first blast
with one hand.
And since then,
he’s dodged every single one.
Why hasn’t a single shot
landed on target?
He doesn’t even have a scratch…
The last guy said that
he was a lieutenant…
That should be only two levels
between him and the captain.
Just two levels,
and yet so far apart…
Is the captain class on
such a different level?!
Stop already, I’m sure you realize…
your skills are certainly great.
It’s hard, fast, and for a human,
you have an impressive destructive ability.
But, you can’t hit me.
I’m sure you can see
where this is going.
Why don’t you give up
and go home already?
Thanks for the warning!
But I cannot withdraw!
Stop it, already…
I’m sure you realize…
There are techniques which completely
run out at the point of exhaustion,
and those you can push beyond that,
at the expense of draining your lifeforce.
Your attacks are obviously
of the latter type.
I won’t say anything rude,
so just go on home!
If you keep going like this,
you’ll really die!
Oh boy, what a problem.
Why do you have to keep fighting so?
What’s your purpose?
Why did you come here?
My purpose is to save Rukia Kuchiki!
Rukia?
Wasn’t it just this spring that
she went missing in the human world?
That’s too short.
It’s a shallow friendship.
I would hardly think
that’s worth risking your life for.
It’s true I know nothing about her…
And that it may fall short of
being worthy of risking my life.
However, Ichigo wants to save her!
So that’s enough!
I don’t need any other reason
to risk my life!
Aw geez, what a problem.
Well, if you’re that determined,
then it would be insulting
to ask you to go away.
I guess it can’t be helped.
Then, I guess I’ll have
to take your life!
Ichigo…
I will…defeat him.
I will probably have to risk my life.
Should I survive, this time, I will vow…
The same promise as that time,
in the same words as that time.
Damn you!
Take that!
How's this?!
Damn!
You’re so stubborn!
Drop dead!
Y-You’re…
Oh no, let’s get out of here!
Aw damn!
You remember this!
Why were you just standing there, Chad?
It’s Sado.
Enough of that already!
This time, you were lucky
I happened to be around,
but you could have gotten seriously hurt.
You’re incredibly strong.
Why’d you let those guys
beat you up like that?
Why didn’t you go at it
like the time you saved me?
I made a vow…
to never use my fist for myself.
It’s a promise I made with Abuelo.
Abu… come again?
Abuelo. It means “Grandpa.”
His name is Oscar Joaquin de la Rosa.
What ethnicity is that?
Mestizo.
He’s Mexican.
Before I came here,
I was in Mexico.
Last month when
you introduced yourself,
you said you were from Okinawa!
Did I?
Yeah, you did!
Oh, never mind!
Say whatever you want.
Fine, I won’t save your hide
the next time!
By the way, that thing you’ve always got
around your neck…
Is that something precious?
Yeah… Sure is.
It’s precious…
Probably more than my life.
Looks like a foreign coin.
Where’s it from?
Mexico.
Geez! There you go again. Hey?!
Hey?!
Whose is this?
It might belong to one of
that earlier bunch.
It's a hassle…
but I guess I’ll get it back to them.
You should just throw it away!
Neither was a lie.
I was born in Okinawa,
and went to Mexico.
That’s all…
I lost my parents when I was young.
With no other relatives,
I was taken in by
my Abuelo in Mexico.
I was eight years old.
Yasutora!
But I was a rotten kid,
hopelessly spoiled.
I relied on my size
and if anyone so much as irritated me,
I would punch them out.
And the one who strictly scolded me
into shape was Abuelo…
Back then, I was truly, hopelessly spoiled.
And…on that fateful day,
I was hopelessly careless.
Huh?
These wires are awfully thick.
I don’t think I can break out of these…
This is the end for the Chad
of Mashiba Middle School.
So, how does it feel?
Does it hurt enough to
make you want to piss? Huh?!
So if it hurts, I’m supposed to piss?
Then I guess it’ll be a while…
Sorry.
Oh yeah?
Then, how’s about this?
I know!
You value this more than your life.
So if you lost this,
then you’ve got to die, right?
So die, you fool!
Wait!
Those big and strong fists of yours –
for what purpose
were you blessed with them?
Learn about that.
This amulet will help you.
Thanks to Abuelo,
I grew up to be a decent person.
I could thank him until
my voice went hoarse,
and it still wouldn’t be enough.
Eh? Wha…?!
No way can you break that.
Kick him down--
Bastard!
Huh?! What the--?!
Thanks!
You’re…
Ichigo Kurosaki of Mashiba Middle School!
Hey, listen up!
Why are you fishing around
in Yokochin’s pocket?
Oh! There it is!
Yokochin, are you all right?
Yokochin!
D-Damn it! I told you guys
not to call me that name…
How many times do I
have to tell you?!
Yokochin!
Ah, excuse me.
I’d like to call an ambulance.
A-An ambulance?
Damn you!
Are you worried about Sado
before you even fight us?
Don’t mock us!
The location is on the second block,
under the bridge.
Number of ambulances…
One, two, three, four, five…
Five ambulances.
Damn you!
Hey, how’s about this, Chad?
You stay the same and
not throw any punches for yourself.
Instead, you throw those punches for me.
And I’ll throw the punches for you.
If you’re going to stake your life
to protect it,
then I’ll stake my life
to protect it, too.
It’s a promise.
Yeah…
That’s right. It’s a promise.
That’s why I can’t lose…
Those big and strong fists of yours –
for what purpose
were you blessed with them?
I’m sorry…
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll always stay close to you
Now and forever
Kenny, one of your bells fell off.
Oh yeah? Wait a sec,
I'll fix it right away.
Did you set your hair yourself?
A man's got to look good!
Kenny, you're so talented!
Want me to do your hair, too?
No, no thank you.
Don't be bashful.
Really?