Nelliel and Nnoitora once worked
together as fellow Espada.
Nnoitora, however,
detested Nelliel's presence and
challenged her to duels on
numerous occasions.
He was beaten each time.
You are a beast.
I don't acknowledge you
as a warrior.
You are not worthy of
being my opponent.
I don't intend to be
responsible for a life
that doesn't belong to a warrior.
Nnoitora could never defeat
Nelliel one on one,
but with the cooperation
of Szayelaporro,
he set a trap and at last succeeded
in defeating Nelliel.
He then threw her out of Las Noches.
At that moment, Spiritual Pressure
flowed out of her injured body,
and Nelliel turned into a child.
Look at you now, Nelliel!
That body suits you perfectly!
What is this place?
We must protect her.
From Nnoitora and Szayelaporro,
from suffering and hardship.
From all dangers and disasters.
We must take Master Nel
who has grown so weak,
and protect her with our lives!
As one who has sworn to serve
Master Nel as our master…
That is our one remaining,
and final duty.
What's the meaning of this?
Okay, I got it!
Now, Dondochakka!
Release Bawabawa!
If Master Nel says she will fight,
it is our duty to assist!
We cannot be bothered
by the likes of you…
Szayelaporro!
Here we come!
Will you still resist?
You sure don't know when
to give up, do you?
I thought it would be rough,
so I really didn't want to use it
so soon after I returned to this form.
Praise…
Gamuza.
Lanzador Verde.
"The likes of you," is it?
That's big talk coming
from lowly Fracciónes.
Wait a minute.
What are you trying to…
take out?!
Ohh! He managed to
strike the bastard!
Or rather is that okay
to broadcast?
Did you see that?!
This is my sword,
called "Ultima"!
This beautiful and shiny blade
is a saber of light
that shows its form because
of Reishi pouring out.
What do you think, Uryu?
Looks familiar, doesn't it?!
Doesn't it look like your thing?!
It doesn't! And don't go
calling it a "thing."
I was expecting a bigger reaction,
you gutless fool!
He called me, whose organs
have been destroyed,
"gutless" as in "without guts."
GUTS
GUT-LESS
Hi, good boys and girls!
This character means guts!
It's a bit difficult,
but this is how it's written.
And, if we take this out,
GUTLESS
we get "gutless"!
That wasn't funny at all.
You have a lot more energy left
than I expected.
For someone who's gutless…
whose organs are really gone…
Let me tell you!
My thing is a lot harder
than your thing,
and it throbs and…
PLEASE STAND BY
Good boys and girls!
Please do not do this at home!
What do you say now that
you know my power?!
Go…
You guys.
Wring that annoying
eel monster to death.
In the meantime…
I'll squash the two below it!
This is my sword!
Szayelaporro…
There is but one reason
for your defeat.
You took us lightly,
thinking of us as adversaries
you once defeated.
In order to protect Master Nel,
we have never stopped training.
We are now at a different level
than we once were.
Take this.
And perish!
This is the new Cero we created!
Incredible…
The lights from the Cero
joined together.
Cero Sincretico!
It's over, Nnoitora.
What is?
Relax…
I will not take your life.
What? Why did Nel…
It's over, Nelliel!
Nel!
Kurosaki!
Give it up.
Nelliel was your final light.
It's gone out.
It's over for all of you here!
Tesla, I'll let you take over.
This guy has nothing left.
Do what you want with him.
Yes, sir.
Kurosaki!
Stay still, pet!
You just watch quietly
from here, okay?
Gore them,
Verruga.
Pet, keep quiet.
Listen…
Your job is to be quiet and watch…
as the man who came
to rescue you
ends up pounded into
a beat-up old rag!
Kurosaki… Kurosaki…
Kurosaki…
Why?
Why didn't it work on you?!
Why didn't it work on me, you ask?
Fused forces definitely possess
immense destructive power.
However, if they do not
blend completely
and fail to transform totally,
they readily split into two forces.
I simply applied a tiny amount
of power to the right point.
Why?
Why is it?!
Why is such a thing possible?
Why? Why? You sure ask
a lot of questions.
But, I will tell you.
The reason is because
you gave me too much time.
Did you think I wouldn't notice
just because you changed
your masks?
I realized it right away,
from the moment I saw you two.
I knew that you two
were Nelliel's Fracciónes.
That's why I continued to
measure everything.
Your movements, Spiritual Pressure,
and experience as you fought
with the Quincy and Soul Reapers.
What?!
Cero Sincretico, was it?
That was a totally powerful
and wonderful technique.
However, it was within
my expectations.
Pesche Gatiche…
Dondochakka Bilstin…
I will tell you.
The reason why you lost
was because
you did not use this technique
at the moment this fight began.
Now then…
Can I assume you've exhausted
all your tricks?
You worked very hard,
all of you.
But I think this fun, but lengthy,
performance is finally about to come to a conclusion.
Let's end…everything.
Aaroniero Arruruerie.
The last remaining Espada
from the first generation
has met a tragic end.
And, as I thought…
They were soft at the end.
Soft…
Each and every one  of them.
I thought, "They can't be alive.
They should be dead."
But there is no way to be
sure that they are dead
unless you break off their heads.
Do not worry, Aaroniero.
I will clean up your mistake.
Both of them are
still just barely alive.
We will begin retrieval.
Kurosaki… Kurosaki…
Kurosaki!
Inoue…
It's over.
Kurosaki…
Kurosaki… Kurosaki…
Kurosaki… Kurosaki!
Kurosaki!
This is stupid.
Tesla… Finish it.
What is this?
You look like you're about to die.
Ichigo!
Cero Sincretico had no effect!
The fusion was insufficient!
In that case, join us,
Uryu and Renji!
Leave it to us! Let's go!
– Combine!
Ishida! What're you waiting for?
Get over here!
I absolutely refuse.
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today, I'll tell you about Nelliel.
Formerly the Espada Number 3,
her special technique is "Cero Doble"
and her Zanpakuto is called "Gamuza."
Her kill technique is "Lanzador Verde."
She's very pretty.
What're you talking about? This is you.
What?! This is how you see me?
Do you have bad eyes?
You don't seem very bright.