connected to the Kasumiohji Clan.
the captain was acting on his own,
of Ichigo Kurosaki and the others?
Ichigo and his comrades enter
the Soul Society in pursuit of Rurichiyo
and disrupt the marriage ceremony
being held in the Kasumiohji Clan.
However, they fall into Kumoi’s trap and
end up surrounded by
Soi Fon and Squad 2.
In order to find the real Rurichiyo
as soon as possible,
Ichigo gets away from Soi Fon and
escapes into an underground passage,
but he is discovered by Squad 3 and
gets into a fierce fight with Amagai.
However, Shu Kannogi throws himself
between them to stop the fight,
and upon learning of
the Kasumiohji Clan’s dark secrets,
Amagai declares that he will support
Ichigo and his comrades.
Move quickly!
This is such a pain.
Lieutenant Omaeda!
Hmm?
The security group has been deployed!
What is your next order?
Maintain present status.
Huh?
Besides us and Squad 3,
all squads have been marching
around since this morning.
Now, the Punishment Force
has joined them.
Which means there’s nothing else for us to do
but to stay put for now.
If they were to harbor Kibune,
this would be the most suspicious place.
But if the Court Guards keep
coming and going,
the chances are low that he’d approach.
I have to search somewhere else.
This is…
Captain and Ichigo Kurosaki have…
The possibility of a conspiracy
inside the Kasumiohji Clan?
So what’ll we do now?
I have several places in mind.
We’ll check those.
Just us?
I’m helping you due to
my personal feelings.
I cannot involve my squad.
So I sent them back to the barracks.
Aida and a few others have agreed
to help out though.
Say… Why have you decided
to help us so easily?
You may end up making enemies
of other Soul Reapers.
I told you, I have some issues too.
Please tell me your reasons.
Well…
First, let’s get away from here.
I’ll explain while we move.
Right.
Shu…
Oh, yes!
We’d better report this
to Captain Komamura!
R-Right!
There’s a man named Kibune
who is a Third Seat in my squad.
He’s extremely skilled.
But it seems he’s somehow
connected to the Kasumiohji Clan.
What?!
Furthermore, it seems
he’s hiding that connection.
Having ties under current circumstances is one thing,
but he’s had connections long before
you guys stirred up trouble.
You think it’s connected to this incident?
I don’t know.
In any case,
I’ve been having Kira watch him.
And now Kibune has been missing
since this morning.
Kira is searching for
Kibune’s whereabouts now.
So that’s why he wasn’t around?
It’s difficult to suspect a comrade.
But I have a bad feeling about this.
Then rather than coming with us,
shouldn’t you report this to the higher-ups?
Kibune is a man I chose personally.
If it’s proven that he’s been dishonest,
it’s my responsibility.
When that happens,
I’ll deal with him myself.
Also, you should know this.
The Thirteen Court Guard Squads
are very stubborn.
It’ll take too long to
run things by them first.
That’s for sure.
You said you had an idea about
where Ruricchi might be?
First, we’ll check out relevant areas
inside the Kasumiohji mansion.
That is the end of
Captain Komamura’s message.
Fine. You may go.
Yes, sir!
Head Captain, what will you do?
Make it known to all squads.
Captain of Squad 3, Shusuke Amagai,
is suspected of grave offenses!
He is to be pursued immediately!
Yes, sir!
I am calling an emergency
Captains’ Meeting!
What?!
Amagai did what?!
Yes.
Squad 7 members witnessed Amagai
collaborating with Ichigo Kurosaki.
I see. And that’s why
we’re being called out?
What’s going on?
Just what’s happening?
Who knows? Just…
Right. We can’t avoid a disturbance.
Hey guys! We’re the ones
who first uncovered this.
Don’t lose to the other squads!
– Right!
Guys, it was around here?
– Y-Yes, sir! That is correct!
But why Captain Amagai?
What are you doing there?
Abarai!
Can’t you see?
I’m looking for someone, just like you.
Really?
But you’re awfully far from
your assigned positions.
I hear your men were the first
to find Ichigo and Captain Amagai.
So it wouldn’t be strange if
they were still in the area, right?
You’re right.
But this is our assigned section.
Go back to your section, as ordered.
What do you think you’re doing, Abarai?
I said to go back. Can’t you hear?
Sorry, Iba.
Don’t get in my way.
What?
Let’s go!
I don’t give a damn about
some Substitute Soul Reaper
or the new captain of Squad 3.
But if there’s gonna be a fight,
Squad 11 will be there first!
Huh?
You’re…
Lieutenant Hisagi of Squad 9.
This is Squad 9’s area.
Go back to your barracks.
What?!
Are you looking for a fight, sir?!
Don’t order us around just
because you’re a lieutenant,
or we’ll get you!
Don’t take us for fools!
I was a fool for trying to reason with you.
I should have used force from the start.
That’s just fine with us!
Hold it!
I’ll take you on, Hisagi!
Madarame!
I don’t know what
this Captain Amagai is thinking.
But one thing is certain…
I know Ichigo and Rukia better
than anyone else!
So Iba, let me through.
I don’t want you guys to
get involved.
Please.
That’s true.
You know that Substitute Soul Reaper
very well.
However, this is an order.
I cannot abandon my mission.
The same goes for you.
So get rid of your
own personal feelings
and act as a lieutenant should!
If you can’t…
I’ll have you leave,
even if I have to kill you!
I see.
I thought you’d be
a bit more understanding.
If that’s what you say,
then I have no choice.
I’m passing through,
even if I have to use force!
What a problem.
You guys.
Don’t interfere.
How was it?
No good.
No one’s seen anyone suspicious.
I see.
But there’s something even worse!
Word has already spread of
Captain Amagai going with the Substitute Soul Reaper!
What?!
Inose, how did you talk to
the head of security
in this current situation?
They seem to have concluded that the
captain was acting on his own,
so our squad isn’t under suspicion.
I see.
Captain Amagai seemed to be
totally trusting of that Substitute Soul Reaper.
I wonder if he’ll be okay though.
We can’t say anything certain about that.
Up until now,
we’ve left that sort of thinking
to Lieutenant Kira and Kibune.
Speaking of which,
where’s Lieutenant Kira?
He’s been out all morning,
acting on the captain’s orders.
Cripes. What’s going on anyway?
I guess it’s useless to
search at random.
Still, why did Kibune choose
this moment to go into hiding?
Is it connected with the appearance of
Ichigo Kurosaki and the others?
Or…
In any case,
I have to find Kibune quickly.
Where could he have gone?
Now that I think about it,
I know so little about Kibune.
I guess he was closer to Inose and Aida.
They used to talk about things
only they would know.
I knew of its existence,
but this is the first time
I’ve ever entered this place.
Me too.
Well, people don’t use
fighting arenas anymore.
But since we have access to it,
Mr. Kibune felt we could use it
for our training drill.
A place to hide without
anyone noticing.
Perhaps!
That is all!
In summary,
capture Ichigo Kurosaki and Rukia Kuchiki.
And quickly restrain Captain Amagai
who is suspected of aiding these two.
Head Captain!
If I may say so,
Captain Amagai’s actions are unclear.
There are also puzzling aspects
of the actions of Ichigo Kurosaki
and the others.
First of all, what reason would
they have to infiltrate the Kasumiohji mansion?
I can’t believe they would act
without good reason.
I think it’s necessary to
investigate the Kasumiohji Clan.
No!
I forbid any investigation
into the Kasumiohji Clan!
All squads! Carry out my orders!
I don’t understand this.
Yes. The Kasumiohji Clan are
high-ranking aristocrats.
However, it’s probably safe to say they are at
the root of this disturbance.
Yeah, you’re right.
At this rate, the chaos may
even spread to the Court Guard Squads!
Captain!
Nanao?
There’s a squabble in the courtyard!
Man, you’re so stubborn!
Abarai, you haven’t changed at all.
What about you, Iba?
Orders, orders…
Are orders that important?!
That goes without saying.
Covering yourself is the one thing
you’re good at, Hisagi.
Madarame… Damn you!
Split apart, Hozukimaru!
Weren’t you going
to capture Ichigo, Hisagi?!
Damn you!
You don’t give a damn, do you, Abarai?
That’s because you’re in my way!
I see.
Then what you’re doing
is disobeying orders.
No! I will stop them.
That’s all.
What’s the difference?
Listen, Iba.
I can’t understand why
Ichigo and Rukia
would act so recklessly without a good reason.
But Ichigo won’t stop until
he gets his answers…
That guy.
What are you thinking, Madarame?
Take your squad and
return to your position!
Cripes. You’re so stubborn as usual.
Think a little, will ya?
They’re on to something
we haven’t noticed!
That’s why Ichigo and
the others are taking action!
Can’t you understand?!
No, I don’t!
That’s no reason for them
to disrupt the order!
You’ve met him before, haven’t you?!
That’s got nothing to do with this!
Jeez. That’s why you’re such a loser!
That’s none of your business!
What’s the matter?
– Lieutenant Kira!
This is…
It’s Sugama, the one who’s been
missing since last night.
The one who went after
Third Seat Kibune last night?
Captain Amagai ordered us
to return to the barracks,
and the squadsman
who stayed back found him.
You can return to the barracks.
– Huh?
Oh, it opened.
Anything is worth trying after all.
It is just like Ichigo said.
Thank goodness,
no one seems to be around.
It seems nothing ever goes
the way you want it to.
Who are they?
And that girl.
That’s Princess Rurichiyo
of the Kasumiohji Clan.
Just what is going on?
I’d better let Captain Amagai know.
Still, the fact that the princess
of the Kasumiohji Clan is here…
That means…
Who are you?
Don’t underestimate me.
You chose the wrong opponent.
Now you will tell me what
you’re doing here.
What’s so funny?
You’re the one who chose
the wrong opponent.
What?
Why you—
What’s with their power?
Their speed and Spiritual Pressure
rose suddenly.
Let me go! I said to let go of me!
You are from
the Kasumiohji Clan, aren’t you?
I am Rurichiyo!
You are being insolent!
– Hold it!
– Let me go!
You’re in my way!
Strange…
It’s not just us.
In various places, Spiritual Pressure
is going every which way.
All this chaos resulting from
just one order.
This is most unusual, isn’t it?
So let me go!
I’ll prove their innocence.
If you’re going so far as to promise that…
Well then,
I’ll believe in Ichigo Kurosaki too.
You’re not the only one.
It’s likely we all do.
Most men have faith in that fellow.
However, we have to carry out
our orders and
find those two and Captain Amagai.
In order to prove their innocence,
as you say.
If you cross swords with Ichigo,
you’ll understand why
he’s raising hell like crazy.
Until then…
I won’t let anyone get in his way!
So what’ll you do?
And if they’re really doing
something wrong?
We’ll deal with it at that time!
I will definitely…
– kill him!
Damn! Can I catch up?
I must say, everything you do
is always too late.
The princess left long ago, Lieutenant Kira.
As I thought.
Everything that’s happened is
your doing…
Third Seat Kibune.
Hisagi, you saw a lot of action today.
Well, it was like this until recently
when Squad 3 started getting
all the attention.
Huh?
I’d better do my best here.
It’s been bugging you, hasn’t it?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Man, I’m hungry.
Want to go eat something?
All right!
I’ll take you somewhere
you can eat free, good food.
Come with me!
What? You came again?
Just in time.
Want some leftovers from lunch?
Sure!
Leftovers?
But free, fancy foods…all you can eat!
Don’t complain.
Don’t you have any pride?