You grave destroyer.
Tch...
Hello, Zack.
You little shit.
I went to all the trouble
of making you a grave.
Why would you destroy it? Are you crazy?
It was a pretty shabby grave,
for all the trouble you went to.
I was in a hurry.
We can keep that same gravestone
for you, though, right?
It's a perfect match for you.
I'm gonna put you in a grave first, brat!
My name isn't "brat" or "little shit."
My name is Eddie.
Shut up!
You ruined her grave, too.
I'll have to remake it.
You know, I fell in love at first sight.
Huh?
All I ever did was make graves
for people who had been killed,
and I was getting bored.
I like making graves,
but I feel no affection toward
the people who go in them.
There's no beauty in that.
I want to make the perfect grave for Rachel.
She's close to my age,
and above all, I can relate to her.
Loving and being loved... Mutual love.
It must be far more beautiful than
one-sided love for a messy corpse.
Ah...
Of course, I don't mind it being messy,
if it's what she wants...
Quit talking like a sick freak.
She's a perfect fit with my aesthetic.
Which is why...
I'll be the one to kill her.
Get over yourself, you stupid brat!
Where'd you go, you little shit?!
This might be useful.
Another letter...
"There is nothing to worry about.
You and I want the same thing."
Who's there?
Hey, Rachel, I'm going to
grant your wish for you.
But I have a wish of my own.
I'd like you to entrust yourself to me.
Mutual love is great, after all.
Don't you agree?
I understand you well.
You want to die, right?
So...
Tell me "yes."
We finally meet, Rachel.
I'm Eddie.
You don't have to run away.
I won't try to kill you out of
the blue, like those others.
Especially that Zack.
He's so messy about killing people.
He has no aesthetic at all.
Don't worry.
I know you very well.
I know what happened to your mom and dad,
and everyone else around you.
I know everything.
Everything?
Yep.
So don't worry.
Why am I here?
You don't remember?
If you don't, that's fine.
What do you m—
More importantly, I can
give you a painless death,
and I can even make the
perfect grave for you.
I'll make your wish come true.
Hey, why aren't you saying anything?
Come on, please, Rachel...
Tell me "yes."
That damn brat!
Hey! Get back here! Right now!
Damn it. He can't hear me.
That little grave-digging bastard!
Is he trying to one-up me?
I can't have the little
bitch dying on me yet.
She said there was a room inside
and to the right, didn't she?
Why do I have to go through
all this trouble, damn it?!
What is there to be unsure of?
Come on, try saying your wish out loud.
I want to die.
See? I knew it!
I'll be the one to kill you, so just...
Say "yes."
Oh, this is infuriating!
Is it because of him?
Why are you with Zack?
Because he...
promised that he'd kill me.
Well, then, I'll kill you in his place.
But then he'll never get out of here.
That's not a problem at all!
Who cares what happens to a guy like that?
Still...
Hey! Can you hear me?
Are you in there?
Ugh, that voice is absolutely grating.
Go on, choose!
Do you want to be killed by him or me?
My beloved Rachel...
I'll give you beautiful, blessed rest.
What you call your
"aesthetic" is pretty damn vague!
You're gonna kill her while she
still has that boring look?
What's wrong with you?!
Oh, keep it down!
I'm talking to Rachel right n—
Not you, you grave-digging bastard!
Hey, can you hear me?
I mean you, bitch!
Me?
Yes, you!
Don't think I'm gonna let
you go off and get killed!
There are a lot of people in this
building who want to kill you!
But I'm gonna be the one
to do it, and that's that!
I swear to God.
To God?
Yeah, that's right.
So...
Don't you dare let anyone else kill you!
All right.
Try as hard as you can
to break the wall here.
Hey.
Why, Rachel?
Where is the little shit?
There wouldn't be any problem
with me killing you.
Moron! There's a shitload
of problems with that!
You're such a savage.
Shut your mouth!
Rachel, is this really
who you want to kill you?
He'll make a mess of you.
It's better if I do it.
Quit your damn yapping! Get out here!
I'll kill you!
Rachel, I will be the one to kill you.
So I'll wait for you, okay?
Tch.
You know, you're weak as hell, anyway.
You'll probably die pretty
soon even if I don't kill you!
Yeah.
Huh?! Like I told you before,
if you wanna die, make yourself useful first!
If I'm useful to you, you'll kill me, right?
That's what I've been telling you, isn't it?
You said it a minute ago.
Huh?
God.
You said "God."
To God...
Yeah, to God.
You said you'd swear to God.
Will you really...
...swear to God that you'll do it?
Will you swear to God...
...that you'll kill me?
You never give up.
Look, I really hate lies!
Okay.
I'll do my best to be useful to you.
As long as you get it.
So, now what?
I heard the sound of a door opening earlier.
I think it's in here.
That "Eddie" kid said he'd be waiting.
Is that right?
Then let's go!
I smell earth.
What? Are there gonna be more graves?
Probably.
Yo, if you do see an open one,
don't jump in it.
I told you, I won't kill myself.
Oh, you did, didn't you?
What'd you say your name was?
Your name.
Rachel Gardner.
I'm keeping you alive to give
you a chance to be useful,
but it's a real pain in the ass...
...having you around.
Hey, we meet again.
Rachel, is there no way I can be good enough?
Do you know about him?
He has no interest in beauty at all.
He was worthless in the past, too.
I read it in his profile.
Then why choose him?
I could kill you, too!
Huh?
Get out of the way, you little shit.
He swore to God...
...that he'd kill me.
That alone is everything to me.
What is "God," anyway?
It doesn't make sense.
I don't believe in...
God never told me anything like that.
That kind of freedom doesn't exist here.
We're not allowed to just do as we please.
The only thing we've been given is the right
to kill people on our respective floors.
And...
this is my floor.
The one who'll kill me...
Eddie...
It isn't you.
You heard her!
Suck on that, you little shit!
You guys don't get to make that choice.
What?
You're gonna have to speak up—
You guys don't get to make that choice!
Rachel, I wanted to make sure you died
as clean and beautiful as you are now.
But...
You can relax.
It's dark, cool, and comfortable
inside the earth.
Rachel...
I'll take you there!
You violent brute!
Worthless loser!
What you're doing ain't any different!
Don't liken me to you!
No matter how physically capable you are,
you can't kill people right because your
head is empty, so you're always angry!
You're the one acting all hard up!
Seems like you've got a lot of
pent-up frustration, for a little kid!
Shut up, idiot!
You shut up, brat!
You're the brat!
The only thing I want, Rachel...
...is you!
I'll close you up for eternity
beneath a beautiful stone...
...after I kill you.
Tch!
You little shit...
No matter how strong you are,
you can't do anything if you can't see.
I dig graves in the darkness all the time,
so I can see just fine in the dark!
Shut up! That didn't hurt one damn bit!
How long can you keep up that tough act?
Whoops! Careful, there!
You little shit! Where are you?!
It's dangerous to swing
that around without aiming!
Shut up!
You!
Me?
Yes, you! Go turn the lights on!
There must be a switch somewhere!
But it's dark...
That's why I'm telling you
to turn the lights on!
Okay, got it.
Wait, Rachel!
He can see?
That's impossible.
Whoa!
Impressive.
I guess that's what they call "instinct."
I made it just for you.
Rachel...
I'll close you up in that
coffin for all eternity.
And I'll make a grave even more
magnificent than the one he destroyed.
So let me kill you.
You're so beautiful, Rachel!
Now our love can be mutual!
I'll make you eternal.
Ra... chel...
Tell me... why?
I even made a coffin for you.
I'm the only one who understands you.
Tell me, Rachel... Why?
Eddie...
That means...
You got shot down, kid!
Rachel...
I wanted to put you in here...
...because I love you.
Hey, that's a perfect fit for you.
I'm impressed you figured out that
the light was controlled by a remote.
The timing of the lights
going out was too perfect.
I figured he had to be
controlling it by hand.
Pretty...
Tch. So where's the elevator that goes up?
Hey!
I think we'll find out if I push this.
It was over here?
That was pretty well done, for you.
Let's go, Ray.
Did you—
What's the holdup?!
Get moving!
Right.
Hey...
Huh?
Was I useful to you, sir?
Would you quit talking to me like that?
It's giving me goosebumps.
Then... is Isaac okay?
Just call me Zack.
Okay.
Was I useful to you, Zack?
Yeah, a little bit.
Keep it up on the next floor, too.
Okay. I'll try to be useful to you.
So...
As you swore to God,
once we get out of here,
you have to kill me.
Do you really have to keep saying that?
I know, all right?
I dunno why we can't just
go all the way to the top.
Tch...
Nasty-looking place.