Odd Jobs Gin-chan
The hell?
It won't make a sound?
What's wrong, Gin-san?
Sugar Content
The damn TV just closed its eyes
with a dark look on its face.
Maybe it has something on its mind?
It hasn't adjusted to
the digital transition?
It's probably time to buy a new one.
Huh?
Is this how the TV always looked?
Now that you mention it...
Some guy from Edobashi Camera
brought it over the other day.
Maybe it's from one of our clients?
I don't remember taking any
jobs that involved
defective merchandise.
Click.
Oh, it turned on.
Gin-san, the TV's fixed.
There's someone familiar on the screen.
A face I didn't want to see
is sticking out of the TV.
This is a 3D TV.
Whoa, 3D? That's amazing.
How do I turn it off?
Press your lips against the button here.
I see.
Sadaharu, turn the TV off.
And turn her off while you're at it.
Bulk trash.
Wait!
Wait a moment!
Huh?
Is something wrong?
N-No, it's nothing.
Just that my glasses broke.
Were they important to you?
Huh?
Y-Yes...
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not a big deal.
They were cheap.
Don't worry about it.
It's just that they were
from my late grandmother...
Huh?
But...
You should probably buy a new pair.
Yes?
Oh, I'm sorry.
They're all I have to remember
her by, but I'm fine,
so don't worry about it.
But you're crying.
I-I'm not!
It's just that a piece
of lens got in my eye.
Wait, what?!
Hmm, it looks okay, but
your eyes are totally red.
You should go to the hospital.
Want me to take you there?
It's okay!
Don't worry about it!
Just ignore those guys.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Let's go, Sa-chan.
Wait!
Something's wrong with this situation!
Why is it all awkward
like I accidentally hit
a girl in the face while
playing dodgeball?!
It was clearly her fault!
She basically moved her face
into the ball and broke her glasses!
I'm sorry, Gin-san.
It's been so long since
my last appearance that I overdid it.
I'm sorry!
I'll be leaving then!
Ah! Sa-chan-san!
Wh-Why are you looking at me?
What are you trying to say?
Even you, Sadaharu?!
Glasses Are Part of the Soul
Glasses for Edogawa
They're all so lovely!
Which one should I pick?
It's like a dream come true!
Gin-san buying a pair
of glasses for me...
Both Nearsighted and Farsighted
Thank you for breaking, Grandma.
I won't let your death be for nothing!
Which should I pick?
Maybe I should ask
Gin-san to pick for me?!
How about one of the pairs
in that clearance bin?
I can't see a thing.
But if this is what you like,
I'll go with these.
Do they fit?
How do I look?
Cute, very cute.
Super Cheap
You look perfect.
Like you were born wearing those.
Mister, Mister.
Are you searching for
engagement glasses?
What the hell are engagement glasses?
I've never heard of those!
And wait,
haven't we met before?
Young lady, I see that
you have excellent taste.
There's a story behind those glasses.
The lens used in the famous
Battle of Red Cliffs
by the Wu to set fire
to Cao Cao's forces
were made by a man whose glasses lenses
were made by a man whose glasses
lenses were seen by a man
who wore this particular
pair of glasses.
That doesn't mean a damn thing!
We'll take these, Gramps.
Since they're used,
give us a 99% discount.
Huh? Wait a moment.
There's a story behind those glasses.
The lens used in the famous Trojan
Horse during the Trojan War...
Um... Thank you, Gin-san.
I don't know how to show
my gratitude for these
wonderful glasses.
I've never received such a
wonderful and stinky present.
Glad to hear it.
Why don't you walk her home, "Gin-san"?
I'll ask Gengai to fix
your Grandma's glasses,
so just use those for the time being.
No, it's okay.
Huh?
Grandma would yell at me
for clinging to the past.
Goodbye...
Grandma's glasses which
were stepped on by Dad
who was stepped on by Mom
who stepped on the poop
of a dog whose owner
had a daughter that owned the
store which sold these glasses.
What?!
That doesn't mean a damn thing?!
I'll think of these glasses
as you and never let them go!
I'll treasure them forever!
Oh well.
Open wide!
Love Garden
Put on the damn glasses!
The hell are you doing
with those glasses?!
Why are you going on a date and going
all the way with a pair of glasses?!
Gin-san, are you jealous of Glassin-san?
Who the hell is Glassin-san?!
You've got it wrong, Gin-san.
I was planning on putting
on Glassin-san right away.
But when I thought of them as you,
I got all nervous...
But I'm finally ready now, so...
I'm going to p-put...
Love Garden
No, I can't say it!
It's too embarrassing!
Why are you making the act of
putting on glasses sound so dirty?!
But they're like another you!
If I put them on, it's like, you know?
The two of us become one!
How can you turn the act of putting
on glasses into such a big deal?
And those are like another random
old guy who owns the glasses store.
Here you go.
I got your glasses fixed.
Just throw away that filthy pair.
Now listen to me.
If you don't want your
glasses broken again,
never sneak into our house again.
I refuse.
How can you come slinking back
and acting like you're my boyfriend?
Now, I...
I...
I'm devoted to Glassin-san!
I want Glassin-san!
It has to be Glassin-san!
I can't even imagine wearing
another pair of glasses.
Don't treat me like one of those
loose-eared sluts that
constantly switches glasses!
The hell is a loose-eared slut?
I got these fixed because
you kept complaining.
Besides, those glasses
aren't your prescription,
so you can't see a thing, right?
That's dangerous.
Leave Glassin-san and me alone!
It's too...
It's too late to try
to be nice to me now!
What's up with this conversation?
Why does it sound like a love triangle?!
Never show your face around
Glassin-san and me again!
Farewell, former glasses!
Farewell, former lover!
I'll buy you a drink.
What's going on?
Why do I feel like I was just dumped?
Hey! Is this country full of idiots?!
Dango House
The target?
A government official,
Zenkichiro Yoneda.
Preparations have been made by
previously dispatched agents.
Your mission is to rendezvous
with the agents and take out the target.
Will you return to the path of evil
for the sake of saving
the weak masses, Sa-chan?
Sometimes, evil can only
be eradicated by evil.
I'm willing to get my hands
bloody to save others...
Sa-chan, those aren't dango.
Echimoya, you're so bad!
Please, I pale in comparison to you.
Come closer.
I have a question to ask
you before we begin.
Who is she?
Intruders!
Damn intruders!
Cut 'em all down!
I'll act as a decoy.
While I draw their attention,
you all should escape.
But Sa-chan...
Don't you understand?
I can't unleash my
strength with you around!
Sa-chan...
Now hurry!
Escape!
Sarutobi, I'll make this easy.
Switch glasses.
I heard that you're not getting
any assassination work.
Only makes sense after all the mistakes,
and you even injured your own men.
There are rumors that you're in a slump,
but you can't fool me.
You can't see a thing, can you?
Th-That's not true.
Can you see what I'm doing right now?
What?
You're just talking to me.
No.
I'm applying Preparation
H in front of your face...
I-Impressive...
You're using your mastery of your other
senses to compensate for
the lack of eyesight.
However, a ninja lives
and dies by the eyes.
You were able to become a member of
the Oniwaban despite your poor eyesight
because of natural talent and hard work,
but those custom-made Iga
glasses also played a role...
Why are you wearing those glasses?
You should know very well that
this world isn't a playground.
It's none of your business.
If I decide to wear these glasses...
If I can't find any work...
If only it were that simple.
The way things stand, you're
gonna get yourself killed.
The former head assassins
are acting suspiciously.
Does Sarutobi intend to desert?
She may intend to defect
to a different group
and provide them with information on us.
Even if she doesn't,
she could still create headaches
by getting herself captured
and leaking information.
We have no choice but to take her out.
Once you've lost their trust,
they'll come for you.
The Assassins of Assassins Squad!
The Lethal Punishers!
P-Punishment?!
Does it involve whips and candles
and things of that nature?!
Why are you getting excited?
These assassins are trained
to kill assassins.
Do you stand a chance
with those glasses on?
I don't care what happens to you,
but if you die a dog's death,
it'll make the rest of the
former Oniwabanshu look bad.
Try to avoid that.
These were the first...
The first present from Gin-san...
But I'm not allowed to wear them.
I believe that you are
Lady Ayame Sarutobi.
Is that correct?
I see that nobody ever
taught you any manners.
A gentleman would
never interrupt a girl who's crying.
My policy is to
gently wipe away the
tears when a woman cries.
I see.
How kind of you.
So what do you do...
...when the woman happens to be
your target for assassination?!
I'll wipe away your tears.
And I'll wipe away your blood, as well.
Ayame Sarutobi the assassin.
Our superiors have
determined that you are
no longer necessary.
Thus, we Lethal Punishers
have been charged with your disposal.
If you have any last words,
we'll hear you out.
Do you have anything to say?
Say...
Would you let me put on my glasses?
Greater Edo Hospital
Fool...
I told you not to die a dog's death.
Why did this happen to Sa-chan-san?
Look at these.
She kept wearing these glasses
when they weren't the
right prescription.
As a result, she kept
screwing up on the job
and attracted the attention
of the higher-ups.
When I found her on the verge of death,
she was still holding those glasses.
I don't care how happy they made her.
She's a fool.
Can you dispose of those?
Greater Edo Hospital
They'll find this place very soon.
She won't stand a chance
if those are still around.
Well, if she still
refuses to put these on,
that's the end of that.
Hey, hemorrhoid ninja!
You're going to leave
Sa-chan all alone here?!
Sorry, but ninja don't band
together the way samurai do.
If you don't want to
die, stay away from her.
I'm sure that's what she wants.
I'm...
I'm sorry...
They were a present from Gin-san.
I promised to treasure them.
I'm sorry I broke my promise.
Sa-chan...
You don't need to see a thing right now.
Don't need to see a thing.
When you wake up,
there won't be any
cracks in your vision.
Gin-san...
Can't help it.
I'm the one who broke her glasses.
The Assassins of Assassins
of Assassins Squad!
Lethal Odd Jobs is moving out!
The hell are you doing in my house?!
Why are you sneaking
into my house in the
middle of night to make fried
rice all dramatic-like?!
And turn off the damn music!
It's bothering the neighbors!
What is this?
Seriously, why are you here?
Well, people usually get
hungry around this time.
So we were making a little snack.
Wait up. This is my house.
Those are my eggs, my ham.
My fried rice!
Don't worry!
We made enough for you!
That's not the issue here!
I'm asking why you're in my house!
Don't tell me you actually
came here to make fried ri--
Oh, Sadaharu's here.
Over there.
Just set her down there.
Uh, wait. Er, what?
Why did you bring Sarutobi here?
Well, we're going to
take on the assassins,
but we don't want to
fight in a hospital.
So we were trying to find a good place.
Oh, I see.
I'm rich and own a big house.
Plus I'm single so
nobody else is around,
so nobody else will be inconvenienced.
That's the logic you used.
What kind of logic is that?!
Now, now, now.
We're just borrowing your place.
It won't take long.
We're just gonna kill
four or five assassins.
You're going to turn my
house into a murder scene?!
Hey, why are you eating?!
Get out of here!
I don't want blood and
innards all over my room!
I'm actually a clean freak!
That's why you're still single.
Women can't stand men who are perfect.
The ideal would be a man
whose room is a little messy.
Hey! That's way too big of a mess!
What should we do, Gin-san?
Now that the trap is
set, where do we wait?
Wait!
What are you doing?! Seriously, stop!
How about the ceiling?
Hey!
I'm seriously gonna kill you!
I'll assassinate your ass
before the assassins get here!
I'll wait here.
Wait! I got it!
I got it so stop!
I'll help!
I'll give you a hand!
So stop destroying my house!
Uh, do you read me?
Hattori here.
I'm right above Sarutobi.
Is everybody in position?
No problem. Everything's fine.
It's really hot.
Are you sure about this?
It's not perfect, but
I did what I could.
We're up against professional killers.
They know that Sarutobi and
the rest of you are here.
They'll be extremely cautious,
so we can use that to our advantage.
Kagura  Shinpachi  Sadaharu
Sarutobi  Zenzo  Gintoki
I left the entrance to the room where
Sarutobi is completely unguarded.
Enemy  Enemy  Enemy
So they won't come from that direction.
It's clearly a trap.
They'll circle around.
If anything goes wrong,
let us know immediately.
Be ready to react if they
come through the front.
Don't let your guard down.
And don't destroy my house.
Got it?
Roger.
Yeah.
Damn, why do I have to do this?
Huh?
Wait a second.
Was someone asleep?
Someone sounded asleep!
I'm calling roll again.
Roger.
Oh, shit.
Hey!
Somebody ran off to Don Quijote!
Don't give me that crap!
I'm trying to help here!
Get your ass back here,
whoever went to Don Quijote!
Roger.
Hey, Shinpachi.
Help me put Kagura on Sadaharu's back.
You all went to Don Quijote!
Wait a second!
One of you is asleep in Don Quijote?!
The hell is going on?!
Why did they all ditch me?!
They could have invited me along!
Not that I wanted to go!
Oh, right.
Could you buy some Preparation H?
I'm out. The suppository type.
Hello?
Do you read me?
Stop lying!
Don't pretend to be asleep!
Even the dog was
pretending to be asleep!
The bastards are toying with me.
I'm pissed!
Screw this!
I've had enough!
This sensation...
Someone's here.
Two on the roof.
One inside.
And in the yard...
I can smell multiple humans.
As expected.
But it doesn't matter
how many there are.
This time, we'll finish her off.
Along with the others.
Th-They're here...
Excuse me, do you have
any Preparation H?
The hell are they doing?!
Hurry!
Hurry back!
To Be Continued
Next Episode
Glasses Prevent You From Seeing Certain Things
Next time:
Glasses prevent you from
seeing certain things.