Ichigo, Sado, and Ishida
undergo harsh training
in preparation for the impending
showdown with Aizen.
Rukia and Orihime also head
to Soul Society in order to get stronger.
Hitsugaya's advance troops
have remained in Karakura Town.
One day, a Mock Arrancar
that can continuously multiply
appears before them.
If they don't destroy
its main body,
the Mock Arrancar
ill continue to multiply.
It all began when
she encountered the Mock Arrancar...
We've concluded that Yui Toyokawa
is a clone created by the Mock Arrancar.
And now Yui is helping
the Mock Arrancar absorb Shota as well.
Yui?! What's wrong?!
Don't... Get away immediately...
Yui!
Don't!
What?!
Growl, Haineko!
Yui!
Are you all right?!
What?!
That's...
Big brother!
Don't!
Big brother...run away.
You bastard!
I can't...
I won't run away and
leave you behind ever again!
So that's the main body...
Big brother...
I'm glad he didn't eat you.
What are you saying?
I'm going to protect you.
It's no good... I...
What's wrong?!
Yui!
Crap... What is this?
Why can't I move?!
Yui... Yui...
This girl...
I never expected her to
still have the will to defy me.
But it ends here!
Yui!
Yui...
Hado 4: Byakurai!
Get a hold of yourself, Shota!
Ms. Rangiku... Yui got...
I know.
Soul Reapers...
I can't forgive you anymore.
Forgive me?
I ate this girl.
And I got this power!
Hold steady.
Get behind me!
Soul Reapers are nothing
in the face of the power I've stored up.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Squad 10 Lieutenant...
Rangiku Matsumoto!
Don't underestimate me!
A lieutenant?
That's good.
Now I'm looking forward
to eating you!
Too slow!
Now to finish you off!
Growl, Haineko!
Don't underestimate me!
Where'd he go?!
Shota!
I'm coming...
Now, which one of you
should I eat first?
I'm not finished yet!
Matsumoto!
Step aside!
Frost unto the Heavens,
Hyorinmaru!
What's this?!
Captain!
Get Shota!
Shota!
Ms. Rangiku!
It's getting out!
Who are you?!
Squad 10 Captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya!
A captain?!
Since you didn't know that we were
in the World of the Living,
it doesn't seem like you're
taking orders from Aizen!
I guess that means
that you mutated
after absorbing
a human's Spiritual Pressure!
You bastard...
This is it. Prepare yourself!
A-Are you all right with that?!
If you kill me,
that girl will disappear with me!
I thought so.
Those are the results
we got from Soul Society.
But such threats
won't work against us.
Don't!
Shota!
Yui's still alive!
She told me to run away!
So...
I can't weigh one soul on
the same scale as the entire town.
Don't!
Hey!
- Shota, stop!
- Don't!
Out of the way!
Yui!
Wait!
You missed your best chance
to defeat me.
What?!
As long as I'm in this sub-space,
you won't be able to find me.
But I can hide
my Spiritual Pressure,
attack souls and
make as many clones as I want.
Behold! My army of servants!
Captain Hitsugaya!
Madarame! Ayasegawa!
What's with these numbers?!
No wonder there was no end to them
no matter how many we destroyed.
I can multiply about 16 times in a day!
It took you too long to realize that.
With this many of me, it'll be impossible
to stop me from multiplying.
I've eaten most of
the souls in this town...
I'll have to eat the humans next.
Later!
Wait up!
Wait, Madarame!
We'll never end this if we
cut down every one of them.
That's true,
but we can't leave them alone.
Squad 11 is a battle squad.
Rather than thinking
about bothersome things,
we'll crush them until
we run out of spiritual power.
Please let us go!
You can think of a way to
deal with them in the meantime.
All right!
- Let's go!
- Okay!
This is Hitsugaya.
This is the Department
of Research and Development.
We encountered
the Mock Arrancar's main body,
but it got away.
Can you track it?
We're doing that right now.
It's no good!
We really can't track it...
I'm unable to provide support.
We lost sight of it.
There are no traces
of any distortions, either.
Damn...
I'm very sorry.
What's this?!
What is it, Rin?!
We've pinpointed
the location of the sound
that the Arrancar uses
to control souls!
What do you mean?
The main body produces the sound,
while the clones only act as speakers.
I'm asking you how it's done.
In other words,
it's as if the main body
and the clones are connected
by a wireless connection.
They probably deliver
the spiritual power
they absorb to the main body
in the same way!
If that's true, we may be able to
pinpoint the location of the main body
by looking at the distribution
of the clones.
Um... Am I wrong?
All systems, analyze the distribution
of Spiritual Pressure!
All right. This is good!
Send them the coordinate data, Rin!
Yes, sir!
Shota...
The Arrancars we're fighting
were originally called Hollows.
They're fallen souls.
A soul that still has
an attachment to the world
and becomes corrupted,
loses its heart and becomes a Hollow.
We Soul Reapers exist
not only to save souls,
but to save Hollows as well.
By cutting Hollows
with our Zanpakuto,
we wash Hollows of their sins
and lead them to Soul Society.
It's all necessary in order for them
to be born anew.
We couldn't protect Yui.
But we can still save Yui's soul.
Ms. Rangiku...
This time, it's your turn!
Hold on.
Let's save Yui's soul together.
Are you finished talking?
Let's go!
- Yes, sir!
You can't defeat me
with attacks like that.
URAHARA'S SHOP
What are you doing?!
Are you those
multiplying Arrancar clones?!
Here I go!
What's with their numbers?!
Looks like my routine chores...
Will have to wait
for the time being, nya!
Don't slack off!
I knew it. The clones aren't
spread out over such a wide area.
When I calculate
the location of their source
by analyzing the distribution of
the appearance of the clones...
Karakura Town, East...
Near the river.
So how do we find him?
According to the Department
of Research and Development,
he's only hiding
his Spiritual Pressure.
The main body needs to be able to
communicate with its clones.
There's no way that he'd be hiding
in a place that's shut off from
the World of the Living,
like Hueco Mundo.
He's probably hiding
within a special barrier.
I see...
In that case, if we hit his barrier
with our Spiritual Pressure
we should be able to break it.
Understood... I'll get to that...
No... I'll do it...
In order to pry him open
from his protective space
we need a proportional amount
of Spiritual Pressure.
You take care of the enemy
when it comes jumping out!
Yes sir!
Here I go!
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
What's this?!
What's going on?!
It's that Soul Reaper from earlier!
He's come this far...
But he won't be able to hit me
if he releases
his Spiritual Pressure recklessly!
Now come out!
Is this Captain Hitsugaya's
Spiritual Pressure?
What is he doing?
Jeez! I just keep
cutting and cutting...!
Will Captain Hitsugaya
be all right?
Maybe he should have
applied for a Gentei Kaijo.
Damn!
Captain...
Yui! Where are you?!
Answer me!
Yui!
Once more!
Fool! You're going to do that again?!
Even if you're a captain,
trying to destroy my space
with Spiritual Pressure is only...
What's this?!
That sound!
It's Yui!
Why is it whistling?!
I should have absorbed
that girl completely...
So why?!
Yui...
Do you know where
it's coming from?!
There!
Captain!
I found you.
How dare you...
I won't forgive you...I won't!
Crush into bits! Dentis!
Here I go!
Is that the best you can do, kid?!
Crap!
I released too much
of my Spiritual Pressure!
Oh well! I'll finish this all at once!
Ryusenka!
My Hierro, Iron Skin,
is like that of the Espada!
So it didn't reach you...
Take a look!
Wh-What?!
Stop!
M-My legs!
Matsumoto! Finish him off!
Yes, sir!
Shota, hold onto the sword!
Okay!
You save Yui!
You won't defeat me...
It stopped moving! Now!
Yui!
Big brother...
Yui...
The souls that it devoured...
What's this?!
Look at that!
What's going on?!
They suddenly disappeared, nya.
Shota!
Ms. Rangiku...
Yui got to go to Soul Society...
Isn't that right?!
She can be reborn, right?!
Yes...
I give you my word.
Then I've got to go
after her right away.
Let's go.
Yeah...
It hurts...Ms. Rangiku...
Everyone's going to be training here
until winter, right?
But you just want to have fun
in the World of the Living, don't you?
That's not true.
As proof, we'll show you our daily lives
in the next episode.
You're just doing
whatever you like...
It's all right.
We've got permission from "him."
Who's "him"? Could it be Ku-?!
- Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
- Golden!
We're having Korean barbecue
for dinner tonight!
- Alright!
- Meat! Meat!
Wait, wait, wait!
Now's not the time
to be eating meat!
- What? You don't like meat?
- What the...
- That's not it!
- This is cheap meat?!
- The town is in danger!
- Cripes Hiyori, can't you get it right?
- Right now,
- And the meat's all stiff!
- Korean barbecue is more important!
- Aww, fine!
- Give me a break!
I'll go by myself!
I'm glad you're full of spirit,
but it's over already.
What?
You're as terrible at
detecting Spiritual Pressure
as you usually are, aren't you?