Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
What incredible Spiritual Pressure…
It just keeps getting heavier and bigger
the closer we get to the top…
Is this really Ichigo's
Spiritual Pressure?!
I wouldn’t know for sure.
We've reached the top!
Just beyond this, huh?
We can't see them…
But I can sense him…
Huh?!
No matter how big his Spiritual Pressure
might have become,
there’s no mistaking the scent of it.
It can't be anyone other
than Kurosaki.
That's strange…
Huh?!
I don't sense
Kuchiki's Spiritual Pressure…
I thought she was
crucified up ahead…
She's already escaped.
Huh?!
Yachiru!
Lieutenant?!
Hey there, Maki Maki!
It seems my old nickname
is back…
What do you mean?!
If Ichigo was able to help Kuchiki escape,
why is he still fighting?!
It means he's fighting
someone powerful.
Just freeing her is not enough
because you know the enemy’s going
to come after her.
To really save her…
He needs to defeat
his enemy thoroughly
and convince them out of the idea
that Kuchiki should be executed.
It's the only way…
That's why Kurosaki is fighting…
He's probably putting everything
on the line.
Th-There really is something wrong
with all of you…
What is Rukia Kuchiki to you?!
You’re willing to risk that much
for just a friend?!
Of course! She's our friend…
She's not just a friend.
Kuchiki is an important person
to Kurosaki…
Inoue…
Because Kuchiki is the one…
who changed Kurosaki's whole world.
Take a look, Ichigo Kurosaki.
This is what happens…
when I abandon all defense…
and risk everything to kill my enemy.
This is the true form of
the Senbonzakura.
Senkei…
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Don't worry.
This procession of
a thousand swords
will not attack you all at once.
This Senkei…
is the form
I show to only those…
who I've vowed to kill
with my own hands.
You are only the second person
to see it.
I'm flattered…
Here I come,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Hey…
Why you!
What is this Spiritual Pressure?!
Inoue, I think we should move
a little further away.
There isn't much
we can do here.
Thank you, Ishida.
But I’m sorry…
I want to stay here.
She knows…
With her power,
she'd only be in Kurosaki's way
if she tried to help him…
She also knows that even if there were
something she could do to help,
Kurosaki would never want that.
She understands all of that,
so she is holding herself back…
waiting…
She's praying for your safety…
And believing in your victory…
Don't lose, Kurosaki…
If you lose…
I will never forgive you.
Win, Kurosaki!
He's fast!
He's become faster since
he revealed his Senkei to me.
But it's still not a speed
I can't match…
I can go a little faster, too.
What's wrong?!
You've gotten quite a bit slower,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
You think so?!
I still think you're moving so slow
that your sword looks stationary…
Hado Four.
Byakurai.
It seems like this is it for you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What…did you say?!
My body…
I can't move!
It seems that you thought
that I've gotten faster after
using my Senkei.
But that's not true.
Senkei compresses my numerous
sword fragments into blades
in order to explosively increase
its killing capabilities.
I haven't gotten faster.
Are you saying
that it's my speed that’s changed
and that I’ve gotten slower?!
You fought well.
You've defeated many captains
and survived slashes from
the Senbonzakura.
It is impressive that
you have fought this far.
But you can feel it, can't you?!
Your flesh and bone are
already dead…
You're only a human…
There is a limit to what
you can endure.
This is your limit.
This is the end, Ichigo Kurosaki!
Move…
Move… Move!
Move!
Why have I come all this way?
Nothing will change…if I don't win!
I want to win…
I…
want to win!
I thought I told you.
It’s a big problem for me
if you get yourself killed…
Impossible…
Who are you?!
Who am I?!
I have no name!
Ichigo, you really suck!
You were crushed by
your own Bankai's Spiritual Pressure.
All the bones in your body
are creaking!
You really are hopeless.
I'll show you…
how to use the Bankai!
A black Getsuga!
This Spiritual Pressure…
that mask…
Are you a Hollow?!
Who cares?!
You don’t need to know,
since you're going to…
Disappear!
Damn! Let go of me!
Don't interfere. Disappear!
You're the one who’s interfering!
Don't you get it?!
You’ll win if you just leave it to me!
Damn! Damn!
You fool!
Sorry for the interruption.
An interruption?!
I see…
I guess defeating me in that form…
is not what he wants…
Very well…
I won't ask you about
what just happened.
I don’t think either of us
has enough strength left
to continue this fight
for very much longer.
We'll finish this…
with the next attack…
Yeah…
Can I just ask you
one more question?!
Why…
don't you save Rukia?!
If you defeat me,
then I will answer that question.
Shukei…
Hakuteiken.
That's amazing.
Sorry, but I don't have any
amazing techniques like that.
Zangetsu only taught me
the Getsugatensho.
The only thing I can do…
is to put all of my Spiritual Pressure
into one attack.
Here I come…
Byakuya Kuchiki!
I won't fall!
You wanted to know…
why I would kill Rukia.
Sinners must be brought to justice.
Once their punishment is decided,
it must be carried out…
That is the law.
So because it's the law…
you'd even kill your own sister?!
Sympathy towards a relative?!
It’s worthless.
What…did you say?!
Compared to the law,
feelings mean nothing…
I don't have such worthless sentiments
like that to begin with.
The Kuchiki family is one
of the Four Great Noble Clans.
We have to serve as examples
for all Soul Reapers.
Who would enforce our laws
if we didn't uphold them?!
Sorry… I still can't understand…
If I…
If I were in your position…
I would fight the law.
I see…
I was never his true enemy.
He's been fighting the law of
the Soul Society from the beginning.
Ichigo Kurosaki…
My sword was shattered by
your reckless abandon…
I won't chase Rukia anymore.
You win.
Oh no…
I can't stand any longer.
Bonk!
I’m sorry, Kurosaki!
Are you all right?!
Sorry I have such a hard head!
I was trying to catch you…
Inoue?!
Ishida, Chad, Ganju!
Thank goodness…
everyone's all right.
We're not all right.
But compared to
how beat up you are,
we're like unharmed.
What about you, Inoue?!
Are you hurt?!
Huh?! M-Me?! I'm fine!
I wasn't of any use!
But Ishida protected me!
And Mr. Zaraki carried me piggyback!
So I'm fine!
I wasn't in any danger…
It’s just…
I was so worried about you…
Sorry… I couldn't protect you…
Thank you…for surviving…
I'm…glad you're all right…
Thank you… Inoue…
What should we do?!
I got no choice.
Stand back.
You don't really plan to…
This is the door to Central 46!
Doing something like this…
The alarm hasn’t gone off.
Huh?!
I broke down the door,
but the alarm hasn’t gone off.
Someone must’ve defeated
the guards and gotten inside,
then locked the door and made sure
that the alarm wouldn't go off
if someone tried to enter after them…
To keep things quiet…
Wh-What is this?!
What's going on?!
All the days gone by
have made me what I am
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
To the people hurrying by,
“Have your dreams come true?”
I’m still struggling…
Forget returning to my youth;
I want to live today well.
I was born timid.
Out where the sun shines
I fisted my hand tight.
Break out of that place, that time,
and I can change my life
But I could never express
everything deep in my heart
Life’s not easy;
that’s why I can go on.
Captain, is it all right for us to
just barge right into Central 46?!
Why not?!
Well, there are a lot of
important people there, aren't there?!
If I touch up my make-up
and act sexy,
I may be able to get someone rich
to marry me!
Matsumoto… Go home.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers
Golden!
It seems the guys from Mitsumiya
have hired someone to help them.
So what?! We've got
the strongest helper right here.
We are counting on you, Sensei!
Yeah.
Just leave it to me!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late!
Those are the kids
from Urahara's Shop!
They’re the helpers?!
There's a girl!
H-Hey…
That kid is even carrying
a stuffed animal.
What?!
Bostov
That's me!
Tune in again!