Ichigo and his friends undergo intense training
in preparation for the showdown in the winter.
Aizen suddenly sends an
elite group of Arrancars before them.
Hitsugaya's advance troops
and Ichigo confront them,
but they have trouble fighting the Espada.
But Aizen's true goal was to
take Orihime Inoue to Hueco Mundo.
Orihime gives into Ulquiorra's threats
and agrees to go to Hueco Mundo.
She is given twelve hours to
tell one person goodbye.
And so Orihime goes to Ichigo.
Thank you, Kurosaki.
Good-bye.
W-What was that?
Damn it... That hurt...
Anyway, screaming in my sleep
and falling out of bed is so clichéd...I...
Aw... My head hurts...
It's healed... Who did it?!
This Spiritual Pressure...
It was probably Orihime Inoue.
Come immediately, Kurosaki...
It's an emergency.
RANGIKU MATSUMOTO
ORIHIME INOUE
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Rukia...
Why is everyone gathered here in Inoue's room?
Where's Inoue?
Well...
What is the status of the
Spiritual Wave interference?
Yes... We've managed to regulate it.
Put me through.
Ukitake?
This isn't the Head Captain?
I had him switch over to me.
What was your reason for that?
It's because I'm the last person
who saw Orihime Inoue
before she went into the Senkaimon
in order to go over to your side.
Judging from your reaction,
it doesn't seem like she's arrived there.
What's the meaning of this, Ukitake?!
Where did Inoue disappear to?!
Do you know anything?!
I'll tell you my assessment.
The two guards I had placed with her
when she went through the Senkaimon came back alive.
According to them...
We believe that Orihime Inoue
has either been abducted
or killed by the Arrancars.
Killed?!
Captain Ukitake!
That's jumping to conclusions!
I know...
I don't want to say this either.
I was just stating the
worst possible scenario.
According to our information,
Orihime Inoue was attacked by an Arrancar
and then disappeared with the Arrancar.
You've got to be kidding!
That's all you have!
She disappeared.
There's no proof,
but you say that she's dead?!
Don't make such assumptions!
Take a look at this!
I was seriously injured
in yesterday's battle!
No one here could
heal my wounds!
But when I woke up this morning,
it had been healed without a trace!
Furthermore...
Here! On my wrist!
There's still some of
Inoue's Spiritual Pressure!
Are you still going to say
that Inoue's dead now?!
I see...
That is unfortunate...
Unfortunate?
What do you mean by that?!
If it is as you say,
then Orihime Inoue is indeed alive.
But at the same time,
it also means that this is an act of treachery.
Treachery?!
If she had been abducted,
she wouldn't have had the time to meet you.
In short, the fact that she healed
your wounds and disappeared
means that Orihime Inoue went
to the Arrancars of her own accord.
You idiot!
Stop!
You'll just worsen your position
if you talk any more.
I understand what you're saying,
Head Captain Yamamoto.
Therefore...
I, Hitsugaya advance troop member
and Squad 6 Lieutenant Renji Abarai,
will head to Hueco Mundo to bring
the traitor, Orihime Inoue, to her senses!
Renji...
You mustn't.
We now know that the Arrancars
are ready for battle.
All the members of the
Hitsugaya advance troop
are to return immediately
and defend Soul Society.
Are you saying that
you want us to abandon Inoue?
Indeed...
We cannot risk the whole world over one life.
Unfortunately, Head Captain,
I cannot follow that order!
I thought so...
I thought this may happen,
so I'm glad that I have prepared for it.
Captain!
That's how things stand...
All of you, head back.
Don't fight us...
We've been ordered to take you
back by force if necessary.
All right...
Then I won't ask
Soul Society to help me,
but at least tell me how
I can get into Hueco Mundo.
Inoue is our friend!
I'll go save her myself!
Ichigo...
You mustn't!
What?!
We need your help in this battle...
I won't allow you to plot your own
course of action and die for nothing!
Stand by until you receive orders!
That is all!
Let's go.
Ichigo...
I'm sorry.
Orihime!
Oh! No...
Sorry...
Orihime...
Where did you go, Orihime?
Shinji!
This was on the ground outside!
What's this?
I don't know!
Don't pick up things if you
don't know what they are!
But, but it was right in front of our place.
I just had to pick it up!
Say, what is it?
Bandages?
Ichigo?
Why would he go through
the trouble to do this?
Bandages? Why bandages? Why, why bandages?
THANKS
Why, why, why, why, why bandages?!
Hey, why?
That idiot...
What should we do?
Definitely dinner first.
Not a bath?
No! Before that,
a passionate embrace by me!
Anyway...
Let's Ichi-go!
How unfortunate. I missed!
Oh... Sorry...
Brother...
Have some dinner...
Otherwise Yuzu won't be
able to clear the table.
Sorry...
I don't feel like eating today.
Yuzu made all of your favorites.
Sorry, Yuzu.
I-It's all right.
You don't need to apologize!
I'll put it in the refrigerator.
Eat it when you feel hungry!
Come on. Let's go!
Come dad, you too!
Oh! O-Okay...
That's amazing, Ichigo!
You just apologized three times! Three!
That's an amazing new Japanese record!
What's wrong?
You're acting gloomy!
I know. It's that, isn't it?!
Are you constipated?!
That's lame. That's lame, brother!
Oh?!
You want to fight?!
Sorry... Could you move from there?
O-Oh... Sorry, sorry!
Hey, what is this?!
You're kind of out of it!
Oh? Palm reading?
Then I'll take a look at mine, too.
Kurosaki...
It's been a while since I've seen you...
Hasn't it?
I was sad. I didn't think
that you wanted to graduate.
You haven't been hospitalized
due to an accident, have you?
Amazing...
What do you have to say?!
She's pounding on him.
Come on! Come on!
Hey, say something!
You changed your hairstyle...
Thanks for noticing!
I changed it three weeks ago, idiot!
Her hand looks sore.
It does...
Ichigo, Ichigo, Ichigo, Ichigo...
Ichigo!
It's been a while...
It's really been a while!
What have you been doing
during the month you took off?
We were worried about you!
You didn't answer your cell phone, either.
Sorry... I was a little busy.
What are you doing, Mizuiro?
Oh yeah!
I was able to get some tickets
for the screening of Bad Shield 2.
When is that?
Huh? It's December 5th...
All right...
I'll come back by then.
Huh?
Thank you, Mizuiro.
Come back by then?
Ichigo!
Tatsuki...
What is it, Tatsuki?
Orihime's gone!
She's not at home or anywhere!
Her presence has disappeared!
I've been looking all over the place,
but she's not anywhere!
You know where Orihime went, don't you?
What do you mean?
Why would I know?!
Besides, did she really disappear?
Look for her again...
Cut it out!
I've always been able to sense her,
but her presence has disappeared!
I can't sense her nearby!
For a while, I could only faintly sense her...
It was as if she was on the
other side of some wall.
But yesterday, she suddenly vanished!
You know something, don't you?!
Ichigo!
Stop being so pesky!
I told you, I don't know!
You think I don't know, don't you?
I've seen you!
You wear a black kimono!
And you fight strange people!
Ichigo...
That's enough...
Tell me everything you're hiding.
This doesn't concern you.
Arisawa!
Stop! What are you doing?!
Are you all right?
What am I?!
What exactly am I?!
What am I to you?!
Aren't I your buddy?!
Aren't I your friend?!
I've saved you many times
when you've cried!
I've seen you troubled many times!
I've saved you many, many times!
So don't hide things from me...
You idiot!
Ichigo...
Sorry...
Keigo...
Mizuiro...
Take care of Tatsuki.
And don't bother with me.
You idiot...
You idiot!
Welcome...
I thought that it was
about time you came...
Kurosaki.
Why did you think that?
You thought that I might know
a way into Hueco Mundo.
You're correct...
I've made preparations.
I was afraid that Aizen
would go after Inoue's power.
So I left her out of this battle...
But I was too late.
Taking her feelings into consideration,
it was a mistake to leave her out.
I shall do anything I can to help you.
Is that all right?
You'll be going against
Soul Society's judgment.
I'm here because I went
against them in the first place.
You're looking pretty glum, 	Kurosaki!
Ishida! Why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
We're here to go to Hueco Mundo.
Chad!
We heard the details from Mr. Urahara.
We're going too.
Yeah.
You can't! I appreciate your concern, though...
Chad...
Ishida...
At your strength...
Ichigo...
Do you still think that I'm not strong enough?
Believe in us.
Chad...
Don't take this on by yourself...
This is what friends are for!
All right! Is everyone ready?
It seems like you're finally prepared.
Are you ready?
There are terrifying Hollows waiting
for you in Hueco Mundo! Brace yourself!
All right! Hey, why are leading us, Kon?!
Are you going with us to Hueco Mundo?
Sorry. I can't do that.
I have the important role of
protecting the girls of this town!
You aren't going, are you?
Illustrated guide to Soul Reapers!
Captain...
You appeared at a really appropriate time back there, but...
Were you hiding with Captain Zaraki,
waiting for your time to appear?
Renji!
Don't be rude!
No...
That's exactly right.
What?!
That's part of my job.
You did that for us, Brother?!
I don't mind...
I killed lots of time with Captain Zaraki.