Ever since the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me,
my whole world has changed.
I’m Substitute Soul Reaper,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I wield this sword
with all of my soul and strength
to protect my precious friends!
You are my one and only.
No one can take your place.
Never fade, my only flower.
The sun never blinds you.
You are like a flower that blooms in shade.
Exhale those feelings you hold inside.
You are my one and only;
now and forever.
The day may come
when all will rise against us,
but I will protect you.
Never give up, my only flower.
TIME NOTICE THAT
YOU SHOULD NOTICE THAT
NOTICE THAT THERE’S NO OTHER
This is the shower and the toilet, and…
Right next to that
is the washstand.
And…
The refrigerator is here.
Karakura General Hospital
Currently, there are no other patients
on the ninth floor…
so we will be in the nurse's station
on the eighth floor.
If something happens,
call me with this.
A special room, huh?!
This is amazing…
It's also convenient that
we're the only ones on this floor.
The other patients could get hurt
if enemies attacked us.
That sounds like something
he'd take into consideration.
Hm?!
This is my father's hospital…
Ah… So your family also
has a hospital?
Well, that's a lot different
from my family.
Ishida, get some rest
while you can.
We don't know if
they'll come again.
Yeah…
That's right, that's right.
Sleep!
Tonight we'll keep watch,
so you should sleep!
I can't sleep if
you rush me like that.
Stay focused.
Focused?!
Who would have thought that
they were targeting Quincies?
But why do they need
the Quincies' power?
Should we take their word for it?!
Ishida might have been
badly injured
and unable to tell the difference
between dreams and reality!
Then why would he be
taken away by that woman?!
You don't understand the situation.
Are you stupid?!
Well, I already know that you are!
What did you say?! You bi--!
Would you like me to heat up
your pre-packed lunch?!
Yes.
Oh! It's spinning, it's spinning!
The World of the Living sure is amazing!
It's as Rukia said…
But I wonder how it heats up.
Hey, can you ring me up already?!
Oh!
S-Sorry! I'll do that right away!
Thank you very much!
What?!
What a noise…
Are you all right?!
Something fell!
Huh?! This feeling…
Y-Yamada, could you take
a look outside?!
Oh…sure.
Be careful.
What is this?! A meteor?!
I don't think we should go near it.
Excuse me for a second!
Oh…
It's an alien!
Oh!
Oh man, that was close.
I almost got myself killed.
Ganju!
It's been a while!
H-Hana?! Is it really you?!
Ganju!
Hana! What are you doing here?!
That's what I'd like to ask you!
This is bad!
That's the sound of
the police here!
There'll be an uproar
if you're seen here…
Y-You idiot!
You should’ve told me sooner!
This way!
Let's get out of here!
Nothing's happening…
It’s best if nothing happens.
I'm getting tired…
They sure are stupid.
It can't be helped.
Normal humans don't have
the capacity to learn
and they have low physical abilities.
Their lifespans are different too.
Well, that's true.
But isn't it boring if
they aren't a challenge?!
Work isn't always fun.
You're unexpectedly philosophical.
That's what happens
when you live long.
You're right.
He's asleep.
Yeah…
Ichigo.
Huh?
Thank you.
Huh?! What is this about?!
No… I just felt like saying it
all of a sudden.
What is it?!
That's creepy…
Creepy?! Creepy, you say?!
Well, it usually feels weird
if someone says something
like that suddenly.
What's wrong with expressing
my feelings?!
I didn't say there was
anything wrong with it!
It just feels weird.
Look, you're saying there’s
something wrong with it again!
The meaning is different!
It's the same thing!
You're just an insensitive idiot!
What did you say?!
Fine!
I can't take it any more!
It's bothering me!
What?! Is this thing broken?!
Ishida's hospital sure is a wreck!
I'll tighten it. Let me do it!
No!
I can do this myself!
No, you can't!
Not things like this…
H-Hey, find something!
Y-Yeah!
Find what?!
Something to catch this!
Hurry!
Something to catch!
Something to catch…
Renji! When did you get here?!
I could hear you making
a big fuss!
I brought it!
You sure brought a big one.
Geez. What's going on?!
It doesn't seem like it'll stop at all.
It's clearly broken.
Shall I call a nurse?!
We'll be flooded at this rate…
Say…
Huh?
What's that sound?!
Wh-What's this?!
I'm soaked.
It's crazy in here, too!
What's going on?!
It's no good,
it won't stop here either!
I'll bring towels!
Sheesh! Really…
This hospital just looks good,
but in reality…?!
Shut up!
What about it, Ishida?!
Just focus on sleeping!
What?!
Huh?! What's wrong?!
It's a doll!
What is this?!
Be careful!
Ishida!
He's drowning!
Damn!
Move away, Chad!
Ichigo!
I-It's still moving…
Let's get out of this room!
Close the door quickly!
It's coming out!
Stop it with something!
Look.
Our doll surprised them.
They're going to die without
knowing that it's our doll.
Be a little sympathetic towards them.
That feeling has already
worn away…
What?!
It's coming from here, too!
Is this a doll too?!
Where is it being controlled from?!
Stairs
At any rate, let's go down!
It's coming!
Huh?!
Damn it! Again?!
A water doll?!
What?!
I don't know where this thing
is being controlled from,
but this Bount's ability is water!
Water?!
Then we'll have to go somewhere
where there's no water!
Sado!
I-I can't breathe…
I'll split it in two!
All right!
What?!
Dang it!
Damn! There's no end to this!
Ichigo…
What should we do?!
I see!
Everyone, get away!
The one who reigns…
mask of flesh and blood,
all creation, the flutter of wings…
The one who crowns us
with names!
Gathering of heat and war,
beyond the seas in reverse,
take steps to the South!
Shakkaho! Red Flame Cannon!
It worked as I thought it would!
Are you all right, Sado?!
What is this?!
Please calm down!
A Soul Reaper is with them, huh?!
They're more trouble
than I thought.
Emergency Exit
It's all right…
Don't panic.
Toilets          Treatment  Rooms
Blood Collection Room
Operating Room
Radiation Room
Drip Infusion Therapy Room
Nurses' Station
It seems that the water systems
are focused around the stairs…
It's not attacking anyone else.
That's because I'm their target…
We should search for a different exit.
Let's take this box down and leave!
We've taken too much time.
We've gone beyond the planned time.
But we'll deal with it.
Yeah. We've had this kind of thing
happen many times before.
Let's finish this quickly…
Huh?! A dead end?!
We did as you said, you big idiot!
Shut up! Why is it so difficult to find
our way around this hospital?!
Because, the hospital director used
some weird feng shui to construct it.
You're Quincies!
You shouldn’t be concerned
with feng shui!
It's become dark!
I know!
What?!
Hey!
These two…
I'm kind of tired.
Yeah…
Say…
It's fine if you all run around,
but don't take too much time.
Could it be…
these children are responsible?!
Do you know what this is?!
It's just water.
Bounts!
Damn it! We were looking for
a place without water.
Ghoul!
Günter!
Ghoul, where's your greeting?!
Damn!
What should we do?! Ichigo…
All right!
Let's run away!
You coward!
We can't fight them
with injured people!
Noba! Can you transport Ishida?!
Come to think of it,
he could do that!
Of course, he can.
But the moving distance
in his current body is…
What is it?!
About two meters…
That's completely useless!
This way!
All right! I see!
We passed this way earlier,
didn't we?!
I don't remember!
Here it is!
Run away!
Run away?! To where?!
Renji! Let's go!
All right!
Shakkaho! Red Flame Cannon!
Did we do it?!
It's not enough?!
We need more firepower…
Damn!
What are you going to do, Kurosaki?!
Wait a second!
Take this!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Don't be reckless!
The steam could burn someone!
Then what should I have done?!
I'm saying that was
too dangerous!
They sure use crude techniques.
But do they think
this is finished?!
Water is important to human life,
isn't it?!
Turn back!
What do you plan to do?!
Chad, take Ishida
and go ahead of us!
I'll deal with this!
Now, go!
All right!
I'll stay back!
Rukia, take care of everyone!
Yes. All right!
Ichigo, Renji!
You better catch up with us!
Let's go!
All right!
Take this! Take this! Take this! Take this!
We won't get there any faster
if you do that!
Take this! Take this! Take this! Take this!
You really are stupid!
What did you say?!
There are things that people do
that they know are meaningless.
No matter how useless…
Even if it only acts as a release…
Even if it's a waste of energy,
I understand that behavior.
Now push without any reservations!
Are you trying to make me
feel better with that?!
Sort of…!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Rats! There's no end to this…
Just a little longer!
Kurosaki…
Red Flame Cannon!
Aren't they there yet?!
We made it!
All right!
It seems they made it!
How are we going to get away?!
We're going to do this!
Heh, so that's it…
Let's go!
Here’s an added bonus!
Oww!
I guess it was a bit much
to jump from the eighth floor.
What's wrong?!
Kurosaki…
What are you doing?!
Run away quickly!
Rain?!
That's why we told you…
You can't run away from water…
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Time goes by, and I get left behind.
But I say,
“don’t forget that anxious feeling”
They tell me,
“A reckless challenge is meaningless”
But I say “don’t give up.”
(Offense!) At times when
the going gets tough, I raise my voice.
(Offense!) And head toward
the direction of my goal.
There is nothing to be afraid of
that towering wall.
Never losing sight in this life
without answers
Keep My Pace
Count one! And move on
Count two! And take a break
Count three! And think through
I’ll just go at my own pace
Damn! Even if they're Bounts,
they're kids!
That makes this difficult!
Bounts are a tribe that live forever.
They're not the age they look.
Don't pay any attention to it.
That's right. That's right!
Sister is pretty old despite
her looks!
Red Flame Cannon!
The Golden Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers after these messages!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
Golden!
This afternoon, in Karakura Town,
4B	01:24:20:27	01:24:25:08	An accidental explosion at
a hospital?!
there was an explosion
at Karakura General Hospital.
High school student unconscious!
Others missing!!
It caused a riot as about
40 patients were forced to evacuate.
Ichigo Kurosaki,
a high school student from
the town who was paying a visit…
is unconscious from the explosion
and is currently undergoing treatment.
According to those involved
with the hospital…
a few of Kurosaki's friends
and Uryu Ishida,
who was hospitalized,
have gone missing.
It is possible they were caught…
Oh no! I forgot!
in the explosion and
the police are investigating now.
Tune in again!