The one who attacked Ishida…
…was me.
Ichigo!
What’s got you so freaked?
Something’s happening to Inoue!
Relax.
I have no intention of
doing anything to you yet.
For today, I’ll head on home right
after I punish this disobedient boy.
Oh?
You’re as kind-hearted
as I had heard you were.
You can’t bear seeing
even an enemy get hurt?
That’s not what this is.
If you’re the one who attacked Ishida,
I can’t allow you to get away.
I see…
Who’re you calling?
Inoue, who else?!
Better not.
That moment when she’s distracted by the
ringtone might give the enemy an opening.
It’s that bad…
I don’t know…
But her Spiritual Pressure
is under tremendous strain…
Is this the right direction?
Yeah…
But I can’t pin down the location
with my Spiritual Pressure perception.
If you’ve got the direction right,
I think I know where she is.
If we keep going…
we’ll reach Inoue’s place!
If I’m the one who attacked Ishida,
you can’t allow me to get away…eh?
Such an ordinary line.
It’s not very interesting.
It’ll never make it into any book.
H-Hey!
What’s the matter with you?
Mr. Tsukishima is serious!
He’s super scary!
You won’t get off with just a beating!
Please be quiet.
I’m not doing this for your sake…
Sushigawara.
It’s Shishigawara…
I have to focus…
No telling what his next move will be.
He’s already taken out his sword,
so maybe I should put up Santenkesshun…
But that might look like I’m
provoking him to attack.
Is there some other way to stop him?
St…Stop!
Santenkesshun!
Where’s Inoue’s unit?!
403!
This way!
Inoue!
Are you okay, Inoue?!
I’m not cut?
That can’t be…
I definitely felt the blade
cutting deeply into my body.
Inoue!
Kurosaki?! Sado!
Why are you guys here?!
Why?
Chad said something was wrong
with your Spiritual Pressure.
Are you all right?
Those fluctuations in your Spiritual
Pressure weren’t normal.
What exactly happened, Inoue?
Huh?!
R-Really?!
Nothing happened, though.
I was bent over in pain
because of a stomach ache—
maybe that was it?
That couldn’t be…
Wasn’t there another Spiritual
Pressure here until a minute ago?
Who was that?
Who? My friend.
I met my friend here and...
A friend?
That was Tsukishima.
After my friend left, my
stomach began to hurt.
That’s all it was.
A friend?
Was Tsukishima my friend?
Sorry about making you two worry!
No.
He’s the one who attacked Ishida.
I’ll be sure to tell
you if anything happens!
So let me know if anything
happens to either of you, okay?
S-Sure…
I can’t tell Kurosaki.
Well…we’ll be going, then.
Okay! See you tomorrow!
That was strange…
Why did I think he was
my friend for a moment?
What in me did he cut?
Hey…
What do you think happened to Inoue?
Yeah…
I’m not sure.
Inoue doesn’t know that Ichigo’s
getting his powers back.
She doesn’t want to drag Ichigo
into a fight because of her.
She wants to keep the danger
she’s in away from Ichigo more than anyone.
She said nothing was wrong.
I guess we have to take her word.
I agree with her that it’s too risky
to involve Ichigo in a fight
in his present condition.
I’ll get in touch with Inoue again later.
I’m sure it must’ve been an error
in my Spiritual Pressure perception.
Don’t worry about it.
Okay.
Another one.
No.
Why not?
You’ve had enough.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
What’re you talking about?
I realize you’re happy that all’s
going well with Ichigo, but…
It’s not like that.
Hey, Riruka!
Why don’t you also go home already?!
Hey!
Don’t ignore me, damn it!
Oh yeah, it’s empty!
Kutsuzawa, give me another!
No.
Why not?!
What’s one more?!
No.
Come on, don’t be like that!
Kugo…
It’s your direct line.
Who is it?
All right. I’ll open it right now.
Inoue and Chad won’t say anything,
but something definitely happened.
It was probably the same
guy who attacked Ishida.
Kugo…
You think it’s?
Yeah.
It was probably Tsukishima’s doing.
So you do know him!
Tsukishima is a Fullbringer, like us.
And…
he was once one of us.
UNAGIYA
Coming!
Who is it at this hour?
That hurt!
This door opens toward the stairs!
I warned you before to
be careful when opening it!
-How many years have you been living here?
-Ichigo!
Where have you been?!
Taking days off again without telling me!
Anyway, come on in!
I’ll hear your excuse inside!
No, here is fine.
Why?
What?!
You want some time off?!
Are you crazy?!
You’ve been taking off this entire time!
Just how much work are you
planning on skipping?!
Are you listening?!
I’m sorry.
Well, that’s all I wanted to tell you.
Wait…just a minute!
Ichigo!
I don’t know what’s going on with you,
but stop worrying about me.
I’m not one of your classmates!
I’m a grown-up!
I’m too old to have a kid
like you worrying about me!
That’s why, if something
happened, spit it out!
It’s okay for kids to rely on adults.
Thank you, Ms. Ikumi.
Tsukishima
used to be our leader.
We came together for a shared purpose
and worked together to erase our powers.
Tsukishima discovered a way
to transfer our powers to
a Substitute Soul Reaper.
He was our leader.
But…
after the Substitute Soul
Reaper we finally found
accepted the powers of several
of our group members,
Tsukishima suddenly had a change of heart.
He killed both the Substitute Soul Reaper
and the members of our group
who gave him their powers,
and disappeared from our ranks.
Or…
perhaps that was his objective all along.
Let me show you something.
This was the Substitute Soul
Reaper’s Combat Pass.
I don’t know what Tsukishima’s
true intentions are.
He wasn’t the kind of guy
who’d tell you his secrets.
and he hasn’t shown himself
to us since that day.
That’s why, right now,
there’s only one thing I
do know about Tsukishima.
His aim is to prevent us
from making contact with you,
a Substitute Soul Reaper.
His actions support that theory.
He attacked Uryu Ishida,
made contact with Orihime Inoue,
and tried to attract your attention
using a different, and more
violent, means than we did.
Ginjo…
I…
I know what you’re thinking.
But don’t rush.
Now that Tsukishima’s
made his next move…
we want to speed things up too.
We’ll start preparing for your
next training session right away.
We’ll contact you when we’re ready.
So for now, go on home tonight.
Dad…
What’s the matter?
No, it’s nothing…
Let’s go someplace else.
Why?
Just in case.
I see.
Let’s do that.
I forgot…
No…
So many things happened all at once
that I tried to erase it from my mind…
Just how much do you know about
Urahara that makes you
think you understand him?
Should I chase after him
and ask him right now?
No…what if Urahara is really my enemy?
Could I do anything against him now?
This isn’t good…
I've got to regain my powers
as soon as possible…!
Are you all right?
Yeah…
I’m fine, I’m fine.
Sorry.
My kitchen came tumbling down…
I see…
So, it’s true?
Yes.
I’m positive I was cut.
But when I came to, there was no wound,
and the people who came here were gone.
And then, when you and Kurosaki came…
for a split second, I thought of that person
as a “friend.”
What do you mean?
Sorry…
I don’t really understand
what I’m saying either.
I just felt like he was my friend.
It’s not like I mistook
him for someone else
or that I was mistaken.
How should I put it…
It felt like I thought about the past and…
suddenly I remembered who he was.
Be careful, Sado.
His abilities seem terribly frightening.
Yeah…
I’ll be careful.
You said there were two of them together?
Huh?
Yes.
Do you remember their names?
I think it was Tsukishima…
and Sushigawara.
May I continue, Shishigawara?
Y-Yes, sir!
Listen…
As far as this matter is concerned,
you don’t need to do anything further.
But! As your apprentice, I…
Will you stop with that apprentice thing?
Oh! I’m sorry!
As your apprentice!
I don’t think it’s right to just
watch quietly as you do your work.
By “this matter,” I meant Orihime Inoue.
I’ve already placed it inside her.
No further contact is necessary.
R-Right.
Who should I go next?
Yasutora Sado?
Or Ichigo Kurosaki?
I wonder what Ginjo would say
if I went after Ichigo Kurosaki directly?
So Sado, about Sushigawara…
Yes, tell me about this Sushigawara guy...
Sorry…
Talking about Sushigawara is making
me want to eat some sushi…
Yeah…
Me too!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
If we’re going someplace else,
there’s a place that I’m fond of.
That you’re fond of?
Yes!
With lots of cute ones…
You can touch all you want!
PLACE FOR GROWNUPS
No no no no!
I have my beloved Masaki!
-I gave her my word that I wouldn’t go
-Come on, come on.
-to hostess bars and places like that!
-Let’s go!
Welcome!
Upsy-daisy!
Okay, let’s talk.
A cat café…?