Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
That's the result of a Zanpakuto
going out of control
after Muramasa manifested it.
You know that Muramasa's ability
affected not only captains,
but also regular
squad members, right?
Some of them were unable to
defeat their Zanpakuto and died.
This Zanpakuto is one of those
who went out of control
as a result of losing its master.
I know…
I think I shall name them
"Sword Beasts."
Did you hear something crash?
I didn't hear anything.
Everything looks normal.
I guess I was
just imagining things.
What's wrong, Ichigo?!
Did you sense something
that cannot be seen?
I see…
Maybe I did!
I know nothing!
I can't see anything
that can't be seen!
You're not making any sense.
I don't know anything!
I know absolutely nothing!
See you later!
What's wrong with him?
I knew I'd find someone here.
Have you come after me?
Who are you?
It doesn't seem like you're
a Soul Reaper or a Hollow…
My master…
Where is my master?
"Master"? You mean, you're?
He's a Zanpakuto!
Wait!
He got away.
A Zanpakuto?
What's going on?
I thought we settled
the whole Muramasa incident?
That's what I came here
to tell you.
I hear things were
very rough this time around.
So how's the Soul Society now?
Has it recovered?
Well, you see…
I hear Muramasa was
betrayed by his master.
The poor thing.
Still, he did immense damage
to the Soul Society.
He's not one to be pitied.
Sword Beasts?
They're Zanpakuto that
have lost their masters.
I feel sorry for them, but we
cannot let them roam free.
And, as I suspected, some have
already wandered into this world.
How dangerous.
That's the situation, Kurosaki.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
Hey, who the hell are you?
It doesn't matter who I am!
I've got no business
with stuffed animals!
What did you say?!
Okay, okay!
Don't fight, you two!
Matsumoto…
Oh, there he is!
There's Captain Hitsugaya!
Captain?
You guys…
I never told you to come with me.
Don't make such a scary face.
Haineko wanted to take a peek
at the World of the Living.
We're not here to have fun!
Here! Check these out!
WE TWO GET ALONG SO WELL!
RANGIKU & HAINEKO
BEAUTY QUEENS HAVE ARRIVED
IN KARAKURA TOWN!
GROWL!
Well, well…
Hey! Who is this woman?!
She's Haineko, my Zanpakuto.
Be kind to her, okay?
No way!
Well, well …
Come on take a look, Ichigo!
No way!
Come on…
It's only natural for a young man
like you to want to take a look.
You don't have to hold back.
Come on, come on, come on.
You guys…
Cut it out!
So about these Sword Beasts…
I wonder how many Zanpakuto
have lost their owners.
Well…
At the very least,
there's probably as many as
the squad members
who died in battle.
Hmm… That's quite a lot.
Not only that,
but our Zanpakuto,
which we thought had
turned back into swords,
are wandering about again.
So it seems.
Well, I'm fine with that.
However…
The Sword Beasts no longer
have a place to return to.
We cannot ignore them
if they lose control any further
and do evil deeds.
I win.
Oh, my. You're right.
I lost again.
Now for your penalty.
Okay, okay…
Here!
Draw for us!
CRAYON
Oh… Okay, okay…
Draw some more!
Like this?
More!
So… Yes, I'm fine
with this and all…
Yeah. Definitely.
I'm fine with it too…
But I still think it's more natural
for a Zanpakuto to
remain inside its sword.
I think so too.
Owowowowow…
Hey, that hurts!
An unexpected
parting gift indeed…
This is an odd feeling.
What is?
I've always been with you,
even before you manifested,
but it's an odd feeling
walking with you side by side.
It is, isn't it?
There was a time when I thought
this day would never come…
When was that?
When I saw you break and
lose your spiritual pressure.
I was petrified.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
It was all thanks to
Captain Kurotsuchi's hard work
that I am here now.
Captain Kurotsuchi, huh?
Let's begin.
Yes, sir.
Captain, it appears to be
interfering with some other wave.
It seems my hunch was correct.
She regenerated.
To be honest, I had my doubts
about his crazy experiments.
But he saved you,
so I guess I should be thankful
to Captain Kurotsuchi.
I suppose so.
Master…
I must find him quickly…
A Hollow…
It was a Sword Beast.
Yeah. But it instantly disappeared.
What's going on?
Shall I call Haineko
and the others?
No, let's not.
They'd just make things
more complicated.
Wow!
You're so cute!
Y-You think so?
Well, the portable gigai
is working out well,
and Orihime's clothes
seem to fit perfectly.
All that's left…
This looks cooler!
Oh, I kind of like it!
Right?!
Say, Rangiku…
What?
How were the Zanpakuto able
to turn back to normal?
Oh… Well, you see…
When a Soul Reaper calls out
the name of his Zanpakuto,
it allows the Zanpakuto
and the Soul Reaper
to synchronize and
fight together.
Captain Kurotsuchi tested out
many different ways to return
the Zanpakuto back to normal
by making use of that property.
I see…
The rest was easy.
The keywords were
synchronization and interference.
All of the brainwashed
Zanpakuto were unstable.
In short, I just had to
stabilize them.
You probably wouldn't understand
my explanation, though.
Stabilize?
That's right.
Muramasa destabilized
our existence.
That magnified
the small anxieties we had
and caused us to
lose control of ourselves.
Hmm…
So that's what happened…
What's so funny?
Nothing, sir.
Then…
Can we bring the Sword Beasts
under control
using the same method?
We need Captain Kurotsuchi
to do all he can.
Sorry, Nanao,
but could you go to
the Department of Research and
Development one more time for me?
Understood, sir.
Don't forget to
take some sweets.
So you want me to do
something about this mess?
Yes.
Easy for you to say.
Can you do it?
It doesn't really interest me.
Interest?
I was the one who released
the Zanpakuto from their mind control.
Yes, you were.
Thinking of a way to tame Zanpakuto
that have lost their masters
and become Sword Beasts
is not very interesting.
But the current situation
requires a…
Leave.
What?!
No. Umm…
I'm sorry.
My captain isn't feeling well.
Nemu, prepare some tea.
Right away, sir.
Hmm… I guess I have no choice.
This thing…
The relationship shared between
Soul Reapers and Zanpakuto…
Yes. In that sense,
what led to Muramasa's madness
could have happened to
any other Zanpakuto.
We now know that
such danger also exists.
I see.
BEAUTIFUL SKIN
BIG EYES
SMALL FACE
You really know all
the new spots, Orihime.
I never knew that there
was a photo booth like this!
The World of the Living
really is amazing!
It changes every time I come.
So, you two want to go to
the new fast fashion shop next?
– You bet!
What's wrong, Rangiku?
Well…
It's about the Spiritual Pressure
of a Sword Beast…
Wait, you were actually
searching for it?
I've been tracking
its presence all this time.
I may not look it,
but I am a lieutenant!
However…
However?
Its Spiritual Pressure changed.
Huh? Why?
Who knows?
We still don't know much
about Sword Beasts.
The only thing we do know
is that Sword Beasts
are Zanpakuto that have
gone out of control.
So I'm going to capture it.
As a Zanpakuto,
what do you think?
Well…
I was able to return
to normal like this
because you,
my master, was safe.
But the Sword Beasts…
They have lost their
place to return to.
We're the same Zanpakuto,
and yet…
Whether a Zanpakuto lives or dies
all depends on its master…
Rain…
Let's go!
It's close!
What?
A Sword Beast?!
It's definitely the Spiritual
Pressure of a Sword Beast.
But something is?
What is that?
This one…
Is it a Hollow?
Stand back!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What the heck?
That's a Hollow!
Oh no. In this form…
Leave it to me!
Haineko?!
I'll fight!
Haineko!
Where?
Where is he?
Give me back my master!
What are you
blabbering about, Hollow?
Where is my master?!
Who is this guy?
Ichigo!
Kurosaki!
Rangiku!
Take care of her.
There's no escape.
Let's end this here.
Ichigo…
This is the Zanpakuto
from earlier.
What?
My master…
Where is my master?!
But it looks completely different.
It appears it has fused
with a Hollow.
You're right. I've never seen
a Hollow use a sword before.
Sorry…
Here I go.
Getsuga…
What power…
Damn it!
Reign over
the Frosted Heavens!
Hyorinmaru!
Toshiro!
That's what I thought…
Yeah, it was stronger
than I expected.
I figured their Spiritual Pressure
would increase
if they fused with
another Spiritual Entity…
But it seems like
they're going to be trouble.
Be careful.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to turn in
my report on this incident.
We're going back
to the Soul Society.
Hey, where did everyone go?
Raingiku and the other went off
to continue shopping.
Hyorinmaru isn't here, either.
They took him along
to carry their things.
Hyorinmaru!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
I want to see what he
looks like under that mask.
Yeah.
MEN'S BATH
This place is perfect!
I can't believe we're waiting here
to take a look at a man.
Well, if we want a peek…
Oh! There he is!
What do you want?
Why don't you
take off your mask?!