Do you not think you are the
one who has acted selfishly?
Eddie's testimony spoke to that.
He told us how you live only for your
own goals, with no thought for others!
No...
And Cathy, after being deceived
by you, found herself bewitched.
Such a proud woman,
and look how she ended up.
No!
I will now proclaim the verdict.
Rachel Gardner is a witch!
She will now be burned alive!
I'm not!
Come, witch! Be cleansed and made pure!
I'm not a witch!
Who would believe the words of a witch?
I'm not!
You still say that after
hearing their testimonies?
You destroyed their very hearts...
Yes, the hearts of angels.
You toyed with their hearts,
and then took them away!
What you did was inhuman.
Angels?
I...
I'm sure you intend to subject
Isaac Foster to the same fate.
No! I don't!
You intend to sacrifice
him for your own purposes.
No...
Now, confess that you are a witch!
Declare what you really are,
and give yourself to the sacred flames,
to the hands of God!
I am... not a witch.
The God I know never said such a thing.
There was nothing like that in the Bible.
Of course there wasn't, Rachel Gardner.
Because the God you speak of does not exist.
But you've been using
God's name all this time.
Yes, because I speak of my God!
I stand in the position of God.
This God exists right here,
in the form of myself!
I stand in the position of God.
This God exists right here,
in the form of myself!
Are you saying that you're God?
Yes, precisely.
In this place, I am the
one closest to being God.
I don't...
I don't know anything about that.
I don't know anything.
A heart that truly believes...
That is what gives God's existence meaning.
Rachel Gardner...
You never had one of those to begin with!
No!
God doesn't exist?
Why?
I don't want to hear that!
I can't accept that. I won't accept that.
This priest called himself God.
No... He's wrong.
I don't want to be killed by this priest.
But... I don't...
Zack...
Zack?
It's hot.
Hot, but... also cold.
There's something cold inside me.
What... What is this?
Something...
Something precious...
...that I harmed... and ruined.
But something that always, always...
...helped me.
Wait!
I'll remember now!
Zack's... knife.
Oh... So that's it.
God is...
...right here.
Wh...
Why did you awaken?
All the strange things on
this floor are illusions.
My God opened my eyes.
I was unable to purify the witch.
I'm not a witch.
I never made any contract.
Only a promise.
And that promise...
...came from my God.
I see.
So this is how the witch has chosen to think.
And even if you are mistaken,
even if what you believe
is varnished with lies,
it matters not to you?
Listen...
More importantly...
Give me the medicine right now.
Pitiful witch who loves none but herself...
Follow me.
The medicine is in here.
Show me.
What need have you of such a favor?
I have no way of knowing what you'll do.
I see.
These are the medicines Danny was carrying.
There are drugs to disinfect, stop bleeding,
and even produce blood.
With all these, his condition
should improve somewhat.
Take all you need.
Will you be returning to Zack?
You aren't going to kill me?
You found your God, did you not?
The existence of multiple
deities creates chaos.
Besides, I know that you have
no concept of compassion.
Are you going to get in my way?
If you don't, then I don't need to kill you.
Because...
I don't need you.
I see.
Then allow me to impart a warning.
God despises those who lie
and those who are unclean.
Assuming that "God" truly is God, of course,
Rachel Gardner.
Zack?
Thank goodness... You're alive.
Burn marks?
Zack, you're awake?
Huh? The hell are you doing?
I brought medicine.
So you made it back alive, huh?
Uh-huh.
Don't "uh-huh" me, damn it.
Well? How'd you get the medicine?
The priest on this floor gave it to me.
Priest? Oh, him...
Don't move. I haven't sewn you up yet.
This stupid cut is nothing.
It needs stitches.
I'll do it.
I'm... good at sewing, you know.
Cut it out.
I can do it myself.
Are you good at sewing, too?
I'm not a damn shirt.
Still, I'm going to do it.
I want to sew up your belly for you.
Huh?
Tch. Have it your way.
Don't blame me if it grosses you out.
I'll be fine.
Shit... What the hell are you, anyway?
What do you mean?
You're touching this stuff like
it doesn't bother you at all.
Well, whatever.
Your weak ass managed to
bring back the medicine.
Kudos for that.
Yeah.
But you know this isn't really necessary.
Tell me, Ray.
What reason do you have for
doing all this to help me?
This knife cuts pretty well.
Hey, you're not getting
out of it that easily.
Answer me!
'Cause...
You are my God, Zack.
Wh-What the hell are you saying, you freak?
Also, my knife...
I'm sorry. I damaged it a little.
Huh? What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
W-Well, not that it matters.
This knife really saved me.
Oh, did it, now?
Ouch, damn it!
Does that hurt?
Yes, it hurts, you dumbass!
I thought it wouldn't bother you.
You really are stupid.
I'm not a masochist!
If you think I'm God,
be more careful with me!
Okay... I will.
Hey, Zack...
What?
What about this burn? Does it hurt?
Huh? Nah.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Okay.
As soon as you're done, we're leaving.
Sure.
All done.
Hey, you did pretty good.
Huh?
Aw, hell. Fine, let's rest a while.
Was I... asleep?
Yeah. Ready to go now?
I haven't found the
elevator that goes up yet.
So we just have to look for it.
Actually...
Pretty damn huge chapel.
So, what happened to that
priest you told me about?
I don't know.
How the hell don't you know?
I can't believe he just
gave you that medicine.
It wasn't exactly easy.
I bet.
But I think...
he might have had a soft spot for you.
Don't puke anymore, okay?
Shut up! Quit saying gross shit like that!
Huh?
Damn, this is one weird building.
Agreed.
Right?
How do we get this thing to move?
Looks like we use this.
All right, let's go.
Wait.
Hey, Zack...
Can I ask you something?
Why the hell would you ask
for permission to ask?
I won't know until I hear the question.
Right...
So, what is it?
How did you get those burns?
Why the hell do you wanna know that?
No reason, really.
I just wanted to know more about you.
It's not an interesting story or anything.
It doesn't have to be interesting.
When I was a kid, the guy in the
house where I lived set fire to me.
A guy? Fire?
I don't remember it too well,
but I think he was the guy that... the
woman who gave birth to me was seeing?
All I remember is that I bit into him
and tore off a chunk of flesh after that.
He probably meant to kill me,
but unfortunately for him,
I just didn't seem to die.
So what happened then?
The woman wrapped
me up in cloth like a mummy
and sold me off to some
shithouse for the money.
I see.
That's about it.
Well? You satisfied now?
Yeah.
What's with you? You think it's funny?
No, it's not funny.
Huh?
But I found out what caused the burns,
so I'm satisfied.
I wanted to know more about you,
so I'm glad I got to ask.
Are you being serious?
Yeah.
Oh, really?
Well, good for you.
Yeah.
Oh, also...
You wanna ask something else?
Do you still want to get out of here?
Huh? The hell are you talking
about? Of course I do.
I wouldn't be risking my
ass like this if I didn't.
I see. Okay, then.
Don't worry.
Once we get out of here and your
expression's a little better...
I know. You'll kill me, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
You're so weird.
Just so you know, I've never
once told you any lies.
Lies, huh?
Zack, listen. The thing is...
Huh?
I...
Hey, what's with you?
Nothing.
Huh?! What the hell?!
Sorry. I forgot what I wanted to say.
Get your shit together.
We're not outside yet.
Don't whack out on me.
C'mon, look. We're almost at the surface.
Yeah.
Let's go.
I can't say it. I just can't say it.
After all, Zack hates liars,
and God hates the unclean.
My hands are unclean,
and if he finds out I've been
hiding that all this time,
he'll hate me.
I can't tell Zack the truth.
Not anymore.
Blood?
God despises those who lie
and those who are unclean.
What do I do now? This is where...
This is where I was.
Wait, Zack.
Wait...
No! Please!
Don't go!
Don't look in that room!