Zangetsu!
Are you Zangetsu?!
No, I am...
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Wait! Ichigo!
What?! Weren't we in a hurry?!
Something's odd.
There's no sign of the Cleaner.
Cleaner?
You mean that Spiritual Pressure
train-like thing?
Yeah...
Ordinarily, a Soul Reaper can't
do anything about the Cleaner.
From the traces of Spiritual Pressure,
it appears Aizen did something.
What are you afraid of, Gin?
Reason exists for those who
must rely on it to survive.
Well, shall we get going?
Towards the end of all reason.
Is it bad if that thing is gone?
If we leave things like this,
it's not good.
But...
Right now, it's to our advantage.
What?
This Precipice World, as
the name suggests,
is a place isolated temporally
and spatially from
both the World of the Living
and the Soul Society.
The Cleaner existed to keep
those who entered
here from staying a long time.
But right now, it's gone.
I'll be able to teach
you in this place.
Teach me? What?
The Final Getsugatensho!
The Final...
Getsugatensho?
Why was I sleeping here?
The Final...Getsugatensho?
That's correct.
And this is where you could teach me?
Why's that?
The Precipice World
is a rupture in space surrounded
by multiple layers of
temporal torrents.
I see...
You don't have to know
what it means.
Put simply,
time flows at a much faster rate
than in the outside world.
Expressed in numbers,
it's 2000 times as fast.
In the time that a year
passes on the outside,
2000 years will have passed
here in the Precipice World.
What?!
Long ago, besides being
the pathway to
the World of the Living, this Precipice World
was also used as an exile for criminals.
That's why the Restrictive Current
and the Cleaner exist.
If the Restrictive Current
captures you,
then you would be unable to escape
the Precipice World and die.
If the Cleaner pursues you,
then you would be hurled
to a time greatly different
than the temporal coordinates at which
you entered the Precipice World.
That is why there was a
variance of several days
when you first entered the Soul Society
after being pursued by the Cleaner.
Anyway, you have Urahara's
technical skills
to thank for getting off
with only a few days
variance after the Cleaner
pursued you.
Ordinarily, you would've been
hurled about a century
and died from your body
being unable to keep
up with the sudden
passage of time.
But right now,
that Cleaner is not here.
This is a good opportunity
to gain some time.
The flow of time within
the Precipice World is
2000 times that
of the outside.
In other words,
even if you trained 2000 hours here,
only one hour will have
gone by on the outside.
There is no means of sealing the
Cleaner in the Soul Society,
but there is a way to stop
the Restrictive Current.
We call it Realm Fixation.
Normally,
it's done by having a group of
low-ranking Soul Reapers
pool their Spiritual Pressure to
fixate the Restrictive Current.
But I can perform it by myself.
I will hold down the
Restrictive Current
until my Spiritual Pressure
is exhausted.
By my rough estimate,
that'll be 2000 hours.
Or about 3 months.
Use that time to get an answer.
Answer?
That's right.
You need to find out.
Get your sword, Zangetsu,
to tell you about the
Final Getsugatensho!
What...What happened?
What's going on?
Everybody's asleep
on the streets.
All the cars and traffic
lights have stopped.
This is not cool!
Why does it look like the world
has come to an end?!
This isn't a dream.
And it isn't a movie, either.
Come on!
Isn't anybody awake?!
Hey! Everybody!
Mizuiro!
Ichigo!
Sis!
Don't leave me here alone!
That hurt!
What's the big...
Huh?
Arisawa!
Oh, thank goodness!
I'm so glad to see someone,
even if it's you!
I mean... Did you take
a look around?
Everyone's all sound asleep!
I was getting lonely,
thinking maybe
I was the only one still
awake in the world!
I mean, no one's waking up.
It feels so real and
creepy, you know?
I would've been able to handle
all this if it was just me here,
but this is way too freaky.
But I sure am glad you're alive!
Not that I was worried about you!
In fact, I'd rather you
worried about me!
By the way, have you
seen Mizuiro?
I haven't yet!
Hey, come to think of it...
Why'd you lariat me, huh?!
Shut up.
Right... Sorry.
Why'd you dodge?
Are you crazy?!
If I don't dodge,
it's gonna hurt!
The fact that you dodged my fist
means you aren't putting your
soul into your sword!
Concentrate!
Don't you even know how to talk
with your own Zanpakuto?!
I get it, ok?
But I've never turned to Old Man Zangetsu
outside of battle like this.
Place your sword on your
lap and meditate!
Concentrate your soul
on only your sword!
That's all there is to it!
I get that, but...
That form is called Jinzen.
It is a form for carrying on a dialogue
with one's Zanpakuto
that was devised over the course
of thousands of years since the
beginning of the Soul Society.
Ichigo, up until now,
all your techniques
were acquired through
brute force.
Do you understand?
For you to progress further,
you must venture into
realms of millennia
you never touched on before.
Go...Ichigo!
I'm really sorry.
How should I put it?
I'm by myself,
and everyone's asleep,
and I was lonely, and it was so quiet,
and no one's awake, and...
And then I got hyper, you know?
Will you stop with the
noisy excuses?
Enough already!
Come over here!
No, I'm serious. I'm really sorry.
Honsho! Ogawa!
I found them.
For now, I'm taking
them to the school.
Can you carry Chizuru?
Right!
Up you go!
You better not touch her butt!
I know that!
Say, Arisawa...
What?
Honsho's got bigger boobs
than I thought.
Here's what I know so far.
I went to take a look
around earlier,
but the town was cut off
right at the outskirts.
There were only mountains
past that.
It's hard to believe, but the entire
town has been moved.
Do you think Ichigo has something
to do with this?
Isn't it obvious?
Who else is there?!
But...
If it was Ichigo's fault,
then Ichigo is going to fix it.
That's the kind of guy he is.
Indeed...
A sight unfitting for
the Soul Society.
This is the last we'll see of it.
Calm down.
How unsightly of you.
You should be able to breathe.
Well?
Who are you?
Old Man Zangetsu is the only
one who should be here.
Is that any way to talk to the person
who taught you how to breathe?
Tensa Zangetsu?!
I can't blame you for
not recognizing me.
This is the first time you've come
here in a Bankai state.
What?!
Zangetsu!
Are you Zangetsu?!
Wrong.
What do you call your Bankai?
I am Tensa Zangetsu.
You've entered.
Be careful, now.
This time, Zangetsu will
not go easy on you.
It was the same with
my Engetsu.
Our Zanpakutos don't want
to teach us this technique.
You'll learn why soon enough.
W-Wait, Old Man... I mean, you're
not old right now, but...
Wait, Zangetsu!
This time I'm not here to fight!
I just need an answer!
Answer? You mean about
the Final Getsugatensho?
That's... Wait a second...
So you can hear what's
said outside?
What are you doing?!
I can't teach you such a thing.
Oh, is that so?
Unfortunately, I need
you to teach me.
So what?
The fate of what you want to protect
is none of my concern.
What?
Don't misunderstand, Ichigo.
What you want to protect is
not what I want to protect.
My head hurts.
What is going on?
The trains aren't running.
I can't get to the office,
or even go home.
Hey, you there!
I'm glad someone is awake.
Do you have any idea
of what is going on here?
Don't come near me.
A human with no awareness
of Spiritual Pressure
is unable to sense my power.
But their body can't withstand it.
Oh? Those kids over there
seem to be awake.
Yes. I recall seeing them
through Ulquiorra's eyes.
They are Ichigo Kurosaki's friends.
What do you mean?
About what?
You said earlier...
"The fate of what you want to protect
is none of my concern."
I'm asking what you
meant by that!
I thought you lent me your
power to help me.
Was I wrong?
Then why did you lend me
your power all this time?
What were you planning?
Answer me, Zangetsu!
It's exactly as I said.
What?!
Look at this world!
This world of yours used to be filled
with skyscrapers, full of hope!
Now it has sunken low to look like
the small town that's dear to you!
The rain that continued to fall
on this world has subsided,
but in its place, everything
has sunk into this ocean!
This all happened, Ichigo, because you
lost hope and stopped moving forward!
Ichigo.
I cannot leave you like this.
I will drag out the root of your
despair right here and now!
What's up?
It's been a long time, Ichigo.
What's with that look?
Don't you recognize me?
Come to think of it...
Huh?
Aren't you going to
look for Kojima?
Well...
I did try looking for him.
But ever since Ichigo disappeared,
he's been going to school on his own.
And he hasn't answered
his cell phone either.
So he's probably still
asleep somewhere.
You two have been hanging
out since middle school,
so I thought you were
best friends.
I guess it's not like that, huh?
We have our personal spaces.
People need that, right?
You think so?
Ichigo was the first person
Mizuiro ever opened up to.
He tends to put up
a wall very quickly,
so it makes me happy just to see
him walk up to people on his own.
Let's stop this. What am
I saying, anyway?
You were telling cheesy stories.
Why you...
Anyway, after we drop off Chizuru
and Michiru at the school,
go and find Kojima.
What about Kunieda and Natsui?
Those two can manage
by themselves.
I'll go look for Yuzu and Karin.
Isn't their Dad with them?
That guy's probably unconscious
with the rest of them.
W-What the hell is this?!
A-Arisawa...
Are you all right?!
Shut up.
I don't need you to
worry about me.
Who are those guys?
Arisawa!
Impressive.
You're this close to me, yet you are
still able to maintain your existence.
Who...are you?
Ichigo Kurosaki will show
up here for sure.
With new powers, no doubt.
I want to bring those powers
closer to perfection.
Your deaths will help that cause.
Run, Asano!
Huh?
Get going!
Or is there something
you can do here?!
Don't bother chasing after him.
I'll start with this one first.
What'll I do? What'll I do?
My body won't move.
What'll I do?
What should I do?!
Arisawa, ever heard of a
misattribution of arousal?
What are you babbling about
at a time like this?
When you're in an agitating situation
with someone for some reason,
your brain misattributes
it as love.
Oh really? So you're in love
with that freak in white.
Sorry I told you to run.
How did you come to
that conclusion?!
Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers!
Hey!
Hurry up and return this place
to the way it used to be!
It doesn't appear all
that inconvenient.
Why not leave it like this?
No, it is!
Everything mechanical
has become unusable.
Once you fall asleep,
there's no telling where
you'll end up.
I've tried equipping myself
with all sorts of things,
but it's really a hassle!
You look like you're having fun!
He sure looks like
he's having fun.