I see…
Orihime Inoue said that, huh?
I’m thinking that’s what
Tsukishima’s ability is.
The power of suggestion—interfering
with memories…
Did Tsukishima’s Fullbring have
that sort of special ability?
Tell me…
Don’t keep anything from me now.
That’s good.
At this pace…
Ichigo!
What the?!
My Combat Pass…
What about Uryu Ishida?
He was attacked by Tsukishima, wasn’t he?
Is Uryu Ishida’s memory in disarray?
If Uryu Ishida’s memory is also affected,
that’s something else
we have to worry about…
If his memories haven’t been affected…
Then what?
It means it wasn’t Tsukishima
who stabbed Orihime Inoue.
Are you sure?
Hi. It’s been a long time, Ginjo.
Tsukishima!
So he’s…
How’ve you all been?
Kutsuzawa, hope you haven’t
been drinking too much.
Yukio…
Looks like you’re still
engrossed with playing games.
That’s not good.
You need to read more books.
Riruka’s not here?
Tsukishima…what did you come here for?
I don’t see Jackie around, either.
Tsukishima!
They in there?
Wait, Tsukishima!
What is this?!
Ichigo.
Ichigo…
That’s…
A Shihakusho!
Could it be…his Soul Reaper
powers have returned?
No…
That’s not a Shihakusho.
It’s…
a Clad-Type Fullbring!
Is this the true form
of Ichigo’s Fullbring?!
Of course!
It was the same with Ichigo’s Bankai.
Not only his sword, but his
Shihakusho changed as well…
He said his Shihakusho was
a part of his Bankai.
It was a Bankai that was worn.
For Ichigo…
wearing his power is his true form.
Did you know?
When Riruka’s “Dollhouse” is broken,
whatever’s inside is forcibly set free.
So you were hiding and
training in that thing…
But I must say, you’ve come quite far.
If that was the case…
You could have told me.
Hmm…
Who are you?
What do you want with me?
Oh? This is a surprise.
You mean you haven’t heard about me yet?
Oh no…
I hadn’t told Ichigo
yet about Tsukishima…!
I’m Shukuro Tsukishima…
Your friend’s…
Chad, wait!
Idiot.
Do something like that in here and…
What was that?!
Was that an explosion?! From where?!
Did a gas leak cause an explosion?!
Call the police!
Hurry, hurry!
What was that noise?!
See?
You get fools going crazy. What a pain.
I’ll handle the neighbors, the
fire department and the police…
Oh boy…
Who do you think has to pay
to fix all of this damage?
Hey! What was that noise about?!
Hey, tell me!
Chad!
He’s not here…
Ginjo!
Somebody explain!
You idiot!
Don’t make things worse
than they already are…
Ichigo’s activated his Fullbring.
I say it’s time we tell
him about Tsukishima now.
Not yet…
We still don’t know how powerful
Ichigo’s Fullbring is.
And, we don’t know if he has
full control of it yet…
Right now, telling him
that Tsukishima attacked
Inoue would only agitate him.
I see…
So he’s the one…
Ichigo!
I didn’t realize…
You guys were so concerned about me…
Looks that way.
Were you the one who attacked Inoue…
and the one who cut down Ishida?
What do you think?
Hmm…
Is this your Fullbring?
You’re strong, I’ll grant you that.
Damn it!
What’s going on?!
None of Ichigo’s attacks are hitting him!
Even though Ichigo’s first
step and timing are perfect.
Take a look at Tsukishima’s feet.
Bringer Light?!
At the moment when Ichigo’s
attacks are about to reach him,
Tsukishima uses his Fullbring
to make a high-speed move
just out of harm’s way.
Ichigo!
Wait!
What’s that…?
You’ll never be able to
hit me with such attacks.
I said, it’ll never hit...
Is that…?
Wow!
Ichigo!
When did he learn to do Bringer Light?
Nice!
He used Fullbring on the concrete
floor to leap farther.
But…that’s still not enough…
Did he just?
It was slight,
but during his jump he
applied Fullbring to the air
to accelerate himself.
Ichigo…
You’ve already mastered
Fullbring to that extent?
I see…
Looks like you’re more
capable than I had thought.
But…
It’s not good enough.
Your Fullbring power itself is still…
Far from being complete.
If you concentrate on your right arm,
the Fullbring on your left arm
becomes undone all too easily.
Case in point,
you were unable to break
your fall just now…right?
Damn…
Sorry…
Looks like it’s still a bit too
early to let Ichigo fight you.
Ginjo…
I’m back!
Man, that was crazy!
You won’t believe this!
I guess they said on TV that
honey was good for you,
and now it’s being sold out everywhere!
So I rode my bicycle to the next, next town
and went to fifteen different stores and…
Huh?
Mr. Tsukishima?
Are you in the bathroom?
Are you taking a dump?
Are you going to interfere, Ginjo?
I guess we see things differently.
If you ask me, you’re the
one who’s interfering.
Ginjo…
Move!
Can’t do.
I said…
Get out of the way!
Don’t you get it?
I’m saying you’re in the way.
You don’t get slammed from
that height and come away
unscathed with a mortal body.
Right now, you’re struggling
just to breathe.
We can’t afford to have you die.
Now shut up and go to sleep.
Ginjo…
Are you serious about this?
If you fight me, you’ll die, Ginjo.
We really don’t see things
the same way, do we?
If we cross swords, aren’t you
the one who’s going to die?
Wait, Ginjo.
I can still…
Chad!
Don’t, Ichigo…
I know you realize the
difference in power…
In your condition, it’d
be impossible to beat him!
What you’re seeing is a fight
between two Fullbringers.
So you want me to simply
stand by and watch?!
You want me to let the guy who
attacked Inoue and Ishida go?!
I’m not saying that!
I’m saying it’s still
too early to fight him!
Something’s wrong…
His sharp attacks clearly shows that
he’s aiming for my vital spots…
And yet…
I don’t feel any blood thirst from him.
Ginjo…
What’s he planning to do?
Damn you…
Now look what they did…
They’re fools! Fools!
Now it’s coming from that way!
Oh, my!
Wow, awesome!
A fire?
What is going on?!
The crowd is growing.
This is not good.
Ginjo!
Don’t!
Let go of me!
Ichigo!
That was dangerous.
You cut pretty deep into the building.
What if there were people inside?
Don’t worry.
I made sure to choose an abandoned
building when I jumped over.
Is that so?
In that case, I’ll also let loose.
Not over yet!
Ichigo changed his fighting style.
Did he learn to manipulate his Fullbring
just by watching Ginjo fight?
Ichigo…
Looks like you’ve gotten a bit better.
But…that sort of attack
still won’t affect me.
You really don’t get it, do you?
Your Fullbring is still incomplete.
Ichigo!
Such a big difference from a second ago.
Not bad…
Your power is now…
much closer to the power you once possessed.
“Invaders Must Die.”
What…is this?!
I see…
You don’t want me to come in contact with
Ichigo Kurosaki when his
powers are still incomplete.
Especially when he’s so close
to perfecting it. Right?
Yukio.
I feel like we’re forgetting something…
Aside from the fact that Ginjo and Chad
owe me an explanation, what else is there?!
No, it’s not about your stupid
issue, but something else…
The story is moving forward without
anyone coming to help me…
I’m sorry…
I was cooking, when all of a sudden…
That wouldn’t cause an
explosion this big, would it?
What’s taking you?
The commotion isn’t dying down at all…
Huh?
It’s already been two years
since I became a single father…
I’m not used to cooking, so
it’s been a real struggle…
Huh? What are you...
I never imagined cooking my daughter’s
favorite, omelet, would cause all this.
What omelet…
Please forgive your Dad.
What a wonderful father-daughter love!
Looks like he’s doing a great job…