I loathe the moon.
With nightfall, it brings you to me,
but it also takes you from
me when dawn breaks.
I wish the moon would never leave us.
Then you would always be here with me.
The moon will come with the night again.
And someday, when it does,
I will take you with me in the morning.
Wait before the cherry blossom tree
on the night of the next full moon.
Do you promise?
I promise.
Promise.
I'll be waiting
for the moon to rise
forever.
The legendary courtesan?
You don't know of her?
The other lady of Yoshiwara,
the courtesan Suzuran.
Why is she legendary?
Is she a descendant of Erdrick?
From Hand of the Heavenly Courtesan?
I'm not talking about Nera.
Nera? I was talking about Bianca.
Don't forget about Debora.
Uh, none of them matter.
The courtesan Suzuran.
Her beauty was said
to come from the heavens.
No one could rival her
in song or dance.
Many elite officials sought Suzuran's
favor by offering her great wealth,
but most were sent home
after a cup of tea.
Sounds like she was beautiful
enough to topple nations.
The other lady of Yoshiwara
isn't toppling nations
so much as toppling from
the weight of her makeup.
Oh, sorry.
My hand slipped.
Must be because our nation
is toppling over.
But it sounds like she's
no longer around.
I would have liked to
enjoy her company once.
You're more than welcome.
You're such a fool.
The legendary courtesan was
the one who invited you here.
She wants to meet the
savior of Yoshiwara.
Courtesan Turns the Tables
This should be good enough?
But wait...
Maybe I should...
It doesn't matter!
Aren't you getting ahead of yourself?
This is important though.
We're talking about a
legendary courtesan.
If I screw something up, this won't
be a Yoshiwara night anymore!
It'll be Tsukiji instead!
I'll turn into a dead fish!
Don't worry. Nothing like
that is going to happen.
Lady Suzuran has arrived!
Oh, she's here.
Here she comes...
Here she comes! Here she comes!
H-Hello.
It is an honor to meet you.
I am Su-Suzura...
Huh?
Who am I?
Allow me to introduce you.
This is the legendary
courtesan, our elder.
The courtesan Lady Suzuran.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Just over to Tsukiji.
Er, sorry.
I heard she was a courtesan, but she
was toppling more than I thought.
I didn't think she would be
completely toppled over.
You said that this is
the legendary what?
Lady Boomerang?
Lady Suzuran.
You girls are mean.
You made it sound like she
was working with you.
U-Um, I'm still on the job.
What?!
I don't mean to brag,
but I've been working here since before
Yoshiwara moved underground.
You're the one who's going
to be put underground soon!
I may be older now,
but my technique is just as
good as those younger girls!
What kind of technique is this?!
Please come over here, savior...
Huh?
Who are you?
Sakata Gintoki!
Oh, I wanted to thank you.
Please drink until you knock
yourself out tonight.
This lady's spilling the whole bottle!
Huh? It's empty.
You drink fast.
Are you listening to me, lady?!
Please knock yourself out tonight.
Lady, you've knocked yourself
out, so can I go?!
Behold Lady Suzuran's famous dancing.
Look at her break dance.
Wait, she's break dancing?
It looks like she's having a breakdown!
This is bad!
Should we call an ambulance?
Y-You're too hasty.
Why don't we get to bed then?
No!
Here is your bed.
What kind of bed is that?!
I-I truly enjoyed our
time together today.
What?!
You don't look like
you enjoyed yourself!
Thank you for being my last visitor.
Don't jinx yourself!
You're so kind.
You're showing so much
concern for an old woman.
Can you make me a promise then?
Come see me again when the moon rises.
I'll be waiting
for the moon to rise
forever.
That's known as a lovers' pact.
Long ago, the women of Yoshiwara would
exchange vows of love
with their customers.
My love belongs only to you.
I will never be unfaithful to you.
As proof, the women would offer
their hair, nails, and blood.
Sadly, most of the
women made these pacts
to squeeze more money
from their customers.
She's as good as they claim, then.
That old woman had a man's hair
wrapped around her pinky.
She refused to retire,
even after she no longer had
any customers and
Yoshiwara was set free.
She offered to do anything
if we let her stay here.
And she intends to spend the rest
of her life here as a prostitute.
She made a promise long ago
when Yoshiwara was still on the surface.
A promise to leave
Yoshiwara together...
Judging from her behavior,
she must have mistaken you for that man.
Do you mean that
Suzuran has been waiting here
all this time for that man?
I don't know.
But Yoshiwara has always been a place
where men and women lie to each other.
Everyone knows that these dreams
will not last beyond morning.
But we all continue to act our roles.
It's your own fault if you
choose to believe that dream.
But some may not wish to
awaken from that dream.
She wishes to sleep inside her
dream, under the moonlight.
Suzuran?
My late lech of a grandpa
mentioned her before.
Yes, I remember her.
She was a fine woman.
But she was out of my league.
I would have loved a chance
with Suzuki Ranran.
Yes, she was incredibly popular.
But personally, I was
more of a Miki-chan fan
than a Ran-chan fan
when it came to the Candies.
I would totally lay Pink Lady.
I would totally lay you.
I just want one last lay,
I don't care who...
I'm a fan of Ketsuno Ana.
Wait, I don't mean that like it sounded...
Kshatriya!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Why are you sneaking around
asking old men who they want to lay?
It's not my fault those perverted
leches got distracted!
Are you looking for the
old woman's darling?
Are you girly enough to think that the
man still remembers an ancient promise?
Who are you calling girly?!
I'm the leader of the
Hyakka, Lady Death!
I came to the surface for a
new pipe, but I got lost,
and when I asked for directions...
Um...
Boss!
We have information on Suzuran!
Shut up!
Huh? Why are you telling
them to shut up?
Did you come to the surface to buy
girly stuff to make yourself pretty?
You're such a girl.
No! I'm buying non-girly stuff
to make myself not pretty!
Get back to shopping!
Huh? Shopping?
For what?
Yeah, you women are hopeless.
That old woman was hoodwinked.
I feel sorry for you women.
Gin-san!
We have information on the old lady!
Shut up!
Oh, I see.
Fancy that.
So you're also doing
some secret shopping.
I'm buying manly stuff!
To make my curly hair manly!
So shut up!
You shut up!
Can you cut it out?
Both of you are so stubborn.
Gin-chan and Tsu-ki
both want to help the
old lady meet her darling
before she dies, right?
What?
Huh? Don't you?
I just wanted to make that man pay
for toying with the heart
of a Yoshiwara woman.
When Suzuran dies,
that man will also die.
This woman's up to no good!
I made her a promise.
If I find the man,
she'll give me all of her wealth.
Don't lie!
Don't make up promises!
So both of you are plotting evil!
What do you mean?
I'm going to end his life.
I won't let that happen. The
lady's money will be mine.
Hold on! Wait!
You need to show more respect, Gin-san!
Respect isn't the only thing
you need to show, boss!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Well, we were able to obtain
information on Suzuran-san's
former customer.
But this customer is big trouble.
Long ago, Suzuran-san had many wealthy
retainers as her customers.
But they all suddenly
stopped visiting her.
It was because of a certain rumor
going through Yoshiwara.
Suzuran-san was the
favorite of that man.
That man?
Who was he?
It's the man
who lives over there.
Shinpachi-kun, are
you saying that...
The former shogun.
Pachi-boy, can I ask you a question?
What will happen to us if
we're caught sneaking
into the castle to see
the former shogun?
We'll be executed.
What will happen if we wait for
the shogun to step outside?
We'll be executed.
Between the old former courtesan and the
old former shogun, who has more money?
Should be the shogun.
Okay, I have a plan.
Tsukuyo will sneak past the
guards into the palace.
Then I report her to the guards and
receive a reward from the shogun.
A perfect plan!
This seems more perfect to me.
Calm down, Tsu-ki.
We're talking about the former shogun.
It'll be hard enough to announce
ourselves, let alone meet him.
What would we say if we met him, anyway?
That his former lover is
waiting for him in hell.
This is bad.
She's going to get us arrested
for assassinating the shogun!
So we won't be able to sneak inside?
They've got guards everywhere.
Something must have happened.
Besides, even if that
old woman used to be the
top courtesan in Edo,
the shogun wouldn't go to
Yoshiwara to visit her.
The shogun was Suzuran-san's customer
before he became the shogun.
And didn't you know, Gin-san?
You haven't heard about the
13th shogun, Sadasada-sama?
When the Amanto attacked,
he replaced the 12th shogun
who collapsed from the stress.
While he was called a traitor
for opening up control,
he's considered a brilliant
leader who rebuilt the bakufu.
Even after abdicating,
he holds incredible influence
and serves as an advisor.
He was known to be a player
with the highest number of wives
ever recorded in the family.
So he went Abarenbo Shogun
every Saturday at 8 PM?
He went Abarenbo Shogun
every night at 8 PM.
He used his position to toy with
Suzuran, then he tossed her aside.
My target is the former shogun.
Could you not use the word target?
I understand that this is reckless.
Nevertheless, I must go.
Hey!
The woman devoted her
life to Yoshiwara.
Yoshiwara must return the favor.
She no longer needs the moon to
show her dreams that won't last.
The last moon she sees will
be when her dream comes true.
Tsukuyo-san...
Wait, Tsu-ki!
There's nothing reckless
about that dream.
Open the gates!
Attention!
Princess Soyo has arrived!
Kagura-chan!
Your Highness, behave yourself!
Soyo-chan!
It's been forever!
How have you been?
I'm doing just fine.
And you look like
you're in good shape.
Your Highness, it's not proper
to embrace someone in public.
I've been so lonely since
the last time you came.
Oh, did you bring me the new
sukonbu like you promised?
Yup!
Huh? What's that? Who's that?
Clara and Heidi?
If my memory serves me right,
that's Princess Soyo, the younger
sister of the current shogun.
If my memory serves me right,
the princess wouldn't
be yodeling with Heidi.
No way. When did she
score a connection
with the princess of this country?
When did she become more
influential than I am?
This is how Alm-Onji must have felt.
He couldn't be happy for Heidi when
she came back from
Frankfurt all grown up.
Alm-Onji wasn't that mean.
I brought my friends
today. Is that okay?
Of course.
Your friends are my friends.
Thank you for coming to visit today.
You must be Gin-chan.
Huh? You know me?
Yes, Kagura-chan has
told me all about you.
I'm honored to meet you.
N-No, I'm the one who's honored.
You've done a lot for Kagura.
You weren't lying about
how shaggy he is.
Uh, Kagura-chan? What have
you been telling her?
So the glasses wearing the
human are Pachi-boy-san?
Glasses wearing the human?!
That's backwards!
What have you been
telling her about me?!
Who is this woman?
She came from Yoshiwara to
knock off the shogun...
Yoshiwara? Knock off?
No, I'm... You know...
She's a delivery hell girl who came from
Yoshiwara to knock out the shogun.
How is that any better?!
So she's a delivery hell girl.
Delivery Hell
It still sounds like I'm
delivering him to hell!
I'm sorry.
You came to visit me, but
we have to sneak around.
Sorry about this, Grampy.
I'm used to your willful behavior.
At least you haven't run
away from the palace again.
Uh, did something happen?
The palace is currently
under martial law.
Your Highness! That's classified!
We can tell them.
Lately, somebody has been attacking
important bakufu officials,
so the palace is really
tense right now.
S-Sorry, it looks like
we came at a bad time.
No, it's perfectly fine.
I couldn't stand the gloomy
atmosphere much longer.
I see. I have no choice then.
Under normal circumstances, I would
tell these visitors to leave,
friends of the princess or not.
But I'll make an exception
in this case.
Since one of my e-mail buddies is here.
Holy!
Sasaki-dono!
Forgive me, these are...
No, it's fine.
Since the Mimawarigumi has been
entrusted to protect the palace,
the princess is perfectly safe.
And since we've determined
that the assailant is most
likely a Joi patriot,
it shouldn't matter if a former
Joi is allowed inside the palace.
Isn't that right, White Yaksha?
From: Sabu-chan
Subject: Your New Phone
"Throwing away your phone was mean.
I'll give you a new one,
so e-mail me again."
Your Highness, please be quiet!
If you cause any fuss, I, Rotten
Maizo, will lose my head.
Soyo-chan, what do you
want to do today?
We can play tag.
Yes, yes!
Were you listening to me?
You whine too much, old man!
Don't call me an old man!
This isn't good.
Do you know that man?
We made it inside the palace,
but we've got a pesky
watchdog on our tail now.
"Nobu-tasu's guarding
the princess right now,
so if you try anything
funny, you'll be killed.
Be careful."
We could ask the princess to help us.
How are we supposed to explain
Yoshiwara to that innocent girl?
And we've got Grampy and the
watchdog monitoring us.
That means we need to lose
Grampy and the watchdog
before we can freely
move around the palace.
I won't let you play
tag! It's not proper!
You're so pissy!
That's why you're known as "Gram-pee."
That's what Grampy stands for?
That's wrong, Kagura-chan.
The Gram is short for Grand,
so it's "Grand-pee."
Your Highness! That's worse!
Enough of this, Kagura.
Tsu-ki...
If we play tag under the
current circumstances,
we'll be making more
trouble for the guards.
See? Did you hear that, Your Highness?
This is how grown-ups should act.
Instead, you should keep it
quiet and play kick the can.
Wait, how does that make sense?!
If you play tag, you'll be running
around and making a lot of noise.
But kick the can is similar
to hide-and-seek.
There shouldn't be too much noise.
Makes sense!
Wait, you're missing the point!
Is she going to use hide-and-seek as an
excuse to shake Grampy and the watchdog?
Grampy's not going to accept that!
It's not proper for Your
Highness to kick cans!
See?
If you want to kick cans,
you should kick me instead!
What?!
Hey! Grampy's the worst offender here!
Now step on me with your pointy heels!
Grand-pee!
Wait.
Kick the can...
Kick the Grampy...
I can't allow that.
Damn, here she comes!
Let's play cut the Grampy.
You're joining in?!
What's cut the Grampy?!
Some kind of killing game?!
Are you going to play
with us, Nobume-san?
Yay!
This is more pointy than her heels.
Uh, it's too pointy!
I'll take a grand piss on that idea!
Both Grampy and the
watchdog are joining in!
Wait, wait, wait.
A guard shouldn't be doing this.
Grampy's going to die, so
we should change the rules.
Then I'm It.
I'll cut down everyone I find.
That'll mean more casualties!
Are you that eager to cut people?!
Hurry up and kick the can.
Wait!
Why are you starting already?!
Gintoki!
Kick the can as far as
you can to buy time!
Shut up!
Why do I have to buy you
guys time to run away?!
Damn it all!
I'll lose my head anyway when they
find out we're sneaking
around the palace!
In that case, I'll kick it good!
Go!
You're being too noisy, Soyo.
Honestly, when will you realize that
you are the Shogun's younger sister...
It-It-It...
It's the shogun?!
To be continued...
Guess what?
This spring...
No, this summer, the second
movie will be hitting theaters!
Yay! So spring...
I mean, summer is when it finally happens!
Time to celebrate!
This doesn't sound very celebratory.
Courtesan Turns the Tables!
The former shogun arrives
right as the current
shogun is taken out!!
Given the terrible timing,
will Gintoki and crew be
able to ask about Suzuran?!