Zanpakuto…
Their shape and abilities are
based on their Soul Reaper's soul.
Soul Reapers gain power
by learning their names
and synergizing with them.
They are born with Soul Reapers
and die with Soul Reapers.
That is what Zanpakuto are.
What is this?!
Don't move!
We're taking you into custody!
Bankai! Getsugatensho!
We don't want you to think
that this is all we've got.
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
I am Third Seat in
Zaraki Squad…
I'm Ikkaku Madarame!
Lieutenant Iba!
Oh, Lieutenant Kotetsu.
What's the situation?
Captain Soi Fon
and the others
are engaged in a battle
at the Squad 6 barracks.
I'm told Stealth Force has
the enemy surrounded
and is preventing them
from moving.
I see.
Then we should join
them there, as well.
Yes…
It seems there are
many wounded.
What is it?
What happened?
There!
What is that?
That's probably…
the Ashisogijizo…
How can you tell?
How shall I put it?
It's very distinctive.
Huh? Is it answering us?
At any rate, a Zanpakuto
has decided to show itself.
Let's capture it!
Wait!
That's…poison?
What?!
This is bad!
We gotta get away quickly!
Hado 1!
Sho!
We have to inform
Captain Kurotsuchi immediately!
Right!
I won't let you.
You're!
That's right.
It's started to rain.
My power is thunder
and lightning.
It is in this rain that I
display my true powers!
What's so funny?
If I'm not mistaken,
your Zanpakuto was Tenken,
wasn't it?
Is it okay to get
so wet in the rain?
No need to worry!
There's no way
this amount of rain
could extinguish
Tenken's flames of hell!
What you just said makes it
sound like you're not that strong.
Tenken? Yes, I see!
You're saying that these
rain clouds are nothing more
than a means to
reinforce my technique,
and that even if
the rain itself is weak,
I have nothing to
worry about, right?
I, Gonryomaru,
am unworthy…
I allowed myself to be
tricked by her sophistry…
I am ashamed…
How are you able to communicate
through such an exchange?
Are you using some sort of code?
Silence!
Tenken is extremely shy!
That's nothing to boast about!
Are you really
captain-level Zanpakuto?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Stop mocking us!
You're not getting away!
Is this the level
of your true powers?
Don't underestimate us!
Now to finish you!
What?!
Your powers seem to be for real.
This isn't going to be easy…
Gotcha!
That was so close!
I almost got the second strike in!
Is this the first time you were
struck by this technique yourself?
Yay!
Are you…Suzumebachi?!
Ding ding ding! That's correct!
What do you think of this look?
I didn't really like
your lame style.
So I thought, if I ever got free,
I would create my own look
and make myself look sharp!
I'm really glad I was
able to manifest myself
the way I wanted to look.
What? Do you have
a problem with that?
Your problem is
that all you ever do
in your free time
is worship Yoruichi.
Are you stupid or something?
If you have that much free time,
you should pay more
attention to your clothes
and find yourself a good man!
This…is my Zanpakuto?
If you can't believe that I am,
then maybe another strike
with this will convince you!
You're not as tough as you talk!
You're kinda weak…
You annoy me!
Damn it!
Why're you looking
at me that way?
You…
I'll never forgive you!
That's okay, you don't have to.
Come on…
Why don't you give up already?
If you give up now, I'd be at least
willing to spare your life…
I'm never giving up!
Listen… Have you noticed
the Spiritual Pressure around here?
Earlier, Ikkaku Madarame's
Spiritual Pressure disappeared,
didn't it?
Ikkaku…
You people can't defeat us with
the level of your abilities.
Ikkaku didn't lose!
Hozukimaru's Spiritual Pressure
disappeared too!
In all probability,
Hozukimaru tailored his to match
his opponent's fighting level…
Those two are quite alike,
you know.
But I'm different.
Unlike you,
I have no hesitation at all
in using this power in public.
Stop it!
Nope…
Tear in Frenzy…
Well?
How does it feel to be struck
by the power you so loathe?
I…don't want everyone to
know about this power…
I won't be able to
stay in Squad 11…
Are you still saying that?
You truly are stubborn…
Squad…11…
Still talking about that?!
Shut up…Fujikujaku!
I see…
Sorry!
What were you doing?!
That woman is your target!
Keep her in check!
Why do I have to back you up?!
Because it's only right!
We lost last time because
you didn't hold up your end!
Oh, really?
Wasn't it because
– you're a bonehead?
– What're those two doing?
– Oh, you make me so mad!
– Who knows?
– You never take responsibility!
– Whatever.
– Let me just tell you that
– Let's get out of here while we can!
– it's always your fault…
– La, la, la, I can't hear you!
Stop!
You're not getting away!
And you show yourself, too!
Oh no!
Hado 31: Shakkaho!
Kotetsu!
Are you okay, Kotetsu?
No you don't.
Iba!
I can't move my legs…
Oh?
You don't know
the power of Ashisogijizo?
The Ashisogijizo
deprives its victims
of the ability to move their limbs.
You were struck by its attack
and lost the use of your legs…
You are like a little bird
clipped of its wings.
Where am I?
You're…
You shouldn't strain yourself.
When you got me back,
your body paid a huge price.
What's the situation?
Muramasa and the others
staged an all-out attack.
The Soul Reapers are
battling them now.
I see…
Then I can't stay here in bed…
Believe in them.
The Soul Reapers
aren't so weak
that they'd perish
because of something like this.
You demonstrated
that to me, Master.
Kotetsu!
It's no use, mister!
Lieutenant Hinamori!
Isane!
What's the big idea?
Hi!
Darn!
You two again?!
We're not letting the two of you
get away this time!
That's what we
were going to say.
Last time we just
let down our guard!
Old lady!
Still the same rude
little girls, I see!
Matsumoto!
This is dangerous!
Let's get out of here!
The tables have turned, old lady!
Renji!
Brother!
Please stop it!
Damn!
Ikkaku's Spiritual Pressure
disappeared…
Yumichika's in danger, as well.
Dammit!
Getsugatensho!
Yahoo!
Bakudo 39: Enkosen!
You've got a quick reaction!
But no matter how hard
you fight by yourself,
it won't change
this battle setting.
Feel the Spiritual Pressure
around you!
We're overwhelming you.
You're giving me that glare
that makes me sick!
I'll gouge out those
eyes of yours!
Is it okay…to repeatedly unleash
so many direct attacks?
What?
What do you mean?
You should know the power
of my Zanpakuto, right?
What about it?
You didn't regain
your Shikai, did you?!
Answer, you coward!
You can't expect me
to answer that…
Something must be
wrong with you.
Come to think of it,
the guy's done nothing
but fend off my attacks and never
tried to attack from his side.
But… Why go through
all that tedious stuff
when he could've
just done a Shikai?
He's bluffing!
What's the matter?
Shut up!
The bastard did it again!
Over here.
You can't do a Shikai!
Even if you did
regain your powers,
I'll cut your life short faster
than you can do Shikai!
Hado 58!
Tenran!
I should answer your question.
I haven't regained Shikai yet.
But you lost the moment you
got caught in the maze of doubt.
You…
Bakudo 63: Sajosabaku.
Okay.
I'd better hurry
and help the others…
Your back is totally unguarded.
Wabisuke…
Oh no!
You're finished…
Kira!
What're you looking at?
Out of my way!
Dammit!
Aren't Kyoraku and Ukitake
joining us in battle?
Ah! Uh… Captain is…
I see…they're commanding
things from the barracks!
So this pinch we're in
is part of the plan!
Uh yes…you can rest assured.
I forgot to inform them…
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
I win.
I lost…
Come on, one more game.
I'm on a roll today!
I'm looking forward to this…
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah…it's just something
in my throat…
Hello, is anyone here?
SILENCE
Isn't there anyone here?!