I'm not falling for that again!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ulquiorra.
Here's what you wanted to see...
My Hollowfication!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
I don't want to be stereotyped...
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Yo, Ulquiorra.
Is it okay to kill
this woman already?
Ishida!
Don't let yourself be distracted.
Focus on your own opponent, Kurosaki.
I can handle this guy by myself.
Leave him to me.
Ishida...
Inoue-...
But how did you...?
What? Asking questions
during a battle?
You sure are easy-going.
What do you want to know?
Mayuri Kurotsuchi treated me.
He treated Abarai first,
so I took longer.
Abarai, Sado and Kuchiki
are still in a battle right now.
But I...
Ishida!
Who the hell are you?
Where did you crawl out of?!
I shot you with all that power,
but it didn't go through.
You're sturdier than I thought.
Why you...
Follow me.
There are too many things in
the way here, don't you agree?
Ishida, are you sure about this?!
I already told you.
Leave him to me.
Interesting...
Ulquiorra, I'm taking this one.
Suit yourself.
Are you that concerned
for that man?
Of course not!
Here I come!
You're such a fool...
Coming here just to get killed.
If you were going to be late,
you should've just run away instead.
Mind not saying things like that?
You make it sound like I got
here late because I hesitated.
Isn't that so?
Wrong.
It's because a dubious scientist
took his sweet time healing me.
Then blame that "dubious scientist."
Because of him,
you're going to die by my hands!
I hate that dubious scientist
quite enough without you telling me.
Bastard... You're making me laugh.
What's the matter?
Are you getting sick of it?
The god-like power of my Arbol...
To create an infinite number
of loyal soldiers...
The power of my Calaveras?
Even I, who was bestowed
creator-like powers by Lord Aizen,
could not become an Espada.
It is absurd for rodents such as
yourselves to defy the great Espada!
End your life here...Soul Reaper!
You piece of crap!
I'm not falling for that again!
You're quick when it
comes to dodging!
And it seems you're not
even quick at dodging.
How many would you
like this time?
Huh? Is that all you've got?
It's the same no matter
how many of these hit me.
They're not worth dodging.
At that level, it has no effect?
Kurosaki...
Is this woman the reason?
Is the reason why you won't pull out
that mask because this woman is here?
If that's the case...
You're wrong!
That's not it!
Then pull out your mask.
Like hell...!
Kurosaki isn't able to exert
his full Spiritual Pressure.
If he did, Inoue wouldn't be able
to withstand his Spiritual Pressure.
Oh? Looks like something
changed a bit.
Yeah, I don't have time
to waste with you either.
It's all the same
no matter what you do.
I suggest you don't assume that
I will do the same thing every time...
You don't get it, do you?
This is nothing...
Unlike my previous attacks,
that loosens your Reishi bonds and
makes them easier to take away.
It makes even
an Arrancar's Hierro penetrable.
Don't underestimate me, small fry!
Quite impressive...
You have the spirit to
continue to fight,
even against such
a large number of soldiers.
I must say, Soul Reaper,
you have limitless energy.
However, this battle is also limitless.
Allow me to be
your endless opponent.
Pushed back by these numbers,
I can't get near Rudobon,
the main entity.
At this rate, it'll just needlessly
deplete my stamina!
Renji!
Sado!
What's the matter?
You looked so chilled
and relaxed earlier.
But now you're starting
to look stifling.
I don't want to be pointed out
by the one who looks stifling.
You don't stop talking, do you?
I don't know what you meant
by stealing Reishi and whatnot,
but that level of power
won't do any good!
I was right about that Soul Reaper
being more interesting than you!
It's too bad for you,
after being saved by
that scientist of yours.
I wouldn't go badmouthing
that scientist too much...
if you don't want to regret it later.
Screw you!
Tsk! Where were you aiming?!
It's useless!
Out of options, I see...
Want to die now?
When it comes to being
a slow learner,
you're right up there with Kurosaki.
Did you think I was just
taking random aim at you?
Huh?
I wasn't aiming for you.
I was creating a field to lure you into.
That was my true aim.
What is this?!
I warned you...
Don't assume that I will do
the same thing every time.
Renji...Sado...
What's the matter?
You're sure taking a long time.
What about the two of you?
What happened to the ones below?
We took care of them, of course!
We're already
an invincible team, you know!
Sado must be quite annoyed
to have you as his confused partner.
What is it with you?!
We came to help you, you know!
No one asked for your help!
What did you say?!
Reinforcements?
More people aren't going
to change a thing.
I'll just send in enough soldiers
to match the three of you.
He can increase the number
of soldiers infinitely, is that it?
Just like some kind of fruit...
No, fruits don't grow infinitely.
Huh? They will if you keep
watering them!
Plants aren't such simple things.
Forget it!
- They seem to be
- For a big guy, you sure like to nitpick!
- getting along better now...
- What do you know about plants, huh?
Like a plant.
How're we going fight him, Rukia?
There's no limit to these numbers.
I want you two to take care of
every one of his soldiers!
I will go after him.
Fine... Let's go!
El Directo!
Normally, I can't use Sprenger
because it takes too much time
during a one-on-one battle.
But because you played with me,
you weren't wary of anything,
and that helped.
Damn you...
You're really pushing your luck!
You can still stand.
You are quite sturdy, after all.
Shut up!
But be careful beyond that point.
That dubious scientist gave them to me.
I've laid mines especially
designed for Arrancars.
Ishida!
You are such a slow learner.
Didn't I explain to you
that luring you into that field
was my biggest aim?
I didn't build that there by accident.
I knew the locations where
I had set the mines,
and after gauging the distance
between us, built it there.
I wouldn't move too much
for your own sake.
You damn brat...
You're Yammy,
who Szayelaporro talked about, right?
Huh?! So what of it?!
Just that I felt sorry for you.
If I hadn't shown up,
you could've gone on
a few more rampages.
Mala Suerte... I feel for you...
Dammit!
On my way here, I snapped
a few pillars at each level,
so you'll surely fall all the way
to the ground.
Ishida... Are you all right?
Do I look like a ghost or something?
No, you don't, but...just now...
Those explosions
you heard were mines
that Kurotsuchi had me bring.
They go off if their Spiritual Pressure
sensors detect
an Arrancar within range.
I carved out the ceiling
of the level below
and placed them there.
That guy, Yammy, never even
gave a second thought to
my aim of driving him into
the minefield, so he fell for my plan.
Any other doubts?
I never doubted you from the start.
You just went rambling on and on.
You're an annoying guy.
Look after Inoue.
If Inoue can't completely block
my Spiritual Pressure with her Rikka,
I want you to protect her with your life.
I was going to do that
even without you telling me.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ulquiorra.
Here I come!
Here's what you wanted to see...
My Hollowfication!
Come back here!
Damn it!
How far does he intend to go?!
Are we above Las Noches' ceiling?
That's right.
What?!
This Spiritual Pressure...
Ohh...This is...!
Master Ulquiorra...
Master Ulquiorra has broken
through the ceiling!
Kurosaki...
Two things are forbidden below
the ceilings of Las Noches.
The first is the Gran Rey Cero,
a Cero that exists for an Espada.
And the other is the sword release
of an Espada
that is ranked
cuatro and above.
That is because both
are so powerful
that they would threaten
to destroy Las Noches itself.
Enclose...
Murcielago!
Don't be flustered.
Hold your stance.
Extend your consciousness.
Don't let down your guard
for a moment.
You reflexively used Getsuga...
A wise decision.
If you hadn't done that,
your head would've been blown off
and rolling by my feet right now.
Sado and I understand
each other completely now!
You can tell what I want to do
even if I don't say it, right?
You can tell, right?
Right?!
Please tell me it's so...
- Illustrated Guide--
- Today, I'll explain the Fifth Tower.
There are no stairs
in the Fifth Tower.
To reach the upper level,
you must either fly in from
the outside...
or break through the ceiling
of the lower level to advance.
Oh...?
The ceiling wall is thick,
with many pillars,
and is well-made to
resist vibration.
How do you know such things?
Didn't you just hear me explain?
To get there, I broke pillars,
dug through the ceiling
and set mines along the way!
Huh? What the hell were you
doing looking all ridiculous?!
Oh shut up!