Now then...
Shall we continue?
Captain...
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Damn it...
Damn it!
Big brother!
What are they doing?
Well, no matter who dies, I'll still
get good research specimens.
That was an impressive Cero.
Damn bastard still
has power left.
Indeed.
All that's left is to finish
him off, you say?
Look at him. I pity your
foolish judgment.
To me, that's all it took.
A good finish!
But I suppose it was too
much to ask from you!
How interesting.
You can feel for yourself whether
it's too much to ask or not!
Sounds good!
I've always
wanted to fight you!
-You're in the way!
-Get lost!
Now then...
Shall we continue?
He really is a nuisance.
That hurts...
You guys really annoy me.
What's with him?
Has he gone crazy?
Un-Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Un-Un...
Un-Un-Un...
Unforgivable!
What happened?!
I-Impossible...
That's good, you guys.
You're really annoying.
The name of my Resurrección is Ira.
I'm a beast of rage!
Anger becomes my strength!
Come on, make me angrier!
Your deaths will be
that much more pathetic!
My, my...
Take care of it, you two.
Just kill each other already.
If he gets any larger,
I'll have a difficult time
dissecting him.
Tosen!
Come down here, Tosen!
I don't understand!
Why did you become
a Soul Reaper?!
Wasn't it for your friend
who passed away?!
Wasn't it to carry out
your form of justice?!
I told you, Komamura.
The only thing I can see with my
eyes is the least bloody path.
Justice is always there.
The path I follow is justice!
Friend of Tosen, whose
name I do not know...
What would you have
said to stop Tosen?
Captain Komamura...
Do you think Captain Tosen
will ever come back
here again?
Of course.
Let's find a way to
open Tosen's eyes.
Huh?
One down.
Hiyori!
Hiyori...
S-Sorry, Shinji.
Don't speak.
I...I couldn't hold back.
What a fierce look.
Your eyes look as if
they've come back to life for the
first time in a hundred years,
Shinji Hirako.
Do you hate me?
If you do, then come at me.
I shall make an exception for you
and fight you with my sword.
Hachi.
Yes?
Sorry to ask you for this
in your current condition,
but take care of Hiyori.
Do whatever you can
to keep her alive.
Just until Ichigo returns.
I will.
Shinji...
"Until Ichigo returns," huh?
You trust that boy quite
a lot, don't you?
It's something you
can't understand.
Not someone who can't even
trust his comrades.
Believing is the same as relying.
That is something the weak do.
We have no need for that.
That's pretty rich coming from a
guy with that many henchmen.
You used your silver tongue to
trick your subordinates
into trusting you.
No.
I've never told my subordinates
to trust me.
I told them to follow me,
but I never told them
to trust me.
I always told them never to
trust anyone, including me.
But sadly, there aren't any who
are strong enough to do that.
All creatures are unable to survive
unless they trust and obey
someone who is better
than they are.
To escape that pressure,
those who are better than others
search for their superiors.
Those who are superior,
search for even stronger individuals
they can believe in.
Thus the king of everything
was born.
Thus the god of everything
Don't believe me yet,
Shinji Hirako.
I'm going to take my time and show
you which god you should believe in.
You can decide on what
to believe afterwards.
I'm surprised.
I never expected Lord Aizen
to go to the front lines.
Since Lord Aizen has
made a move,
I should take you on
with my true power.
True...power?
Your Bankai, huh? Very well.
I shall use mine too.
My Bankai?
Don't make me laugh.
Lord Aizen gave me a power that
is far better than a Bankai.
Damn you, Tosen!
Could it be?!
No...
Stop! Tosen!
Is that how far you've fallen?!
Tosen!
Captain...
Hollowfication...
Is that...Is that a Hollowfication,
Captain Tosen?!
That's right.
Why?
Hisagi!
Tenken!
What?!
What...is...this power?!
How odd.
That half-Soul Reaper boy
you consider as an ally
has the power of Hollowfication
as well.
Must you scorn me so much
for gaining this power?
He...Ichigo Kurosaki did
not Hollowfy by choice.
But you are different.
As a Soul Reaper, you had
more than enough strength.
And yet, you went astray
of your own volition!
Yours is that of corruption, Tosen!
Corruption?
How is it corrupt for Soul Reapers
to become closer to Hollows?
Such words come from a
narrow-minded dualism
that deems Soul Reapers and
Hollows as good and evil.
No!
You betrayed your comrades,
you betrayed your friends,
and you even betrayed
your subordinates.
All for the sake of gaining
excessive power.
That is corruption!
Komamura...
It seems I didn't step
in far enough.
How naïve of me.
No,
I instinctively dodged
it by a hair.
Whenever I draw my sword,
I position myself to always be able
to dodge everything by a hair.
You taught me that,
Captain Tosen.
Captain Tosen, it's because
of you that I was able to...
What's wrong, Hisagi?
Why have you called me here?
What did you want to
talk to me about?
Captain Tosen...
Please relieve me from the
position of Seat Officer!
I was wondering what
this was about.
Don't worry about your mistake
during training yesterday.
Everyone starts off like that.
This is different!
I didn't fall behind because
I made a mistake
or because I was careless.
I was afraid!
Long ago, when I went to train
in the World of the Living,
I injured my right eye.
Since then, I've been no good.
Whenever I draw my sword,
whenever I face an enemy,
I always feel discouraged!
Captain Tosen...I...I'm
afraid of battle!
"Afraid of battle," huh?
That's why you should
remain an officer.
The most important thing for a
warrior to have is not power.
It is a heart that fears battle.
A heart that fears...
That's right.
Even I'm afraid of battle.
You, Captain Tosen?
I cannot see. How can I
not be afraid of battle?
Holding my sword
and even taking a step forward
like this are incredibly terrifying.
Fearing battle, allows you
to pick up your sword
and fight for those who
are also afraid of battle.
Those who are not afraid
to hold their swords
do not have the right
to hold swords.
Hisagi...
If you truly fear battle from
the bottom of your heart,
then you have gained something
that is invaluable to a warrior!
I...I cannot understand,
Captain Tosen.
Those were your words.
So why did you discard
everything for power?!
Right now, what are
you afraid of?!
Cap...tain...
Tosen...
I am afraid.
These past hundred
years, my fear was
being assimilated into
you Soul Reapers
and to die as one of you.
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
Tosen!
I will do whatever it takes
to open your eyes!
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
Like hell I'm going to
believe you, Aizen!
I would have provided you with
a huge feast and a castle,
as well as anything
you could desire.
If only you would have
believed in me.
What?!
How unfortunate...
Hold it! Give me a second
to think it over!
Say goodbye to your old self!
The Charismatic Dr. Mayuri Kurotsuchi's
Magical Clinic
My name is Dr. Mayuri.
Allow me to help resolve
any issues
you may have with
your appearance.
Before surgery
Gloomy single-edged eyelid...
Case 1
Going from a gloomy
single-edged eyelid
After surgery
Turns into bright double-edged eyelid!
Case 1
to a bright double-edged
eyelid is a piece of cake!
Case 2
Before surgery
Think there's no hope for you?
After surgery
Case 2
Well, think again!
Before surgery
Reconstruct your body
at the cellular level.
Case 3
We can also reconstruct your
body at the cellular level.
After surgery
To become a completely
different you!
Case 3
Hey, I didn't go through this!
This is excessive advertising!
You want a beating, baldy?!
Contact the following to
request our brochures.
There are currently trials
available as well.