Ulquiorra...
To drag her down from that place!
Inoue!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
Not done yet...
I can do this.
I can see his moves and react.
Watch!
The last time we fought,
I couldn't read
your movements at all...
But now I can.
Is it because you've become
more human like me?
Did you say...
I've become more human...?
I see...
You must feel really good being
able to keep up just at this level.
No you don't.
Hey, hurry up, will you?
You know...
Let's not do this.
I don't want anything to do
with that girl anymore.
You heard it too, didn't you?
What Lord Aizen said...
Now is the time...
Now is the only time to
drag her down.
To drag her down from that place!
What are you doing?
Huh?
Tell me why you saved him.
Why? B-Because...
He's one of you?
Then why didn't you protect him
from the very first attack?
Why did you hesitate?
I...uh...
You don't know?
Then I'll tell you why.
You're...
Shut up.
Hesitated this, hesitated that...
going on and on about stupid things.
Who cares about that?
Thanks for saving me, Inoue.
But it's dangerous, so stand back.
Kurosaki...
Ulquiorra...you're quite talkative,
aren't you?
I thought of you more as
the silent type.
A Getsuga?
You still don't get it, do you?
That won't work on me.
Instead of releasing the Getsuga,
he kept it on the blade to create
a slashing attack
with the power of a Getsuga.
Not good enough!
I suppose you were
trying to be clever.
But have you forgotten?
You were unable to defeat me even
using Getsuga with your mask.
Regardless of how it's used,
a Getsuga without the mask
is meaningless.
Kurosaki...
I got you.
Inoue?!
What are you doing?
There might not be many left,
but we're still in
the middle of a battle.
But Inoue!
Inoue?
Ichigo should be with her...
Ichigo is up against the largest
Spiritual Pressure right now.
Damn it...
So we need to take care
of these guys quickly,
or else we'll be too late.
- Ishida!
Sorry I'm late. Mayuri Kurotsuchi's
treatments took a long time.
Hey, looks like you made
a complete recovery.
Ishida, Inoue is...
Yeah, I know.
For crying out loud,
what is Ichigo doing?
Remember me?
Maybe you don't.
Of course not.
There's no need for
a monster like you
to remember someone
normal like me!
But your time of sitting high up
on the stairs is over now.
Inoue!
Who are they?!
Stay away!
If you come closer,
I'll gouge her eyes out!
Getsuga...
Ulquiorra?!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't save you.
Move!
Make me...
Kurosaki!
Your friend isn't all that much, is he?
Menoly!
Rip this woman's body apart!
Menoly?
I don't want to do it...
What are you saying?!
That girl has the ability
to heal any wound, right?
No matter what we do,
it'd be useless.
It'll just make us feel
more empty.
You...can't get yourself
to kill this woman
because your own life
was saved, is that it?
It's not that...
Coward!
Forget it. I'll do it alone.
Loly!
Shut up!
Lord Aizen said it.
You're no longer of use...
Understand?
It means that Lord Aizen
won't scold me
regardless of what I do to you.
You're done for.
I will tear out everything
you stole from me!
Inoue!
Getsuga...tensho!
Damn it!
I said move!
If you want to fight an opponent
other them me, then kill me first.
Shut up!
Move!
Stop it!
What?
What was that?
What's the matter?
Why don't you say the same thing
you said earlier?
"Your subordinates
have all fallen."
If you wish, I'll let you say it
as often as you'd like.
Nice... I like that expression.
Something's going on
with Master Ulquiorra.
Could this be...?
Another huge Spiritual Pressure
has appeared where Ichigo is.
What in the world could it be this time?
Ulquiorra...
I came to help!
When did I ever ask
for your help, Yammy?
He's...that guy from back then.
Don't be so unfriendly.
That Soul Reaper kid looks like
he's gotten a lot stronger.
Let me join you.
I see.
Looks like you've
completely recovered.
But there's nothing
for you to do here.
Go back and get some bed rest,
or go and take care of
the captain-level Soul Reapers below us.
What's with that!
Stop being so stingy, Ulquiorra!
Your shortcoming is that
when you get in that state,
you become very stubborn, Yammy.
Come on, don't be like that.
Y-Yammy...
Huh?
You have no business with us, right?
We'll leave right away, so...
Let's go, Loly!
Are you kidding me?!
Not after we came this far!
Loly! That's enough of that.
Menoly!
Ulquiorra!
What are these bitches doing here?!
Ask them.
Yeah...You're right.
Hey, you!
What're you small fries doing here?
You're in the way.
How's this?
One more time!
Oh, come on.
Are you finished already?
You're not even good for
a little warm-up exercise.
Hey, Ulquiorra!
These two are no fun, after all,
so I'm going to join you!
Yammy, that bastard...
You...
You must be enjoying this.
Watching us, who tried to kill you,
getting treated like this...
Go ahead and laugh if you want.
J-Just a minute... Stop it!
What's the big idea?!
Are you crazy or something?
I almost killed you, remember?!
And... And yet, you're helping me?
What are you?
Inoue!
This is getting really old.
I told you to do that after you kill me.
Huh? What's with you?
What are you wasting time
playing house for,
instead of just dropping dead?
Actually, this woman here
seems a lot more interesting.
Wait!
Huh?
What? Where in those clothes
were you hiding a sword?
You're a naughty woman.
What?
I was sick of the idea of having
to owe you any favors!
Bitch... What are you getting
in my way for?!
You keep your hands off
of my catch!
Poison!
Escolopendra!
I...
I didn't come here to be defeated
by the likes of you! Yammy!
With my poison, I'll kill you, Ulquiorra,
and everyone and anyone,
dissolving everything into pulp!
W-Wait!
Stay away!
You really piss me off.
I can't tell you how much
you piss me off.
Small fries shouldn't act so big!
Damn you...
You...
You...scumbag...
Huh? What'd you just call me?
You...scumbag.
I couldn't hear you...
Huh? What the...?
She's dead.
I figured this wouldn't be any fun.
Wait!
Huh?
Did you say something?
Yo, Ulquiorra.
Is it okay to kill this woman already?
Don't do it!
Inoue!
Ishida!
Don't let yourself be distracted.
Focus on your own opponent, Kurosaki.
I can handle this guy by myself.
How did Ishida get to
the Fifth Tower?
He'd have to fly to make
that kind of entrance.
I'm told there exists a tribe
in the World of the Living
who use mysterious powers
to fly around on broomsticks.
That must be it!
Could you not put Quincies
and wizards together?
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
Today, we will talk about Loly.
Loly's sword release is "Escolopendra."
It possesses a powerful poison
that melts everything it contacts.
But even if I explain it,
she's already dead and
can't come here...
I'm not dead!
Huh?
Hurry up and come save me!
But I'm in the World of the Living
and can't go to rescue you.
Save me!