Aizen has abducted Orihime.
In order to save her,
Ichigo and his friends
They break into Las Noches,
the Arrancars’ hideout,
and begin fierce battles with powerful
Arrancars who are waiting for them.
Sado defeats Gantenbainne,
but Nnoitora, one of the Espada,
appears immediately afterwards.
Sado is powerless before him.
Look at that.
You really are weak.
Chad was defeated?!
That's impossible!
Believe in him.
We vowed that
we'd come back alive!
It seems you've noticed.
That idiot Nnoitora was impatient.
We were ordered
to wait in our palaces.
Sado isn't dead.
He isn't dead.
Meanwhile,
Rukia clashes with Aaroniero,
an Arrancar who has the face of the late
Squad 13 Lieutenant, Kaien Shiba.
At that same moment,
Renji was also in a tough situation
against Octava Espada, Szayelaporro.
Oh. Of course,
you're wonderful too.
So I'll give you the greatest welcome.
I'd like you to accept it.
How about it?
There's no need to be modest.
Wait.
What do you mistake this for?
I didn't come here to talk to you.
I came here to crush you guys.
I don't care who you are.
I don't want your welcome.
If you want to talk,
then talk to me while I'm slicing you.
But I have no intention
of holding back!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
What?
See?
This is what happens when you don't
listen to everything I have to say.
You can't use
your Bankai in this room.
I can’t use my Bankai?
Yes, that's right.
It's nice that you
confirmed it verbally.
Not bad for an idiot.
I have complete information
on your Bankai.
From its form, abilities,
and Spiritual Pressure,
to even its reishi composition.
I used that information to seal away
your Bankai within this palace.
Complete information on my Bankai?
Only those who have fought against it
first-hand should know about that.
How is that possible?
My older brother.
What?
Do you remember my name?
You probably don't.
Oh well. I'll say it once more.
My name is Szayelaporro Grantz.
Illfort Grantz is…
my older brother.
Him?
Oh. You remember that scum?
I must thank you for that.
From the way you talk…
You're not here to avenge
your brother, are you?
A fool would think that.
Did you think
I came after you for that?
I gained information
about your Bankai
from the Rokureichu,
the recording spirit bugs.
I placed them all over his body
while he was healing his wounds.
To me, he was just a box
to carry my Rokureichu.
I'm not childish enough
to get mad at you for breaking my box.
You're real scum.
What a completely
unexpected complaint.
I'm stunned.
Fine.
You no longer have a way
to win or escape.
Don't struggle.
This is the first time
I've seen an individual
who can use a Bankai
in person.
I'm actually quite excited.
So don't struggle.
I want you to die in as close
to perfect condition as possible.
Sanomai…
Shirafune.
Wha—?
Aaroniero, huh?
Master Halibel,
what should we do?!
That kid.
Dying in such a pathetic way…
Master Nnoitora…
Kaboom!
You woke up!
Hey there, Stark!
Lilinette…
Give me a break.
Hey! Don't sleep!
Come on, wake up!
Wake up!
– Hey, hey, hey, hey!
– S-S-Stop that, Lilinette!
You idiot, that's my…
I'll stop if you wake up!
– Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
– Hey… You…
Aaroniero was killed.
I know.
Is that all right?
What do you want me to do?
Roar! Zabimaru!
I'm not finished yet!
What's wrong?!
Didn't you have
complete information on me?!
It looks like even though
you have my information,
you can't keep up
with my actual movements!
Crap!
Hey, hey, hey!
You're just all talk!
The finishing blow!
Just kidding.
Why you…
Your swings are pretty slow.
You're slower than
my information on you.
Bastard…
Don't you realize yet?
I was just making you dance
on the palm of my hand.
You bastard…
It can't be…
Oh? You seem to have noticed.
You dodged my attacks
without moving much.
I was testing to see
how good your attacks are.
They were below
my expectations.
Is this the best you can do
without your Bankai?
Don't underestimate me!
Roar! Zabimaru!
I don’t even have to
see your swings anymore.
I can see your attacks.
That attack won't work
against me anymore.
You bastard…
Master Szayelaporro!
Lumina and Verona?
What's wrong?
Aaroniero died!
Died! Died! Died!
Hmm…
Oh, it's true.
I've got the report.
I was so engrossed in what I was doing
that I didn't notice it.
Oh?
They killed each other, Soul Reaper.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that one of your friends
and an Espada killed each other!
Congratulations!
That's quite the accomplishment!
Whether they killed each other…
We're still not sure, you say?
You should stop with the optimism.
I've received the name of
your dead friend.
Kuchiki is one of
your friends' names, isn't it?
That was the reaction I expected.
You really are amusing.
But I've told you many times.
You can't damage an Espada
with just your Shikai.
Quit your blabbing.
Get out of the way!
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Rukia?!
So you've noticed.
I thought that you were a kid
who possessed only brute strength.
Amazingly,
you have some decent senses.
You're…
It's been a while, Soul Reaper.
I sense several
Spiritual Pressures nearby.
Someone is fighting.
And that Spiritual Pressure earlier
was Kuchiki.
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Did you sense something
happening to your friends?
I'm Uryu Ishida.
Remember that, already!
All right, Ichigo!
So where are we headed?
You're doing that on purpose,
aren't you?
It's easy to play
the straight man
thanks to my obvious
funny man, isn't it?!
This is my talent!
Let's keep it up.
You're wasting time!
Let's go!
Oh! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Hey, Uryu!
You're…
Ulquiorra!
You remember my name.
I don't think I ever
told you my name, though.
Oh well.
Rukia Kuchiki has died.
What?!
More accurately, she and
Espada Number 9 killed each other.
Her whole body was covered in cuts
and she was stabbed by a spear.
She can't be alive.
Don't make assumptions.
Rukia's Spiritual Pressure
only decreased just now.
You weren't even fighting her.
There's no way that you would know.
Synchronized Awareness…
That was one of Espada Number 9's
abilities as well as one of his roles.
He can immediately
convey information
about the enemies he fights
to his comrades.
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Please let me out!
Let me out.
I'm coming right now.
I don’t want it to be like this.
Kuchiki…
Where are you going?
I'm going to save Rukia.
I thought I told you she's dead.
I don't believe you.
You sure are stubborn.
Is it all right for you to leave
without killing me?
I have no reason to fight you.
What do you mean?
You're my enemy.
But you haven't hurt
any of my friends yet.
I see.
So what if I tell you
that I was the one
who brought Orihime Inoue
to Hueco Mundo?
So Inoue really didn't go
to Hueco Mundo of her own free will!
How unexpected.
You were slightly doubtful of her
even though you came to save her.
Do you understand what you did?!
Because of you
Inoue is being called a traitor!
Probably.
If not, then we’ve
miscalculated things.
You bastard!
Do you have a reason
to fight me now?
I-Ichigo…
Nel, stand a little further away.
Ichigo…
It seems that he's not
going to let me past.
Sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
I'm going to go at full strength!
Bankai!
Soul Reaper,
you're exhausted,
but you seem to have
recovered quite a bit.
Of course!
I covered him with my saliva,
which has excellent healing properties.
Ichigo can't live
without me anymore.
Don't speak poorly of me!
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
– Golden!
Butter…
– Butter… Butter…
– It's “cheese,” Nemu!
Butter…
Run away!
Capture them.
I don't know what you're up to,
but you lost from the moment
you chose me as your target.
FAILURE