Ichigo defeats Espada
Number 6, Grimmjow,
in a deadly battle and
rescues Orihime.
But shortly afterwards, Espada Number 5,
Nnoitora, appears and challenges him.
Unable to tend to the injuries
sustained from his previous battle,
a wounded Ichigo is forced
to fight back.
As a result, his mobility is greatly affected
and the situation becomes dire.
What?
Does this just look sharp?
I shouldn't have bothered
dodging it.
Ichi…
Are you…
Nel?
Meanwhile, after making contact
with the purple ooze Szayelaporro
created from his sword release state,
Ishida and the others find themselves
facing their own clones.
And before they can
fight the enemy,
they must first fight themselves,
who possess the same abilities and powers.
See, what did I tell you?!
It is an attack!
I can't take anymore!
There's no time for this!
What are you talking about?
We must look for Nel!
I know that!
We'll look for Nel!
As soon as we get away
from here!
No. We must find her
right away!
I sensed it a while ago.
Nel is frightened.
We can't let Nel get any closer
to Las Noches.
What's this?
I wondered what
she was doing here.
You brought her?
Well, judging from your face,
you've been dragging her around
without knowing who she is, eh?
What do you mean?
Well, if you don't know,
I'll tell you.
This kid is Nel…
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck.
A former Espada.
Former Espada?!
That's right!
What? You thought
she was harmless?
Fools! You've all been tricked!
She is, without a doubt,
one of the Espada!
Right, Nelliel?
I-It's a lie.
There's no way Nel
could be an Espada.
That's impossible.
Oh? What're you saying?
Are you joking around?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
N-Nel didn't forget.
N-Nel is not an Espada.
I haven't seen you in a while,
but during that time,
you've become irritating
in a different way.
What?
You tricked these guys
and used them.
And you've come deep
into Las Noches.
N-Nel didn't trick them!
Nel is…
What did you come back here for?
You must have a purpose, right?
Did you come to settle our fight,
looking like that?
N-Nel doesn't have a purpose.
Nel just…
It was fun until now!
Really, really fun!
What did we do to you?!
– United, we're…
– The Neldonpe Phantom Thieves!
– The Great Desert Brothers!
– The Three Super Powered
Siblings of the Burning Sands!
You're not in unison!
We never thought that
our game of eternal pursuit
would cause such
a misunderstanding.
Nel is a real masochist.
It's no fun unless Nel is chased to
the point where Nel cries a little!
What kind of words are you
teaching this kid?!
Oh Mr. Soul Reaper…
If you aren't bad guys,
then play with us!
Here we go!
Catch Nel!
Then beat Nel up
and make Nel cry!
Why you…
Ichigo!
N-Nel!
Super acceleration.
Mucus! Mucus! Mucus!
Ichigo, you idiot! Baldy!
Piece of crap!
Good-for-nothing!
All right! I get it. Don't cry!
I'll take you with me,
so give me a break!
Go faster! Go faster!
Nel still wanted to be with Ichigo
and everyone else!
Nel didn't want to be parted
with them!
Nel…
Quit joking around!
I never did like you.
Well then, it's over.
Please believe Nel, Ichigo!
Nel did not trick you…Ichigo!
Ichigo!
Your babbling irritates me.
You're such a bore.
Ichigo…
It goes without saying.
You wouldn't trick us.
Ichigo…
Don't worry, Nel.
Me, the others…
We all trust you.
You didn't use us.
Who cares if you used
to be an Espada?
I…
The Nel who's here right now…
That's who I believe in.
Talking nonsense like that.
I won't let you touch a hair
on Nel's head!
Don't make me laugh!
It's heavy!
Like you can do anything.
Huh? Soul Reaper!
Ichigo!
Huh? Seems like you've
lost your memory.
Well, whatever.
I did split your head open
pretty good.
I guess losing your memory
couldn't be helped.
Hold it.
Split, you said?
Oh yeah!
I'm the one who broke
her head open!
Nel!
Stop!
Not worried about yourself?
Have you forgotten?
Your sword can't cut me!
Kurosaki!
She was so irritating.
This girl here.
Just like you right now.
Don't go near Nel!
That's why I broke open
her head from behind,
and threw her outta Las Noches.
I said don't go near her!
Shut the hell up!
No matter how many times you try,
it'll be the same!
What are you?
You can't beat me.
Can't you understand that?
No matter how times you try,
it's useless!
It doesn't matter whether
I win or not.
What?!
I-I'll protect Nel.
That's all.
Then go ahead and die!
He's coming!
H-He's fast!
Kurosaki!
It's useless. That Soul Reaper
can hardly move.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's your turn.
Wait.
It's not over yet.
Didn't I tell you?
I won't let you touch a hair
on Nel's head!
You're so persistent!
Eat this!
Ichigo!
You're still alive?
I hate guys who keep attacking
when they can't win.
I-Ichigo…
Let's end this, Soul Reaper!
Ichigo… Ichigo…
Ichigo…
Ichigo!
Th-This is… P-Pesche!
Yes!
What's the matter?
How nostalgic.
This Spiritual Pressure…
What?! Spiritual Pressure?!
What's going on?
Yes. This Spiritual Pressure…
There's no mistake.
It belongs to Master Nel.
Nel?
That's Nel?
So you've returned to
that form, Nelliel?
Why you…
Nel?
Are you really Nel?
Yes.
Thanks to you, Ichigo,
I was able to return to this form.
Thanks to…me?
Yes.
I was small and you…
protected me.
And brought me all the way here.
Please stay still for a bit.
I want to thank you.
W-Wait, Nel!
By "thank" you mean…
Don't tell me
you're gonna fight him!
It's all right.
It'll be over in an instant.
Wha—?!
Why you…
What?!
Master Nnoitora!
N-Nel?!
Damn!
Eat this!
S-So fast!
Like you can kill me!
Over here.
Th-That's…
That's the real…Nel?!
It's a Cero! Nel!
What?!
That's…
Damn!
W-What was that?!
Huh? What? You heard that?
No, I didn't!
But why don't you have
any sense of anxiety?!
No, I am anxious.
That's why my stomach is…
I'm not listening!
That Spiritual Pressure
didn't belong to Ichigo.
But it was immense!
Master Nnoitora!
K-Kurosaki!
J-Just a minute.
I'll heal you in a moment.
Nel…
Ichigo!
Thank goodness!
I'm so relieved you're all right!
W-Wait, Nel… I mean, Ms. Nel!
He'll die! You'll kill Kurosaki!
Nel! I mean Ms. Nel, please!
See? Kurosaki's eyes
are turning white.
Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Ms. Nel!
That's the finishing blow!
Who said to release the girl?
I-I beg your pardon.
What is it?
I thought it was gonna
be over quick.
Huh, Nelliel?
You added Cero to
the one that
you had absorbed and
released it towards me.
So why am I still alive?
Looks to me like
that's what you're thinking.
I had totally forgotten.
"Cero Doble" is your specialty.
I should've been more careful.
However, you've forgotten one thing.
How many years have passed
since you disappeared from here?
Don't think that
the Espada's ranking
is the same as back
when you were here!
Nelliel!
Ichigo, please wait a bit longer.
B-But…
It's all right.
Nnoitora is my opponent.
This time, I will protect you.
I shall teach you
that the number on your back
is totally meaningless now!
This Spiritual Pressure that
I've sensed for a while…
So you noticed, Uryu?
You see, Master Nel is
actually a magical girl
who can transform into
an adult using a stick!
And Pesche and I are Master Nel's
cute mascots and servants!
Don't lie.
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers.
Why did they call me for this?!
We'll take a short break.
Oh, break time!
Time for candy!
She's here too?!
Byakki, what's for snack?
If this will do,
you are welcome to it.
What is it? It's weird.
No thanks!
That was a great
counter-strategy, Captain!