You keep moving around!
Huh?
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi mo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
tanoshii uragiri ni atte
Sure, betrayal can be pleasurable...
torawarenai atashi ga koko ni iru no
But I stand right here - not giving in to temptation.
tarinai tsukinai nandatte
"Enough," "not enough," whatever.
motto hizumasete yo
Open your mind.
pataan kashita konna sekai ja
Living in this routine-laden world...
...is enough to make you forget who you are.
jibun ga dare nano ka wakaranakunaru
waku ni hamaritakunai wa
I don't want to be stereotyped...
kimetsukenaide yo
...so don't make assumptions about me.
michi naki michi wo yuku no
I'm going to blaze my own trail.
soko ni itatte matteitatte
Nothing will ever be accomplished...
nani mo hajimaranai
...if you just stand around waiting!
chAngE
nabikanai nagasarenai yo
I won't give in. I won't be dragged away.
ima kanjiru koto ni sunao de itai no
I want to stay honest to the way I feel now.
dareka no omoidoori ni wa sasenai wa
I won't let you tell me what to do.
chAngE
nando demo umarekawaru no
I will be reborn as many times as it takes.
kanashimi wo dakishimete
I'll take my sadness with me...
hashiridasu yo
...and run.
anata no moto ni wa
I'm past the point of no return.
mou kaerenai wa
I cannot go back to you now.
atashi wa atashirashiku
On my own terms...
I wanna chAngE
...I wanna change.
What do you have to fear?
All of you already
died on that night
a hundred years ago.
Hiyori!
One down.
Hiyori...
S-Sorry, Shinji.
Don't speak.
I...I couldn't hold back.
Hiyori... What should I do?
How can I help Hiyori?!
That's right...
Orihime...
Orihime's power can
still heal her!
Ichigo!
Isn't Ichigo here yet?!
This is bad!
I caught you!
You're the last one.
You're so small, I had a
tough time catching you.
You're not getting away!
Don't struggle.
It's pretty difficult to hold on
to you without crushing you.
Now then...
How should I kill you?
Let's see...
Crushing you like this
wouldn't be amusing at all.
Sokatsui!
That hurts! That hurts!
That really hurt!
That was really painful!
He isn't affected at all.
That was so painful...
it made me lose my grip on you!
What incredible power...
I can't regain my posture because
of the wind pressure!
That was boring.
I don't feel satisfied at all.
Oh well...
I guess I'll go kill the guy
who defeated Ulquiorra.
And who might that be?
Huh?
Y-You!
Hey.
You've gotten pretty big since
the last time I saw you.
I thought you were
someone else.
Ichigo!
Ichigo Kurosaki...
I'm going to kill you!
I-Ichigo...
Why are you alone?
I thought you went
to save Inoue?
I did save her.
Right now, she's above
us healing Ishida.
It's safer there than here.
Ichi...
Quit moving around, damn it!
Wait here, Rukia.
I'm going to settle things quickly and
go to the World of the Living.
I'm going to put an end to
this whole stupid battle.
Ichigo...
What happened
to you up there?
That look in your eyes is not the look
of someone who was victorious in battle.
Nor is it the look of someone
who is about to enter a battle.
What happened?
Ichigo...
Quit moving around,
you piece of trash!
Damn it!
How long are you going
to keep running away?!
I told you to quit moving around!
You sure are noisy.
I'm not exactly jumping around
to run away from you.
I'm trying to draw you
away from that area!
If it's only the two of you...
I can crush you with force.
What's this? Just now...
I couldn't see it clearly,
but were the markings
on his mask different?
If I'm not mistaken,
the markings on his mask have
been changing little by little.
That's what I've heard!
But that just now was a completely
different marking!
What's going on?
Ichigo!
What was that odd
feeling just now?
There was something strange
about my Hollowfication.
My mask seemed heavier.
Is it because of "that"?!
"That" did something
to my Hollowfication.
Damn it...
You cut me a little.
Piece of crap!
Cut him a little?!
He got hit with my Getsugatensho
while I was Hollowfied.
And it only gave him a cut?!
Huh? Why are you shocked?!
Take a look at my number!
I'm Number Zero!
I'm Espada Number Zero,
Yammy Riyalgo!
None of the Espada you've fought
before are stronger than I am.
Stronger than Grimmjow,
Nnoitora, and Ulquiorra!
They're trash
compared to me!
How's that, huh?!
That's not a Cero. It's a Bala!
Look at that power!
Does a pest like you have any
strategies against that?!
Do I have any strategies
against that?
I've never really had any strategies
against anything.
I just had to defeat
people, so I did.
That's all.
I don't care if you're on a different
level than the other Espada.
It's all the same.
I've got to defeat you, so I will.
That's all.
You piece of crap!
You're really cocky, kid!
Do you think you can negate the difference
in our strength with that reasoning?!
Ichigo!
They're trash compared to me!
That's strange.
Grimmjow, Nnoitora, Ulquiorra,
all of them!
What an odd feeling.
One of their comrades died.
And yet, Inoue looked
more pained by his death.
What an odd feeling.
I don't expect any of you
to know friendship.
And I don't regret defeating
your comrades.
Even so, I don't like
you speaking ill
of the people who I've fought.
Wha-?
Damn!
I'm not sure what's going on,
but it looks like you can't take out
that troublesome mask anymore!
Damn it...
Why can't I take
out my mask?!
Does it have something
to do with that odd feeling?!
Well, no matter.
You did well.
Much better than that scum
lying over there.
Die, scum.
My, my...
How long will it take for
us to reach the place
where those idiots are fighting?
Creating a giant desert below
the ceilings of Las Noches...
Honestly, Aizen sure
does crazy things.
But if this silly battle ends
on my way there,
I won't have to waste my time,
and I can collect specimens.
Taking a leisurely walk may
not be such a bad idea.
Hado 33:
Sokatsui!
What?!
That hurt... What was
that explosion?
Jeez, I can't see
anything below.
Why are you attacking
him before me?
Stay out of this.
What are you talking about?
I arrived here first.
Know your place.
It's not my fault if I slice
you up by mistake.
Byakuya! Kenpachi!
He got up already!
Step aside, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Stop looking dumb.
You get beaten up
wherever you go.
It's pathetic, so move out of
the way, you piece of crap!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What are
you doing, Kenpachi?!
You swung at me for real!
That's dangerous! Are
you trying to kill me?!
That's right. Wimps should die.
Wait, Kenpachi!
Now's not the time
to be doing this.
Kenpachi!
That hurt...
That hurt, you piece of crap.
I won't forgive you.
How dare you cut my leg!
I'll kill you, you damn bug!
Oh good.
So you can punch.
That last one only
gave me an itch.
I thought you were
some giant fly.
If you're going to hit me, do it
with all your might, maggot.
You're an impudent little fly!
How's that?! Can't do
anything, can you?!
You're just a damn bug!
Kenpachi!
I told you to step aside,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Byakuya...
There is nothing for
you to do here.
Hurry to the World of the Living.
I'll go to the World of the Living!
But I've got to defeat him first!
Besides, I can't leave so easily!
Mr. Urahara has to open things
up on the other side.
My, my...
You sure make a fuss
about Urahara.
Mayuri Kurotsuchi!
A Substitute Soul Reaper dares
to address me without respect?
Humph... Well, I suppose it's
better than being addressed
on a first-name basis like
you do to those two.
How generous.
Is it because of that cart?
That's right.
I've just obtained some
rare treasures.
I'm in a very good mood.
Furthermore, I was able to
analyze the structure of the
Garganta at the place where
I obtained these treasures.
Analyzed...the Garganta?
That's right!
Furthermore, it has no flaws!
It lasts nearly indefinitely!
I can just imagine his
look of frustration!
There is no way I can't
be in a good mood!
I can easily overlook the chattering
of a rude monkey!
Make preparations, Nemu!
We're going to send this Substitute Soul
Reaper to the World of the Living!
Yes, sir.
Wait! I still-
Shut up.
You're a test subject,
so don't talk.
This is an experiment!
You have no right to refuse
or decide anything.
Listen well.
You are test subject
number one!
Test subject?
There's no need to worry.
I'll go with you.
Unohana!
I never expected a volunteer.
You're out of your mind,
Squad 4 Captain.
I trust you, Captain Kurotsuchi.
It's all right.
Your experiment will
be successful.
After all, you've come all this
way to Hueco Mundo
and analyzed a Garganta using
data from an Arrancar scientist.
If you fail, Kisuke Urahara
will surely laugh at you.
Think before you talk.
Since I've analyzed
the Garganta,
I can close it while you're
passing through it!
That's impressive.
Isane!
Yes, ma'am!
You stay here and assist
Captain Kuchiki.
Understood.
Now then, Kurosaki. Let's go.
W-Wait, Unohana!
That Yammy is really strong!
I should stay here so the
three of us can fight him!
Don't get cocky,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
A captain of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads
doesn't need help from
the likes of you.
Byakuya...
What is your duty?
Your duty
is to protect that town.
Go. You are Karakura Town's
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Yeah. You're right.
Ichigo!
Rukia...
I'm going.
koe sae ushinattemo
Even if I was stripped of my voice...
boku wa koko de utau darou
I'd be here, singing my song.
koko kara hibike
Echo out from here!
miminari ni kesareta seijaku no yoru
The ringing in my ears stole the night's tranquility.
katachi nai mirai wo oikaketeta
I chased a future that doesn't exist...
sono te wa kuu wo tsukandekita kedo
Yet all I caught was nothing itself.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
deai ga tsumuideku merodi
The melody of the people we meet.
Listen to me! Listen to me...
oto ni kawaru
...as I become sound.
ima wa mada konna ni chiisa na kono koe ga
Though my voice is still small and meager today...
itsuka wa tsuyoku hibiiteiku kara
One day it shall gloriously resound.
Listen to it! Listen to it!
yasashiku yuriokosu merodi
The sweet melody that'll awake
you from your slumber.
Listen to me! Listen to me!
kimi ga omou kimi e
My song will reach the person you want to be.
I thought I went inside
the Garganta.
So where am I?
Chigo!
Huh? Rukia?
I thought you stayed behind
in Hueco Mundo.
My name is not Rukia.
I am Rukiruki.
Let's go, Chigo!
What's a "Chigo"?
What the hell is going on?!
The Seven Wonders
of Karakura Town
of Karakura Town!
I shouldn't have chased down
the Seven Wonders.
But you've got one more left.
I'm sure it has nothing
to do with spirits.
Let's see...
A high school student who flies through
the sky with his incredible leg strength.
- When he sees a girl, he lunges
at her like a wild beast.
- Let me give you a kiss!
- When he sees a girl, he lunges
at her like a wild beast.
He is a symbol of fear for the
girls of Karakura Town.
Noooo!
I'm going to keep
quiet about this.