Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Scars that just refuse to fade
from memory
Sometimes the burden’s too much
for one to bear
Don’t give up on me,
please don’t turn me away
Whoa!
I’ll hold your hand in mine
Will I lose my hold on her someday?
Will her smile fade  In a flood of tears
Or can I keep the fears at bay?
Echoing, distant voices wither into silence.
But there is one thing that
will never ever age…
my love for you is timeless
Pain that won’t heal
Sadness you feel
Smiles with hearts’ bitterness replaced
“I’ll never smile again”
“I’ll never let love in”
Don’t ever say such things to me
A future we cannot see
All happenings
Find meaning in the story
In time the clouds will clear away,
so just stay, please stay with me…
Whoa!
Who are we to pass through you?
That answer will find you someday
Such a narrow sky.
What is that?
The sky is glowing.
It crashed!
It ran into the Soul Shield Membrane
and stopped!
To crash there and not be destroyed…
Could it be a body of spiritual power
of such great concentration…?
If we are separated,
we will be blown apart by the shock!
Wha--!
Grab onto whoever is nearest to you!
Don't let go, no matter what!
Damn it!
What do you mean by that?!
Let me sit on your shoulder.
Yoruichi!
Ishida…!
Chad…?!
Chad!
C-Chad!
Damn it…!
Ichigo!
Inoue!
Damn…! They split up into four!
The strongest one…
Which one is it?!
Hold on to me, Ishida!
Hinagiku! Baigon! Lily!
Santen Kesshun! “I reject!”
What’s your problem?!
Shut up! Stay back!
Turn to sand! Seppa!
Thanks to your weird skill,
we are saved…
How’d the sand get in there?
Your skill did this!
Quit coughing!
Hey…!
You got a lot of nerve,
punching the guy who saved your life!
Who said that?!
I only said we were saved--!
Yahoo! What luck!
We skipped out on the
tiresome guard duty,
but you fall right into our hands!
Lucky, I’m lucky!
Today, I’m lucky!
You, on the other hand, are not.
Huh?
This hole’s huge.
How is this possible…?!
N-No body. That means he’s still alive!
Find him!
Right!
Now… What do I do?
It’s coming!
Get ready!
Wha--? It disappeared…
Damn. Find them!
So now I’m all alone…
But it might be better this way.
Uh-uh. No good Ichigo…
No… Not Poo-san, it’s Pee-tan…!
They sound alike,
but they’re different…
Ms. Inoue…?
No, Ichigo!
Ms. Inoue!
Oh Ichigo!
Ouch.
Ow!
Oh? Ishida…
Are you all right, Ms. Inoue…?
Oh… That’s right…
It appears we were able to land, luckily,
in an unpopulated area.
Huh? How lucky! Owwww!
Oh! Careful!
You were injured in the fall.
I administered first-aid with
the bandages I had,
but I didn’t have any painkillers…
S-So you did. Thank you…
You keep bandages on hand…?
Uh…oh, I’m fine!
I’m sorry.
You were shielding me…
If it weren’t for me,
you would never have gotten hurt.
You think so?
I’m such a klutz,
I would’ve gotten hurt, anyway.
And if you weren’t there
with the first-aid kit,
I would’ve bled, become anemic…
and wouldn’t be able to move.
Does that sound weird?
No… Let’s just get going.
That was a pretty loud landing.
A crowd will be gathering soon.
Right…
Luck, luck, luck, luck, luck, luck…
Lucky!
Luck, luck, luck… Lucky!
Luck, luck, luck, luck...
Lucky-y!
What’re you doing, fools?!
I was doing
my “Lucky Dance” for you
while waiting for you
to come crawling out!
What’re you gaping like idiots at?!
Don't you understand human kindness?!
What's with him?
Hey!
Huh?
What is it?
I’m gonna run first chance I get.
Courtesy is the basis…
You’re gonna run? What're you thinking?!
of the Samurai Code!
Fool! Can’t you see?!
They have way greater spiritual powers…
than ordinary Soul Reapers!
What’s this arguing about?!
Hmph…maybe they’re scared out
of their wits to fight us.
Well, let them take their time
and argue.
But if they take too long,
other guys will come
and steal our glory.
Yeah, that’s true.
Fine! I’ll set a time limit!
So kind!
I’ll do another dance…
Anyhow, I'm gonna run!
so you two can do what you want.
If you wanna fight, be my guest!
Huh?
A disagreement?
Something like that.
Crap. Don’t give us trouble.
Yumichika!
Right!
As I expected, one of them
is after me! Damn!
Yo!
Huh?
Tell me… Why didn’t you run?
The other guy ran because he saw that
our strength was greater than his, right?
I think he made the right decision.
If your strength is greater than mine,
it’s useless to run.
You’d catch me for sure.
But…if my strength is greater…
I’ll just defeat you and be on my way.
That’s all.
I see…I guess you’re not stupid,
after all.
He dodged it!
Moves well!
With the sheath?!
At least…tell me your name.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ichigo…? That’s a good name.
Think so?
No one ever praised it before.
Yeah. Guys with “ichi” in their names
are full of talent and good looks.
I’m 3rd-Seat Assistant Adjutant, Squad 11.
Ikkaku Madarame!
My fellow “ichi,” let’s be friends!
No way!
Dammit! He’s persistent!
Won’t he ever stop?!
Humph… What ugly running.
Up ahead.
Turn into sand! Seppa!
Hmm! What an unusual skill!
That’s how you made
that earlier crater?
But if you’re not careful…
Seppa!
Up ahead, there’s…
W-What’s this?!
This is dangerous!
This is the old execution ground.
We brought captive Hollows and
threw them down here to fight criminals.
We would watch from up there.
Soul Reapers do crude things,
don’t they…?
Not as crude as your face.
Pity you.
“Pretty”? Even you recognize
my dazzling handsomeness, don’t you?
Not “pretty”! I said, “Pity”!
I know that! I made a witty,
humorous joke!
Besides, that “crude” practice
no longer exists.
Only, those who fall in
can never get out.
That should be enough chasing
around and prattle for now.
It’s time. I’ll let you choose.
Will you die…by my sword?
Or will you fall in that hole…and die?
Which will you choose?
Oops…
If you’re angry,
turn and let me see your face.
No matter how it looks…
I love that look of agony when
one must choose how to die.
You’re a crude bastard,
after all, aren’t you…?
I don’t get it.
Hm?
Sure, we got a distance between us,
but only a greenhorn would let
one hand leave his sword during a match!
S-Shut up!
I can’t see with the blood in my eyes!
I only wiped it!
On the forehead,
even a shallow wound bleeds profusely…
Unless you stop the bleeding,
it’s useless to wipe it.
Hey! That’s dirty!
You have a styptic to stop
the bleeding!
It’s not dirty! It’s brains! Brains!
You should admire me for
being experienced!
Yeah?
Hah!
You sure are a strange guy…
You behave like a greenhorn.
And you don’t look much like a fighter.
But…
You have excellent reflexes!
And fierce attack!
You could even say your movements
are coming close to mine!
Don’t look so angry.
I’m praising you.
You’re too good to be dismissed as
a mere greenhorn with natural abilities…
Who was your teacher, Ichigo?
It was only for ten days,
so I don’t know if I can call him “Teacher,”
but there is a man who taught me
how to fight.
Who?
Kisuke…Urahara.
I see…
He was your teacher…
In that case, it would be rude
to kill you without giving my all.
Lengthen! Hozuki-maru!
A spear?!
No time to look surprised, Ichigo!
I’m coming at ya!
Don’t misread this!
Not me!
Heh! A spear’s reach is long.
I know that much! I won’t misread it!
Wrong!
An opening!
Split apart! Hozuki-maru!
Now…look this way.
Show me your expression in
your last moment of life.
Each time I see such things,
my beauty grows even keener.
Get beautiful without my help!
You wretch!
Turn into sand! Seppa!
What are you doing?!
To beautiful me…!
Oh, no! I’m falling, falling!
Falling!
Disgraceful.
Talk about digging your own grave.
I guess some actually do it.
How trifling.
Huh?!
Gotcha.
A strange trick…!
What is that orb?!
Heh… Good thing I brought a spare…
This is a Cannonball developed
by Shiba Kukaku,
the best sis in the world.
Not even a Zanpaku-to
can easily shatter it.
Oh, my. How he underestimates me…
I am 5th Seat of Squad 11,
the strongest Squad.
Don’t think I’m any
ordinary Soul Reaper…!
Bloom! Fuji Kujaku!
I’ll break that spiritual partition
with a single blow!
Oh yeah… I forgot to tell you,
this bomb of my Sis’s…
Once its concentration of spiritual power
is broken, it quickly…
You sneaky…!
Clever strategy, wasn’t it…?
Still…
You are a tough bastard!
Don’t tell me you thought that
was enough to kill me off.
Now I’m really mad! You’ll pay…!
Can’t hear you.
Seppa!
Running again?!
Kiss my butt.
Ugly… Too ugly…!
I warned you not to misread it.
Hozuki-maru isn’t a spear.
It’s a “sansetsukon.”
Does it hurt? That hand probably
can’t hold a sword anymore.
I’m a kind-hearted guy.
Ordinarilly, I would’ve taken you in alive.
Sorry, though.
I get no recognition unless I kill you.
Fine!
What’re you doing?
Let’s go!
Don’t talk as if it’s over.
I still haven’t shown you my skill.
It starts now, Ikkaku.
Fine words. Greenhorn!
I looked up into the night sky
and saw a comet
I want to see you right now,
but I can't fly
If I could become a comet
I would fly across the sky… I'm sure
I would circle the skies and shine over you
With this instantaneous light
that will definitely reach you
If I could become a comet
I'm sure I'll alway stay close to you
Now and forever
You’re pretty good, Ichigo.
But the real battle starts now.
It’s too late to come crying
with apologies!
That’s my line! Fight!
Hit it, Cover it,
Rock Scissors Paper!
Not that kind of battle!