Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
One, two...
The sound resonates
Into my heart, so hard and deep
A field of stars spans endlessly
And through it I carve a passageway
In step with time as generations change
Close your eyes and listen closely
Shooting stars stream on silently…
until the goodbye
Keep the light inside of you,
never give up don't ever lose
Transcend time and you will prove,
there is a special place for you
A blaze of glory is there,
It's all a part of our estate;
life is our story to create
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old by voice of light
Throughout the age, never fade away
A secret fire, a scream of light,
voices calling through twilight
Cast your thoughts to the wind,
hang your wishes on the moon
Live your life with all your strength
for dreams will reach you very soon
Raise your eyes you can see
shooting stars up in the night sky
Wishes speak from ages old
by voice of light
Throughout the age,
never fade away
Someday your dream will find
its place somewhere
Keep shining like a star
Who is that?
Captain of the Squad 3,
Gin Ichimaru.
Oh, this isn't good.
Jidanbo!
Unacceptable.
A guardian of the gate isn't supposed
to open the gates.
We were careless…
I didn't expect that someone like him
would come all this way.
Even if these kids have
become strong,
Captain level’s strength is
beyond imagination.
They cannot fight him…
We must avoid that
worst possible scenario!
Ugh… I lost!
Opening the gate is what is expected
of a gatekeeper who has lost!
What are you saying?
A gatekeeper who lost isn't
opening any gates.
When a gatekeeper loses…
it means…"death."
I-Ichigo!
What the hell are you doing?!
That's my line!
Don't come now and try to butt in,
you fox face!
Anyone who'd attack
an unarmed guy…
will be killed by me!
Hah! You're a funny kid.
You're not scared of me?
Not at all!
Hey!
Stop it Ichigo!
We will retreat for now!
Ichigo…?
Huh?! Why?!
So then…
I'm only just getting started!
He's the one…
No way I can forgive guys like this!
It's okay.
I'll just end it…
So you're Ichigo Kurosaki…
You know about me?
Oh, just as I thought.
Huh?! Hey! Where're you going?!
Hey wait!
All the more reason why
I can't let you pass.
Why're you standing so far back?
Are you going to throw
your short sword?
It's not a short sword.
This is my Zanpaku-to.
Impale him, Shinso!
Kurosaki!
Darn it!
The gate…!
Bye bye!
Ow! Owwee!
Are you all right, Kurosaki?!
Kurosaki!
The gate?!
Dammit!
It seems you're all right.
Sorry…the gate closed because of me…
No, your opponent was Gin Ichimaru.
It couldn't be helped.
Be glad that you weren't hurt.
Inoue…
Huh?
Take care of him.
Okay.
Who are they?
They were hiding until now.
Why?
We were feared.
Souls who come illegitimately
to Soul Society
without the aid of Soul Reapers
are called Ryoka,
and are said to be the cause
of all kinds of calamities.
They think we are enemies?
Stay here!
Please wait.
Huh?
I am the elder of the Rukon District.
I witnessed everything that
happened just now.
We want to welcome you as
Jindanbo's saviors.
There are many rotten Soul Reapers,
but Jidanbo is a native of
the Rukon District.
And he's always kind to us.
You fought Gin Ichimaru for Jidanbo.
That's why you must be
a good person.
But…what a terrible wound.
Okay! Right!
Don't worry. I'll heal Jidanbo's wounds.
Huh? Inoue…you can heal that?
Yes, just leave it to me.
Shuno, Ayame!
Hi! Need help?
Hello.
Please, lend me your power.
Certainly! We are your power!
All you have to do is desire it.
Recite the Kotodama – Spirit Chant!
Soten Kishun!
I reject!
Wow, that's amazing, Inoue.
When'd you get that power?
Excuse me! Please let me through!
Let me through!
Oh! Mister!
It's me! Shibata!
Shibata?
Yes! The parakeet, Shibata!
Mister!
Shibata…!
You put on some weight, huh?
No way!
That's because you only
knew me as a parakeet.
Here, you don't change at all.
You stay the same as when
you first get here.
I see…
Shibata…
Err…
About your mother…
This is my house.
It's kind of run down,
but it's cool during summer and nice.
And my family are all really nice.
Family?
Yuichi, you came back.
Mom and Dad were worried.
Uh-huh…
Mom and Dad?
Umm… This boy is Hironari Horiuchi.
He's like my big brother.
How do you do.
Like your big brother?
In Soul Society, or rather
the Rukon District,
people who aren't related form
family-like units and live together.
People who died in different places,
at different times, live together.
It's rare for one to meet up with
a real family member who died earlier.
Don't the Soul Reapers reunite
you with your family?
No.
By the way, I died in 1947
in Yamanashi Prefecture.
It's way before Shibata died.
Our age, the location, we're far apart.
Then you haven't seen
your mother yet?
No, although I'm looking for her.
Don't worry! You have all of us, Yuichi.
Please don't worry.
We're all like him in the beginning,
but we change with time.
I…I won't see my mom again…
I'm sorry, but can I stay with
Shibata for a bit longer?
Sure. I'll tell the family.
By the way, why are you here, Mister?
You're not dead, are you?
No… I'm not.
Then why?
I wonder that too…
Huh? On that rooftop…
Isn't that your Soul Reaper friend?
Even if he goes that high up,
he won't be able to see beyond the gate.
But he'll still keep looking,
without giving up.
That's the kind of guy Ichigo is.
I guess I was around your age…
when I started worrying about my looking
different than everyone.
And I had this amazing strength I couldn’t
handle that was different from them.
What is this power I got?
I want to know…
I have a feeling that coming here
will give me some clues.
That's why I came…
I thought I'd risk everything
to search for answers.
You're really giving it
your best, huh Mister?
That's why, Yuichi, don’t give up.
Huh?
If you keep searching
without giving up,
you'll find your mother.
Isn't that so?
Mister…
Right, let's make a promise.
Uh-huh!
Chad?
Yo!
What? At least speak up
if you’re here.
I'm always behind you.
Huh?
What?!
Give up breaking through the gate?
Not give up.
Once the gate has been opened,
the security on the inside
becomes even tighter.
Which means the same strategy
is not the best one.
I agree.
What about other gates?
There won't be much difference
with this one.
Then what do we do?!
If we can't use the gate,
we must enter another way.
Elder, do you know
the Kukaku Shiba?
W-What?!
I understand she's someone who
constantly changes residences.
I haven't been able to find out
where she lives now.
Kukaku…Shiba…
You're not planning to go through
the wall with that!
That?!
Huh? What's that noise?
What is it?
What's happening?!
Owwee!
W-What is this guy?
Huh? A boar?! Why?
What's a boar doing here?!
Owee…
Darn…thrown again by my Bonnie.
Hey! Been a long time, Old Man.
Ganju, what are you doing here?!
Go home!
Some greeting! I come to visit after
a long time and I get that?
Your guests are shocked.
Oh…
What?
What's a dirty Soul Reaper
doing here?
What?
Not "what?"!
What's a dirty Soul Reaper
doing here, I asked!
Huh?
Huh?!
Say something, you dandelion head--!
W-What're you doing?!
You picking a fight?!
That's my line!
Trying to goad me like that!
You primeval boar!
"Primeval boar"?!
What'll we do?!
We must stop them.
Are you stupid?
Oh dear... Just as I expected.
I'm not stupid!
I got a name you know!
This is no time to drink tea!
Who is that guy?
You don't know who I am?!
I don't.
Neither do I.
Don't know.
Don't even wanna know.
Hah… Then it can't be helped.
I'll tell you.
My name is Ganju!
Self-professed Crimson Bullet
of West Rukon District!
Self-professed the most
"want-to-call-you-big-brother" candidate
for 14 years running! And…!
Self-professed West Rukongai's
Top Soul Reaper Hater!
All self-professed!
Hah! You're hopeless.
What?
Kurosaki!
Hold it! Won't let you get in
Big Brother's way.
If you really want to get involved
in this fight…
We'll be your opponents.
Henchmen…
Wow…
All of them…
Riding on boars!
Get outta here!
While I'm alive, no Soul Reaper
will be allowed to step foot…
in West Rukongai!
Huh?!
Brother!
Cripes! Cut it out, will ya?!
If you wanna fight, I'll fight you.
Why you--! You punched
my handsome face…
not once, but twice!
I kicked you the second
time around, idiot!
Enough, Ichigo! Don't use up your strength
in a meaningless fight.
He started the fight.
If you want us to stop, tell him.
Sheesh! Getting worked up for
such a silly thing…the fool!
It seems we're destined
to fight, you and me.
Stop, Ganju!
He is not an evil Soul Reaper!
Shut up!
Soul Reapers are Soul Reapers.
There's no good or bad.
Ganju…
Get ready!
This is bad! Kurosaki doesn't have
his Zanpaku-to!
Oh!
Thanks, Chad!
Huge! So that's your Zanpaku-to!
However…
Don't think you can win
with a bigger sword!
Sink!
W-What's this?!
The ground!
It's like quicksand…!
Huh?!
Why you--! Using weird tricks!
Damn, if that didn't drop you,
you're pretty tough.
What's wrong? Come at me!
Hey, what time is it?!
It's bad, Big Brother!
It's nine already!
What?! No!
Come on, Bonnie!
Huh?
Bonnie…?
Continued next week
With much appreciation
send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
I was casually walking through town
Around the time dusk fell
and the city was bathed in red
It was an afternoon with
crowds of people coming and going
I don’t know why but
I just stood there and watched
Then my cell phone started to vibrate
and I made myself move
hoping it could fill
in this hole in my heart
You’re not alone
You see, everybody
We gotta hold each other up
With much appreciation
I send a rhapsody filled
with treasured thoughts
To the people who have
always held me up.
Thank you for everything
Thank you so much
Wherever I may be
I’ll always be grateful for who you are.
The next Bleach:
"Orihime Inoue's Architectural Visits,"
will be coming from Kukaku Shiba's
house in West Rukon District.
It's a gorgeous wooden structure
surrounded by open land.
What's the secret to this building?
Just watch and see.
These natural wood pillars... Huh?