Rurichiyo, princess of
the Kasumiohji Clan,
a high-ranking noble family
of the Soul Society,
was supposed to have returned
to her mansion as head of the clan
once the internal strife
had been resolved.
However, Rurichiyo appeared once
again in the World of the Living.
Rurichiyo, who wanted to
hold a kemari tournament
in order to cheer up
her subjects,
had a difference of opinion
with Kenryu,
who believed that mending relations
with other noble families
and the people in power
was more important,
and Rurichiyo ran away
from home.
Kenryu, however,
felt responsible
for being unable to
persuade Rurichiyo
and decided to commit suicide.
When she became aware of this,
Rurichiyo realized how
important Kenryu was to her,
and stopped him from
committing suicide.
You moron!
L-Lady Rurichiyo…
You really are a moron!
Do you really think doing that
is going to make me happy?!
Protecting my retainers
is my responsibility.
I cannot let you die!
Is that understood?
Then, Lady Rurichiyo…
They sure are a handful.
You're telling me.
My, my… I guess I will have to
give in just this once.
I am so happy that you understand.
I won't have to lose my life for
something as silly as kemari.
As silly as kemari?
What do you mean by
"as silly as"?
Are you finding fault
in my idea?!
No…I…you know…
a mere pastime like kemari is…
A mere pastime?!
Umm…no, I mean…
At any rate, kemari is out!
You don't understand because
you have never done it!
I have, that's why I'm saying this!
I can do something like that
better than you, Lady Rurichiyo!
If you are going to talk like that,
let us have a kemari competition!
We shall settle it with this!
Let us say the loser
never says anything again!
I wouldn't have it any other way!
How do things get this way?!
So we're participating
in this thing too?
Don't complain, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Consider it an honor to
be able to participate
in a noble family's
kemari competition.
You've got nerve saying that
when you forced us into it.
But what's with these teams?!
Sorry, Ichigo.
I couldn't refuse on account of
our relationship as nobility.
I was your enemy from the start.
I'll always be together with Rukia!
That's how it goes.
Good grief…
This team looks like
we're short a member.
What'll we do?
I'm glad you noticed, Ishida.
One of us, whose duty is
to admonish Lady Rurichiyo,
has betrayed us.
Unlike Kenryu,
Enryu is always on my side!
The truth is,
I want to be on the same team
as Lady Rurichiyo too.
That Enryu…
Well, anyway…
I suspected this might happen,
so I've readied a powerful helper!
Yoruichi!
You're as good as home.
Leave it to me!
I asked Urahara Shop to help me
find the best helper!
The Kasumiohji Clan
is a major customer,
so I have to treat them
accordingly.
That's how it is,
so thanks for your help, Yoruichi!
Mr. Urahara!
Why are you here too?!
Didn't I tell you?
Our store is the top sponsor
of this competition!
URAHARA SHOP PRESENTS
ULTIMATE SUPER
KEMARI CHAMPIONSHIP
IN KARAKURA TOWN
We have arranged for
the referees, as well.
How do you do?
I'm going to watch you
very closely, so be ready for it!
You can't be serious.
We will now explain the rules.
Miss Kuchiki.
Yes.
Kemari is a peaceful ancient sport
of Japan played using a ball.
Players kick the ball
in the air to a set height
without letting it
fall to the ground
PEACE
by passing it.
Those are horrible drawings,
as usual.
KAKARI
All you do is keep kicking the ball
within the open space
marked by trees called kakari
at each of the four corners.
The rules are extremely simple.
In essence, it's a game where
keeping the ball up
and assisting each other
are important.
But then there'd be no end.
And that's why…
For this competition, we're using
a special Kasumiohji Clan rule!
Ahem!
It's nothing all that difficult.
The side that drops a pass loses.
The referees will
make the decision.
Do you understand, Lady Rurichiyo?
Of course!
If you win, Kenryu,
I will obediently return
to the Soul Society
and do what you say.
If I win, we will hold
a kemari tournament.
Is that okay with you?!
That's fine.
Though there is
no doubt I will win.
Will it really go as you think?
For this competition,
we've marked the entirety of
Karakura Town with kakari.
For the duration of
the 90-minute time limit,
we've set the conditions
to be identical to
an Area Freeze and
Konpaku Protection,
so please do not
go outside the kakari.
What do you mean by "time limit"?
If we keep it frozen for too long,
the Soul Society will reprimand us.
Is it okay to do that?
Men shouldn't worry about details!
She's right.
It's much easier to put all
your effort into it if there's
a time limit rather than letting it
drag on without a resolution!
No doubt.
Umm…
If everyone's ready, we'll begin.
Kickoff.
You put too much strength into it!
Oh yeah!
Lady Rurichiyo!
What do you think of that?!
That's nothing!
Whoa!
Both team captains are going at
each other from the very start!
All right!
Let's do it, Ichigo!
Got it! You can count on me!
No, you don't!
Missed.
That's dangerous!
I forgot to mention that it's okay
for those without the ball
to obstruct the opposite team.
Say that at the start!
What are you doing, Ichigo?!
Damn!
Uh-oh!
The ball's about to go
outside the kakari!
This is where I come in!
Everyone might have forgotten,
but I am a Mod Soul,
a reinforced leg strength model!
Kon Kick!
How's that?!
I said no going out-of-bounds!
Kon went out-of-bounds
and was blown away
by referee Jinta's attack!
There'll be trouble if
the Soul Society finds out
that the barrier is being
used as a kakari.
To keep it a secret, they must
not go outside the barrier.
That's right!
It's that idiot's fault for going
out-of-bounds on his own!
There'll be trouble
if they find out?
Why the hell are we
taking so many risks here?
Got it! Kuchiki,
I'm passing it to you!
I am not going to let you!
Come on, Enryu!
What the—?!
A nice play by Enryu!
Daichimaru is
a defense-type Zanpakuto
that can "flip the mats"
around in any location.
Even if there are no mats,
it can block an opponent's attack
by hardening the surface
and standing it up.
What do you think of that?!
Why're you shouting
all of a sudden?
Because Enryu is embarrassed
to have others hear his voice.
What good is it going to do
to scare your teammates?!
Kurosaki! The ball!
Chad! Pass it here!
Go easy!
Ichigo! Go after it
using Flash Step!
Guess I'll have to!
Yoruichi!
I won't lose to you
in a contest of speed!
We'll see!
I'm limited in this form.
Okay! Made it with time to spare.
You underestimate me if
you think you can overtake me
with such a slow
Flash Step, Ichigo!
Put your clothes on!
Looks like Yoruichi transformed!
No…problem.
It's his fault for
getting caught off-guard!
Lady Yoruichi!
Pass the ball here!
Oh fine.
Take care of the ball
while I put my clothes on!
What're you doing?!
Sorry… I think I used
too much strength.
Sotenkishun!
Good job, Orihime!
Did you see, Kenryu?!
Our teamwork!
That's nothing!
The real contest starts now!
The way it's going,
I won't ever finish.
Ruricchi and Kenryu both went
to the World of the Living
and haven't come back.
I wanted to go to
the World of the Living too.
Lord Shu!
I brought more documents!
There's still more?
Well, about that…
What?!
Ichigo!
I know!
Wait, Kurosaki!
Santenkesshun!
Inoue!
Kurosaki, now!
Thank you, Inoue!
No, you don't!
Come on, Kon!
Dance, Sodenoshirayuki.
What're you going to do, Sis?
Sorry.
Grit your teeth!
What?
Tsuginomai…
Hakuren.
You!
That was brilliant, Miss Kuchiki!
My nose is bleeding.
You must not go outside the kakari!
Bakudo Number 99 Part 2: Bankin!
My body!
After all,
we are doing this
without telling
the Soul Society, so…
And I keep asking why you all
are eager to do something illegal!
What's this about
keeping something secret
from the Soul Society?
Yo!
What's all this
commotion about, Ichigo?
Ikkaku!
Umm…well…it's…umm…
There have been some
strong adversaries lately,
so I'm retraining Ichigo.
Special training… Is that it?
Yeah… You came at the right time!
Someone got injured a while back.
Will you lend us a hand?
I don't know what's going on,
but it seems interesting.
Substitution!
Madarame taking the place of Kon!
Hey, wait! We won't agree to that!
Umm…
We will allow the substitution.
What?!
I see you liked the candy
made by the candymaker
from the Kasumiohji Clan.
You are a sneaky one, Kenryu.
Not at all.
I'm no match for you, Mr. Urahara.
It's been a while
since I've taken you on!
On guard, Ichigo!
Is this for real?!
Wait a…
Don't hold back, you!
Why you…
Fine!
Now the real fight starts!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
What does Kurosaki
think he's doing,
not bothering to
kick the ball?
Beats me.
Hang in there, Kurosaki!
Looks like everyone's forgotten
the original intent.
That's a big problem.
Does it really matter?
You really are persistent,
aren't you!
Back at you!
Let's put an end to
this contest already!
I'm telling you that if you
admit you've lost, it'll be over!
Restoring the clan as soon as
possible is what's important.
I've told you repeatedly that
providing recreational activities
can still be done after that.
Why won't you understand?!
Not yet!
Lady Rurichiyo…
Why are you so determined to…
That's obvious!
Because I want to see
smiles on everyone's faces!
Ever since I returned
to the mansion,
everyone has been giving up sleep
to work hard on restoring the clan.
But there are still many things
that are too difficult for me,
so in the end, I am putting
a burden on you and the others.
That's…
I know!
It cannot be helped because
I am still a child!
Still…
I thought very hard, wondering if
there was something I could do!
Some way that I could
make my subjects,
the staff at the mansion,
and you smile.
I thought my very hardest!
Lady Rurichiyo…
A Hollow?!
Did we exert a bit too much
Spiritual Pressure?!
This isn't good!
Run!
Lady Rurichiyo!
Shake, Daichimaru!
Please get away!
No! I'm not leaving
you behind, Kenryu!
– What?
– Huh?!
Getsugatensho!
Lady Rurichiyo, are you hurt?
No, I am all right.
By the way,
what about the kemari ball?
When the Hollow attacked,
it went somewhere.
Which means it fell on my turn.
So this contest is…
Is this…the Senkaimon?!
Oh, here you are!
Shu?!
Why did you come to
the World of the Living, as well?
I wanted to show this
to you Ruricchi.
These are letters from
your subjects.
Remember you once mentioned you
would hold a kemari tournament?
No details were released
for the longest time,
so we received many
letters from everyone.
See, look!
Isn't that great, Ruricchi?
Your idea wasn't a bad one,
after all!
Everyone is looking forward
to the kemari tournament!
I see.
But…the kemari tournament…
Lady Rurichiyo…
There could be no more
definitive outcome to the contest.
It is clear for anyone
to see that I lost.
We will cooperate with all our
effort to put on the tournament!
Kenryu! Enryu!
That's how it is!
I have preparations for the kemari
tournament that I must attend to,
so I must return immediately.
Sorry for causing a commotion.
Ichigo Kurosaki,
we've put you through a lot.
Farewell!
H-Hey!
So in the end, what was all this?!
Starting in the next episode,
we're going back in time 110 years.
I'm embarrassed to say this,
but it'll feature me
when I was very young.
Huh?! Then what about my scenes?
Don't worry.
They booked you a regular spot
in the Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers segment.
So that's how it's gonna be?
Illustrated Guide to Soul Reapers!
What're you guys doing?
Ikkaku!
GINTONBO
Ichigo can't read
the name of the store.
This character, eh?
It's "Gingokiburi"!
There's no way he'd use the word
for "cockroach" in the store name!
And don't you go making
an "oh, I see" face too!
Then, "Ginnamekuji"!
That's what I said earlier!
That doesn't make it right!
Ginooyama mayuga!
Ginmizumushi!
Get out of here already,
you guys!