Ichigo rescues Orihime after
a deadly battle with Grimmjow,
only to come up against Nnoitora.
Though his injuries are left untreated,
Ichigo begins battle again,
but he is overwhelmed by
Nnoitora’s immense strength.
And Orihime is taken
captive once again.
Furthermore, Nel, who had
been hiding, is discovered
as Ichigo and the others stand
at the edge of defeat.
However, Nel suddenly
undergoes a change.
Ichigo!
Nel?
So you’ve returned to
that form, Nelliel?
Nel?
Are you really Nel?
Yes.
Thanks to you, Ichigo,
I was able to return to this form.
I want to thank you.
It’s all right.
It’ll be over in an instant.
Damn!
I don’t look like that!
Roar!
– Zabimaru!
Too soft!
Even if our techniques
are the same,
a fake is still a fake!
You’re not a challenge!
Go!
Damn it! There’s no end to this!
I agree.
Well? This is the limit of
one-to-one clone technology.
However, every time
these clones are defeated,
they’ll split apart and multiply.
You think you can win?
Look out, Renji!
You idiot! I’m the real thing!
Oh, that was a close call, wasn’t it?
You need to ask?!
If you’re not sure, don’t attack!
Watch out, Dondochakka!
You look so much like Renji!
Why you… I just know that
was on purpose.
When did I multiply?
You fool!
What’re you guys doing?!
I discovered the difference
between myself
and the clones and I
came here to tell you! Listen!
First, the clones of Renji
and myself…
Other than the base of the eyes,
there’s only a slight difference in our hair.
And it’s hard to distinguish!
We’ll put them off until later!
Next, Dondochakka’s clone.
His clones lack the spots
on their backs.
This is very easy to discern.
They are not spots.
Call them polka dots.
Finally, Pesche’s clones.
I think you’ve all noticed.
As you can see…
The fakes all wear pants!
– What?!
Hey, you’re right!
He’s right!
The difference is so great,
I didn’t notice.
You didn’t notice?
Just what have you been
looking at all this time?
Still… This is a big mistake.
Maybe he’s really stupid.
And who was it that didn’t
notice this big mistake?
I’m not stupid.
You were eavesdropping?!
The loincloth and spots just
didn’t appeal to my refined taste,
so I deleted them.
They’re clones!
You’re stupid to change them
to your own taste!
They’re not spots!
They’re polka dots!
Eat this!
Too slow!
– Roar, Zabimaru!
Is this the end of Renji?
Ishida!
It’s a losing battle to fight
this many!
Let’s get outta here!
How?! We tried and failed earlier!
Well… I’ve got an idea!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Idiot! If you use something
like that here…
Bankai!
– Bankai!
Just as I thought.
They’re copies of me.
I had a feeling all they could
do is copy me.
So I tested them with my Bankai,
and they copied me after all.
Hey! Still alive?
What do you think of
my brainy idea now?!
That was brainy?!
I’m telling you…
You and Kurosaki are
so much alike!
Don’t start!
If you bring Ichigo’s name up,
I won’t feel like
you’re complimenting me!
Because I’m not!
It’s an insult!
Now then…
How many are left?
Dondochakka and Pesche
should be okay.
They’re pretty hardy.
The problem is Szayelaporro.
Watch out.
Knowing him, he’ll come at us
from right under our feet!
My, my…
Look what you did to my palace.
How will I explain this to Lord Aizen?
I’m very displeased.
The clones!
Let’s stop this.
I was very bored with this fight.
It’s time I personally stepped in.
I shall show you…
the true strength of my La Lujuriosa.
Whoa! Stop, Dondochakka!
Get your butt off me!
I-I sensed it!
Sensed what?
That we’ve been acting stupid
all this time!
It’s amazing.
A new ground level is
opening up!
All right!
Don’t get excited.
Get your butt off of me!
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
Oh, I beg your pardon.
It seems you didn’t hear me.
Even if it’s a fake,
it doesn’t feel good to
watch yourself explode.
Now then…
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I shall show you…
La Lujuriosa and its true power!
Thank you for your thoughtfulness.
But we have no interest
in something like that.
I’m gonna interrupt
your performance.
Damn right!
I’m the one who’s sorry.
You have no choice.
You’re being forced to
appreciate this show.
Ishida!
Crap!
Delicious.
What?!
Ishida!
Ishida! Hey Ishida! Snap out of it!
Are you all right? Hey!
Are you?
I’m okay.
Don’t yell into my ear.
Hello…
I’m over here.
An Ishida doll?!
What’s the big idea?
What? I just answered you.
Because you were calling.
Thank you, Ishida.
Your role as “Ishida” is now over.
From now on, he is “Ishida.”
What?
You did, didn’t you?
Feel that touch.
Maybe I didn’t explain
well enough.
To put it simply…
This is the controller that
administers your five senses.
In other words…
Ishida!
You see?
Furthermore…
What are you doing?!
Stop…
Stop!
Damn it!
Fool! Why are you panicking?
This doll is simply made this way.
Did you think that if
I broke it apart,
the same would happen
to the real person?
No matter.
Can you see?
All these body parts…
So what of it?
Nice and colorful, aren’t they?
Like a child’s toy.
This is the fun part of this doll.
Well, it would be faster to
just show it to fools like you.
“Stomach”?
Ishida!
Why you…
Don’t make a fuss.
Just because I crushed
this petty thing.
My, my… Just because
I teased you a bit.
I just threatened you a bit
and you couldn’t see what
was in front of you.
You’re all the same.
Just like kids…
Humans and Soul Reapers.
And Quincies too. All of you.
You’re all so vulgar.
Abarai!
If there’s a reason why Lord Aizen
should destroy you…
It is because…
of your vulgarity.
I thought it was gonna
be over quick.
Huh, Nelliel?
How many years have passed
since you disappeared from here?
Don’t think that the Espada’s ranking
is the same as back
when you were here, Nelliel!
Nel…
You make me sick!
Why did you stop your sword?
You did too.
Idiot!
I stopped because I saw you
stop your sword!
You’re so irritating.
I remember the old days
when I'm fighting you.
You haven’t changed at all.
Not a bit since back then.
So what do you think of
the Ishida doll?
This attack means nothing!
I know all your weaknesses.
Next, I shall tear
this cape apart!
What?! Damn, how dirty of you!
Wait… There’s no need to
bother with that part, is there?
Arrancar Encyclopedia!
ARRANCAR ENCYCLOPEDIA
Today we’ll talk about
Szayelaporro’s sword release,
La Lujuriosa.
It has pretty sick abilities,
like creating enemy clones from
the fluid in his back,
or engulfing the enemy
with his wings
to create a doll that can control
the enemy's five senses.
Shall I create a doll of you
as well?
No thanks, but…
you’re being way
too prominent there.
I’ll also become a regular
in this show.
I think I’ll pass.