Don't rush and take it slowly, huh.
But being told that gets me even more fired up.
I hope you're not feeling that way just because Azuki said that.
Isn't that fine?
Even Miyoshi was...
Cheer up! On to the next one!
...like that.
She doesn't get that the more pressure I'm under, the less I want to work.
She's not wrong. You're already feeling better and thinking about the next one, right?
Our next one, huh.
The next work after a serialization is both important and difficult.
Yeah.
I'm kinda jealous of KOOGY, since he's still being serialized in Jack SQ.
And we can't even touch Eiji.
But we can't lose.
Let's do our best to surpass him this time.
Yeah!
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Gag and Serious
Start out with a one-shot?
Yeah.
We'll try things out with a one-shot, and if it's popular, a serialization will follow.
Awfully cautious of you.
Is it because Azuki told you to take it slow?
That's not it.
If we have two serializations fail, that's it for us.
So we'll tread carefully.
Just to be certain, huh?
It would be ideal if our one-shot came in second
like Takahama's Business Boy Kenichi  so that we could start a serialization storyboard from there.
First, we need to put out a smart one-shot.
We don't have school, so let's sleep on it.
For college, I'm thinking of Yana College's business school.
Business school? That doesn't mean anything to us.
I wouldn't even pass the entrance exam.
It's only two subjects, English and Japanese, and I could help you, so there wouldn't be a problem.
I see.
Have you told Miyoshi about this?
Oh, sure, I'll go.
Tutor me!
O-Okay, starting tomorrow.
Miura, don't you have any storyboards for the next serialization meeting?
No, sorry.
Takahama's can't make the February meeting...
Takahama and Ashirogi Muto... you've got two golden eggs there.
You'd better shape up.
Golden eggs, huh?
Certainly, anyone can see that they're a cut above the rest of the newbies.
I have to get them serialized soon...
I think we should take the safe route by trying things out with a one-shot first.
Huh? What's with that, Mashiro?
That's not like you.
It's obvious that you need to get serialized as soon as possible.
The editorial department and your fans are all expecting great things from Ashirogi Muto.
If you're gonna do it, aim for serialization!
Even if you make a one-shot and it's popular,
that's entirely different from having a completed serialization storyboard.
Even if I tell the editorial department that you should make a one-shot to test an idea,
you should still be drawing with serialization in mind.
Leave the decision to us, and just draw a serialization storyboard.
Okay!
Shujin?
But right now we have no idea what to draw...
Oh, right.
I think your next work should be...
a gag manga.
Gag?!
There's no way...
Yeah!
Why?
When you put more jokes into the last two chapters of TRAP,
Survey Rankings    Detective TRAP
they both came in 13th place.
That's true, but it only rose from 17th to 13th.
Getting to 13th from down there is a pretty big deal.
The turns of phrase were really good, too.
Takagi has a pretty good feel for jokes.
I do?
Yeah! Your humor can be your weapon!
You've got to make use of it.
No. That's not where Shujin's talent lies.
Jokes, huh?
Right now, Jack's popular manga are mostly serious and battle manga.
It's best to assume that if you try beating them at their own game, you'll lose.
I see.
That's definitely...
No.
It's not a bad thing to try!
We're not seeing eye-to-eye anymore!
Miura's no good.
He isn't?
Why not?
We should definitely make a one-shot that could potentially get serialized instead of a serialization storyboard!
Aren't they basically the same thing?
Hattori!
You sure are working hard, even though your serialization just ended.
If you were in our position, would you go straight for a serialization storyboard...
or do a one-shot with serialization in mind?
Hey, Saiko!
It's a tough question,
but your editor is Miura.
I shouldn't be giving my opinion while he isn't around.
All I can say is that it's okay to disagree with your editor.
That's it.
See you.
Thank you.
Miura just likes humor.
We can't just do what he says.
But Miura is really helping us out.
Yes, he is!
He's working as hard as if it were for himself!
But it won't work out if we're going in the wrong direction!
Keep your voice down!
Shujin.
Are you planning on doing what he asks?
Well, when he mentioned gags, I felt like he was wrong...
But then I got carried away with it...
Right?
Well, this isn't the time to act cool.
Oh, Takagi. Goo' efeningh.
Niizuma!
I'm asking this as your rival!
Do you want to read a gag manga written by Ashirogi Muto?
I'll rea' anyfing writt'n by Afirogi Muto, but...
But?
More than humor, what really draws out your appeal is a harsh story.
I want to read a harsh story written by Ashirogi Muto.
Thank you.
He said a "harsh" story.
"Harsh"?
What does that even mean?
Money and Intelligence.
I've received it.
That, huh?
It was harsh and it did  rank higher than Eiji's, even if it was only in the early results.
Hattori said that kind of story suits us, too.
This isn't good. It feels like Miura's wrong.
That's why I'm saying we should dispute this.
We've got no choice but to fight Miura with what we feel is right.
Nakai
This is Nakai.
Hello.
Are you thinking about your next work?
No.
I don't think I'm writing for Jack anymore...
What do you mean, you're not writing for Jack?
I think I will draw my own shoujo manga.
That's...
Won't you work with me again?
Your art is wonderful, and I think you have a lot of talent.
You should illustrate a story that will make better use of your art.
I want to work on your manuscript.
It doesn't have to be me... in fact, I think it would be better that way.
Why are you so fixated on me?
Th-That's...
Because I love you!
I respect you...
as a creator of great art, and as a manga artist.
But I'm sorry.
As a man...
This is Yamahisa from Weekly Shounen Jack.
Yes?
Haven't you heard from Aida yet?
I'm your new editor.
I was thinking about arranging a meeting soon...
Well, I think I'm finished with Jack...
What are you saying? That's such a waste!
I read your one-shot for Magnolia.
Let's do one like that for Jack.
I was touched by the way your art portrayed the feelings of those in love.
It'll definitely sell!
A love story in Jack?
Yes!
As long as you have at least three panty shots a week, it'll be fine.
Definitely! It'll definitely be popular!
There are always some manga in Jack that are a bit raunchy.
It's always an essential and in-demand genre.
Please believe me!
Let's do it!
Aida, did you not tell Aoki about the editor switch?
Didn't we decide yesterday?
We're waiting to tell her while I look into it.
Well, I already told her.
She's going to stay with Jack!
It's great!
I wanna read it!
Well, new editors should be a bit reckless.
Compared to that...
Miura! Were you paying attention to that?
If you keep lolly gagging, you'll be overtaken soon!
Hurry up and submit Ashirogi Muto's contract!
Even I'm  starting to feel pressure from the higher-ups about it!
Oh, sorry.
I just forgot...
"Just forgot"?
Come on!
I-I'll get them to sign it soon!
Why do Japanese people have to study English?
Shut up!
Stop whining like a little brat and get to it!
Scary! You've been in a crazy bad mood lately!
It's Miura!
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
Sorry to do this while you're trying to study.
It's fine.
So, lets take care of the contract.
Um, before that...
I don't think a gag manga would suit us.
I told you, the rankings don't lie. It does suit you.
I want to go with a serious feel.
With humor where it feels appropriate.
Huh? Have you drawn something serious already?
No, not yet.
Then just do as I tell you!
I'm the editor!
I'm not pulling this out of my ass!
Gag
In cases where an author starts a new work after their serialization has ended,
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
even if their previous work was a big hit, they need to change their literary style.
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
Feudal era
Futuristic
School life
Sports
Serious
Gag
We will  change our style.
But I don't believe humor highlights Takagi's strengths.
Are you saying I'm wrong?!
Yes!
If the authors don't trust the editor, they can't work well together!
I think so too!
Two... We'll create two works!
A humorous one and a serious one!
It's unheard of to submit two serialization storyboards at the same time!
I can only submit one!
So if we finish two, we have to get someone else to look at them?
Do you really have so little trust in my eye for manga?
Submitting two works and asking them which they think is better...
There's no way I could do something so pitiful!
Hey, hey. If you're going to shout, do it in the lobby.
I-I apologize.
This wouldn't be happening if Hattori was our editor...
Fine.
Give me two serialization storyboards within the first ten days of March.
Each of them three chapters long.
In other words, six chapters.
I won't pass out half-assed storyboards at the meeting.
Understood?
Yes.
It feels like we just made things worse.
But we should keep doing what we want to do.
Even if it means fighting Miura.
Well, we're already halfway there.
I see!
If it's okay to fight with him...
Huh? What is it?
We still have a hand to play.
What?
You're quitting studying?!
There's only one week till the entrance exam!
Right now, this is more important.
Don't bother us!
But Shujin, you really are amazing.
How did you come up with this idea?
They mysteriously pop into my head when I'm under pressure!
It's like a switch was turned on!
It came from doing TRAP.
The knack for writing storyboards just suddenly came to me!
"Two of Me".  This is pretty cool.
Show it to me!
Whaaa?!
A
Me?
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
Who are you?
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
Who
are you?
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
No, who are you ?
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
A
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
Who
are you?
Face and pose
are the same
Who
are you?
...are you
me?
A
Are you me?
Did I split
into two?
Did I split into two?
A
We should make use
of this situation
effectively!
We should make use of this situation effectively!
A
But what good is
if our thoughts
and actions are
exactly the same?
Ok, when this pencil falls,
whoever it's pointing
towards has to leave.
No way!
You!
I've
got
it!!
No, wait,
i should take
advantage of this.
You!
We have to
decide this some
other way.
Of course
we're gonna
say the same
thing in a fight.
Wait,
wait.
You're
me.
Once we're apart, we'll have
to make sure not to get hurt
or sunburned or anything.
If we're not exactly alike,
what's the use in there being
two of us?
...We can figure
that out once we
decide who's going
to go we'll probably
just say the same
thing, so it'll be easy
to decide.
But
where
will we
go and
where will
we live?
But which
of us should
move out...?
That's not
a bad idea
we'll live
apart for a while
and then
meet up again...
Isn't this kinda sci-fi ish?
It's like you, and it's interesting!
Yeah, I want to read the rest of it.
Will this be our gag submission?
No, I think this one should be serious.
Huh?
And I've already got the gag one all planned out.
Wow! What kind of story is it?
I call it Hitman 10.
A multi-millionaire searches out the world's top ten hitmen
and offers them a huge reward to kill each other.
If even one of them takes up the offer, the others don't know when they might be killed,
so all of them have to participate.
The main character is a young hitman who's caught up in all of this.
Jumbled together with professional killers,
it becomes a battle to be number one!
Isn't that pretty serious?
No, since the premise is pretty out there, it'll be easy to put gags in.
You really do have talent.
I'm falling for you even more!
But my talent will get overshadowed in the world of the pros.
It's a tough market.
So cool~.
Ashirogi Muto
_.Yana College Entrance
Examination Hall
I couldn't sleep last night.
_.Yana College Entrance
Examination Hall
It's pointless trying to cram overnight for a test.
No, I was writing the storyboard.
Hey, now.
We all passed!
Oh, okay.
A college that'll accept you even if you sleep during the exam...
Be a little happier, will you?
You're bringing me down.
Um, Miss Miyoshi?
"Miss"?
Could you do the inking and tone for me?
Inking on the day we passed... that'll cost you.
Then I'll pay you 2,000 yen per hour.
I'm just joking. I wouldn't take money from you guys.
Miyoshi...
Thanks.
I don't need thanks.
Huh? Inking and tone... aren't you
submitting a storyboard this time?
Why are you preparing a manuscript?
The things people can do if they put their minds to it...
At any rate, we did what we could.
I'll call Miura.
'Kay.
In Hitman 10... the jokes were too repetitive and ruined the elaborate setting.
Two of Me
Ashirogi Muto
What really shows Shujin's talent, after all...
Wonderful.
Both of them are great.
If we fix them up a bit, I can confidently present either one to the serialization committee.
Either one?
No matter how you look at it, Two of Me  is...
Which one? Which one will Miura choose?
Ashirogi Muto
Let's aim to serialize Hitman 10 !
All right! This will definitely pass at the meeting. Let's polish it up.
It's no good. He's definitely wrong.
Takagi definitely has a sense for humor!
It won't get through to him no matter what I say.
Ashirogi?
Why did you submit something to the monthly contest?
The monthly contest?!
I see!
If it's okay to fight with him...
Huh? What is it?
We still have a hand to play.
The monthly contest?
That's a contest for amateurs!
Yeah. If we submit it here,
it'll get looked at by people like the
vice-editor in addition to normal editors.
Treasure Rookie-
This is J-Treasure's charm!
Examiner for February contest
Niizuma Eiji
And Eiji is a judge, too!
I trust his judgment more than Miura's, frankly.
But wouldn't it be bad for us to go over Miura's head?
Like I said, if we're gonna fight him, we might as well go all out!
Of course, we'll also make two serialization storyboards.
W-We're making three works?!
Too hard for you?
It's strange.
The more impossible it sounds, the more fired up I get.
Let's do this.
Three great works!
Let's make them so good, they won't be able to decide which one to serialize!
Yeah!
I didn't hear about this!
What were you thinking by going over my head?!
We want to try things out with a one-shot!
Use your common sense!
It's not fair to the other applicants if authors that
have already been serialized enter the monthly competition!
We don't need the prize!
We just want it to be judged!
By Niizuma Eiji!
You're saying that Niizuma has a better eye for manga than me?!
Hey, sit down.
Niizuma's drawing CROW, and you're not drawing anything!
Mashiro, that's going too far.
Hattori.
Why me?
It's a problem between Miura and Ashirogi.
Miura's still a newbie, and Ashirogi even more so.
What will you do?
If they insist on it being judged, I can consult with the Chief.
Before that, we should address
the problem with the authors' attitudes!
Let's start from there!
Miura!
Calm down.
Takagi, Mashiro, think about Miura's position.
You're not that naive.
B-But...
Do authors really have to do what the editor tells them?
That's right.
If they have an objection, they need to tell the editor up front.
All manuscripts must pass through the editor.
All right.
I'll take what you submitted to the monthly contest and get it judged, then aim to get this serialized for you.
What are you saying, Miura?
Tokyo Metropolitan area,
Chiyoda ward, Hitotsubashi 0-x
Yueisha Weekly Shounen Jack
February Jack Treasure
And if this one-shot ends up in the magazine and goes on to become serialized...
I'll quit editing!
Miura...
That's spiteful.
There's no problem in saying you'll reflect on your actions,
but saying you'll quit is just breeding resentment.
You're right. I apologize.
But it's all right.
I really think Hitman 10  is good.
I'll definitely get this serialized.
Okay. Then I'll take this up.
Um, sorry for acting on our own.
Really.
It'll be a problem if the serialization storyboard isn't good after all that.
First off, Ashirogi. "Do not cause any more problems", he says.
Yes.
Well then, in regards to this manuscript...
It can be submitted for judging, but cannot win the prize.
If it is exceedingly well received, it will be published in the magazine.
Okay!
Please do so!
However...
If the storyboard submitted to April's serialization committee is no good,
Serialization Storyboard
we won't give priority to this one-shot and won't publish it.
One-shot
If you submit a sound storyboard, we'll compare it with the one-shot and decide which is more suitable for serialization.
Serialization Storyboard
One-shot
Basically, nothing will happen with your one-shot until after the meeting.
The priority... is to give your all on the serialization storyboard!
Yes!
I see. I'm fine with that.
Let's get Hitman 10  ready to submit to the committee!
Yes!
First off, lets make this gold-rich multi-millionaire's character more exaggerated to make him funnier.
I thought that too, but...
In just a month and a half, they finished two storyboards and a one-shot manuscript...
They haven't changed.
Those two may just be fine as they are.
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
Future Watch  or Hitman 10...
Which will be more popular?
If you worry too much, your jokes will become old geezer jokes.
I know, right?
We're still young.
You old fart.
Next time on Bakuman:
Manga and
Youth
Manga and Youth.
A young man's dreams are hard to achieve!