I'm sorry.
I'm still inexperienced as an editor...
Well, we're even more inexperienced as manga artists...
And yesterday, I just...
So please guide us with more confidence.
I see!
Thank you!
Let's move forward together!
So...
We have conditions for doing a gag manga.
Two of them.
Y-You guys have too many conditions...
First off:
If we're doing a gag manga, it won't be TEN.
We're going to try out a new one-shot.
Also, it's going to be aimed more towards kids.
Another one-shot?
Even though you just did two of them in a row?
Is it asking too much?
TEN 's ranking wasn't very good,
so this time, we want to try for better jokes.
Right...
I've learned from all this that it's important to try out a one-shot first.
There's a way.
You can do a one-shot!
In NEXT!
NEXT?
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Alliance and Classmates
Jack NEXT!, published tri-annually.
It's become something that newbies publish one-shots in.
Yes.
We debuted in that.
But it's not like there's no place for experienced authors to try out a one-shot.
They're looking for someone to do the featured one-shot on the upcoming issue.
The featured one-shot gets a color page, and if it gets first place, it'll definitely lead to a serialization.
Please let us do that!
We'll try our best to get first place!
Okay! So what kind of gag manga will you be trying out for this summer's NEXT?
We don't know yet...
We only just decided to try out a gag manga.
But I'd like to make a gag manga that appeals to everyone, from kids to adults.
I get it. Let's head in that direction.
But since it's Jack, you'll need a hook.
I know...
The main character has to be a young boy.
An elementary schooler?
And the heroine should be a girl that he's fallen in love with.
A heroine, huh.
They always give me trouble.
I hear that at the serialization meetings, they said the girls in your stories aren't very appealing.
They said that?
You have a girlfriend, so why can't you write girls?
Well, Miyoshi's kind of a tomboy.
Maybe the protagonist should be something other than a human?
Not human?
Do you mean something like a dog or a cat?
It's possible to do animal-themed characters.
I see.
Which means the heroine should also be an animal.
Miyoshi could be a model for that.
You... probably shouldn't tell her that.
Animals, huh?
That's tough.
There's a lot of different kinds of animals.
Yeah, nothing really comes to mind here.
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Chicken
Monkey
Frog
Cat
Takagi.
Don't push yourself too hard.
All-nighters aren't good for you.
I know.
Thanks.
See you.
'Kay.
Animals...
Animals, huh...
Zoo
Enjoy with sound and music
Now lending out for free
This doesn't really feel right...
In any case, even if the heroine is an animal, she's still a girl...
So in the end, the problem is understanding how a girl feels...
Huh? Why did I come here?
Man, I don't even know anymore!
Ashirogi?
Japanese Monkeys
Animals are great, aren't they?
Just watching them calms me down.
R-Right.
My college is nearby, so I come here sometimes.
Really? I haven't been here since elementary school.
Is something on your mind?
You were yelling "I don't even know anymore!" before.
Actually, I'm having some trouble right now.
Apparently, my heroines aren't very appealing, so I guess I don't understand what girls feel.
Same here.
Since it's a shounen magazine, I was told to rewrite my story from a boy's point of view.
But it's difficult.
I see.
Um...
If you'd like, I can help you understand girls...
and in exchange,
you could help me understand boys.
O-Oh my, what am I saying!
We're being serialized in the same magazine, after all...
That doesn't matter!
We can exchange opinions as fellow manga authors.
Working with you would be reassuring! Let's do it!
Really?
I'm okay with it if you are...
Then it's settled.
Awesome! Zoos are great!
Shall we start right now?
Well, not right here.
I know a café that's just—
Right, we shouldn't be alone together.
Oh no, that's fine.
Let's not.
Your college is nearby, and it'd be inconvenient for you if your friends see us together and get the wrong idea.
I'll call you. Around 10 tonight.
How about that?
Okay.
If you'd like, I could tell help you understand girls.
I can't believe I said that.
Hello?
I-It's Tagaki.
Er, I stuttered.
Good evening.
U-Um,
you said that your college was near that zoo.
Yes.
Could it be Tooh University?
Wow!
You can really do manga and schoolwork at the same time!
I admire you!
You flatter me...
What year are you?
I'm in my first year of grad school.
I'm basically aiming to be a teacher.
Aoki as a teacher...
More importantly, let's talk about manga.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
For my next work, I'm drawing my own art,
and I'm trying for a love story.
Oh. So that's why you want to understand how men feel.
Yes.
Have you told that to Nakai?
Was it a shock for him?
It may have been.
Um, this may be too nosy, but do you have a boyfriend?
Please keep this a secret.
I don't.
I see.
I'm surprised.
I know! Should I make my next heroine a beautiful college student or teacher?
Huh? Busy?
Hm... you're daring to write a pure love story for a shounen manga?
Yes.
A boy who perseveres in his pure love of the girl he likes.
From a man's point of view, I suppose that isn't very realistic.
That's not true.
You know, Mashiro and his girlfriend...
In elementary school, they fell in love at first sight,
and in the last year of middle school, they finally confessed to each other.
But they made a promise to each other that they wouldn't meet until their dreams came true,
Azuki Miho
Mashiro
"Detective TRAP" was great!
I sent in the survey card (lol)
and they've generally kept to that.
Received Box
Mashiro Moritaka
Manager
Miyoshi Kaya
Office
Mashiro Moritaka
Happy Birthday
That's wonderful.
Is it?
Wouldn't you normally see each other if you like each other?
Yes, but it's still wonderful.
So, I think love differs from person to person.
Reality and ideals don't match up very well.
You're right.
The person you like may not like you back,
or you can become interested in someone unexpected after that person confesses.
Really. Do you have experience with that?
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
You're pretty funny, Aoki.
It may be rude, but I thought you were more aloof.
Am I what you call "tsundere"?
Tsundere? You haven't got the "sweet" part.
Well, you're not aloof either.
It's morning already, is that okay?
Oh, I'm sorry!
We've been talking for so long...
No, I'm fine.
It was fun.
I bet love can start from an experience like this, too.
Maybe.
I've learned a lot.
I'll talk to you again.
Okay.
So you talked until morning?
Yeah.
So tired...
Hey, if Miyoshi finds out, she'll be pissed.
We're just helping each other out to improve our manga.
It's fine.
More importantly,
exchanging opinions with fellow manga authors is really helpful.
Thanks to that, I can see the direction for a plot.
Have you thought of something?
Tooh University
I'm glad I talked to him.
It's great to have other manga authors as reference.
And besides...
Aoki.
May I talk to you for a minute?
The main character is an elementary schooler and the grandson of an inventor.
The grandpa invents things for his grandson without the rest of the family knowing.
Since he likes his grandson's beautiful teacher, he comes to the school often.
Something goes wrong every time...
and at the end, either the invention breaks or the teacher confiscates it and scolds him.
That's pretty cliché.
But it could be interesting depending on what kinds of inventions you come up with.
I know, right?
If I write in an evil inventor, there could even be battles!
Yeah, that's great!
Cafe Latte
(hot or iced)
Cafe Mocha
American coffee
(hot or iced)
Tea latte
Chai
Hot chocolate
So what did you want to talk about?
Are you familiar with Takagi Akito, another Shounen Jack author?
I do know him.
I was his classmate in middle school.
He rejected me in our third year.
He said he'd choose manga over his studies.
And I laughed him off.
I see.
But when I see you two working so hard,
I feel like I should be acknowledging the act of making manga.
Do you value literature over manga?
Anyone can see that literature is more cultured.
Yes.
This girl still likes Takagi, and has come to me...
But "I feel like I should acknowledge it"...
No, this may be just another form of love.
Do you want to see him?
I want to show him who I am now.
Now that you've become an author?
Yes.
But it would be too humiliating to go to him myself.
She's too proud.
But so was I a few years ago.
I may be able to arrange a meeting.
I'm sorry, should I not have called again today?
Of course not.
It was helpful, and I really enjoyed it.
Same here.
Um, what can I help you with?
Oh, well...
Takagi, do you want to see my underwear?
Wh-What are you saying?!
Are you teasing me?
No...
I'm serious.
Seriously?
Why would I want to see your underwear...
Did I say "mine"?
Yes, you definitely did.
Oh dear, I'm sorry!
I meant any girl's underwear.
Oh, so that was a mistake?
I'm sorry. I just had to get it out...
It's busy again today?
Yes, Miyoshi?
So, Takagi isn't talking to you, Mashiro?
He's been on the phone all day for the past two days!
Isn't that kind of suspicious?
M-Maybe it's Miura?
For hours on end?
Our meetings can last pretty long...
Well, that's fine, then.
Three panty shots every week?
Your editor makes a good point.
I think that'll go over well.
I see.
By the way, Takagi, which way would you prefer to see underwear?
You're serious, right?
I'm serious.
It's no good if they're shown on purpose.
What's important is for it to be accidental.
For example, seeing them when she stoops over while wearing a miniskirt.
Right then, the girl's shyness should...
Hold on, let me write this down.
You're taking notes?
This will be very helpful.
Well, if it's useful to you, that's fine.
How about you, Takagi? Am I being useful to you?
Of course!
Thanks to our talk yesterday, I was able to make a lot of progress.
I see.
It's just...
I was thinking of putting in an animal, but I haven't gotten that far yet.
An animal?
If it's a fantasy, you can have an imaginary creature.
Imaginary?
A fairy or mythical animal.
Like a cute animal the author makes up.
Made up...
I see!
You've given me some inspiration!
Thank you!
I'm going to revise the storyboard right now.
Um.
Can we meet once again?
The zoo would be fine.
Zoo
Enjoy with sound and music
Now lending out for free
Is this what you would call a date?
Isn't this kinda bad?
Takagi.
Aoki!
You were already here?
Iwase?
It's been some time.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
What's going on?
I just happened to hear about this meeting from my classmate, Aoki.
Classmate?
We're in the literature department at the same college.
Tooh University Literature Department?
Awesome!
You always were good at studying.
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Take this.
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Green Graduation.
It's my first published work.
You wrote this?
Seriously?
I'm more and more impressed.
Are you still  working on manga?
What do you mean by "still"?
I read all your manga.
Money and Intelligence, Detective TRAP...
...Future Watch.
You casually left out TEN !
That one had many ambiguous aspects.
But I'm glad you took the time to read them.
Thank you.
You should be capable of writing a novel, Takagi.
Um...
You should write a novel instead of wasting time with manga!
Something much more cultured!
True.
Compared to novels, manga is worthless.
But I'll write manga.
It's strange to write it after saying it's worthless!
Of course I don't really think it's worthless!
Sorry.
But you shouldn't be talking about which is superior...
when both are made by hardworking people with aspirations.
I think so too.
Both manga and novels have the ability to entertain people.
Each week, millions of people buy and enjoy Jack.
I believe that has meaning.
Millions?
My book only sold 30,000.
The worth of a publication isn't measured by the number of copies it sells!
That's why I just said...
It's wrong to compare them.
It doesn't matter which is more culturally valuable or which sells more.
In that case...
I'll write a manga story like you two!
What are you saying, Iwase?
If you like novels, then write novels!
Are you afraid I'll surpass you?
No, it's not that.
And you won't, anyway.
Why?
I dont want to lose to you.
I want to stand shoulder to shoulder with you.
You haven't changed at all since middle school.
No matter how hard I work, you just say "Wow!" with an expressionless face...
and think that you're winning.
Huh? I don't think that.
And if we're talking about winning and losing, you've clearly won at everything.
Liar! You don't mean that!
She's a child.
I'm not lying.
Tooh University, and this novel...
I really admire your accomplishments!
And you're really pretty, too.
You're a thousand times smarter and prettier than Miyoshi.
You're still dating Miyoshi?
Yeah.
Takagi has a girlfriend?
If I'm a thousand times better, then date me!
But I like Miyoshi even a thousand times more.
See, you were lying when you said you admired me.
I've had enough.
Thank you for coming.
Iwase's going to write manga?!
For Jack?
I'm sure that's what she intends.
She's made me into her rival.
Iwase and manga, huh.
It'll never work.
Green Graduation
Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
Aoki said that if she can write a whole novel, she probably can do it.
She'll just do it because she can.
It's Takahama.
I heard from Miura that you're writing a gag manga for NEXT.
Yeah.
You'd better not do it.
Miura says that Business Boy Kenichi  is staying in the top ten because I'm putting in jokes,
But I'm already at my limit.
I would really like to try my best with the genre I'm most suited for.
Thanks for the warning.
Green Graduation
_Akina Aiko
But Takagi feels like doing it now.
I see.
It's not something I should butt into, then.
Sorry.
It's fine.
And one more thing.
Aoki
Nakai and a fellow female assistant?
Yes.
So I don't think you need to worry about him anymore.
Actually, that particular girl liked Mashiro when she was assisting us with TRAP—
Um, I have to write my storyboard now.
Ah, okay.
Until next time.
Goodbye.
Because I love you!
I shoud head over to their office...
Would I be in the way?
I'm sure it's all messy.
That's it!
This is good!
It was a good idea to gear it towards kids!
Really?
Yeah! Can we have a meeting about this now?
In an hour, at the usual restaurant.
Yes.
Okay, I'll be right there.
In an hour, at the restaurant.
Chapter two's storyboard is still only half done.
Bring it anyway.
Yeah.
Have no fear! Super Cleaning Girl Miyoshi is here!
Huh?
You're going out?
We've got a meeting now.
We at least do our own cleaning.
Oh really?
Um...
I'll have it sparkling by the time you get back.
It's fine, we don't even know how long it'll take.
No, I'm doing it.
"No"?
Okay.
With this, you can come and go whenever you want.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
See ya!
She's too loud...
Now then!
Jeez, why can't guys ever clean up properly?
Huh? What's this?
Since I probably can't be honest when talking with you,
I slipped in this letter.
I'm very happy I was able to see you, Takagi.
These are my true feelings.
I want us to encourage each other.
That's what I've always, always wanted.
I'm looking forward to meeting you at the zoo.
I'm praying for a wonderful date.
I can't cry...
I can't cry till I get home!
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
Takagi and Iwase have definitely gotten together!
The manuscript for NEXT isn't coming together, though.
Read the atmosphere and don't make a joke like that right now!
Next time on Bakuman:
Unfaithfulness and Trust
Unfaithfulness and
Trust
A girl's dream is to continue being loved by the one she loves!