Ashirogi Muto
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First Chapter
Ashirogi Muto
Here it is!
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First chapter
Ashirogi Muto
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First chapter
Ashirogi Muto
Perfect Crime Club ?
Is this really 100 times better than KTM ?
Just read it!
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Win and Lose
Thanks for the food!
At my school,
when lunch is over,
everyone puts their dishes in the bin on the table in front of the classroom.
Then 80% of the students go to play on the playground,
while 20% remain at their desks.
For example, Takahashi spends lunch break pretending to study.
So, if I covertly place my dishes on Takahashi's desk
while he disposes of his dishes...
It's a perfect crime!
It's a perfect
crime!!
What's this?
Something this petty, a perfect crime?
It doesn't really live up to its title...
It's fine if he does petty things seriously.
Yeah, it's best to start out small.
"It's a perfect crime..."
But it wasn't!
There was a witness—Minami.
But he just looked at me with a face that said "I saw what you did"
and laughed.
I was shocked...
It was the first time my perfect crime...
wasn't perfect.
I'm home.
Damn.
Maybe all the perfect crimes I've committed so far...
Like finishing Yasuda's drill on my own,
or letting a sparrow loose in the classroom and disrupting class...
Maybe he's seen them all...
I suddenly became interested in Minami,
and I started observing him the following day.
Huh? But I cleaned this up...
When lunch ended, Minami did the same thing I did yesterday.
Why is he copying me?
But I saw it.
His wasn't a perfect crime, either.
Ding
dong
Even after school ended, I kept following him.
To my surprise, Minami himself was following our classmate Kitamura!
Tailing...
Tailing.
I had done it with a random person before.
The next day, Minami tailed an upperclassman.
We kept this up every day for a week.
Then Minami came up to me.
Chimitsu.
Oh crap!
I thought this was petty at first, but I'm getting drawn in by the realistic art and how serious these guys are.
Because this is a kid's world, things like this are actually more realistic.
I see.
And then...
I see! So that's how you'll do it!
And so, the Perfect Crime Club was formed.
You did it!
It's 100 times better than KTM !
I've never seen anything this good.
No, I can say it's an entirely new type of manga.
I can see the gutsiness and serious humor clearly in this one!
This is the best! The ultimate form of Ashirogi Muto!
Congratulations!
Save that for when we're serialized and go head to head with Niizuma...
No, you'll do it!
But how'd you think this up?
The events are strangely realistic.
It's because we tried some of them out in real life.
You did? Like what?
I can't tell you... you know?
If we told you, it wouldn't be a perfect crime anymore.
I see.
This suits Takagi!
And unlike the unconventional manga you've done before, this isn't cynical!
Okay, we'll go with this for the first chapter.
If you make any changes, keep them small.
Actually, messing around with it might make it worse.
Okay!
I'll jump right into our plans for chapter two, then...
A girl will join their group!
Oh, a heroine!
Her name is Annojo Mai.
Right, that's a heroine-like name.
Mashiro came up with it.
Nice naming sense.
Thanks.
Mai is extremely calculating, and she loves mystery novels, so her deductive reasoning is excellent.
The current two members of the perfect crime club decide that they must have her abilities,
so they thoroughly investigate her.
How will they get her to join?
It should be in a perfect crime-like way, right?
They'll arrange a mysterious surprise for Mai's birthday,
which will lead her to investigate and eventually deduce their identities.
The serious humor can come from the
usually unflappable Mai getting flustered,
and it'll show her cuteness as a heroine!
I think it'll be interesting that they let themselves be discovered.
You've already got it all planned out, huh?
Yeah.
Then you two should go ahead and make the second chapter.
It sounds like I'm better off waiting to read it than hearing about it now.
Yes!
Okay!
In a week, then!
Miura!
What's going on with Ashirogi?!
There's not even a week left until the deadline for the storyboard!
Well, they'll definitely make it in time, so let's stay calm—
Stay calm?!
You know...
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, Takahama, are you finished?
Okay, I'll come right over.
It looks like Takahama finished his storyboard, so I'll be heading out.
Shouldn't Ashirogi be more important than Takahama right now?
Takahama
I fixed everything like you said!
It's way better than last time!
I'm confident in it!
It's certainly better.
But something's missing...
I get it!
It's good, but...
Yes?
I won't submit this to the serialization committee.
Huh? Why not?!
If it's good, then please submit it!
Actually, Takahama,
if Ashirogi doesn't submit a work that's as good as Niiuzma's to the next committee,
they won't be able to draw for Jack anymore.
It was the condition for them being allowed to quit Tanto.
So in order to make things easier for Ashirogi, you're asking me to swallow my tears?
No!
Before I saw their storyboard,
I would have told you to go forward with this.
But now, I don't think you should submit a work at this level.
Because Ashirogi's is far better than this.
Far better?
Yes.
I haven't shown it to the higher ups yet,
but their storyboard is pretty much
complete up through the third chapter.
I can assure you that there's no way theirs will fail and yours will pass.
The difference is too great.
If you still want to submit it, I'll try talking to the higher ups...
Please do.
I can't stand the idea of losing without a fight.
Besides, you're the one who always says "If you can just get serialized, everything else will work out"!
You're right. We both worked hard on this hoping to get it serialized.
I shouldn't have said that.
Up until now, getting a serialization was all that mattered.
That's what I thought...
Now, I've finally realizing that there's more to it than that.
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
Niizuma, I have some good news for you.
+NATURAL is getting an anime.
And it's starting in April!
That's quick!
It's because it got more popular than CROW.
But will Ashirogi be okay?
Unless they're as popular as CROW
and +NATURAL,
they won't be able to draw for Jack anymore.
Akira, you'd usually say "Ashirogi won't lose to you next time!"
They sure are in a tight spot.
Even if they get serialized, they'll have to draw even with CROW
and +NATURAL.
They've got some tough acts to follow.
Maybe they should change the condition to just getting serialized.
Well, Ashirogi will get what they deserve.
There it is! Yoshida's trademark "They get what they deserve"!
Miura... Hattori...
I've had enough.
No matter what kind of manga they submit, I
don't think they can easily measure up with Niizuma!
I'll negotiate with the Chief Editor to
consider their work as a normal manga
and not hold it up to Niizuma as a standard at the committee!
Please don't.
It'll be okay.
This is no time to act cool!
This isn't a question of you or Hattori taking the blame!
This is about an author's career here!
I told you before!
We editors are in a position to determine an author's life—
No. If it's bad, they'll get what they deserve.
Oh, where were you?
Buying food.
I needed a change of pace.
You can use your bike, but don't get in an accident.
It'll be no laughing matter if you break your arm.
I wouldn't be so clumsy.
Well, having a hobby isn't a bad thing.
Ashirogi's under a condition like that?!
Yeah.
And their manuscript wasn't considered at the last committee...
That's bad!
The next committee is all they have left!
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
If Ashirogi can't draw for Jack anymore,
it'll definitely have an effect on Niizuma.
So they're that determined, huh...
I'll leave the rest to you, then.
Good work!
Hey, I've done all I can with KIYOSHI.
Yeah, I guess so.
We've brought the delinquent tournament all the way to Y-1.
It's my third year of serialization, and the ranking always floats around 10th place.
And there haven't been any anime offers.
And now, Ashirogi is trying to get a
serialization that can match Niizuma's work.
What's happened to the Fukuda Team?!
All right!
The deadline is the day after tomorrow... is there really nothing left to change?
Well...
Incoming Call
Takahama Shoyo
Takahama!
It's been a while.
What? Our storyboard?
Sure, that's fine.
Yeah, see you.
He's coming over. He asked to see the
storyboard we're submitting to the committee.
What?
And you said that was okay?
He might be our rival next week!
He seemed pretty serious,
and it's already the deadline, so what's the harm in showing him?
"Perfect Crime
Club"
Third Chapter
Muto
More importantly, I want to hear his thoughts on it.
Well, there is that.
He has a good eye.
I'm not going to submit anything to the committee this time.
You don't have to go that far.
No, Miura was right.
It's way better than mine.
Now I'm fired up and ready to make something
better; something that won't lose to Ashirogi Muto!
I was about to submit my pitiful storyboard to the committee.
Takahama.
Thank you.
I'm cheering you on!
And I'll catch up to you soon!
After seeing Takahama's reaction, I'm even more confident in this.
I'm grateful.
And I want to try hard for his sake, too!
Here's Ashirogi's storyboard. Please submit this!
O-Okay.
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
Huh? Perfect Crime Club ? Is this okay?
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
It's much more than "okay"!
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Serialization Storyboard
Ashirogi Muto
(Temporary) "Perfect Crime Club"
You've never seen a
manga like this before!!
Editor:
Miura
Coming!
Here's the fried chicken.
Oh, thanks!
Should I really be here?
This is the first Christmas since you've been married.
Don't worry, it's fine.
We'll be stuck to each other once you leave.
Let's get ready to celebrate while we wait for results from the committee.
You're confident, right, Saiko?
Yeah.
I think the storyboard will pass.
Miura told us that Hattori praised it, right?
"This is what I was looking for", he said.
If only Miho would come.
They won't meet until their dreams come true, right?
Well, we met at the hospital and your wedding.
I'll definitely make our dreams
come true with Perfect Crime Club,
and we'll be together like you two are soon!
Well, Mashiro, you sure are talking big!
Especially for you, I have...
this!
A homemade cake from Miho!
You drew Miho a picture for her birthday, right?
She said she wanted to do something for you, too.
Azuki did?
It's obviously Ashirogi this time.
It's got a good review from the higher ups.
It's hard to admit, but it looks like a sure thing.
I didn't think they'd do it like that.
And they'll definitely get the kids' vote.
But really, I never thought the three of them could come up with such a good manga.
Maybe I underestimated Miura.
Strictly speaking, it wasn't just the three of us.
Because Hattori was there...
You did well, Miura.
Well, it hasn't been decided yet...
Right, it hasn't been decided.
This time, it isn't just about whether it's good or not.
Do you understand, Miura?
Up next is Ashirogi Muto's Perfect Crime Club.
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First Chapter
Ashirogi Muto
The editor is Miura.
If I may say, I do not think there is a better work than this.
Yes. Everyone present gave it a good mark, and there appear to be no problems.
Only Yoshida believes that it is good, but needs some changes.
They're trespassing on school grounds.
It wouldn't be good if children imitate this.
If you go by that reasoning, then every manga where someone hits someone else is no good.
Why even bring that up?
That's true, but...
because the story and art are both strangely realistic,
it seems easy to imitate, or rather, it makes you want to imitate it.
That should be taken as a laudable aspect.
This realism is good, right?
We should proceed with discretion, but it shouldn't be a problem.
You're right.
If there's no problem on that front, then I
believe it's the best work we have here by far.
It looks like Ashirogi finally found their way.
It's wonderful!
It pulled me in,
and even though it's serious, I was blown away.
It reminds me of the secret base I made as a kid.
Because it's a secret club.
It evokes a child's mindset.
In that way, it really is a shounen manga.
In elementary school, I tailed a girl I
really liked to find out where she lived.
It reminded me of that.
If you did that now, you'd be a stalker!
Although we're having fun with old stories,
let's pass Perfect Crime Club with a unanimous "yes"—
No.
No?
I rated it highly,
but before we say yes or no to this manga,
we first must consider whether it can beat Niizuma's manga, CROW  and +NATURAL.
Chief Editor,
so you really were serious
about not letting them draw for Jack if they can't win against CROW  and +Natural?
Of course I was.
If it's a question of winning or losing...
It's difficult to say.
Perfect Crime Club  will be serialized, won't it?
Huh? Of course it will!
Why are you asking again?
But this time, it's not a question of being good or bad.
It's about whether it can compete with CROW  and +NATURAL.
Well, we knew it wouldn't be easy.
Well, you know, there are magazines other than Jack.
Oh, sorry.
I heard about it from Aoki.
You knew all along?
Yeah.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
But we'll definitely be serialized in Jack.
Right.
Shujin, if we don't pass, you won't give up on manga, will you?
What are you talking about, Saiko?!
I'm just saying, "What if"?
In that case, we'll draw for some other magazine and surpass Eiji that way.
That wouldn't be the best option, but there wouldn't be any other choice.
We won't quit being manga authors.
Sorry, but I just wanted to confirm that.
Of course!
Even if we don't sell, we'll do it for the rest of our lives!
You two are so cool!
W-Well then, shall we begin discussion on whether Perfect Crime Club
can win against CROW
and +NATURAL ?
Isn't this sort of a strange topic to discuss?
But...
I think it can beat them!
Aida, this comes from one of your team members, right?
Th-That's got nothing...!
To beat Niizuma would mean to beat an already popular manga.
It would be difficult.
Indeed.
They can't beat him so easily.
Wait a minute!
We won't know if they don't try!
Isn't that what you always say?
This is a discussion about whether or not they have the potential to beat him!
If you put it that way, then any manga
would have a small potential of winning!
It's as Heishi says.
This is about whether or not they can beat him right now.
This is very good, and the fact that it doesn't
overlap with other serializations works in its favor.
I believe it's off to a good start.
But a good start isn't enough...
Not if they can't beat him.
When you put it that way...
The committee is running long, surprisingly.
I thought they would finish early today.
Shouldn't they be wrapping up soon?
Ashirogi's as good as in.
For sure.
I wish that were true, but if they don't pass...
And I'm worried that Hattori, who said it was really good, has been looking depressed this whole time.
Niizuma and Ashirogi have different levels of experience.
You can't compare them.
If you're talking about experience, I think Ashirogi's struggles have made them stronger in that area.
It doesn't make sense to compare two completely different types of manga on experience level.
We can't seem to come to a conclusion on if it'll win or lose.
We'll decide it by majority vote.
Ma-Majority vote?
Are we really deciding this on a vote, Chief Editor?!
First, Oonishi.
Because the situation is so complicated, I believe it'll be difficult for them to win.
One vote for lose.
Lose
Win
Next, Yoshida.
One vote for win.
Nakano.
Lose.
Win: 1. Lose: 2.
Aida, you vote for win, right?
Yes.
Win and Lose are tied at 2.
Heishi.
They can't win.
Win: 2. Lose: 3.
Lose
Win
Next is me...
I think they can win.
Win and Lose are tied at 3.
A tie, huh.
You have yet to vote, Chief.
Me, huh.
We're all ready!
All that's left is to get news of the serialization!
Saiko, do you honestly think that Perfect Crime Club  can win against CROW  and +NATURAL?
TRAP  tied with CROW
once.
We can definitely win!
Chief Editor, please vote.
Perfect Crime Club  is good.
But... it can't win.
I don't think it can win against CROW  and +NATURAL.
Th-Then, with a majority vote of 3 for Win and 4 for Lose,
Ashirogi Muto's Perfect Crime Club  will not be serialized...
toomawari wo eranda no wa
The reason I chose to take a detour
motto kimi wo suki ni naru tame datta n da
was to fall ever deeper in love with you
boku no namae yobu sono koe wo
I have a feeling I've always known
zutto zutto shitteta ki ga shita n da
what your voice sounds like when it calls my name
boku no yubisaki de egaita
With my fingertips I drew
subete no sen wa kimi ni tsuzuku kakehashi sa
many lines that make up a suspension bridge leading to you
Show me the way
Show me the way I'm sure our path
bokura no michi kitto
Believe in your way
your way connects us without any turns
hitosuji ni tsunagari
Show me the way
Show me the way It leads to the place where we promised
yakusoku no basho e tsuzuku
Show me the way
Show me the way I will never give up
akirametari shinaide
Believe in your way
your way Raise your gaze
sono hitomi wo agete
Show me the way
Show me the way and see that we're certain to meet again
bokura wa massugu deau sa
Next Time
Preview
Perfect Crime Club
is good.
But it can't win.
Then, Ashirogi will...
Next time on Bakuman:
Expression and
Imagination
Expression and Imagination.
Sometimes reality crushes dreams.
To Mashiro-kun