I think Azuki just dumped me.
She found out that I've been hiding what happened between her mom and my uncle...
and told me she couldn't trust me.
That's not good.
Unlike Miyoshi, Azuki isn't the type to forgive cheating.
I didn't cheat!
W-Well, yeah... but this is bad.
Yeah, for now, I'd better apologize.
H-Hi, this is Mashiro.
Yes?
I'm sorry about before.
But I haven't done anything wrong, so please trust me.
I do trust you. So just tell me.
Well, um, if you trust me, I shouldn't have to tell you...
If no one's done anything wrong, you should be able to talk about it.
I can only think you're covering for Takagi.
But when you were worried about doing that photo book, you hid it from me.
I think hiding something to avoid worrying others
and hiding something you did wrong are two different things.
But I already told you I didn't do anything wrong!
How come you get to decide?
If nothing's wrong, you should be able to tell me.
You don't trust me!
You don't trust me enough to tell me!
I've had enough!
That's my line!
I can't do it.
I'm pissed now.
In the end, neither Azuki nor Miyoshi trusts us.
Even though we haven't done anything wrong.
If Saiko and Azuki break up because of something I did...
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Monkeys and Marriage
This won't work.
Let's just tell them everything!
What about Aoki?
Will Miyoshi accept that?
First, I'll stop exchanging ideas with Aoki.
I'll tell her afterwards and promise never to do it again.
And that thing with Iwase was just a misunderstanding.
If there's nothing left to hide, then you and Azuki can make up.
I'll ask Aoki.
Hello, this is Aoki.
H-Hello.
You seem quite cheerful today.
Ah, I'm sorry.
You're the only man I can trust right now,
so honestly, I enjoy talking with you.
You enjoy it?!
Talking with me?
Yes.
This is the first time I've been able to be honest and talk freely with a man.
Thank you for everything.
I look forward to continuing our relationship as manga authors and occasional rivals.
S-Sorry.
I couldn't tell her I wanted to stop talking with her.
Well, she didn't do anything wrong.
Should you tell just Azuki everything?
She'll just tell Miyoshi.
And if I tell her not to, she'll just get even angrier.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Let's just wait it out and see how it goes for a while.
But I've caused trouble for both of you...
If they apologize, then we can tell them everything.
Otherwise, they'll walk all over us in the future!
Now, let's get started on that serialization storyboard for when Tanto  gets first place!
Y-Yeah.
"If they apologize..."
This is bad.
Saiko's really stubborn when it comes to things like this.
What?! You called him?
No luck with either Takagi or Mashiro.
They're both hiding something.
Both of them? You talked to Mashiro?
Yeah. We got into a fight.
A fight?
Miho and Mashiro had a fight?
I can't believe he'd hide something from me.
That's unforgivable, right?
Huh? Yeah...
Crap.
It's our fault...
What should I do?
Miho's stubborn when it comes to things like this...
Well, Mashiro too.
It usually comes on release day...
An email from Azuki about her impressions.
What else...
Hey, how about you stop being stubborn and tell Azuki everything?
Let it go already.
I won't be the one to fold first.
Anyways, let's get to the office.
O-Okay.
Thursday, August 23rd
It's gonna be a while before we find out NEXT's final rankings...
I should have asked him to tell us the early results.
Tanto... can get first place, right?
It's not "can", it's "will".
I think it'll go over well with little kids,
but NEXT has a higher readership age than Jack does.
Saiko, you're just useless without Azuki's "It was great!" email.
That's not true!
I'll be waiting downstairs.
Okay.
Thursday, August 30th
That's him!
Tanto  took 1st place in the final rankings!
We did it!
This is the first time we've gotten 1st place!
I'm so happy!
It's the first time one of my edited works has gotten 1st, too, idiot!
Let's ride this momentum all the way to the next serialization meeting!
Yes! We'll do our best!
We did it!
I didn't know I'd be this happy about getting 1st in the final rankings.
Next time, let's get 1st in Jack!
Yeah...
What's wrong, Saiko?
I'll try telling Azuki.
Right!
Oh, Yamahisa.
Time of Blue Leaves  got 2nd.
I think it did well, considering it was up against Ashirogi.
2nd is just fine for getting serialized.
It didn't get to have the first few pages in color, after all.
I wonder if that's all it was?
Yamahisa.
Yes?
Time of Blue Leaves did well with older males and females.
That was pretty much what we were aiming for.
It's been a while since I've seen a romance like this.
It'll work!
You really think so?!
Yeah, if we do something about the art.
So that was  the issue, after all.
I was concerned about it.
If Aoki is fine with drawing the faces alone,
you could try pairing her up with Nakai Takuro again, with him as the artist and her as the author.
This time, in the magazine itself.
I understand.
I'll keep pushing her to pair up with Nakai.
I won't lose to Tanto  lying down!
I'm counting on you.
If it goes well, it could get a drama adaptation!
She could have said "Congratulations", at least...
Maybe she's working really late?
I guess she won't reply unless I apologize.
Don't you think she's taking things too far?
Oh, that's mine.
Congratulations on getting first place!
Oh, thank you.
I was second.
Second? That's great!
You don't mind if I congratulate you, right?
I am frustrated, but...
I'm glad that Ashirogi, whom I collaborated with, was number one.
Let's both work hard from here on out.
Yes, thank you!
Talk to you later.
Why am I so happy even though I only got second place?
Do I like...?
No, I can't feel that way for him.
He has a girlfriend.
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
This is Yamahisa from Jack.
H-Hello.
This may be sudden, but we decided to try out Time of Blue Leaves as a one-shot in Jack!
Really?
Yep! If we can have Nakai do the art.
The general consensus in the editing department is that it would be for the best.
Nakai and a fellow female assistant?
Yes.
So I don't think you need to worry about him anymore.
I don't have the right to criticize Nakai now.
Aoki?
I understand.
If it will improve the manga, I'll trust you and do as you say.
Okay!
Then I'll follow up with Nakai immediately.
No.
I will speak with him directly.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Um, what was it you wanted to talk about?
I was wondering if you would draw for me again.
Time of Blue Leaves, which was published in NEXT...
is going to be tried out as a one-shot in Jack.
I love you!
I didn't think it was possible, but could that character in Time of Blue Leaves  really have been...
Being popular sure is tough.
My editor suggested that you should do the art.
I'll be brief, since I slipped out of work to come talk to you.
Okay.
You see, I'm enjoying my current job, and I'm getting along well with Katou Natsumi, a fellow assistant.
I'm having trouble deciding between you two.
I don't really understand...
If you want to work with me, go out with me.
That's my condition.
Nakai.
Yes?
Wow.
That stuff actually happens?
You're horrible!
Dating as a requirement for working together?
As a man... as a person... you're awful!
I see. I'm relieved.
Since you've gone this far, my doubts have all been cleared up.
Natsumi is waiting for me, so...
Goodbye.
For the first chapter, we'll go with "The gum that makes you say cool stuff"
and "The cast that punches back".
Which of these inventions do you want to use for chapters two and up?
He hasn't sent Azuki any mail since then.
This is getting bad.
We have to get this serialized, make it into a big hit, and then we'll get an anime...
I can't even email her until then?
Actually, is our promise to get married once I get an anime even valid at this point?
Hey, you alive?
Saiko?
What?
I'll go home for today and think about it.
Here's the list of inventions.
Number them in the order of which ones you like most.
If he's like that, it'll affect our work.
This isn't the time to be stubborn.
What's wrong?
Even though you've finally come to visit, you've been looking down this whole time.
I'm sorry for staying over so long.
I don't mind. It's like I have more daughters now; It's kind of fun.
I fought with my friend.
Your friend... is it a boy?
Well, yeah.
Hey, what's going on with Miho and Mashiro?
She doesn't tell me anything,
so give me the details before she gets back from work!
Th-The details?
Excuse me for a minute.
I'm saved.
Takagi Akito
You Have New Mail
Takagi?
Takagi Akito
No Subject
If you are still at Azuki's house,
move to a place where she won't hear you.
What's this?
What's with that attitude?
A friend?
Y-Yeah.
I need to go make a call.
See you later!
I won't wait 30 minutes!
Oh, Miyoshi.
That was fast.
What's with the "Oh"?
You guys are idiots!
What was with that manga?
Huh? You didn't like Tanto?
It got 1st place, though...
Not that one!
The one that used Miho and Mashiro's romance!
What are you doing, telling everybody about it?!
Oh, that.
"That "?!
You're so obviously prattling away with both Iwase and that female manga author!
Are the two of you going on group dates with both of them every day, or something?
Sounds like fun!
Even though you never take me out on a proper date,
you're really chummy with pretty girls!
You should only do stuff like that after you break up with me—
Shut up!
Be quiet for a minute!
Just come back already.
I can't stand that Azuki and Mashiro ended up like this because of us.
I feel the same way, but...
It's because of you, not because of us.
All right, I get it.
Anyways, I'm going to explain it to you, so just calm down and listen.
I can't get Nakai to do the art now.
What should I do?
I'm telling you, it was a misunderstanding!
I told Iwase I liked you 1,000 times more than her.
I really did!
And how much more do you like me than Aoki?
Three times?
Why are you being realistic there?
That's so stupid.
But since it's realistic, I'll believe you when you say you like me.
Yeah, I like you more than anyone.
If you're going that far, then take me out on a date to the zoo.
Huh? Why?
All right. Then I'll explain everything properly at the zoo.
Hmm, so you're really  gonna make it up to me by taking me out on a fun date?
If I'm not satisfied, I'll beat the crap out of you.
That'll be up to you.
But I really do like you more than anyone.
I get it. I'm coming now.
Okay. See you at 3 at the monkey mountain, then.
Why the monkey mountain?
Let's see... monkey mountain, monkey mountain.
I hope I can tell Miyoshi apart from the monkeys.
Aoki?!
Takagi!
Wh-Why?
Could Miyoshi have arranged this?
No, she's not capable of that...
We meet again by coincidence.
At this time of all times.
Of all times?
I don't know what to do!
Wh-What's wrong?
She smells good...
Wait a minute, I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Miyoshi!
You didn't have to go this far to show off to me! I get it already!
Wait! That's not it!
Th-That's my girlfriend!
Oh no!
Please wait!
I-I'm no one suspicious!
Suspicious?
You're super suspicious!
How can you say that when you were all over him, you temptress!
She wasn't all over me!
I just had my hand on her shoulder!
You should have just kissed while you were at it!
That's what you wanted me to see, right?!
Wait!
I hope you're happy together!
Takagi!
Miyoshi!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Marry me!
I love you more than anyone else!
Idiot.
You're just trying to keep hold of me by copying Mashiro.
I'm not copying him.
Let's do it now.
Marry me right now.
R-Right now?
I'm 19, and you're still 18!
We can legally marry!
But we're still college students!
I think it's a wonderful thing for college students to marry.
You think it's wonderful ?
Who the hell are you, anyway?
I thought he was cheating with Iwase.
I'm Aoki Yuriko.
I was serialized in Shounen Jack under the name Aoki Kou.
I know that,
but you two were hugging back there.
Since you drew a manga like that, you and Takagi must be real close, huh?
Well, that's...
I won't deny that.
I thought so!
No, we just talked about manga!
While hugging?
There's a really good explanation for that...
There is, right?
No, I don't have a reasonable justification for hugging you.
You don't?!
I get the overall picture.
Would you really meet at the zoo by coincidence twice? This isn't a manga.
And on top of that, Aoki was troubled both times?
Well, that's what happened.
I'm really sorry.
I won't call him anymore, and I won't talk to him if we meet by coincidence again.
Sorry for all this.
So trust Takagi and marry him!
He proposed on a whim just to stop me from running off.
No, if you say yes, then I'll do it.
If we're always together, there won't be any more misunderstandings like this.
I would have preferred to do it after becoming a famous manga author,
but if you're willing to struggle with me, then...
I think it's wonderful for people to struggle together and form a strong bond.
You guys say some nice things.
B-But there's stuff like the ceremony and my parents' permission to worry about...
Oh, right. I have to ask for your hand in marriage and stuff.
Do you think I'd get permission?
I mean, I'll do my best!
Then let's get married when you get serialized.
It's decided.
O-Okay.
Congratulations!
But you'll be busy when that happens, so we'll just get registered.
We'll have a ceremony when we can.
Right!
Please let me know when that happens.
Oh, sorry. I will support you from behind.
I just said I wouldn't talk with Takagi anymore...
But Takagi's the only man you can trust and consult, right?
I've never had a person I could get along with like Takagi.
I'm sorry. I think I was starting to like him.
Why did you have to be so honest about that?
You should have stuck with the "We're just fellow manga authors" story.
Yeah.
But Takai and Nakai are both idiots.
If I were a man, I'd definitely choose you.
I can still change my mind...
Takagi!
What are you saying in front of the girl you just proposed to?!
I'll think less of you!
No, that was just one of his jokes.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Aoki, please continue talking to Takagi.
In exchange, I want you to become friends with me, too!
I-I'm very happy.
Thank you.
What?
Um, well, I was just wondering if Azuki will be satisfied with this.
Yeah, probably.
I can't trust you, but I can trust Aoki.
What's with that?
That was a joke, too... right?
I wonder?
Miyoshi!
Miyoshi?
If I don't apologize, our relationship might end like this!
But Azuki should trust me more...
It's no good!
I can't make any progress.
Azuki!
Crap! This might be a break-up email!
If it was going to come to this, I should have...
Aoki
It's hard for me to forgive you for hiding that he was exchanging opinions with
Aoki. But I will forgive you. Aoki is a nice person. We became friends (lol)
Huh?
What's this?
Family Restaurant
Hachiouji
If anyone saw this, they'd think "Who does this guy think he is?"
He's got three beautiful girls around him.
Two beautiful girls, you mean.
He's picking on you, Miho.
Oh, a reply from Mashiro?
What does it say?
"Huh? I don't get it."
Figures.
I should tell him the four of us are having tea.
He'll get even more confused.
Yeah.
Huh? The four of them?
I see, so Shujin...
Even though he said he was headed home for today.
Hey, Saiko.
Don't "Hey" me!
What are you doing leaving me out?
Sorry. But you're mailing each other again, right?
Y-Yeah.
You'd better be grateful.
Because of you, I was forced to agree to marry Miyoshi when we get serialized.
M-Marriage?!
What do you mean by "forced"?!
Ow!
Miyoshi!
But Kaya looks happy.
Shujin.
Let's get serialized for sure and make a popular manga!
Yeah!
When it gets an anime, you get married, too!
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
I'll work hard and aim for a serialization.
We're going to get married!
But will it go well?
It'll work out somehow!
Next time on Bakuman:
Prince and
Savior
The King and the Savior.
Is there anyone who will lend me a hand in accomplishing my dream?