You slapped Nakai?!
So that means... there's no going back?
Yes. I apologize.
No, it's fine.
He wanted you to date him in order to work with him, of all things.
Of course you'd get angry.
But we're in trouble now.
All we need are good female poses and panty flashes.
I understand.
I'll keep looking for people who can draw them.
Sounds rough, Yamahisa.
Yeah.
Well, as for me, I'm lucky that KIYOSHI has got panty shots in the bag.
Please don't be like that.
Introduce me to someone who can draw them!
Hirameki
Tanto-kun
Ashirogi Muto
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Prince and Savior
Are you really getting married if we get serialized?
Yeah.
All this has reminded me of how much I like Miyoshi,
and made me realize that I want to be with her.
But you're still only 18!
Enough about that.
They'll be here soon.
Long time no see, Mashiro.
H-Hello.
She went to Miho's place yesterday to apologize,
and today, she's here.
She's really serious about this.
Yeah, too serious.
I'm not being too serious.
I caused trouble for you all by exchanging ideas with Takagi without telling Kaya.
That's taking it too seriously.
Um, well, I really...
It's fine, it's fine.
Here, have a seat.
Thank you.
Nakai did that?
You can't work with a guy like that.
I can't even bear to see him now.
So you'll draw Time of Blue Leaves  yourself, then?
Yes.
I will study the kind of drawings men like,
or get someone who's good at that to help me.
What are the kinds of drawings men like?
Well, that's...
Stuff like panty shots.
Right?
Oh, come on.
But guys do like that kind of stuff.
You know, like KIYOSHI.
Fukuda's good at showing underwear.
Yeah, it might be good to reference him.
I don't want him thinking
I'm using his work as a reference!
Fukuda
Looks good.
We're definitely in the clear for next week with this.
It doesn't mean much if I can only get votes by putting in panty shots.
Leave this to me.
Good work.
Hey, how'd the results from NEXT  turn out?
Ashirogi got 1st place.
Oh, they did it!
And Aoki Kou?
She got 2nd, but she's in a tough spot right now.
Her story's good, but her art needs work.
Yeah.
This ain't even the most basic of the basics of panty shots.
After some deliberation, they were going to ask Nakai to do the art for a Jack one-shot, but...
Aoki and Nakai had a fight and it all went to waste, it seems.
A fight?
Fukuda again?
Fukuda Shinta
He'll just rag on me...
The person you have dialed cannot come to the phone at this time.
If you wish to leave a message, please—
It went straight to his voicemail!
What is he thinking?!
Doing a Jack one-shot is a great chance for him!
If he upset her, all he has to do is apologize.
All right!
Now that it's come to this, I'm going on the offensive!
I know he's usually at Takahama's around now.
I'll come with you!
Just go home!
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir.
Nakai's out, Fukuda's out...
Is anyone else good at that kind of art?
There is one other person who's good at it.
Who?
You know, Ishizawa—
Don't even go there!
Why?
Yes, he is good at that.
But he's out of the question.
Huh? But...
Anyone but him.
Um, if Mashiro's saying it's good, it must be quite good, correct?
Yeah, he's got a 3 page slot in a monthly magazine.
He's not a pro?
He was our classmate in middle school,
and he happens to go to the same college—
Hey! Stop running your mouth.
Give up on him, I'm telling you.
I know you guys hate him, but...
That's not it.
It's his personality that's the problem.
Even at the best of times, Aoki is distrustful of men.
I'd like to try meeting him.
What?!
Ishizawa
Takagi? Why are you calling me?
Just listen.
Ishizawa was all gung-ho.
Yeah, being a Jack author might not be so bad.
So he said.
Well then, Aoki, shall we go?
Yes.
Hey, why is it just you two?
I'm coming, too!
Why?
Well, even if it's just for work, you two would be together...
Okay. Then you can watch from a different table.
'Kay.
If it comes down to it, protect Aoki!
Am I the security police?
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Uh, okay.
But seriously, Ishizawa?
Will they be okay?
Maybe I should have gone, too.
Fukuda?
Mashiro.
Takahama was your assistant, right?
Yeah.
Where's his office?
Um, I think he works at home.
Then tell me the address.
Sure, but... did something happen?
Yeah.
I'm gonna get Nakai back on track and make him work with Aoki again.
Huh?
Family Restaurant
Open 24 Hours
So, I'm the chosen one, eh?
Me, the savior of Jack author Aoki Kou.
Her prince on a white horse!
He's not joking!
I'm not too interested in being an assistant.
You'd just be helping her out with drawing women in a way that guys like.
In other words, I'll be her panty-shot guy?
W-Well, yeah.
Fine.
But you'll have to do what I say.
Aoki will make it easy for me.
Just take pictures and movies of yourself in various poses.
I'll sort through them and decide what's best.
You're not being serious, are you?
Of course I am.
That's the best way to do it, isn't it?
Even so, you shouldn't talk to a girl like that.
So I should be elegant and beat around the bush?
That's not my style.
I'm sorry, Aoki.
Asking Ishizawa was a bad idea.
I might have to step in soon.
H-Hey, wait!
Nakai!
Fukuda!
Why are you destroying your
own chance at a one-shot in Jack?!
Stop sticking your nose where it doesn't belong!
I chose Katou over Aoki.
That's all there is to it.
Are you done?
I'm in the middle of work here.
Don't bother me anymore—
Wh-What the hell are you doing?
When we were serialized together, you were glad you didn't give up!
You told me that!
I was happy to be serialized with you, too!
Because we could compete as rivals!
I won't say not to fall for some girl!
But why aren't you aiming for serialization anymore?
Have you given up already?
It's... comfortable here.
Comfortable?
I can see and talk to Katou every day.
That's my happiness!
You guys wouldn't understand!
You could never understand the feelings of a man who's never been popular his entire life!
Don't get in the way of my love life!
You didn't come here to work, but to date?
No wonder your art has gotten worse.
Sorry for barging in.
Nakai's useless right now.
But what will happen with Aoki, then?
What exactly do I want to do?
I know that Aoki isn't bending or changing her opinion.
It may seem cold to other people.
But I think with what I draw, I can turn it around into something with passion.
Mashiro.
Wait, Takagi!
You were the one who asked for my help!
I'm saying I'll cooperate!
I'm sorry it turned out like this.
It's fine...
If Aoki models...
I have to hurry and shut him up.
I know, how about a swimsuit?
I'll draw something great for you!
Aoki, are you listening?
You should think about what poses are best—
Shut up, Gonzalez!
Her manga doesn't need to go that far!
I will teach her how to draw panty shots!
Fukuda!
Why is Fukuda here?
I heard from Mashiro.
Well?
What will you do?
You'll teach her?
What about your own serialization?
I can coach her while drawing.
I can check her rough sketches through faxes.
In return, I'll be tougher on her manuscript than the worst editor.
Fukuda...
Would it be humiliating to be taught by me?
Well, I suppose so.
Please do.
Ah, okay.
Aoki and Fukuda?
This is a powerful combo...
This is too cruel...
I'm heading out to meet with Ashirogi.
He doesn't seem too happy, even though Tanto  got 1st place.
Business Boy Kenichi  hasn't been doing so well lately.
Hello, this is the Weekly Shounen Jack editorial department.
Hey, Hattori!
You've got a call!
Oh, Taninaka! It's been a while.
You seem to be doing well.
I thought for sure that they'd be working you to death.
Well, thanks.
You're working at Novel Pleiades, right?
Yeah, they're working us hard here, but not as hard as you.
Actually,
_Green Graduation
.Akina Aiko
Pleiades Amateur Novel Contest Winner
I have a bit of a favor to ask you, as a former classmate.
A favor?
You're helping out Aoki Kou?
Yeah.
I don't think it's manly to hide things like this, so I'm letting you know.
What do you mean by 'helping out'?
I'm primarily coaching her on panty shots, but I'll check over her storyboards through faxes, too.
That's her editor's job!
There are things that manga authors know better than editors.
But do you even have the luxury to do that?
KIYOSHI  is—
I won't let KIYOSHI 's popularity drop!
If it does, you'll just blame me for helping her.
I'll make sure KIYOSHI  becomes even more popular than it is now!
How's that for you?!
And don't go thinking I've got feelings for her, or something.
If I had to choose, I'd say I hate her.
I can't believe you'd go so far for someone you hate.
She participated in my boycott, remember?
I'll help her out if she's in trouble!
It was back when we were assisting Master Niizuma.
I told this to Mashiro and Nakai:
"We'll change Jack!"
That's so cool!
Don't open the door
without prior
warning! Knock first.
Master Niizuma, Ashirogi Muto, Aoki Kou, Hiramaru Kazuya,
and Nakai Takurou.
With this many of us, anything's possible!
Change Jack, huh?
Oh yeah, at first, Niizuma said, "If I become the author of the most popular manga,
give me the authority to end one manga I hate!"
The same guy who said that has been apathetic ever since TRAP  was canceled,
and he's even been overtaken by Otters 11  recently...
Team Fukuda, huh?
If it raises competition between the authors, then...
Alright. I approve of Team Fukuda!
I knew you'd get it, man! I'm glad I told you!
Hey! Show some more respect!
Could you at least flush, Fukuda?
Do you have a favorite shounen manga?
Not really.
Do you read a lot of shounen manga?
I've read Jack for about four years now.
It looks like you attend the same college as Aoki Kou, and you also went to middle school with Ashirogi.
Yes.
May I ask a blunt question?
And that would be?
Do you truly want to write a manga
manuscript to become Takagi's rival?
I heard about it from Taninaka.
You are particularly aware of Takagi.
I won't ask why you view him as your rival.
But frankly, you're a complete novice when it comes to manga.
If you want to compete with Takagi, you'll have to do as I say.
If I listen to you, can I beat him?
We won't know until we try,
but when Takagi and Mashiro first submitted a manuscript, I was the one who met with them.
A completed manga manuscript is completely different from just a written story,
but I feel the same level of talent with you as I did with them back then.
I'm glad.
But this story is based on feelings; it doesn't have any action, so it will never become a manga.
You have to redo it all.
It will take time. Are you still willing to do it?
Yes.
Alright then, try marking your work like this to divide it into pages...
for when it's time to draw the art.
I understand.
I'll have it done by tonight.
Well, by tomorrow is fine.
Okay.
She's got spirit.
I think she can do it.
Okay, let's go with this for chapter one.
I'll put in as many gags as I can think of up until the serialization meeting.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Keep going at this pace for two more chapters.
Anyway, as long as you have three chapters, you'll most likely be serialized.
What do you mean?
There aren't many manuscripts being put up for consideration at the next meeting.
With a 2nd place one-shot in Jack, Arai's Hustlemin Ace  is a shoe-in,
and since you were first in NEXT, you guys are also pretty much guaranteed a spot.
Is that how it is?
Yeah.
Since Aoki's manga got 2nd in NEXT, it'll be tried out again as a Jack one-shot.
So even if the storyboard isn't so great, we'll get serialized anyway?
I definitely want to avoid getting serialized and canceled right away!
That's right! Let's make a three chapter serialization storyboard that we can all be proud of!
Yes!
For Miyoshi, too!
Yeah.
Well then, let's decide on the invention for the 3rd chapter!
I want to bring in Ms. Noa,
so how about contact lenses that
make clothes look transparent?!
Oh, all guys would want a pair.
But that might be a bit cliché.
Then how about the "Chef Hat"?
While you're wearing it, any meal, even a school lunch, becomes a three course French dinner!
Oh!
They ask Ms. Noa for help, and have her wear a maid apron.
But the apron makes her want to wait on tables dressed in a miniskirt!
The grandpa, Chotto, wants to see her in the miniskirt and...
That's good.
We still have time.
Let's make it as funny as we can!
Yes!
Would you show me that list of inventions?
This?
I wrote down whatever popped into my head, so it's pretty stupid.
It's my job to expand on those stupid ideas.
Business Boy Kenichi  will be in danger at the next serialization meeting.
I've got no choice but to bet it all on Hirameki Tanto !
How many times do I have to tell you not to do it this way?
Y-You don't have to say it so violently.
I'm the teacher here!
Don't complain!
I told you not to show upskirt in weird ways!
It doesn't fit your manga!
All you need to do is show normal stuff, like changing clothes and bathing!
That's why I put in a changing scene right before a bath!
Why would you see up someone's skirt from a low angle while they're changing for a bath?
That's weird!
Even if you don't have a knack for this, you should be able to see that!
Are you following me?
Here, you should either show the panties at her ankles,
or from an upwards view as she takes them off her legs!
That's  how to express getting changed for a bath!
Please hold on, I'm taking notes.
Just memorize it! You're going to a good college, aren't you?
Shut up! My college has nothing to do with this!
And why is she lost in thought while washing herself?
That doesn't happen!
It's a girl washing herself.
Shouldn't that make guys happy?
In these kinds of scenes, she'd usually be in the bathtub already!
Do you lose yourself in thought while scrubbing your ass?!
Ass?
Please watch your language!
Ah, sorry.
While scrubbing your butt—
Hey, that's the same thing!
No, it's pretty different!
Um, while washing your ass...
No, bathtub, bathtub...
Listen, fix the parts I pointed out to you by tomorrow.
What? That's impossible!
In an hour, it'll already be  tomorrow!
You're aiming to get serialized, right?
You'd better draw all night!
Don't say lack of sleep is bad for your skin, or something.
I won't.
I'll do my best.
Good girl.
Aoki Kou. A mysterious author.
She seems like a different person with each manuscript.
Yeah, really.
It's becoming more and more like a shounen manga.
Did she hire someone to help her?
Maybe. A college friend, perhaps?
What do you think?
Since it's gotten this good,
I'm thinking of submitting it to the serialization committee instead of doing a one-shot.
Yeah.
If she can make three chapters that are this good.
All right!
Wow, I can't believe things are going this well for me, even though it's only my first year!
Huh? Aoki's, too?
Yeah, it looks like her manuscript's gonna be submitted to the serialization committee.
I coached her on panty shots.
She'll be a formidable enemy!
Of course, the best thing would be for you both to get serialized.
Don't lose.
Go for it!
Master Niizuma and I are waiting.
Okay.
We'll definitely score a serialization this time!
I never thought Aoki would be in the mix, too.
Fukuda must really be something.
It's fine! I'm kinda fired up now!
I feel kinda bad for Miura,
but since we're up against such a formidable rival, it'll feel even better when we get serialized!
Yeah!
Right, let's go for it!
Tomorrow's the big day.
Yes.
I believe it's all thanks to you that I've made it to the serialization committee.
Thank you.
It's too early for thanks.
The real challenge comes after you get serialized.
I know.
My editor told me that I need
more practice with drawing people.
Yeah, because your art kinda sucks.
It's not as bad as yours, though.
Oh, now you've done it.
My editor told me to aim to be better than Ashirogi...
but I have mixed feelings about that.
They're friends, as well as rivals.
Isn't that what we always say?
I told Ashirogi not to lose to you.
I'll say the same to you.
Don't lose to them!
Do your best.
Okay.
I will.
What's this?
We've got this many editors, but they could only scrape together eight storyboards?
I'll tell the lead editors to encourage them.
Oh, excuse me. May I see the commentary on the storyboards?
Let's see.
Ashirogi's, where's Ashirogi's?
Oh, there it is.
Huh?
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
Tanto's  serialization will be decided in this committee!
I'm worried about Nakai, too.
I wonder what'll happen with Takahama's serialization.
Everyone's at a crucial moment!
Next time on Bakuman:
Special Relationship and
Hometown
Special Relationship and Hometown.
Even if your dream's been shattered, never give up!