Kiyoshi Knight
To Mashiro
Perfect Crime Club
is good.
But... it can't win.
I don't think it can beat CROW
and +NATURAL.
Th-Then, with a majority vote of 3 for Win and 4 for Lose,
Ashirogi Muto's Perfect Crime Club
will not be serialized...
Wait a minute!
What is it, Oonishi?
If we don't pass Ashirogi here, they won't be able to draw for Jack anymore, right?
Yes, that's the reason for this vote.
I... I want to change my vote!
Ch-Change it?
Hey!
That makes it 4 against 3.
Now Ashirogi passes, right?
It's ridiculous for us to let Ashirogi go based on a vote in the first place!
We should take better care of our authors!
That's right. We're in a position to influence the lives of our authors.
Well...
It would be a different story if the vote was 7 to 0,
but to abandon our authors over such a
narrow margin may not be the right thing to do.
Heishi?
I judged they would lose,
but we should leave this decision to the readers, after all.
I cast my vote for them to win.
No, I want them to win.
Leave the decision to the readers, huh?
That's what we've always done.
I'll also change my vote to win.
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Expression and Imagination
Here it is!
Answer it.
Hurry.
Congratulations!
Perfect Crime Club
will be serialized!
All right!
That's the news for now! Details will come later!
Okay!
Let's get to celebrating! I'll get the cake!
Yeah!
Yo, it looks like you've got yourself a serialization.
I'll congratulate you, just for today.
Thank you!
Now we can compete with you again!
Yeah, bring it on!
I'm looking forward to your first chapter!
Congratulations!
Niizuma!
Now our real battle begins.
Thank you!
It's thanks to you that we were able to come this far!
What do you mean?
Ever since we saw your name listed as a Tezuka prize finalist at a convenience store back in middle school,
we made you our rival and pledged to overtake you.
We decided to stop Tanto
and aim higher because you were there as our rival.
Indeed.
Ashirogi and I are fated rivals.
"Eternal rivals".
It should be written as "formidable
enemy" but pronounced as "friend".
Or something like that.
Niizuma!
We're going to put everything we've
learned into this one, so we'll win for sure!
So you have confidence in it, then?
Then I shall return to work.
A rival, huh.
I'm getting all tense now.
Yeah.
Hey now.
Let's put the complicated stuff on hold for now and get to celebrating!
Yeah!
Oh, that's mine.
Aoki!
Here.
Mashiro gets the piece with the chocolate.
Hello?
Thank you!
It's Azuki's homemade cake!
They're both really happy with being serialized in Jack!
What is it?
Something's inside...
To Mashiro-kun
A USB stick?
Oh, Miho prepared this kind of surprise?
Akito, bring your computer over here.
Well, is it alright for the two of us to see it?
Yeah. It's a bit embarrassing, but it's fine.
She said it's fine!
All right!
To Mashiro-kun
Mashiro, your birthday present made me really happy.
Thanks.
Because I received a drawing from Mashiro, the manga artist,
I'll give you a vocal present, as a voice actress.
Huh? Just her voice?
I thought it was a video letter.
Be quiet, Kaya.
I can't hear it.
Has she gotten better at singing?
Oh yeah, she did say she was going to learn how to sing.
Do we absolutely positively have to wait until our dream
comes true?
Azuki Miho
Nickname: Amame
Dream for the future
Voice Actress
Oh, there's been an editor change?
The Chief Editor noticed, after all...
Chief, can I have a moment?
What is it?
I'm very sorry!
Have you do something you need to apologize for?
U-Um... for Perfect Crime Club
!
I submitted it as if it was all my work, but I had Hattori help me...
I deserve to be removed from it!
It is not a bad thing to receive the advice of others.
Of course, that is only if you are willing to cast aside your pride and listen carefully to the person offering advice.
This serialization is a result of you taking action to help Ashirogi.
Well done.
Chief...
Well, I could tell that Hattori played a large part in it.
And he also understands Ashirogi well.
That's why I decided to leave them to him.
Now, I suppose it's time for you to return the favor.
It looks like he's having some troubles.
Huh? We're getting a new editor?
Again?
Now that we just got serialized...
It's not a bad thing.
In fact, you should be happy.
We should?
It's Hattori.
Hattori?!
We're getting Hattori back?!
But Miura, you've done so much for us,
and we finally got this far together...
I told you, it's okay to be happy.
Miura...
It is frustrating to get a different assignment now,
but it worked out so that Hattori and I have swapped places.
I'll be in charge of +NATURAL.
Make Perfect Crime Club
a big hit with Hattori!
And then we'll duke it out!
Yes.
We definitely won't lose!
To you or to Niizuma!
Or Akina Aiko!
Right! We won't lose, either!
Shujin, I'm going to our studio!
How nice... it feels like a man's world!
Yeah!
Why the long face?
Is it really okay for me to be Ashirogi's editor?
Just be happy!
This is what you wanted, right?
That's why I did all that... but now it
seems selfish, and I feel bad about it...
You're too serious.
But really, Ashirogi overcame some huge obstacles.
I hope Fukuda understands this and
doesn't get any crazy ideas...
Yeah!
We won't lose, either!
Shouldn't you take a break, at least for today?
Just kidding!
Hattori!
Lets head over to Ashirogi's now!
Now?
Yeah!
They've been waiting for you all this time!
Right, the earlier the better.
Okay.
I guess we should.
Congratulations!
Everyone from kids to housewives are snatching up Otter figures!
Oh! I did hear some rumors about that!
And now, it's time for "This week's Aoki Kou!"
Ta-da!
Aoki wants...
She wants...
I want...
An Otter figure!
Then I'll sign one of each kind and give them all to her personally!
No... she told me to give it to her editor.
Aoki!
This is Hiramaru.
Good evening.
It looks like the Otters
anime is doing well.
Yes, it does.
And, well...
I asked my editor about this, but...
Here it comes...
Do you know about that "secret" Otter figure?
Of course! You can exchange the hands with real limestone!
That's the one. My assistant really wants it.
Your assistant?
Mr. Yoshida? What's this all about?
Huh?
Mr. Yoshida?
Hey, you two!
Congrats on your serialization!
Thank you!
Hattori, I'm glad to be working with you again!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm happy, too.
"Perfect Crime
Club"
First Chapter
Ashirogi Muto
We're about to look over it again, starting with chapter one.
I see.
I think the first chapter can get first place.
Really?
Right, of course.
It got serialized because they judged it
could win over Niizuma's manga, after all.
Actually...
It seems like they took a vote on whether this
manga could win over CROW
and +NATURAL.
The result was 4 vs. 3 for Lose.
But there's plenty of potential for you to win from here on out.
That's why it got serialized.
4 vs. 3 for lose...
It won't be enough to just look it over again.
We need to rewrite it so anyone can agree that we'll win!
Yeah!
Hey now! You don't have enough time to rewrite it!
It's okay. We'll make it work.
Putting this zeal into their manga...
This is Ashirogi Muto!
So we need battles after all?
CROW
may have battles,
but +NATURAL
has storylines that don't.
Hattori, where do you think we're losing to Eiji?
Let's see...
If I had to say, it would be his expressiveness.
The way he uses perspective and sound effects.
The feelings and representations of the
characters are straightforward and full-bodied,
and his dialogue is polished and easy to understand.
He gets inside the characters.
On the other hand, you beat him in your
sketching. Mashiro's realistic art is better than his.
There's also the sheer amount of Takagi's ideas.
Miura, do you have the novel version of +NATURAL
on you?
Yes.
Since I'm their editor now, I carry a copy with me.
Can you show it to us?
Yeah.
The original book for the super-popular
"+NATURAL" currently serialized in
Weekly Shounen Jack!!
Akina Aiko
The real story written by
the receiver of the amateur award of Novel Pleiades
She wrote it herself?
Yes, at Akina's urging,
it will be made available soon after the new year.
But the content is pretty much the same as the manuscripts Niizuma received.
He cuts out the unneeded parts in the manuscript...
and inserts new scenes as necessary.
If you compare the two,
you'll see that Niizuma's expressiveness made +NATURAL
much better.
Yeah.
He's done so much with it, I'd say this is
more about his imagination than his expression.
I see. Imagination, huh?
Also, the way he uses the space in his panel layouts...
Panels with no dialogue.
Something...
Panels with nothing but scenery.
Panels where he zooms out and shows the whole picture.
Silent closeups of characters.
Readers can freely give it their own interpretation.
It engages their imagination.
Certainly...
Is this because I don't put blank panels in my storyboards?
No, I put them in myself later,
but they're few and far between.
Right. You both need to consider
your panel choices more carefully.
Yes.
Um, Hattori...
Oh, sorry.
We jumped straight into a meeting without officially handing it over...
Oh, I don't mind that at all.
Actually, I'm glad.
I'll get going, then.
Miura...
We haven't even properly thanked you yet.
Thank you for all you've done.
If we work together in the future, please take care of us!
Yeah, go for it!
I'll try hard, too!
Miura.
Yes?
Thanks.
I'm glad I could come here right away.
Thanks to you, my doubts are gone.
Hattori,
I'll take what you've done with +NATURAL and use that popularity to my advantage.
I won't lose to you!
Yeah, bring it on!
Thank you!
Jumping straight into such an
advanced meeting... they're amazing.
I'll work hard so that I can reach their level soon!
Well then, Miura, you can take it from here.
Yes, leave it to me!
Well, let's start our meeting.
Even if it's only for work, it's nice to be meeting with such a pretty girl!
Don't be ridiculous!
The next time you say something like that, I'll sue you for sexual harassment!
Sorry!
I've made up my mind.
What?
Please don't sue me...
Takagi and Hattori cast me aside...
I won't lose to anyone anymore.
I won't fall in love anymore!
I will be the best author in the business!
The best!
And you
are my editor!
You'd better act like it!
I-I understand.
Mom, I feel sorry for him.
Can I really do this?
Don't look at them!
Drawings that get you inside the characters, huh?
Putting in blank spaces and sound effects, too...
It's all difficult.
Is it that hard?
Yeah.
No matter how much we revise, I
don't think we can beat Eiji's sense for it.
What?
If I can let my imagination flow like Eiji's...
and express Shujin's storyboards better...
Huh? It's from Hattori.
How's it going? When do you think you'll have the storyboard done by?
Hattori, aren't you on vacation?
Until January 6th, right?
Hey now.
You're rewriting your storyboard, right?
I can't afford to take it easy.
I'll come see it when you're done.
Well, maybe not on New Year's day.
Sorry about that... it feels like we're
making you go along with our schedule.
Hattori is a really nice guy.
Then how about on the 2nd?
Huh? Don't you have to redo 52 pages?
Yeah, but we'll get it done!
All right, then. I'll contact you after noon on the 2nd.
Bye.
Oh, he's here.
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
This is Miura, the editor who will be taking over +NATURAL.
I'm Miura Goro.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you were Ashirogi's editor, right?
I'm happy to meet you!
However! You shouldn't have made them write a cliché gag manga!
Ashirogi's all about realistic stories with realistic art!
Y-You're right.
The next one they're doing is like that.
Perfect Crime Club
!
It suits them perfectly!
Good job on getting them there!
You did it, Miura!
Yeah, I guess...
This time around, Ashirogi will be a tough opponent.
With a manga that can compete with mine: Perfect Crime Club.
I'm sure it has serious humor along with serious art.
And the protagonist must be someone just like Takagi!
Hattori, did you tell him what it was about?
And they'll do this... and that!
No, I didn't tell him anything.
He must have ESP.
Akina and Niizuma...
With them as my partners, I'll definitely grow!
Miura!
Let's work hard so that we don't lose to Ashirogi!
Yeah, that's right!
Let's do it!
Imagination... blank spaces... and sound effects.
It probably comes to Eiji naturally.
Like how he turns a script into a manga.
Shujin's script shouldn't be any worse than Iwase's!
What is it, Takagi?
Um, Mashiro's saying some weird stuff.
Please come over and talk to him, if you can.
Weird stuff?
All right, I'll be over soon.
He's saying he wants the story in script-only format!
Script only?
Even though I know how to do paneling now...
Isn't this a step backwards?
I get it, Mashiro!
Right!
With just a script, I can use my imagination!
I always feel constrained by the storyboard.
I'd rather just be given a script so that I can draw freely!
I can put the blank panels where I want!
Only if Takagi's okay with it, of course.
I can't say for sure if that'll make it better.
No, maybe doing it that way will give me more time to write out details on the characters' emotions.
What do you think, Hattori?
It's worth a shot.
You should do it!
Okay!
What was I worried about?
We do work well together, after all.
They're relying on me!
I can aim for the top with them!
Yuujirou!
I started drawing a new one-shot.
Huh?
What're you saying?
KIYOSHI
's rating is below Master Niizuma and Hiramaru's, and just about even with Aoki's.
If I let Ashirogi pass me, too, we won't be the "Fukuda Team" any more!
That's not true!
You can still aim higher!
And if this one-shot affects your serialization...
Of course I won't let KIYOSHI
slip!
Well, yeah, that would be...
I'll write this 45 page one shot while continuing with KIYOSHI
as usual.
I'll draw straight through the New Year's holiday without a break!
All right. If you're this determined, then I'll support you.
Just you wait, Ashirogi Muto!
toomawari wo eranda no wa
The reason I chose to take a detour
motto kimi wo suki ni naru tame datta n da
was to fall ever deeper in love with you
boku no namae yobu sono koe wo
I have a feeling I've always known
zutto zutto shitteta ki ga shita n da
what your voice sounds like when it calls my name
boku no yubisaki de egaita
With my fingertips I drew
subete no sen wa kimi ni tsuzuku kakehashi sa
many lines that make up a suspension bridge leading to you
Show me the way
Show me the way I'm sure our path
bokura no michi kitto
Believe in your way
your way connects us without any turns
hitosuji ni tsunagari
Show me the way
Show me the way It leads to the place where we promised
yakusoku no basho e tsuzuku
Show me the way
Show me the way I will never give up
akirametari shinaide
Believe in your way
your way Raise your gaze
sono hitomi wo agete
Show me the way
Show me the way and see that we're certain to meet again
bokura wa massugu deau sa
Next Time
Preview
Our serialization finally begins!
We'll definitely beat Niizuma Eiji!
But what about Fukuda's one-shot?
Next time on Bakuman:
Votes and
Charts
Votes and Charts.
An inherited dream can become even bigger!