Congratulations on the discharge.
Congratulations!
Th-Thank you. Sorry for making you all worry.
I baked some cookies, so if you'd like...
Thank you.
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Resumption and Low-Rank
This is my share for today.
Oh, thanks.
TRAP chapter 20 will continue from where it left off with the front page color spread, right?
Yes, starting from issue 45.
Chapter 20 Restart
Color
It means they have high expectations of you!
I sure hope so.
We're done for the day, but should we come back next week as usual?
You have quite a few manuscripts piled up.
I was wondering if we should really draw so far ahead.
We'll decide what to do in our meeting today.
I see. Well then, if you'll excuse me.
Thanks for your work.
Aren't you leaving yet, Takahama?
No, I'll stay a bit longer.
Okay. See you later.
Thanks for coming.
Um... there's something I want you two to see.
What? You're not going to high school?
Nope.
We're best friends, right?
You bet.
Promise you won't tell anyone?
Don't tell me something you don't want others to know.
Then just hear me out.
Fine.
I got 300 million yen...
Okay.
What? You should be more surprised!
I guess I should be.
You know how my dad passed away last year?
He was running a pretty big company, so I inherited well over 300 mil.
Even after the inheritance tax.
Anyway, where did you get the 300 mil?
My old man bought 200 lottery tickets and told me "I'll give you half if I win".
He ended up winning two 300 mil jackpots.
Two?! Impossible!
Now that's a surprise!
So I decided that I'm not going to high school.
You serious? Are you gonna play around with that cash for the rest of your life?
I don't think it'll last a lifetime.
Playing around all day would make me a failure.
I'm starting a business!
Miura said he'd submit it to the monthly contest in September...
What do you think?
I think it's awesome.
Really?
Yeah.
I think it's really good for a one shot.
I love the way it ends, personally.
Business Boy Ken'ichi can definitely win!
I'm starting to feel more confident about it!
Thank you. Good luck with your meeting.
Okay!
It might not be long before he's our new rival.
I hope so.
What?!
Kyoichi Murasaki's writing a detective manga in Shounen Week?
He's a prolific detective novel writer!
The title is Detective Gosuke Akechi.
I just heard it from Hattori.
In addition to that, Mr. Hibiki's manga, Phantom Thief Cheater,
is also slated to begin next week.
Phantom Cheater...
We'll be after the same audience for sure!
There's nothing we can do.
TRAP  was supposed to be canceled.
But TRAP 's success is what caused this detective manga boom.
The first volume of TRAP sold more than 200,000 copies over three reprints.
What?
200,000?
Yeah, and the serialization is resuming.
The second volume is set to be published in November.
Also, these are for you.
During your hospital stay,
we received these fan letters from people waiting for you to resume TRAP.
Whoa...
More proof of TRAP's popularity.
For now, let's publish the completed manuscripts.
Don't push yourselves too hard before you graduate.
You can just pace yourself at one chapter every two weeks.
Got it.
Oh, and I convinced them to increase the recap for the returning chapter from one to three pages.
Thank goodness.
I was worried about our readers forgetting the story.
It just shows that the Editorial Department has high hopes for you.
Let's do our best.
Yeah!
Rice Balls
Yen
All
How is it?
It's like he turned a detective novel into a manga.
Shounen Week
Detective
Akechi Gosuke
Authentic
A high-level work!
Better than TRAP ?
Don't ask like that...
Mashiro
Shounen Jack
Series Resumes!!
Detective
Ashirogi Muto
It feels great to have your manga in Jack, huh?
And it's even on the front page!
Chapter 20 ranked 4th in the early results!
4th?
That's great!
Your fans really were waiting for you!
Wait, weren't we trying to beat Eiji with this front page color spread?
There you go again.
Don't be so greedy.
But CROW  is almost certainly going to rank higher than 3rd.
Maybe even 1st or 2nd.
By the way, doesn't that CROW anime start today?
The night is painting the town pitch black
Where light falls asleep, this is Holy World!
If you can't stand watching, then just close your eyes
If you can't stand this place, then just fly away
Not into someone else's sky
Ohh! It's so nice seeing manga move.
That's what anime is all about.
But into the sky your heart points to
Man, they really put effort into the opening song.
Now CROW  will really take off and sell over a million prints per volume.
One day, we'll make an anime for TRAP, too!
Don't get so depressed.
The most votes would obviously go to Cheater, the new series.
But going from 4th in chapter 20 to 12th in chapter 21 is too big of a drop...
Shounen Jack
Grand Appearance!!!!
____________ Magnificent
New Series
Phantom
Shounen Jack
Grand Appearance!!!!
____________ Magnificent
New Series
Phantom
Miura.
Yes?
You'll just make Ashirogi worry even more with that attitude of yours.
The voters went for Cheater  this week.
Nothing we can do about that.
12th place wasn't uncommon when we were just starting out.
Let's climb up again, one step at a time.
But falling to 12th from 4th is quite a shock.
It is...
The serialization meeting is at the end of the month, right?
Yeah. October 28th.
Hey now, don't worry so much!
But depending on the results from the next two chapters before the meeting...
The case-concluding chapter will be published right before the meeting!
No worries! Let's just do what we've been doing, all right?
Do you really think we should keep drawing?
It'd be all for nothing if we got canceled.
Don't jinx it.
Takahama is still here.
Oh, my bad.
Takagi, Mashiro.
Yes?
I was runner-up in the monthly contest with Ken'ichi, the one I showed you before!
Oh! That's amazing!
Congratulations!
It'll be published in the December 5th issue, the first issue of the year!
Great! It was interesting, so I'm sure you'll do well!
I hope so.
I'm kind of jealous.
Don't say that when you're the one being serialized!
Right.
We'll do our best to maintain our ranking.
Detective TRAP
Manga
Even the case-concluding chapter we were counting on was ranked so low...
It's time. Let's get going.
It's gonna be a depressing meeting today.
I was warned that we won't be safe in the next meeting.
What?!
I guess that isn't surprising.
Only 14th place with the case-concluding chapter...
Series lasting over 10 weeks are usually warned this way.
Cheater and hideout door are in the same position.
Hi-door too?!
Yeah, the latest survey results weren't that great.
They're warning us...
So basically, they're telling us to do something about it before the next meeting, right?
It needs major fixing?
That's our only choice.
Comedy elements and captivating lines...
We've done what we could.
All we have left is...
Battles, huh?
This is not what we agreed on!
"Phantom Cheater" Author
Hibiki Kyotaro
We started this because TRAP  was supposed to be on hiatus until April!
We're just at each other's throats!
This is fraud, damn it!
I'll be a laughing stock if they cancel my manga like this.
Do something about it!
Manga...
just need to be interesting to be popular!
Don't blame everything on TRAP and do nothing but complain!
Why you...
Think of ways to make your own work more interesting!
What's with this fight? It's over!
On the contrary! This is just the beginning!
The hiatus was a big blow to our popularity, after all.
Battles...
Takagi
Sorry, did I wake you?
No, I'm still at work.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I know.
So, what is it?
Can I come over right now?
Fan letters?
Yep.
There are suggestions in our fan letters, right?
Let's add these ideas to our work.
Hold on.
Most of them were written by girls.
They'll be biased.
But they're definitely our biggest fans.
Readers who send us fan letters would definitely vote for surveys too, right?
That may be true, but...
I don't want to force battles into our manga.
It feels like we'd be destroying the characters we made.
But at this rate...
We should try whatever we can, huh?
We don't want TRAP to end, no matter what.
That's right!
Niizuma
Eiji Ltd.
A phone call when I'm on a roll. How annoying!
Mr. Fukuda?
I hear Nakai and Ashirogi will be in danger in the next meeting.
I wonder if there's anything we can do to help...
What are you talking about?
Well, they'll both be finished at this rate...
If it was an unfair cancellation, I'd agree with you...
but it's a whole different story this time.
What?
There's nothing I can do for them now.
It's survival of the fittest.
Ashirogi Muto
Japan
"I want to see more of TRAP's school life" is the most common request.
Let's see what characters they like the most and give them bigger roles.
Yeah.
It's already Saturday, but we can finish the storyboard on Sunday, right?
Probably.
I wonder if Nakai and Aoki are thinking of ways to fix up their manga, too?
It's already 3 o'clock.
There's nothing I can do to change your mind?
If my manga will end unless I compromise my principles even further,
then I would rather end it myself.
No, you can't let it end!
Yeah. I understand how you feel.
Don't agree with her!
What do you think, Nakai?
I-I don't want it end, no matter what I have to do.
We've worked so hard for this.
We should try to continue...
But you know...
Change her mind, dammit!
Series Name Chapter 28
___ Aoki Ko
I don't mind you two coming up with the plot.
However, make it clear to the readers that Ko Aoki is not longer the writer...
and credit yourselves.
We can't possibly...
I-I'd like to try if you'd let me!
Nakai...
Change the title, too.
W-Wait, Aoki! We'll go with this storyboard!
I'm sorry we didn't finish the storyboard until Sunday.
What is this?
Who came up with this story?
It was me...
Don't give me that!
This is not  your storyboard, Takagi-kun!
I really was  the one who came up with it.
It's just that I read all our fan letters and took some of their ideas.
So that's what happened.
That's the last thing you want to do.
It's okay to add ideas that match perfectly with your work and values.
Actually, that's the ideal approach.
But if you include everything,
it'll just turn into a big mess!
If you keep succumbing to fan requests,
it will be a manga made by fans, not Ashirogi Muto!
Got it?
Yes.
Not only that, these fan letters are mostly sent by girls.
But you're serialized in Shounen Jack.
Even if you have female fans,
they're girls who were drawn in by shounen manga.
Weekly Manga Magazine
Shounen
Making interesting shounen manga is what being a Jack manga author is all about.
Fine, forget about battles.
Series Meeting
You have five chapters until the serialization meeting.
The current arc has three chapters left.
Chapter 26
Chapter 27
Chapter 28
Chapter 26
Chapter 27
Chapter 28
Chapter 26
Chapter 27
Chapter 28
You don't need to change that part.
Let's bet on the remaining two chapters.
Chapter 29
Chapter 30
Draw what you think is most interesting with everything you've got!
Okay!
We will!
It's that bad?
Yeah.
I'll definitely turn things around, though.
When's the next serialization meeting?
December 16th.
What? So soon?
Watch it!
Hey.
Hiramaru!
Where did you get this car?
I bought it. It's a German import.
I took out a loan, though.
That's quite a purchase.
Yeah, I was looking at a magazine ad, and Mr. Yoshida said...
All About
German Cars
You can probably afford a car by now.
It should come in handy when you want to take a breather.
His idea. It has built-in GPS.
With a car like this...
You should move to a condo with parking in the basement.
So I took his recommendation and moved.
The rent's pretty expensive, though.
I hate to say this...
Huh?
But you totally fell for his scheme.
You'll have to pay a lot of taxes next year.
He's getting you to spend more than you have so that you can't get out of drawing manga.
A classic scheme.
Th-That's crazy!
I knew about the taxes.
Mr. Yoshida, did you trick me?
Italian cars are nice, too!
Well, you know... There's been talk about an anime adaptation for Otters 11.
Really?
But it hasn't been confirmed.
Anyway, I've taken my breather,
so I guess I'll get back to my posh condo and do some work!
Sent Mail
Azuki Miho
Miho
Happy birthday!
An anime adaptation, huh?
Shujin always supported me in getting an anime adaptation by the time I turned 18...
Sent Mail
You Have New Mail
Azuki Miho
I got the voice-over role for the daughter
in US TV drama "Doctor Family" on BS!
It's a side character, but I'll do my best.
Amazing. Azuki keeps getting more work.
CROW 's anime has already started, and even Otters might...
Yet TRAP is...
The case-concluding chapter 27 is...
17th...
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's an honor to be published in Jack with you.
I think I'll buy 10 issues on Monday!
Sending 10 surveys back by yourself is cheating!
What are you talking about, Miyoshi?
I think he'll get more votes than TRAP, anyway.
If we don't show some results in the next survey, TRAP  will...
Friday, December 16th
Day of Series Meeting
Now that the new series have been decided,
we'll move on to the termination meeting.
Most likely, two of the three story-driven titles will be dropped this time.
We gave them a warning and their ranks stayed low. We have no choice.
That's right. The terminated series this time are hideout door...
as well as...
Takagi
You're not going to the studio?
We don't want to hear their decision in front of our assistants.
Then I'll leave for today, too...
Stay with us.
Takagi...
Here it comes!
Hello, Takagi speaking.
Five more weeks...
before... termination?
It's over.
Of course.
We were 15th in chapter 29.
Only hi-door was below us in chapter 30.
The meeting starts at 10.
It's not going to be pleasant.
It's my fault.
It's because I was hospitalized.
Stop blaming yourself.
Cheer up... I guess you can't, huh?
Sorry.
Thanks, but my mind is blank right now.
Mine too.
It's so frustrating.
Yeah.
We couldn't beat Eiji.
An anime adaptation by age 18 is no longer...
Nakai
Unfortunately, it's terminated.
What?
Aoki and I will decide how we wrap things up.
That is all.
Damn it!
Why?! Why...
Calm down, sir...
I see. I understand.
About how we wrap things up...
Can I draw the ending my own way?
Okay. It might lead to your next title.
No. I'm thinking of going back to shoujo manga after the completion of this series.
Aoki is probably finished with Jack.
What a shame. She's such a beauty.
Yamahisa...
Aida, let me handle her if you don't intend to.
Aoki Ko is a handful.
A rookie in his second year can't...
Don't worry, I'll make her fall for me.
You'll have to talk to the higher-ups for that.
I will, then.
Not yet!
Wait until after the series ends!
I see.
What a shame.
Um, do you know who the authors for the new serializations are?
Not yet...
I'm sorry.
I thought I might be able to find work there.
No, I understand.
Okay, let's do our best for the remaining three chapters.
Yes!
Family Restaurant
Open 24 Hours
Regarding what to do with the remaining three chapters...
We can try two patterns.
Either continue with the best mystery you can think of for TRAP  and go for a similar genre again...
or try new things and go for different genres.
Decide which route...
You're probably not in the mood for a meeting right now.
I'm sorry.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Just decide on which pattern you'll go with.
Okay.
It's been nice working with you.
Likewise.
I've learned so much.
Please let me know when you start another series.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
All right. Okay!
Want to grab a bite?
No, we're fine...
I see.
Let's aim for a long series next time!
See you.
Final Chapter Manuscript UP
It's over.
It feels like graduation.
I have a sense of accomplishment and other mixed feelings...
But the strongest feeling is sadness.
Frustration is still number one for me.
Now that I think of it, we're pretty amazing.
What do you mean?
We're just high school students, but we were serialized in Jack.
Yeah, that is amazing.
Eiji is even more amazing, though.
Don't mention that.
My bad.
To Azuki?
Yeah, I have to tell her.
She'll be shocked.
How'd you like the storyboards for final three chapters?
I think it was a good idea trying out new things.
The assistants liked it too.
I see.
But is it really going to lead to our next title?
You Have New Mail
[From] Azuki Miho
[Sub] Re: Unfortunately...
Hello...
On graduation day I said...
"I'll wait forever"
But I want to get married by 40!!
Of course, to you.
What did Azuki say?
Let's lead it to our next title.
Huh? Did Azuki cheer you up?
No, she said she wants to get married before she turns 40.
I can't make her wait that long!
I'm getting fired up too for some reason!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
kurikaesu nibuku detarame na sekai
In this world, every day is dull and full of nonsense
urusakute mimi wo fusaida
I cover my ears, trying to mute the noise
nan no tame ni kizutsukeatteiruno?
Why do people hurt each other?
zetsubou ni fushita kokoro no sumi
In the contradictory, overlapping shadows
orikasanaru mujun no kage ni
on the recesses of my heart, fallen into despair
mune wo itamenagara
While carrying this pain in my chest,
ashita wo yumemireruno?
can I really dream of tomorrow?
tooriame no ato ni mitsuketa niji wo motte
Remembering the rainbow I found after the rain,
me wo tojiru Fly with me donna nagai yume mo
I close my eyes; come fly with me into my dream
iroasenai kimi to nara
If I have you, who shines so strong
egakidaseru kienai niji mo
I can envision an everlasting rainbow
deaeta ano hi ni mita tsukiakari desaemo
And even remember the moonlight of the night we met
utsuhidasu nandodemo
I can picture them... countless times
nandodemo
over and over again
Next Time
Preview
Let's work toward our next series!
But we can't come to terms with Miura on what our next title will be like.
We've gotta stand our ground, then!
Yeah!
Next time on Bakuman:
Gags and
Serious
Gags and Serious.
We need a strategy to make our dreams come true!