The serialization committee is on the 25th... you mean, Christmas?
Yeah, for some reason, it often ends up on Christmas.
The rival inventor's name is Metal Black... I like that it sounds evil.
It reminds me of the Black Demon Lord.
I thought I'd go with color related names for the villains.
I see. Black's granddaughter is "Pink",
and she's in Tanto's class.
So these two will appear at the end of chapter two.
The problem lies with the third chapter. How will they interact with the protagonist?
But if you do this well, it'll definitely be better than the last storyboard you submitted to the serialization committee.
A
Secret
Step by step
and little by little
A
Secret
Step by step
and little by little
steps
Soft
Stealthy
steps
I like how he's going to "take over the world little by little".
This pose is good, too.
We both tried to think of petty evil inventions, but it was pretty tough.
We thought of a soda that makes you want to do bad things once you drink it, called Evil Dew...
That's great!
If you combine that with the chef hat that turns a school lunch into a full course meal...
Yeah, that would be great!
Miura, that's too simple!
Let's think harder about it.
Oh, sorry.
Okay then, let's go with "Step by step, little by little".
Are we really going to be okay for the next serialization meeting?
Hey, have some confidence in your work! Don't look so down!
yume kanaeru made chousen wa tsuzuku
The fight doesn't end until I fulfill my dream
boku wa dokomade chikazuketandarou?
I wonder how far I've come now?
juunengo no mirai kagayaiteru sugata wa
In ten years, I'll be living the dream
koukai wa shinai jibun de egaita story
It's the scenario I wrote for myself, so I'll have no regrets
fumidaseba yukute habamu genjitsu
But life isn't that easy, and it's full of obstacles
makenai to ima mune ni chikatta
Still, I swear to myself that I won't ever back down
kokorozashita tsukamitai yume ga arukara
I have a dream that I absolutely want to achieve
moyashite yuke jounetsu wo atsuku
So I fuel my passion until I succeed
yume no tochuu de meguriau deai to wakare
There will be meetings and partings along the way
kimi ga oshietekureta boku dake ga motsu chikara
But I'll simply believe in my strength that you've taught me
tachiagatteikundayo nando tsumazuitatte
And rise back up again and again and again
Dream of life
Complaint and Roar
What do you think of the storyboard that MONEYS wrote?
It's wonderful!
I know now that my manuscript can become a wonderful manga!
I'm impressed!
He moved things around quite a bit; is that okay with you?
Of course it is—it's far better than my manuscript!
Please have this person do the art.
She has a lot of pride, but she's got an eye for good manga.
I asked you today to write a second chapter, but you've also done a third, and it's all very well done.
But about this "God" in "The children chosen by God"...
I think it's best to leave it as an "unknown entity of great power", since that would be more like a shounen manga.
You're right. That will also pique the readers' interest.
She's a quick learner.
I think it would be better that way.
Are there any other areas that need fixing?
We can do this!
Sorry, let me read it one more time.
If I have Niizuma make a storyboard from this,
it'll be more than good enough to pass at the serialization committee.
Can you make a manga that can compete with it...
Ashirogi Muto?
Today's Friday, so the sample of next week's issue should arrive at our office today.
Aoki's second chapter, huh?
Her first chapter got 1st place. It's really great.
I heard all her staff are female, but the art is done well, especially the backgrounds.
Oh, I heard Katou's doing that. And she's the chief assistant, at that.
Really? Katou?
Katou, I really like this background.
Thank you!
I hope I'll be able to draw as well as you soon!
Editorial Department
Shounen
Jack
Jack SQ
There's a week until the serialization committee.
This time, Tanto  will definitely pass!
There aren't any promising amateurs this time around, either.
Hattori!
+NATURAL  is awesome!
And it's suited for serialization.
Thanks.
We can promote Akina Aiko's manuscript as being
written by a Novel Pleiades amateur context winner.
But who is this MONEYS artist?
He's Yuujirou's hidden gem.
Is it too risky to serialize an unpublished artist?
No, there's no problem if he can draw this well.
On the contrary, if he can draw this well, I'm surprised he hasn't been published yet.
At any rate, I'm submitting this to the committee.
Yes, please do.
Hattori...
Give me a break! Where'd you get such a great amateur?
What're you saying? It isn't just the manga authors who are competing.
I'm not going to go easy on you.
Frankly, NATURAL  is better than Tanto.
What?
You have that much confidence?
Yup.
Say, why don't you tell Ashirogi Muto that Akina Aiko's
manuscript will be submitted to the same committee as theirs?
She's apparently been a rival of Takagi's since middle school.
What?!
A storyboard made from Akina Aiko's manuscript will be submitted to the next serialization committee?!
Are you for real?
So it's true that she's been your rival since middle school.
Th-That's Iwase, right?
Yeah.
She's more like someone I really don't want to lose to.
That's what you call a rival!
Then I'm counting on you for the third chapter.
Iwase's already gotten to the serialization committee.
And on top of that...
What?
Hattori's her editor.
Which means that Hattori's
acknowledged her talent, at the very least.
M-Maybe she knows that we're planning
on getting married if you get serialized...
Of course not.
Maybe Aoki told her...
There's no way she would tell her that.
But...
Well...
If she gets serialized and we don't,
it really will feel like she's getting in our way.
But don't worry, I won't let that happen!
Yeah.
Saiko, let's revise everything, not just the third chapter!
Right!
Go for it, you two.
Yeah!
Iwase.
Stop this.
If Miyoshi saw us here together,
there'd be another misunderstanding.
That last meeting and your letter caused me a lot of trouble.
I'm sorry.
If we are serialized together after the next committee...
and my manga becomes more popular,
I want you to acknowledge me.
Fine.
If that happens, I'll acknowledge you.
Really?
But only your talent.
What do you mean by that?
Miyoshi and I are going to register for marriage when I get serialized.
I will definitely surpass you.
I can't accept your marriage if I don't!
If you do worse than me, you can do whatever you want.
What's with that?
Well, if you do worse and still get married, you'll be pitiful!
I could hold on to my pride that way.
It doesn't matter if you're better or
worse—we're registering when I get serialized.
Good night.
Damn!
I can't lose to her!
All right, it's perfect!
It'll definitely pass!
Your "definitely" isn't a sure bet, though.
Hey, don't say that.
I'm sure this time!
Will Tanto  really be okay?
December 25th Tuesday
Day of Serialization Committee
I don't really care about a committee I haven't submitted anything to.
Should I leave early?
Shut up, Yamahisa!
If you want to leave, then leave!
Hey, Miura, quiet down!
Hey, let's just sit quietly and wait for now.
Oonishi.
Since we're not on the committee, that's all we can do.
Just sit quietly...
and wait, huh?
I can't believe that December 25th is our fated day.
If you pass, can we turn in the registration form before the end of the day?
My stomach hurts...
Crap! No matter how many times I go through this, the stomachache never goes away!
I see you're in no shape to do that.
Next is +NATURAL.
The editor is Hattori Akira.
The artist is someone Yuujirou had on hand, it seems.
"It seems"? Also, I've never heard of this MONEYS.
At least give us his name and age.
I said the same thing, but Yuujirou refused.
This is Niizuma, right?
Huh?
Maniizu... Niizuma.
Manuscript: Akina Aiko
Artist
His art and composition is different,
but he forgot to change his habits with layouts.
Now that you mention it...
Bring Akira and Yuujirou here.
Yuujirou! Akira!
Is it over already?
You two, come with me!
Is it okay for us to sit in on the meeting?
It's fine, just get in there!
Hurry up!
Are both Hattoris on the committee now? Wow.
I wonder if they'll be offered lead editor positions?
Is this art Niizuma Eiji's?
Come out!! Hiruriramu!
Yes, it is.
What's the meaning of this?
Niizuma said he wanted to do two manga,
and he has the ability to do so.
It's not possible for an author to have two simultaneous manga!
A one-shot is one thing, but a serialization?! The other authors will complain.
But this is really good.
Each chapter is good on its own,
but it's been a while since I've read something where the second and third chapters step up the pace like this.
Well, I agree that it's good, and I wouldn't want Jack SQ to get it.
There is also the option of having
someone other than Niizuma draw it.
We can't do that.
I have Akina Aiko's manuscript here.
Please read it.
This is amazing. From this composition...
So you're saying it's only this good because
Niizuma's the one who turned it into a storyboard?
I hid the fact that Niizuma drew the art because I feared that you wouldn't accept it if you knew.
Chief Editor, I was objecting to this a little while ago,
but there's no rule that states that an author
cannot have two serialized manga at the same time.
There's probably never been an author that could do it before.
Yuujirou, you know how important
CROW  is to Jack right now, don't you?
If the quality of CROW  suffers due to the
artist working on two manga simultaneously—
It's just the opposite!
Niizuma wants to work on this so badly that if he doesn't, he'll lose motivation.
He's boasting that he'll have two excellent
manga in Jack and become the number one author!
So if this is serialized, he wants
to do it under his real name?
Yes!
Akina Aiko attends the same college as Aoki Kou, and feels that she is her rival.
She was also Ashirogi Muto's classmate in middle
school, and I hear she's been Takagi's rival ever since.
Furthermore, there's a clear rivalry
between Niizuma Eiji and Ashirogi Muto—
You two may leave.
Excuse us.
Ugh, I'm so nervous about whether or not
we'll get married, I'm gonna have a heart attack!
If we register, we should make sure it's after we beat Ayase!
If we get serialized, it'll be a nice Christmas present for Azuki.
Congratulations! Hirameki Tanto-kun  will begin its serialization in Issue 12!
We got it!
No way, we're getting married?!
Hey are you listening to me?
Another one's starting in Issue 11...
with a manuscript by Akina Aiko.
And art by Niizuma Eiji?!
Which means that Niizuma Eiji will have two serialized works in Jack?
Yeah.
What do you mean, he's doing two works at the same time?!
+NATURAL  will be serialized in Issue 11, one issue before yours, with the script written by Akina Aiko and art by Niizuma Eiji.
It's not fair to have Niizuma do the art! It's wrong!
Yuujirou, this is unfair!
There'll be one less slot for new authors!
It was agreed that Tanto  was much better than last time.
It's not unfair! It's revolutionary!
Was this really your scheme, Hattori?
Anyway, keep working on the first chapter.
I did it in order for it to pass.
So anything goes as long as it passes?
I'll get you some assistants.
Got it?
It sounds like the editing department's in an uproar over Eiji doing two manga at once.
This is unprecedented, after all. It's a drastic decision.
Will he be able to manage two manga?
Authors have done three weekly manga in the past.
They must have decided that Eiji could manage it.
And Iwase's getting serialized, even though it's only
been half a year since she said she'd break into manga.
Hattori and Eiji's help was probably a big factor.
We won't lose!
Yeah!
Because Iwase and Eiji are teaming up with Hattori as their editor!
Anyway,
you got your serialization, so why aren't you happier?
Oh, right! Sorry.
All right! I'll tell Azuki.
"As of issue 12, Hirameki Tanto-kun  will be serialized!"
Send!
Wonderful! A serialization.
Re: News
Congratulations!
I can't believe you have a serialization
only a year after TRAP ended.
You two really do have talent! Go for it!
PS: Merry Xmas (lol)
She says we've got talent!
Right!
We'll get an anime this time, for Saiko and Azuki's sake!
And we're  getting married!
Yeah.
You're coming over tomorrow, right?
Let's practice greeting my parents.
Well, uh, we might have a meeting tomorrow...
Just get to practicing already!
Well, you don't have to if you think you'll be fine on the fly.
I'm counting on you, too, Mashiro.
If someone as good as Niizuma is allowed to
have two manga, newbies won't stand a chance!
You can't say there aren't any newbies
involved in this. Akina is a complete amateur.
Right. Whether you're a veteran or a
newbie, a good manga is a good manga.
Quality trumps all.
So nothing else matters, as long as it's good?
Then I'll ask Oda to draw something!
You'd just be a copycat!
Shut up, all of you!
If you have something to say, say it to the Chief Editor!
More importantly, has each lead editor
informed everyone about the new team?
There's a new team?
Y-Yeah.
So I'm the new lead, after all!
The new lead editor is Oonishi.
You can be in the serialization committee now.
Congratulations!
Thanks!
Too bad.
I guess I'll go tell Niizuma.
I'll make a report, too, then.
Congratulations.
You've been serialized!
I see.
You should be happier about this.
Sorry, but I've never failed to win or pass at anything, whether it be exams or literature.
I-I see.
Then please continue to keep up the good work so that it won't be canceled.
And what about Ashirogi?
They were also serialized.
It was just the two of you this time.
And I didn't tell you this before, but your artist,
MONEYS, is actually Niizuma Eiji, the author of CROW.
Have you heard of it?
Yes. It's a popular manga that's been on the front cover many times, and also frequently gets color pages.
Right.
We've hidden it up until now, but we're going with "Art by Niizuma Eiji" for the serialization.
You won't fail with him.
He's the best artist you could possibly have for this.
I see.
Thank you.
I would like to meet him at least once.
I don't think you two would mesh well...
Either way, the New Years party is on January 15th. I'll introduce you then.
Very well.
I'm looking forward to it.
Will Takag–I mean, Ashirogi be
attending this New Years party as well?
Of course.
I'm looking forward to it even more.
Great!
Fukuda
It's Ashirogi Muto's comeback!
Thanks.
Master Niizuma must be happy, too.
Niizuma's got a new serialization, too.
Huh?
He's drawing the art for a new one.
What does that mean?
Is he going to have two manga running in Jack concurrently?
Yeah.
The original work is +NATURAL  by Akina Aiko...
Two manga by himself...
Niizuma's really something.
Even before the serialization was decided on,
he drew up a rough sketch of the first chapter.
He's ready to go.
It'll definitely go well.
And next time, I'll become a lead editor!
Fukuda?
Yuujirou!
What the hell is this I hear about Niizuma doing the art for another serialization?!
You heard right.
Isn't it great?
Niizuma Eiji, the man with two serializations. It'll sell.
So anything goes if it's good for business?
Don't put it that way.
Fukuda, you stick your nose into
other people's business too much.
Focus on KIYOSHI!
I don't like this.
What? Two serializations in a weekly magazine?
Niizuma Eiji is unbelievable.
Compared to that, look at you.
The guy who can't even finish his year-end work.
I'll be done in a few hours.
I'm only late because the love-work schedule you made for me got all screwed up!
Sure, she looked better than Aoki in the picture.
But she looked completely different in person!
Next time, I'll meet her before I introduce you.
I made it through this year somehow, but I'll be
counting on you for more motivation next year.
On Aoki Kou's level.
Aoki this, Aoki that.
Why don't you just go after her ?
R-Really?
If you keep your deadlines, you're free to do as you like with your love life.
It's common for manga authors to get married.
But it's up to Aoki...
That kind of girl is weak against a bit of pressure.
Really?
Without a doubt!
Of all the times...
Hello?
Oh, Fukuda?
Tomorrow, at Niizuma's...
Aoki's coming, too?!
I'll be there! Definitely!
See? God is on your side, Hiramaru.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
But can a manga author make a good living, Akito?
All it takes is one hit, and you'll be rolling in dough, Father!
You can't talk like that!
Hello?
Hey, sorry I cut it short earlier. I was in a hurry.
Fukuda?
Tue
Wed
Serialization
Commitee
Greet Miyosh's parents
Apparently, we're all getting together at Eiji's tomorrow.
What about coming over to my house?
Sorry! This is part of my job.
We'll do it the day after, all right?
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
Everyone's here.
We're one short.
Unfortunately, Nakai is...
No, +NATURAL's  author, Akina Aiko.
Right, we should invite her.
Um, let's not.
Why not?
Actually, we were classmates in middle
school, and we don't get along very well...
Classmates?! So she must be young!
Fukuda's right.
If she's pairing up with Niizuma, she should be part of Team Fukuda.
I think she'd be happy if we let her into the group.
Is your relationship that bad?
Did something happen?
Iwase... Akina Aiko is interested in Takagi,
but he already has a girlfriend...
This girl is so clueless!
Whoa, what a waste!
Master Niizuma, give her a call.
I don't have her number.
I have it.
Better than I imagined!
No, I'll stay faithful to Aoki.
After the party today, I'll take her home in my German car!
Which one of you is Niizuma?
It's me!
HOW DO YOU DO?!
I'm looking forward to working together.
Me too.
What is this meeting regarding?
Well, it's a gathering where we share
opinions on each other's manga, and stuff...
Sharing opinions?
Yeah.
I even looked at Aoki's storyboard for her.
Is this true, Aoki?
Yes.
Do you have no pride?
I have confidence in my work!
I would never accept opinions of other authors!
I will excuse myself.
Niizuma, I leave the art to you.
Roger!
I was kind of expecting things to turn out like this.
She's just like Aoki was two years ago!
True that.
I was like that?
Well then, let's have a toast!
And then I'll take Aoki home...
Before that...
Master Niizuma.
Why are you doing two manga?
Is it so that you have something to fall back on if one goes south?
You should devote yourself to CROW.
Don't you all agree?
Yeah, it does seem like an author's attention would be split if he worked on two manga...
And personally, I don't want to lose to Akina Aiko, so you drawing for her is sort of...
I also don't want to lose to +NATURAL.
I am against you drawing the art, since it feels like a ploy by the editorial department.
Don't do two manga! It's impossible.
Don't hurry to your death!
What do you think, Mashiro?
I'm not against him working on two serializations,
but I don't want to lose to the second one!
Where did the idea even come from?
Your editor pushed you into this, didn't he?
If we do this, It'll definitely fire up Ashirogi Muto!
Quit your whining, all of you.
I draw because I want to.
If you have complaints, say them after you make a better manga than mine.
Neither of my manga will lose to any of yours.
SPIN!
It's frustrating, but Niizuma is right.
He is. We'll just have to make
a manga that's better than his.
Yeah.
Aoki, since it's getting late, please
allow me to drive you home.
Oh, thank you.
I did it.
Kichijouji Police
It was towed?
Aoki, I'll take you on my bike, if you don't mind the cold.
Okay.
Mr. Yoshida...
God has given up on me.
toomawari wo eranda no wa
The reason I chose to take a detour
motto kimi wo suki ni naru tame datta n da
was to fall ever deeper in love with you
boku no namae yobu sono koe wo
I have a feeling I've always known
zutto zutto shitteta ki ga shita n da
what your voice sounds like when it calls my name
boku no yubisaki de egaita
With my fingertips I drew
subete no sen wa kimi ni tsuzuku kakehashi sa
many lines that make up a suspension bridge leading to you
Show me the way
Show me the way I'm sure our path
bokura no michi kitto
Believe in your way
your way connects us without any turns
hitosuji ni tsunagari
Show me the way
Show me the way It leads to the place where we promised
yakusoku no basho e tsuzuku
Show me the way
Show me the way I will never give up
akirametari shinaide
Believe in your way
your way Raise your gaze
sono hitomi wo agete
Show me the way
Show me the way and see that we're certain to meet again
bokura wa massugu deau sa
Takagi, you've got a serialization and a marriage on the way!
Next Time
Preview
What great news!
But both are a big pain!
I hope neither ends...
Next time on Bakuman.
Fate and
Star
Fate and Star.
We're all connected through our dreams!