kokoro no naka itsumo itsumo egaite'ru (egaite'ru)
In my heart, I'm always, always drawing (drawing)
yume o noseta jibun dake no sekai chizu
My very own world map, where my dreams come true
(Takecopter!)
(Bamboo-copter!)
sora o tonde toki o koete to'oi kuni demo
To fly through the sky, to cross time, to go to faraway countries...
door o akete hora ikitai yo ima sugu
I wish I could open the door and hey, just go there right away!
(Dokodemo Door!)
(Anywhere-Door!)
otona ni nattara wasurechau no ka na?
What if I forget all of these when I grow up?
son'na toki ni wa omoidashite miyō
When the time comes, let's try to remember!
sharararara
Sharararara
boku no kokoro ni
Inside my heart
itsumademo
there's always
kagayaku yume
a shining dream!
Doraemon
Doraemon!
sono pocket de kanaesasete ne
With that pocket, make it come true!
shararara
Shararara
uta o utaō
Timing: usotsuki
Translation: Puto
Let's sing a song...
min'na de sā
...and everybody...
te o tsunaide
...hold hands together!
Doraemon
Doraemon!
sekaijū ni yume o sō afuresasete
Who throughout the world, makes dreams come true!
Space Tarzan
If we make it so nobody can drink from this spring,
not even that cursed Space Tarzan
will be able to fix it!
Come on, hurry!
Let's do it!
You evil Skull Men!
I can see through your evil plans.
That voice... it's Space Tarzan!
I, Space Tarzan, won't allow you to disturb this planet's peace!
Prepare yourself! You shouldn't have messed with me!
What? Don't run!
Fire! Fire!
Go get'em, Space Tarzan!
Go! Go!
Oh! Look out, behind you!
That's right! Just like that!
He did it! Space Tarzan won!
And today, the peace of the universe was saved once again.
That was fun.
Don't you think so?
I dunno...
It seems to be getting worse.
The sets are terrible, the animals look fake,
and the stories are even worse.
How about we start watching another show next week?
What are you saying?!
I won't allow you to talk about Space Tarzan like that!
Space Tarzan is my dream hero!
Space Tarzan is awesome!
He protects the peace of the universe all by himself!
When I grow up, I want to be just like him!
Geez! At least listen when I'm talking to you!
If you did more than just blabbering about Space Tarzan...
Enough already!
Whoever likes Space Tarzan, raise your hand!
Are you still in kindergarten?
Space Tarzan's stupid!
What's with that? You all used to say it was fun!
When we were younger.
And we've had enough of it.
And it's been pretty boring, lately.
I never watch it anymore.
Every episode's the same.
Besides, the recent Space Legion series is a lot cooler.
Yeah!
I'll ask Dad to let all of us watch it at home!
I'll never leave you, Space Tarzan.
Wha...?
Whoa! It's Space Tarzan!
What do I do?!
Space Tarzan!
Hey, what's up?
I'm a big fan of yours!
Can I please have an autograph?
Sure! I'd love to.
Wow! How exciting!
I'll keep this notebook for the rest of my life!
Thank you.
I saw today's episode. You were really cool, Space Tarzan.
When you were fighting the Skull Men... Bash! Bash!
You really like it that much?
Of course! I really really love it!
Then would you like to come to our studio?
It's close by.
Really?
Of course!
Let's go, let's go!
Whatever it takes, I wanna go!
This is where the series is filmed.
Awesome!
Hey! Morning.
Good morning, Director.
Who's the kid?
Ah, he's Nobita-kun.
He's a big fan of the show.
A big fan, you say?
Whoa! It's Baron Skull!
This man's Baron Skull?
And the ones sitting there are the ones who wear the monster suits to make them move.
The Skull Soldiers, the cameramen, the ones in charge of the lighting, the set arrangers...
Amazing!
With so many people working here, no wonder you make such an awesome show!
What? Did I say anything weird?
No, nothing.
Really, I never miss an episode!
If only the other kids were like you,
we could smile like that, too.
But there's tons! Everybody likes the series...
Thanks.
But...
We'll have to quit soon.
What? Why?!
They're about to cancel the series.
Seems that less and less people watch it.
End it? You can't!
Why does this have to happen!?
But we get less funding every time.
And little-by-little, you can tell the quality gets worse.
But then you just have to get more money...
Look, kid. Almost nobody watches it anymore.
We can't get sponsors to pay for it.
It's sad, but there's nothing we can do.
Thanks for watching the series so far.
What are you saying?
I...
I don't want to believe it!
Hey!
Won't you do anything while they cancel Space Tarzan?
Lend me some invention so I can boost up the ratings!
How annoying.
If I had something to raise the ratings, they wouldn't have to cancel it!
I beg you, Doraemon!
What you're asking is impossible!
But...!
Fine! If that's how it is, I'll do anything so Space Tarzan can continue!
I'll do it somehow. I have to think.
Think, Nobita!
Nobita-kun! Dinner!
Nobita-kun?
Nobita-kun!
Don't be so noisy.
I'm trying to think here.
Well, then I'm going to eat.
I'm hungry...
Isn't dinner ready yet, Mom?
Mom?
Don't yell, it's midnight already.
Midnight?
It's this late already?!
Then dinner's already over?
I called you, but you told me to shut up.
Eh? No way!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry...
I'm hungry, I'm hungry...
Can't help it.
Just eat this.
Aren't these the Momotarō Dumplings?
Humans aren't affected by them.
Either way, just let me sleep.
If you give these dumplings to an animal,
he'll do everything he's told.
Is it really all right for me to eat them?
Tastes better than I thought.
Of course! That's it!
Doraemon, wake up!
What? What is it?
I just had an awesome idea!
This way we can boost up the ratings,
I'm Tarzan!
Boss...
We can't go on like this.
We can't.
We don't have many sponsors.
I guess we'll have to cancel.
Please wait!
Can't you wait 2 to 3 days?
You need large sets that look like the Earth of a hundred million years ago, and good dinosaur suits, right?
I can get them for free.
Don't be stupid. That sounds like a dream tale more than anything.
But...
Don't play pranks like that on adults.
It's not a prank! I'm serious! Really!
Enough already!
I don't have time to waste with a kid's pranks.
Go home.
Please wait, boss.
Yes, what he says is hard to believe, but...
How about we give him a chance?
I'm sure he's not trying to trick us.
Besides, we can't really get any worse.
And it's free! Free!
Free, huh?
That's my favorite word.
All right, got it.
Fine, we'll wait one day.
If it doesn't work, it's all the same.
One day? Can I get everything done in one day?
I can't have doubts. I have to make it!
100 million years ago, in the Cretaceous period...
Where did Doraemon go?
Either way, I have to find some appropriate animals, and give them the Momotarō Dumplings.
They have to be tame for the filming.
Doraemon!
There he is.
Hey! Did you find any?
Did you find any?
Yeah, one.
That's a Parassaurolofus!
How would Space Tarzan look on one of these, yelling...
Eh? That's not cool at all.
It'd make the situation even worse.
Now that I'd found one...
That one's no good.
It has to be a much bigger and stronger one, kind of like an elephant.
One that makes Space Tarzan look really cool!
I think you're asking too much.
Come on, let's hurry!
Then we'll meet in an hour.
Until then, we'll gather as many dinosaurs as possible!
Got it.
I thought in the Cretaceous period, dinosaurs were everywhere...
The Earth's huge!
But I can't find any dinosaur!
I was saved by the branches.
I was caught by surprise.
I lost my bamboo-copter!
And I don't have the dumplings, either! Now what?!
You've got to be kidding!
If I find a dinosaur now, I'm finished!
Dinosaurs, don't show up!
Rain? No, it's too warm, and it smells like fish.
But I told you to not show up!
Help!
Wait! Stop! Stop!
Stop!
It stopped when I told it to...
Move!
Stop!
Look that way.
He looked...
Of course! I get it!
He must have eaten the dumplings I dropped!
All right! Spin around!
Sit!
Amazing! If Space Tarzan rides him, he'll look super-cool!
Run! Run!
I'm Space Tarzan!
It's huge!
Doraemon!
Nobita-kun!
Isn't this Tyrannosaurus cool?!
I found him!
I got lucky, too! Found an entire herd of Sauroposeidons.
Really? This is awesome!
Give them all the Momotarō Dumplings you have left!
Here we go!
All right! Once you've eaten them, gather together!
In a Sauroposeidon pyramid!
Nobita-kun, aren't you getting a little carried away? We still have to find some more dinosaurs.
Oh, that's right. Do you still have any dumplings?
Yeah, don't worry.
Off they go!
Huge success!
But how are we going to bring the camera crew here?
We can hook up the Anywhere Door's exit with the Time Machine.
The more I think about it, the dumber it sounds.
That they'll let us use a huge set for free...
Sounds like a dream story.
But...
I knew it! We were tricked! I'm going home!
But since we came this far...
That's right.
Wouldn't it be great if it is true?
And it's free! Free!
Just because it's my favorite word...
Sorry for the delay. Please, come in.
It's just a normal house.
It's free, free!
The studio is in the garden.
Ta-da! Nobita Studios!
This is... a studio?
Didn't I tell you it was fake?!
There's a limit to jokes.
That's why I said it wasn't worth it...
Now, now...
Why don't you take a little look?
Right? Right?
This is...
A-Amazing!
I can't believe it!
This is a set?!
And that's not all!
What?
What's happening?
Look!
Amazing! Incredible!
Those are props?
Whichever way you look at them, they look real!
I can't believe this is a set!
Well...
I don't want this to get out...
Understood! We won't tell anyone!
I beg you, let us use it!
Nobita-kun!
Thank you!
We can film amazing scenes here!
Today I'll finish you off, Space Tarzan!
Go, Space Tarzan!
The series is much better now!
And it's a big hit! Ratings went up by 40%!
Really? I'm glad...
They won't cancel it anymore...
Space Tarzan is here!
What are you on about? I'm Tarzan!
What? Why you?
I'm the one who gets to be Space Tarzan!
I'm Space Tarzan!
What are you doing?
It's all right! I'm glad everybody likes Space Tarzan again.
Come on, let's go!
fukurettsura
That sulking face,
that frowning face,
shikamettsura
tokidoki wa suru kedo
those faces you sometimes show...
nakittsura
Your crying face,
bucchōzura
or your cranky face,
itsumademo shoge-te nankararenai
You can't always be down!
why? haruyasumi kibun
Why? It's spring vacation!
why, why? pocke ni yume ga ippai da yo
Why, why? When there's tons of dreams in this pocket!
hai hai, kimi to issho nara
Yeah, yeah! Because if you're with me
hai hai, nandemo dekiru ne
Yeah, yeah! Then anything can happen!
hug-shichao, hug-shichao
Everybody hug! Everybody hug!
otona mo kodomo mo hug-shichao
Adults too! Children too! Everybody hug!
hug-shichao, hug-shichao
Everybody hug! Everybody hug!
inu ni mo neko ni mo hug-shichao
Even dogs and cats, everybody hug!