kokoro no naka itsumo itsumo egaite'ru
In my heart, I'm always, always drawing
yume o noseta jibun dake no sekai chizu
My very own world map, where my dreams come true
(Takecopter!)
(Bamboo-copter!)
sora o tonde toki o koete toa iku ni demo
To fly through the sky, to cross time, to go to faraway countries...
door o akete hora ikitai yo ima sugu
I wish I could open the door and hey, just go there right away!
(Dokodemo Door!)
(Anywhere-Door!)
otona ni nattara wasurechau no ka na?
What if I forget all of these when I grow up?
son'na toki ni wa omoidashite miyō
When the time comes, let's try to remember!
sharararara
Sharararara
boku no kokoro ni
Inside my heart
itsumademo
there's always
kagayaku yume
a shining dream!
Doraemon
Doraemon!
sono pocket de kanaesasete ne
With that pocket, make it come true!
shararara
Shararara
uta o utaō
Timing: usotsuki
Translation: Puto
Let's sing a song...
min'na de sā
...and everybody...
te o tsunaide
...hold hands together!
Doraemon
Doraemon!
sekaijū ni yume o sō afuresasete
Who throughout the world, makes dreams come true!
The Great Avalanche in my Room
What do you think? Cool, huh?
They're the latest and greatest models of skis and snowboards on the market!
But my skis are cool too, aren't they?
My skis look pretty good, too.
That's right!
My family planned to go skiing at our country house next weekend,
so how about you guys come along too?
Really?
Awesome! Let's go, let's go!
Me too!
OK! Then we're all going.
Hey. What's wrong, Nobita?
Uh...
You see, I...
I don't really have skis, but it's all right.
Then buy some.
But...
I get it. The problem is you don't want to come because you can't ski, right?
Nobita's always been terrible at sports.
Fine! Let's see if my dad'll buy me some.
If he does, I'll go ski too.
That's right, Nobita! That's the way to go!
Let's go ski!
It's gonna be so fun!
I'll go! Of course I'll go!
I hope Dad doesn't want to buy them...
Skis?
Yeah! We want to go ski, but...
Of course, you can't buy them, right?
They're too expensive, right?
You're not gonna buy them, right?
Sorry, guys! Can't be helped!
He won't let me.
So you want to ski? That's great!
I was starting to get worried since you show no interest in sports.
I'm glad you finally decided to do some exercise.
Look!
Just in case this ever happened, I'd already bought the skis.
No... No way!
That's great, Nobita!
Well then, Nobita, good luck!
Yeah...
Isn't it great, Nobita-san?
Now you can come ski with us.
Though the best part will be seeing if you can ski at all.
It's all right. I'm sure he'll be great.
Right?
Yeah...
But fortunately,
I mean...
Unfortunately, in the news they say there won't be a lot of snow in the mountains.
And now, the weather forecast.
In the next few days, there'll be a lot of snow.
Congratulations to all ski fans!
All right!
All right...
Doraemon!
Please, do something...
What's wrong?
What about it? If the problem is you can't ski, just practice a bit.
I can't, there's no snow yet!
Do it when it snows.
By then it'll be too late!
Everybody's looking forward to seeing me fail!
I guess it can't be helped.
You're gonna lend me something, right?
Here it is...
Portable Ski Track!
It'll allow you to practice skiing here in the house.
How do you use this?
Let's try.
First, climb onto the mat.
And go!
See how I'm skiing?
The conveyor belt leans taking your speed into account.
And you can keep skiing as long as you want.
If you change direction...
The belt moves too.
Awesome!
If you stop...
The belt stops too.
Sounds fun! Let me, let me, let me!
First I climb onto the carpet, right?
I'm falling!
The ski belt won't stop!
This isn't working! It won't stop!
And now that I stopped, the belt stopped too.
That's enough.
Wait!
I thought you didn't want the others to laugh at you.
I don't want to be laughed at,
but I want to get hurt even less!
Don't be such a wimp!
I can't try in a place like this! No way!
A place like this?
You can't try to ski unless you're in a place surrounded by snow as far as the eye can see.
Otherwise, there's no inspiration!
All right.
We'll use one of the options in the track.
How about this?
Amazing! But how did you do it?
A three-dimensional projection.
Now you're inspired, right?
So, start training.
Y-Yeah.
All right. The belt's here.
Then go!
When you move, the background moves too.
When you fall, snow jumps around you like in a real track.
And when you stop, the background stops too. So?
Isn't it just like a real ski track?
It's not cold!
Like this, I can't do it.
Wait!
Wait! Listen!
If I make the snow cold, will you do it then?
I guess.
I didn't want to use this button, but...
How about it? Feeling up to it now?
It-it's cold!
You're the one who said you'd ski if it was cold!
I did this for you!
You're running away?!
I'm just going for a scarf!
I'll go get it.
There. Put on this scarf.
Hey! Let's practice, practice!
Please, drop it!
I really don't like skiing!
You're not going to do the same as always!
If something doesn't go the way you want, you drop it right in the middle!
I'm serious. Stop running away and face up to reality.
I'm saying this for your own good.
Do you understand?
You've got to stop making the same mistakes!
Doraemon...
I didn't know you were that worried about me!
Of course I was.
Doraemon!
I'm sorry!
I didn't know you cared so much about me!
I'm so sorry, Doraemon!
It's all right, if you understand.
So long as you understand, it's enough.
Doraemon!
I promise I'll fall... err, I mean try, with everything I've got!
Yeah! Good luck!
That's right! That's the way to go!
See how little by little, you got better?
It's easier than you thought.
Yeah!
And this skiing thing's more enjoyable by the minute!
Oh, geez...
All right. One more time!
That's right! Go for it!
B-But...
You're fine since you're exercising and all, but...
But I'm going to catch a cold here!
I'm gonna bump up the temperature a bit...
Let's see...
Where was that button...?
Here.
What's that sound?
Oh no! I think I pressed the wrong button!
You didn't have to make it that realistic!
You can't even ski like this!
I can't take this! I'm going to freeze!
Let's run away! The exit. Where's the exit?!
Was it here?
Doraemon!
What... But there was no option to make avalanches!
Doraemon...
Doraemon!
Doraemon!!!
Oh, no! Doraemon was buried!
I have to find help and save him!
This... can't be!
My room isn't that big! And no matter how much I run, I can't find the door!
Somebody help!
Somebody help! Mom!
Nobi-chan? What's wrong?
This hurts...
Somebody help!
Help!!!
What's going on with you two?
Somebody! Please, somebody help!