What's that?
Is this like the entrance exam
where the lessors already started?
Don't move!
Those are villains.
Thirteen... and Eraser Head, huh?
The teacher's schedule
we received the other day...
...said that All Might was
also supposed to be here.
The trespassing the other day was
the work of these scumbags after all, huh?
Where is he?
I went through the trouble of
bringing this whole crowd, too...
All Might...
The Symbol of Peace...
And he's not here?
I wonder if he'll come
if we kill some kids?
What the pro heroes fight against...
...and what they face...
...is...
...an extraordinary evil.
Episode 10: Encounter with the Unknown
Episode 10:
What? Villains?
No way...
There's no way they could
get into a hero school!
Teacher, what about
the trespasser sensors?
We have them, of course, but...
Did they only appear here,
or around the whole school?
Either way, if the sensors
are not responding...
...that means they have someone
with a Quirk that can do that.
An isolated area separated
from the main campus
during a time when a class
is supposed to be here.
They might be fools,
but they're not dumb.
This surprise attack was carefully
planned with some sort of goal in mind.
Thirteen, start the evacuation.
Try calling the school.
These villains even had something
to counteract the sensors.
It's possible someone with
radio-wave-type powers is interfering.
Kaminari.
You try contacting the school
with your Quirk, too.
Yessir.
What about you, sir?
Will you fight by yourself?
With that many, even if you
can erase their Quirks...
Eraser Head's fighting style is capturing
after erasing the enemy's Quirk.
A frontal battle is...
You can't be a hero
with just one trick.
I'm leaving it to you, Thirteen.
Shooting squad, let's go.
Didn't our intel say it would
just be Thirteen and All Might?
Who's that?!
I don't know!
But if he thinks he can come at us
from the front by himself...
...then he's a huge idiot!
Huh?
My Quirk...!
The bullets won't come out?!
Idiots!
He can erase Quirks
just by looking at them!
It's a Eraser Head!
Erase?
Are you gonna erase the Quirks of
heteromorphic-type villains like us, too?
No, I can't!
But the skills of guys like you...
...are statistically more likely
to manifest in close combat...
...so I've taken measures against that.
He's also strong in
hand-to-hand combat.
And since he's hiding his eyes with goggles...
...you can't tell whose Quirk he's erasing.
When he fights against a group, that
makes it harder for them to work together.
I see.
I hate pro heroes.
The masses don't stand
a chance against them.
Wow...
Teacher actually good at fighting
by himself against a lot of people, huh?
This is no time for analysis!
Hurry up and take shelter!
I won't let you.
Damn!
I just blinked once and the guy who
looks like the most trouble got away...
Nice to meet you.
We are the League of Villains.
It may be presumptuous of us...
but we have invited ourselves in to the
home of the heroes, U.A. High School...
...in order to have All Might,
the Symbol of Peace, take his last breath.
Huh?
I believe All Might
should have been here.
Has there been some kind of change?
Well, that is neither here nor there.
This is the part I am to play.
Did you consider that you'd get
beaten by us before you did it?!
Oh dear, that's dangerous.
That's right.
Even if you are students,
you are excellent golden eggs.
This is bad!
Move away, you two!
My job is to scatter you all
and torture you to death!
What the—?!
Ribbit...
Everyone...!
A warp?
Is that his Quirk?
They want to kill All Might?
What in the world is going on?
What the heck?
Here he comes!
I don't have anything
against you, but see ya!
Midoriya!
Ribbit!
See ya...
See ya.
Shipwreck Zone
For a frog, they are pretty big...
...your boobs...
Ribbit.
Thanks, Asui.
Call me "Tsu."
Asui
Tsuyu
Quirk:
Frog
Asui Tsuyu!
Quirk: Frog!
T-T-T-T-Tsu, thanks!
She can do pretty much
anything a frog can!
As expected!
This has turned into
a bad situation, though.
Yeah.
What the villain said earlier...
All Might should have been here.
Has there been some kind of change?
They knew U.A.'s schedule!
Looking at the big picture,
those guys must have set up the media intrusion
the other day to get information.
They were waiting to pounce,
just as Todoroki said.
But, but—!
It's not like they can kill All Might!
Once All Might comes,
he'll pound those guys!
Mineta.
Huh?
Don't you think they are trying so hard
because they have a way to kill him?
Guys that strong just told us they
would torture us to death, you know.
I wonder if we'll be able to
hold out until All Might arrives...
Even if All Might comes, I wonder
if we will all make it out in one piece...
M-M-Midoriya!
What the heck is that?
Ribbit!
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
There's a ton of them!
Those guys have a way
to defeat All Might.
She's probably right about that.
I can't think of any other possibility.
Why do they want to kill him?
Because he's become a person
who deters villains and evil?
Because he's the one and
only Symbol of Peace?
No.
I mean...
You...
...can become a hero.
I like that!
Right now... I don't...
Come, young Midoriya.
Congrats on getting accepted.
I don't...
It's fine now.
Why?
Because I am here.
I don't...
...care about why!
If those guys...
Ribbit.
...have a way to defeat All Might...
...then right now, we should be...
...stopping whatever they're planning!
By fighting... and winning!
Landslide Zone
It's pathetic to lose against a single child
Get a hold of yourself.
You're an adult, aren't you?
Collapse Zone
Mountain Zone
Fire Zone
Squall Zone
Lounge
The number you have dialed is not in service,
or has been temporarily disconnected.
I can't reach Thirteen or Aizawa...
Whatever the reason,
I am neglecting my teaching duties because
of what happened outside of work hours.
I did something very foolish.
What if I go say something at the end?
My body will last for
another ten minutes or so.
I will g—
Hold your horses.
Principal Nezu!
Yes!
Am I a mouse? A dog? A bear?
My real identity is...
...the principal!
Your fur is well-groomed today, as usual.
The secret is keratin.
Humans can't get this
kind of color and luster.
But let's talk about that later.
All Might
Resolves Three Incidents in Only One Hour!
Look at this!
"All Might Resolves Three
Incidents in Only One Hour!"
The fault mainly lies with the ruffians who still
cause trouble in this town even with you here...
...but you also shouldn't react
every time you hear of an incident!
You really haven't changed
at all, have you?
Your hero activities are limited because
of your injury and its aftereffects.
Along with that, you need to
train your One For All successor.
Since you insist on remaining
the Symbol of Peace,
the only way you can keep the world
from finding out about both of those
is for you to come here.
That's why I suggested
you become a teacher.
I think you can stay here
and relax for a little longer.
In actuality, you can only teach
this next class for a little bit, right?
I'm the one who suggested it,
but since you have accepted the position,
I wish you'd prioritize your teaching duties.
I mean, there are a lot of
hero agencies in this town.
It is as you say.
But that is why I was
preparing to go to USJ.
Even if you went now, you would be
forced to return right away, right?
if that's the case, then you might as well
listen to my theories on teaching
and use that to help you in the future.
He's pouring tea...
Have a drink.
He's always been long-winded.
What bothers me most is that I didn't get
a voicemail and couldn't connect at all...
First of all, regarding the vulnerability and
responsibility of being both hero and teacher...
You haven't changed at all either, sir.
Shouji!
Is everyone here?
Can you check?
Everyone's scattered,
but they're all in this building.
Damn it, physical attacks can't hit him,
and he can warp things...
His Quirk's the worst!
Class rep!
Yes?
I entrust this duty to you.
Run to the school and tell them
about what is happening here.
The alarms are not sounding,
and our phones don't have signal.
The alarm system is
based on infrared rays.
Even though Eraser Head is
erasing people's Quirks left and right,
they are still not working...
...which means they must have
someone with an interference Quirk...
...who hid right when they arrived.
It would be faster for you to run
than for us to find that person.
But it would be a disgrace as
class rep to leave everyone behind—
Go, Emergency Exit!
If you can get outside, there are alarms.
That's why these guys are
only doing this inside, right?
As long as you go outside,
they won't follow you!
Blow away this fog with your legs!
Use your Quirk in order to save others!
I can totally support you
like I did in the cafeteria!
I will!
Please, class rep!
Even if you have no other choice,
are there really idiots who talk about
their plans in front of the enemy?!
We did it because it doesn't
matter if we're found out!
Black Hole!
What do you mean, fight?
Are you stupid?!
These guys might kill All Might, right?
You're contradicting yourself, Midoriya!
The best plan would be to sit tight and wait for
the U.A. heroes to come save us, of course!
Mineta...
...those guys down there...
...are clearly assuming
we'll fight in the water, right?
Are you ignoring me?!
Does that mean they knew what was in
these facilities before they gathered people?
Yeah.
For people who gathered
that much intel so meticulously,
there's something strange.
They sent you, Asu—
Ribbit?
I mean, T-Tsu—
to the shipwreck zone.
Your own pace is fine.
Oh, is that right?
Well, what about it?!
This means, in other words, the villains
probably don't know what our Quirks are.
Ribbit!
That's true...
If they knew that I was a frog...
...then they probably would have
thrown me into that fire zone over there.
They probably separated us
because they didn't know our Quirks
so they planned to
overpower us with numbers.
We have inferior numbers
and less experience.
Our only hope...
...lies in the fact that our opponents
don't know what our Quirks are!
The enemy isn't trying to climb the boat.
That supports my hypothesis!
But that...
...probably means they aren't
underestimating us, either.
I'll tell you more...
...about my Quirk.
I can jump high...
...stick to walls...
...and stick my tongue out
up to about 20 meters.
I can also spit out my
stomach and wash it,
and secrete toxic mucus...
...though that actually just stings a little.
"Secrete"...?!
The last two are practically useless,
so you can probably forget about them.
Secrete...
I already kind of knew,
but you're really strong.
I have super strength, but...
...once I use it, I'm pretty much
out of commission.
It's like a double-edged sword.
My Quirk lets these...
...stick super tight.
Depending on how I'm feeling,
they can even stick for a whole day.
They grow back after I pull them off, but...
...if I pull off too many,
I'll start bleeding.
They don't stick to me.
They just bounce off.
That's why I said we
should just wait quietly!
My Quirk is totally unfit for battle!
Th-That's not it!
It's an amazing Quirk, so we
should think of a way to use it—
I'm getting impatient.
Let's end this quickly!
What power...!
The ship's broken.
You can't give up!
What are you doing?
The enemy will figure out your Quirk—
What the heck are these? Gross.
They're being cautious
and not touching them?
The boat will sink in less than a minute.
Once they get into the water,
we're sure to win.
That's true...
Mineta, did you really enter U.A.
to become a hero?
Shut up!
It's weirder to not be scared right now!
We were only in junior high
until a little while ago!
Who would have thought that we would be
almost killed right after starting school?!
I wish I could have at least touched
Yaoyorozu's boobs first!
When the enemy...
When the enemy becomes certain
of their victory, that will be our chance.
All Might said so before on TV.
What...?
This is the only way...
...to win!
You really must be kids,
with all the chirping and screaming.
Hey, Shigaraki said just don't
let down your guard, remember?
Don't judge them by their ages.
Look at their Quirks.
It's common sense, isn't it?
Because our Quirks will definitely
have an advantage in the water.
Act like Kacchan...!
You serious, Midoriya?!
Die...!
He's a kid after all.
Even if it's a smash, I can't get them
all at once if they form a circle.
Anyway, even if we get through this
shipwreck zone, there are still other enemies.
I can't sacrifice my arm!
After he hits the water...
I know!
Imagine...
...the egg not exploding!
Mineta.
Even though he's shaking...
Even though he's the same as me...
Even though he's scared...
Why?!
Delaware Smash!
Tsu! Mineta!
Ribbit!
Damn it!
What the heck, Midoriya?!
Why are you acting so cool?
Even I...
Even I can...!
Hey!
I m getting dragged in...
Is this that kid's?
What is it? I can't get it off!
If a strong force is applied
to the surface of the water,
it'll spread...
...and then converge back in the middle!
Move!
Get away!
You too!
You're in my way!
Rounded everyone up at once.
I guess...
...it's like we've cleared the first hurdle.
You're both amazing!
Next time
Everyone, do your best until
Iida comes back with help!
Next time, "Game Over"!
There will be a violent explosion
in Yaoyorozu's physical development!
Go beyond!
Next time: Game Over
Plus Ultra!