U.A. High School's hero course.
U.A.
High School
Entrance Exam
Location
A training school for those whose goal is to acquire
the necessary qualifications needed for pro heroes.
Among similar courses across the country,
theirs is the most popular and most competitive...
...and their acceptance rate is less
than one in three hundred every year.
The hero who refused a National Honor Award—
The number one hero, All Might.
The hero who resolved the most incidents in history—
The Fiery Hero, Endeavor.
The winner of the Best Jeanist award eight years in a row—
Best Jeanist.
Graduating from U.A. is a requirement
for becoming a great hero.
And so, I also tackled the U.A. entrance exam.
I will take...
...the first step toward my dream of becoming a hero!
U.A. High School Hero Course
Entrance Exam Location
Battle Center B
What is this?
It's like a city!
They have more than one of these on the school grounds?
U.A.'s amazing!
As it says in the application requirements,
you listeners will be conducting
ten-minute mock urban battles after this!
Three different types of faux villains
are stationed in each battle center.
You earn points for each of them
based on their level of difficulty.
Your goal, dear listeners, is to use your Quirks
to earn points by immobilizing the faux villains.
Mock battles...
How can everyone be so confident?
Aren't they nervous?
They even have equipment to go with their Quirks...
Oh, it's the person I met at the school gates!
The nice person!
She was assigned to the same battle center, huh?
Oh yeah, I have to thank her for earlier.
He's here, too?
That girl appears to be trying to focus.
What are you doing here?
Are you taking the entrance exam
to interfere with everyone else?
N-N-No, of course not...
That guy's the one who was about to
trip in front of the school gates, right?
The one who winced after being called out.
At the very least, we have one
less rival to worry about, huh?
Lucky
Lucky for us.
I feel like the others think they
lucked out because I'm here...
Okay, start!
What's wrong?
There are no countdowns in real fights!
Run, run!
The die has been cast, you know!
Huh?
Huh?!
Huuuuh?!
I... I'm behind already!
Episode 4: Start Line
Episode 4:
Start Line
I'm behind.
Calm down, calm down.
It's fine. It's fine!
Dagoba Municipal Beach Park
I have All Might with me.
All right!
You swallowed the hair, right?
I don't feel any different, though...
Of course not!
What do you think the stomach does?
Well, you'll feel something in two or three hours.
I'm so nervous...
I need to hurry back, take a shower, and eat breakfast.
You have become a proper vessel,
but it was one that was made in a hurry.
You didn't even get to take it for a test drive...
Prepare yourself for the physical
repercussions it'll have on your body.
Huh?
I don't have time to explain
in detail, so I'll just tell you this.
When you use my Quirk, One For All, squeeze
your buttocks and yell this inside your heart—
"S—"
One point!
Target acquired.
I'll kill you!
It's coming!
It's coming! It's coming!
Huh?
Why can't I move?
Idiot, why?!
Thanks for distracting it!
A laser?
Merci!
We made a good team.
But... I don't think we'll meet again.
Adieu!
We won't meet again...?
Six minutes and two seconds left!
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh no!
Points...
I need points fast!
The nice person!
Release!
That's twenty-eight points...!
What? Twenty-eight?
Forty-five points!
Forty-five?!
That's thirty-two!
That one's mine! Don't take it!
It's first-come, first-served!
The number of enemies is decreasing fast!
Oh no!
In this practical exam, the examinees have not been
informed of the number of villains or their locations.
They have a limited amount of time in a vast area.
They have to draw the villains out from there.
Information gathering ability to understand
the situation before anyone else.
Mobility that can be used in many different circumstances.
Discernment to be able to stay calm in any situation.
And pure combat ability.
These basic abilities needed to keep the peace
in the streets are turned into points in this test.
Doesn't this year's group look promising?
Well, we can't know for sure yet.
Their true test is still to come.
An obstacle that will go crazy in narrow spaces.
I recommend that you listeners try to avoid it.
Isn't it a little too big?
An overwhelming threat.
How people act after they have
seen this shows their true nature.
This isn't funny!
I have to run away!
I'll get points as I run...
Shoot, shoot, shoot, I'm still at zero points!
Less than two minutes left!
Two minutes?!
It'll be wasted.
Everything All Might gave me...
...will be wasted!
Ow!
It'd be bad luck if you fell, right?
There is absolutely no merit in taking on that faux villain.
But that creates the opportunity...
...for it to shine brightly...
...and rise to the surface.
Squeeze your buttocks...
...and yell this inside your heart—
Smash...!
That's right.
It rises to the surface—
The most important qualification of a hero—
The spirit of self-sacrifice!
The conditions are the same as when I tried to save Kacchan.
But it's different.
This time—
One minute left!
Wait, this is All Might's power.
I'm able to jump this high now.
Landing should be a piece of cake-cake-cake-cake...
Break
"Break"?!
You have become a proper vessel,
but it was one that was made in a hurry.
Prepare yourself tor the physical
repercussions it'll have on your body.
Oh yeah!
I'm such an idiot!
A mere ten months was just barely enough time.
I can just barely hold this borrowed power.
I was being conceited for a second!
I've only been given the right to stand at the start line!
Think!
What to do? What to do?
Detroit Smash!
If I aim that move at the ground...!
Both my legs and my right arm are broken.
I only have my left arm!
And the timing—
If I'm too early or too late, I'll die!
Even if I succeed, I still won't have any points!
If I break my left arm, there's no way I'll pass!
Release...
I'm safe...
No, she saved me...
Is she all right?
She looks uninjured, at least...?
I'm so glad...
And...
...thank you!
If I can just get one point...
Time's...
...up!
What was that guy?
He suddenly jumped at the obstacle.
He seemed to have a reinforcement-type Quirk...
...but that was unusual...
But if he had such an amazing Quirk, what kind
of life did he live that made him so jumpy?
Maybe he was acting to trick others?
But it doesn't look like he gained anything from doing so.
Anyway, there's no mistaking that he's an amazing guy.
They're missing the point.
Didn't they see?
He jumped out to save that girl.
He was aware of the remaining time, his own
safety, and the points he needed to pass...
And even so, he did not hesitate at all!
If we had not been in an exam...
...of course, I would have done the same!
Wait.
"Exam"...?
"Of course"...?
Wait a sec...
Okay, good work.
Good work, good work.
Here you go. Here are some gummies.
Eat some gummies.
Th-Thanks.
Yes, yes, you, too.
Thanks...
That mademoiselle...
...is the backbone of U.A.
Oh dear...
...you were hurt this much by your own Quirk?
It's as if his body is not used to his Quirk yet.
Smooooooch...!
Old lady!
Wh-What was that?
U.A. High's licensed school nurse...
...the Youthful Heroine, Recovery Girl!
Her Quirk is the super-activation of healing ability.
U A. can only go through with such
a reckless entrance exam because of her.
Let's finish this quickly.
Is anyone else injured?
I see!
If this exam is set up like that...
Then he's...
One week later
Izuku...?
Izuku?
Izuku?!
Hey, are you all right?
Why are you smiling at the fish?
Oh, sorry!
I'm fine!
From self-scoring, I know that I just
barely passed the written exam.
But that was cancelled out by the
big fat zero in the practical exam.
And ever since the entrance exam,
I hadn't been able to contact All Might.
The results should arrive today or tomorrow, right?
Yeah...
Jeez, I think it's amazing that you even applied to U.A.!
Neighborhood Circular
I didn't even tell my mother about
what had happened with All Might.
I kept that secret so he could
continue being the Symbol of Peace.
There was no way I could tell anyone, not even my family.
All Might!
After you saw potential in me,
I'm sorry I didn't live up to it!
But I did what I thought was right.
All Might, you...
Izu-lzu-lzu...!
Izu-lzu-lzu...
I-I-I-Izuku!
It's here!
It came!
U.A. High School
It's here!
I am here as a projection!
All Might?!
Wait, this is from U.A., right...?
What?
I had to do some paperwork that took
some time, so I couldn't contact you.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I came to this town to work at U.A.
All Might is working at U.A.?
Hm? What is it?
Wrap it up?
But there is something I must talk to him about...
It's going to push everything else back?
All right.
Okay.
Even if you passed the written exam,
you got zero points on the practical exam.
Of course, that means you didn't pass—
I knew that.
I knew that...
I knew that, but...
...it's so frustrating...
—if that was all there was to it.
I am an entertainer, as well!
First, take a look at this video!
Excuse me... um...
The nice person?
She came to negotiate directly in person after the exam!
Negotiate what?
Keep watching to find out!
Um... the person with curly hair...
...and freckles...
Do you know who I'm talking about?
Um... kind of plain-looking...
It's me!
Is it possible for me to give him some of my points?
I heard him say, "If I can just get one point," so I thought...
...maybe he was still at zero points...
What the hell can you do?
At least the points he lost because of me...
There was absolutely no reason
for you to put yourself in danger!
He saved me!
Please! Please! Please!
In addition to now having a Quirk,
your actions spurred others to act.
The entrance exam the other day
was not graded only on villain points!
Even if you ask to, you cannot give him your points.
Anyway, there's no reason to give him any, female listener!
How can a hero course reject people
who save others and do the right thing?
Perish the thought!
Call that lip service?
Fine by me!
This is a job that requires risking one's
life to put that lip service into practice!
Rescue points!
And they're given by a panel of judges.
It's the other basic ability we at U.A. look at!
Midoriya Izuku, sixty points!
And Uraraka Ochako, forty-five points!
You both pass.
This is too crazy...
Come, young Midoriya.
This is...
...your hero academia!
Yes, sir!
After receiving a lot of help...
...my life changed and will continue to change.
And now...
...my dream high school life is about to begin!
Izukuuuuuuuuuuuuu...!
Food Menu
Next time
Welcome, young Midoriya!
This is U.A. High, your hero academia!
All Might, I'll do my best on the Quirk
assessment test on the first day!
Your homeroom teacher, Aizawa, shows no mercy
and expels people if they do badly, so be careful!
What?!
Next time, "What I Can Do for Now"!
Oh no, young Midoriya's index finger is...!
Go beyond!
Next time: What I Can Do for Now
Plus Ultra!