Kill... the Symbol of Peace.
Nice to meet you.
We are the League of Villains.
It may be presumptuous of us
but we have invited ourselves in to the
home of the heroes, U.A. High School
in order to have All Might,
the Symbol of Peace, take his last breath.
Everyone...!
Idiots!
He can erase Quirks
just by looking at them!
It's a Eraser Head!
Class rep!
Yes?
I entrust this duty to you.
Run to the school and tell them
about what is happening here.
But it would be a disgrace as
class rep to leave everyone behind—
Use your Quirk in order to save others!
Black Hole!
What do you mean, fight?
Are you stupid?!
This is the only way...
...to win!
Delaware Smash!
Even I...
Even I can...!
Move!
Get away!
You too!
You're in my way!
I guess...
...it's like we've cleared the first hurdle.
You're both amazing!
Bastard, get off!
I had a bowel movement this morning,
so those things will stick all day.
We were lucky that was all of them.
mutter mutter mutter mutter mutter mutter mutter mutter
I took a huge gamble.
Normally, they would have kept
some people underwater in reserve.
I was trying to keep my composure,
but I couldn't stay calm.
Midoriya, stop that.
This is dangerous,
I have to be more careful...
It's scary.
Rather than reflecting back,
shouldn't you think about what to do next?
Y-You're right.
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
Anyway, we should make
getting help our top priority.
It would be best to follow the shore
and avoid the central plaza
as we head toward the exit.
That's true.
Mr. Aizawa has drawn a large
number of villains to the plaza.
But... there are too many villains.
Of course, Mr. Aizawa
is trying to suppress them...
...but I think he overexerted himself by jumping
into that crowd of villains to protect us.
Wait, Midoriya, don't tell me you...
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
I'm not thinking of doing
anything that'll get in his way.
But... if we can just find an opening and
lessen Mr. Aizawa's load, even a little...
We had our first win in our first battle.
That was where we were mistaken.
We were under the illusion that our powers
could actually work against the enemy.
Episode 11: Game Over
Episode 11:
Landslide Zone
"Scatter you and kill you," huh?
I hate to say this...
...but you just look like guys with
Quirks they didn't know what to do with.
Th-This guy...
The instant we warped here...
Is he really a kid?
O-Ow...
Where is he?
I went through the trouble
of bringing this whole crowd, too...
Killing All Might...
At first glance, I thought
they had gathered all their elite
and would overpower him by numbers...
...but a closer look shows that
the pawns they prepared for us...
...were just a ragtag bunch of thugs.
From what I saw, there were only
four or five truly dangerous people.
If that's the case, then the
next step I should take is...
Hey, at this rate,
your cells will slowly die.
I want to be a hero.
I would like to avoid
something so cruel if possible.
On what basis do you
think you can kill All Might?
What's your plan?
Mountain Zone
Scary! Seriously, did you
see that just now?!
I saw the River Styx, seriously!
What the heck is up with these guys?!
What's going on?!
Worry about that later.
Right now, we need to figure out
how we'll get away from all these people.
Then give me a weapon, too!
You're the electric guy, aren't you?
Hurry up and take care of them!
You saw during the combat
training, didn't you?!
We were paired up!
I can only cover myself with electricity!
I can discharge electricity,
but it's not like I can control it!
I'll hit you two, too!
It's like, you know,
the same as Todoroki!
Even if we wanted to call for help,
there's interference jammin' the signal.
Listen, you two!
Right now, you can't count on me!
I'm counting on you!
You're a guy, stop whining.
Then, I'll use you as a human stun gun!
Seriously?! Idiot—!
Oh, it's working.
I'm strong!
You two can count on me!
Hey, you're too happy-go-lucky.
Stop messing around, kid!
Both of you should take
this more seriously.
Sorry, I thought it was
a good idea at the time.
Jirou
Kyouka
Quirk:      Earphone Jack
Jirou Kyouka!
Quirk: Earphone Jack!
She can amplify and send her own explosively
loud heartbeats by inserting her plugs.
She can also catch
very quiet sounds and stuff!
Kaminari, you should have requested something
to help you aim in your costume order!
Done!
Huh?!
It takes some time...
...to create something big!
A sheet?
Is it supposed to be a shield?
It's an insulation sheet 100 millimeters thick.
Kaminari.
I see.
In that case I can be...
...really strong!
Now then, I am worried about the others.
Let us join them quickly.
Wait, your clothes got super punk!
I can make them again!
Yaoyorozu
Momo
Quirk:
Creation
Yaoyorozu Momo.
Quirk: Creation!
She can create any non-living thing!
What makes this possible
is her vast knowledge and understanding
of the molecular structure of materials!
Violent growth...
Kaminari, don't look this way!
Kaminari
Denki
Quirk:
Electrification
Kaminari Denki.
Quirk: Electrification!
When he goes over his watt limit,
his brain short circuits,
and he becomes a huge idiot for a while!
Hey, Midoriya, we're just here
to see how things are going, okay?
Ribbit...
I know.
We'll run away the instant
it seems dangerous.
23 seconds.
The last boss?!
24 seconds.
20 seconds.
17 seconds.
Ribbit?
Damn.
It's hard to see because
you keep moving around...
...but there's an instant
when your hair falls.
That's when you have finished an action.
And the space in between
has gotten shorter and shorter.
Don't push yourself, Eraser Head.
My elbow's crumbling!
That Quirk isn't suited for fighting
long fights against a large group, is it?
Isn't this too different
from your usual job?
What you're good at...
...is a short fight after
a surprise attack, right?
Even so, you jumped right
in to fight us from the front.
Was that to put your students at ease?
You're so cool...
You're so cool...!
By the way, hero...
...I'm not the last boss.
Mr. Aizawa...
Black Hole, which sucks up
everything and turns it all to dust.
I see.
That is an astounding Quirk.
However, Thirteen, you are a hero who
works to rescue people from disasters.
As expected...
...your battle experience is less
then half of that of a normal hero!
A warp gate!
You turned yourself into dust.
H-He got me...
Teacher!
Iida, run!
Hurry!
Use your Quirk in order to save others!
Damn it...!
One of the children
who was not scattered...
We are only waiting for All Might.
If the other teachers are
called here, it will be hard for us!
Everyone...
...was entrusted...
...to me!
The whole class...
I will...!
Go!
Hurry!
Everyone... wait for me!
You impertinent—
I will not allow you to go outside!
An automatic door!
Should I kick it down?!
Is it a thickness I can kick down?!
You're impudent, four-eyes.
Be gone!
Villains.
The world of pros.
We still hadn't...
...seen anything yet.
I'll tell you, Eraser Head.
He's the anti-Symbol of Peace,
the bioengineered "Nomu."
Collapse Zone
Die...!
Is this all of them?
They're so weak.
All right.
Let's hurry up and go save the others!
If we're here, then everyone
else should be inside USJ, too.
I'm worried about the guys
with less offensive ability!
Besides, because we ran off ahead,
we slowed Thirteen down.
If Thirteen had been able
to suck up that fog,
then this wouldn't have happened!
As men, we have to take
responsibility for what we did!
If you want to go, then go by yourself.
I'm gonna kill that warp gate.
Huh?
You're gonna act
childish at a time like this?
Besides, that guy's attacks are—!
Shut up!
That gate bastard is the
enemy's way in and out.
I'm gonna cut off their getaway
route for when the time comes.
It's not like we don't
have a way to fight the fog.
Stop your chit-chatting!
Since you have left
your guard down—!
Anyway...
...if these small fry are the ones assigned to us,
pretty much everyone will be fine, right?
That reaction time was amazing...
Anyway, were you always
so calm and rational?
I thought you were more like—
Die! Die! Die!
Die!!
I'm always calm and rational,
you spiky-haired punk!
Oh yeah, that's more like it.
Then go if you want to!
Wait, wait!
Believing in our friends!
That's real manly, Bakugou!
I'll follow you!
Fire Zone
Damn it!
He's too fast!
I see 'im! Over there!
First, I need to make sure
I'm not caught by the enemy.
Squall Zone
Found you!
That makes six.
If we can just reduce
enemy numbers little by little...
...until help comes...!
You're being impudent, four-eyes.
Be gone!
I don't know the theory behind it,
but if he's wearing something like this...
...then it must mean
he has a physical body!
Go, Iida!
My body!
Oh, no!
However—!
I won't let you!
Go...!
Engine Boost!
He's going to call for support.
It's game over.
You can erase Quirks.
That's wonderful, but it's
nothing impressive.
In the face of overwhelming power...
...you might as well be Quirkless.
It's like he's breaking a twig...
I'm sure I erased his Quirk.
That means he is just that strong.
He's as strong as All Might...
M... Mi...
M-M-Midoriya, I can't take it anymore.
I'm sure you must be
having second thoughts, right?
Ribbit...
Shigaraki Tomura.
Kurogiri, did you kill Thirteen?
I put Thirteen out of action, but there
were students that I was unable to disperse...
...and one of them was able to run away.
Huh?
Kurogiri... you...!
If you weren't a warp gate,
I would have crushed you to pieces!
We can't win against dozens of pros.
It's game over.
Man, it's game over this time.
Let's go home.
They're going home?
Did he say they're going home?
That's what I heard.
A-All right!
We're saved!
Yes, but...
I have a bad feeling
about this, Midoriya.
Yeah.
For them to simply
retreat after doing all this...
Don't they want to kill All Might?
If they leave like this,
U.A. will just beef up their security.
"Game over"?
What is it?
What are those guys planning?
Oh, yeah.
Before we leave,
let's smash some of his
pride as the Symbol of Peace!
Tch.
You really are cool...
...Eraser Head.
Crap, crap, crap, crap!
He's clearly different
from our earlier opponents!
I've gotta save Asui and run away!
Let go of her!
Smash...!
My arm's not broken?!
I'm finally able to control
my power at a time like this?
I did it!
I was able to get in a good smash!
All right!
When in the world...
Wait, it didn't... hurt him...?
Don't you think they are trying so hard
because they have a way to kill him?
No way...
You move well.
Your "Smash"—
Are you a follower of All Might's?
Oh well.
I'm done with you.
Ribbit!
It's fine now.
I am here!
All Might!
Ribbit...
All... Might...
Ah...
...we're getting a "Continue."
Next time
It's fine now.
I am here!
Next time, "All Might."
As you can see, they will keep
going after my weakness!
Go beyond!
Next time: All Might
Plus Ultra!