Hey!
Deku has a Quirk, right?
You saw that extraordinary strength, didn't you?
Did he dare trick me?!
That damn nerd!
He's a piece of work...
...but his goal, his confidence,
his physical strength, and his Quirk...
...are way more amazing than mine.
But...
...that's why right now...
...I don't want... to lose...
Now, let's start the indoor person-to-person
combat training with Team A and Team D!
Come Deku...
...don't dodge.
I won't do so much damage that this fight
gets stopped, but I'm gonna get close!
Wow, he's like a martial arts master!
What's with this guy?
Did he read my moves?
My "Deku" isn't always going to mean "useless"!
Kacchan...
...my "Deku" means 'You can do it!"
Because Kacchan and I lived
in the same neighborhood...
...we've known each other
since we were little.
No Trespassing
You can't go in there!
Let's go kill the enemy!
Okay!
O-Okay...!
He was the type who could do
anything he tried his hand at...
...a rascal who led the group
of neighborhood kids.
Good or bad aside...
...Kacchan was full of confidence...
...and I thought he was so cool.
But...
...after his Quirk manifested...
...it accelerated him down the wrong path.
Even though you're scared...
That's what I...
...hate about you!
All men are not created equal.
This was the reality I learned about
society at the young age of four.
Episode 7: Deku vs. Kacchan
Episode 7
Hey, Bakugo!
Give me your status!
What happened?
Just shut up and defend.
I'm really angry right now!
I'm not asking about how you feel!
Hey!
He hung up...
Going off on his own like that...
What is wrong with him?!
Jeez!
What was Bakugo saying?
Can't tell with just the cameras
in a fixed position and no sound.
He's talking to his partner
over the small wireless radio.
You can bring that plus
the building's floor plan...
...and...
...this capture tape!
Once you wrap this around your opponent,
it shows that you have captured them.
The time limit is 15 minutes,
and the heroes don't know where
the nuclear weapon is located, right?
Yes!
The heroes are clearly at a disadvantage here!
Heroes should be able to turn the tables
on whatever predicament they're in.
Besides, didn't Mr. Aizawa tell you, too?
You know—
Here we go—
Plus Ultra!
Monsieur, Bakugo is—
Uraraka, go!
Looking away?
You must be sure of yourself.
The capture tape—?!
Hero Analysis for the Future
Hero notebook number 10...
Erasure Hero
Eraser Head
...page 18!
I'm glad I got to see
Eraser Head's moves in person!
What's next?
If it's Kacchan, he'll be impatient
and swing with his right again!
I was right!
That guy's amazing!
He's not even using his Quirk fighting against
the guy who finished first in the entrance exam!
He was always good at
reacting quickly in a crisis.
He spent years writing his notes
and internalizing them.
That fanboy knowledge...
...is now paying off...
...as it propels him forward.
He kicked first this time to keep me
from predicting his moves.
He's being cautious now.
Come back here, Deku!
I can't get close to him as easily anymore.
I need a plan.
Hey!
You tricked me, didn't you?!
Was it fun tricking me all this time?!
Huh?!
You have got a flashy Quirk there, don't you?!
Try and get me with it!
'Cause I'm way above you!
He seems real angry.
It's scary!
I had heard from young Midoriya that young Bakugo
thinks well of himself, but this is too much.
He completely ignored Uraraka and shot at me.
I knew it.
If they were going to send an advance guard, it would
have been better to send Iida, who has more mobility,
and I'm sure he knows that.
That probably means he's running wild on his own,
and the two of them aren't working together.
In the first place, our chances of winning are lowest
if we have a head-to-head battle with those two.
Current Location
Villain Hideout
If Uraraka and I both went to the
hideout, that's what would happen.
Current Location
Villain Hideout
And even if the two of us
stayed here to fight Kacchan,
we're in danger of running out of time.
Current Location
Villain Hideout
This is fine.
All that's left is for Uraraka to
find the weapon and Iida,
and then I'll head over for a 2-on-1 fight.
That's how we can win.
Current Location
Villain Hideout
That's assuming I can beat Kacchan, though.
It's fine.
As long as I'm careful
of his palms, I can do this.
Where are you?!
You damn nerd!
And...
...I forgot to tell you, Kacchan—
You're Quirkless!
How can you even stand
in the same ring as me?
It's not like I'm trying to
compete with you or anything!
Believe me!
I take back... everything I said!
That's why...
I'm going...!
My "Deku" means "You can do it!"
He's just a pebble!
Wow, Kacchan!
This is easy!
Ow!
Izuku, you really can't
do anything, can you?
Midoriya
Izuku
You can read the characters for
"Izuku" as "Deku," you know.
Kacchan, you can read?
You can't?
And "Deku" means someone
who can't do anything!
Ohhh?
Stop that...
Why don't you know?
Kacchan, how many times did yours skip?
Seven!
Wow!
As expected!
What about you, Deku?
Z-Zero times...
Why can't you do it?
Wow!
Lucky!
That's so cool!
Wow, that's an amazing Quirk!
It really is!
It's a flashy Quirk just right
for a hero, right, Katsuki?
Oh, I see!
I'm amazing!
No one is...
...as amazing as I am!
You're so lucky, Kacchan.
Your Quirk's so cool!
I hope I get mine soon, too.
No matter what Quirk you get,
you'll never beat me.
He's just a pebble!
Hey, did you hear?
Deku doesn't have a Quirk.
What? Really?
Yeah, it's called being "Quirkless."
That's so lame.
Too bad for him.
He's so weird!
Don't worry about it, Izuku.
You're the least amazing, Deku.
Forward march, members of
the Bakugo Hero Agency!
Kacchan!
Hey, are you okay?
He's fine.
Kacchan's real strong!
See?
I was fine!
Hurry up and get back up here!
'Kay, no problem!
Nothing was wrong!
Are you all right?
Can you stand?
It would have been bad
if you hit your head.
Don't look at me with that face!
You looked like you were asking for help...
Stop it...!
I'm...
I'm way above him!
Found it.
Now I just have to tell Deku
and hide until he gets here.
Baku go is a natural at being bad,
but that fits this training perfectly.
Then I must also devote
myself to being a villain.
That's right.
This is another trial to turn me into a man
who will not bring shame to the Iida family.
Become a villain!
Be dyed with evil in order to become a hero!
I am...
...extremely evil!
Bwa-ha-ha-ha
He's taking this so seriously!
Have you arrived, Uraraka?
I knew that you would come here alone
the instant Bakugo ran off by himself.
Your Quirk allows you to make
the objects you touch float.
That is why before you arrived...
...I put away all the things on this floor!
Now you cannot play your little tricks!
You have blundered, hero!
He's starting to look... like a villain...!
Deku!
Uraraka!
How's it going?
Iida found me.
Sorry!
I'm evil!
Right now, he's slowly...
Where are you?
The middle of the fifth floor.
Almost directly above!
We probably don't have much time left, either.
If we run out of time, our opponents win!
I can't...
I can't... lose this fight!
They're loaded.
Kacchan.
Why won't you use your Quirk?
Are you saying you can win
even if you don't use it?
Are you underestimating me, Deku?
I have no choice but to do it.
I can do it.
I can!
I'm not scared of you anymore!
With your stalking, you probably already know...
My Quirk, Explosion,
lets me secrete nitroglycerin-like sweat from the sweat
glands on the palm of my hand and make it explode.
If they made this the way I asked,
then these gauntlets will store
the nitroglycerin inside them, and...
Don't tell me that's...
Young Bakugo, stop!
Are you trying to kill him?!
If I don't hit him, he won't die!
This is supposed to be a class!
Young man!
Young Midoriya!
Is that...
even allowed...?
Wow...
The more that's stored in these
gauntlets, the stronger the blast.
Come on, use your Quirk, Deku...
Even if you're at full strength...
...I'll force you to surrender!
Bakugo, answer me!
Did you do that?
What in the world did you do?
This is my chance!
Explain yourself!
If we retrieve the weapon, we'll win!
I won't let you, hero!
We need to touch the weapon itself
for it to count as being retrieved.
Can she make herself float now, too?
Release!
It's a special move that's hard on my body!
Your Quirk is not a threat if
you cannot touch anything.
I'll hold out until time runs out!
Deku's trying so hard, though!
Hey, hey, what's wrong, Deku?
I didn't hit you, so you
can still move, can't you?
Come at me!
The explosion shot out.
He had his costume made so that his Quirk
would work even for long distances.
Uraraka, what's the situation?
Deku!
Ignoring me again?
I can't believe him!
Teacher, you should stop them!
That Bakugo's really crazy!
He's gonna kill him!
No...
I won't do so much damage that this fight
gets stopped, but I'm gonna get close!
If I don't hit him, he won't die!
Strangely enough, part of him is still sane.
I don't know if it's small-minded or what...
But anyway...
Young Bakugo, the next time you use that,
I'll stop the fight, and your team will lose.
Huh?
To attack on such a large scale inside
is inviting the destruction of the
stronghold you should be protecting.
That is a foolish plan for
both heroes and villains!
You will lose a lot of points for it!
As a teacher...
...I should stop this.
However...
Go to the pillar by the windows!
Over and out!
Fine, then!
Let's fight it out with our fists!
It's no good, I can't dodge it!
A counterattack...
Watch the timing...
Now!
What was that just now?
He doesn't look like the type to think...
...but he's more subtle than I expected.
What do you mean?
He changed his course in a blast
that doubled as a smoke screen
and then did it again immediately.
Getting in a clean hit
while fighting against inertia...
...requires fine lateral adjustments
to the power of the explosions.
He's too talented... too talented...
Ugh...
Look, here I come!
It's your favorite right swing!
Deku!
You are...
...below me!
He's not going to give me a chance to think...
I couldn't do it after all...
He's too strong...
I have no choice...
but to use it...
This is a lynching!
He can capture him for this exercise
by just wrapping the tape around him!
Those are not the actions of a hero.
I thought Midoriya was pretty amazing, too...
But in terms of combat power...
...Bakugo is definitely...
...a ball of natural instincts!
I should stop it...
But...
...I don't want to stop them!
He's running away?
That's not something a man should do...
...but he has no choice.
But something's strange...
Why...?
Why won't you use your Quirk?
Are you underestimating me?!
No...
You have been like this
ever since we were kids!
Have you been underestimating me
like that since then, you bastard?!
That's not it...
You're...
You're an amazing person, so that's why...
...I want to beat you!
I want to win...
...and surpass you, you idiot!
Don't look at me like that!
You damn nerd!
These are the first passionate emotions
he's shown other than "I want to be a hero!"
I'm sure this is necessary for you...
to arrive at the future you're looking at!
Detroit...
I said, this looks bad!
Teacher!
Both of you, sto—
Let's go, Uraraka!
Okay!
There's still no way I can
beat you one-on-one...
But—
...Smash!
What the—?
Sorry, Iida!
Improvised special move—
Comet Home Run!
You call that a home run?!
Release!
Retrieved!
No...!
The weapon...!
The weapon...! The weapon...!
That's what...
From the start, you were...
You are underestimating me, aren't you?!
I wasn't...
...going to use it...
Because I can't use it...
Because my body...
can't handle... the impact...
Mr. Aizawa too...
said... so...
But...
...this was all...
...I could think of!
Hero...
Hero team...
...wins!
Next time
You kids still have a lot of room to grow!
This is just the beginning!
Next time, "Bakugo's Start Line"!
Young Bakugo will get all teary-eyed!
Go beyond!
Next time: Bakugo's Start Line
Plus Ultra!