A hero...
...can always break out of a tough spot!
Hey, villain...
...have you ever heard these words?!
Go beyond!
Plus...
Ultra...!
I really have gotten weaker...
In my prime... five hits
would have been enough.
But it took more than 300 hits.
And now...
...I'm out of time...!
Now, villains...
I'm sure... we'd all like to
end this as soon as possible.
"Weaker"?
No way.
We've been completely overwhelmed.
I can't believe he did that to my Nomu...
He used a cheat?!
Hands up.
No Quirks allowed.
If you use your Quirks, I'll kill this guy.
Kaminari!
He got us.
We let our guard down completely.
An ambush after they made
us think we got all of them.
I can't believe we didn't predict this.
I don't wanna kill someone
who's an electric-type, like me,
but I guess I have to, huh?
An electric-type...
He was probably the one Todoroki
said was jamming communications.
I'm going over there.
Don't move a muscle.
You and Kaminari...
...electric-types like you
are born winners, right?
Huh?
What are you—
I mean, even if you aren't a hero,
there are a ton of jobs you could do.
You're in great demand, right?
Well, it's just an innocent thought.
I'm just wondering, why is
someone like you a villain?
I see.
Jiro can attack without moving
as long as she gets her plug in!
It's fine if you don't want to answer.
Give it up.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
A kid's naive thinking
only works on dumb adults.
Novice heroes shouldn't
make light of hostages.
If you two don't put up a fight...
...I'll let this idiot go.
Someone else's life...
...or your own?
Now.
Don't move.
Episode 13: In Each of Our Hearts
Episode 13:
Hey, what's going on?
He's not any weaker at all.
Did that guy... lie to me?!
What's wrong?
You're not coming?
You said you'd "clear" this
or something, right?
Come and get me if you can.
All... Might...
As expected.
It looks like there is
no need for us to fight.
Midoriya!
We should get out of here now!
It'll be worse if we end up
getting taken hostage instead!
No...
He's... bluffing.
It's almost lost under the cloud of dust...
...but I can see the steam-like substance...
that comes out when he transforms!
All Might is...!
I can't... move anymore...!
That Nomu thing was too strong...
Frankly...
...if I move even one step,
I won't be able to keep up this bluff.
I'll go back to by true form.
Just a little more...
Well, what's wrong?!
Hesitate!
If I can stall...
...for just a little longer...!
If only I had Nomu...!
That guy...
...would have been able to go up against him
without thinking about anything!
Shigaraki Tomura!
Please calm yourself.
Looking carefully...
I see he was damaged by Nomu's attacks...
...and definitely was weakened.
Besides...
...the children appear to be frozen in fear.
We still have underlings who can be used.
There are likely only a few minutes left
before reinforcements come.
If you and I work together...
we still have a chance of killing him.
Yeah...
Yeah, yeah...
That's right...
You're right.
Right.
We have no choice but to do it.
I mean, we have the last boss
right in front of our eyes.
All Might will do something
about the main bad guys.
Let's go help the others!
Midoriya?
I'm the only one who knows...
The mist guy is probably more dangerous.
All Might has most likely...
...gone past his limit.
If the mist guy toys with him...
...I'm sure...
You're coming, huh?!
This is revenge for Nomu!
Jeez, holy shit!
Hurry!
Everyone... hurry!
He s fast!
I'm the only who knows
the predicament he's in!
Midoriya!
They're broken... even though
I controlled it earlier...
But... I made it!
The hidden part of his body!
As long as I aim at that...
...I can blow him away!
Get away from All Might!
This hand is...
...the one from back then?!
I won't fall for that again!
They here?!
This attack...
Could it be...?
Sorry, everyone!
Sorry we're late!
I gathered all who were
immediately available!
Iida!
I, class 1-A representative...
...Iida Tenya,...
...have now returned!
Split up and protect the students!
Yes, sir!
Aw man, they're here.
It's game over now.
Shall we go home and
try again later, Kurogir—?
Someone whose Quirk can capture
them all from this distance...
Me!
Shigaraki Tomura!
This is...
...Thirteen!
I may have failed this time...
...but I will kill you next time...
...Symbol of Peace...
...All Might!
What the pros deal with...
What they fight against...
The world of evil...
That was an experience...
that we were not ready for yet.
I wasn't able...
...to do anything...!
That's not true.
If it weren't for those few
seconds you bought me,
I would have been killed.
You saved me again.
All Might...
I'm so glad...
...you're okay...!
My goodness...
I can't believe we let them escape after
they made such a big show of trespassing.
They caught us completely unguarded, huh?
More importantly, we must
make sure the students are safe.
If this many pro heroes have gathered here...
...then it looks like they did
not attack the whole school.
Midoriya!
Oh, Kirishima...
Are you all right?
Young Kirishima...
...I applaud your concern for your friend!
But wait, he'll find out!
Crap! Wait! Damn it!
K-K-Kirishima, wai—!
We want to make sure that
all the students are safe...
...so please gather in front of the gate.
We will deal with the injured here.
That makes sense.
Roger that!
Hey, he said to gather in front of the gate!
Thanks
You saved me, Cementoss.
I am a fan of yours, too.
Cementoss
Quirk:    Cement
Cementoss!
Quirk: Cement!
He can manipulate the cement
he touches like clay!
He's super strong in modern society!
Let's get you to the nurse's office
while keeping you hidden.
But man, you act recklessly
every time, huh?
If I didn't act recklessly,
I would have been killed.
That was how strong the enemy was.
Ouch...
I was shot in both arms and both legs...
We lost completely...
Even Nomu was defeated!
All the underlings were defeated in an instant!
Those kids were strong...
The Symbol of Peace was healthy...
You were wrong, Master!
No, I wasn't.
We were just not prepared enough.
Yes, we underestimated them.
It's good that we did it under that
cheap "League of Villains" name.
By the way...
...what about Master and
my joint creation, Nomu?
He was not retrieved?
He was blown away.
What?!
More precisely, without coordinates
to his precise location...
...I could not find him, even with my warp.
I did not have time for that.
After all we did to make him
as powerful as All Might!
Well, I suppose it cannot be helped.
That's unfortunate.
Power...
That's right.
There was one child who
was as fast as All Might.
Oh?
If he hadn't gotten in the way...
...we might have been able to kill All Might.
That brat...!
Brat!
Of course you have regrets.
But this was not a futile exercise.
Gather the elite.
Take all the time you need.
We cannot move freely, which is why
we need a symbol, like you.
Shigaraki Tomura.
Next time, show the world
that you are to be feared.
...16, 17, 18, 19.
Other than the boy with both legs seriously
injured, everyone else seems unharmed.
Ojiro.
I heard you were fired up this time.
You were strong by yourself, huh?
I thought everyone was by themselves.
I survived by using hit-and-run tactics.
Where were you, Hagakure?
In the landslide area!
Todoroki was super strong.
I was surprised!
Anyway, I'm glad you weren't hurt.
I almost froze her...
That was close.
Where, do you think...
...I was?!
I see...
So the people you fought
were also just hooligans?
They underestimated us
'cause we were kids.
Where--
So it was All Might who put
the hole in the dome after all?
That's some crazy power.
Yeah, as expected.
Where do you think I was?!
Where?
It's a secret!
Let's have the students return
to their classroom for now.
We won't be questioning them
right away, anyway, right?
Detective, what about Mr. Aizawa?
Comminuted fractures in both
arms and a facial fracture.
Fortunately, there does not seem
to be any serious brain damage.
However... his orbital floor
had broken into small pieces...
...and his eyes may suffer
from its aftereffects.
That's what he said.
Ribbit...
No...
What about Thirteen?
Thirteen has been treated.
The laceration from the back
to upper arm was bad,
but his life is not in danger.
All Might will also survive.
Recovery Girl's healing
is enough to treat him...
...so he's in the nurse's office.
Deku...!
What about Midoriya?!
Midori...?
Oh, treatment in the nurse's office
is enough for him, too.
Oh, good...
Now, go back to your classroom.
Okay.
Sansa, I also have some business
in the nurse's office.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yes, sir!
It's a cat.
Not a dog, huh?
Tch!
Bakugou, he said to
go back to the classroom!
I know, bastard!
We need to make some drastic improvements
to school security, don't we?
Yes.
A warp Quirk is already very rare...
...but for a villain to have one, of all things...
Detective Tsukauchi!
We received word that someone thought to be a villain
was captured in a grove of trees on school grounds.
How is it?
He has no apparent injuries and seemed docile, not resisting capture.
He does not respond even when
called out to, so he is thought to be mute.
Principal...
...we would like to investigate every
corner of the school, just in case.
Of course!
Some people might complain,
but you police have more authority.
Investigating is what you're good at.
I'm counting on you!
Teams, proceed with the
investigation of the school!
Nurse's Office
Because of the situation this time,
I can't really scold you...
I'm not sure...
...but I think I might have shortened
the time limit of my hero form again.
I hope I still have at least an hour...
All Might...
Well, it can't be helped.
These things happen.
Excuse me.
All Might, it's been a while.
Tsukauchi!
You're here, too?
All Might!
Is it all right to show that form...?
Yeah, it's fine.
Why?
Because he's Naomasa Tsukauchi,
my best friend in the force.
What's with that introduction?
Sorry to cut to the chase, but All Might,
can you give me details about the vill—
Wait! Please, wait!
More importantly,
are all the students okay?
What about Aizawa—
Eraser Head and Thirteen?
Other than that boy, only a few
students had light injuries...
...and the two teachers are
in stable condition for now.
I see.
If you three heroes had
not risked your lives...
...then the students would not have survived.
You're wrong about one thing, Tsukauchi.
The students also fought...
and risked their lives.
All Might...
Experience a real fight so soon..
...survive...
...and learn of fear and the world of adults,
have there been such first-years before?
The villains did something dumb.
This class is strong.
They will become strong heroes.
I am certain of that.
Nurse's Office
Well then, thank you very much!
Sure.
Be careful on your way home.
Yes.
The attack on USJ by
the League of Villains...
...was only the beginning...
...of what would become
a major incident later.
Deku!
But...
I had no way of knowing that at the time.
It doesn't matter, as long
as I get to the top!
I will refuse him completely.
I'm gonna go for it with
everything I have, too!
Go beyond!
The second season of the TV anime...
2nd season coming soon
...is coming!