Hey, you!
How are All Might's classes?
Uh, excuse me, I have to go
to the nurse's office!
Will you tell us about what the
Symbol of Peace is like as a teacher?!
Wh-What he's like?
Um...
He's very muscular!
What do you think of
All Might as a teacher?!
He made me recognize anew that I attend
an educational institution that is the best of the best.
Of course, his dignity and
character go without saying,
but we students are constantly
able to see his humorous side.
It is a unique opportunity to learn about
being a top hero directly from one.
Excuse me!
Can you tell me about All Migh—
Oh? You're the one who was
caught by the sludge villain...
Stop it!
Um, about All Might...
Wow, you're scruffy...
What's your deal?!
He's not on duty today.
You are disturbing the classes, please leave.
I would like to speak directly with All Might—
I feel like I've seen him before...
Don't you think you're too scruffy?!
I can't believe All Might was able
to work as a hero with all this.
Hey!
Let me see All Might just for a little—
Ah, stupid!
Wh-What the...?!
It's the U.A. Barrier.
That's what we call it.
That's so lame!
What the heck is that?
If someone tries to get in without
a student ID or a pass to enter,
the security system kicks in.
Apparently, there are sensors
all over the school.
What the heck?!
They think they're so high and mighty!
They could at least give a brief comment!
You said it, seriously!
We've been here for two days,
and they still won't say anything!
The news that All Might had been
hired as a teacher at U.A.
surprised the nation...
...and the media descended on the school
and caused a commotion for days.
Everyone knew about it.
Yeah... everyone.
Episode 9: Yeah, Just Do Your Best, Iida!
Episode 9:
Good work on yesterday's combat training.
I saw the video and results.
Bakugou.
You're talented, so don't act like a kid.
I know.
And Midoriya...
You settled it by breaking your arm again, huh?
You can't keep saying you can't help it
because you can't control your Quirk.
I don't like saying the same thing over and over.
As long as you fix the control issue,
there's a lot you'll be able to do.
Feel a sense of urgency, Midoriya.
Yes, sir!
Now let's get down to homeroom business.
Sorry about the late notice,
but today, I'll have you...
...take another special test?!
...decide on a class representative.
It's actually a normal school activity!
I want to be class rep! Pick me!
Me tool
I want to do it, too.
It's a job made for m—
I'll be the leader!
My manifesto is for all girls' skirts to be
30 centimeters above the knee!
In a normal class, it's about taking on
daily duties, so this wouldn't happen.
Let me do it! Me!
But here in the hero course,
it's a role that allows one to practice
being a top hero by leading a group.
Silence, please!
It is a job with the serious
responsibility of leading others!
It is not a job for just anyone
who wants to do it!
It is a calling that requires
the trust of those around you!
If we want to use democracy
to decide on a true leader...
...then we should hold
an election to choose one!
Your hand is raised the highest!
Why did you suggest that?
We haven't known each other for that long,
so how can we have trust or anything?
If that's the case, and everyone
votes for themselves...
Don't you think that is precisely why
whoever receives multiple votes here
can be truly considered
the most suitable person?!
What do you think, teacher?!
I don't care, as long as you decide
before homeroom is over.
Thank you very much!
Election Results
Yaoyorozu Momo                          2
Midoriya Izuku                            3
I got three votes?!
Why Deku?!
Who voted for him?!
Well, it's better than voting for you.
What did you say?!
It'll be scary if Bakugou finds out...
I give up! I give up!
Zero votes...
I knew that would happen...
That is only to be expected of a person's calling!
You voted for someone else, huh?
But you wanted to do it, too.
What are you trying to do, Iida?
Then, the class rep is Midoriya,
and the deputy class rep will be Yaoyorozu.
S-S-Seriously?
Seriously?
How vexing...
That might not be too bad.
After all's said and done, Midoriya
can be pretty fired up, anyway!
And Yaoyorozu was cool when we
were going over the battle results!
LunchRush's Eatery
There are a lot of people today, too!
That's because everyone in the hero course,
support course, and management course
meets in the same place.
The rice is so delicious!
Even though I've been chosen as class rep,
I don't know if I'm qualified for it.
You are.
It'll be fine.
Your courage and judgment
at critical moments...
...make you worth following.
That is why I voted for you.
It was you?
But didn't you want to be
class rep, too, Iida?
With glasses and everything.
Uraraka just talks without thinking...
Wanting to do it and being suitable
for it are different issues.
I merely did what I judged to be correct.
"Boku"?
You usually use "ore"...
Oh, that's...
I've been thinking...
Are you a rich boy, Iida?
Rich—!
I tried to change how I talk because
I didn't want to be called that.
Yes, my family has been
heroes for generations.
I'm the second son.
What?! Wow!
Do you know the Turbo Hero, Ingenium?
Of course!
He's a really popular hero who has
65 sidekicks working at his Tokyo agency!
Don't tell me...!
He is my elder brother!
He's telling us straight out!
That's amazing!
He is a likable hero who honors
the rules and leads people.
I set my sights on being a hero
because I want to be like my brother.
However, I think it is still
too soon for me to lead others.
Unlike me, Midoriya realized the point
of the practical portion of the entrance exam,
so he is more suitable for the job.
This might be the first time
I've seen you smile, Iida.
What, really?
I smile!
Ingenium is to Iida what All Might is to me.
But, I should tell him...
About the entrance exam...
An alarm?!
There has been a Level 3 security breach.
What?!
All students please evacuate outdoors promptly.
I repeat...
What's "Level 3 security"?
It means someone is trespassing
on school grounds!
I've never seen anything like this
in the three years I've been here!
You should hurry, too!
Don't push!
Wait, I'm falling!
I said, don't push!
Ow...!
What's going on all of a sudden?
As expected of the best of the best.
Everyone reacts quickly in a crisis!
Th-They're so quick that it's causing a panic!
Oh, shoot!
Midoriya!
Deku!
Who in the world trespassed?
That's...
...the press!
Give us All Might!
He's here, isn't he?!
We told you, he's not here!
If you just give us one
brief comment, we'll leave!
If you get one, you'll want another,
that's just how you are.
They're illegal trespassers, you know.
You could call them villains.
You think we can beat 'em up?
Don't do it, Mic.
They'll write up a bunch
of half-truths about you.
Let's wait for the police.
I wondered what it was,
but it's just the media.
Everyone, calm dow—
Ouch!
Wait, someone fell!
Don't push!
Where are the teachers?!
Are they busy trying
to deal with everything?!
Everyone, stop!
Slow down! Slow down!
Kirishima! Kaminari!
What the heck?!
Is there anyone here
who knows everything is fine?!
No one has noticed and
everyone's panicking!
Uraraka!
Iida!
What Midoriya...
...or my brother...
...would do?!
Uraraka!
Make me...
Make me float, Uraraka!
A place in everyone's line of sight...!
Engine boost!
Iida...!
Be concise... clear... and bold!
Boooom
Everyone, everything is fine!
It is just the media!
There is nothing to panic about!
Everything is fine!
This is U.A.!
Let us act in a way
befitting the best of the best!
The police are here!
Oh, good...
Goodbye, bad mass media!
Come on, class rep.
Start.
N-Now, let us decide on
the other class officers...
But first...
...can I say something?
I think... that Iida Tenya should be
the class rep after all!
He was able to get everyone's
attention in such a cool way.
I think... it would be best for Iida to do it.
I'm good with that, too.
Midoriya's saying it...
...and it's true that Iida was
a big help at the cafeteria today.
Yeah....
...and he kind of looked like the person
on the emergency exit signs, didn't he?
You're wasting time.
I don't care what you do,
just hurry up and do it.
If the class rep has nominated me,
then it cannot be helped.
From this day forth, I, Iida Tenya,
promise to do my best to carry out
the duties of class representative!
We're counting on you, Emergency Exit!
Emergency Exit Iida!
Do your best!
What about me...?
How were the ordinary members of
the press able to do something like this?
Someone instigated this.
Did someone evil slip in...
...or was it intended to be
a declaration of war?
Listen heroes, don't come after me.
If you do, I'm gonna kill
this rich family here!
It's fine now, family!
Missouri Smash!
Why? Because I am here...
...on my way to work!
A hit-and-run!
It'll be bad if I'm late, but...!
I've gotten slower...?
After I gave young Midoriya One For All...
...my powers have been weakening.
On top of that...
...after forcing myself then, the time I can
spend in this form has gotten even shorter.
You told young Bakugou?
I'm sorry.
I didn't even tell my mom...
...but for some reason,
I just had to tell him....
I'm really sorry.
I judged that he was not the type to show off,
so I did not admonish him strongly...
...but this seems to be the result
of his sincerity backfiring.
Fortunately, young Bakugou
did not seem to take it seriously...
...so I'll let it go this time.
But please don't do it again.
Please think carefully about
what it means to have this power.
If word gets out,
it's clear that the world would be teeming
with those trying to steal the power from you.
This secret should be kept both
to prevent chaos in society...
...and for your sake.
Understand?
Even if he is a suitable vessel...
...he is still only a 15-year-old boy.
I have to pull myself together.
Someone's barricaded themselves
in in the neighboring town!
For today's hero basic training...
...it's turned into a class with three instructors,
All Might and me, and one more person.
"Turned into"?
I wonder if it's a special case?
Excuse me!
What will we be doing?
Disasters, shipwrecks,
and everything in between.
It's rescue training.
Rescue...
Looks like it'll be a lot of work this time, too.
Right?
Idiot, this is the duty of a hero!
My arms are ready to rumble!
No one can beat me in water, ribbit.
Hey, I'm not done.
You can decide if you want to wear
your costume or not this time.
Because there are probably costumes
that limit your abilities, too.
The training will take place off-campus,
so we're taking a bus.
That is all. Start getting ready.
Rescue training...
What I've admired...
It's training to get another step closer
to being the greatest hero.
I'll do my best!
Huh?
Deku, you're wearing your P.E. clothes.
Where's your costume?
It got ripped up during
the combat training...
...so I'm waiting for
the support company to fix it.
Class 1-A, gather round!
Form two lines by your student numbers in order
to make boarding the bus go smoothly!
Smoothly
Iida's... going at full throttle.
Shoot!
I didn't think it'd be this type of bus...!
There was no point, huh?
I say whatever comes to mind.
Midoriya...
Um, yes, Asui?!
Call me "Tsu."
Ugh...! Um...
Your Quirk is like All Might's.
Huh?! Y-Y-You think so?
But... I'm... uh...
Wait a sec, Tsu, All Might
doesn't get hurt when he uses his.
They just kind of look the same.
But it's nice to have a simple
augmenting-type Quirk.
You can do lots of flashy stuff!
My Hardening's strong against others,
but unfortunately, it doesn't look like much.
I think it's really cool!
It's a Quirk that can
definitely pass as a pro's!
A pro's, huh?
But you have to think about popularity
as a hero, too, you know.
My Navel Laser is pro-level
in both flashiness and strength.
But it's not great that
it gives you a stomachache.
Well, if you're talking
about flashy and strong,
it's gotta be Todoroki and
Bakugou, though, huh?
Bakugou's always mad, so he doesn't
seem like he'll be popular, though.
What the hell!
You wanna fight!
See?
We haven't known each other that long,
so it's amazing that everyone already knows
his personality is crap steeped in sewage.
What's with that vocabulary, bastard?!
I'll kill you!
Kacchan's being teased...
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
That's U.A. for you!
What a vulgar conversation.
But I like stuff like this, too!
We're here.
Stop messing around.
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir...
Everyone, I have been waiting for you.
It's the Space Hero, Thirteen!
The gentlemanly hero who has rescued
tons of people from disasters!
Oh, I love Thirteen!
Let's go inside without delay.
Look forward to working with you!
Woooow!
It looks like USJ!
Universal Studios Japan
A shipwreck...
...a landslide...
...a fire...
...a windstorm...
...et cetera.
It is a training ground that I made with
different types of accidents and disasters.
It's called the "Unforeseen Simulation Joint,"
or "USJ" for short!
It really is USJ.
Thirteen, where's All Might?
He was supposed to meet us here.
About that...
It looks like he did too much hero work
on his way to work and ran out of time...
...so he's resting in the lounge.
Sorry...
I should be able to go
for a little bit at the end.
I'm really sorry!
That's the height of irrationality.
Well, we took precautions just in case...
It can't be helped.
Shall we begin?
Let's see...
Before we begin, let me say one thing, or two...
three... four... five... six... seven...
It's increasing...!
Everyone, I am sure you are aware of...
...my Quirk, Black Hole.
I can suck up anything
and turn it to dust.
You have been able to use that Quirk
to save people from all kinds of disasters, right?
Yes.
But it is a power that can kill easily.
Some of you also have Quirks like that, right?
In a superhuman society, personal Quirks
have been certified and stringently regulated,
so that doesn't seem to be
a problem at first glance.
However, please do not forget...
...that there are many Quirks that
can easily kill with one wrong step.
With Aizawa's physical fitness test...
...you found out about the possibility
of your own hidden powers.
And with All Might's
person-to-person combat training...
...I think you experienced the danger
of using those powers against others.
This class is a fresh start.
You shall learn how to use your
Quirks to save people's lives.
You do not have powers
so you can harm others.
I hope you leave here with the understanding
that you have powers in order to help others.
Thirteen's so cool!
That is all.
Thank you for listening.
That was wonderful!
Bravo! Bravo!
All right then, first—
Gather together and don't move!
Thirteen, protect the students!
What's that?
Is this like the entrance exam
where the lessors already started?
Don't move!
Those are...
...villains.
And coincidentally,
...during the time when we were supposed
to be practicing saving lives...
...they showed up in front of us.
Next time
Asui, the villains have attacked!
Call me "Tsu."
T-T-Tsu...
N-Next time, "Encounter with the Unknown."
I know why Mineta's hair is like that now.
Next time: Encounter with the Unknown
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!