You're so lucky, Kacchan.
Your Quirk's so cool!
I hope I get mine soon, too.
No matter what Quirk you get,
you'll never beat me.
He's just a pebble!
Until a little while ago...
...he was just a pebble on the side of the road.
You have got a flashy Quirk there, don't you?!
Hey!
You tricked me, didn't you?!
Was it fun tricking me all this time?!
Try and get me with it!
'Cause I'm way above you!
What the—?
Improvised special move—
Comet Home Run!
You call that a home run?!
Retrieved!
From the start, you were...
I wasn't...
...going to use it...
Because I can't use it...
Because my body...
...can't handle... the impact...
Mr. Aizawa too...
...said... so...
But...
...this was all...
...I could think of!
Someone told me...
"You can become a hero"...
That's why...
I'm going...!
Indoor person-to-person combat training...
Uraraka?!
Hero team...
...wins!
What the heck?
The losers are practically uninjured...
...and the winners are on the ground...
They lost the battle, but won the war, huh?
This is training, though.
To the nurse's office.
I know.
My right...
Deku predicted it...
On top of that...
...he found a way to win the exercise...
You're an amazing person,
so that's why I want to beat you!
I want to win...
...and surpass you, you idiot!
Does that mean...
...even if we fought all-out...
...Deku would completely beat...?
Come back, young Bakugou.
It's time to review the results.
Whether you win or lose...
...looking back and learning from
your experiences is a part of life.
Episode 8: Bakugou's Start Line
Episode 8
Person-To-Person Combat Training
Battle 1
Review
Well, even if I say that...
...the MVP for this battle was young Iida!
It's not either of the winners, Ochako or Midoriya?
Hmm, well...
Why is that?
Does anyone know?!
Yes, Mr. All Might.
That is because Iida adapted
the most to the context of the training.
From watching the match, it appears Bakugou acted
on his own because of an obviously personal grudge.
And as Mr. All Might said earlier...
...it is foolish to launch
a large-scale attack indoors.
In the same way, taking into consideration
the damage he received...
...Midoriya's plan was also rash.
As for Uraraka...
She let her guard down mid-battle...
...and her final attack was too reckless.
If she treated the papier-mache
as a real weapon...
...she would not have been able to
do something so dangerous.
Iida had prepared for
his opponent's arrival...
...and assumed it would be
a fight over the weapon...
...which made him late in
responding to the final attack.
The hero team only won because they took
advantage of the fact that this was training.
They were practically breaking the rules.
She said more than I expected.
W-Well, young Iida also has parts
of him that could be more relaxed...
...but well...
that was correct!
Start with
the basics
to develop
depth of
learning
Devote oneself
wholeheartedly
We should always start with the
basics to develop depth of learning.
We must strive to devote
ourselves wholeheartedly.
Otherwise, we cannot
become top heroes.
Yaoyorozu Momo
Yaoyorozu Momo!
One of four students admitted to the
hero course based on recommendations!
All right everyone, let's change locations
and start the second match.
Tackle this training after thinking about
what we just talked about.
Yes, sir!
Battle Building B
Match two!
Duo B are the heroes!
Duo I are the villains!
Ojiro.
I'm going to get serious!
I'll take off my gloves and boots, too!
O-Okay...
Hagakure, that's the correct
decision as an invisible person,
but that's not great for a girl,
morally speaking.
You can't look, okay?
I can't see you anyway.
Now, let s start the second indoor
person-to-person combat training match!
Shouji
Mezou
Quirk:
Dupli-Arms
Shouji Mezou!
Quirk: Dupli-Arms!
He can create replicas of his own
body parts on the tips of his tentacles.
One in the hall on the
north side of the fourth floor.
The other is somewhere
on the same floor...
They're barefoot...
The invisible one is coming to
ambush and capture us, huh?
Go outside.
It's dangerous.
I'm sure our opponents intend
to fight a defensive battle...
...but that does not matter to me.
Owww...
My feet!
Th-This Quirk is...!
You can move if you want...
...but the skin on your feet will come off,
so you won't be able to fight your best.
He did not cause any damage to
his teammate or the nuclear weapon,
and on top of that, he weakened the enemy.
He's so strong!
Hero team wins!
Heat?
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Sorry.
The difference in our ability was too great.
Todoroki Shouto
Quirk:
Half-Cold, Half-Hot
Todoroki Shouto!
He's another one of the four admitted to
the hero course based on recommendations.
His Quirk is Half-Cold, Half-Hot.
He freezes with his right
and burns with his left!
The range and temperature
of his ability is unknown?!
What is he, a monster?!
W-Wow!
What's up with that Quirk?
As expected of someone who
got in through recommendations.
All right, everyone gather round
for a review of the second match.
Next, we will begin the third match!
Yes, sir!
Battle Building C
Duo
Ribbit, ribbit.
No, no, no, no!
Duo
Yahoo!
Sorry, sorry!
Good work everyone!
We didn't have any major injuries
other than young Midoriya, either!
You guys took this on seriously!
You all did a good job
for your first training!
To have such a proper class
after Mr. Aizawa's class...
...it's kind of anticlimactic...
We're free to have proper classes, as well!
Well then, I must review
the results with young Midoriya!
Change and return...
...to the classroom!
All Might's amazing!
Why was he in such a hurry?
So cool...
Young Bakugou...
...is a mass of pride...
...and there's nothing more fragile
than a heart that's swelled to bursting.
As his teacher, I must counsel him well.
But right now...
Staff Only
Open
Close
If I teach a class...
...I barely have enough time.
Shit!
Nurse's Office
The school year has just begun,
and he's already been in here three times!
Why didn't you stop him, All Might?!
I apologize, Recovery Girl.
What are you apologizing to me for?
On top of his total exhaustion,
he was here just yesterday.
I can't treat him all at once.
I did first-aid treatment already,
so after the IV is finished, we can only wait
for his body to heal slowly overnight.
Jeez...
I know he's your favorite and that you passed on your
powers to him, but doesn't mean you should spoil him!
There is nothing I can say to that.
Because I wanted to consider his feelings...
...I hesitated to stop the training match.
Even so...
...will you please not talk about
One For All so loudly?!
Yes, yes, Mr. Natural-Born Hero.
Mr. Symbol of Peace.
My injury and this form of mine are common knowledge
among the U.A. teachers and a certain group of pros...
...but the secret of my Quirk, One For All,
...is known only to you, the principal,
my close friends, and young Midoriya.
I know it's not like you want
to rest on your laurels at the top...
...but is being a "natural-born hero" or the
"Symbol of Peace" really that important?
If I no longer am, then the superhuman
society will be seized by evil.
This is...
...the responsibility of those of us with this power.
If that's the case, then it's even more important
for you to learn what it means to guide someone!
Yes, ma'am.
You...
...can become a hero.
Will you accept my power?
"One For All"...
Smash...!
Come, young Midoriya.
This is your...
...hero academia!
I have a lot to learn from here on out...
...in order to get closer to
what I dream of becoming!
My "Deku" isn't always going to mean "useless"!
Kacchan...
...my "Deku" means 'You can do it!"
It's... late afternoon...?
Are you awake?
That's all for today's treatment.
Come back again tomorrow, okay?
I ended up skipping my afternoon classes...
Mr. Aizawa's gonna wrap me
in those bindings again...
Oh, Midoriya's here!
Good work!
Man, I don't know what you
were saying during the match,
but you were fired up!
I can't believe you fought evenly with Bakugou,
who was first in the entrance exam!
You did a good job dodging!
You guys did that in the first match,
so the rest of us had to give it our all, too.
You were far from elegant, but—
You did a good job dodging!
H-Huh?
I'm Kirishima Eijirou!
We're all going over the
training together right now.
I'm Sero Hanta.
I'm Aoyama Yu—
I'm Ashido Mina!
You did a good job dodging!
I'm Asui Tsuyu.
Call me Tsu.
I'm Sato!
Um...
Er—
I'm Mineta!
Where the heck did you pop out from?
I am Aoyama Yuuga.
You did terrible in the training.
I am a man who never stops shining.
You're too loud.
Tokoyami!
That desk is not a chair!
Get off immediately!
It's not that big a deal, is it?
Wh—?!
What's with those hands, anyway?
You people...
I cannot condone actions
that disrespect the desks
the great men and women who are
our upperclassmen once used!
You're too loud.
Iida never wavers, does he?
Hey, Uraraka, wanna grab
a bite to eat sometime?
What do you like?
Mochi—
Wait, Deku, she didn't heal your injuries?
Oh, uh, it's because of how
much stamina I have, and...
Huh?
Um, Uraraka... more importantly...
We all tried to stop him,
but he went home just now
without saying anything.
Hey!
You tricked me, didn't you?!
Was it fun tricking me all this time?!
You have got a flashy Quirk there, don't you?!
Kacchan!
Huh?
It's a secret I didn't even tell my mom.
But...
There's one thing...
...I feel like I have to tell you.
My Quirk...
...is something I received
from someone else.
Huh?
I can't say who I got it from, though!
I won't say.
But... it's like a story out of
comic books, except it's true.
On top of that, I still can't control it properly.
It's just a borrowed power
that I haven't made my own yet.
That's why...
...I tried to beat you without using it.
But in the end, I couldn't win
and had to rely on it.
I've still got a long way to go...
That's why...
That's why...!
One day...
...I will make this Quirk my own...
...and beat you with my own power!
I just came to tell him I didn't trick him....
What am I...?
What the hell is that?
"Borrowed power"?
You're talking nonsense.
What are you trying to do, make me out
to be more of a fool than you already have?
Huh?!
What are you trying to say?
Today, I lost to you...!
That's all it was...!
That's all!
As I watched the ice guy...
...I thought, "I can't beat him"!
...it is foolish to launch
a large-scale attack indoors.
Damn it!
I ended up agreeing with
what that ponytail girl said!
Damn it!
Damn it, damn it!
Hey, you too, Deku!
I'm just...!
I'm just getting started!
You hear?!
Here, I will become number one!
You won't beat me again, bastard!
There he is!
Young...
...Bakugou!
Just so you know...
...pride is important.
You definitely have the abilities
needed to become a pro.
You still have a lot of—
Let go of me, All Might.
I can't walk.
I'll become a hero that surpasses
even you without you telling me!
Huh?
Uh...
Right...
He's gotten over it.
It's hard being a teacher...
What was that?
The fated battle between men.
It looked like Midoriya was just
giving excuses one-sidedly, though.
The fated battle between men!
Kacchan's fuse has been lit.
That doesn't change what I have to do.
I just have to chase after him!
Young Midoriya!
What were you talking about
with young Bakugou?
Um, we were, uh...
Hmm...
I'm so curious.
Why don't you tell me in detail?
U-Um... a-actually...
A few days later...
...we would find out...
...how terrifying the truly cunning villains...
All Might warned us about were.
Closes Agency
Temporarily
All Might
Becomes
U.A. Teacher!
Did you see this?
It says he's a teacher...
Hey.
What do you think will happen...
...if the Symbol of Peace...
...is killed by villains?
Next time
All heroes have their starting point!
Next time, "Yeah, Just Do Your Best, Iida!"
A lot of stuff happens and young Midoriya
gets swept away in the crowd!
Look forward to it!
Go beeeeeeyond!
Next time: Yeah, Just Do Your Best, Iida!
Plus Ultra!