That's mean, Kacchan.
Can't you see he's crying?
If you keep going...
I-I-I'll nevelfolgiveyou!
Even though you're Quirkless...
...you're pretending to be a hero, Deku?
All men are not created equal.
This was the reality I learned
about society at the young age of four.
And that was my...
...first and last setback.
"Midoriya Izuku"
"Tatooin Station"
That's a huge villain!
It all began in China, in Qingqing City.
There was news that a baby that gave off light was born.
"Papa"
Ever since then, superpowers
were discovered in various places...
...and time passed without the cause being identified.
Before we knew it, the supernatural became normal,
...and dreams became reality.
The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos...
...the profession that everyone once dreamed
about and admired came into the limelight.
That profession is...
Oh, it's Death Arms!
He carries out justice through his great physical strength—
The Punching Hero!
Everyone, this is dangerous.
Stay back, stay back!
The rescue specialist, Backdraft, is here, too!
But man, turning into a monster's an amazing Quirk.
What did he do?
He stole someone's bag and
went out of control when he was cornered.
A Quirk like that, and he's a bag snatcher?
I'm sorry, the train's...
Yes, I don't know what time I will make it into work...
You can do it, Kamui!
Get away!
Who's fighting?
Kamui Woods!
The young and talented rising star!
You were the one asking,
but you gave a perfect commentary, kid.
You're a fanboy, aren't you?
Uh, well...
Illegal use of powers during rush hour
and robbery resulting in bodily injury.
You are the incarnation of evil.
Oh, here it comes!
Show us something flashy, Tree-Man!
Pre-emptive...
...Binding...
...Lacquered Chain Prison!
Canyon Cannon!
Huh?
Here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is.
Today is the day of my debut!
My name is Mt. Lady.
A pleasure to make your ass-quaintance.
Here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is.
Sh-She's getting the credit...
Along with the superpowers
came an explosive increase in crime.
As the country was stuck in the
slow progress of drastic law reforms,
courageous people started performing
heroic acts from out of comic books.
Guarding against superpowers and defending against evil.
Heroes were soon accepted by the public,
and it was established as an official position.
Based on their performance, they are paid by the government...
...and gain renown among the masses.
Gigantification, huh?
She looks like she'll be popular, and it's an amazing Quirk,
but thinking about the damage to
the city that'll go hand in hand with that,
its use might be limited?
No, but whether or not she can control the size...
Hey wait, you're taking notes?
You wanna be a hero?
That's great! You can do it!
Yes! I'll do my best!
"Episode 1. Midoriya Izuku: Origin"
"Aldera Junior High"
Since you're all third years, it's time
for you to think seriously about your future.
I'll pass out handouts for your future plans now, but...
...you're all...
...pretty much planning to go into the hero course, right?
Yes!
Yes, yes, you all have wonderful Quirks!
But using your powers at school is against the rules!
Teach!
Don't lump us all in the same group.
I'm not gonna be stuck at the
bottom with the rest of these rejects!
"Bakugou Katsuki"
That was uncalled for, Katsuki!
Yeah, yeah!
You all should shut up like the extras you are!
Oh, if I remember correctly,
you want to go to U.A. High, right, Bakugou?
U.A.? That national school?!
It was in the top 0.2% this year, you know!
Their acceptance rate's always really low, too!
That's exactly why you guys are just extras!
I aced the mock test!
I'm the only one at this school
who could possibly get into U.A.
I'll definitely surpass All Might and become the top hero!
My name'll be inscribed on the list of top earners!
Oh yeah, Midoriya wanted to go to U.A., too, right?
Huh? Midoriya? No way!
You can't get into the hero course just by studying!
Th-They got rid of that rule!
There's just no precedent...
Hey, Deku!
You're below the rejects!
You're Quirkless!
How can you even stand in the same ring as me?
No, wait, Kacchan!
It's not like I'm trying to compete with you or anything!
Believe me!
It's just that it's been my goal ever since I was little.
And well...
...I won't know unless I try...
Whaddaya mean, unless you try?!
Are you taking the test for fun?!
What the hell can you do?
You're Quirkless!
"12:02 p.m. - The same city"
Thief!
Someone!
Catch me if you can!
Huh? There's no hero around.
Normally someone would come right away.
This guy's taking advantage of the chaos from this morning.
There are tons of people around who
don't know what to do with their Quirks.
There's no end to them.
There is an end.
Why?
Because I am here!
Hey, let's go to karaoke!
Sure, nothing better to do.
The incident this morning is all over the headlines!
I wanna hurry up and go home
so I can write it down in my notebook.
We're not done talking yet, Deku.
Katsuki, what's that?
"Hero Analysis for the Future"
Huh?
"Hero Analysis for the Future"?
Seriously?
Midoriya...
I-It's fine, isn't it?
Give it back!
That's mean...
What?!
Most top first-string heroes have
stories about them from their school days.
I want the shine of being able to be
called the only student to make it into U.A.
from this mediocre city junior high school.
I mean, I'm a perfectionist.
He's so petty.
So anyway...
...don't apply to U.A., nerd.
Come on, you could at least say something back.
Don't say that.
He's pathetic.
He still can't face reality.
If you wanna be a hero that badly,
there's a quick way to do it.
Believe that you'll be born with a Quirk in your next life
and take a last chance dive off the roof!
What?
Idiot!
If I really jumped, that would mean you instigated a suicide!
Think before you speak!
That's not fish food, stupid.
That's my notebook...
Stupid...
"Hero Analysis for the Future"
Stupid bastard...
Mom!
Mom, the computer!
Again?
Hurry!
Jeez, you have probably added
ten thousand views just by yourself, Izuku.
It's too scary for me. I can't watch it.
That was an old video.
A disaster that happened a long time ago.
The video of a hero that debuted right after that.
Can you see that?
He's already saved a hundred people!
That's crazy! It hasn't even been ten minutes!
That's crazy!
He's laughing!
It's fine now.
Why?
Because I am here.
He's so cool!
Once I get my Quirk, I wanna be like him, too!
You should probably give it up.
That's...
Is something wrong with him after all?
Most of the other kindergarteners'
Quirks have already manifested...
He's the only one...
Excuse me, but you're fourth generation, right, ma'am?
May I ask about your Quirk?
Yes, of course.
I can pull small objects to me.
My husband can breathe fire.
Normally, by age four, he would
have manifested one of those Quirks,
or some combination of the two.
In the past, when the superpowers first started showing up,
the results of an early research study were published.
It became common practice to see if
the pinky toe was missing a joint or not.
When parts of the body aren't used,
they're deemed unnecessary.
People who didn't have the joint
were thought to be a newly evolved form.
You can see by looking at this x-ray
that Izuku has two joints.
It's unusual to see that these days,
but that means he has no Quirk.
Can you see that?
He's already saved a hundred people!
That's crazy! It hasn't even been ten minutes!
That's crazy!
He's laughing!
It's fine now.
Why?
Because I am here.
Mom...
He saves everyone with a smile,
no matter what trouble they're in...
He's such a cool hero...
Can I... be a hero, too?
I'm sorry, Izuku!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
No, that's not it.
That's not it, Mom.
What I wanted you to say back then was...
Watch Your Head
You decided back then, didn't you?
That's right.
Don't worry about what other people think!
Hold your head up high and plunge forward!
A villain?!
A medium-sized invisibility cloak...
Don't worry.
I'm just going to take over your body.
Calm down.
It'll only hurt for about 45 seconds.
You'll feel better soon.
I can't... breathe...
You can't grab me. I'm fluid!
Thanks for your help.
You're my hero.
I didn't think that had come to this city.
My body...
There's no strength...
I'm dying... Am I dying?
I'm dying...
Somebody... Somebody...!
No...!
It's all right now, young man.
I am here!
Texas Smash!
Wind pressure...?!
All... Migh...
Hey! Hey! He— Oh.
Thank goodness!
I'm glad you're okay!
Sorry 'bout getting you caught up in my villain fighting.
I don't usually make mistakes like this,
but I was in high spirits on my day off in a new place.
But, you were a big help. Thanks!
I captured him safely!
The number one hero... All Might...
H-He's the real thing...
He looks completely different in person!
Oh, right! An a-autograph! Where should I—?
In that notebook—
He already did!
Th-Thank you very much!
It'll be an heirloom! A family treasure!
Okay!
Well, I need take this guy to the police.
See you again on the other side of the screen!
Wait, already?
Pros are constantly fighting enemies and time.
Wait...
There are still... things I want to ask...
Well then,
I'm counting on your continued support!
Wait.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Let go of me! Your fanaticism is too much!
If I... let go now... I'll... I'll die...!
That's true.
I... have... a lot of things... I want to ask you directly!
Okay, okay!
I get it, so close your eyes and mouth!
Shit.
Th-That was scary...
Good grief.
If you talk to the people downstairs,
I'm sure they'll let you down.
I seriously am outta time, so I really must go.
Wait! Um...
No! I will not wait!
But—
You should probably give it up.
I'm sorry, Izuku!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
What the hell can you do?
You're Quirkless!
That might be true...
But... even so... I...
Even if I don't have a Quirk, can I become a hero?
Can even someone without a Quirk be like you?
My meeting with All Might... This miracle...
At the time, I couldn't even imagine
how much it would change my fate.
"Next time"
I am here for the next episode preview!
What? The villain I caught escaped?
It took a boy hostage and is going wild around town?
But I can't use my powers for much longer.
You're pathetic, All Might!
Is there another hero around?
Next time, "What It Takes to Be a Hero"!
Pros are always risking their lives!
Go beyond!
"Next time: What It Takes to Be a Hero"
Plus Ultra!