Impossible!
You're telling me you bet 15,000,000 Yen on a ‘pig’?
Well, yeah.
I thought you'd notice since Yumeko's win in the third round was so obvious.
It wasn’t easy for me either.
Why are you getting high-and-mighty?
you only won once so far!
I’m fine with that.
As long as I have the funds to gamble there's no way I'd lose against a shitty idiot like you.
What was that?!
I’m certain this goes without saying,
but violent conduct is prohibited.
Saotome-sama, I ask you to refrain from such provocations as well.
Sure, sure.
Now then, let us begin the fifth turn.
Damn livestock...
I'll strip them down to nothing!
Bet!
Kiwatari, one chip.
Ca–
Fold.
Raise.
kiwatari, four chips.
No, wait. That's a bluff.
Call! Kiwatari, one chip;
tsubomi, two chips.
Now, please reveal your hands.
Seven and nine.
‘Pig’.
If she’s bluffing, I can win. She has...
Two and five, a ‘mark’!
Bet!
kiwatari, three chips.
Another maximum bet?!
My hand's a ‘pig’.
I can't compete with that.
I fold.
Lucky! I won with just a ‘pig’!
What?!
They’re screwing with me.
This is way bigger than just reading
people or being good at bluffing!
Don't tell me... !
Finally noticed, have you?
Say, you really are an idiot aren't you?
Tsubomi-san...
You may be taking orders from Kiwatari-san, but I do recommend you stop.
Showing the marks by the way you place your cards is just a tad too obvious, you know?
Looking at your hands so far... placing it straight means spades.
Tilting it a just a little
to the right means clubs.
Left would be diamonds.
And having one card slide forward
a little would mean hearts.
What's with ‘I can see right through livestock like you’ now?
The way you handled it was way more obvious.
We know...
Tsubomi Nanami, part of the livestock
In the second year Camilla Class,
is treated by your group like a slave and exhibition piece.
The announcement for the groups actually had me sweating.
Kiwatari and Tsubomi...
you’re definitely in this together.
That's why...
I asked Yumeko for a little help.
It may have been mere carelessness,
but the moment you inspected your hand you showed some emotion.
Having an incompetent master like that makes Tsubomi-san rather pitiable, doesn't it?
Shut up...
Tsubomi-san.
Allow me to show you a good method.
You can tell each other what cards you have by using your fingers under the table like this.
Certainly more reliable, no?
Fucking underestimating me...
It would seem as if everyone here is guilty of cheating in one way or another.
Now then, how to deal with this…?
Igarashi-san.
I will not report Kiwatari-san and Tsubomi-san's cheating.
If it isn’t reported, there should be
no reason to stop the game.
I see. You want to enjoy the game while making use of cheating. Is that what you mean?
I think this game is more fun when cheating is involved.
Ah! Could it be that you’re bad
with subtleties, Kiwatari-san?
After all, you so openly revealed what your hand was!
Fine by me.
let's get on with it already!
It’s gotten quite interesting, wouldn't you say?
Everyone is completely aware of their own hand.
This match has already…
devolved to a battle of bluffs!
Very well. We will resume the game.
This table is drenched in lies.
Whoever can overcome these lies may grasp at victory.
A seven-and-eight ‘mark’...
Tsubomi, get into the match.
Y-Yes! Ca-
You idiot!
Wrong! You have to raise!
Use your head a little, will ya?!
The idiot here is you, though.
What good does it do to have a
strong hand and let us know about it?
Fold!
Y-You...
Shitheads... they’re getting in my way!
Kiwatari Jun
Saotome Mary
Jabami Yumeko
Tsubomi Nanami
Yumeko’s at the top right now.
I’m here with a debt!
If I don’t come in first, that debt’s
for real and I’ll become livestock!
Me? Becoming livestock?!
There’s no way! I’m an owner!
I'll make them understand that...
Call!
saotome, one chip.
Challenging me now means you're pretty confident in your hand...
Just kidding.
If you really were confident,
you would've bet one of Jabami's chips.
Well, too bad!
A ‘pair’, here?
What is this? Why do I get this unfair treatment?
We will proceed with the ninth turn.
Two turns and I come in third...
If these rankings stay set, my debt’ll end up being 50,000,000 Yen!
Tsubomi!
Yes!
Bet the Jabami chip!
B-But...
Just do it already!
carry your chips over to me!
All you do is drag me down anyways,
so be useful for once!
Yes...
Call.
jabami, one chip.
kiwatari, one chip.
Fold.
Yumeko... got a good hand, huh?
But I can't pull back here, no matter what.
As long as I can get Tsubomi's chips first place is almost guaranteed.
This is a gamble without any plans;
a pure battle of cards!
Now then, please reveal your hands.
Seven and five, ‘mark’.
Six and two, ‘mark’.
I won! I won!
Five Jabami chips - 155,000,000 Yen!
First place by a huge leap!
Serves you right, all of you!
starting tomorrow, I'll show you hell.
How a gamble will end is uncertain until the very end.
Huh?
Now then, let us proceed to the tenth turn.
You may laugh or cry, but this will be the last.
Everyone, please make sure to bet without regrets.
Is it over already? It feels like time
passed much too quickly.
I wanted to play a bit more.
I've had enough already.
Let's get this gamble over with already.
What? How can they be so relaxed?
I just have to back down for this round and me coming in first is a guarantee...
Kiwatari Jun
Saotome Mary
Jabami Yumeko
Tsubomi Nanami
No wait... There is one, isn’t there?!
There’s a way for them to take first place easily!
For example Saotome could bet all her Jabami chips, then Yumeko would just have to win.
Or even the other way around!
What should I do? Just what should I do...?!
No, there's nothing I can do. The only way out is for me or Tsubomi to have a winning hand.
Come on! A winning hand...!
Tsubomi has a matchup of two nines?
This time it's my win, no doubt about it!
Bet.
saotome, one chip.
Think as much as you want. Bet or fold,
the outcome is already decided!
Call.
jabami, one chip.
Jabami, one chip...?
Huh?!
What the Hell are you doing?!
We could win if we don't do anything!
Well, ending it like this is somewhat upsetting, is it not?
I'll bet on Tsubomi-san winning this game.
Saotome-san, could I ask you for assistance?
Huh? Why do I have to…
What are they talking about?
Ah! I get it, I get it already!
I'll humour your bad habits.
Raise.
jabami, three chips.
There are five Jabami chips, if Tsubomi wins
It'd be 170,000,000 Yen?!
She’ll go over me!
Back down, Tsubomi!
You're not allowed to win against me.
Back down!
Y-Yes...
Tsubomi-san.
Are you really alright with that sort of treatment?
Huh?
Haven’t you just resigned yourself
to this position until you graduate?
That way of thinking is wrong.
People with personalities like yours who don't rise up against oppressors never change.
Truly livestock for life.
Can you really handle living that way your whole life?
Tsubomi! Back down already!
There may be no way to avoid his orders; it’s as the school mandates it...
But being given a chance at an uprising and not taking it is like an unmoving pig in an open cage.
It would be like admitting that you are indeed nothing more than livestock, no?
I...
Ah... could this perhaps be the way you wish to live?
Being terrified of confronting such outrageous people,
then showering them with compliments and expecting only the slightest kindness in return...
I see, this is also a way one can choose to live by.
Although I can’t comprehend it whatsoever.
In that case,
backing down while you still haven’t raised Kiwatari-san’s ire might be for the best.
Right?
Tsubomi-san, you lifelong livestock?
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
You... You don't know anything!
Anything...
Oh, how pretty!
Amazing!
I'm so jealous!
Right?!
It's about time I try it!
You look like a doll!
Hey, when did you start growing it?
Since I was still in primary school.
It really is pretty...
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
No! Stop...
No, Stop!
Hey, come on. Just calm down.
It's not like we're gonna rape you or anything!
We're just taking a little from the top.
No!
Why...?!
Why?
Why...
are you doing something this cruel?
Huh?
I've just been wanting to cut that
long hair of yours for a while.
Doesn't it feel good when you trim your long nails?
It's just like that.
The strings that held me up were severed.
Since then, just to maintain my mental stability..
I've been crushing all emotion within my heart.
But today... right now is different.
With a single expression of my will, I can make this man suffer an enormous loss.
The emotions I've been killing off are being revived.
The fear I felt that day...
The loss...
The rage...
The frustration...
My vengeful heart!
I'm...
I'm...!
I'm not livestock!
I'm...
A Human!
Episode 5
I call!
Tsubomi!
I do believe I asked you to refrain
from any violent conduct, correct?
You bitch. I'll remember this, got it?
This has taken quite
the unexpected turn.
The words of the President truly
appear to have hit the mark.
'Jabami Yumeko is a madwoman'.
'She cannot be read through logic'.
Is this chick wrong in the head?!
What's the point to letting Tsubomi compete like this?
Hold on...
Is there even any point?
So her hand is a guaranteed winner?
A 'Pair' of Tens?
That can't be...
Now then. Please display your hand.
Thinking that this match may end soon
makes me a tad reluctant.
Two and Ten.
a 'pig'.
A 'Pair' of NInes.
Oh my! Quite a hand, played at the Eleventh Hour!
Congratulations!
She's fucking nuts.
how much did she bet on a 'pig'?
Kiwatari Jun
Saotome Mary
Jabami Yumeko
Tsubomi Nanami
Being second means I'm short ten million, huh?
It doesn't matter. I can manage somehow.
More importantly...
The bigger problem is that she went against me.
I'll crush her to pieces and make sure she never plays the rebel again!
You've done well, everyone.
All ten turns are complete.
I will now announce the results.
The first place goes to Saotome Mary-sama.
Her acquired sum is a total of 166,000,000 Yen.
Saotome Mary
Second, Tsubomi Nanami-sama. 92,000,000 Yen.
Tsubomi Nanami
H-Hey...
Third, Jabami Yumeko-sama. 74,000,000 Yen.
Jabami Yumeko
Hey, w-wait...!
Fourth, Kiwatari Jun-sama. 58,000,000.
Kiwatari Jun
Hey, hold on! That's not right!
Don't just spout bullshit, dumbass!
There are no mistakes in these results.
Don't fuck with me!
I have five Jabami chips!
With just these I should
be way over 58,000,000 no problem!
Saotome-san, if you laugh that much
I can't help but pity him.
I didn't think it'd go this well!
We may have been lucky,
but your acting was splendid to boot!
Really? Thanks.
Huh?
How do you still not get it?
Just crunch the numbers. You have a chip that turns it all on its head, right?
What? A chip?
God, you're a slow counter.
Whatever, I'll tell you.
These here are the opposite of our debts.
Yumeko's chip is worth 5,000,000, which means that mine is worth 31,000,000 Yen.
Well? The numbers finally fit, don't they?
D-Don't be an idiot! That's just–
The rules explained it, didn't they?
In the end, all debts here are self-proclaimed.
In other words, Yumeko has a debt of 310,000,000 Yen,
but just filled in 50,000,000.
And my debt may be 50,000,000,
but I still filled in 310,000,000.
With that fake report of yours,
your friend gets 10,000,000 Yen, right?
We just did the exact same thing.
you weren't the only liar here.
Right about now, someone I know should be getting my portion of the money.
Suzui-san?
Huh?
I have something from the Student Council.
W-What the Hell is this?!
With all that done, the rest is a cakewalk.
I get a board that says 310,000,000.
yumeko gets one that says '50,000,000'.
So, all we have to do is exchange those boards.
Once that's done, wouldn't you know it?!
The total sums are exchanged too!
Who'd have thought you'd get tricked this badly, huh?
T-That's ridiculous!
Hey! That's against the rules, isn't it?!
There is no rule that states that one must place their own board in front of themselves.
That's insane!
that's 260,000,000 isn't it?!
What can the Student Council even gain from taking on a fake report like that?!
This is not something you could comprehend.
Kiwatari-san, judging everything by
your own standards is no good.
Not all people are from the same cloth, after all.
What is forgivable and unforgivable...
There is no such thing as a person that completely aligns with your beliefs.
That's why it's grand, no?
S-Stop fucking around! I'll never accept this, I won't!
We have no need of your approval. We merely deal with others as their ranking dictates.
You're the moron for falling for it!
You
bitch!
'Violent conduct is prohibited'.
that makes the third time.
Regardless, do you understand?
You now owe a grand total of 310,000,000 to our Student Council.
Should you not be able to comply...
You will become 'livestock'!
Now then, our proceedings have been concluded.
We thank you for your efforts.
It's finally over!
Oh, of course. Tsubomi-san?
Huh?
Please don't forget that spirit from earlier, alright?
In the end, I came in second.
I'm still livestock, and my debt remains unchanged at 20,000,000 Yen.
I've been had.
But I feel no anger.
Yumeko-san's given me a chance.
And anyways, that's what that was about.
So could you give us back that check?
I don't know how he'd handle a smaller sum, but we're talking about 260,000,000.
I really hope this doesn't give him any weird ideas...
Oh, so that's what it was!
I got scared, thinking it was some kind of joke.
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Still, it's amazing you won a match that big.
Congratulations.
That ridiculous honesty is almost enough to make me laugh...
Thank you kindly.
Well, that's it for me.
W-What?!
Thank you so much!
The suggestions you made turned it
Into quite the thrilling game!
W-Well, I guess I could say the same to you...
That aside, let go already!
Where are you even touching me?!
Oh my.
That was rude of me.
Saotome-san, if you wouldn't mind.
may I call you Mary-san?
We've become friends, haven't we?
Huh?
I-I don't...
I don't mind, I guess...
Thank you ever so much, Mary-san!
Hey! W–
don't cling to me!
I guess... they got pretty close?
Mary-san!
Again! Mary-san, Mary-san, Mary-san!
That game was something only heard of in theory.
More than that, either result would have been beneficial.
Kiwatari is the son of a governor.
jabami Yumeko is already under surveillance.
Our aim was for either to utterly vanquish the other in a one-sided match.
The result was a success.
Nevertheless, was it really alright?
At the final turn,
Jabami Yumeko sank to third rank of her own accord and gained a debt of 30,000,000 Yen.
She does not see money as her principle for conduct.
The most effective means of
manipulation do not register for her.
Council President...
Letting go of her reins and allowing her to roam free... was that truly alright?
Decide Jabami Yumeko's Life Plan Forms?
You're not someone who could understand...
You don't have to worry about anything!
Let's enjoy ourselves, to our heart's content!
Episode 6
Tempting Woman