Good morning, Suzui-san.
Oh. Good morning, Jabami-san.
Oh, that just won't do.
The two of us are friends now, or am I mistaken?
Huh?
Just 'Yumeko' is fine.
Huh?!
Um...
Right!
I mean... Yu-Yumeko...
Well, I've built up a big debt, huh?
Hm?
From yesterday.
I can't do it immediately, but I'll definitely return it at some point.
That was a present from me to you. Please, pay it no mind.
True... There's not much sense in paying it back...
Wai– No, no! I can't just let this go!
Worst Kind Of Girl
Uggo
Flattie
Serves You Right Lolololol
Scum
Die Brat
Moron
Saotome-san, what's going on?
Whatever happened here? Are you being bulli–
Shut up!
This is only happening
because I lost to you!
Hey, you should hurry up
and put that on.
Go against the rules
and you're deeper in debt.
Mike.
Mike! Mike! Mike!
Hyakkaou Private Academy.
That name tag bears
one's rank in this hierarchy.
What decides that is neither studying, nor athleticism.
Only one's prowess at gambling.
What happened to
saotome wasn't your fault.
It's just a rule of this academy.
A rule?
Yeah.
This place has tons of kids with big names and backgrounds in industry and politics.
'In the future, what someone who uses others needs...
...the most is an aptitude in bargaining and reading others.'
'Even more so, the strength to deal with others during a crisis.'
That's the whole thought process of this academy.
I see...
That's why gambling
prowess gets you renown,
and failing to meet end's meet can leave you open to persecution.
Specifically, the students are divided by a class system.
The student council watches over the students' gambling and collects a tax from the students.
The amount of money gathered decides the social class.
The rankings are announced irregularly,
And out of all the three thousand students, the one hundred that rank the lowest are labelled as
'students with uncooperative tendencies'.
They become 'livestock'.
The men are called 'Pochi', and the women 'Mike'.
Oh, then your tag was...
Yeah.
But with the money you gave me, I was able to pay the tax and get rid of it.
It's all thanks to you.
Well, that certainly
calls for congratulations!
I'm really thankf–
It was never this bad before.
It all changed two years ago.
Ever since the current student council president came to power.
Momobami Kirari...
She attended both middle and high school, but she was still incorporated as a senior.
And just like that, she became student council president.
She gambled against the president of those days for her position and won.
Oh my! She won her seat through gambling?!
The student council here is a group of the best gamblers around.
They're worthy of standing at the top.
She cemented her own
reformation of the rules.
That's when we started getting 'Pochis' and 'Mikes'.
That's also when the discrimination started getting worse and worse.
That said, in Saotome's
case it's pretty extreme.
All because she was so harsh with forcing them to help her out.
The deadline for the tax was right around the corner. She was plain unlucky.
Oh, sorry. Did that story scare you?
Really, now...
The more I hear about this academy, the more it exceeds my expectations.
Aah...
I'm ever so glad
to have transferred here...!
Does this girl not
even know what 'fear' is?
Full house! It's my win!
Yes!
My...! They even gamble during recess?
They do.
Ah! That girl!
She's an executive of the student council. She's a first year, kind of well-known too.
Because of gambling, I assume?
No. There's a rumour that she just pays the with an absurd amount.
She's supposedly the daughter of the Ceo of Japan's leading toy company.
Ridiculously wealthy, and a skilled gambler to boot.
She's also supposed to be
unbeatable at card games...
Unbeatable you say?!
That's quite something, isn't it?!
I'd love to ask her
to play one round with me...
No no no!
You really shouldn't-
Jabami-senpai!
Episode2
How do you do?
I'm a first year, from the flower class - my name is Sumeragi Itsuki!
Truly a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
What's this, all of a sudden...?
Senpai, you're
becoming quite the topic!
They're saying you made
a complete fool of
Saotome-senpai the same day you transferred here!
Thing is, I'm pretty
confident in my gambling...
So I thought that comparing our skills might be fun!
Oh, it truly does!
Wait, Yumeko!
Good, that's the spirit!
C'mon, another pig?!
How did I end up... like this...?
Why...?
How...?
How did it come to this...?
I... I'm... How am I...
Hey, Mike!
I spilled my coffee. Clean it up.
Guys, get this!
Someone's gambling against Sumeragi Itsuki from the council!
No way! Who is it?!
Listen to this - it's our own Jabami Yumeko!
Seriously?!
Where?!
The cafeteria!
Now, about the gamble...
How does
double Card Memory sound?
Like the name suggests, we'll be using two decks.
For normal Card Memory, drawing two equal numbers is enough.
Here, you have to get the same mark too if you want to get a point.
So, we'll be using a hundred and four cards in total.
The winner is decided with just one set.
I understand! How fascinating!
I'd love to play!
Okay!
Now, about the money we'll bet...
Twenty chips straight from the student council, each worth a million Yen...
How does twenty million Yen sound?
It's rather unfortunate, but I have no such amount at my disposal.
I couldn't possibly
prepare twenty million Yen.
Really?
You really don't look like the type to spend carelessly...
Or could you be in debt?
Huh?!
I... I'm sorry.
But there's no need to worry!
I'll gladly lend you the money!
Interest-free, even.
What?
What could you even gain from that?
In all honesty, twenty million won't leave much of a dent.
Getting the viewers interested in my playing cards is an even bigger reward for me!
It's great publicity.
If that's indeed the case,
I'll happily oblige!
Okay!
The gambling arrangements are met!
As I explained before, I'll be preparing two unopened deck of cards.
This is one of our finest products, Raclette!
The second best-selling cards in Japan!
Blends right in your hand and brings itself to life!
I'm counting on you!
She's really putting it out there...
Double Card Memory. Let's begin!
Please, Senpai.
I'll let you make the first move.
Oh, thank you kindly!
There's hardly a point in hesitating on the first draw.
Two fours, but the rules don't accept that as a victory. Correct?
That's exactly right.
I'll be going next, then.
The Four of Hearts and Diamonds I can recall, at least.
Isn't this game too hard?
If you just need one to win, getting it by pure luck is a one-in-a-hundred and three chance!
The only thing you can do is remember which cards were opened...
But who's going to remember all hundred and three?!
King of Diamonds... Ace of Spades...
That's Two of Hearts...
And that was a Club...
I can't! This is making my head hurt!
Oh!
A Four of Diamonds was already opened before!
But where...?
It was here, if I recall.
I did it!
Once you win, you draw again. Go ahead.
Seven of Diamonds...
King of Clubs...
A loss, I see.
I remember where the King of Clubs was!
Right here!
Sumeragi sure isn't taking blows here!
Amazing...
They're a hairline apart!
Yumeko already has eighteen. Sumeragi has twenty-two.
Neither of them's giving in.
Hey, I might be seeing things...
But they haven't been drawing duds for a while now.
What do you mean?
Well... Like I said...
Once they've opened a card, I feel like they won't miss it again...
Huh?
Five of Hearts.
I've certainly seen that one before.
I knew it!
Did they remember all the cards they opened?!
If they have a good memory,
they only need the luck to open a card that matches one they've seen.
Twenty-eight left now.
Yumeko has thirty-six.
Sumeragi has forty.
It's still a close call...
But it'll just get harder from here on out.
The fewer cards are left, the easier it is to get the right one.
This game would definitely move fast.
Not half-bad, Senpai.
I can't say I've had such
a good match before.
Oh, you exaggerate. I'm honoured.
If I don't put up my guard more...
Oh! That's a winner.
And this was here... a winner!
Oh, and this one here... Alright!
Oh? I've seen this one too!
Oh dear...
Ten in a row.
Looks like Lady Luck's on my side, wouldn't you agree?
She's fourteen cards apart from Yumeko...
At this point, that's way too much.
Oh, darn. A miss.
Please, Senpai.
If you lose the next turn...
I'll definitely win, you know.
Give it your all now!
Oh...
She missed?!
There we go, another win.
Now, I have the majority with fifty-four cards.
That means it's my win, doesn't it?
Yumeko...
A debt of twenty million...! What are you gonna do?!
You already told her you don't have that much!
Yay! I won again!
Sumeragi-san...
Hm?
One more... Could I ask for one more match?
Huh?
I couldn't possibly pay twenty million!
Just as you did, I remembered every single opened card!
I simply can't be satisfied with an outcome like this!
Please, I ask you for one more match!
Truth is, I have this habit.
I collect nails, see...
Look here! Aren't they adorable?
Of course, these are just a small part of my collection.
Also, there's a small secret trick to making them.
These are all real nails.
Oh...
I suppose it's easier to purchase them...
But since no one seems to want to sell theirs to me, I simply gather them through gambling.
Which means, if you want to bet twenty million...
Senpai...
I... I want those nails of yours as payment...
You can't be serious. Betting nails?!
What do you think, Senpai?
Yumeko! You can't take on something so ridiculous-
I understand...
I take no issue with that.
Just what are you–
Because! I have no other way of repaying such an amount!
Or are you insinuating that you could pay for me?
No, well... that's...
Now, that's the spirit!
I'll be using brand-new ones again.
You're kidding...
I'm getting excited!
This is insane.
Even at an academy like this, betting parts of the body is almost unheard of.
And still, they're getting excited...
This isn't some simple joke!
Well then, let's begin.
I'll be betting twenty million Yen.
Senpai, you'll be betting the your finger-and-toenails.
You're fine with that, I assume?
I am.
Well then, you may go ahead and make the first move.
Thank you kindly.
My collection's getting bigger again!
I'll definitely win this time too...
After all...
I know what of half those cards -
what fifty-two of those cards are!
At first glace, this card doesn't appear different from any other card in circulation.
But the truth is that it's a different type of card I had manifactured by my personal line.
There's only a single difference.
One it's exposed to temperature beyond a certain point, a pattern rises to the surface.
The inside of my bag is lined with hand warmers.
Once I line them up like this, it takes two to three minutes for them to cool down,
and the new pattern continues receding.
It's a tiny detail and it vanishes quickly, so no one can see through it!
I can remember them all!
There no way I can lose, right?
Choosing the game to be Double Card Memory
was just for making more room and hiding my trump.
Once I know the cards, be it Poker or Old Maid, there's no way I can lose!
I suffered trying to remember those cards, but the pay-off was amazing!
Senpai!
Those nails... I'll be taking them!
A hit!
That's some luck on the first try...!
By the way, Sumeragi-san.
You come from a famous toy-making family, correct?
Pardon?
Just what is the market capitalisation for such a home?
Ten billion?
Dare I say a hundred billion?
Yet this gamble is worth twenty million.
Woefully mismatched proportions, wouldn't you say?
What are you talking about?
Allow me to offer a single warning.
If you ever try to bet something like your family's net worth,
do so once you've gathered at least a modicum of resolve.
Huh? What's she saying?
My 'family'?
Could she have... Is she seeing through my tricks?!
Is she threatening me?!
True, if word got out that a toy company manufactured these cards of its own accord...
That's a scandal it would have to bear!
Just how much has she caught on?!
Did she see the disappearing patterns?
No, there's a chance it could be a bluff...
I can't take it!
At the rate this is going, I just have to open all my cards once it's my turn...
Then switch them with cards from a regular deck!
That's all I can do now..
Once it's my turn... As soon as it's my turn... As soon as it comes...!
As soon as–
Yu-Yumeko...?
That would make fifty-four cards.
That makes it my victory, doesn't it?
Hah...?
No way...
How...?
Had you exercised a little more caution, it would have been my loss.
After all...
The patterns on the back are the same as the ones from before, no?
Had you simply prepared another deck for this match, victory would have been yours.
What...?
Is... Is she implying that she remembered all of them?!
So she was memorizing the patterns during our first match.
She continued and pretended to not notice anything!
She was even in tears when she lost... Was that an act?
Still, those patterns should only be visible for three minutes at most!
Did she memorise them that quickly and just build connections with opened cards?!
Is that something a human is even capable of?!
Now then, this brings the game to a close!
Shall we move on to the next one? Please!
what should we play?
Black Jack? Baccarat, perhaps?
N-No... I'm done–
Really now? Were you in any position to refuse?
Oh, I know!
Why don't we both bet our nails for the next game?
Whoever loses must have all their finger-and-toenails pulled out!
You're the one who suggested it after all, so you should take no issue!
I... I can't...
They say that pulling out nails is unbearable.
The stress it places on the fingers, all the blood you lose...
And since it came from all extremities, it would turn day-to-day life on its head, no?!
A match with such immense risks and stakes...
Just imagining it makes me feel like...
I'm overflowing!
Come now, Samuragi-san! This is the perfect opportunity to let loose your latent urges!
Preparing your tricks so thoroughly
and yet being beaten so soundly - you can't just stop now!
Let's go again.
all that's left is for you to agree!
Now!
Come On!
Hurry Up!
I... Can't...
I can't continue...
Please... Forgive me...
What?
F... Forgive me...
Yu-Yumeko...
You've gone this far already...
What a bore...
...That concludes the report.
Winning against Sumeragi-chan this quickly! What an amazing girl!
She's getting on her high horse after beating a small-fry, huh?
In the end, she only joined the council through by paying an excess in taxes.
Oh? Who was it that endorsed her again?
You're noisy. Shut your mouth.
Now, how do you propose we deal with Jabami Yumeko?
It's entertaining, isn't it? How about we try meddling in her affairs a little?
Wait, were you serious? You're still gonna do this?
Such a lackluster conclusion makes me feel half-dead!
You said it yourself, Suzui-san.
The whole school turns into a gambling den after school!
Where are they?!
Do come along, Suzui-san!
Welcome to the Traditional Culture Research Club!
Honoured guests, an official game occurs at this very moment!
Would you enjoy partaking of such a spectacle?
Official game?
The result shows 'death'.
Saotome-sama receives a negative total of forty-nine million and six hundred thousand!
The match is settled!
F-Forty million?!
Saotome-san, I shall call and inform you of the retrieval method soon.
Someone guide her away, please.
Our business has been settled.
Now, get excited!
My, what a scary face...
Just shut up and open it.
Just one is worth thirty million!
Episode 3
Slit-Eyed Woman
As I have said - I will slaughter you...