Good morning.
Yu-Yumeko?
What might you be looking at?
Ah, no... this is...
This girl's a really popular indie-idol,
and at the same time a member of the Student Council.
My. Someone like that was in the Student Council.
Yumemite Yumemi.
She’s a second year student and publicity manager.
Some of her YourTube videos
get over three million views.
People say she's guaranteed to be a big
hit if she ever makes a major debut.
She sometimes holds concerts on school grounds,
but she's so popular that you have to be in her fan club to get tickets.
You certainly are well-informed.
I’d like to cheer her on, as a fellow schoolmate,
but the entrance fees are just too high...
Thank you, everyone!
If you liked it, then I’m counting
on you to spread the love.
Share me, okay?
Oh?
This is...
President!
Oh, Sayaka.
Just where are you going?
You never even told me where you were going...
I'll be leaving the academy for a while.
I have to take care of some minor business.
What could it possibly be at a time like this?
Just yesterday, Ikishima-san
lost to Jabami Yumeko–
I heard.
That's why I have business.
Deal with the leftovers as you see fit.
I'll leave it to you.
No...
If you're not present, then...
Please wait!
Like a broken record...
A week has passed since then.
The Student Council is by no means a monolith.
Those that seek out power...
Those who want to protect themselves...
Those who pursue pleasure...
And those that cannot be read.
What connects us all are the foundations built upon
the absolute authority of the Council President…
The influence we possess as
a Student Council members.
But with the appearance of Jabami Yumeko,
our state of affairs is beginning to waver...
It's been a week since Ikishima's shameful display.
The Council President isn't attending school...
Why is that?
That is... I was not told the
reasoning behind it myself.
And here I thought
she’d let you know, of all people.
Nyahahahaha!
Then we have no choice.
We may be on our own,
but why don't we decide how to deal with the two that lost against the livestock?
Neither Ikishima-san nor
nishinotouin-san have lost!
That's only because of the President’s
aid and their opponent’s pity, isn't it?
Rumours are already spreading
throughout school grounds.
The Student Council's dignity is taking a fall.
How disappointing...
How can you go on as a member,
pretending nothing happened?
Manyuda-san!
You’re showing great
disrespect towards a Third Year!
The concept of disrespect
doesn’t exist in this academy.
You should know better, considering that you’re
always at the President’s side, Igarashi Sayaka.
Then why don’t you try and take on Yumeko?
And why exactly should
I waste my time on mere livestock?
Yumeko, you know...
She got guts and insight.
She trusts her allies.
She has everything she needs for success.
And more than anything...
Those eyes!
Just remembering them is enough for me to...
Ikishima-san, the meeting is still underway.
Bath
room
break.
I really can't stand that eccentric side of hers.
I don't think Ikishima-san's
comments are that far off.
Jabami Yumeko is livestock.
That is exactly what makes her so terrifying.
If she uses her privilege as livestock to
challenge the President to an official match...
Depending on the outcome...
The President becomes livestock.
If you lose you're treated like
everyone else, after all.
I will never let that happen!
I oppose that as well.
More importantly, what about collecting our debts to weaken her funds?
Did you forget?
That’s been forbidden by the President.
Not to mention she's already assigned a Life Plan.
Yep. I guess she passes.
You just leave Yumeko-chan to me.
Episode 8
Yumemite, you...
Yumemite-san...
I’m gonna take on Yumeko-chan!
I see.
You are indeed someone easily capable of creating stage to utterly crush Jabami Yumeko.
Right?
And since it’s such a rare opportunity,
I wanna go all flashy about it!
Manyuda-kun, I'd like your help too.
Very well.
I’ll accept all responsibility of
organising this plan of yours.
Please wait a moment!
The President gave orders…!
T-This is hopeless.
I can hardly hold them back on my own.
On top of that, I cannot even begin to comprehend the nature of the President's will...
I’m telling you, it’ll be fine!
Just leave this to us Second Years.
It's about time for the Student Council to start
thinking about the next generation, after all.
Did something good happen to her?
I don't know...
She's been like that all morning.
I wonder if there
was something in that letter...
Letter?
Jabami-senpai.
Long time no see!
1st year Flower Class,
sumeragi Itsuki arrived!
Surprise!
A Traditional Montblanc from
seifuudou. Dropping it off here!
Ah, is that our...?
They're delicious!
I know about you.
You were kicked out of the
student Council a few days ago, right?
So, now you plan to suck up to Yumeko
to find some weakness that gives you a chance to get back into the Council, huh?
How shallow!
Oh, come on!
There's no way I'd do something like that!
Okay, okay. I get it.
I’ll spill the beans.
My father...
The president of one of Japan’s
top toy makers, right?
I'm jealous you have a
bright future laid out for you.
It’s... not that simple.
My father’s pragmatic to the core.
I was to enter this academy and join the Student Council,
then establish connections to the elites of society.
If I can't do that... worst case,
I might get disowned!
Jabami-senpai!
Is it true that you’re aiming for the
position of Student Council President?
It's a rumour...
A rumour that’s being perpetuated and talked
about by students, especially the livestock.
Even after winning at the Debt Adjustment Assembly you decided
Mike
to stay as livestock voluntarily....
They’re saying it was all to retain the right
to challenge the President for her position!
Yumeko just came here to
gamble in any way she liked.
But still…
Before we even noticed, the whole
academy started revolving around her!
If these rumours really are true,
then there's only one thing for me to do.
I want you to make me a member of the Student Council again
after you take the President's position!
For that, there’s nothing I won’t do.
This is how I really feel,
no lies involved.
I’m begging you.
please make me an ally.
I welcome you with
open arms, of course.
Setting aside the issue with the
student Council President...
We both really enjoy gambling, right?
That already makes us friends, no?
T-That's true…
Is she really that deluded?
That girl…
Dvds are over here!
The new song's Cds are available here!
As always, that was a superb concert!
Shinnouji-kun, you came today too, huh?
Of course I did!
As the president of your fan club
I can't afford to miss a single show!
Unfortunately, the timing of our cheers
during 'Gambling Girl' was a bit off today.
I'll make sure it'll be better next time!
All in moderation, okay?
No, no!
As a fan awaiting your major debut,
I have an obligation to lecture the others on proper conduct!
As the president,
that’s my responsibility!
I mean, those lazy bums are slacking
on their 100 views per day quota!
I'm not saying they should load the
video on five different phones like I do,
but if they can't give you at least a hundred views
they shouldn't be allowed to be called a fan of yours!
Yumemite Yumemi    -     Sama
Waiting Room
All of those pigs are fucking disgusting!
Would you rather cancel the handshake event after your live performance, at least?
We can't.
It's not just the concert; it’s the personal
Interactions that keep them coming back.
Even so...
It's okay, Saori.
For my dreams, this is nothing.
If I can't handle this much,
I'll never achieve anything.
More importantly, when
are we challenging Yumeko?
By tomorrow.
We've already received the funds necessary thanks to Manyuda-san’s organisation skills.
I see. I'm looking forward to it...
I'll make Yumeko-chan bet
her whole life on this!
Eh? A gamble with Yumemite-san?!
Indeed. I just had the pleasure
to speak to her manager...
This is serious...
Yumeko's been taking down the
student Council members one by one.
There's no doubt about it...
yumeko's being targeted!
Okay then, Manyuda-kun.
take care of the rest, okay?
Leave it to me.
With the Council President gone,
this is the perfect chance.
We Second Years will have the total
power of the Council in our grasp.
I'll begin with the preparations for the event.
Make sure that Jabami doesn't
pull the rug out from under you.
Manyuda-kun, you're such a worrywart...
Yumemite Yumemi    -     Sama
Waiting Room
Would it be alright to take Suzui-san with me?
A boy... you mean?
Well, it should be fine...
Thank you so much!
Now then...
H-Hold on, please!
I'll get her permission now.
I apologise. I just couldn't wait.
Before you enter,
please let me conduct a full-body search.
Every now and then,
some people try to enter the waiting room with cameras and recording devices.
Of course. I don't mind.
Come on in! I'm Yumemite Yumemi.
I'm working as an idol!
It's a pleasure to meet you, Yumemite-san.
Oh? Who's this?
Um...! W-Well... I'm from the
second Year Flower Class, Suzui–
Suzui Ryouta-kun!
Huh?
You came to one of my live performances, right?!
It was during last year's school festival!
on the second day of my live performance!
Huh?
I-I'm surprised you even remember that.
It was such a long time ago, too...
I remember the names and faces of all my fans!
as an idol, that's a given!
Now then, what kind of gamble
do you have in mind for me?
Right, right. The gamble.
Two-Hour Special Program Plan
A Battle To
determine
The
Top-Class Idol
YOU
MAY
BATTLE!
Look at this.
"Battle to determine the top-class idol"?
It kind of sounds like some sort of variety program...
The plan's actually supposed to be for Tv,
but I really wanted to
go on stage with Yumeko!
After my live performance,
right in front of everyone.
As long as I won't be a bother, I don't mind...
There's no way you'd bother me!
Because, this gamble's supposed to double as a new member election!
Huh?
The stakes'll be 50,000,000 Yen.
With that much, you can get out of being livestock, right?
True.
So! If I win, your debt's
obviously gonna get higher...
So, when that happens...
I'm having you form an idol unit with me!
Huh?!
I had your Life Plan Forms written out that way!
the unit's been decided!
Its name, too!
DREA
Drea
MING
Ming
Dreaming Creaming Sisters!
DREAMING
Dreaming
CREA
Crea
MING
Ming
CREAMING
Creaming
SISTERS
Sisters
Wow. E-Embarra–
Both of our names have the character for
'dream'! This is fate, don't you think?
But still, an idol's life isn't all fun and games.
The lessons are strict,
and having no private lives is a given...
And of course,
having a love life is out of the question!
Yumeko-chan, I'm having you
risk it all on an idol life too.
I see...
But nevertheless, why would you
go to such an extent as an idol?
For the smiles of my fans, of course!
Please leave that facade of yours aside.
Yumemite-san, you despise your fans, don't you?
What are you even saying?
there's no way that's true!
Oh, is that so?
Then just what might this be?
Let's read this, shall we?
To Our Beloved Yumemi-chan,
As always, thank you for a fun
live show! Also, good work!
Recently, you've gotten pretty popular on YourTube,
and I'm truly proud
as the head of your fanclub.
Teehee~
But as a long-time fan,
I'm kind of lonely. (Lol).
I've been really busy
with studying lately,
but whenever I see
you doing your best–
That's enough!
Yumemi...
It's exactly like you said.
But so what?
To think that you would continue working as
an idol, despite your contempt for your fans.
You must have quite
the lofty goals in mind, no?
Having never heard of them,
I feel rather left out.
I want an Academy Award.
I've been admiring it since I was little...
The air that only allowed those blessed with talents,
raw ability, and fortune to walk in its vicinity...
The entire world focuses on
every little movement they make.
I want to become one of those
lone flowers that paint the red carpet.
I signed up with a talent agency,
went through lessons every day, and became a Tv regular faster than anyone else in my class!
But then I realised... this was too slow.
Even if things went well,
there'd be no guarantee that 'd stand at the top of this small-minded country called Japan!
If I wanted to obtain some epic role of importance at Hollywood,
there was an entirely different approach.
That would be this academy.
And being an idol!
As long as I have this academy's support,
taking the top as an idol isn't impossible!
Once I reach the height of my popularity and move on to being an actress,
I can stand among Japan's top class!
And if I make it that far,
It's not too hard to debut in a Hollywood film!
What a wonderful objective.
For that, you would continue despite your hatred of interacting with your fans?
That's right!
In their case, I can't say that
I care about how bad they look.
That just means that they're spending
more money on me than on themselves.
But still...
Why the Hell do they dance like crazy during my live shows?!
If you've got time to dance, then listen to my damn song!
Why are you working up more sweat than I am?!
Accepting those sweat-soaked
handshakes of yours is disgusting!
Being an idol is rather tough, it seems.
You should start getting ready.
you'll be doing the same.
Until I listened to that story of yours,
I can't say that I ever thought of becoming an idol.
But the very idea of offering one's
entire life to such a profession...
That is quite the marvelous risk!
I'll be sure to teach you thoroughly.
Nevertheless, if we were to both risk our entire lives instead of relying on my own,
this gamble would be all the more interesting.
Huh?
What are you...?
I've taken the liberty of
recording our little conversation.
In all honesty, I thought that only
bringing a ripped letter wasn't enough.
Should this be released to the public,
your life as an idol would surely meet an end.
Why are you working up more sweat than I am?! Accepting those sweat-soaked handshakes of yours is disgusting!
Yumeko...
Why?!
Why does Saori have that?!
No, this isn't...
Back then...
For you, Yumemite-san, why don't
we use this voice recorder for our bet?
Hand that over!
Please, rest assured. I wouldn't do something as
underhanded as to keep another copy on hand.
As long as I can gamble, then I'm satisfied.
Well then, I do look forward
to the day of our gamble.
Um... Well... That is...
Yumeko!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Because of me, your... our dreams are...!
This is fine, bring it on!
Jabami Yumeko. I swear to you,
I'll make you regret underestimating me!
Yumeko... That voice recorder...
I found it together with the torn fan letter.
All I was told was,
"Use this and threaten her".
I wonder, just whose
work could it have been?
I don't get it...
I thought I put that letter away here to burn it later...
We were paying close attention to the doors, too...
I don't think anyone could
steal in front of me or you.
That means that the culprit
has to have a master key...
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hello, hello? Prez, you alive?
Things are really
heating up 'round here!
If you don't come back soon, then don't blame
me for what's gonna happen to this school!
YOU
MAY
BATTLE!
Third Auditorium
14:00 Opening /14:30 Curtains Rise
That was 'You're a Black Jack'!
Thank you, all of you!
You're the best!
As sad as it is, today's
live performance ends here...
Whaaat?!
But just like we announced, we'll be starting
with the New Member Election!
It's finally Yumeko's turn...
Still, is it really that bad to
not be here until she finished?
Like I said, you didn't have to come.
I just made preparations for as many people
as Jabami-senpai wanted me to, after all.
Saotome, these tickets
aren't exactly easy to come by.
Honestly. How hard do you think I had to work
to get the fanclub president to fork them over?
I get it already. I already heard that story.
Alright then, let's introduce her!
I wonder if you all know her.
She's been advancing ever since
she transferred here last month...
From Hyakkaou Academy's Second Year,
flower Class - it's Jabami Yumeko-chan!
She really is adorable when you see
her like that, that Jabami-senpai!
Yumeko-chan. Go on,
show your enthusiasm.
I've never had a chance like this,
so I do feel a tad nervous...
But I'll be sure to enjoy it to its fullest.
Okay!
With that said, here we go!
A battle that decides the top idol,
"You May Battle"!
Here it goes!
Yumemi-chan, I love you!
That... that's just a battle of luck, right?
It's nothing more than luck.
Is that not enough?
Keep quiet...
And thank you all for cheering me on up until now...
Episode 9
Dreaming Woman