I couldn't tell with the mask you wore yesterday,
but you're pretty cute.
Is something the matter?
Hey, Nono, if it's not too weird,
I think I'm going to leave it like this.
Is it weird?
Of course not!
I think you look better this way!
I-is that so?
Alright, I'll do it then!
Hey, Chouka.
Tell me, how do you think I look today?
You are more beautiful than anyone once again,
and you smell lovely!
Merci, Chouka!
Alright, then...
...let's head out!
Episode 5
Notes on a Scandal
What is this all about?!
Outrageous! There's something wrong with them!
He looked so cool when he stepped up
to fight in the Warabimpics!
I totally saw him in a different light
after he won against that big bear!
These haiku techniques are called
butsumei, oriku, and kutsukaburi.
By the time of the Shin Kokin Wakashu,
haikus got even more complicated, with yaedasugi...
Listen to the teacher!
Jeez.
Return to your own classrooms!
My goodness. I've got to be vigilant.
I don't understand it!
They're making that shrill sound every time!
Goodness, every last one of them...
Is something wrong?
No, I thought I heard something else
amongst the cheers...
Huh?
Wait! You bastard, where are you going?!
Where? To eat.
You'll be allowing us to
accompany you then, of course!
Jeez.
Eating's the only time I get a little freedom.
Hey, you two, you're puttin'
a lot of pressure on me right now.
You idiot!
Do you know what would happen to you
if our glares weren't working?
All the girls wanting to speak with you
would rush at you all at once!
That sucks.
The pain of bein' popular.
Don't let this get to your head!
Yeah, yeah.
Seriously, you two, if you keep makin' that face
all the time, it ain't gonna make you cuter.
Especially when...
Whose fault do you think this is?!
Ow! Ow!
We'll come for you tomorrow morning!
I can't hear you!
Yeah, yeah.
Jeez.
I can't believe this!
He never noticed my uniform was different
from what I usually wear.
He should have said something about
my different perfume today...
I've been watching a while,
but I'm still surprised he's won them over this bad.
At first I'd thought he was just like
all the other violent delinquents, but now...
I get it.
He's completely hopeless!
Yes! Exceedingly hopeless!
We can't let this get to his head like this!
You should have never given him
your stamp so easily, Rin-san!
B-but you gave him yours, too!
I-I hit my head extremely hard back then!
I-I had a high fever and my mind was hazy!
We have to do something about him
before things around here take a turn for the worse.
Yeah.
Perhaps we should take this to the next level,
and attempt to correct him again!
No, we don't have to go that--
No, it could be what he needs.
He should go through that horrible experience.
That idiot.
What's wrong?
Nothin', just had a really bad feeling.
Did I eat too much?
Man, I'm crazy tired.
What're you gonna do about showering?
Nah, not today.
Too sleepy.
Sup, you two!
You're pretty late today.
You're actually waiting for us?
What are you trying to pull?
Man, I just slept so well last night,
I woke up in an awesome mood.
Wh-what?
Your usual uniform looks
way better on you, Onigawara.
Wha-- you bastard, you'd noticed?!
Well yeah, I...
Huh?
Wh-what?
You went back to your old perfume.
The one yesterday was good,
but this smell's definitely you, Kikakujo.
Wha-?!
Okay, let's get this day started!
Started with a big bang!
H-hold it just a minute!
Huh?
C-c'mon, Rin-san!
Wha-?! Umm, well!
You haven't had your inspection yet!
Th-that's right!
We'll try correcting...
...him tomorrow!
Jeez.
Oui! It's okay!
What's this?
Huh? What'd you find?
Die!
Huh?
I...
I trusted you...
Onigawara? Are you crying right...
I was a fool to trust you even for a second!
M-Rin-san?
Huh?
What...
What is the meaning of this?!
The hell are you...
Wh-what the hell?!
Wh-what the hell is this?!
Well?! Don't you have an explanation?!
Salope!
W-wait, wait!
I have no memory of this even...
Pathetic.
Truly pathetic!
Onigawara!
I won't let you get away!
Die!
Nomura Fudo!
Hold it!
What the hell is with that picture?!
The girl in it's, uh...
Tamaba Satori, one of the Five Swords, right?
This is seriously not funny!
They're really gonna kill m-
Ow! The hell?
What's going on, boy?
You should walk on the sides.
Where are you?!
Crap!
Give me a break! I don't have time for this!
Let go!
Jeez!
That fast little bastard!
They're gone.
Thanks, Kyo-bo.
Can't believe you've managed
to win Kyo-bo's heart, too.
Excuse me?
Female
So, what is this all about?
Those two are so naive!
And how very resourceful!
It's no laughing matter.
Why would Tamaba do
something like this in the first place?
What are you talking about?
That's your strong point, isn't it?
What do you mean?
If she took you out, Princess Oni and
Princess Kikakujo wouldn't shut up about it.
Those two?
That's why she's trying to
wreck your relationships with them first.
That is to say, if those two don't realize
they're being tricked, Satori can plot all she wants.
Do you have a plan?
Do I? No really.
Wait!
That's it!
What is it?
I remembered one thing very clearly!
I did not have a boner!
What's that supposed to mean?
There's a big ray of light covering up
the important bits in the photo, right?
I see.
So if you get the original data,
you can provide the others with an explanation.
That's right.
That's what I'm gonna go with.
Hold it!
Don't tell me you're going to
sneak into the girls' dorm again!
Kinda?
You fool!
Thanks to the disturbance you caused last time,
the traps have intensified tenfold!
If you're found there,
they'll send you straight to the torture room!
I get it. That sounds good.
What are you talking about?
You cannot possibly sneak in!
Well, if I can't sneak in...
Take this!
Buri-buri!
Spit it out! Explain yourself!
What is that picture about?!
When did it happen?! How do you know her?!
I can't believe we've beat him this much,
and he hasn't made a peep!
Buri-buri! Buri-buri!
Say something!
Buri-bu...!
What is that?
That's enough, you two.
Let him down. Take a break.
What was that horrible scar?
They really did a number on you.
Here, I brought you some dinner.
Something dry? Man, you're thoughtful.
Got enough water in me to bathe in.
My goodness. You truly like to do insensible things.
If you can't sneak in, then...
Yep. If I can't get in, I'll get them to let me in.
Basically, I just let them catch me.
I see.
Well done. I'll take part in this as well.
Huh? You sayin' you're gonna help me?
Whatever the reason, Princess Satori
is taking unreasonable action,
and I do not find it funny in the slightest!
Ahem!
Nomura! You've done well to appear before me!
There he is!
You'd better be ready for us!
Still, this kind of unreasonable action isn't like you.
Had some reasons to go through it.
It's okay. I'll go on by myself.
What?!
We've both boarded this ship. I will accompany you.
Hey, it's gonna be dangerous.
Kyo-bo...
And if anything happened to you, she'd be upset.
Well, can't say I'm not happy for it.
Princess Satori is not in her quarters at present.
Now is the time to search through her things!
Alright then, let's get moving and
start sifting through her secrets!
Good morning.
Found it!
Is now the time for this?!
Can't find it.
She must have given it to someone.
Which means...
One of the masked girls from back then?
Yes, but I don't know just how many
of those masked girls there are.
And it's hard to point one out specifically.
There's a chance they are
keeping it on their body as well.
So we won't know unless we meet 'em face to face.
No, perhaps not.
Right now, Princess Satori is in the bath.
Well, all right!
This is not the time to make lewd faces.
Princess Satori is a strange one.
She behaves like a mysterious creature
pretending to be a human.
Pretending to be a human?
You think it's strange to say that, yes?
Well...
I told you they've increased the traps!
This is way overboard!
Oh, no! This way!
Don't push me!
Good evening, Hanasaka-senpai.
Y-yeah...
C-can't breathe.
Don't tell me she's...
Her boobs?!
They're coming.
If they find out...
...it's game over.
...but if we don't line up early, they'll all be gone.
I feel like it's kinda serious...
Then let's go buy some tomorrow!
Crap!
Wh-what?
N-nothing, just...
I felt like I heard a guy's voice.
Huh?
Oh my god, what is that?
It's kinda cute!
Hey!
It ran off.
Could that little thing be...
Huh?
We got away some--
You fool!
I-I couldn't help it!
By the way, what was with that little cub?
Oh, I haven't told everyone yet,
but it's the cub Kyo-bo gave birth to this year.
Its name is Do-mo.
Kyo-bo's a married woman?
Man, more to you than meets the eye!
To think I was this close to
troddin' on another man's territory!
Stop your insolence!
Kyo-bo!
Are you alright, ma'am?
Madam! How improper! This is really gross!
It's not here.
I thought she might have sewn it into her underwear...
Nomura!
What's up? Did you find it?
Just the opposite.
Princess Satori's sword is missing!
Wha-?!
Ten... su... metsu...
Misogi!
Misogi?
Out of all the masked girls, it is said that she
is the right hand of Princess Satori!
Her weapon's... a short bamboo stick?
Don't let your guard down!
You fool!
Sorry, Hanasaka!
It's alright.
You get back.
I'm not sure who you are fighting for,
but I have my own reasons to fight!
Man, never expected a ranged technique
to come flying like that.
Blowgun Technique
Oh, you did come!
Wha-?!
But wowie, I'm surprised that Warabi's working with you!
The mysterious creature...
You really can't tell what people will do, huh!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
We saw some buri-buri today!
Buri-buri is a torture technique where you
hang someone upside down and spin them around,
and whack them with thick rattan canes
while shouting "buri-buri!"
They don't hit you with leather strops in buri-buri, right?
Oh my god, you use that for it
and you deserve to be buri-buri'd!
Episode 7
000000000000000000000
The Dubious Sword, Tamaba Satori