How did it come to this?
That horde is finished.
There's no point in staying
now that they've been halted.
I need only keep myself alive.
I'll go back to my nest, reproduce
using the prisoners I have there,
and try again.
I failed this time, but as long as I'm alive,
there will always be a next time.
I'll make it work next time.
Next time, for sure!
I knew that was what you'd think.
You fool.
That army was just a decoy.
Your home is gone.
The Fate of an Adventurer
I'm not used to fighting them face-to-face.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I did it...
Looks like most of them
have been taken care of.
Yeah.
Still, the possibility of all these goblins
attacking the town gives me chills.
I think we've become pretty
knowledgeable about goblins.
We've got a great teacher.
I'd rather not hear that.
This isn't how adventures are supposed to be.
Thank you.
Take that!
He's...
used to fighting!
I'll draw him to me and give you an opening.
You take him down.
Leave it to me!
You're mine!
Wow...
Looks like I saved your life again.
Yeah. You deserve its head.
You're thanking me with the goblin's head?
You don't want it?
No, I'll take it.
Hey, you want some help?
Shut up!
Is he going to be okay?
Damn it!
Take this!
Uncle...
What is it?
Do you remember what you
said about him before?
About him not being all there?
Do you still think that?
I'm not sure.
What do you think?
I...
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I-I'm sorry...
I'll... never do anything like this again...
I-I'll go back to the forest...
and live peacefully...
Like hell that's going to work...
Lord? Preposterous.
You're just a goblin.
Just a filthy little goblin.
And I'm...
Goblin Slayer.
That's one goblin head...
Goblin Slayer!
I'll act as the bait.
Use Protection to render the lord immobile.
Protection?
Yes. Use two and try to trap
him from the front and back...
No, actually, use three and
create a cage to trap him.
Three?
Just in case.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please place your gentle hand
upon this being's wounds.
Heal!
I'm sorry.
I ended up only using two Protections.
Yeah, thanks.
Please don't push yourself so much.
It's not that I think I can win
just by pushing myself...
Goblin Slayer!
You said you wouldn't
push yourself anymore!
Goblin Slayer...
Please try to think things
through a little more!
I'm sorry.
It's because... I trusted you.
You truly are...
such a helpless person.
It's over.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Yeah!
Calm down, please.
You're going to trip and fall.
Heck no, I'm not gonna fall!
Hurry up! The festival's
gonna start without us!
I still don't see why we had to leave so early...
We're going there to crush
the evil sect's plans.
We're still pretty far from the
town and the start of the festival.
Speaking of remnants of evil,
apparently goblins appeared around here, too.
Goblins? They're just underlings, though.
Wow, you don't know, do you?
Goblins can be pretty scary.
Well, I heard there's a Goblin Slayer.
I think everything will be okay.
A Goblin Slayer?
So the reason I'm able to attend the
festival is thanks to whoever that is.
It would sort of suck if the town was
destroyed right after we saved the world.
To our fallen comrades,
our victory,
the farm, the town, adventurers...
And of course,
that weirdo over there who never
talks about anything but goblins!
Cheers!
Hey, over here!
You got it!
Hey...
Ow!
What?! But it was a champion!
Even a champion's only
worth single gold coin?!
Yes.
The deal was a gold coin
for each goblin, so...
Couldn't you add a special reward?
Absolutely not.
Rewarding gold coins to all
of you is the special reward.
Not to mention the lord
that Goblin Slayer defeated
is also only worth one gold coin.
She must be exhausted.
She's a girl, so don't make
her push herself too hard.
Yeah.
You're being nice. Did something happen?
No. I'm the same as usual.
I see.
Woohoo! I'm worth five gold coins tonight!
Keep the food and drink comin'!
Adventurers, we've brought more alcohol!
Hell yeah!
Thanks.
For what?
For saving us.
I didn't do anything.
I'm still...
I'm still not completely sure...
But I'm getting a clearer idea.
I think I want to be an adventurer.
I see.
I'm sure you'll be able to.
Really?
Yup, I'm sure.
Huh?! D-Did I fall asleep?
You worked so hard.
Huh? Um... I-I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
I'm going to go thank everyone.
Have a good time.
Um... What's this?
You're the one who finished off the lord.
Me?
Are you sure that's okay, Goblin Slayer?
Why not?
I-I mean, the money...
There's no problem. I paid just
like we'd originally negotiated.
I bought them a drink.
Goblin Slayer...
What?
Why didn't you... um...
post a quest for everyone sooner?
You didn't have to go about it that way...
Couldn't you have just posted a quest?
Of course, if you didn't want to,
that's totally fine.
It's simple.
No one came when it happened to my village.
The same thing might've happened this time.
There were no guarantees.
I had to trust in luck.
That's all.
Apparently, I'm a weirdo.
That's not true.
If you asked me for help,
I would be happy to!
It's not just me.
I think all the adventurers in
this town would say the same.
This time, next time,
and every time after that.
If you asked for help,
we'd always be there for you.
So...
It has nothing to do with luck...
at all.
Really?
Yes.
Hey, Goblin Slayer...
Do you mind if I ask for a reward, too?
What do you want?
Please take off your helmet.
Why?
I kept my eyes closed that other time
because I was so embarrassed...
I think you look a lot cooler this way!
Really?
Hey!
Orcbolg took his helmet off!
No fair! I'd never seen his
face before, either!
Huh?!
Oh, my goodness! This is a rare moment!
Huh? Is it?
I guess it is.
The only time he willingly
takes off his helmet
is when it breaks or when he sleeps.
Hey... Let me see...
Ah, now this is the face of a warrior!
You have excellent features
indeed, Beard-cutter.
Hey! Get outta the way!
As I... figured... He's quite...
handsome... isn't he?
Huh... I could swear I've seen
him somewhere before...
Damn it! This pisses me off for some reason!
Hey, it's Goblin Slayer's face!
Bring out the betting pool!
Damn it! I was betting that he was a woman!
I totally thought he was a goblin.
Hey! Did anyone guess correctly?
If you did, buy us all a round!
If you asked for help,
we'd always be there for you.
So... It has nothing to do with luck...
at all.
I see.
I hope that's true.
This adventurer was an ordinary young man.
He was a man you could find anywhere.
The gods favored him as well,
but they didn't expect
anything special from him.
For he was just another pawn
they could find anywhere else.
However, that adventurer was
slightly different from the others.
He was always concocting strategies,
thinking, taking action,
training, using his wits, and being thorough.
He never let the gods roll the dice.
And then, one day,
the gods finally realized...
He would probably never save the world.
He would probably never change anything.
For he was just another pawn
they could find anywhere else.
But he would never let
the gods roll the dice.
And that's exactly why
even the gods don't know
the fate of this particular adventurer.
His battle continues today,
somewhere out there.