The others should've come with me.
I'll pass.
Baths feel like the spirits
of fire, water, and air
are all mixed up together.
That kind of bugs me.
We'd much rather have some food and wine.
I cannot think of anything better
for fatigue than some cheese.
What about you, Goblin Slayer?
I'm going to send a letter.
A letter?
Yeah.
I really have no idea what he's thinking.
I guess that's natural.
It's only been a few months since we met.
If I hadn't met him...
I...
Oh.
Do you mind if I join you?
I'm sorry for startling you.
My duties kept me a bit late.
I-It's fine...
Um... Those scars...
Oh, these? I made a slight mistake.
They got me right in the back of the head.
It happened more than ten years ago, though.
Well, um...
Are you okay now?
You're a kind person.
When I tell most people,
they just say, "I'm sorry."
But that's...
You needn't worry about it.
With these eyes,
I have seen many, many things.
Things you couldn't even imagine.
That gentleman...
Goblin Slayer, was it?
He seems like quite a dependable fellow.
Oh, um... Yes, he really is.
It seems your search is going well.
But someday...
I'm sure he will disappear.
U-Um, I-I...
Yes. Make sure you don't stay
too long, or you may get dizzy.
She knows...
She knows
what the goblins are like.
Onward Unto Death
Hey, look. It's a high elf.
Seriously? I've never seen one before.
And she's a looker, too. Nice.
Well, that's rather unpleasant.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
So, did you send your letter?
Yeah.
There was an adventurer heading to town,
so I formally requested that he take it.
Come to think of it,
I've never written a letter.
What do you write in one?
Do you just report that you're okay?
You're not wrong on the reporting part.
Which would mean he's sending
them to the farm girl.
Well, well, Orcbolg, looks like you're
capable of caring about others now.
Something's wrong.
Wrong? What do you mean?
Despite how large their sewers are,
there isn't a single quest to slay giant rats.
What a hick.
Why would those things
even exist in this town?
Now that you mention it, you're right.
Where are you going, Orcbolg?
There's something I need to get.
Ooh, what are you going to buy?
What is that?
You don't know what a bird is?
Of course I do!
It's a canary.
I told you, I know what it is!
I see.
It's not gonna cause some huge disaster
if we touch it, like that scroll, is it?
Do you think a canary could kill people?
G-Goblin Slayer, that's not what she meant.
She's wondering why you brought a canary.
When canaries sense even the slightest
hint of poison gas, they panic.
Poison gas?
Yeah.
The goblins in the nest
here have been educated.
It wouldn't surprise me if they could
use the mechanisms in these ruins.
Sir Goblin Slayer, where did
you acquire such knowledge?
Miners.
Most people in this world have
more knowledge than I do.
Beard-cutter, where are we headed today?
We're going upstream.
Their boat came from upstream.
I see.
We'll do everything we can
to avoid running into goblins.
Wow, that's unusual coming from you.
You're actually letting the goblins go?
I'm not letting them go.
I'm going take down their
leader and crush them,
then I'll slaughter them all.
Do you think it could be another
shaman, or maybe an ogre?
I don't know.
I'm sure he will disappear.
It appears this is where the map ends.
Th-This is...
There are traces of soot.
Does that mean there was a light up there?
A very long time ago.
Goblins have very good night
vision. They don't use lights.
Warriors or guards... No, it would
seem they are adventurers.
I heard there were quite a few
battles in this area back then.
This painting is probably from
four or five hundred years ago.
Oh, could this actually be a grave?
For those who had fought on the side
of order in the Age of the Gods.
And now it's just a nest for goblins...
"Even the brave are at
last brought low," huh?
That doesn't matter right now.
You're so impatient, Beard-cutter.
I'm sure the goblins will go
running when they see you.
That would be a problem.
It'd be a hassle if they ran away.
The path is getting more complicated.
They must've built it this way so that
monsters wandering in would get confused,
to keep them from disturbing
the dead warriors.
Having to wander around this place as
a lost spirit would be a cruel fate.
It would also remove one from
the circle of death and rebirth.
But this place already
belongs to the goblins.
The drawing of the map cannot
be done half-heartedly.
We must all remain vigilant.
So we're going into this room first?
It's not locked, and it doesn't
look like there are any traps.
Not on the door, at least.
Also, I'm not an expert at this, so don't
get mad at me if things go wron—
Let's go.
Look, over there!
How awful!
Wh-What is it?
Look.
This is not good. They've locked us in.
Goblins!
Looks like they got one over on us.
N-No... G-Goblin Slayer...
Calm down.
We're still alive.
Poison gas!
This is not good. We're trapped like rats.
The poison gas probably won't kill us,
but it definitely doesn't make things easier.
It's no use. I can't find another exit.
Wh-What should we do, Goblin Slayer?
I haven't been granted the
miracle to remove poison yet...
Wrap this in a piece of cloth, and
hold it over your nose and mouth.
Is that... charcoal?
It'll protect you from the poison.
If you have any herbs on hand,
put those in there, too.
Be quick, or you'll die.
Those are bags of quicklime and volcanic
earth. Mix them up and block the holes.
Concrete!
It won't dry immediately, but...
Don't worry. I've got a weathering spell.
I'll go around and block all the holes!
Dwarf, get going on that spell!
You got it!
Tick-tock, tick-tock, spin, spin, O Chronos.
Let the pendulum swing and move again.
Weathering!
Well, well. It appears that Sir Mage
has many tricks up his sleeve.
So, what are you planning to
do next, Sir Goblin Slayer?
We'll move one of these stone coffins
in front of the door to block it.
Once the poison dissipates,
they're going to barge in here.
This should take care of things.
We've finished plugging all the holes, too.
That being said, I'm out of spells.
Then take up a weapon.
Shall I summon a dragontooth warrior?
I-I'll cast Protection!
Thanks.
O horns and claws of the father, Iguanodon,
be four limbs and walk upon
this earth with two legs...
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
A dragontooth warrior!
Protection!
It's quiet outside now.
Since we plugged up the holes,
the poison gas will reverse its flow.
I'm sure at least a few of them died.
Footsteps...
I can't tell how many there are,
but something strange is among them.
Here they come!
A hob... No...
A goblin champion.
We'll cut our way through.
Indeed. Let my blade assist you.
U-Um...
Six.
You can go all-out.
Understood.
Damn it, there's a lot of them!
No use complaining about it!
You holdin' up over there?
Some... what...
Seventeen.
Goblin Slayer!
Orcbolg! Did they get him?
No!
The Protection...
How could this be?
Calm down and concentrate!
Long-ears!
You stupid goblins! Unhand her!
N-No...
Let go of me!
Why, you...
You think you can slay goblins?
You just sat and watched quietly.
You were powerless. You didn't do a thing.
Bullshit.
I heard that assassins like using string
made of human hair as a killing tool.
Apparently it doesn't break
easily or come undone.
Go! Hurry up and heal her!
Thank you for the assistance.
Thanks.
To think I'd end up owing a dwarf a favor...
But I'd shame all elves if I didn't thank you.
You were on the verge of tears.
You sure have a lot of spunk.
At least I have some!
Orcbolg!
Beard-cutter!
Sir Goblin Slayer!
Kill it!
Onward unto death!
Die like a nail hammered into a coffin!
Hey, take a good look, goblin!
Who's next?
Is it you?
Or you?
Orcbolg.
Are you all right?
Somewhat. But you're not all right, are you?
Yeah... Where's the girl?
Over there. Can you walk?
I'll try...
Up you go. Come on, get a hold of yourself.
We still have to get home.
Yeah...
Bless the stars... Thank goodness
we somehow made it.
How is she?
She will survive.
Had the wound been any deeper,
there would've been nothing I could do.
I see.
I'm... sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Gob... lin... Slay... er...
These things happen...
Next Time
Whispers and Prayers and Chants