Kirari-sama.
have you prepared yourself?
Yes, quite.
The distinguished family
heads have assembled.
Well then... shall we begin?
Mike
Let's have an official match!
W-
Wait a second!
Yumeko-senpai!
Didn't you hold on to your right for an official
match to challenge the Council President?!
Oh? Have I ever
said anything of the sort?
She didn't!
The plan to get Yumeko to
become the Council President is...
I'm not that patient of a person, you see.
Now, Manyuda-san.
let us gamble into madness.
See, I told you.
Every time things look like they're going well, you'll get the rug pulled out from under you.
Come now, Manyuda-san!
I understand now...
I have to admit. I miscalculated...
I underestimated this woman.
She was just gambling
for the sake of gambling.
Jabami Yumeko is a compulsive gambler.
This means she doesn't feel the joy and worry of winning or losing.
She's enraptured by gambling itself.
That makes this all the easier.
I just have to factor that in, too.
Fine by me.
I'll allow an official match.
How did things turn out like this...?
Having two Student Council members lose in a row in a broadcast for all students...
Something like that
should never come to pass!
Furthermore, Manyuda is most likely the
culprit behind the scheme against Yumemite.
Should he win, then that traitor
will amass even more power!
The Student Council that
the President created...
All of it will come to fall apart
thanks to my inadequacy!
Yumeko-chan, what are you
gonna do about the rules?
If we need a dealer,
we should get to it right now.
Why don't I be the dealer, then.
The Vice President?
Fine by me.
Decide the rules.
We can't waste any time on something so sudden.
You'll be playing an original card game.
Its name is "Choice Poker".
The general rules are
no different from regular poker.
Each player can change the five cards in their hand once,
and will compete using the rank of hands.
The deck you'll be using is a set of
fifty-three cards with a single Joker.
But in this version of poker,
you can't fold or call.
The player can only bet or raise.
Each round will end in a showdown,
but the player with the most earnings earns the right to "choose".
"Choose"? And just what do we choose?
"Stronger" or "Weaker".
The weak order, or the strong order.
In regular poker, it's a given that the order is from strongest to weakest.
But in this game,
the one with the right to choose can determine whether the weaker or stronger hand will win.
For the strong order, just like in normal poker, the one with the better hand is the winner.
On the other hand...
If you decide on the weak order, the
value of hands is completely reversed.
Then, the one with the
worse hand will be the winner.
Tln: 'Pig' is the Japanese equivalent of a 'no pair'.
This means that as long as you can earn money, you can turn a 'pig' into the strongest hand.
A fitting gamble for this academy, isn't it?
That explains the rules.
You can bet without limit.
We'll have you play to your limit.
I see! Even with a weak hand,
your earnings can decide your victory!
The rules are simple enough...
With reversing the order
as their special feature..
What's up with that rule...?
This is bad...
It's so out in the open, too..
Huh? What is?
Don't you get it?
No matter how you look at it, Yumeko's at a huge disadvantage.
You could even say that her
chances to win are zero!
I'm guessing neither of
you have any objections?
None.
I have none.
Well then, let's begin Choice Poker!
Why is Yumeko at a disadvantage?
You know that in regular poker, whoever
has the most funds has an advantage, right?
With larger funds, you can intimidate
your opponent by raising.
If your opponent folds because of the uncertainty in funds,
you can win regardless of the strength of your hand.
It's the reason why they say that
poker is a game where you have to bring down your opponent.
But... even she doesn't have as much as her opponent in this game,
she can still take him on, right?
The right to choose'll get taken from her, though...
That's incredibly lethal.
The player that chooses can decide the order so that it works to their benefit.
In other words,
this is a game of poker where the stronger hands are always distributed to one player.
It it were me,
as long as I couldn't be sure that I have the bigger funds,
I'd never accept a game like this.
Even an idiot can make sense of it.
B-But... Yumeko should have more than enough money on her, right?
It'd be better if you didn't
underestimate the Student Council...
One chip will be 10,000,000 Yen.
How many do you need?
Well, since I'm in possession of 310,000,000 Yen...
Thirty-one chips, if you would.
Manyuda.
Let's see. For now...
I'll take a hundred chips.
No way!
One hundred chips...
One billion?!
That's insane!
He really does have a huge
advantage in funds, huh?
It's pretty likely that Manyuda-senpai has more where that came from!
Yumeko...
First, the participation fees.
both of you, lay down one chip.
Oh, that reminds me. How did we
decide the strength of a 'pig' again?
I've never tried to aim for a
weaker hand before, you see.
In case of a 'pig', the one who has even
a single higher card is the stronger hand.
For example,
if you have a 'pig' with one king, and a 'pig' with one ten,
the one with the king is stronger.
Oh, that's how it went.
thank you kindly!
Trying to act as if you're going for a 'pig', are you?
Aren't you the shrewd one...
Well then,
I'll exchange two cards.
I'll change one.
The hands are now final.
Move on to the betting.
The cards Jabami exchanged
were a king and a jack.
If she wants to go for the weaker order,
getting rid of the stronger cards is only natural.
Still...
Of course, there's a chance that the
remaining cards are a three of a kind.
Even if she has a 'pig',
she could still be hiding an ace.
She's trying to make me go for the stronger order
by pretending to go
for the weaker herself...
My hand is a straight just
short of a few cards, a 'pig'.
Is Jabami going for a
stronger or weaker order?
I need more data for my calculations...
Let's test her.
I bet ten chips.
Ten...
100,000,000 right off the bat?!
Jabami, are you going to raise even more?
I raise by ten chips. That makes twenty-one in total.
Huh?!
Yumeko has thirty-one chips.
one loss, and she loses more than half!
Manyuda, will you raise?
No need.
Since she won at betting,
jabami has the right to choose.
Stronger, or weaker?
Let's see now... I suppose I'll be taking the stronger order, if you don't mind.
Stronger...
Now then...
Show
Down
It's a 'pig'.
A 'pig'.
Both have a 'pig', but since
she has an ace, Jabami wins.
She did it!
It should be a little easier now!
Now then, let's move on to the next round.
Just what should I do? Rules are difficult when you're unused to them, no?
I understand now.
Unlike with normal poker,
large raises mean nothing.
After all, just raising by one chip makes it possible to earn the right of choice.
That's why it'd be only natural to raise one chip at a time in this game.
If there's any reason for it,
It'd be intimidation, but...
It only leads to the one with more funds being raised over by one chip and collapsing.
That means that in the end, depending on the
proportion of the risk, they get barely any merit.
And the reason why Jabami Yumeko
does so regardless is simply...
Because she's insane.
It's because she experiences
pleasure when chasing after risks.
If I hadn't witnessed this in person, her illogical actions could have made a fool out of me.
With this, I can factor Jabami's
eccentricity into my calculations.
You have my thanks.
nishinotouin, Ikishima, Yumemite...
Thank you so much for becoming my stepping stones!
Yumeko has forty-two chips.
manyuda has eighty-nine.
Jabami Yumeko
Manyuda Kaede
She has more than enough to
be able to turn this around!
Yumeko will definitely win.
She's won a lot of gambles
where she had no advantage up until now!
This time will be the same!
I'm sure she'll win in a
way I can't even imagine!
Do you want to change?
Hmm... Let's see here...
I'll be changing two, then.
Huh?
She changed a pair of tens?!
What's up with that?
Who'd throw those away now?
I don't get it...
Two possibilities come to mind.
One, she's simply aiming for a 'pig'.
But I'm going to get
the right to choose now.
It'd be suicide to show that
you're aiming for a weak hand.
She could also have a
two pair at the start.
There's also the chance
that she has a full house.
With her showing that
she wants to go for a 'pig'
and having me choose the stronger order on top,
my gut's telling me that she's trying to win with a three of a kind, or a pair...
But the chances of her having a
pair at the start are at 4.31%.
As for a full house,
It would only be 0.23%.
Even if she were to get cards that rare, would she really toss them aside?
If she didn't do anything unneeded and just hoped for me to choose the stronger order.
She'd have a higher chance to win...
So considering Jabami's actions...
The low chances of her first hand, and the futility of a bluff...
They're nonsensical
In more ways than one.
If she were a normal opponent, that is.
This very situation,
me coming here and gambling against Jabami Yumeko, is already nonsensical.
I've already learned that she's won against other Council member through unexpected methods...
It's all because this woman
Is nonsensical herself...
Manyuda. What will you do?
That she can!
Changing five cards, then?
No.
I'm not changing.
Wh... what does he mean?
He's enticing Yumeko to bet.
Right now, if Yumeko earns the right to choose, it'll be a certain victory.
If she wants to earn that right,
she has no choice but to bet big.
Conversely, it'd be better for Yumeko-senpai to
back down if she has no confidence in her hand.
She can only take
him on with a good hand.
Just what are you doing, Manyuda-senpai?
Doing something that risky...
It's ridiculous.
Isn't this wonderful?
Can I take this as a written
challenge of sorts?
If you show me that kind of spirit...
Then how can I stand to lose?!
I bet! Forty-one chips!
All of your funds?!
Why did it turn out this way?!
I knew it. He's completely seen
through Yumeko's nature!
I raise. One chip.
Jabami.
anything to declare?
Nothing at all!
Manyuda. Choose.
Stronger.
No hesitation...
True, I'd pick the stronger order too...
Yumeko already got rid of a ten pair, so there's a high chance of her having a weak hand!
She's completely easy pickings!
No... Just believe in
jabami Yumeko's skills!
If Yumeko loses,
then it's over for me too!
She has to win!
Declarations are over. Now then...
Show
Down
It's a pig.
Oh, what a shame.
Wha...
Yumeko-chan lost!
Seriously?!
What? A pig?!
Just what the fuck are you
doing, Jabami Yumeko?!
You winning was the only way that'd get me back into the Council,
the only way that'd
let me succeed my family...
It's over... everything's over...
I see...
So she was aiming for a straight.
something like that shouldn't be possible...
This really exceeds expectations.
Still...
The fact that she'd exceed expectations
was something I'd already reckoned with...
People lose because they keep judging her
by the standards of a regular human being.
For betting as much as 410,000,000 Yen, she must have quite the trick up her sleeve.
They'd think that, and then get deceived.
But I'm different.
I fully intend on pursuing
the path to the throne.
Since the beginning, this gamble's given me a substantial advantage with my funds.
As long as one doesn't rely on cheap tricks and walks this noble path, they can never lose!
Jabami Yumeko.
In the end, you were nothing more than a pebble on the road of my righteous path!
This game is over.
and so are you.
Jabami. You're out of chips.
Are you going to
continue with the game?
What?
Sumeragi-san.
a moment, if you would.
Huh? M-Me...?
Just how much can you pay?
Huh?
Well, Sumeragi-san?
how does it look?
W-Well...
The other day, you said that
you'd like us to be friends, no?
You repeatedly stated that you wanted me to become the Student Council President.
Friends assist each other in
times of need, do they not?
I seem to have run out of
funds and am in quite the bind...
Could I ask you to lend me a hand?
Sumeragi.
Did you cut ties with the Student Council and choose to follow Jabami Yumeko instead?
Give up.
Right now,
I'm willing to let it slide.
Or would you rather
antagonise the Student Council?
I can definitely say that
It's something you'd do...
That's the exact reason why I recommended you to the Council in the first place.
Ambition.
The will to rise up,
no matter what you do.
I could see that inside you.
Ambition is the foundation
for growth and effort.
It's an important quality
for those at the top.
And it's also a quality
we happen to share...
In all honesty, I felt something
close to familiarity towards you.
Manyuda-senpai...
But still...
You didn't have the skills
to realise those ambitions.
They're out of your reach. That's all.
Skill is determined by results.
That's something a failure
like you isn't equipped with.
Give up while you're ahead.
You have no right to
walk the path of rulers.
I know. I don't mind smoothing things out and having you rejoin the Student Council...
Huh?!
If you're aware of your own skills,
then you can find a purpose.
Come back to us, Sumeragi.
I...
Oh my, oh my...
That's quite the way to put it...
Sumeragi-san has no talent?
just who decided that?
If that were even true,
for argument's sake, just why is it enough reason to throw aside her ambitions?
Because it's for her own good, of course.
No matter how much effort the incompetent show, they'll never see any results.
They only turn things from bad to worse.
that kind of effort is worthless.
In that case, giving up is better.
I do wonder about that...
The only one who can decide her
worth is Sumeragi-san herself.
Sumeragi-san, in order to obtain anything, something else must always be offered.
Sportsmen sacrifice their own youth to focus on training,
while merchants take out mortgages and borrow funds.
For the sake of realising one's
ambitions, risks must be taken.
The larger the ambitions,
the larger the risks become.
That could be time, or perhaps even effort that scrapes away at your own life...
This time, it is simply money.
Come now!
Please, make a choice!
Will you choose
peace as an incompetent,
or will you risk your own destruction for the sake of reaching the top?!
You will be the one to decide!
Sumeragi-san!
What do I do...?!
If I go with Manyuda-senpai,
I can become a council member again and report back home with my head held high!
But if I go with Yumeko...
Winning would be great, but losing would ruin everything, no question!
What do I do?!
what's the right thing to do?!
You want to join the Student Council?
Yes. Did you take a look at
the most recent tax rankings?
It showcases my resolution.
Quit while you're ahead.
Wha... And just why should I?!
You're only interested in the perks of being a Student Council member, aren't you?
It's true, right now the Student
council's influence is immense.
If you went out and exploited the status and funds of the student body,
you'd get anything you want.
Hyakkaou Private Academy
No one can disobey.
Its domination of the whole academy is what makes the Council what it is.
I'm well aware...
I'm sure that there are plenty of people that want to join the Student Council, too...
But I have the funds!
I'm someone who can contribute
to the Student Council!
If necessary,
I can prepare even more...!
You just don't get it, do you?
Huh?
The Student Council
dominates the academy.
If you look at it another way, it means that it's responsible for the entirety of the academy.
Just how many of our graduates do you think make up the backbone of Japan?
They're placing their hopes on this academy, and always keep an eye on it.
Should we betray their trust,
It would mean the literal end.
You may as well think of any open
paths in your life as sealed off.
And the Student Council
shoulders all of that.
Do you really have what it takes?
If you understand, leave.
you'll be much happier as a student.
I want to become the
student Council President.
What was that?
My father ordered me to become
a member of the Student Council.
But I don't want
to be confined to that...
If I'm doing it anyways,
then I might as well take the throne!
Just for that, I can risk anything!
"Don't betray the graduates' expectations"?
"Shoulder responsibility"?
Bring it all on!
If it means I can become Council President, I'll do anything!
Is that still not enough?!
We really are the same,
the two of us...
Huh...?
It really is an impressive tax payment.
There doesn't seem to be a problem with your personal history, either.
Alright then.
I'll recommend you myself.
The two of us will take the throne.
are you ready, Sumeragi Itsuki?
Of course!
I thought that I was accepted...
As a partner with the same goals,
someone who hid the same secret...
I thought that we felt the same,
that we both held the same ambition towards the Council President's throne...
But I was wrong.
To him, I was nothing
more than a single pawn.
If there was no use for me,
I could only be thrown aside.
I was despised...
Come on now, Sumeragi-san...
Why don't we gamble
Into madness together?
I'll pull one over you!
Episode 10
A hundred chips.
please increase it by 1,000,000,000 Yen!
I myself...
will take the throne!
Return to us, Sumeragi Itsuki!
I've increased your chips.
I'm overflowing...!
It'd be better if this was just gambling!
You just have to walk the path of rulers...
And just for that...
If it means winning,
there's nothing I won't do!
Episode 11
Life-Wagering Woman