Nomura.
Did you sleep well?
Ow!
Where am I?
The infirmary in the girls' dorm.
Which means my wounds been...
Jeez, I'm naked, no wonder I'm cold!
Your clothes are in that basket over there!
The dorm mother said when you wake up you should
get out of here without causing a scene!
How's Hanasaka?
She's sleeping in the bed
next to you but she's all okay!
That's good.
Wait, so how did I even end up here?
Episode 8
His and Crossdressing Her Circumstances
C'mon, what's wrong?
If you don't need it I'll take it back.
You little-
Shhh!
What's all this?
Princess! Stay with me!
No harm in seeing this one's true identity, yeah?
Wha-?!
What the hell is with this girl?!
That's what we should be asking you!
What the hell did you do here?
They've only just arrived here.
They haven't done anything.
Forget them, please examine the two
who have passed out.
Huh...
I'm disappointed you aren't thanking me.
After all I've done to cover you?
How is she?
The bleeding from her right hand
can be easily stopped.
But she got taken down by the same drug
that got the bear over there.
Hanasaka's body is just much smaller.
Can you do something about it?
Well, it is what I'm good at.
Leave her to me.
C'mon! Help me carry them, you idiots!
Go on without me.
I have business with the ones inside.
What do you want?
I'm the only one here right now!
I'm disappointed if you're trying to hide it from me.
There's no point in obstructing the view.
I told you, nobody else is here!
Well, alright.
I don't want to get wet, anyway.
To put it simply, Hanasaka-san and
one of your masked girls
were discovered poisoned in the dressing room.
Just to be safe, Eva...
...the dorm mother has brought them to the infirmary.
Also, I need to speak with you,
so I will be waiting by the fountain in the yard.
Speak with me? You can do that here.
I want to speak with someone who isn't here.
That's all.
It's okay now, isn't it?! Leggo!
You're gonna drown me!
After all I did to hide you!
If you'd popped out,
I'd have to give you your last rites!
And why the hell is that?
'Cause you'll never beat Tsukuyo.
If you fought her right now,
you would die without a doubt.
You sure?
Don't tell me you did this for me?
Did you think you couldn't put me
at risk for your own sake?
I'm not that weak!
Shove off.
Just can't turn down a girl when she asks me out.
You can't stop me.
Okay, but I don't think I'll need to.
Even if you try to pretend it doesn't hurt,
your body is very honest.
After all the torture and fighting me...
...you're at your limit.
I bet you'll sleep real good tonight!
It's no use, no matter how many sheep I count,
I can't stop seeing his face!
I can't sleep!
What the hell is wrong with me, really?!
N-now that I think of it, I haven't truly heard him out.
Or his reasoning, or explanation, or apology...
Maybe if I talk to him I'll feel a little better.
K-Kikakujo! What a coincidence!
Oh, it's you, Rin!
N-never would have expected you
to be going to the punishment room!
O-o-o-oh, please!
Wh-wh-why would I be going there?
You weren't planning on heading there either, right?
O-o-o-of course not!
I just wanted to have a drink before I go to bed...
That's right!
I was just going to the cafeteria!
I-I see! Me too!
I can't believe we were going to the same place!
Yes! Then why don't we go together?
T-today was truly a hassle in so many ways!
Yes, and thanks to that I'm sure I'll have
an exceedingly deep sleep!
If Kikakujo doesn't leave and go back to her room,
I can't go to the punishment room...
If Rin doesn't leave and go back to her room,
I cannot go back to the punishment room...
But how do I get Kikakujo to...
How do I get Rin to leave the room?
Onee-sama, there you are!
Ch-Chouka!
A-and Nono...
I thought for sure you'd be in the punishment room!
O-o-o-of course not!
Shoot, now that Nono and
U. Baragasaki are here, I'm locked in!
It's become exceedingly difficult to get out of here!
Onee-sama, once you find yourself comfortable,
let us return to our room!
When you're satisfied, Onee-sama, come back with me...
I-I haven't had enough yet!
I-I'll have another, too!
If I let the tea do the work for me...
I-I can't drink any more!
Alright, let's go back to our room!
She'll be forced to go back to her room!
I have to keep up the drinking pace!
I-I'll have another!
M-me too!
I'm not going to let you win!
I can drink much, much more!
M-me, too!
M-Onee-sama, you won't be able to sleep...
I'm really close to my limit...
But I can't stop drinking...
I can't slow down...
Chouka will notice if I do!
Oh, God!
Oh, Buddha!
Onee-sama! Please, stop all this!
We're going back to our room!
H-hey! Wh-what are you doing?!
I can still drink much m...
Oh, great, you're both here!
Nomura's sleeping in the infirmary right now.
Huh?
W-wait, why do you know that?!
'Cause Nomura attacked me in the bath,
and he hit me...
What?!
I get it, so you carried me all the way here.
Hey, don't tell me you carried me
through the girls' dorm in the buff.
I did!
Gee, thanks.
Buri-buri! Buri-buri!
To the outside, it looks like Oni and Kikaku overdid it,
so Warabi and I took you away.
After that we had a bit fight about what to do with you.
That's a little tough to believe.
It'll pass! That's one of the great things
about being one of the Five Swords!
Wait, am I forgetting something?
39 degrees.
It's still cold outside,
so why were you napping out there?!
What did you have to do out in the yard?
I wasn't napping there because I wanted to.
How disappointing.
Your body has been weak since you were born!
You can't be reckless like this!
Tamaba, hey, uhh...
No, just, how're your injuries?
Huh? What?
I can't hear you real well.
My left eardrum got blown out.
S-sorry.
There's something way more important
you should be worried about!
Don't worry, I explained the truth
to those two girls for you!
Thanks.
I told them you attacked me in the bath,
hit me, and blew out my eardrum!
HEY! They're gonna take that the wrong way!
Let's play again sometime, Nomura!
Sh-she's the devil.
I get that a lot!
Is your eardrum really busted?!
Anyway, you got another visitor!
Now the Oni's here!
Hey, wait, Onigawara!
Yesterday was just...
Mirrored Breathing?!
And then...
I'm so sorry!
90-Degree Bow
Huh?
Tamaba told me it was all part of her plan!
That bitch. So she actually did tell them the truth.
I know it's ridiculous to ask you to forgive me,
but I'll do anything to get your forgiveness!
That's why I told you to wait.
Hold back! Calm down!
Mirrored Breathing
What's this?
What's going on?
Infirmary
It was all Tamaba's doing.
Nothing for you to worry about.
That's not all I wanted to apologize about.
That... scar, on your back...
Was that...
Onigawara, you talk too much.
A-are you angry?
No.
P-please hit me as hard as you want, Nomura!
Whoa, hey.
I know it's selfish of me, but I want to put an end to this.
I'm not worthy of speaking with you
until I've been punished.
I feel like I'm losing myself.
Well alright, there's something
I've always wanted to do to you.
You can do whatever you want to me.
Okay, close your eyes.
M-my eyes?
Look up a little more.
This situation is almost like...
No, no, what am I expecting him to do?!
No, think...
If that were the case, I-I'd be reluctant,
but I'm the guilty one here, so I've got no choice.
Oh, I should have brushed my teeth
before coming here!
Okay, don't make a fuss or try to hide it.
Hands behind your back.
Did I do something wrong?
I didn't expect you to be this upset about it.
I'd rather you look at my naked body.
but showing you my face is
the only equal price for what I've done.
I heard you were embarrassed about it
but I don't get it.
Why do you go this far?
My mother said that I was ugly.
When I was little, my father
cheated on my mother and left us behind.
She must have seen his face in mine.
She said I was the daughter of the devil.
She ordered me to cover my face
when I was around her.
I felt like the only time I could live without shame
was when I was wearing that mask.
So when I left the house and
came to live in the dorms,
I took it upon myself to continue wearing the mask.
I've never told anyone this.
I'd really appreciate it if you didn't tell anyone.
Th-this isn't good.
I need to go to the restroom,
but this is really not the time to interrupt!
There was one time when you said
something nice about my face.
I couldn't tell with the mask you wore yesterday,
but you're pretty cute.
I was really happy to hear that.
I felt you'd accepted me for who I was.
It was the first time I thought it might be
okay to take off my mask.
I want to take it off.
I want to be able to take it off.
I thought about smashing it, but if you want to
take it off, you've gotta do it yourself.
You don't have to rush it though.
You'll get there someday for sure.
Keep it on till then.
Okay.
Shitty story, but you still love your mom after all that.
Yeah.
I can't understand that feeling.
I'm an orphan.
I can't even remember my parents' names or faces.
And the old man who took me in
was obsessed with swords.
Every day he put me through
all the training and abuse.
But it had an effect on me, for better or for worse.
No! I'm about to relieve myself,
but I can't interrupt this!
I've got to think about something fun
to take my mind off it!
My grandfather got real excited about
my talent for the sword.
Every day, the training got worse and worse.
My body hadn't fully matured yet,
and soon it failed me.
Don't think about water!
Kyo-bo! Don't give me weird temptations!
I couldn't hold a sword anymore,
but I got my freedom in-
Hey!
Hey, c'mon, don't cry!
Trading secrets is the best way to keep 'em safe.
Let's put 'em away, okay?
It's our little secret.
Nomura, thank you.
Kyo-bo, thanks for nothing!
Nomura!
Not another person!
Kikakujo?
Satori-san told me everything!
I-I've done terrible things to you!
You are absolutely right to be angry!
I don't know how I should apologize to you...
O-of course, I know you will not let me off easy!
So please...
do whatever you like with my body!
Nah, I'm good.
What?! So quick?!
Don't tell me you've done something worse to Rin-san!
Y-you fool! Don't lump me in with you!
But...
Put your clothes back on!
Yo!
W-welcome back.
So you're alright.
What's that supposed to mean?
I-I mean, you weren't in class yesterday.
Yeah, somethin' came up.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Nah. Nothing.
Hey, question.
What do you think of me?
Ew, gross!
That's such a gross question!
Just that it's damn hot and you take up space, and...
I'm a terrible person, right?
Yeah, my roommate did drug my dinner.
But I bet he did it 'cause he
had to protect the guys' dorm.
A thoughtful guy like that ain't terrible.
He's my friend.
I washed your pillow cover for you.
That was the best I could do.
Aichi Symbiosis Academy
Permission card
Thanks, now I can sleep really well tonight.
This school really is...
...full of great people.
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Tamaba Satori puts the
craziest plans together sometimes!
Not only did she wait for him in the bath,
but she fought him naked to distract him!
But those tactics won't work on us!
I'm so not interested in a woman's naked body!
So what if you saw Nomura naked?
Episode 9
0000000000
The Day Love Died