Rin Onee-sama... how horrible!
My, aren't you...
One of the Supreme Five Swords
Kikakujo Mary
Rin-san's friend, Nono Mozuno?
Oh, Mary!
I'm sorry, is it your group's time for the baths already?
No, I simply came early.
Don't you worry about me.
I don't see Rin-san here.
Well, I can understand.
After being held down by that transfer student
and having her exceedingly
precious lips stolen from her...
P-please don't go on!
It's well of you to be exceedingly
concerned for Rin-san.
I will correct that exceedingly
disgusting transfer student.
There's no need for that.
My, Chouka.
You shall not need to act, Mary-Onee-sama.
Your younger sister Chouka
will take care of the whole matter.
I, Chouka, who is said to be
the closest to the Five Swords,
will erase the blemish of Rin-sama's embarrassing
mistake as head of the Supreme Five Swords.
Who said you're closest to the Five Swords?
And I don't want you getting revenge
for her at all, U Chouka-chan!
Pray stop calling me U Chouka, if you please!
Chouka, let's stop playing about, now, shall we?
Let's enjoy the baths.
Episode 2
The Chastity Dorm Riot
Looks like it's swelling a little.
I can't believe the only thing you hurt was your right foot.
Yeah, when I tripped over that root.
That meant I couldn't use any of my footwork.
I was screwed if I couldn't finish her there.
With your magic bullet thing?
How'd you do that with your foot all messed up?
It's somethin' special I came up with.
I can fire it no matter what stance I'm in.
I spent most of my youth to get my hands on that move.
Not really worth it, but hey, it's a good thing to have.
By the way, this permission slip to leave the grounds?
Where do I get one?
You should be able to get a slip from
the head of the Five Swords, Onigawara Rin.
Well, that's pretty unlucky.
On top of that, you need a stamp from each of
the five Swords for the permission slip to be valid.
The hell?! Every one?!
Their impression of you is the lowest it can get.
Without a lot of good material,
it's going to be impossible to get one.
Ugh, my headache's back.
I've got some aspirin.
The school store will sell the basics you might need.
If you write down a list and turn it in in the morning,
it'll be here when you come back from school.
What about luxuries?
Huh?
Don't play dumb.
You didn't get like this just off what they serve here.
God, you have good eyes.
We've got a smuggler.
Costs a pretty penny, but if there's
something you want, he'll get it in for you.
Jeez, it's like a foreign prison over here.
So if I ask him to get something
by tomorrow morning, could he get it?
Having an emergency?
Depends on the goods. What do you need?
A box of cakes.
What is he even thinking?
Figured I'd come appease you with cakes.
Hey...
Watch out!
If you let your guard down, he might kiss you!
Hey, Purple.
Hey!
Don't call me by the color of my undies!
Kurasaki! Kurasaki Sasa!
Sorry 'bout that.
So, Sakki, you know where Onigawara is?
Excuse me? Whose fault do you-
I feel like I've never met such an insensitive guy before.
Ui! C'mon, tell him off!
Who're you?
Migii Ui.
Got it.
Micky, could you tell me where Onigawara is
and what color her underwear is?
She got a fever from the shock and is lying down in bed.
I think it was white.
Hey! Don't tell him that!
I see. Thanks a bunch! Really learned a lot!
Forget about that last answer!
Hey, Masuko.
Do the girls go back to the dorms for lunch?
No, the girls can eat the dorm lunches
wherever they want.
I don't think they'd go all the way back
to the dorm for lunch.
Where's the girls' dorm?
On the southeast end of the academy grounds.
Omigod, don't tell me. You're kidding!
I'm free to go wherever I want during lunch, right?
Good on you, Masuko!
Only been a little bit since we met
but you've got me down cold!
Nono should come around soon to check on me.
Not only did he give me a shock,
but he gave me a cold, too...
Nomura Fudo.
Nomura!
You shallow, playboy, lecherous, crude, rude,
droopy-eyed, loose-lipped, scruffy-haired, blabbermouth,
idiot, liar, moron!
37.6 Degrees
Moron, moron, moron!
Well, to be honest, I can't say
there's nothing good about him.
That was the first time I've ever been pinned.
Or kissed...
No!
It's all because I was weak.
So I should just forget about that.
But he didn't...
He didn't have to back off after that, that idiot!
He should be somewhat grateful,
even if it was with me.
It was my first kiss, too...
I can't get any rest thinking about it!
You're looking better than I thought!
C'mon, don't push yourself so hard.
You've got a fever, right?
Man, you really are burning up.
38.5 Degrees
Wh-why are you here?!
Came to check on you.
Heard you were passed out in bed.
Nice place you got here!
Like a five-star hotel.
Way better than the guys'.
Here, got you a box of cakes. Have one.
Th-thank you.
Man, this is interesting.
I couldn't tell with the mask you wore yesterday,
but you're pretty cute.
Guess I was lucky I got to kiss you.
R-really? Well, good!
Man, good for you! Yeah!
Man, that mask is such a shame.
Can't you just take it off?
N-n-n-n-never, no!
I'm, i-if I don't wear it, everyone can see my face,
and I'll be too embarrassed to go out...
Well, you're free to do what you want.
Not gonna force you to take it off.
By the way, I want one of those
permission slips you were talking about.
Can I have one?
Wha-?!
Y-you idiot!
We only give that to students that are in good moral
standing who will not embarrass themselves off-campus!
Why the hell would I give one to you?! Seriously!
Wh-what? Getting angry won't help your case!
Huh?
No, I was just wondering, you don't wear
your uniform outside the school, right?
Of course not.
Are you implying that you want
to see me in regular clothes?
Yeah.
37.5 Degrees
I'd really wanna see that. It'd be real interesting.
38.0 Degrees
S-so you're saying that you'd like
to come with me, outside...
38.0 Degrees
G-guess I have no choice!
Here! Just for you!
Alright!
That's it?
Will this make up for you
taking the time to check on me?
It more than makes up for it!
I feel bad. Want me to pay the difference in kisses?
39.0 Degrees
H-hey!
It's Nono!
Onee-sama, I asked the dorm mother to
make you a special sick day meal for...
You p*****t!
I'll castrate you!
It's a misunderstanding! Just hear me out!
Stop right there!
What the hell is this place?!
A booby-trapped haunted house?!
Stop right there!
My, I thought I heard Nono-san's
vulgar yelling from the dorms.
Well, isn't that the porco to whom
Rin-san failed to put an end.
I see.
Nono-san, pray forgive me, but I am going to
snatch this one up from you.
The right hand of the beautiful Mary Onee-sama!
La regina delle farfalle, Chouka U. Baragasaki!
Hold it right there, if you please!
You're the man who escaped from
Rin-sama's grasp yesterday, yes?
Nomura Fudo, am I correct?
C'mon, now. The accent's on the first syllable.
And who might you be?
Forgive my late introduction.
Yes, I am the younger sister figure to the beautiful Mary Onee-sama,
the woman closest to the Supreme Five Swords,
and head of the Junior Five Swords!
La regina delle farfalle, Chouka U. Baragasaki!
Queen of the Butterflies
Chouka
Baragasaki
Pleased to make your acquaintance!
Regene delle farfar?
That is what everyone calls me, yes!
Nono! U Chouka!
Call me la regina delle farfalle, if you please!
So you've got a middle name, huh?
What's the "U" stand for?
W-well, uh, it's...
Just "U"!
"U", like a cormorant?
And she doesn't have a middle name, she just took
the "U" from Ubarasaki and made it an initial!
She pretends to be Italian,
but she's really just a Japanese girl!
Ubarasaki
And most important of all,
the head of the Junior Five Swords is me, Nono!
It's me, the little sister figure to
the wonderful Rin Onee-sama!
Mozuno Nono
That's old news.
That will change once I defeat the prey
that Rin-sama let escape!
It will increase my beautiful
Mary Onee-sama's reputation as well.
So please, be a good boy and let me
correct you to death!
Jeez, what an annoying immature brat.
S and M play is twenty and up, you know!
You don't know when to give up, do you?!
U Chouka! Stop getting in my way!
Right back at you!
Hey, hold it!
Stay out of this!
Ah, jeez.
I'm gonna start crying if I have to be a babysitter.
I'm not gonna play with you that much.
U Chouka?
Look, U Chouka is fighting!
With Nono!
I thought I heard a nice sound!
Kikaku's U Chouka and Oni's Nono!
And is that the man from all the rumors, Nomura?
I feel bad for him being so outnumbered!
But I'm not gonna cheer you on, okay?
Because I hate you sooo much.
Kashima Shinden Jikishinkage School!
Shortsword Form!
Kashima Shinden Jikishinkage School
Shortsword Form
Strike and Shove!
Strike and Shove
She went for my wrist with the weapon
and kicked at my weak spot.
She needs to stop aiming there with her kicks, jeez.
Her stance reminds me of how Onigawara returned to hers.
The same teacher?
Stop screwin' around with that.
That girl, my goodness.
Is she picking a fight with Rin-san's girl again?
I could do this all day!
We are the Junior Five Swords,
and this is considered a level two correction!
Level two correction?
It's when two or more people carry out a punishment!
Only one person in the long history of coexistence
has made it through this.
That person is the horrid Empress!
Empress? The hell is that?
There are people above the Five Swords?
She's a transfer student who came just before you!
An extremely rare, female delinquent!
She uses a whip, huh? Don't see that often.
It's fast and moves too irregularly to predict.
And the crack of the whip drives fear into her enemies.
However...
Nono! Go around to the other side of the barcaccia!
Barcaccia?
My goodness!
By the Spanish Steps!
Drive him into a corner from the Trinita dei Monti!
Stop calling the places in the school courtyard
like they're the Spanish Plaza!
Water's Current
U... U Chouka!
I-I know!
A whip is made for punishment and torture.
It's not a real weapon.
And it's not good in group battles or with obstacles.
And if you two don't work together, there's no point
in you both going after me, it's just an insult.
Nono! Please get off of me!
I can't... breathe!
Nono! This is not right!
That's enough of your kiddie pranks, little girls.
I hope you're ready.
I'm gonna beat the respect for your elders into you.
Onee-sama!
Nono?! You can't cry- you can't lose!
Nono's heart is breaking!
I've got to do something!
Please, give me strength, Onee-sama!
I must hold out!
I'm scared, too!
What?!
Ohmigod, he's a p*****t.
A p*****t?!
He's a p*****t!
P*****t!
Hold it, hold it! That's just not fair!
I'm the one who should be crying here!
So that's the magic bullet that took out Oni.
Even with my sharp eyes, I couldn't tell what it was,
but maybe Tsukuyo's sharp ears did?
Well, forget about that.
I hope you're ready for her.
You laid your hands on U Chouka,
and Kikaku won't let that slide.
Ugh, after all that it was a bust.
You mean this?
Are you sure?!
I said I'd do it once,
I wouldn't go back on my word.
Take it.
Whoa there.
Thanks a ton!
Get rested up and come to school tomorrow, alright?
School's so much more boring without you.
Hey!
I can't believe you're all the way out here!
Wh-what's wrong?
Well...
What?!
39.5 Degrees
Rin-san, are you okay?
O-oh no! What do we do, Ui?!
Please forgive me!
Please, Mary-Onee-sama!
My, you must be exceedingly pitiful, Chouka.
This is a punishment, Chouka.
Submerge your shoulders until you've finished counting.
To lay hands on my exceedingly cute Chouka...
I'll have you repay the exceedingly
large debt you incurred!
Nomura Fudo!
Hey, good morning.
Looks like you feel better.
Don't act all friendly with me!
Huh?
If he gets too close, you might get pregnant!
How terrifying...
He's hit rock bottom.
Don't look at me!
Even Masuko?
Listen up, Nomura Fudo!
I don't want to do this, but it's for the sake of
protecting the order of the academy!
I will be supervising you from now on!
Huh?
What?!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Chouka U. Baragasaki uses a whip!
A whip is fast and moves at random,
making it hard to read its movements!
Still, if there's something in the way,
it's hard to wave it around properly.
It's not really suited for mob action.
You didn't know that?
There's nothing cool about that whip!
Episode 3
The Fair Sword, Kikakujo Mary
What a horrible pun.