Mary Onee-sama!
P-pardon me!
Mary Onee-sama! I was looking for you!
You are exceedingly loud during my dinner, Chouka.
My apologies!
I have to eat properly in preparation
for tomorrow's correction.
About that transfer student...
I see. Is that so?
That story is quite different than the one I'd heard.
I'm sorry to have made you worry!
You don't have to worry, Nono.
I won't let that man lay a finger
on any of the other Five Swords.
There should not be any more victims.
He's been placed under Rin-san's supervision?!
I have no idea what she means by this,
but it's exceedingly unacceptable!
He's to be my prey, after all.
Episode 3
The Fair Sword, Kikakujo Mary
Man, it's so big!
I've been waitin' to read this!
You better hide it.
You're acting all casual,
but do you understand the situation you're in?
U. Baragasaki, the girl you made cry,
is one of the Five Swords' pet basket cases.
She's one of Kikakujo Mary's favorites.
Basket case?
Haven't heard that word in a long time.
That's because it's a new word.
They all love buri-buri water basket torture!
God, not that!
Wow, can't believe you knew that.
In any case, Onigawara likes to
drive transfer students out,
but Kikakujo likes to drive them into a corner.
She's a whole lot crueler.
And both of them have got their eyes on you!
But wasn't there someone who survived
both those girls correcting them?
Yeah, the Empress.
So this is the Five Swords?
Huh. You weren't half bad.
You're well worth reigning over.
Her striking hand was less like a chop, more like...
...a blade.
Yes, that's totally it.
Huh? Didn't she transfer in a little bit before I did?
What's up?
Nothing.
But her nickname means she's a girl, right?
Well, duh.
Nomura Fudo! Get out here!
Hey! The accent goes...
...on the first syllable, right?
You're up late, Nomura.
But good morning!
No, you just get to school way too early.
Are you still mad about what happened the other day?
Lemme explain.
You mean with Nono and Chouka? Relax.
The Five Swords are not ones to believe in rumors.
I have the gist of what happened.
But for the sake of maintaining order at this school,
it's only natural that someone should supervise you!
Not very organized, but no problems to report.
Do you have a handkerchief?
You're gonna make me cry.
You can use it to wipe your tears.
So what is this?
You gonna follow me around
everywhere that's not the dorms?
That goes against this
freedom-lovin' guy's beliefs, you know.
Don't tell me you're gonna
come in the bathroom with me, too.
Should I?
You've gotta be joking.
It's no joke!
Keeping watch on your behavior and
attitudes is exceedingly lax!
You're going much too easy on him!
That's right!
So that's the girl with a rapier on her belt.
Kikakujo...
Listen up!
He trampled through the girl's dorm and
made a huge mess, contaminating our sacred space!
Then he laid his hands on you,
and Nono-san, and my younger sister!
He stripped them, tied them up, shoved them down,
and tried to sink his venomous fangs into them!
Whoa, these rumors are getting way outta hand.
It's a simple misunderstanding.
I guarantee you he did not do anything out of ill will.
He himself accepts that he was the cause of
this confusion and is apologetic about it.
Apologetic?
So I will be watching over him
to make sure it doesn't happen again.
There should be no problem with that, yes?
There is an exceedingly large problem with that!
Pas question!
Je me permets de vous dire que...
Sister, you're getting so worked up
you're forgetting to speak Japanese!
Pardon!
Comment direz...
I'm sorry to have to say this, but you!
Ever since he bais...
um, uh...
...k-kissed you!
You've been acting exceedingly strange!
Wha?! Y-you don't have to translate every little thing!
Nomura, go on ahead!
Hey now, I don't need a chick to protect me.
I can wipe my own ass.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just going to talk it over with them.
And men shouldn't take part in girl talk.
Go.
Okay, okay, I get it.
Well, get along, you two!
Kikakujo, he is mine. Don't touch him.
Not if I get to him first.
I suppose we can't avoid it, then.
You could say we're talking things out with battle.
Chouka, let me handle this.
You go prepare that cochon for me.
Of course, Sister!
Good luck!
I'll be right there!
Don't underestimate me!
I won't make the same mistake with you one on one!
You sure about that?
Take this!
Whips are easy to catch things with,
but it's hard to make them go exactly where you want.
Jeez! It's all because Onigawara
made me rush this morning!
If someone sees this, I'm totally...
A...
Amou...
You're still recovering from your illness,
so your true strength is out of reach.
You're no match for me.
Well then, pardon me.
W-wait!
Feel free to chase after me.
Though I'm not sure if you can keep up
in your current condition.
Hey...
Stay back.
Her voice has a higher pitch, but they look so alike.
The name is Amou.
Nomura Fudo. Become my subordinate.
I will not take no for an answer.
Those eyes...
The aura about her...
Stay back!
I have need to prepare to face you.
Come again later.
The way you speak...
You're Amou, aren't you?!
Hey! Do you remember me?!
When the hell did you become a woman?!
I am very different from the "Amou" you speak of.
And I have always been a woman.
You sure about that, huh?
One punch and we'll know!
Nomura Fudo!
My God!
What are you doing with your clothes like that?!
Don't turn towards me!
H-his porcini mushroom...
His sea lion... his snake...
His dick...
Come on! Snap out of it, Chouka!
Are you alright, Chouka? Hey!
She disappeared on me.
I won't go easy on you!
I'll cut off your bits and castrate you like a pig!
I hear that's called your "bullet".
The force and speed behind it
certainly lives up to the name.
Or perhaps that was a name you gave it yourself?
Who knows.
But hey, you can call it whatever you want.
I'll say it again.
Become my-
Is this your answer?
How truly foolish you are.
Answer me carefully.
Become my subordinate.
They call that the katana, right?
Heard only half the story but the name's perfect.
Really suits you, too.
Remember this fondly!
That's right.
I attacked him with the perfect strike
that would make him completely fall for me.
Why did I not swiftly take out my target?
For what reason is my hand swaying?
Could it be...
No.
I will never give that man any recognition!
The next time I see him, I'll kill him.
Class Duty
Inaba
Whoa there, you tryin' to kill me?
Oui. Enjoy my exceedingly
tortuous treatment, you filthy pig!
She's actually pissed at me.
Bladeproof material is good at deflecting swipes,
but piercing strikes cut through real easy.
And this is making it real hard.
I don't know much about Western swordplay.
That transfer student and Kikakujo-san
are embroiled in a fierce battle.
The way she avoids vertical movement of the hips and
elbows is similar to Japanese swordsmanship.
This kind of movement is especially
prevalent in the jigen school style.
But her outer-facing left-side hip and leg
act differently than in Japanese swordplay.
The flexible footwork using the knees and toes
allows for increased reach and speed of attack.
Flick!
Flick
You don't have time to be standing there in shock.
I won't be stopping for you!
At this rate I'll be trapped by her movements
and at the disadvantage.
I've got to take the initiative somewhere!
Redoublement
Touche par touche
My, it's just like a Spanish bullfight!
Except I'm fighting a cochon, a pig!
As long as he continues to take damage,
I won't get hit by any attacks.
All I have to do is whittle down his strength!
At the same time, the pain
wears down his mental strength.
No man can resist admitting defeat!
Nomura...
U. Baragasaki!
Yes.
Hey! Where did those two go?!
B-b...
beyond the Spanish Steps...
I see.
Nope, no clue!
Spanish?
What kind of code is that?
Steps...
Over there?
I'm coming for you!
Trying the same thing again?
A bull would learn better than you!
I need just enough space to be able to hit her!
Touche par dessous
You're much more resilient than I expected.
But there are ways of attacking you
at close range as well!
Petite bête!
What'd you say?
My, if you like, I can translate it for you!
Kikakujo-san is aiming for areas
where nerves are concentrated.
This makes him reflexively flinch,
slowing his movements.
And the transfer student
doesn't have a special weapon.
It will be impossible for him to break through.
Then you have Onigawara-san,
who is heading in the completely wrong direction.
I have no idea what is wrong with her today.
I'm at my limit.
Well, here goes nothing!
A tackle?!
Hope you got my back, God!
I thought you'd come at me like this!
Don't hate me for killing you!
This doesn't feel like...!
I knew you'd come at me like that!
A manga magazine, under his clothes?!
Onigawara was stupid not to check here, too.
I have distance between us again!
You have no weapon, you can't reach me!
Reach-extended-by-one-magazine
Magic Bullet
It can't be, I can't be...
Knew the monthly manga mag is where it's at!
I thought you couldn't use your left hand
to defend in fencing.
I know following the rules is important and all,
but is now really the time to stick to them so closely?
Shut up, you filthy animal!
Kill me!
I would rather die than endure this embarrassment!
Shit, your sword went through all the way
to the reader's comments!
Are you listening to me?!
What?
What do you mean, what?!
Y-you're going to treat me even worse
than Rin-san, aren't you?
Like in a doujinshi!
You orc!
Not really.
What did you say?!
Are you implying that Rin-san
is more charming than I am!?
The hell?
This situation is exceedingly horrific, isn't it?!
He took an exceedingly horrific pleasure
in taking Rin-san's lips,
and not only did he assault Rin-san's Mozunono,
but also my little sister Chouka,
doing all kinds of horrible things to them as well...
So if he doesn't do anything to me...
That would be exceedingly humiliating!
Took a hard blow to the head
Whatever, just hurry up and
fondle my breasts or something!
C'mon, c'mon!
No way.
Ain't gonna!
Is it because you like smaller breasts,
or do you have some fetish you can't state aloud?
Nah, I like big ones.
I just don't like being coerced into doing it.
Coerced...
More importantly, you know about
the permission slip to leave the school, right?
Do you have your stamp on you?
I'd be super happy if you could give me one!
Yes, I have it.
Here it is.
Come and get it!
Now you have to touch my boobs!
It's only natural for him to touch them now!
What?!
She's right, this ain't forcing...
It's perfect.
She's turned things around on me at the last moment!
I told you, I'm not gonna grope anyone
if they're forcin' me to.
Petit bête...
I thought men were just animals
following what was practical,
but there are men like you who value
their own morals over their desires, too.
I've lost.
Well, I'll get your stamp another way.
Hey.
I take my eyes off you for one second...
What are you doing?
Wait, I haven't done anything yet-
That's it.
Say anything more, and I swear...
I'll correct you!
H-hold it right there!
Th-this was a test!
Nomura didn't touch me, even after I went this far.
So that means he must have
no sexual desires for you at all, Rin-san!
Hey, what is that supposed to mean?!
You passed! I'll give you my stamp!
Huh?
But for me to give you my stamp,
I'll have to take responsibility for you.
What?
I will also be joining Rin-san in
supervising your behavior from now on!
What are you saying?! I told you, he's mine!
He's my cochon!
He doesn't need two people watching him!
Well then, you can just quit!
Wait, why did things end up this way?
Why me?!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Kikakujo Mary uses a rapier!
A flick is a scary technique that uses the flexibility
of a rapier to prick at your opponent's back!
You can defend all you want, but it just keeps
pricking you and pricking you...
like some harpy of a mother-in-law!
Omugi, there's so much dust on that old joke.
Episode 4
00000000000000000000000000
The Warabinpics are Starting!