A tense car chase is continuing at the scene.
That bastard...
Nagai! Are you sure we have to do this?
Out of the way, Nakano!
And your job is?
To protect you.
I never wanted to see your face again.
Kill!
Stop!
I’m here to make a deal.
You think I can trust an Ajin?
We're taking down Satou even if it’s the last thing we do!
We'll become your pawns!
Your immortal soldiers!
We’ve apprehended the suspects.
Was it Nagai Kei?
No, it was someone else. It did look like him, though.
-Please support Ajin financially when it becomes available to you.-
So, we meet again. It's Satou.
As far as I know, the government has not responded to my demands.
So, I’ve decided to get started.
Yes, it’s the young man who’s at the start of the batting list.
And with that...
...I begin the countdown.
And as the second wave progresses,
we’ll start preparing for the third one.
And third wave will be the last.
I will take over this country.
This video was uploaded to Ajin.net 10 minutes ago.
The storm is coming.
Everyone around
here is an idiot.
Make sure to mix it properly.
I won’t mess it up!  You’re starting to sound like Okuyama.
If you mess it up, the only consequence is that you’ll die.
Sounds just like him, that was great!
Okay, all finished!
Wow, this is impressive.
Might even say that it's Oscar nomination worthy.
[screen: flight ticket confirmation]
Here, give this to Satou.
Did you make sure to get two seats?
Yeah.
I wonder if it’s really untraceable.
If you put that much care into your marksmanship, you'd get really good.
Shut up.
I paid with a card under a stranger's name, so it's fine.
I used card info that I bought on a Russian site. They have a quite a few with Japanese names.
And I use virtual currency to do business, so it can’t be traced.
Oh?  The world changed a lot while I was away.
With some effort, even a junior high school student could do it.
Tanaka-kun.
Who are you?
On edge, as usual. It’s me.
Satou-san, is that you?
Remarkable work, isn’t it?
Are you okay with Okuyama handling everything? I don't like his attitude.
Ideally you'd be suitable, but your face is too well-known. I'm sure it's fine.
Why do I... have to do this...
I can't do any more.
You haven't even done twenty.
I’m from a white-collar background.
I know you're right for this job.
But you weigh 4 kilos more than our data from 40 days ago. You gotta lose it.
I wonder if this is what corporate hell feels like.
Nagai Kei!
Do it properly!  No slacking!
I should have killed you when I had the chance!
I'll dunk you in a vat of formalin!
Can't believe him...
What?  Three more sets? That’s way more than Nagai!
You're right for this job. You’re our muscle around here.
What? That sounds pretty idiotic.
Don’t complain. If you finish, I’ll show you how to use the tranquilizer gun I mentioned earlier.
Really?  Don’t break your promise!
Tosaki-san. I got word from Sokabe-san, it seems that in the end Sakurai-san isn’t going to change his plans.
Is that so? Good grief.
To take a business trip at a time like this... He really is careless.
He upped his bodyguards, and said that on the contrary,
once he reaches his destination, he’ll be safer.
Well, then...
Shimomura-kun. You should move here as soon as possible.
We need to focus on coming up with a plan for how to restrain Satou.
Understood.
To do that, we need to clarify what we have that Satou doesn't.
This is our outpost.
You’ll never lose weight drinking that.
Recovery from exhaustion calls for sugar content.
All you did was strength training.
Nagai-kun.  Nakano-kun.
Do you need something?
I want you to meet someone.  Come with me.
Okay.
What is it? Is something wrong, Nakano?
Shimomura-san is... really pretty, isn’t she.
Think she and Tosaki-san are going out? They’re always together.
I doubt that. I mean, she’s an Ajin.
What?
You didn’t notice?
She brought out a ghost at the hospital.
And when we were escaping from the village.
I wonder if she has a boyfriend.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Oh?
Who’s that?
Ogura...Ikuya! The American Ajin researcher!
Genius.
You’re Nagai Kei, correct? Japan’s third Ajin.
I’m Nakano.
Ajin are interesting. They make you wonder if even the most meaningless of lives have value.
I’m uh, Nakano-
Mind if I smoke?
Please don't. I can't stand the smoke.
Nagai-kun. Why do you think people have to die?
...Because their hearts stop?
Because there’s a limit to the number times that cells can regenerate.
Once you reach that, regeneration stops, and life ceases to functi...
Wrong. It’s because that's how the universe decided it'd be.
Ogura-san. Save the small talk for later. Get on with the discussion.
According to Tazaki-kun behind that  camera-
It’s Tosa-
-your IBM is pretty unusual.
It's Tosaki.
Bring it out.
You might die.
You sound like a pack of cigarettes.
Is it really okay, Ogura-san?
No, it’s not!
Shut up. I can’t write a chart without seeing my patient first.
You won’t be able to see it, anyway.
Do it like you mean to kill me.  Then I’ll be able to see it.
Its shape is plain, but it’s very concentrated.
It’s unusual for it to be so well-defined.
I wonder if this is what corporate hell feels like.
I need to pee.
Keep talking.
It’s just as reported. So it does exactly
the opposite of what you command?
It seems its nature is twisted through and through.
Why me?
And it's self-propelled without orders. Very interesting.
There was a similar case with an ajin farmer in Iowa.
At first, the IBM was allowed to do
simple farm work, like pulling up weeds.
But one morning a few years later, it decided for itself
to start harvesting corn. It was even riding a tractor.
In your case, you’ve left it alone for too long.
What? No, I first brought it out about a month ago.
No, it’s been a lot longer for you. Probably since infancy.
Hey, watch out!
What should we do?
Leave it there. It’ll disappear in five minutes.
Huh?
What?
Well, when I was trying stuff out before, I was
able to keep it out for as long as 30 minutes.
How many times could you bring it out in a row?
According to the report, five times.
My record is nine.
That's odd. Your IBM is abnormally concentrated.
My ghost is... concentrated?
What’s with that amount?
That’s true, Satou-san said the same thing.
Hey, Nagai! You got my shirt dirty!
Aren't you used to that, blue-collar boy?
But this is red!
That kind of concentration is unthinkable without a suitably long period of time.
No, this isn't just because of time.
Variations occur depending on a person's ego
and stage of emotional development.
How long have you been an Ajin?
Like I said, only for about a month.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you for waiting. Boarding
starts 30 minutes before the flight.
Have a good trip.
I sure will.
Ok, all clear.
Here... you are.
Good work.
You’re... wall...well...ca..come.
You’re dexterous, but you can’t get
the hang of controlling your IBM, can you.
It doesn't work quite the... some... same as a machine.
Well, it’s just a matter of practice.
Simo Hayha?
As I'd expect of Okyuama-kun. Well, I’ll be off.
Day two is Miyako-jima. I wonder if they're'll be any cute girls?
This is bad, I’m getting nervous.
Still?  I told you, it's fine. My dad's nice.
Do you think we need to worry about terrorism?
Forget about that, let me check the documents.
Now that you mention it, did you see the first-class
passengers? I wonder if it's a criminal escort.
What?  There’s no way they would use first class for a criminal escort.
Don’t be so nervous.
They've checked every passenger on board. Isn’t that right?
Yes sir.
Would they really follow me to Okinawa?
Well, if they do come, we’ll catch ‘em, and experiment on ‘em!
Hey! Sakurai-san!
We will be taking off momentarily.
Well then.
Sir, the seat-belt sign is still-
Huh? Where’s Sakurai-san?
Excuse me, sir-
What’s going on?
Satou!
Oh, hello. So you were in the bathroom?
Bon voyage.
So... I can create more IBMs than Satou and the others.
I might be able to factor that into the plan.
How long have you been an Ajin?
Nagai.
Freeze!
Are you okay?
Hey, Nagai!
Aren’t you acting a little strange?
They were just teaching me how to shoot!
You’re the one who’s strange!
Stop acting like those suits are your friends.
Eh?
One of their skills is that they're capable of dying. It's something our side has that Satou's doesn’t.
We may be able to use them as pawns
we can sacrifice as part of our plan.
Watch your mouth! Are you telling me you've
never had anyone important to you in your life?
I haven't.
Then what about that person they talked about on the news?
That friend of yours they said helped you escape?
I’m fine.
I’m on my way!
We’re okay right now.
We’re friends, right?
Kei. You’re human.
I don’t need him. Not anymore.
Spare emotions just make bad situations worse.
Clinging to them won't get you out of trouble.
Honestly, I’ve known it for a long time now.
Let your heart guide you and your body will crumble.
Scum.
Idiot.
Have you seen Nagai and Nakano?
After me.
I repeat.
Today at 3:25 p.m., flight TA16 from Haneda to Naha experienced problems,
and made an emergency landing in the ocean off of Shizuoka Prefecture.
According to our sources, we have information that Mr. Kazuo Sakurai,
who is on Satou’s assassination list, was on the plane.
Police are considering the possibility of Satou's involvement, and are investi-
That’s why I told him to cancel his business trip.
That means-
Yes. This is Satou’s work. No doubt about it.
Idiot.
I don’t need him... anymore.
Keep talking.
Don’t cut down that tree.
Hey!
How annoying.
Kill!
Okay!
Idiot! Stop it!
You!
You’re the one who’s strange.
I’ve known that for a long time.
I should have killed you when I had the chance!
I should have killed you when I had the chance! I should have killed you when I had the chance!
Idiot. Idiot. Idiot. Idiot. Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!!
Shut up.
Everyone around here... is an idiot!
Next episode
I’m always scared.