Man has four beginnings.
Benevolence, honesty, courtesy, and wisdom.
With sincerity, you have the five Confucian virtues.
We protect these virtues.
We are the blades who lead the way to coexistence.
So this'll be my new stomping ground.
Hope I can spend my time here peacefully for once.
I see you're all here.
Onigawara Rin
Oui, you are the last to join us?
Kikakujo Mary
Sooo, something weird?
Tamaba Satori
Aye, there's a face we don't see often.
Warabi Hanasaka
Someone in need of punishment? I'm disappointed.
Is that all you've gathered us here for?
Inaba Tsukuyo
No.
I have called this meeting of the Supreme Five Swords
to discuss one matter of importance.
Supreme Five Swords
An enemy has entered our grounds. In other words,
we must discuss how we will deal
with this transfer student.
Armed Girls
The hell is this place?!
All the girls're armed to the teeth!
He's basically the same as all the others.
He was expelled from his previous school
after causing a brawl.
But his was on a much larger scale than usual.
Suspicious Individual
More than forty people were seriously injured.
There's no information on
what weapons he is skilled with,
but without a doubt, he is trained
in some kind of martial art.
However, I heard that he was
the worst injured of all the victims,
and was only recently released from the hospital.
If he did all that with his bare hands,
that'd make him quite a threat.
But regardless, he's not our enemy, right?
Hey, Warabi-chan! Lemme pet him again!
Step back! Your ways of loving animals
is much too self-serving!
Aww...
Hey! Pay attention to me!
Huh? I'm listening.
His name's, uh... Nohmura?
Nomura
It's Nomura.
Say it with the accent on the first syllable.
He'll love it.
Kirukiru Amou
Hey, you!
A cross-dressing dude?!
This isn't crossdressing! It's makeup!
In any case, you must be new here.
What's that look for?
Nah, just never knew this school
had its own giant Buddha statue.
We do have one, in the auditorium, gosh!
One that looks a lot better than this, okay?!
Right then, Mister Buddha.
It's Masukodera!
There a lotta piggies like you runnin' around here?
That nickname's even worse!
Masukodera! Masukodera Kusuo!
Alright then, Masuko!
All the guys here are like this.
Are you kidding me?!
I'm not.
Huh, weird school,
but as long as I'm free to do what I want,
couldn't bother me.
Free to do what you want, huh.
Well, if you do what the rest of us are doing,
then you'll be granted the smallest bit of freedom here.
What's that supposed to mean?
And I'm not into dressin' up like that.
In either case, you'd better keep your head down.
C'mon, now.
I'm a guy who loves freedom and quiet
more than anything.
I'm done with all that crap.
My. It's a rare occasion for you to be
gracing us with your presence, Empress.
What do you want?
What? I heard the name of an interesting man
being brought up, so I came to warn you.
Could you please refrain from
acting as if you are above us?
I'd rather die than feel this level of disgust.
From what she's saying, it sounds like
she's fought with this Nomura before.
That's correct.
Huh...
so you're gonna do it then, Kirukiru-chan?
No. That man will be joining my class.
I will be the one to do it.
I'll correct him,
and his holier-than-thou attitude!
Well, be careful of his "magic bullets".
Move out!
This'll be an entertaining homeroom.
Thanks, I'm out!
Excuse me, could you wait just a few more moments?
Nah, don't worry about it,
I'm just gonna get there a little early.
Wh-what?
Th-the hell is goin' on here?!
Episode 1
The Magnificent Blade, Onigawara Rin
I am Onigawara Rin, one of the Supreme Five Swords,
and I am here to correct your behavior!
Hold up, hold up!
What? Why's this happening all of a sudden?
Correct me?
Like my teeth? Little late for that.
Seems you're not aware of your place in this school.
How the hell am I supposed to know?
I've got no idea why you all got weapons,
or why the guys're wearin' makeup,
or what these Supreme Five swords are!
Wait, you seriously don't know anything?!
The Supreme Five Swords are the five girls
led by Rin who control the school!
Aichi Coexistence Private Academy
used to be an all-girls school!
But when it became a co-ed school,
the girls were scared of the boys,
so they started arming them like a vigilante group.
That custom has continued ever since,
and five of those girls were
given permission to carry swords.
Their actions and successes led to the school becoming
a place where delinquents were sent for reform.
Long story short, problem students
that couldn't coexist in other schools
are brought here to be corrected
in the name of coexistence!
Coexistence
Correct
That is why the Supreme Five Swords
stand atop all the armed girls here!
Get it?
It is standard for the Five Swords
to correct a transfer student like you.
It's nothing surprising.
Do you finally get what I was saying this morning?
There's only one way to survive here.
Throw away your dignity as a man
and live as a woman.
Just like the rest of us "girls."
I get it.
They gave away their upper and lower fangs.
Seems like even an idiot like you
can understand the situation.
Hold up, hold up.
I get it, sure, but look, I'm unarmed.
You're sayin' you're still gonna come at me
with a bunch of weapons?
Don't worry, I'm the only one who will be correcting you.
Or are you trying to say that you would have been
able to take all of us if you were armed?
Well, be careful of his "magic bullets".
If you would like a weapon,
I will have one procured for you.
Fine, get me a megaphone.
I'll shout for help real loud.
Guess this is what they mean by
a dog whose bark is worse than its bite.
Go ahead, insult me all you want.
To think I'd worried what he would be like...
what a waste of my time.
I don't feel like fighting someone
who has no intention of baring his teeth.
You have two options:
coexist with the rest of us, or leave this school.
Pick one.
I've already got my answer for you.
Looks like everything will end quietly,
without any bloodshed.
Hell no.
I'm free to do what I want, right?
So I'm sayin' no to both.
You do know what this means, right?
I'm a Japanese guy who knows how to say "no".
So you have no intention of coexisting. Well, then...
It'd be easy to get outta here, but that'd be boring.
And I won't get a chance to get in
if I miss out on this, right?
We're all here, might as well have some fun.
So you finally show your fangs.
But how exactly will you choose both options?
Dunno.
Because you cannot!
Before homeroom is over.
Before the bell rings, I, Onigawara Rin
will correct your behavior!
Okay, then...
'Scuse me.
Was that glance to fake us out?!
Stop right there!
Where the hell are you going?!
I'm free to go, aren't I?
I'll be back by the next bell.
So you plan on literally running out the clock, huh?!
That's right.
Purple!
Hey!
So fancy.
See you later!
I think I finally understand why you ended up here.
C'mon, now.
I'm a guy who loves freedom and quiet
more than anything.
He loves it way too much.
But you can't have both freedom
and quiet at the same time.
That rings especially true for us girls here.
Hold it right there!
She's chasing me?!
How far are you going to make me chase you?
Is it against school rules to leave the school grounds?
Men of the academy must request permission
from the Five Swords to leave the grounds!
Are you frickin' kidding me?!
Mozunono.
Could you open the window for me?
Yes, it is a bit hot!
I hope we get a good breeze coming through!
Oh, I don't want a breeze, I want to hear.
Huh?
Hey! That's mean! I just bought that!
I don't care!
Rin Onee-sama is fighting!
Hey! We're still in homeroom!
That doesn't matter!
What a pain.
I'll just knock you off-balance!
Horizontal Strike
That was close! I almost lost my damn head!
You've got good eyes.
And you've got a strong, limber lower half.
Your legs are not to be underestimated.
Gosh, thanks, you're makin' me blush.
While I'm sure you have natural talent as well,
it's clear you've done your training.
Training, huh...
Well, why don't we stop fightin'
so we can talk about how great we are?
The fact that you're swingin' around that sword
with those tiny arms like it's nothin' is pretty charming.
I like a girl who's got muscle on her.
Too much muscle will hinder
your ability to breathe properly.
That is the way of the
Kashima Shinden Jikishinkage school,
Mirrored Breathing!
Mirrored Breathing
Jikishinkage school, huh...
I see.
Onigawara is going all out.
Mirrored Breathing...
If a foreign object gets into the lungs, you will cough.
The body will use all of its muscles
to force the invading object out.
Onigawara makes use of that reaction.
With each breath, she focuses her will
to strengthen her immobilized core,
and by controlling it, she can draw forth power
surpassing her physical abilities.
Syncing the timing of her breathing and movements
leaves no openings in her attacks.
No normal man could stand a chance
against Onigawara.
That guy's not half bad.
Dragon's Tail
Jeez, ya really got me here!
Your frank honesty stands in contrast
to your shallow act.
I can see you're an earnest man.
Were you not, you wouldn't have
attained this much power.
And that really makes me mad!
Blur
Give me your head!
Chest Strike
Are you going for my head or my nipples?
You're a man, you don't need them.
I need 'em for nipple wrestling at New Year's!
I'm the champ!
Then you'll give up your title this year!
I don't think so!
What?!
Crane Stance
What a pain.
I went to take out her leg in front,
but she jumped into that stance immediately after...
Kashima Shinden Jikishinkage school,
Hidden Technique.
Carpenter's Square!
Carpenter's Square
Your ability to see movement
has become your weakness.
You fell for my technique because
your rash judgment of distance was accurate.
An eight-SUN sword, huh!
So you do have some knowledge of swordsmanship.
You're pretty strong.
Guess I'll bring out my secret weapon, too.
Blade-resistant gauntlets, huh?
Onihime's attacks can shatter bone
just by the shock of impact.
To avoid that, he's parrying her attacks
with the back of his hand
and trying to push her off with his palms.
How very amusing!
Hanasaka?
I've never heard such a weird response
to roll call before...
The fight's becoming a stalemate.
If she doesn't finish this quick,
Kirukiru is going to give us that cocky grin again!
222 seconds until homeroom is over.
I've got the advantage!
Outer Rotation
Hidden Technique
Cycle
She has to step back to keep breathing!
That's her weakness!
I know that's what you're waiting for!
I'll take you down before that happens!
My hands can't hold out much longer!
What's wrong?
Did you fall forward because your posture wasn't right?
In either case,
I should praise you for being able to touch me.
But it's much too unpleasant.
Do you have any last words?
Ditch the sword and put your hands up.
You might have a sword, but I've got a gun.
There's no way you can beat me.
That's a failed secret sword technique
that I made into my own special technique.
I don't have a name for it...
Whoa!
...but I guess I'd call it...
Magic bullet!
Hey! Who told you that?!
Get your hands off Rin Onee-sama!
What did you do?!
This is my fault?!
You're the one who did it!
Are you stupid?! It was an accident on my part!
Now Rin Onee-sama is-
F-first, let's calm down!
Onee-sama, you can't!
Murder isn't allowed on school grounds!
Oh, no, she's gonna cry!
You bastard!
I remember, your name was...
Oh, yeah, I hadn't introduced myself!
Nomura Fudo.
The accent's on the "No".
Nomura.
I swear to you...
I, Onigawara Rin...
Oh, she's trying real hard to say her catchphrase!
...will castrate you!
Don't you mean "correct"?!
This is pretty different from the freedom and quiet
I wanted in the beginning!
You must request permission from the Five Swords
to leave the school grounds!
For now, I've gotta get permission from
Stop running, you bastard!
the Five Swords to leave the grounds!
How much longer are you gonna run from me?!
For now, I've gotta get permission from
the Five Swords to leave the grounds!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
The sword techniques Onigawara Rin uses
Horizontal Strike
Dragon's Tail
are from a school called the
Kashima Shinden Jikishinkage school!
Blur
Her special technique is her method of breathing
that she calls Mirrored Breathing!
Mirrored Breathing
Breathing certainly is important!
Episode 2
The Chastity Dorm Riot
Why are you doing it like that? Are you giving birth?