How are the promotion exam
applications going?
There's one today, and one tomorrow.
Oh, this is...
The one who's traveling with Goblin Slayer...
Goblin Slayer?
Oh, that guy...
What?
Oh, nothing.
Good morning! You're awake, huh?
Yeah.
Everything okay?
There's no sign that any goblins came by.
That's not what I mean.
I'm talking about you.
You collapsed as soon as you got
home and were asleep for days.
I rested for three days.
Only three days.
You need to get proper rest.
It was just exhaustion.
Nothing to worry about.
That said, I was told that my lack of
ability to take care of myself is a problem.
From that Priestess girl?
No, another adventurer.
I see.
So you're going with more people now.
Just once so far.
That makes it sound like you
plan on going with them again.
Does it?
Yup.
I see.
Adventures and Daily Life
Take care of that thing!
I know!
Are you okay? It didn't bite you, did it?
Yeah, I'm fine.
My sword...
Huh?
I-I can't get it out!
H-Hey, time out! My sword's still stu—
Chief of justice, lord of the
sword, ward of the scale...
May your forces manifest before me!
Holy Smite!
Must be nice. Miracles from the gods can
take those things out with one blow.
Quit your complaining.
They only answer my wishes once a day...
You idiot! Run!
You weren't able to complete the quest, so...
No reward. Sorry...
Right...
Um... I think it'd be best to
wash up as soon as you can...
Right...
We'll need weapons before we do anything else.
Yeah. It's a waste to leave
that sword in the sewer.
No, I mean, we're going to need
weapons just to go retrieve it.
Do you have any money?
Well...
Then what are we going to do?
Maybe I can get someone to loan me one.
Let's try to avoid going into debt.
No, I mean, maybe I could
borrow someone's spare weapon.
From who?
Yeah, about that...
I'm going to go get the receptionist's signature.
All right.
Orcbolg?
What are you doing?
Unloading cargo.
Are you sure you should be moving
around already, Beard-cutter?
Yeah.
I heard you were asleep for three days,
but you seem to be back on your feet.
Yeah.
Sir Goblin Slayer, we had a favor
we wanted to ask... You see...
How do I put this?
What is it?
I'd like to request, um... that one item.
What item?
Scaly here wants more of that cheese.
All he's talked about the
past three days is cheese.
Will this suffice?
You can pay the guild for it.
Yes, yes, of course, Sir Goblin Slayer!
H-Hey...
Now what?
Well... you see,
we're currently surveying some ruins.
I see.
So, um... We might be asking for your help.
I'll think about it.
Yeah, you do that.
You're so difficult, long-ears.
Why don't you just ask him to join us?
Shut your mouth, dwarf!
Don't make me shoot you!
Sweet nectar!
Thank you.
And thank you.
You lost your weapon? Yeah, that sucks.
I'd like to go retrieve it,
but I don't have another weapon...
So I was hoping I could
borrow someone's spare...
I mean, I've got plenty to spare,
so I could lend you one, but...
you aren't strong enough to wield them.
Magical weapons... that aren't...
a good match for you...
would be a bad idea... right?
R-Right. Um... Sorry for bothering you.
Wait...
I'll give you... something... even better.
A candle?
This candle... will help you
find what you're looking for.
When you get close... to what you're
looking for... it gets hot.
Say... You could also...
sell it for cash... you know?
Er, right... Thank you very much.
Don't mention... it.
I just... wanted to help...
Right. Let's head off to our next adventure.
Well, I'm going to head home.
Okay.
I'd like to request some repairs.
Again?
How many times must you destroy my work?
Be more careful!
I am careful.
Damn, you don't even get sarcasm.
Also, I'd like you to procure a scroll.
Scrolls are hard to come by as it is,
and they're expensive to boot.
I'll pay whatever you want.
If some adventurer comes around
and tries to sell me one, I'll buy it,
but don't get your hopes up.
I know. That's fine.
Goblin Slayer!
I'm running into everyone today.
Look at this! See?
So you went from 10th to 9th.
Yes! I got promoted yesterday!
I was a bit nervous, but apparently
fighting an ogre really helped!
I see. Good for you.
And it's all thanks to you, Goblin Slayer.
I didn't do anything.
But you saved me the first time we met.
But the rest of your party didn't make it.
Yes, but... You still saved me.
I thought that I should at
least thank you properly.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm going to the temple to report
to Mother Superior about my promotion!
No way, no how!
I just lost my own short sword,
and I'm using a loaner myself.
If I let someone else borrow that,
the boss is gonna kill me.
You lost it? How?
A giant slug melted it. Unbelievable.
A giant slug, huh? Must be nice...
We're porcelain, and they're silver.
We're no match for them.
You were out hunting rats?
Yeah, and I lost my sword.
Man... I'm so jealous.
I want a two-handed sword...
like that great sword.
If you even tried to hold that
thing up, you'd collapse.
Not to mention...
it costs m-o-n-e-y.
Looks like he got Silent cast on him.
Hey, why not talk to the guild about it?
Talk to them? About borrowing a weapon?
No, about how to slay those rats.
Maybe they could suggest a good method.
Would it really be that easy?
Goblin Slayer!
Pardon me...
Yes?
How to slay giant rats...
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
I mean, we're asking
adventurers for help because
they're difficult to deal with...
Isn't there anything you can do?
Anything would be great! Please!
This is pretty simple, but why not boost your
defense with chain mail or something?
We don't have any money.
In that case, it's probably best to ask for help
with adventures from another adventurer.
G-Goblin Slayer?
What's wrong?
Oh, um, it's just...
Um... We were kind of rude to him before.
Oh, don't worry. That sort
of thing doesn't bother him.
You think so?
Yes, I guarantee it.
Um...
What?
Th-There's something we wanted to ask.
When you lose your sword,
what's the best way to fight enemies?
Steal one from a goblin.
But we're not fighting goblins.
I see.
Have you ever used any
weapon other than a sword?
No...
Also, we have no money.
In that case, how about a club?
A club?
Yeah. Throw, stab, break, and shatter.
Even using a sword properly, you couldn't
cut five goblins with one sword.
What about rats or bugs?
I couldn't say. I'm sure if you swung one
around and it hit them, it'd at least hurt.
If nothing else, it wouldn't get nicked
like a sword, so it's easier to use.
Easier...
A club, huh?
Yeah, a club.
The observer can't come?
They apparently got hurt in a quest
yesterday. Do you have anyone else?
Um... In that case...
Goblin Slayer!
Goblins?
No, no goblins—
Wait, please don't leave!
But there are no goblins, right?
Er, um... Yes, that's correct, but...
Does it absolutely have
to... involve... goblins?
Keep it short.
I will! You see, there was a mix-up...
so I'd like you to act as an observer.
An observer? For a promotion exam?
This candle's supposed to react when
I think about the sword, right?
Well?
I think it feels warmer over here.
So my sword's over there?
There they are.
Why, you—
Die! Die! Die!
Where's the other one?
It ran away.
So what do you think of the club?
I'm not sure, but they do die when
I hit them really hard with it.
It suits you much better than a sword.
Oh, shut up.
All right, let's begin the promotion exam.
Bring it on!
Let's just skip sapphire and
emerald and go straight to ruby...
no, bronze, even!
No, that's not how this works.
Your leather armor and boots...
Those are new, right?
Oh, you can tell?
They're excellent quality.
I had them matted. They're a perfect fit for me.
How is it that you seem to be
doing so well for yourself
when the same quests are
available to everyone?
Oh, uh... Well, that's, uh...
I actually had my family send me some money.
That's a lie.
Huh?
I swear on the name of the Supreme
God that what he just said was a lie.
Sense Lie! The ability to see through lies!
Damn it! Curse these seekers!
It appears that you acquired some new gear
in the raid at those ruins the other day.
Oh, I get it!
You told the others that you were going
to scout, found a treasure chest,
kept it for yourself, and sold the contents!
N-N-No, I-I would never...
I-I'm sorry!
This is truly a problem.
It's because of guys like you that
so many people have prejudiced views
against other rheas and scouts.
But since it's your first offense,
just demoting you to porcelain and
banning you from adventuring
in this town will suffice.
H-Hang on a second! That's messed up!
I'm getting kicked out just because
I kept a treasure chest to myself?!
Huh?
"Just"? Are you stupid?
Those who betray other people's trust
don't deserve to be adventurers.
You are hereby demoted on the
grounds of falsifying a reward,
though you may stick around if you'd like.
Don't get any silly ideas.
C-Come on, Goblin Slayer!
You're a fellow adventurer of this town!
What? I'm just an observer.
Nothing more and nothing less.
But you're an adventurer...
I am, but you also tricked other adventurers.
D-Damn it!
You'll regret this!
I think not.
It's hot!
What's wrong?
This thing's getting hotter and hotter.
That means my sword's getting closer.
Watch out!
Hey, what are you doing?
This way!
How's the candle?
It's really hot!
Don't tell me...
It's inside that thing?!
What should we do?
Go back to the surface?
They'll catch up to us
while we climb the ladder!
Should we jump into the water?
Do you want to get the black plague?!
In that case...
Use a miracle!
What are you—
Just hurry!
Now!
Chief of justice, lord of the
sword, ward of the scale...
May your forces manifest before me!
Holy Smite!
I-Is it still alive?
S-Stay back. It's dangerous.
I'm sure my sword doesn't taste good.
So just... give it back already!
That was so scary...
Thank you so much, Goblin Slayer.
I didn't do anything.
That's not true.
When I was going through the training
courses at the capital, it was awful.
All those creeps who couldn't open their
mouths without making lewd remarks...
And the ones who wanted to hit on me...
There are so many of those in the capital.
I'd have to deal with people
like that on my own, so...
I feel so much more relaxed just having
someone I trust acting as an observer.
Really?
Yes, absolutely!
If we're done here, I'm leaving.
O-Oh, sure. If you go to the front desk,
they should give you your compensation...
All right.
U-Um!
What?
Uh, um... Good work today.
Yeah, you, too.
Good work.
That rhea's probably going
to try something again.
But surviving adventurers are rare these days.
What he did wasn't clearly illegal...
It'd be worse if he gave up
on being an adventurer
and became an actual troublemaker.
Well, the adventurers run the gamut
from Lawful Good to Chaotic Evil.
As long as they're adventurers,
they're allowed to make that choice.
Thank you for everything.
It was nothing. It's my job as a priest for
the Supreme God, so it's no problem at all.
And from the perspective of the God of
Law, how do you think I handled that?
Most people seem to misunderstand
the God of Justice.
You see that all the time in plays.
Justice is not about striking down evil,
but making people aware that
evil exists in the world.
That's a lovely way of thinking.
If you can put it into practice.
I'm still nowhere near the
Sword Maiden, not even close.
She was one of the adventurers
that defeated the Demon Lord.
The Sword Maiden, a servant of
the all-powerful Supreme God.
I admire her so much.
Well, all I have to do is see
through lies, so I have it easy.
You still have work, right?
I have to get started on the
paperwork to demote him...
So... that other guy's the one you like?
Huh? U-Um...
Y-Yeah, so what?
You always had a soft spot for strait-laced
people, even back at the capital.
To the brave adventurer who
got his sword back on his own!
Cheers!
I mean, I wondered if there were
more stoic adventurers around...
But maybe he's a bit too stoic...
I'm glad you seem happy.
So, don't you have work to do?
Yeah, I need to stop thinking about
silly things and get to work.
Hey.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What is it, Goblin Slayer?
What else? I'm going to slay some goblins.
That quest listing...
It's a special one that arrived on
a parcel carriage from far away.
It's specifically asking for Goblin Slayer?
Who could it be from?
Next Time
Goblin Slayer in the Water Town