You're nothing to me.
You suck at games.
It's not like I enjoyed spending time with you...
Keep up the good work at the game club.
I'm rooting for you.
Sure, you're right.
What the hell is this?
What was that?
Wasn't Tendou-san just crying?
Is it relationship drama of some kind?
Weren't they talking about a club, though?
If you're curious, why don't you ask Amano
what they were talking about?
Me?
Don't bother.
There's no way we could hold
a conversation with that guy.
That's true.
Just what is your deal?
Isn't it kind of frustrating, though?
Huh?
Er, well, not for any particular reason,
but he seems kind of stuck-up.
He does seem a bit high-and-mighty.
He deserves almost nothing,
and yet he's condescending.
He really should learn his place.
I know, right?
Lame.
No, I mean, his life seems lame.
Oh, that's what you meant.
You scared me. I thought you'd snapped.
No, I didn't.
In regards to auxiliary verbs,
it's important to understand
how conjunctions are used.
In other words, what
precedes the auxiliary verb?
Damn him.
Tasuku!
Let's eat together!
Time to charge up on Tasuku-power!
You sure do like Uehara.
I made lunch today.
Ta-da!
It's a cute kitty.
It's all squished together!
Hey, hey, that Amano-whatshisface
is in your class, right?
Yeah.
Everyone was talking about him in Class C.
Something about the Tendou-san being rejected.
Oh, yeah?
You're not surprised?
Are you two really even dating?
You think so?
I think it's pretty normal.
I just never had a reason to refuse.
It doesn't matter, as long as I love Tasuku.
Sure.
Really? You're happy with that?
I don't care. I'm happy
as long as we're together.
Do you think we'll all fit?
I don't have money. Masaya, can you take it?
It's on me again?
Tasuku?
I think you already have too many people.
Come on, join us.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Retro Games
Quit staring.
Yes!
Damn it.
When am I going to stop having these visions?
Wait, it's you!
Um...
I'm Amano.
I'm in your class.
I know.
So? What do you want?
U-Um, do you like games, Uehara-kun?
I haven't really thought about it.
This game...
Let's see!
I've never played it,
but it's famous, isn't it?
Paradigm of Phantasia.
This one's a masterpiece!
You should definitely play
it if you haven't yet.
Y-Yeah?
Yeah.
They pitched the game as revolutionizing
the concept of gaming,
but it turned out to be extremely orthodox,
so it was blasted at the time,
but it's really polished.
I recommend it wholeheartedly.
Er, I don't need your recommendations.
Sorry, I got a bit passionate.
You don't need to apologize.
O-Okay, I'll be going now.
Video Games
What the heck is he doing?
Don't tell me he doesn't come to arcades,
even though he likes gaming.
Hold up.
U-Uehara-kun?
Come with me for a bit.
I have no interest in men!
Spare me the clichés, would you?
Well?
Are we playing or not?
Please! I'd be happy to!
Is this the one you wanted to play?
Yeah.
I've always liked this game,
and I've been wanting to play.
Yeah?
I was here before, too,
but I felt bad wasting time watching
the demo videos and stuff.
So you just went home without doing anything?
I guess so.
How passive can you get?
I can't believe this is the kid
who straight-up rejected Tendou.
Amano, what's your relationship with Tendou?
Oh-Oh, yeah... You saw that, huh?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
Well, actually...
Holy crap, that's hilarious!
That's way too much.
Come back, Tasuku, or I'm going home.
Who's she?
The game club, huh?
I never knew there was such a club.
Yeah.
What I don't get is,
how were the games in game club different
from the games that you want to play?
Um... I don't know. It's hard to explain.
You wanted friends you could
talk about games with, right?
Y-Yeah, but...
Get a grip.
It's open, Uehara-kun.
Don't you want to take time
to watch the videos?
I'm good. Let's play!
Okay.
I'll mesmerize you with my skills.
Okay. Go easy on me, please.
He's throwing me off.
Amano's playing the main character, huh?
Uehara-kun, have you played this game before?
No, I just chose the one that looked cool.
Oh, really?
No surprise, he's better than Aguri.
She just mashes the controls.
Go, go, go!
Players like Amano are easier
to get a read on, though.
I mean...
Tries all the moves
Makes an approach with unnecessary jumps
Uses only heavy attacks
Always forgets to do throws
Inevitably gets thrown
Remembers that you can throw
Tries to get behind to throw, and gets beaten up
Becomes dependent on projectiles
Goes for a last-ditch special attack
when he's low on health
Misses
Loses unceremoniously
You're so good, Uehara-kun.
You just suck.
I'm winning this time.
Already?!
Wait... Wait, wait, wait!
It's just a fighting game. I don't know
why he's having so much fun.
You got me again!
You're way too bad at this.
Even elementary school kids are trickier.
That was really fun, Uehara-kun!
Sure.
So what should we play next?
It's no fun if I just keep winning, is it?
Y-Yeah, you're right!
Oh, then let's play that one next!
What should we play next?
You're planning to play all the games
you couldn't play alone, aren't you?
Th-That's not true.
All right, what should we play next?
Jeez.
Come to think of it,
this has happened before...
What was it?
What is she doing?
Hey, Amano.
Uehara-kun...
I totally forgot.
Thanks for today.
S-See you.
H-Hey!
Tasuku!
A-Amano-kun!
I haven't given up yet...
There you are.
I've been calling you this whole time!
Where were you?
Huh?
Oh, sorry, I didn't notice.
That's awful, Uehara.
Wait, Masaya, didn't you have work?
Crap! I forgot!
You're hopeless.
Sorry, I have to be somewhere.
I'll be right back.
Wait, Tasuku!
Damn it!
What am I doing?
There he is.
Amano!
H-Huh?
What's wrong, Uehara-kun?
Why did you run away?
What? I wasn't running away.
You were!
I wasn't running away.
But, I mean, why would you want me around?
You have a life, after all.
Seriously, the more I look at this kid...
What are you—
Screw that!
Who do you think you are?
What the hell do you mean, I "have a life"?
Don't you dare try to
sum people up like that!
If it looks like I'm content,
it's because I make an effort!
It's because I busted my ass to
stop being a geek in high school!
Don't you dare give me that
patronizing "you have a life" bull!
I'm not patronizing...
I bet you think your time's way better
spent gaming by yourself, don't you?
You just want to have fun playing?
That's some salty excuse.
"A different perspective," my ass.
You think you're so cool?
Like hell you are!
Why are you even getting so serious
over video games? It's stupid!
Then again, I think Tendou's
game club is stupid, too.
Why don't you say something?
Take it back.
Take back what you just said!
Sure, I'm just a slacker with
no interests other than gaming!
I knew that from the beginning!
I'm sorry!
You're so right about me thinking I'm cool for
Dude, calm down...
sticking to my position
on gaming that it hurts!
Yeah, I'm a pest, aren't I?
I'm crazy, right?
N-No, no, I never said that!
I'll even admit that games are stupid,
for the sake of argument!
But that doesn't give you the right to insult
someone you barely know for being
H-He's going to kill me!
engaged in something, even if it's
something as stupid as gaming!
You don't get to insult me!
Tendou-san really is a good person.
She's kind, she takes action,
and she invited me, of all people,
into the game club, twice.
So I want you to take back your
insulting remarks about Tendou-san
and the game club!
All right, just calm down!
Calm down, all right?
I-I'm sorry!
What the hell?
It was stupid to compare him
to myself and get all pissed.
I feel bad.
Sorry.
N-No...
But, man, I never thought the
same guy who turned down
a direct invitation from Tendou would
defend the game club so passionately.
Th-That's, um...
All right, I'm heading back to the arcade.
What about you?
I'll go home for today.
There's a game I want to play at home, too.
Yeah?
All right. Later.
Yeah.
Sorry I talked down to you
about having a life.
Forget about it.
My past self has got nothing on him.
I've just witnessed something insane.
Our school idol... Oh, dear.
Prologue to Tendou Karen's Breakdown
The End
Yo, Tendou.
What do you want of the Tendou Karen?
Konk
Okay, got it.
I wish you well.
Wait up!
What do you mean? You "got" what?
You wish me well how?
I...
think you and Amano look cute together.
Later.
To think the cutest girl at school
would fall so madly in love...
I'm going to egg those two on like hell.
It'll be a good way to harass Amano.
I forgot.
Hey, get this one for me!
Give me a break.
How much money do you
think I've spent already?
I knew it!
You won plushies for
someone else, didn't you?
No, I was just playing video
games with another guy.
Gaming with someone besides me, huh?
Good for you, Tasuku-san, you cheater!
We've been dating for the past half-year,
but all we've really done
is hang out after school.
Why am I even dating her?
So, Aguri, what was it you liked about me
that made you want to confess to me?
Huh?
Haven't I told you?
I bet she just liked my face or something.
That's because you were awesome, of course.
See?
Back in middle school,
when you got me a plushie.
What are you doing?
Middle school?
Me and you?
Yeah.
I could tell you were having a lot of
fun when you were playing here,
every now and then.
I've been in love with you ever since.
Middle school?
Back in my dark ages?
That's right, I remember now.
I came here sometimes to distract
myself, and I just happened to...
Just happened to...
So when I found out we were going to the same
high school, I was like, "It's my chance!"
Otobuki High School
Entrance Ceremony
But you'd turned into a real hottie.
I heard you liked girly girls,
so I worked really hard.
What's wrong?
I-I'm done for the day.
Aw, let's walk home together.
You live nearby!
Bye!
Wait, Tasuku!
What the hell?
What the hell?!
Why am I feeling for Aguri now?
She's had her eye on me since middle school?
When I was such a loser?
Was she ever that cute?
Why does she look so cute all of a sudden?
Why?!
Be Passionate
Morning.
Yo.
Hey, Amano.
Morning, Uehara-kun.
You were right. It was fun.
Paradigm of Phantasia.
Let me know whenever you
find more good games.
Sure, I will!
Tasuku, were you that close
with Amano before?
I guess.
You're in a good mood.
Did something good happen?
I've been having a blast
with video games lately.
Some Days Later
I wonder what's wrong with Tendou-san...
Huh? Amano-kun?
What's up?
Are you here to see Tendou-san?
I'm here to meet another girl
today, not Tendou-san.