Just as expected
of the Anti-Ajin Special Forces.
It’s not just a name.
Now...
time for the last stage.
It’s your fault
that my quiet life is all messed up!
Nagai-kun, I-
hate people who get in the way of my
games more than anything else!
Even though he’s unconscious...
How is the ghost still moving?
If you want a quiet life,
I’ll grant that wish-
Ghost!
Come out!!
Nagai...
it’s okay!
Come out!!!
-forever, in the darkness.
You guys take the stairs!
Bring them under control!
The EMP got rid of the electronic lock,
but we still haven’t gotten the analog key.
S- Satou-san?
We still didn't get his confession!
What will really prove our power
is coming next.
We’ve captured Nagai Kei and Nakano Kou.
This will save a little face
for the Committee.
Let’s go.
Continuing
our report from the scene.
According to those involved in the panic
caused by the ajin Satou
President Hashiguchi of
Musashi Heavy Industries has been killed
and there have been heavy casualties among the
Anti-Ajin Special Forces and riot police.
Meanwhile,
still no trace has been found as to how Satou escaped,
and police are increasing efforts all around to try and determine his whereabouts,
but due to the effects of the simultaneous attacks, a state of chaos has forces...
You guys look like you’ve been to a funeral.
What happened on the inside?
Why did you let Satou go?
Hey, Tosaki-san!
How could you let things end
up in this sorry state?
With your IBM, you should have been
able to take down Satou!
Am I wrong?
Say something!
Please calm down, Tosaki-san!
To put all the blame on Nagai...
it’s unfair.
It’s just as Suzumura-san says.
It’s not only Nagai’s fault!
No...
It’s my fault.
That Satou-san couldn’t be stopped...
That Hirasawa-san and the others were killed...
It’s all my fault.
Is that all?
Hey, Nagai!
We were live at the scene.
The police are also investigating
the whereabouts of Tosaki Yuu
and Shimomura Izumi, members of the
Ajin Management Committee.
The suspects are-
Tosaki-san.
Of course they are.
What are you going to do, Tosaki-san?
You’re as big an idiot as ever.
There’s nothing left to be done.
It’s over.
All of it.
No,
the biggest idiot is me.
To join forces with ajin...
this is the result.
My salary all went down the drain.
And now I’m a real criminal!
How is it?
The feeling that others are
dying because of you.
Please! Ghost!
Come out!!!
You're sure there's been no mistake?
I’m sure.
They’ve all been taken by Satou.
Get ahold of the Prime Minister immediately.
Prime Minister.
If word of this gets out,
all of Japan will be thrown into a panic!
They’re that dangerous?
If they use everything they’ve taken,
they could kill the entire population of
Japan three times over.
Prime Minister.
Perhaps we should assume the worst,
and prepare a compromise?
Understood.
Continue the search for Satou,
and begin preparations here.
Yes sir.
As you can see, the countdown has been completed.
In the end, the government gave us no response.
It’s truly unfortunate,
but as I’ve said previously,
our advance cannot be stopped.
Which means,
within the next ten days, the third wave-
we will begin the final battle.
We’ve come this far,
but to those of you who still think
you’re not involved...
well, there’s nowhere to run.
[TV announcer] What you are currently seeing is a is a new video taking
responsibility for today’s attacks that Satou
has uploaded to ajin.net.
How far are you planning to take this?
You’re really messing things up.
Here it comes!
Unlike lives, those can’t be replaced.
Satou-san is just playing around!
He’s not thinking at all about
the future of ajin!
What are you doing?
Stop spacing out.
Were you thinking about what to eat?
No, I wasn’t.
Hey,
Tanaka-san.
You know....
Is Satou really thinking about our-
About ajin-
I thought I told you.
All we can do is trust Satou.
Even so,
however it goes, this is the last battle.
Isn’t that right,
Tanaka-san?
Yeah.
This will be... the last.
With this.
I hope you’re right.
I got the blueprints you asked for.
All that's left is to get data on
the drainage systems,
so I can finish that today.
Thank you for your work, I'm sorry you had to be responsible for everything.
Very good.
How are things over there?
I think it'll be done in time.
As expected of you, Okuyama-kun.
Ah, this will make things fun again.
This is the last operation, right?
It depends on the other side’s reaction.
How come?
Ah-
no particular reason.
Is that right?
But don’t worry.
This time, I intend to genuinely
negotiate with the government.
That’s why we picked up ‘that’ from
Musashi Heavy Industries.
Ah.
I see.
But that’s right.
We can’t keep playing at war forever.
That’s how it is.
Ah.
Then,
I’ll get back to work.
Results of the investigation.
Suspicions have arisen that Professor Ogura
was kidnapped by the ajin Satou.
On that note,
I’ll confirm the security of the safe house
was suddenly attacked by Satou,
and report back again.
In summary, this is more or less what happened.
And following this last email,
Douglas Almeida and Carly Meyers disappeared,
and currently their whereabouts are unknown.
When we questioned the security at the safe house,
they said they were attacked by a unit of a few people, including ajin.
We also have reports that after that,
a car chase took place in the
vicinity of the safe house.
Given the circumstances,
we can only conclude that Satou erased them.
Which means that,
as we thought, Satou has Professor Ogura captive.
Shall we ask the Japanese government to intervene?
It’s no use.
I don’t think they can handle Satou.
Having said that,
sending another team might result
in the same failure.
Then...
We can afford to wait for Satou’s
next terrorist attack.
As we'd hoped,
this might require a military intervention.
I see.
If that’s how it turns out,
we can even legally secure the ajin in Japan.
(they want to steal the ajins)
Exactly.
I’ll send the report to the Secretary of Defense.
What’s that?
The weather’s nice today, too.
We broke through the front without even resorting to tricks!
This will be the best show.
We have an emergency!
Terrorists armed with guns have invaded!
They set fire to the ammunition dump!
Unit on duty, head to point 4!
Confirmed that the terrorists are using automatic
weapons and rocket launchers.
Other units, arm yourselves and move out!
Take positions quickly!
This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
We can’t use the vehicles?
The bullets are with the munitions!
Who are these guys?
They came prepared!
Just take them down!
You...
can’t stop us!
Go, go, go!
Shit,
kill them!
Stop them!
What?
The ammunitions dump and armory have fallen.
We have reports that the enemy are ajin!
What did you say?
Shit.
The backup unit still isn’t ready?
They’re on their way,
but it will take time before they arrive!
Hurry them up!
What you are seeing
is the draft of the compromise with Satou,
prepared by the Ajin Management Committee.
Prime Minister. It’s an emergency.
[background- I’d like to hear your opinions.]
A Ground Self-Defense Force base is under attack by Satou.
[background- I hope to have things finalized
by tonight. What do you think?]
What did you say?
It’s Tanaka.
We’ve taken control here.
Roger!
Then go ahead and transport our objective..
We’ll be done soon here, too.
Understood!
Wait, Satou-san!
There’s no way we can end this quickly!
Don’t let them come any closer!
What about the others?
Hold out here until backup arrives!
Shit!
Aim carefully!
They’re terrorists, after all!
Keep killing them!
W- What was that?
That ended pretty quickly, didn’t it?
Uh, yeah!
Well then,
then let’s finish taking control!
You got it!
Whew!
I mean, that took even less time than I expected.
The Self-Defense Force is bound by law,
so there's a limit to what weapons they can use.
It was a good plan to take out the
ammunitions dump and armory first.
Nagai!
This is...
Satou-san’s video...
Got it?
We have to be prepared to support the backup unit.
Whatever we do, we have to hold out here!
Yes
Don’t move!
I know things were hard for you all,
but it was kind of Easy Mode, wasn't it?
Prime Minister.
It seems the head of the base has passed away.
You can’t be serious.
What’s going on?
They’re pinpointing the important
facilities, and taking control.
Damage continues to mount as the
fighting continues at the scene.
In order to reorganize the units,
they’re under retreat for the time being.
We’re just letting them do as they wish?
We won’t allow that.
Backup forces are already spreading out
around the outside of the base.
We can’t fight back immediately?
There are also chemical weapons.
Please allow us to handle them with caution.
Satou-san.
It’s all set.
Okuyama-kun,
you really are good with machines.
It’s no big deal.
It’s a standard device.
They seem pretty impressive, but
can we use them effectively?
They’re a new model with a lot
of military capabilities.
Did you just imitate Okuyama again?
Sniper squad, in position.
Roger.
The terrorists have taken hostages.
Wait to invade until we understand
the inside situation.
Satou-san.
We've finished setting up the missiles.
Very good.
Let’s restart the show!
Let’s get right to the point.
Right now, including this one, twenty missiles
filled with chemical gases are loaded
and ready to fire.
Their effectiveness should be well-known.
These lethal weapons were developed at
Musashi Heavy Industries,
with Tanaka-kun as the guinea pig.
Now then, I’ll convey our demands.
By twelve noon one week from now, I want you to hand over Japan.
There, we will create an independent
country ruled by ajin.
Hand over Japan?
What a crazy demand.
Of course,
I understand that it’s a lot to ask.
But it seems that the government has no
intention of recognizing ajin rights,
so we have no other choice.
We are forced to show our full strength.
Yes.
With this lethal gas,
we will kill all the humans in this country!
Yes.
We have plenty of reason to
hold a council of war.
Yes.
We can’t allow him to fall into the hands
of the Japanese government.
All citizens should already know this, but...
I...
am very serious.
[Screen- End of transmission]
Suzumura.
Can I rely on you to procure weapons?
Procure weapons.
Th-  That is possible.
What for?
Isn’t it obvious?
We’re stopping Satou.
Are you serious?
We don’t have anything left-
It doesn’t matter.
Up to this point,
Satou has killed
a large number of people.
And he will without hesitation
kill many more.
I...
No.
This is no longer just my problem.
Please, Suzumura.
I follow my orders.
That’s all there is for me to do.
Hirasawa-san would have said the same thing.
Yes.
I don’t really get it,
but we’re stopping Satou.
That’s right.
Alright!
Let’s get revenge for the old guys!
Nagai?
I won’t do it.
What did you say?
To be continued...
Preview
Next time, episodes 24 and 25 will air consecutively!