I'm gonna go to the city!
I'm gonna go to my uncle's farm and
help one of the cows give birth.
I'm going all by myself, too!
And once I'm done helping,
I can go shopping in the city.
My mom gave me some money.
I wonder what I should buy.
Is there anything you want?
I'll buy you something.
No.
There must be something. I mean—
I told you, I don't want anything.
Why do you have to say it like that?
I just wanted to buy you something
since you've never been to the city...
Shut up! Just go to the city or wherever!
Why are you getting mad?
I'm not mad!
Yes, you are!
Now, now.
Sis...
You shouldn't be fighting.
We're not fighting.
Right?
Y-Yeah...
What happened?
It's nothing.
All right, then.
Please take care of her.
I will.
How long are you going to keep pouting?
Weren't you looking forward
to going to the city?
I wanted to go with him...
But since he couldn't come,
I wanted to buy him something,
and then he got really angry...
I'm sure he wanted to come, too.
Think about how he feels.
Did you two make up?
You should, once you get back.
I wanted to make up with him.
I wanted to apologize.
But saying "I'm sorry"...
is hard, even now.
Good morning!
I see you're an early riser, as always.
Yeah.
It's such a nice day today.
The sun's so bright!
Yeah.
Is my uncle already up?
I don't know.
I see. I'm pretty sure he'll be up soon, though.
I see.
You must be hungry.
I'll go get breakfast ready,
so let's eat together.
Okay.
He always checks to see if there
are any footprints at dawn.
The goblins move around at night.
They return to their nests in the morning,
but they always scout before attacking.
He told me that those are the
footprints he's looking for.
If he doesn't find any footprints,
he then carefully checks the fence to
see if any part is loose or damaged.
If any parts are broken,
he gets out some wood and a stake to fix it.
This hasn't changed since
he came here five years ago.
It's his daily routine.
Goblin Slayer
Here you go!
It smells great, as usual. Let's eat.
Let's eat!
Well? Is it good?
Yeah.
Here.
It's what I owe you for this month.
It's pretty heavy.
I guess being an adventurer
is pretty lucrative.
I've had a lot of work lately.
I see.
Say, um... Are you going again today?
Yes. I'm going to the guild.
There's plenty of work there.
I see. Don't push yourself too hard.
Yes, sir.
Hey, I need to make some deliveries.
We should go together.
Sure.
Actually, I'll ready a wagon for that.
Oh, we'll be fine!
You're too protective, Uncle!
I'm stronger than I look, you know.
Do you want me to take over?
Nope! I'm fine.
Okay.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
How are things lately?
There are more goblins.
Really?
Far more than usual.
Are you busy?
Yeah.
You do go out a lot more lately.
Having more work is a good thing, though.
No, it's bad.
Is it?
It's better when there are no goblins.
You're right.
You gotta help me out!
Li'l goblin critters done
showed up in my village!
They're gunna eat my cows an' burn my fields!
Ah, so you need an extermination.
Please submit your form and payment.
Y-Yes'm. I got 'em right here.
Looks like your form is filled out correctly.
I'll just confirm your payment now.
Two, four, eight...
All right, it looks like it's all here.
An adventurer will head out there for
the extermination within a few days.
Is it true that them li'l goblin
critters rape women and eat 'em?
There have indeed been cases like that.
Another goblin-slaying request?
That's the third one...
What's the pay?
That's going to rule out
any experienced adventurer.
Only newbies would...
There is one...
who's always willing to take care of them...
Thank you again.
No problem! Thank you.
I'm going to get a signature
at the reception desk.
All right.
So this troll was bearing down on me,
but I swung at it like this and dodged
its attack just in the nick of time.
I see. Well done, sir.
I am very aware that
trolls are powerful foes.
I faced a troll with just a single spear.
Don't you think I'm amazing?
Indeed. If you're feeling tired,
I'd recommend a stamina potion.
I'll take one.
The Goblin Slayer...
That's him?
That's the weirdo who only accepts
goblin-slaying quests, right?
He's a silver rank, just like us?
If all he hunts is weak monsters, who knows
if he can even handle bigger prey?
Guess they'll let anyone
be silver these days.
Leave him be. We'll never
have to deal with him.
Look at him. I've never
seen such filthy armor.
Even our equipment is better than his.
Stop it.
He must be a newbie just like us.
I'd feel bad if he heard you.
Good morning, everyone!
It's time to post all the
quests available this morning.
That's what we've been waiting for!
Dragons!
Is there one for dragon slaying?
I need to gain some more experience
points by doing heroic feats.
Don't even try it.
You don't have the right equipment.
Just settle for taking out some bandits.
The pay isn't bad, either.
Quests for porcelain ranks...
don't pay very much.
I don't want to just clean ditches...
You can't be too picky.
Hey, how about this one?
Goblin slaying.
That seems made for rookies.
No way. You heard the Guild Girl.
We need to start with the sewers.
I can't see! Get out of my way!
Stop it. Don't push!
We're taking this quest. Look somewhere else.
That's no way to talk to
the best on the frontier.
Come, now, everyone. You mustn't fight.
So he's really not going
to look at the quests...
I guess he did say that there's no need
to rush, since no one likes goblin-slaying.
Hello.
Hey.
A-About the other day...
I still think destroying a cave with
flammable liquid is going too far.
What's your point?
It's a far better option than
letting the goblins live.
Shouldn't you think more about consequences?
You might cause an avalanche doing that.
The goblins are a bigger problem.
Y-Yes, but...
What I'm trying to say is that
you shouldn't think that way.
I see.
Don't you understand?
He said he'd formed a party with
someone about a month ago, but...
I guess it was with a girl.
Also, couldn't we use something...
different... to cover our scent?
Do you remember what time we're attacking?
E-Either early morning or early evening...
Now, tell me why.
Because early evening for goblins
is early morning for us.
Correct. So during their afternoons,
or the middle of the night for us,
they are the most guarded.
Next. What are the steps to approach them?
Um, if possible, light a
fire and smoke them out,
because it's dangerous inside their nests.
Correct.
The only time we enter a nest is when
there's no other way, we don't have time,
or we're certain we can kill them all.
All right.
Huh?
Oh, good morning, Goblin Slayer.
Goblins. Are there any quests?
Ah, yes, goblin-slaying.
We have three quests.
One is from a river village in the west,
one is a small nest in the southern forest,
and one... I guess you could call it an old fort.
It's a mountain castle in
the mountains to the north.
They've settled there?
Yes, and there have already
been some casualties.
The younger sister of the one who
put up the request was kidnapped,
and a wandering adventurer who went
to find her hasn't come back yet.
It's too late for them, then.
But I can't let the goblins live.
If I take them out now,
there shouldn't be further casualties.
We'll be counting on you, then, Goblin Slayer.
One question. Did anyone else
take a goblin-slaying quest?
Yes, a party of rookies accepted one.
They took the request from the river village.
Rookies? What was their party like?
One warrior, one wizard, and one priest.
They're all porcelain-ranked.
Not a bad balance.
If it's the three who were in the lobby
earlier, they won't be able to handle it!
Even my party had four members...
I explained that to them, but...
We can't leave them alone!
We have to go save them!
Do as you please.
Huh?
I'm going to destroy the
mountain castle in the north.
Y-You're just going to abandon them?
If you want to go save them, you can.
But that means you'll be facing
a horde of goblins on your own!
I've done that many times.
Honestly, I can never get through to you.
Are you coming?
Yes!
I'm going.
Huh? O-Okay.
Be careful.
Be careful getting home.
He didn't come back that day.
Or the next day...
I wonder if he's still fighting.
You're going to have a hard day
tomorrow if you stay up too late.
Yeah. I'll go to bed after
I wait a little longer.
Think about how it would feel
if your home was suddenly
attacked by monsters...
Yes, if your home was suddenly
attacked by monsters one day.
They act as though they own the
place and kill your friends,
kill your family,
and plunder the rest of the village.
Another example would be if
your older sister was attacked,
tormented, made a plaything, then killed...
Let's say that you witnessed
all this, from start to finish,
in hiding as you held your breath...
There's no way you'd forgive them.
You would take up weapons and do
whatever you could to get revenge.
You would hunt them all down and attack them.
You'd kill, kill, and kill even more.
Of course, there will be days
you're successful and days you fail.
You'll try to figure out the
best way to kill them next time.
You'll think about this for days and months.
You'll test every single idea you come up with.
As you continue to do that,
you start to enjoy it.
A kind moron will suggest that
you let the children live,
with a smug face, not realizing that
these things will attack villages
and steal livestock to survive.
Young, aspiring adventurers as well as
new, porcelain-ranked adventurers
will confidently say,
"I chased away a goblin that
came to my village once!"
"They're weak." "They're easy to deal with."
The goblin that the proud youth
of the village had chased away
was no more than a goblin that had been
smoked out and was trying to escape.
This gives them confidence,
and they become adventurers.
Meanwhile, the goblins that
survived and gained experience
become Wanderers and continue to grow.
Eventually, the Wanderers become the
leaders or the bodyguards of nests.
Which means...
I am, in turn, a goblin to them.
He's one matter, but you need to remember...
I let him stay here because he pays,
but you shouldn't get involved with him.
I know you were childhood friends,
but now matter how he was in the past...
Truth is, right now...
He's completely lost it.
You realize that, too, don't you?
Still...
I'm going to wait a little longer.
That makes five.
They'll be here any minute.
R-Right!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I'd heard that you'd been
granted a new miracle.
That's six.
Thanks to that, we took care
of them pretty quickly.
T-To think that I'd be using Protection,
the new miracle the merciful Earth
Mother bestowed upon me, like this.
They might have a back door
or an alternate escape route.
Don't let down your guard.
I'm amazed you could even think of that.
Imagination is a weapon.
Those who lack it are first to die.
Like the ones who dove in before?
Precisely.
Great Earth Mother,
why did you bestow this miracle upon me?
Now we don't have to put out the fire.
Once it goes out,
we're going to hunt down
any survivors and kill them.
I won't let a single one survive.
People may call you a specialist
who only hunts weaklings,
but you are doing something
that needs to be done.
Please be more proud of yourself.
You're a silver-ranked adventurer.
As I figured,
it's hard to act more like a silver.
Good morning, everyone!
It's time to post all the
quests available this morning.
That's what we've been waiting for!
Welcome back.
Yeah.
Are you hungry?
Want me to make you something?
Yeah.
I'll make you something extra delicious!
The Goblin Slayer swung swift and true,
sending the goblins' heads into the sky.
O, behold his blade blazing blue,
tempered in true silver,
never betraying its master.
Finally, the Goblin King's
reign came to an end.
The rescued beautiful maiden
leans into our hero.
However, he is the Goblin Slayer.
He is sworn to wander the
land, never to settle down.
The princess reached out her
hand, but only grasped air.
But of course, our hero continued
on his way, never turning around.
From the passage in "Goblin Slayer:
The Brave Warrior from the Frontier"
named "The Stronghold Up in Flames."
Thus ends our tale for now.
Hey, that adventurer you
were just singing about...
Does he actually exist?
Yes, of course.
You can find him in the frontier city
about two to three days west from here.
I see.
Orcbolg...
Next Time
Unexpected Visitors