Really now...
We have already
made our move...
Why must we go out
of our way for a girl like her...
I'm utterly displeased with the former head's choice...
How boring...
All of you really are boring...
Thinking that we're part of the same household makes me want to cry.
The same old greed, the same
old selfishness, the same old malice.
I'm sick of it.
As the family head,
I deny all of you!
You bitch! Who do
you think you're talking to?!
Little brat...
If you have complaints,
then I suggest you come at me.
I'll welcome you...
...to that ideal castle,
created by my hands.
Please increase
It by a hundred chips!
You idiot. That was a stupid move.
"I'll let you back into the Council"?
Ridiculous.
There's no way the Student Council
president would ever allow something like that.
Also... the most annoying thing here is the way you keep looking down on me.
Senpai, you said yourself, right?
you said that we were the same.
It's because of that...
It's exactly because we are the
same that I'll win against you!
We will now resume the gamble.
Any changes?
I'll change two.
I'll be changing two as well.
A Pair of Queens?!
Is she serious?
Yumeko-chan's laying traps again!
This woman...
I didn't think she'd go for it twice.
Thinking about it normally,
she should be aiming for a "pig" next.
She's planning to win
with the weaker order, but...
Now then, we will move on to the betting.
Hmm, now that I have all these chips
I don't need to hesitate anymore.
I'll bet twenty.
Yumeko!
Twenty? If I don't raise I can
challenge her with just one chip.
Can I win if I forfeit the
right to choose to her?
No, only a fool would pass up a chance
for 200 million with a hand like this.
All I need to do is follow
my path to kingship.
I raise by twenty chips.
Wonderful...
Then I will raise by twenty.
I raise by ten chips.
Seventy-one chips in total, is it?
Quite the bad stroke of luck, no?
Why don't we push ourselves to the limit?
I raise, twenty-nine chips.
What the Hell?!
All-in again?!
Is she sure she'll win this time?!
And you surprise me yet again.
Quite the nerve you have there.
Impossible for a normal person to have.
You're someone who might come in handy for the Student Council I'll make...
Oh dear, that's rather
high praise. I feel honoured.
And that's why I have to win here.
I thought that restoring the Council's dignity was more than enough...
I was wrong.
I raise, thirty chips.
Come to my side, Jabami Yumeko.
Why's Manyuda going along
with Yumeko's raises so far?
Someone who has as much
money as Manyuda
doesn't need to bet anything on a game like this...
In that case, there's only
one answer I can think of...
He thinks that as long as he gets
the right of choice, he'll win.
Yumeko's already out of chips.
she's gonna lose at this rate!
Vice-President.
Please increase the chips.
I'll raise by ten.
They're still going?!
What?
I'm not holding anything back.
I'll pay to the limit!
I told you, right?
I will win against you!
I raise, ten chips.
Magnificent...
I raise by ten chips!
Same for me.
So very magnificent...
They're not even competing for
role orders anymore...
I raise by ten chips!
Same for me.
It's become a money-stacking contest!
What is this? This isn't
even gambling anymore...
This isn't a good turn...
Huh?
Manyuda is the Student Council Treasurer.
That position has the right to money more than anyone else.
In a contest of who can pile up the most, naturally...
I raise by ten chips!
I'm already close to my limit,
any more and...
Sumeragi.
I pity you, you know.
Your ideals and skill dissociate and you refuse to admit it, instead just making wrong choices...
You really have no right to
walk along the Path of Kings.
You're just an incompetent with a little more money than the average person.
Enough of that pretentious talk!
hurry up and bet, or do you want to qu–
I raise by a hundred.
The sum's getting pretty big, isn't it?
In this game, piling up money is essential.
You do realize I can't just accept money that doesn't exist though, right?
You should at least be aware of how much
money I pooled into school accounts.
I have more than enough.
True.
On to the next one. Jabami Yumeko.
Are your declarations over and done?
Sumeragi-san, are you
already out of money?
I'm sorry, I really don't have
a way to add any more...
Is that so...?
But you needn't worry.
there is still something you can bet.
Huh?
Some time ago, after I had
made a significant debt,
I was issued a Life Plan Form
from the Student Council.
That would mean that my life is
worth 310 million, correct?
It's your life!
Why don't we literally bet
everything, Sumeragi-san!
You're the daughter of the Ceo of a leading toy factory here in Japan!
Just how high a price can be given to someone of such standing?
I couldn't even begin to imagine!
If... If we do that and lose, then I...
Indeed.
Livestock until death!
24 Years Old
Marriage
Birth
I made a mistake...
I should never have gotten
Involved with this stuff...
For Jabami Yumeko,
gambling means risking it all.
As far as she's concerned,
that's the ultimate pleasure!
Of course she'd recommend it to her friends, and with everything she has!
Whatever is the matter, Sumeragi-san?
All that's left is for you to nod!
I'm being pulled in...I'm being pulled in by the gaping depth of gambling!
Come on now!
Hurry up!
Well, if you happen to opt for not betting, there can be no helping that.
But allow me to give you some advice.
If you're not prepared to bet on such a hand...
If that is all your resolve amounted to...
Then it really might be better for you to give up on reaching the top, don't you think?
That's exactly right...
Was this all my ambition amounted to?
Was it really something to give up
just because I'm risking my life?
Absolutely not!
If that's my ambition, then I shouldn't
have had it from the start!
I won't run anymore.
I won't cry.
Imagine it...
As long as we have that hand, we'll win!
I'll pick up where I left off!
I'll take the throne!
For the sake of doing that...
For the sake of winning...
I'll do anything!
Vice-President.
I raise my own life!
Episode 11
Magnificent!
truly magnificent, Sumeragi-san!
This is how gambling should be...
If you show me such resolve...
I might overflow!
I'm not sure what you're
fantasising about, but...
I only placed my bet
for the sake of winning.
I have no intention of fading out, either.
Sorry to say this after you ripped out your nails...
But there's no way a raise
like that is acceptable.
Huh?!
Oh?
"Choice Poker" is all about stacking up money.
Betting something as impossible to value as one's life is out of the question.
For that reason, that raise is rejected.
Isn't it too late for that stuff?!
It looks like you're
misunderstanding something...
Jabami's Life Plan was put in place as collateral to repay her debt.
It wasn't meant to value her actual life.
Besides, the Student Council President is the one with the final say about the Life Plan Forms.
Having your raise accepted is
ridiculous, and in more ways than one.
Well... As players, having an argument over such a thing is completely unavoidable...
But in the end, the only one
who can decide is the dealer.
What are your thoughts on this raise?
The system this academy
uses gravitates towards
the rules of the survival of the fittest, and bears no fondness for regulated norms.
How do you deem this?
I acknowledge the raise.
Huh?!
Do you even understand
what you're saying?!
I'm the dealer here. And I'll decide
what can be used to bet here.
Sumeragi's household has a market cap
In the hundreds of millions.
Her father is a managing director
and a major stockholder on top.
She has the right to inherit it all.
Accepting a mere ten billion
should hardly hinder them.
Ten billion?!
You don't have the authority
to play the mad referee here!
And for that matter,
neither does anyone else!
Well, I wonder about that.
Huh?!
Boo!
W-Why are you...?
Why?
There's no need for you to know.
But still... if I had to mention one thing...
Perhaps it's for the sake of seeing that face you're making right now...
Th... That's ridiculous...
Woah... I definitely
didn't see that coming...
The Council President
took her leave of us without mentioning her whereabouts or her intentions.
And on top of that...
Come to think of it...
Just how long has
she been at our side?!
Sayaka...
Do me favour, come over
here and make my hair.
Now then...
Shall we continue?
Itsuki raised by ten billion Yen.
With that, Jabami Yumeko's bet comes to a total of twelve billion Yen.
This is bad... this is bad!
Whenever that woman says
she'll do something, she will!
Twelve billion Yen?!
there's no way I can prepare that much!
If you have nothing else to declare,
we'll just be moving on to the choice.
Wai...!
What is it?
You can't raise anymore, right?
That's the one thing I can't handle!
If my right to choose gets nabbed by Jabami, then my loss is decided!
And it won't just be a loss, either...
It's a loss greater than
paying 3,000,000,000...
My influence as a Student
council member would be over!
That's the one thing I have to avoid!
And if it does come to pass...
Kaede.
From here on out, you must become
someone who walks the Path of Kings.
The Path... of Kings?
As long as you're my own flesh and blood, you have a duty to rule this country.
Money is the foundation of any country.
And the one who governs it is a "King".
You'll become vice-minister
for the Ministry of Finance.
Both your environment and the path
you take have been prepared for you.
Monthly Magazine for Young Fans Of Flight.
Become a Pilot!
What do you have to do to become one?
the method to becoming a bona-fide pilot
What if... I don't become that?
Then you have...
No worth whatsoever...
Fine by me.
I'm betting my life, too!
This is the turnaround you
were hoping for, right?
Oh, who can say...
Now then, Kaede...
evaluating your worth is a bit of a challenge.
If you're really to become the vice-minister for the Ministry of Finance,
then that's quite the profit...
I know. As an estimation, why don't I value you at ten billion Yen?
But... that means...
Oh my, oh my. It would seem that we've lost at the money-stacking contest...
Huh?! Please don't give up here!
I'm betting my life here, you know!
If our right of choice
gets stolen away...
Don't we have anything else we
can bet?! Something like...
Oh, I-I know!
Let's get Saotome-senpai and
Suzui-senpai to bet their lives!
We can hardly slap a price worth billions on
people with no foreseeable riches or positions...
That's just...
So, it looks like all
declarations are on the table...
Kaede, your choice?
I choose...
The "stronger" order.
We're done with the formalities.
Whoever wins gains a hold
of the losing side's life...
To realise that,
I'll offer whatever help I can.
Running away is unforgivable.
No matter what.
No...
No...!
I...
This kind of
mistake...
What a pitiable woman...
She's been gnawed down to
the marrow by Jabami Yumeko,
who doesn't care what happens
as long as she can gamble...
She exploited those wishes that
were just too much for her...
And here they say that excessive
ambitions alone can destroy the self...
There's no need for worry, Sumeragi.
I'll be sure to look after you from now on.
As long as you can make me
more money, I don't mind.
And all of it is for the sake of letting me become Student Council President
and dominating this school...
Show
Down
I know I can do it!
I will abide by all rules... and I will rule all!
Three of a kind!
It's a set of eights!
Amazing!
Now, show your hand, Jabami Yumeko.
Discarding a Pair of Queens and feigning a "pig"...
Did you prepare
a straight flush this time?
As sad as it is,
there was no such miracle.
Had that been the case,
It would have been quite thrilling...
Moron. I already know that...
You only bet money because you were
aiming for a "weaker" order with a "pig".
A simple scheme can't win
against proper tactics.
As long as I walk the Path of
kings without fail, she will fall!
What now, Sumeragi?
Allowing yourself to be tempted by Jabami Yumeko was your greatest mistake to date!
Come back to us, Sumeragi Itsuki!
Do you truly believe that Sumeragi-san
was merely tempted by me?
What?
Did you truly believe that she was nothing more than a patron financing a gambler?
It that is the case, then it's
quite the lapse in judgment.
There is no such thing as a
bystander that hands out money.
Especially when she has
put everything at risk...
Right now, Sumeragi-san stands
among us as a gambler!
Please, do take a look.
This, right here... is Sumeragi-san's
own divorce letter to you!
A set...
...of Jacks?!
Huh?
Why?
A set of Jacks?
Manyuda-san, you seem to be rather fixated on the term "Path of Kings".
Now then, just what was the proper
"Path of Kings" to be taken for this gamble?
That's obvious, of course.
"Conceding the match".
To avoid any form of narrow match, and to pick up any good fruit that come your way.
Had you chosen to thoroughly apply such a strategy,
my lack of funds would have led to my own decline...
The question was whether or not to allow your opponent into a position of victory...
Personally, I found this to be much more problematic than victory or loss!
Jabami-senpai threw away a Pair of Queens and pretended to get a "pig".
But that just wasn't enough.
If you backed down on us, it'd be over.
There I was,
overstepping my boundaries and betting on a hand so weak that it was worth my life...
We just had to make you think that's what happened,
then drag you to
a position where we could win.
Had I been alone, you would have surely continued on the Path of Kings...
But because Sumeragi-san was here, you simply had to respond with a bet of ten billion...
It was all due to Sumeragi-san being here
that you stepped off the righteous path and walked a path of deviance...
What are you saying?
Three Jacks?
Betting your whole life on a half-assed hand like that... You shouldn't have been able to...
It looks like you still
don't get it, Manyuda-senpai.
To put it simply, there was
one reason for your loss...
It's the fact that
your underestimated me!
Serves you fucking right!
No... this can't be happening...
Something like this can't be happening!
I'm going to take her down and become the
Student Council President. That was my worth!
Kaede. You fought well.
I didn't think you had it in you to bet your own life.
If I can't even do that, then I'm...
To think that you had that kind of nerve...
I really do think that
I was able to see your appeal as a person during this gamble in its entirety...
This is wrong...!
So...
You're fired.
You're such an idiot, Manyuda-senpai...
You really were in the running
with your funds and advantage,
but then you go and humiliate
yourself in front of so many...
All of it... Everything's because
you underestimated me....
Sumeragi-san. There's no
need to force yourself.
Let the both of us show
our respect for his bravery.
Look...
That is the beauty of someone who offered and lost everything about himself.
Itsuki, what's with those flashy nails?
Cute, aren't they?
They're unacceptable!
If you're really aiming for the throne, then you should take better care of your appearance!
Have you ever seen a supernova?
No, sadly not.
If it were possible, then
I'd love to see it for myself...
An explosion that occurs at the
summit of nuclear fusion...
Quite literally an explosion
on the scale of the Milky Way...
Surely, it must be so beautiful
It can't be comprehended.
Are you implying lives are the same?
That momentary glow
as one's life burns out...
How mysterious...
No matter how often I see it,
It's the only thing I don't tire of.
The reason you haven't
grown tired of it is because your true wishes have yet to be fulfilled, no?
"The sight of a life burning out is beautiful..."
that's quite the thing to say.
But what you really desire...
...is the beautiful sight of
your own life blazing and fading away.
Am I mistaken?
How peculiar...
You... you really are something, aren't you?
I'm ready at any time!
Goodness...
I'll be sure to invite you, then.
What...? What are the two
of them talking about?!
I don't understand... it's just beyond me!
Hey there! Really going
at it, the two of you!
If the two of you want to get it on that badly, what's the point in holding back?
You should be more honest with yourselves.
I'll even keep an eye on the two of you!
Oh my, how embarrassing...
Runa, are you saying that
even you'd goad us into it?
President!
Please, tell me! Just what
are you planning to do?!
Well, obviously...
Something risking it all...
A Gamble!
Yumeko's... leaving the academy?
The intent of cheating is...
There's no way...
Jabami Yumeko!
Should be begin, then?
Will you bet?
Now then...
Let us gamble into madness...
Episode 12
Compulsive Gambling Woman