You're so stupid, Amanocchi.
You're not helping me at all.
Excuse me?!
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm?
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm?
Mmmmmmmmmmmmm                  mmmmmmm?
She's blatantly depressed.
I'm just going to mind my own business.
Oh, Uehara-kun.
You seem really anxious.
It makes you look suspicious.
Well, what can I do?
I thought you were more used to things.
There's no way I can maintain my
composure with all this attention.
Really?
Amano-kun seems pretty happy
when he's with me these days.
Our Amano?
I suppose it's Aguri-san's influence.
I feel like Aguri's grown
up a little lately, too.
Do you think that's also
Amano-kun's influence?
Amano has a way of getting into
people's heads, for better or for worse.
He does.
If you were to get close
with someone like that...
You suppose he's bringing out her true self?
Aguri's taking a step into adulthood,
inspired by Amano.
Amano-kun's growing as a human being,
influenced by Aguri-san.
What an ideal couple!
Slump.
To be clear,
I'm not seriously suspicious about
Amano-kun and Aguri-san's relationship.
Yeah, I know.
Neither of them would ever be cool
with such a betrayal.
We know that better than anyone.
But...
But when I think about whether or not
I have anything more with Amano-kun
than he has with her...
But we can still turn things around.
How so?
We have our own ways of doing things.
Wh-What do you mean?
T-T-Tell me more!
Er, isn't this your place?
I don't care about that, Uehara-kun!
Tell me more about how
we can turn things around!
Tell! Me! More!
All right, fine.
Listen up.
How do you make it absolutely
clear what your relationship is
with someone who's become full of doubt?
You do it by...
Y-You do it by?
Creating an indisputable fact.
It's the only way.
That is, if we can be alone together and
show each other how attached we are...
Indisputable fact... Indisputable fact...
Indisputable fact...
Tendou?
Wait, why am I conspiring
with Hoshinomori's rival?
Indisputable fact... Indisputable fact...
A d-double date?
Yes.
What do you think?
What do I think?
Uh...
We'll invite Uehara-kun and Aguri-san
and go out together, the four of us.
When you put it that way, it sounds like
an extension of our meet-up, but...
But?
A double date?
Don't you think anyone who
does such cheeky things
deserves to go fall into a bucket toilet?
I do not!
I mean, jokes aside, I'd be
embarrassed out of my mind.
W-Well, me, too.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
feeling shy about it.
It does seem a lot more
next-level than a normal date.
Th-That's the thing.
A double date could be higher-level
than even marriage or childbirth!
No, that's impossible.
So are you absolutely opposed
to going on a double date?
I want to answer to
Tendou-san's wishes, as a man.
But even I have principles!
No matter... what?
Of course I'll go!
Double dates for the win!
Really?
I'm glad.
Then Sunday, the day after
tomorrow, at 10:00 AM.
Meet at the station.
I can get free tickets through my parents'
connections, so don't worry about that.
I just ask that everyone bring their
own transportation and food money.
There are apparently parades this time
of year, so we'll be arriving home late.
Please inform your family.
How does that sound, Amano-kun?
Any questions?
Uh... No, not really.
Great.
I look forward to seeing you then.
Goodnight, Amano-kun.
Right.
Goodnight.
Viva Spiel Kingdom!
I never get tired of this drab,
mid-game town vibe.
I know! This drab, mid-game
town vibe is so well-done!
I really don't get why they're so excited.
This town is pretty awesome if
you're a fan of this particular RPG.
This theme park.
Yup!
This exquisitely balanced half-assedness!
It's perfect because it has
that mid-game town vibe!
Uh...
You understand this
mysterious excitement, Tasuku?
No, even as a gamer, that nerd couple
is straight-up creepy to me.
I feel better.
They are, right?
That couple's actually mental, right?
Yeah.
They're actually mental.
This cheap real-world look is something
to cherish especially now,
with VR in its prime.
Indeed!
Look over there!
The slightly under-maintainedness
of that statue!
Please, Tasuku, I already
feel like abandoning them.
Stay calm, Aguri.
I totally know how you feel.
Are you two fighting already?
Whose fault do you think that is?!
So far, so good.
Yeah.
What do you think, Amanocchi?
I guess it is...
Earlier That Morning
A double date, huh?
I can't figure out what
my boyfriend's thinking.
It hurts.
Aguri-san,
it's a unique experience being at a family
restaurant in the morning, isn't it?
You seem pretty cool about this.
Yup, I'm cool.
Because...
Because?
Because Tendou-san and Uehara-kun
finally declared that we're all going
on a date in front of each other.
There's nothing left to stress over!
It's game over, man!
I take back what I said!
This kid's more messed up than I am!
I have to snap him out of it!
I've never seen Tendou-san so excited.
Do you think...
They're totally...
...covering up the fact that they're cheating!
Uehara-kun, I'm going to make a push.
Yeah.
This is where our fight begins, in a sense.
We have to make ourselves attractive,
as a man and as a woman.
Oh? It's Amano-senpai!
Huh?
Konoha-san?
K-Konoha!
What's going on?
Tomorrow?
That's so sudden.
You don't have anything to do,
anyway, do you?
No, I spend my weekends
working on my games.
I have plenty of plans.
Think of it as checking it out for when
you go on a date with Amano-senpai.
Nobe's Game Room
Wh-What... Why?
I don't want to waste
these two free tickets I got.
B-But I can't.
Nobe's Game Room
A d-d-date?
So are you going or not?
W-Well, I...
I'm not emotionally ready.
And Keita has Tendou-san, anyway.
You should be more honest about
your own feelings, Onee-chan.
Nobe's Game Room
Senpai's emotions are going to fade
while you're trying to get your own ready.
I see.
If you aren't going, maybe I'll invite him.
Nobe's Game Room
Right, it's settled, then.
Goodnight, Onee-chan.
I'll go.
Say what, Onee-chan?
I'll go to the amusement park with you.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Wear your cutest outfit.
Goodnight!
C-Clothes!
I don't care about that, Uehara-kun!
Tell me more about how
we can turn things around!
Tell! Me! More!
I don't know what they're scheming,
but they won't get away with
leaving me and Onee-chan behind!
I'm Hoshinomori Konoha.
Uh...
Konoha-chan?
Whoa, stay away from me, Uglyhara.
So vile.
Uglyhara?!
Sulk...
By the way, what brings you two here?
We sisters are best buddies.
Got a problem with that?
I'd actually like to know
why you've left my sister out of a
Gamers Meet-up trip to the amusement park.
Just kidding.
Karen
I-I'm sorry.
But it wasn't that we left her out.
The four of us, you know, have dates.
Konoha
Ah, so it's a double date!
I'm single, so I can't help but envy you.
A double date!
Karen
U-Um...
Since you're here, why don't we hang out
so you can get to know each other?
The loner's giving us advice!
Ouch!
Keita
I think I spun it too fast.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Let's go here next.
Yes.
Spiel Kingdom's most famous attraction,
Kizuna Dungeon.
It really sets the mood.
This one might do it for me!
Tendou-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's too early to give up, Tendou.
You're right.
We can still get back in the game.
Now, come on, you two.
Let's go inside.
Lockie the Hero, what are you doing here?
The interior's really detailed, too.
What? You've been trapped in this
massive dungeon by the Evil King Hades?
That's some pretty high quality.
Here lies a trap to slow you down.
Look out!
There's a shock trap, too!
And an army of Evil King Hades's
monster minions!
Are you okay?
Amano-kun...
Hmph.
Ahead there is darkness.
Go forth with your partner,
reaffirming your bond.
Chiaki, are you sure you're okay?
Well, let's go, Aguri.
Yeah.
Ahem.
W-Well then, Amano-kun, shall we...
Huh?
Give-up Exit
That was scary, wasn't it?
Konoha-san!
What do you think you're doing?
Huh?
Was that the wrong exit?
Jeez.
Hey, are you sure you're feeling okay?
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Sorry, I'm okay.
I just feel a bit dizzy.
Chiaki!
Onee-chan!
You're finally awake.
You're heavy, Onee-chan.
Sorry.
I'm okay now.
Chiaki, are you really okay?
K-Keita!
Amano-senpai carried you all the way here.
K-Keita did?
You have a surprisingly manly side, Senpai.
You still look pale.
I-I'm okay, really.
Well, I'm going to go buy some drinks.
Oh, I'll do that.
You stay right here, Senpai.
Wait with Onee-chan, please.
Right...
S-Stop looking at me.
Oh...
It's Tendou-san.
Sorry, one sec.
U-Um...
I get a bit lonely being by
myself in places like this.
Okay.
Um...
She'll contact me again.
Tendou-san's diligent.
See? Look.
She says she'll be waiting at
the Kizuna Dungeon exit.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you going to sit down?
We don't get many chances to
come to places like this, huh?
There're so many people around.
It's not surprising that you collapsed.
By the way, why are you here today?
Oh, no, Konoha kind of forced me
into checking it out for a date.
A date?
Wh-Who are you going on a date with?
Wh-What does it matter who it is?
Y-You're right.
Keita...
What do you think of Mono-san and Nobe-san?
Well, I mean...
They're really important to me.
Although I still haven't quite processed
the fact that they're Konoha-san.
More than Tendou-san?
Why would you ask me that?
Sorry, I just...
There's no real reason.
Tendou-san's important to me, too.
So I'm really fortunate that
I'm given the opportunity to be
in a relationship with her.
But of course, Uehara-kun and Aguri-san
are really important to me, too.
And so are you.
I was a loner with zero
friends until just recently.
I would have never imagined that I'd get
to hang out with you guys like this.
It's all because Tendou-san
said hi to me that day.
Though it hurts at times that I still don't
know what Tendou-san really thinks of me.
You're not that cool, Keita. Stop trying.
What's your problem?
You're the one who asked me!
Konoha?
Huh?
What about the drinks?
Shut up, Senpai!
Why do you even care anymore?
Let's get going.
We're keeping Tendou-san
and the others waiting.
No, I'm going to head home.
Onee-chan?
Do you still feel sick?
No.
You should go enjoy the
last bit with Tendou-san.
Onee-chan...
It's okay.
What are you talking about?
Let's go see the parade together.
Come on.
W-Wait for me!
Amano-kun
Sorry for the wait.
Took you long enough, Amano.
Where were you?
S-Sorry, Chiaki collapsed.
I-I'm fine.
I just got a bit dizzy.
Thank goodness.
We've gotta hurry.
The parade's starting.
Is it already that time?
We don't want to miss it.
Let's hurry.
Let's go, Amanocchi.
Come on, Hoshinomori-san.
There are so many people.
Wh-What's wrong?
Why don't we go up front?
T-Tasuku?
Amano-kun?
Why don't we go, too?
W-Well, I suppose.
I'll have to hold on to you
so you don't get lost.
Okay, let's go.
O-Okay.
Sorry about today.
I got a bit carried away.
No, it's okay.
So how'd it go?
How'd what go?
Did you get rejected?
N-No, I didn't get rejected.
Good, good.
Stop, Konoha.
Though I may not have revealed the truth,
I shall someday make that man a
slave to my overwhelming charms.
You're breaking character.
Let's go to the front.
Are you sure you won't collapse again?
Yes.
I'm totally fine now.
Let's go, Konoha.
Hey...
Thanks for everything today.
Sure.
It wasn't game over at all.
It's so pretty.
Let's go up further, Tendou-san.
Amano-kun?
Amano-kun!