Why am I being so indecisive about this?
Well, I'll be going now, Ayumi.
Good morning.
Y-Yeah, morning.
Then, let's go.
Over here.
Episode 9
The World is Not in Here
Isn't it a bit early
compared to when the gig starts?
It's so I can buy goods from the gig.
You can't do that after it's over?
Most of the popular merchandising sell out.
I guess that's how things go?
In any case, you're a pretty big fangirl.
If that's so, you should
have just met Sala yesterday.
I don't have any desire to buy
t-shirts, hoodies, or stuff like that.
I just want their highly functional
smartphone case!
It comes with an internal battery
and a high-sound quality linear PCM recorder!
Yeah, I get it. that's nice.
You don't want one?
If I bought one, we'd have
a matching pair. You're fine with that?
Oh, I see.
Please make sure to not buy one.
She said it so bluntly...
it's kinda shocking.
There's a huge line...
I guess we have to honestly line up.
Why are you just standing there?
Well, I'm not buying anything.
Either way, you're here with me.
If I'm alone, I won't have anyone
to talk to so I'll be bored.
In the first place, didn't she hate me?
Inviting me to gigs, lining up together...
why are we getting all friendly?
I hope they don't sell out.
What's wrong?
No, well, I was thinking it's a long line...
Of course, they are a band
that is popular globally.
In the first place, they aren't a group
that is too good for a box of this capacity.
So she's someone amazing...
Got my case!
Look, look, look here!
What do you think about the logo
on the back! ZHIEND is such a figurative art!
Yeah, I think it's wonderful.
Isn't it! So awesome! It looks so cool!
In the end, you are a fangirl....
It's starting!
Lying before me
Scene painted in green
I was never found
And I played hide and seek
There remains a little scar
on your face still facing down
To the ground you hold yourself
and crouch like you've been wounded
I adored the days when we just want
more things with no means oh
I adored when you were always
just there for me by my side
What is this strange sensation?
Next up is a world premiere
of a song right here in loving Japan!
TRIGGER!
Come now heading to the oblivion
To the darkness sink me
Future is lonely as it seems to be
And I am reaching from there
I remember this song..?
This should be the first time hearing it...
My mind is clear now
I feel like I can do anything
When I want to do it, yeah
I feel I'm notorious
Do you know what you can handle?
Do you know me?
Spinning round and round
Going back and forth
Will be here as an angel that's fallen deep
See there's the dark side waiting for me
Never end forever
Out on the rim no need to breathe ever I'm
Big Brother Yu, what is the matter?
I'm sorry... ZHIEND's new song
was too sensational...
ZHIEND is so amazing after all.
It's a song that seems like
you just can't ever forget.
No matter what happens in the future...
What about you?
Haro-haro was Haro-haro. Stable as usual.
It is time for dinner in D-block.
I repeat. It is time for dinner in D-block.
Oh, I'm starving right now!
It's this old man again...
Why is he here all the time?
Classical music is great.
There is virtually no stagnation...
just like a mathematical formula.
So that is your little sister?
Yes...
I see... I pity you.
So there's a researcher
that feels that way towards us?
Why are you here every day?
It is always the case that the extraordinary,
or hypotheses that trouble
researchers are ridiculed.
That is why I am here, lost in thought.
I see...
Do you know about the Ptolemaic theory?
I believe I've heard of the term...
It's an extraordinary theory
when you think in today's standards,
but back then it was the
normal way of thought.
But, reality was different.
What do you think happened to the first person
that asserted a different opinion?
Dunno...
He was treated as a nonconformist, shunned,
and couldn't do anything anymore.
Just like how I am now.
I see...
All right! It's curry today!
I'm sure there are chemicals
that boost abilities in it again,
so it will taste like medicine.
But still, Ayu thinks that curry is chock full
of deliciousness that makes people happy!
I wish Big Brother Shun was here too.
The three of us eating together!
Big Brother's ability is way too protrusive.
That's just impossible.
What was his ability?
Traveling through time... "time-leap".
That is just too amazing!
Because he has such a
power that is too strong,
he's being imprisoned...
Poor Big Brother Shun....
Yeah, you're right.
So we shouldn't talk about this ever again.
Time to eat!
Tastes like medicine as usual...
They think that my ability is
merely taking over someone's body
for no longer than five seconds.
If they had caught on to my true ability,
I'm sure they'd take my freedom away,
just like my big brother.
But, if I keep getting tested like this,
such a day isn't in the distant future...
It's been a while. Stay put, and stay quiet.
Kumagami..!
Did something happen?
I finally found someone with telepathy.
Is that for real?
Yeah.
And, that person can send AND receive.
That's amazing...
But, that person has already
been caught, right?
Exactly.
First off, take over the guy
with the pompadour behind you to your right.
He's someone with the ability to pulverize,
that I brought with me.
However, he doesn't have much power.
Got it...
W-what is this?
Next, I have the location
of the one with telepathy. Take this.
Just make sure to time it right.
You're the only hope that we have.
If you fail, they will dispose of you,
and we will follow you soon after.
Yeah, I know that...
Oh man, is Kumagami
really seeing that sissy right now?
Oh, Shichino, you jealous?
Of course not!
We've been waiting a long time for this.
This is the only timing
that the little brother will get serious.
He just has a sister complex!
The two of them
are always playing alone together!
That is especially why.
The only thing we can
do is to trust that guy.
But this bet.... what's
our odds of winning it?
I'm troubled if it's not 100%!
I won't allow for any mistakes!
By the way,
when is your ability going to be developed?
We properly found someone
who had telepathic abilities.
That's forthcoming!
I'll make sure to use it
at a really good place!
That's a flag setting up for your death.
I'm not gonna die!
Hey! Cut the chatter!
Dammit.... Is this world
really going to change?
It's time. Head back.
So that's it for smelling the outside air?
Sheeesh. Yeah, yeah.
Hey, you.
Did you accept something from someone?
Nothing...
Then, you're fine.
Why are those people
treated differently than us?
They're not as powerful as our big brother,
but they all have abilities
that are pretty amazing on their own.
Now, all the plans
for saving Big Brother are in place...
the only question now is...
when to go through with it.
That ends today's program.
All test subjects other than those called
over must return to their rooms immediately.
I guess we'll go back.
Oh, come to think, they called Ayu over!
Why didn't you say something so important!
Go back.
Wait! That's absurd!
My little sister has no abilities!
Why is she being called over!
Big Brother Yu!
Ayumi!
An earthquake?
We have shut D-block down.
Until the next set of instructions are given,
please stand by where you are now.
What is going on?
I repeat. We have shut D-block down.
I have a really bad feeling about this!
Until the next set of instructions are given,
please stand by where you are now.
Open up, please! Come on!
Dammit...
You are...
What just happened?
What happened to Ayumi?
Your little sister's ability
was forced out into the open.
Her ability was "collapse".
The reason they shut D-block down was
because half of it collapsed from her power.
What about Ayumi?
She's fine.
However, because her ability was too dangerous,
she is being restrained right now.
Just like my big brother...
No. After they dissect her,
they're going to get rid of her.
Is this time for you to be standing still?
You can save her if you use the
true ability that you possess.
The most powerful of abilities... "plunder".
How do you know...?
Before that... you realize
you have no time left, right?
Indeed... he's right...
All right!
And now, they will dispose of me as well...
I'm going up against
someone with telepathy...
Gotta be mindless... mindless... mindless...
Who is it?
A voice within my head?
So this is what the powers of telepathy do?
What do you want with me?
If I could see his face!
What about my face?
It's fine. I'm done here already.
What do you mean—
Hey! Stop!
Can you hold on a second?
Um, I don't need to
erase this guy's memory, right?
I hope not...
- What is going on?
- Let me out! Let me out!
- Shutting down B-block!
- It hurts...
I repeat. There is an emergency
situation in D-block.
All employees arrange yourselves
according to regulations.
Dammit! What's going on out there?
- I don't care who it is, just tell me..!
- Help me... help me...
This voice! I can figure
out the direction, too!
- Hey! Let me out of this place!
- Mom, I'm scared...
Big Brother,
can you hear me? It's me, Yu!
Just kill me now...
Yu? You took that kind of power?
If they find out, it will make a huge mess!
That's how big the current situation is.
They're about to dissect Ayumi!
Ayumi? Why?
She gained an ability powerful
enough to destroy the facility!
Even Ayumi, too...
I'll save you, Big Brother!
So, do your time-leap, and
change this world for us!
How does he plan on coming over here?
Dammit! Only if I could get light into my eyes..!
What?
What's wrong?
Shichino?
Dammit... why do I have to do this
for a sister-complex guy like you!
What the hell—
We don't have time!
Take my power of permeation!
Are you sure?
I'm telling you, we have no time left!
Got it!
This way! Hurry up and go!
I'm sorry! I'm sure my big brother
will change this world, so..!
What is this ability.... It tires me out...
What's wrong?
I got Shichino's ability, too!
I'll be right there, Big Brother!
Big Brother!
It's been a while, Yu.
But, I have to get going immediately.
Right... I'm leaving you
to do the rest, Big Brother.
Yeah, for the future...
No, for everyone.
I'm going to change the world!
Dispose of him!
Please don't surprise me!
Where is this?
A hospital. You collapsed during the gig.
Do you remember that?
That's right... Ayumi is already...
Did you have a bad dream or something?
Dream... was the thing I just saw
really a dream..??
No, in the past Ayumi had said
that she felt like we had
one more member in our family...
It's best if you don't get up yet.
I might have a big brother...
no, there should be one out there....
What?
Oh, so you remember now.
Who is it?
One with the ability to find wielders of
special abilities, is the quick way to put it.
Oh, it's you! You're pretty
handsome when you're dry!
You were there too, in my dream!
I think this is the first time
you've seen me looking like this...
Kumagami. You know about
my big brother, don't you...
Well, yeah.
Tell me everything.
Calm down. That's what
I planned to do by coming here.
If you quietly follow me, every question
you have in your head will all melt away.
And, that's when you're going
to go rescue your little sister.
What did you say just now?
You are going to go
rescue your little sister, Yu Otosaka.
How can I rescue someone who is already dead!
At this point, don't you know what
the ability your big brother
Shunsuke had as well?
Got it.
Um, about Shunsuke...
are you talking about THE Shunsuke?
Yeah, I am.
You were his little brother?
You guys look nothing alike!
That doesn't matter, does it?
Um, can I go see him as well?
It's been a while now.
How do you know him?
He is the one that guided my path
after my big brother turned into a cripple.
I have met the one person
I can put my trust in,
and that's how I'm here now.
So that person was my big brother....
Fine. Follow me.
Thank you very much.
We have to walk from here.
This is amazing!
Money is the one thing we have plenty of.
This place is..?
You could say it's a research
facility for special abilities.
Isn't that the enemy for all of us?
Not so. Stop yapping and follow me.
Amazing! Can I record this?
Of course not.
It's quite a chore.
This is the final stronghold
for us, after all.
Here, ahead of me, is my big brother...
It's you, Yu. It's been a while.
I brought him.
Yeah, thanks.
Is it really... my big brother..?
You still haven't remembered?
It seems like he still hasn't regained
the memory that Maedomori erased.
I see.
Erased memories? What's that?
That voice must be Nao.
It's been quite a while.
Yes. I still walk down the path
that you have guided me onto.
As a result, you are helping out
quite a bit. You are doing well.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
And what about you, Yu?
I'm your big brother, you know?
This is the melodramatic rekindling!
You're not going to embrace me or anything?
I'm confused... I'm full of questions...
What, that's a bit lonely.
Though, I guess that's
reaping what I have sewn.
Well then, I guess I'll tell
the whole story. Right, Pooh?
Yeah...
Pooh?
Now, let's start the long,
long story about my time-leap...
I'm definitely interested!
What... is he going to start talking about..?