Whyyyyy?!
Just a Moment Ago
Damn it, Aguri, where'd
you go off to with Amano?
Oh, so I was wondering if I could talk to you
a little about game development today.
Oh, yeah?
Wait, you're working on a game?
Y-Yes, I am.
Don't you know someone who'd
know more about game stuff?
You hate him that much?
I really don't care about Keita.
He can go be reborn in an
alternate world, for all I care.
I have a feeling he would like that.
S-Sorry, I got a message.
You're a loner. You don't actually
have anyone to message.
Really?
Sorry, it won't take long.
Two minutes... No, one minute.
You guys really are like-minded.
Mono, huh?
Mono, eh?
Mono.
Mono?
Hoshinomori, is "Mono" your name?
Yes, why?
Why is your nickname "Tsucchie"?
I like using a name that isn't
like my own when I'm online.
My mom's maiden name is
Tsuchiyama, so I'm Tsucchie.
I use Yama-san sometimes, too.
Lame. I was expecting a cooler reason.
Shut up!
Tsucchie
U-Uehara-san?!
Sorry.
H-Have you known T-Tsucchie for a while?
Yes.
He's been my friend since
I started playing this game.
I feel strangely close to him.
It's kind of exciting
communicating with someone
whose face you've never seen, isn't it?
Yes, I see.
U-Uehara-san...
How much more star-crossed can you get?!
Star-crossed
Aguri-san?!
S-Say what?
What do you really think of Amano?
I hate him more than idols that end up in your favorite drama only because
the agency demanded it.
But why?!
Colorful Tapioca in Jelly
Banana Milk
I just want to make sure.
You don't like Amano in a
tsundere way or anything?
Not one bit.
If we were stuck on a deserted island
together, I would bite my tongue off.
Oh. Okay.
So, Hoshinomori-san, why is your name "Mono"?
Oh, my nickname?
It's simple.
Simple?
Yes.
My mom's maiden name is Mononobe.
I got it from there.
Don't you feel like kind of being
someone else when you're online?
So I use the name Nobe sometimes, too.
Especially when I make games.
Damn it, how much more
star-crossed can you get?!
Sorry. Sorry.
Wh-What's gotten into you?
Nothing. It's nothing.
So...
You wanted to talk to me about
game development today?
Oh, right.
Um, I'm trying to decide which direction
I should take my next game.
I mean, I really enjoy making the types
of games I personally like, but...
No, seriously, how are
these two not dating yet?
Where the hell did your red
string of fate get tangled up?
Then again, I want to root
for Tendou, too, so...
Uehara-san, are you listening?
And where the heck did Aguri
and Amano go together?
If only there were some convenient way
to just, bam, take care of this situation...
That's it.
Uehara-san?
I stood speechless, trembling, at the
thought of how perfect this solution was.
A meet-up?
Yeah!
The three of us are going
to hold a gamer meet-up!
Right...
You guys are both enthusiastic
about a gathering of gamers.
But there's something about the game
club that just isn't right for you.
You have the same interests.
Right...
Thus we need to make a new
gathering spot for you two.
That's right,
an assembly of gamers, meeting with
the purpose of enjoying video games!
That is the Gamers Meet-up
that I intend to form!
These kids are too easy.
Um, there's a problem, though.
Yes.
What's that?
We seriously don't need this guy!
We seriously don't need this girl!
Damn it, you're so stubborn!
Still, that's part of the
purpose of the meet-up.
You two will be engaging in
meet-up activities together.
Not only will you be discussing video games,
you will be permitted to debate about them.
De...
...bate!
They're so dumb.
Well?
It's common to want to share
your opinions with someone especially
because you hate them, isn't it?
In that case...
Pfft
Got them.
I baited them both.
It's like shooting fish in a barrel!
Wait, don't we need more than
three people for a meet-up?
Yeah, is it just the three of us?
No, there's one more,
who hasn't said she's in yet.
Sorry I'm late.
I got caught up talking to a teacher.
T-Tendou-san?!
Thanks for coming.
Thank you for inviting me
to the Gamers Meet-up.
I'll also have to make time for the
game club, but I'll see what I can—
Tendou-san?
Hey, Tendou.
U-Um...
I-I never knew you were a member of
the meet-up, too, Hoshinomori-san.
Y-Yes.
I know I turned down the game club, but...
M-Me, too. Sorry I turned you down.
N-No, that's all right, but...
Did you choose the Gamers Meet-up over
the game club for... well... each other?
Does she have suspicions
about their relationship?
She's wron—
Yes.
We did.
You idiots!
I-I don't think I'm needed
for the Gamers Meet-up.
Crap! My master plan to get
Tendou in the meet-up so that
I could put Amano in a rom-com
situation with two hot chicks,
while at the same time keeping
an eye on his behavior with Aguri!
A-Anyway, have a seat, Tendou.
You can decide whether
you want to join later.
Right?
S-Sure.
I don't mind, I guess.
Were you always so creepy, Uehara-kun?
Shut up!
So, what are we doing today?
We're discussing the next game
Hoshinomori's working on.
Oh, so you make games, Chiaki?
Lame.
Huh?!
Dude, you're a rabid fanboy of her games.
These two are always like this.
O-Oh, really?
So...
What were you stuck on again, Hoshinomori?
Oh, um...
I don't know what to think these days.
I like doing whatever I want when
I make games, but then it's...
Not very popular.
My games are more popular when I play it
safe and mind people's feedback, but...
Then it's not fun.
You heard her.
I see.
What do you think, Amano?
I honestly don't care either way.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
You mean you aren't interested in my games?
Well, yeah, that too.
H-How could you...
It's true, though.
What matters is whether your
end product is good or not.
That's all.
What are you supposed to say to that?
Th-Then, so you don't expect anything
from game developers, Keita?
I don't, I guess.
So just make what you want.
Whether or not you want your game to
be popular, it's your work either way.
You could do whatever you want,
and end up with a masterpiece.
Or you could glue together
all kinds of clichés,
and end up with something ridiculously fun.
Well...
Sorry, that was kind of superficial.
U-Uh...
There's this freeware game
developer that I love.
What I like about their work is
the humanity that seeps
out of the small details.
So whether that developer is
aiming for a popular hit or not,
at its heart, it's going to be the same.
Yeah, you're right.
That's the kind of person you are, Amano-kun.
I mean, I honestly don't care
about the flops that Chiaki makes.
That's the thing!
Wow, this fight is unbearable to watch.
I-I knew it! These two...
B-But you're the reason Amano and
Hoshinomori started hanging out.
He wanted to learn to be able to talk to you,
so he tried to start by
talking to a fellow gamer.
This is how it ended, but...
I-I see.
I caught the last one!
Aguri!
H-Hey, Amanocchi, over here.
O-Okay!
S-Sorry.
Okay, guys, I have plans with her.
I gotta go.
Okay, let's go, Aguri-san.
Wow, who would have guessed, huh?
I never thought Keita would
have such a cute girlfriend.
Huh?
He was chasing after her the other day, too.
They sure are close.
Oh, my bus will be here soon!
Bye, you two!
I'm going to decline my invitation
to the Gamers Meet-up!
I know, right?
Hell, I already want to quit, too!
I-I'm sorry, Aguri-san.
This is all because I didn't do enough.
Why is this happening?!
Ow, ow, ow!
Didn't you tell me there's nothing going on
between Hoshinomori Chiaki and Tasuku?
That Tasuku loves me?
I-I did.
And you said you were
rooting for me and Tasuku,
so I bought you a fountain drink because
I was in a good mood, remember?
It was only 200 yen, but yes.
So why is the situation getting even worse?!
That hurts! You're hurting me!
You've been wrong about everything so far.
You were like, "Hoshinomori Chiaki
isn't pretty or anything,
nor is she a go-getter type."
B-But she really wasn't at first.
What a jerk.
Terrible.
You haven't forgotten what you
told me after that, have you?
"I've made up my mind.
I'm going to wake Uehara-kun up,
no matter what it takes."
You were surprisingly manly
when you said that.
You kind of moved me, remember?
I-I did.
So why...
Why are four guys and girls, including
Tendou-san, starting a gamers meet-up?
Could you please be a little quieter?
Sorry.
I never knew Uehara-kun was such a player.
I kind of suspected, honestly.
That Tasuku wasn't really interested in me.
Do you still like Uehara-kun anyway?
Of course I do.
Are you happy with that?
Wouldn't it be better if you both found
someone you had more in common with?
You're so stupid, Amanocchi.
You don't do love. You fall in love.
It can't be helped.
It's like an accident.
Even if it hurts, even if
they're out of your league.
I-I'm going to do everything I can
so you two can get back together!
Yeah, thanks!
Let's both do our best.
Yes!
Chiaki!
S-Speak of the devil.
Hang on, Aguri-san!
Amanocchi!
No worries.
I told her how perfect your relationship is.
Really? What did you tell her?
That you're the most thoughtful
girlfriend in the world.
That there's no other girl who's as
beautiful and cute and impeccable.
So there!
I made sure she absolutely knows about you.
Good job, Amanocchi!
You're such a man.
Thanks.
Although it kind of bothers
me that she was like,
"Well, good for you,"
like she was annoyed by it.
I guess she's just a sore loser.
You did all that for me?
All right, I've decided, too.
I'll do what I can for you so that
you can talk to Tendou-san properly,
even if that means turning down
hanging out with Tasuku at times.
R-Really?
Thank you!
Let's both do what we can
for each other, Amanocchi!
Yes! Thank you, Aguri-san!
It's fine.
There's definitely nothing going
on between Amano and Aguri.
If they have anything in common, it's me.
It's probably like, Amano was being nice
again and talked to Aguri, and then...
No, wait.
Those two are kind of similar in a weird way.
They might actually hit it off...
Nah, no way.
Aguri's way too ditzy for Amano.
No, hang on!
Aguri liked past-me, didn't she?
Back when I was an enthusiastic gamer,
when I was dull and kind of like Amano.
No, that's impossible.
Please insert coin.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to keep things
as they were between us.
Golden Memories
I was dreaming...
This is my third time through.
It always works out with
the other heroines, but...
I wonder why.
Of course it's always the girls who resemble
Tendou-san that I'm defeated by.
Bye.
The Next Day
I'll text you later.
After School
Gamers Meet-up
That doesn't count as
relationship advice, Amano.
Please don't say that.
Think of it as a valiant effort on my part
to learn to talk to Tendou-san!
Please!
I'm about to give you some news that'll
come as a shock to you otaku types.
Sorry, never mind! I don't need advice!
Dating sims are not...
I can't hear you!
...a simulation of real
relationships by any stretch.
Don't say it!
Why don't you start worrying about
your real-life girl problems
instead of how to finish a game?
Like what?
You know.
Isn't it about time you made a move on Tendou?
What are you talking about?
I'm less than a tick in
Tendou-san's presence right now,
so I'm training so that
I can talk to girls properly.
That's the point.
What do you mean?
"What do you mean"?
Give me a break.
You're already having pretty normal
conversations with the Tendou.
Not to mention Hoshinomori.
And... Aguri, too.
You played a medal game with Tendou
the other day, too, didn't you?
I kind of was?!
It took you that long to notice?
B-But we were competing in a game then.
No, forget competing, you two
were hanging out together.
You already count as friends.
Are you sure?
Isn't Tendou-san just being friendly with me
because she's interested in Uehara-kun?
Are you sure your bar for being
a "friend" isn't too high?
You say that, but it's Tendou-san
we're talking about.
Whether it's Tendou or a princess, at the
end of the day, she's a human being.
But I'm like a flea to Tendou-san.
I'm telling you, maybe you were when
you turned down the club invitation,
but at this point, that's not true.
Would you ask someone you hated
to go for a walk with you?
Sure, if you ran into
an acquaintance in town,
you might invite them
as a matter of courtesy.
You would not!
Is this kid for real?
I feel like you're concerned for these
relationships of mine more than I am.
Well, yeah, we're buddies.
You're thinking so much about me!
Thank you, Uehara-kun!
I'm so happy we're friends!
Save those kinds of lines for girls.
Chiaki?
Um... I...
I just remembered somewhere I have to be.
U-Uh...
Um...
Excuse me!
Whoa! Wait!
That's it for today's meet-up!
You aren't getting away!
Wh-Wh-What the heck?
I need to contact them!
Jeez... What am I supposed to do?