Finally, you all arrived.
No, Inaba didn't arrived yet.
She never is present.
Let's start.
I gathered you here today to talk about the incident
that the Empress caused the other day.
It was a big surprise that a single person, defeated the Supreme
Five Swords,which are supposed to protect this academy.
It is time to take action.
Wait! If you will punish us, I will take the responsibility.
No! It is irrational to think that the responsibility is yours.
It does not matter. It was my mistake.
Warabi-chan, you really...
That's what I mean.
You girls are too proud. If you had worked together,
the result could have been different.
So this is my punishment for the Supreme Five Swords.
The Supreme Five Swords will go on a school trip
to get along better.
A school trip?
Hey, did you heard?
Episode 13 :
Exciting! Five Swords' Inn trip
Translated by: OrionRBR
Yes! The Supreme Five Swords will go on a trip!
How nice.
The Supreme Five Swords going on a trip.
I never heard that before.
Wait, that is a big problem , Ui-chan!
It seems that they will choose a
student to go with them.
Ah! What will I do if they choose me?
I would not go even if they begged me!
It seems that you are sleepy, disciple.
Thanks to you, Wagashi.
That would be a simple Wagashi.
You know that the accent goes in the end.
wagashi = Master / Traditional Japanese sweets.
Yes, yes.
The truth is that i wanted to rest today after so long.
But, you came because you decided that the best
you could do is become my disciple, right?
At that time, when I did what you told me, i felt a great
resistance, one without comparison, that caught my attention.
Well, if she had used her Auto-counter, you would have lost.
But, even so...
Being careful is important, but also trust as well.
Apparently you resist what others teach you.
But don't worry, at least I...
A magical bullet ?! No! Simply.
She simply put a lot of force in her movement!
I don't like teaching others things that they can not
master, since respect comes from admiration.
What do you think? I guess it's not that strong given my build. That opened your eyes, right, disciple?
Yes, thank you, Master.
That sounds good. Say it again.
So, it is already decided that we will go on a trip.
Where will we go?
And with who we will go?
T-There is someone that you want to take?
I haven't decided.
But, obviously it will be someone who is close to me.
Me, me! Then take Kyobo-chan!
I refuse! I will not allow that happening!
The school headmaster asked me to watch Nomura. It doesn't matter if I go on a trip, i can't stop watching him!
I could say it's to watch Nomura-san, but...
If I were to propose that, it would be weird...
Maybe Rin-san can't make something up?
Maybe Kikakujou can't invent something?
To me it sounds fun to go on a trip with Kyobo-chan!
It's me who decides if he goes or not!
Well, I'm not going to give up.
Let's finish for today. What disappointment, i thought that you were more resistant, disciple.
Well, I've fought a lot since I got here, so i haven't completely recovered yet.
A vacation wouldn't be bad.
I guess Oni-hime and Kame-hime are thinking about taking theirs sisters, right?
How wonderful! Love between sisters!
Well...
Well it is obvious!
Rin-onee-sama will reserve that spot for me!
Nono?
No, Mary-onee-sama has prepared it for me!
Chouka?
Very good, I accept.
Princess!
They don't have to decide. It is better that you girls decide amongst you, who is worthy to go.
Onee-sama, I trust in you!
Now i can't say it!
Onee-sama, It will be me, right ?!
It is not the time to rest!
They have always passed over us, I will not allow it!
Good heavens! We can't do something? Can't someone say something?
Nomura Fudou.
Certainly, it seems that you want to go to a hot spring.
No-Nomura?
Well, if it is the person who defeated the Empress, we can't complain.
I agree.
That's right.
It is decided.
I'll have fun if he goes.
You heard it, good for you, disciple.
Well, i don't understand, but I'll do anything if that means that i can go to a hot spring, Master.
O-Oi! Nomura! You just called her "Master"!
Maybe... You will really let her train you?
Well, many things happened.
I can't give permission.
school headmaster!
He has transferred recently and has not taken his exams. I can't let him go out.
If he fail, he will have extra classes. In other words, he can't go to the trip.
That isn't fair!
If it is about studying...
The ones at the top of the academy...
What is this?
I will take care of teaching you
so that you have the best grades!
I will beat you until you reach the level that you can learn from pain!
Do not worry. The five of us have the best grades.
Certainly. How much is a thousand divided by 75?
Discipline is born when acquiring knowledge.
Well, let's start, my student.
Wait! Leaving aside the trip, i took the responsibility of teaching him.
What are you saying, Rin-san! You are not the only one who is watching him.
Since you guys are fighting, i can take care of him.
I do not like other people's disputes.
Did you understood? Ku, Karu, Kukari, Siki, Karu, Kere, Kare.
Do not start...
by your own account!
Ah! If we continue like this,
we will stay without doing anything.
We will decide with our grades.
The one with the best grades will take care of him, right?
If we don't do that, it would be like trying to climb a mountain by boat.
It seems good to me.
Do not forget that I'm here.
To think that the five of us have the same grades ...
All the same...
I can't believe it ended in a draw...
We will do it together then?
It seems good to me.
We lost a lot of time in our fight!
It is better to remember the main objective!
It's true. The headOnee-sama devised this so that the five of us let aside our differences...
All right! We must answer the expectations of the headOnee-sama.
Where did Nomura go?
I was looking for you, Nomura! The five of us are going to...!
That is it, the unknown X comes out here!
That's right. Not bad.
It's because my teacher is good.
I recognize that kind of thing.
Flattering me will not help you.
Start with the next problem.
Let Inaba Tsukuyo be in charge of him, make it look like there are six now.
So you will go as an extra.
It is a vacation! A trip!
We arrived! The hot springs inn just for us!
Geez, Do not make a fuss, it looks very bad.
Come on, come on, Rin-san
It is a unique opportunity, you should be more extroverted.
To come here... I really don't understand the hearts of other people.
Being in the hot springs that even Kame-hime
speaks about, and you look good Oni-hime.
It is silly. Don't you agree, disciple?
Listen. You should discuss that when you are carrying your own things.
It does not make sense to talk so enthusiastically
if you are not even carrying your own suitcases.
You do not accept my statement?
What a disappointment, you lack discipline.
Okay! Okay!
It is important that you can trust a man.
So help us a lot during the trip.
Poor guy! But i will not help you.
Hey! Do not put on that sad face!
We will wash your back as compensation.
There are many colors.
Come on, choose a girl!
You do not have to be reserved.
You have chosen me? All right, do not worry, leave it to me.
You are not allowed to be scared.
Who were you thinking of?
It wasn't me, right?
Who knows... What would happen if I say yes?
I'll castrate you!
And if I say no?
Well well... It's obvious that it is me.
Eh!
You really have weird fetishes!
Just because they are big doesn't make them better. Right, Tsukuyo-hime?
Do not look me like that! Do not worry, from here on out you will grow.
Master?
I will kill you!
What Onee-sama and the others are they doing now?
I wanted to accompany them.
Surely they are in a great inn,
Eating a big feast.
So jealous...
I envy Nomura!
Why am i the only one here?
What inn is it?
It has a legend called "The unique stars"
How interesting.
This is the life! Do you want a drink, Satori-hime?
Then, I'll take one.
Do it! Do it!
It's Nono.
Also one from Chouka.
What happened?
It seems they looked up something about this inn.
It seems that in this place you can see many shooting stars.
And it is said that the first to enter the bath, will have his wish will fulfilled.
Well, a wish, huh?
That is a simple fairy tale.
Even if they say it, they have no proof.
Surely it is gossip.
Well...
Where are you going Hanasaka?
Today i sweated a lot from the excitement...
I hope they don't fight to see who enters the bath first.
Do not worry. There will be no problem.
It is true!
I will go first!
I will be the first to enter!
I do not like that you are on top of me.
This is good. I love this.
This is very unpleasant!
Idiot!
Silly!
What a disappointment, dust fell on the food.
In the case of fencing, you can't see the eyes of the opponent. You should look at other things like his legs and torso.
On the other hand, a fighting style based on
strength does not work against Kikakujou-san.
You really are scary, Kame-chan.
However...
Fencing moves do not work well with a yukata
What's up, Hanasaka?
Your sword has not touched my body.
Exactly, not your body...
Silly. This is strategy.
The next one is you, Warabi-chan...
Eh?
I will take the first place! None of the 5 can reach me!
Wait!
What!
Are you running in underwear?
However, i was prepared for this!
And I didn't put on underwear!
Now I can get there first!
Goal.
S-She brought her katana here...
There is no need to fight.
There are two baths, so you can enter the one that is empty.
Master, what are you doing in the men's bathroom?
What a disappointment!
In the end, Tamabaka was the first to enter. What did you wish?
That is obvious.
Ahh!!!
Don't scream!
What's going on?!
How disgusting!
My wish has been fulfilled.
I'm bathing with Nomura-chan!
I will make you into pieces!
I'll castrate you!