Today, I overslept and didn't have
time, so it's omelet rice again.
You know, I don't need lunches anymore.
Oh? Why is that?
Most of the guys don't
bring their own lunches.
Everyone buys food at the school cafeteria.
So, to get along with new friends,
I don't need them anymore.
That is such a pity!
But, since I made it today, I
want you to take it with you!
S-Sure...
Something nice will happen <3
There's no way I'd be able to eat
an omelet rice with a message
written on it in the classroom...
Episode 3 - Love and Flame
Good morning.
Yeah, morning.
You seem to be pretty spiritless today.
No, this is about how low my spirit is to
begin with. Especially in the mornings.
Then, for lunch today.
I'll splurge and go for the limited edition
beef tongue curry to lift your spirits up.
Limited edition? Will you make it in time?
If I use my ability, a piece of cake.
Right...
I have been waiting for you. Here you go.
For now, I think you're better off
if you went to the hospital....
Oh, this? I'm pretty much used to this...
I'm sorry to make you worry about me.
This is an ability that is
way too incomplete after all!
An outpouring of spices!
This is how curry should be!
Delicious!
I'm glad I could meet your expectations.
Curry was something that
should be spicy after all...
It's medium spicy, but was this the
right spice level for you then?
The beef tongue also melts
in your mouth! It's the best!
You must really love curry.
Yup, yup...
Oh, I remember now...
Yes, I understand.
Our helper is going to
make another appearance.
Let's head over to the student council room.
Why is that guy always soaking wet?
He can't use his ability unless he
gets soaking wet while fully clothed.
What a cumbersome ability!
The ability is... channeling.
Channeling?
Spiritualism. Allowing dead individuals
to possess them, like ITAKO shamans.
Not just a fraud, but someone who can
really use it as a special ability...
that's pretty amazing.
One more... pyrokinesis.
To think that someone has two abilities!
I'd like to get moving to grab this person...
But this is an ordinary road.
What does that mean?
It means, the person is on the move.
In the middle of a weekday?
Is the person ditching school?
But you know, this road... this should be
a narrow alley that is not that popular.
What are you asserting?
Anyhow, let's try heading
out to this location.
This place is it?
Yes.
What?
That person was pretty desperate
in passing through here.
Why?
This side is the only one
that has no dust on it.
In other words, whoever
it was ran through here,
and bumped into this box or something.
In other words, that means
this person was being chased?
Sounds like an incident...
Another troublesome one...
For now, let's move forward.
Two new footprints. One has a
short stride, and one is longer.
This totally indicates a girl
being chased by some adult.
We're going to hurry.
Oh, that thing earlier?
What was it?
That filming session where an idol
was being chased by a big guy, right?
An idol?
Let's see... that's right,
it was Yusa Nishimori.
I've heard of that name.
Me, too...
Yusarin?!
Just as I thought! It's
the idol that Ayumi likes!
You know her?
She's the vocalist for the band How
Low Hello (nicknamed Haro-haro) –
an upcoming idol that can sing and dance.
You were that big an idol
otaku? That's such a turn-off!
When she was in 6th grade,
her career started from the achievement
of winning the grand prize...
...in the 14th reader-model audition for the
low-teen fashion magazine "Petit Banana."
She debuted on that magazine
as their exclusive model!
The year after that, she landed a job as a
regular member of the
"Movement Morning!" show.
But, she quit two years later to concentrate
on high school entrance exams.
She re-started her career in showbiz
after advancing to high school...
Hold it, hold on, let's go back
a bit to the issue at point!
So that girl caused some issue with her
special ability, and became a fugitive.
Am I wrong?
You don't have to say
that for us to know that.
Her agency is Sea Rex Productions.
Wouldn't it be quicker
if we just called them?
We're talking about someone in showbiz.
They won't tell us anything..
What should we do?
Let's see...
Found a suspicious target.
Going to chase him!
Tomori!
Otosaka, please do it!
The one that actually gets in pain is me,
so I rather you not use this tactic...
This is exactly why we have you on board.
Dammit!
What would you do if the camcorder broke?
Is that your issue?
Wake up, bastard.
Who the hell are you?
No, who are YOU?
if you spill it, we'll call
an ambulance for you.
Right now, you're headed
straight to death, you hear?
I was just offered a job...
What kind?
I can't say that...
Is that something you'd risk your
life to protect the secrecy of?
I'm looking for Yusa Nishimori!
Asked by who?
Taiyo TV.
Who from there?
I don't know that far... that's the truth.
Understood! I had already
called for an ambulance.
What the hell are you guys?
We are just looking for a
woman named Yusa Nishimori.
Her nickname is Yusarin.
For what?
I don't know the reason why, but it's a fact
that she's being chased,
so we thought we'd help.
You guys know Yusa?
I'm a huge fan!
Don't break the flow of the
conversation every single time!
I was watching you the whole time.
How did you defeat that guy?
With special abilities.
That is most likely something like
the ability that Nishimori has.
How do you know that?
If you trust us, I believe
that we can save her.
I see... then, prove to me that
you have the same power as her.
It's not the same power, but here.
She disappeared?
Here.
Now do you believe us?
Yeah... now, come with me. But
I'm sure you'll be confused.
What do you mean by that?
Things got slightly complicated. I
want you guys to see for yourselves.
Impressive. it's a club.
You don't have to go so far to film this...
This way. Don't be slowpokes.
I'm back.
How was it outside?
It actually is the real Yusarin!
I have all the Haro-haro CDs!
Such a turn-off!
Thank you very much!
It really is the girl I
saw on TV back then...
Hey, what's with those guys?
They're just like Misa, and
can use special abilities.
Misa? So her real name wasn't Yusa but Misa?
That's the complicated part.
Is it all right to trust them?
They used their powers to
defeat those other guys.
Now, can we ask her directly
what's going on here?
If you ask something stupid, don't think
you can get out of here unscathed.
Come on, you're being scary...
Tomori, be careful here...
Yeah, yeah.
Nice to meet you. I'm Tomori.
Nice to meet you! I'm Yusa
Nishimori, nicknamed Yusarin!
She calls herself Yusarin?
This is the first time I
meet an idol in real life.
You really are so cute that it
feels like someone created you...
I want to get that close, too...
Hey, you.
Now, now...
So, first off, please tell me your real name.
"My name is Yusa Kurobane!"
I wasn't asking you.
Your real name sounds more
fitting as a stage name...
Yes, I hear that often... But,
black feathers (kurobane)
doesn't sound too suitable for an
idol, so they renamed me to Nishimori!
Indeed. So, Kurobane... there are
times that you are not Kurobane.
Are you aware of that fact?
She is not aware of it.
How do you know that?
I wasn't asking you, bastard.
What was that?
So, Kurobane, how is it?
That's exactly it!
I guess you can call it sleepwalking.
Lately, I don't realize I fell asleep,
and when I wake up I'm somewhere else...
The doctors tell me that there
is a chance that I have a
multiple personality disorder...
Is that so?
It's not schizophrenia,
so please rest assured.
She has a special ability just like us.
Her power is to allow a dead
person to possess her body.
Seriously?
I believe that this power calls forth
this Misa girl that you guys talk of?
Misa?
Is something the matter?
Don't ask anything.
Is it someone she knows?
That's Yusa's sister who
was older by a year.
She passed away six months
ago from an accident.
You bastard...
don't go blabbing this and that
to someone stranger you just met!
Oh, can it be that you're Misa?
Such a cramped place... all you
gathered here? So annoying!
What a change in personality...
Whoa! What an impressive ability!
Calm down, Misa! Are you going
to burn us all to death?
That guy has no sense at all...
I'm surprised.
So she can't call the spirit forth on her
own will, and Misa actually controls it all.
You got a problem with that?
Another ability that is somehow imperfect!
That means, she has an unparalleled
ability to be possessed.
And Misa, who possesses Yusa,
has the pyrokinetic ability.
Yeah.
What is your relationship with these two?
They're my buddies from back when
I was alive and mischievous.
Do you know the reason why your
little sister is being chased?
It's this.
Yusa accidentally brought this
home on accident from some shoot.
It belongs to one of the bigger-named
producers at the TV station.
Yusa accidentally read a
text that was sent to this.
Using up company money, connections
to a dangerous crowd -
stuff that will get the guy under
arrest if this was taken to the cops.
Did you turn the power off?
Yeah. But it wasn't turned
off until yesterday.
Then they probably know already that you're
hiding somewhere in this area from the GPS.
Even if you returned the smartphone
now, you won't stay safe.
And even if you handed it to the police,
that would mean Kurobane sold
off that producer off...
...and make it impossible
to keep working in showbiz.
Then, I'll burn it all
down, TV station and all.
Are you stupid? You do that, and
your little sister will be arrested.
Who the hell do you think you are, huh?
And you really want to send your little
sister off to juvenile hall or something?
That would be in bad sense...
Please calm down. You want to
save your little sister, right?
Of course...
Then, we should help each other, and
instead threaten this guy instead.
What's the chances of winning?
I'm really good at creating plans for
threatening others! Please trust me!
You've got good character. All
right, I'll do as you say.
I'd like both of you to help as well.
Of course.
If Misa says so.
Huh? Right now... was I asleep again?
You must be tired. It's all right. Have
some roasted marshmallows and calm down.
Oh, the marshmallows turned into
freshly-roasted marshmallows!
I have absolutely no clue how I should
approach Yusarin from now on...
You're a scary guy.
Then, we should first head to
a shop that sells work clothes.
Why?
The two of you will need fireproof clothing.
It's me...
So you finally show up.
You realized that you can't escape?
Um, I really don't know the reason
why I'm being chased so much.
Did Yusarin do something wrong?
Give me back my smartphone!
Is this it?
That's it!
Even if I return it, like,
is Yusarin still in a crisis?
Whatever happens, there is no
future for you in this industry.
I don't have a future?
You bastard! Such a person is more like you!
I guess I'll take out one more of them...
What... what the hell is going on?
You probably thought that you cornered me,
but you really didn't realize that it was
me cornering you. You really are senseless.
What the hell are you... are
you really Yusa Nishimori?
Of course, I'm Yusa Nishimori,
the real Yusarin.
In order for me to succeed, I can
kill anyone, just like those guys!
It does hurt after all!
This is cumbersome. I'll
get rid of them at once.
W-W-Wait! Hold on!
Like I'm gonna wait!
What the hell is going on?
We can bury you into the
shadows at any point we want.
I get it! I give up! Help me!
I'll give this back to you.
But, there is no next time.
I'll eradicate you, no ifs, ands, or buts.
Thank you for your assistance.
No, you helped us.
He believed that everything that happened
just now was done by Yusa alone.
That producer will no longer
be able to go against Yusa.
No.
It's not settled in stone quite yet.
And so, I'd like you to transfer into
Hoshinoumi Academy,
and do everything alongside us.
Why's that?!
Just like how I explained earlier,
she'd get caught by the scientists and
her days as a guinea pig will begin.
She will never be able to return to
normal life ever again, you know?
The condo next to our academy will be the
safest place in all of Japan for Kurobane.
That's a life-saving story for Yusa.
Please go ahead and do that.
Hold on.... then, well...
If Yusa's powers disappear...
we can never meet Misa again?
That's what I wanted to ask.
Well, I guess that will happen.
But she's already dead first
and foremost, isn't she?
Isn't it more abnormal that you were
able to see her for all this time?
But!
Sho, everything is like what she says.
In reality, she no longer exists.
Maybe this is time for us
to say goodbye to Misa...
why don't we decide on that?
Then, let me tell her how I truly feel...
Well, how to put it...
This has to be when I can't
think of anything to say...
Sho, did you have the hots for me?
That's right. Misa, I loved you. It's
embarrassing to say, but I was in love.
But you passed away before
I could tell you that...
And it was an accident while we were
riding one motorcycle together.
I was okay with just small wounds...
So I was the one that killed you...
I see. Right, right.
I made you harbor such immense feelings.
But I was the one that sought
such dangerous thrills.
I reaped what I had sewn.
Don't cry. That's not like you.
Sho, forget about me, and starting
tomorrow, live your own life.
Don't keep dragging the dead into your life.
Otherwise, your life would get screwed up
and you won't be happy in the future, okay?
Geez, you really are a troublesome boy.
Sho...
All right, Misa...
I will walk down my own path
that you are not a part of.
I'll sever off my feelings for you...
and that is how I will live on.
All right! Both of you,
lead a very happy life!
Yeah.
Sure thing!
See ya! Thank you for everything until now!
It was absolutely the most fun!
For some reason, it was a really long day...
You're really late! If you're going to
be this late, I wanted you to call me!
As for you... you were up this late?
Eating dinner together is a rule passed
down the Otosaka house for generations!
I was busy again today doing
work for the student council.
If you say that, I can't say anything back...
And what is the home-made food tonight?
I am most satisfied with the
meat-sauce spaghetti tonight!
Otosaka house Secret! Pizza sauce.
Oh, it's Haro-haro again.
It really is the same person.
Who and who are you talking of?
Well, I mean "Yusa Nishimori,"
and the actual person.
The actual person? Can it be that
you have gotten to know her?
Oh crap... but they didn't tell
me to stay quiet about this...
so I guess I can tell her...
Tomorrow, she's transferring into my academy.
That makes me way too jealous!
Would Ayu be able to meet her or something?
Well, the possibility is there.
Anyway, start by wiping your nosebleed clean.
That is something amazing!
Come on... you're getting
too excited about this...