Hold it right there!
I've always wanted to say that.
I can't fathom why you would throw
away the advantage of a sneak attack.
Come on, now. Introductions are important.
If you successfully provoke them,
they'll focus all their attacks on you.
How did you know our
sect's secret meeting spot?
I just had a hunch.
What?!
We know about your evil plans.
You can't escape now.
Exactly!
Th-That holy sword! I-It can't be!
The Hero has arrived!
And just like that,
the Hero appeared and defeated
all of the Demon Lord's minions!
Apparently, the Hero's a cute girl!
No fair... I wanna go on an
adventure with the Hero, too!
You couldn't handle it.
What?
Just because she's a hero doesn't mean
she could take them all out on her own.
Otherwise we'd be out of a job.
Don't get so... cocky.
Hey, did you hear?
The Hero defeated the Demon Lord's—
That doesn't matter.
It's time to slay some goblins.
The location is Water Town.
The reward is one bag of gold each.
Goblin Slayer in the Water Town
It's up to you if you want to come or not.
Seriously...
I thought I had it figured out,
but now I know for sure.
I wouldn't last if I were to continue
being surprised by your every move.
So, listen.
Like I said before,
it's not a discussion when
there really aren't any options.
But there are options.
You're basically only giving us two choices!
If we say we aren't going,
you'll just go by yourself, right?
Of course.
So she's right. This isn't a discussion.
Still, the fact that Beard-cutter
is even mentioning it to us
means that he's softened up some, perhaps.
Indeed. I do believe this is a good thing.
Sweet, sweet nectar.
Then I'll do as I please.
I'll go with you.
There are many goblins.
The more spellcasters you have, the better.
Oh, very well. We just finished
getting our travel expenses in order,
so we'll go with you.
Once we're done slaying these goblins,
you'll go on an adventure with us.
Does that work for you, Orcbolg?
Yeah, that's fine.
And no waterboarding the goblins.
Or attacking them with fire.
Or poisoning them.
No poison, either?
Of course!
Very well.
He agreed surprisingly easily.
I see it.
That's...
Water Town?
I've been here before.
Because of the channels, they
have plenty of wares and food.
What's good to eat around here?
Let's see...
Around here, it'd probably be lamb liver
stewed with wine, or fried river fish.
Apparently, the wheat here is very
coarse, so it makes great batter.
Ah, you seem rather knowledgeable
about this, Sir Goblin Slayer.
Someone I know is. When I told them
I was coming here, they told me that.
Is it the person from the farm?
Yeah.
So this is the Temple of Law...
This is my first time seeing it.
Isn't it amazing, Goblin Slayer?
Is it?
Jeez.
So, the person who requested
this quest is here?
Yeah. They said we can meet them in there.
Is the client a priest of the Supreme God?
No, they're the Archbishop
of the Supreme God.
Huh?!
Th-The Archbishop?
Let's go.
Th-The Sword Maiden.
The person in charge of the law
all across the western frontier.
The Archbishop beloved by the Supreme God.
Ten years ago, she was one of the adventurers
who defeated the resurrected Demon Lord.
A gold-ranked adventurer,
the second-highest rank.
She isn't a hero from some legend.
She was born of the people
and became a legend herself.
That's...
the Sword...
Maiden.
Oh?
Well, well... Who do we have here?
I came to slay some goblins.
U-Um, I beg your pardon!
Thank you for seeing us.
It's an honor to meet you.
A brave warrior and an adorable
priestess... And the rest of you?
We are fellow members of this party.
Though we were not summoned,
we will be happy to help.
Welcome, adventurers.
I welcome you from the bottom of my heart.
So, where are the goblins?
It happened about a month ago.
We sent one of the acolyte girls on an
errand from the temple late at night,
and her corpse was found in
an alleyway in the morning.
We received a report saying
that it looked as though
she was sliced apart while still alive.
Still alive? So it happened right there?
Yes.
Was any part of her eaten,
or was she only killed?
What else?
Have some tact.
Continue.
It was truly a terrible incident.
I had the city guard increase their patrols,
but these crimes continued to happen.
Casualties seemingly perpetrated
by thieves or slashers...
Violent acts against women...
Even children were kidnapped.
And then an adventurer
happened to see and cut down
a small, shadowy figure
that was attacking a girl.
That small corpse...
Was it a goblin?
Goblins, huh?
I'm sure there are more than a few...
But how did they even get into the town?
I doubt they somehow got through the gates.
Maybe they got in underground...
or perhaps by the channels.
But it seems like a lot of casualties
if they just wandered in.
Goblins dwell underground, do they not?
This town was built on
top of an old settlement,
so there are probably some underground ruins.
If I were them, I would
just settle underground.
They're not bright creatures,
but they aren't complete fools.
You're always thinking like a goblin.
Of course I am.
If I didn't know what they were thinking,
I wouldn't be able to fight them.
We also concluded that they were underground
and sent out a quest for the
adventurers in this town, but...
What happened to them?
I see...
And that was when I heard the song of the
brave Goblin Slayer from the frontier.
What song?
You didn't know?
There's a song about you, Orcbolg.
It's sort of disappointing,
having actually met you, though.
That's not my problem.
You mustn't say that. Bards singing songs
of brave feats is how these tales survive.
Why do they need to survive?
Don't you get it, Beard-cutter?
The more the words of your
deeds spread throughout the land,
the more requests you'll get to slay goblins.
Kind sirs, I beg of you...
Will you save our town?
I don't know if I'll be able to save it,
but let's kill some goblins.
Goblin Slayer! Can't you say it a bit nicer?
It's the truth.
It's because it's the truth that you
should be more tactful with your words!
Sir Goblin Slayer, shall we
head to the sewers, then?
We're going to go in and wipe them out.
The underground is huge.
It'd be annoying if one got away.
Remember, no using water, fire, or poison!
I know.
But why not just have the city guard or
the troops of this town take care of them?
I'll admit that I do not know
everything about this town,
but surely this couldn't be
out of their jurisdiction.
Well...
Were you told that there was no point in
mobilizing the military against mere goblins?
Yes.
Well, you can't really blame them.
They're in the middle of battling with
the armies of the Demon Lord, after all.
I guess that means goblin slaying
is a job for us adventurers.
I'll admit that human politics and money
issues seem rather troublesome.
I have no interest in that.
How can we get down there?
Hey.
Oh, yes. I do beg your pardon.
I believe your best option
is to go down the well
behind this temple, into the sewers.
Is this accurate?
Well, this is an old sketch from
when this temple was first built.
But the water flow indicated
here should be correct.
Even if there is erosion or damage,
it shouldn't be severe.
All right.
You get to navigate.
Understood.
Let's go. We don't have time to waste.
Well, I guess I wouldn't expect
you to be any other way, Orcbolg.
Miss.
Yes?
This may seem rude, as I am
the one who requested this...
but are you not frightened?
Well... Yes, I'm frightened, but...
I'm sure...
I'm sure that everything will be all right.
That should take care of things.
Yup.
And done.
To think that there were this many
goblins dwelling underneath the town...
It's about what I expected.
Just so you know, I'm not copying him.
This is going to be a long battle, right?
Unlike Orcbolg, I don't want
to use the goblins' arrows.
They're terribly made.
Are they?
They are!
But this is the fifth attack just today.
At this rate, who knows how many
goblins are actually down here?
Seriously, how long is this going to go on?
Don't worry. These walls are made of stone.
There shouldn't be any
surprise attacks through them.
Please don't remind me of
such a terrible memory.
Sorry.
With all the waste down here, you
probably don't need to mask your scent.
Please don't remind me of
such a terrible memory.
What is it, long-ears?
I just felt something weird.
The sound of water?
Is it coming from above?
It appears to be raining...
But is rain underground even possible?
It must be raining on the surface.
I'm sure all the water from the canals
and sewers flows down here.
What do you think, Beard-cutter?
We'll be at a disadvantage if
our light source is extinguished.
What's the matter, Goblin Slayer?
Be on your guard.
Something's coming this way.
Beard-cutter!
A boat...
...full of...
...goblins?!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak,
with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I can't hold this for long...
What do you want to do?
What else? The same as usual.
The goblins must die.
That's one.
Jeez... Just leave that to me, all right?
How many spells do you have left?
Plenty!
Then use Tunnel. Dig a hole.
Are you trying to destroy the town above us?!
Not up. Dig down.
Dig a hole in the channel
and let the water run down.
But that's going to back up the sewage!
But it's not water, fire, or poison.
Think of something else!
I can't hold this any longer!
Do you have another transfer
scroll like last time?
If I did, I would've brought it with me.
I'm going to throw this as
soon as Protection goes down.
Once I do, use Protection again
to strengthen our defense.
R-Right.
Just a moment, Sir Goblin Slayer.
O sickle wings of the velociraptor...
Slice, fly, and hunt!
I believe that might be to your liking.
Oh, but if possible, please don't throw it.
I'll do my best.
Just... a little longer...
We're jumping.
Five.
Fearsome dragon,
behold your descendant in battle!
Nine.
Ten.
They're wearing armor. It's easier
to just knock them off the boat.
Understood!
Sixteen.
But you know... there sure are a lot of them.
An elf's arrows hit their mark,
even when their eyes are closed!
Here you go.
Ugh. Such an unrefined arrow...
Protection!
Thanks!
I'll block the attacks from the rear guard,
so please continue your attacks.
You got it!
Time to work, you gnomes!
Roll bits of sand together,
and it shall become rock!
Beard-cutter! Scaly! Get back here!
Stone Blast!
Now... what's next?
For now, let's rest for a while.
No, we need to keep moving.
I agree. We did cause quite a ruckus.
The rain is masking some of the noise,
but the others may have realized we're here.
What's that?
Is it a goblin?
That's not a goblin.
Thanks for stating the obvious!
Run!
Who knew a swamp dragon would be down here?!
Swamp dragon... An alligator...
Scaly, isn't that a relative of yours?
Do something about him!
I'm afraid that I regrettably
have not kept in contact
with my relatives ever
since leaving my house!
Not to mention, I haven't a
relative who is so violent, Sir Mage!
Well, this sure beats walking!
Steady your breathing.
I-I'm fine...
You have one miracle left, don't you?
I can't have you fainting here.
Let's feed the dwarf to that thing and run!
It'll definitely get food poisoning!
Why, you little—
Something's coming from the front.
Another goblin ship... Actually,
there might be a number of them!
Wh-What should we do?
There is a way.
Hey! I don't know what you've thought
up, but no poison or burning!
We'll go with your idea.
O merciful Earth Mother, please bless us,
the wanderers in the
darkness, with holy light!
I get it. You cast Holy Light
on the swamp dragon's tail
and lured out the goblins.
Since I can't use poison, fire, or water,
this was all that was left, really.
But to think they'd be so easily
fooled by just some light.
They've learned that adventurers
travel around with light.
Oh, really?
I don't know when they learned it,
but they all seem to know it.
First of all, their kind only pillages.
They don't think of building
anything on their own.
Again, they're not bright creatures,
but they aren't complete fools.
They quickly learn how to use various tools.
If they're taught how to use boats,
they will quickly catch on.
Well, aren't you knowledgeable?
I did some research.
That's why I won't give them any more ideas.
I'll slaughter them all.
Which means... someone showed
them how to use boats?
Yeah.
But it's possible a goblin shaman
could have figured it out...
Could be.
But if they naturally increased
in numbers down here,
why didn't they... What was that thing again?
Um... the swamp dragon?
Yeah, that.
The goblins didn't know about that thing.
If they had, they wouldn't
have thought to use boats...
because they're cowards.
What are you suggesting, Sir Goblin Slayer?
The goblins down there
didn't multiply naturally.
Someone, or something,
is artificially causing all this.
Next Time
Onward Unto Death