I’m telling you!
What? No way!
M-Mary-chan! We heard!
You cleared your 50,000,000 debt and got out of being a Mike, right?
That’s so like you, Mary-chan!
You got that right!
S-So, um... for everything up till now...
We're sorry, okay?
Come on! There’s nothing to worry about, right?
We're friends, aren't we?
Y-You're right!
My, what was I thinking!
Sure! Let's go out for some cake again some time!
It’s nothing. Bullying livestock is
an academy rule, after all.
It was no wonder...
R-Really?
Livestock becoming human again
almost never happens, after all.
They were just too focused on that one exception
they could bully at their leisure and let it get to their heads.
Honestly, what a bunch of idiots.
Well, leaving that aside...
I'll never forgive the Student Council
for making a fool out of me.
More importantly, about Yumeko...
Did you know? She really cashed in at the Debt Adjustment Assembly,
but she still hasn’t paid back her debt.
She already had the chance to lower her debt at the Assembly,
but she’s willfully wasting it.
What do you mean? I don't get it.
She doesn't want to let go
of her Mike position.
I guess it’d more accurate to say
she wants to keep
the benefits that come with being a Mike...
How could being a Mike have benefits...?
That's right. Official matches.
No way! Is Yumeko planning to challenge
the Student Council to an official match?!
You. You haven’t heard anything about that from Yumeko?
Anything, meaning…?
If she just wanted to gamble, she'd have ample opportunity.
So why does it have to be an official game?
No, I haven't heard anything...
What?
Now that you mention it,
I think she mentioned that she wanted to play against the Student Council President...
Huh?!
Suzui-san, Mary-san.
Good morning.
Morning, Yumeko.
Mary-san, I gave it some thought.
I don’t believe I could possibly accept
the money we gained at that assembly.
Don't worry about it.
I already used 10,000,000 to pay off my debt anyway.
But that money is something we won by virtue of cooperation, so...
I don't want to owe you anything!
Get it.
Through.
Your.
Head!
O-Of course..
I suppose I'll take you up on that, then...
Yeah, yeah. Just take it already!
Jabami Yumeko’s life plan forms won’t be withdrawn?
Yes. The President herself decided so.
And just what does that mean?
She should have won 260,000,000 from last week's assembly.
Do we just forget about that?
I cannot say for certain what the President may be thinking.
However, I have conducted a background check on Jabami Yumeko by her orders,
and have learned that she has quite the assets at her disposal.
What?
Jabami Yumeko is living alone.
Her parents have passed and her only relative is an older sister.
For a long time, her sister has been hospitalised in a university's special ward,
and she has been taking responsibility for her treatment fees.
Having enormous assets is the only perceivable conclusion.
Does that mean that, should she feel no need
to pay back her debt, she simply won’t?
Just what could she be planning?
NIha! That's super obvious, isn’t it?
She wants an official match.
Yumeko wants to gamble with the Council President!
Woah, that surprised me!
What's wrong, Midari-chan?
Yumeko wants an official match with the President...?
That's bad!
The president's gonna break her!
Not good!
Not good! Not good! Not good! Not good! Not good! Not good!
She's mine!
Hey!
Ikishima!
Just what's the matter with her?
Nyaha...
Better take care, Midari-chan.
Classes are finally over!
I simply couldn't wait; my head was in the clouds!
Now, let us go!
Um... You’re not talking about an official match, are you?
Yes, of course!
Uh… wouldn't it be better if you prepared yourself a little more?
My mental preparations have already been met,
so there is no issue on that front!
No, that's not what I meant...
Wanting to challenge the President that made her lose again...
What’s driving Yumeko to do this?
All right. You should be able to issue
a challenge in the Student Council Room.
I'll show you the way.
Thank you very much!
An official match with the Student Council President, huh?
Well, that 250,000,000 was just easy money anyways,
so I don't care what she does now but...
Mary-chan, wanna go back together?
What should I do?
I've both lost and won in the web of their plots...
Just thinking that they're playing me makes the blood rush to my head, it makes me sick...
Is it fine to keep on like this?
Saotome Mary-san, would you mind joining me for tea?
Just the two of us.
Episode 6
I found you, Yumeko.
You are… the one from before!
Thank you for your assistance back then.
Yumeko. I hear you still haven't paid
back that 310,000,000 debt, right?
As the head of the beautification committee, I can't let that slide.
What are you doing
so out of the blue?!
Correcting the garbage around school to make sure it becomes beautiful again...
That's the duty of
the beautification committee.
I'm also one of the few with the right to arrest students.
Wai–
Take her away.
Okay~
I do have to investigate her, after all. Thoroughly.
No, wait! You can't just arrest–
While you're at it.
Take this guy with you too.
Okay~
No Unauthorised Entry
Beautification Committee
Don't make that face, Yumeko.
Here you go.
Whatever could you want from me?
I have plans for later, I’ll have you know!
Plans, huh? I know.
Do you think a delinquent like you
could even meet the Council President, huh?
An official match is even more out of the question.
But hey, if you insist...
If you keep insisting on getting it on with the President…
then you'll need to gamble with me first, Yumeko.
Oh my! Gamble?!
If that’s the case, I do wish you
would have mentioned so sooner!
Well, what will we play?
I thought you’d say something like that...
I get it, you know...
You and I are the same!
We’re both perverts that get off on thrills!
Oh my. Calling me a pervert is rather crude!
Now then,
this is an underground investigation facility that was built specifically
to deal with the trash of this academy.
There’s a hearing room for directly questioning people...
and a separate observation room
where you can keep an eye on them.
Both rooms are completely soundproof
and the only thing connecting them are the cameras and monitors installed in both rooms.
We call this the ‘Esp Game’.
The rules are simple.
It's a card-matching game where
all we have to do is guess the cards the dealer in the other room lays down.
To explain the game with more detail:
First, the dealer can place the cards in any order they like.
We can see the dealer’s movements through the monitor.
Once the dealer’s done, it's our turn to line up the cards.
Once that’s done, all three of us show our cards.
The one with more cards in their
line-up that match the dealer’s wins.
Each matching card is worth one point.
I see, it's nice and simple.
How much do we bet?
Hey Yumeko, you’re being rude.
Don't fuck around.
We're not gonna bet on something as simple as money.
The winner of the game
gets to pull the trigger once for every point they have over the other!
We'll load the gun with as many bullets
as we want and spin the chamber.
The highest you can go is six bullets!
You can load all of them, but loading none's just fine.
After that, we send them down that chute so that we don’t know the difference.
The winner gets to take one of the guns and pull the trigger,
but only for every point that goes over the opponent's.
It's a loss decided by getting hit just once!
What do you say? Pretty interesting, isn't it?
Sorry, but that can’t be anything other than an air gun, ri–
If you get it we’ll start, Yumeko.
You're the only one I can rely on.
Let’s have the best read-and-kill game, huh?
Don’t worry, it's not like you'd just drop dead from just one hit.
We’ll take you to the hospital real quick, too!
Oh. Are you worried about what happens if you kill me?
Moron! It's all good!
The President’s gonna do something
about whatever happens then!
A shooting incident at school would
make its reputation take a nosedive!
I'm telling you, she'll definitely do everything to keep it a secret from society!
You don't need to worry about anything!
Let's enjoy ourselves to our heart's content!
Does she have a few screws loose?
Let's go back, Yumeko. We don't have any reason to play along with someone like–
Listen, you...
Why are you getting in the way of our fun?
Even the Council President won't
take me on. Yumeko's all I've got.
Huh?!
I'm begging you. Just let me do this.
I just... I can't hold it in anymore!
It's making me go crazy!
Stop fooling around!
Just let us out of here already!
Why, huh?!
Can't you see how much I'm begging?!
A gamble this insane... there's no way
In Hell we'd play, begging or no!
I get it...
I get it already...
You. You're in the way.
Come now, do calm down.
I haven't said anything about not playing.
Yu-Yumeko...!
I can't say I'm too fond of gambles this pragmatic,
but since you've gone this far I see no choice.
I will accept.
W-What are you saying?!
A gamble like this is just... too...
You're kidding, right?
That makes you seem like...
The same kind of person!
This is Ceylon Dimbula tea.
It has a rather florid scent, wouldn't you say?
I do hope it suits your taste.
You've certainly made me enjoy the Assembly.
You were the first to actually garner hundreds of millions from us.
Most don't notice the loophole in
the rules of the Debt Exchange.
And when they do, they mostly stick to small, minute earnings.
How boring.
You've managed to move beyond
your debt and Mike status, no?
Now I have no choice left but
to tear up your life plan form.
What a loss.
J-Just what are you trying to say?
That was just some arbitrary rule you decided to push on me–
Well, I can't say that it matters.
Mary.
Join
the Student Council.
Huh?
Before accepting this gamble,
I have three conditions that should be met.
We only play three rounds in total.
Suzui-san will be playing the dealer.
Huh?
And... the losing side must pay a total of 1,000,000,000 Yen.
Do you even get your situation?
Why are you setting conditions here?
You're fucking insane!
Let's see...
1,000,000,000, huh?
That's fine. I couldn't care less about money, after all...
And I don't care if this... Suzui?
whatever his name is plays the dealer.
You probably think that I'd cheat, right?
But still...
The fuck is this about three rounds?!
You're not trying for a fucking draw, are you?!
"As long as I win at the card line-up
and miss on purpose it'll be fine."
You're not thinking about shit like that, right?!
Who knows.
Fine! With guts like yours, there's no way
you'd make a game boring, right?!
I believe in you.
But I'll need some insurance.
I'm adding a rule!
If someone misses a shot, the other gets to shoot instead.
Then I won't mind having three rounds.
Of course, I don't mind.
Great! Let's get this started!
That's just...
Even if you get the right cards,
you still can't miss on purpose!
It's guaranteed that one of them gets shot–
Suzui! Get to the observation room already!
Having Suzui-san as the dealer is rather reassuring.
No... you're overestimating me.
Yumeko's life depends on the way I set up my cards...!
Suzui-san...
It's fine.
The two of us have 'that' after all, don't we? 'That'...
Huh?
If we use 'that' as a sign, we'll definitely win.
That's the spirit, Yumeko!
Well then, Suzui-san. I will see you later.
A sign?
You really think he can tell you
the right cards with just his hands?
You need to be careful.
Here you go, these are the Esp cards.
You lay them down on the desk's black field
so that the camera can see them...
And showing anything other than
the cards and your hands is a no-go.
The one thing I have to watch out
the most for in this game is cheating.
In other words, having Ikishima know the order of my cards.
Right now, there's nothing that warrants that suspicion.
All that's left is figuring out how to line these cards up.
The problem is...
If we use 'that' as a sign,
we'll definitely win.
If we use 'that' as a sign...
Just what...
is 'that'?!
Please spare me your jokes.
Why should I join the Council?
Oh, I'm completely serious.
That ability, that talent of yours... it earned you
310,000,000 Yen from the Student Council.
I'm saying that you're just the right fit for the Student Council.
There's no way...
In other words... you're declining the
request of the Student Council President?
And just why, I wonder?
You should understand the profits of being
a Council member more than anything.
So, why?
Do the other members frighten you?
Then why would you even make the
council suffer such an enormous loss?
Do you doubt me, perhaps?
Then you can just put the position on hold.
There's no way you could just reject it without hesitation, no?
Well? Why?
I'm listening.
Oh, I apologise.
It's just that I can't understand your actions, not one bit.
People like you that I can't comprehend...
I love them.
Suzui, get on with it already!
Thinking won't get you anywhere.
She may be right.
There's no way
someone who only just got out of being livestock could shoulder this kind of task...
It wasn't even my own power that got me out of being livestock.
It was thanks to Yumeko.
Of course. That's exactly why I have to be the one to do it!
Yumeko's saved me before. Now it's my turn!
Think this through. What can I do to help Yumeko?
Think! As if you could die!
Ah. Looks like he's done with preparations.
Yumeko's objective is to definitely win
by using a 'sign' we both know.
At least, that's what
she wants Ikishima to think.
There's no way she'd load her gun in a match she can't win.
So Ikishima can't load her gun
until she sees through that 'sign'!
If I'm reading the situation right,
the sign can be anything.
Sending any kind of sign is vital!
Two? Or are those supposed to be scissors?
Just what could that mean, huh?
Does this screen show the room
suzui-san's in at the moment?
Yeah. You can't hear his voice, but unlike with
him our hands aren't the only thing being taped.
I see. I do believe I understand.
Good. First, load the gun.
Yumeko, you don't need to tell me how many bullets you loaded.
Still, I should probably tell you something...
I'm loading six!
What?!
J-Just now... Ikishima definitely
loaded six bullets, didn't she?
T-That's ridiculous!
If we did have a sign, that'd be suicidal!
No way... did she find out the 'sign' was a bluff?!
Finally! A card line-up that risks our lives!
You're ready, right?
Of course.
Okay. Make him show his cards.
Okay~
Suzui! Show the cards!
All I can do is pray...
Please!
I can't get enough of this moment!
Okay. Let's go!
I'm flipping them!
Ikishima, three cards.
Yumeko... two cards!
Yumeko... lost!
What's the matter?
Was that sign a bluff?
Well, whatever.
You said you were ready, right?
Hey, Yumeko...
Don't make it hard to look at you!
Ikishima-san.
I don't recommend that you pull that gun's trigger.
Huh?
No one's seen the dark side of the moon...
Is that the trick?!
Please keep your ridicule in moderation.
Someday, I'll do you a favour and kill you...
Council President!
Episode 7
Refusing Woman
Goodbye.