Princess?
Tell them all.
Yes, ma'am!
Get changed and get inside.
And...
all personnel, switch into Red Pepper Tower Shift!
Huh?!
The games are over.
This is war!
Episode 5
The Love-Crazed Blade, Warabi Hanasaka
What's goin' on?
Where'd they all go?
Rin-san, this means...
Yes...
Nomura Fudo!
I can't...
No, I can believe you've done this well!
The Warabimpics are now over!
What?! After one match?!
Indeed!
As promised, I will give you your reward,
at the awards ceremony!
In ten minutes, the door atop the staircase
leading to the room will open,
and you must make it there alone!
Huh?
And once again, my camerawomen
will be broadcasting it live!
Rin-san!
That's kind of a great shot.
This will not end well.
The Red Paper Tower Shift is
an impenetrable castle siege battle!
Saruwatari,
Tanukihara,
and Tohko will be waiting on each level.
In addition, each will have ten
high-level members assisting them!
So thirty-four in total!
This is the true Hanasaka 34!
The WRB34!
Just made that thirty-two just now.
I think you know this, Nomura, but it's a trap.
C'est exact!
We made it through the Warabimpics.
We don't need to go along with her any further.
If you go, it will not end well for you!
She's given me the invitation,
so I might as well accept.
Hey!
Are you listening to us?!
Gonna be real lonely without that girly man in my room.
I'm gonna need their help to get him down.
And if I drop out here,
I won't get the stamp I need,
so I'll have to do it someday anyways.
You two don't have any reason to fight anymore.
I'll go on my own.
I told you to listen to us!
It's our job to supervise you!
You guys...
The door's not open yet, so we should get changed!
Or do you intend on fighting in your mawashi?
Jeez, girls take so much time to get ready.
I see.
Yo, you ready yet?
Don't rush us!
It's these darn mawashi!
How do you take them off?
I can show-
Just tell us, idiot!
Pervert!
Jeez, how was I supposed to tell?!
You two?
I thought you went to the infirmary.
Our Onee-samas...
...will be going to the roof as well!
I really don't want to ask you any favors, but...
Please tell my Onee-sama this!
It's time.
Princess, they're here.
Onee-sama! Let Nono take care of this!
We'll take out these small fry!
Nono and...
Chouka!
Why didn't you stop them?!
Calling in reinforcements now will--
Hold it.
They're your underclassmen. Believe in them.
They're causin' a bit of trouble for me.
Forget that,
The Sports Deathtival:
Warabimpics
right now, it'd be best for me to
go around them and take out the boss.
The Sports Deathtival:
Warabimpics
Impossible! There's only one way there!
All the other doors are locked!
You gotta think outta the box.
If we can break that door down--
Huh?!
What?!
Hey, hello!
Tamaba?!
Satori-san?!
So you're makin' a path for us.
I've got a lot going on, too, you know...
I'm not gonna be happy if Warabi
keeps playing around like this.
The Council decided on the Warabimpics
and nothing else.
So I'm free to do as I like now.
She's got eyes like a fish...
But don't get me wrong.
I reaaaaally hate you.
Is she acting in good faith or not?
I can't read her at all!
Bastards...
Those masks...
I can't believe they're making their move now.
Sup!
Came to deliver somethin'.
My, what was it I asked for?
Two girls who left the rest to their underclassmen,
and the angry yell of my lady-boy friend.
Well, I have good news for you.
Someone else is just rescuing him now.
Who're those guys?
However...
you two sure are acting on your own accord.
Coming all this way
despite my not having summoned you.
So the two of you have already done it with him?
And you call yourselves part of the Five Swords?
How unsightly!
Y-you moron!
Of course not!
Then why are you fighting on his side?
Give me an acceptable reason!
I told ya already.
If I win, you're all gonna be wearing mawashi.
Oh?
And for you, I'm gonna have it
broadcast on all the school TVs.
That's right. Do you need another reason?
Non!
And we can't allow you...
...to do as you wish with him!
Indeed.
But I will not allow it!
Feel the sting of my swordplay!
Hurry!
We have no time to be bothering with children!
It's getting quite noisy downstairs.
I will face them.
Alright.
Thanks!
Kyo-bo, you don't have to hold back!
So this is your horrible "style" of
leaving the fight to your bear
while you hang back the whole time.
And of course it's called Bear Style!
Don't turn your back on 'er even if you're wrong!
I could not call myself a follower of Kashima Shinden
if I was afraid of a mere bear.
Alright, then.
Well, watch this!
In this technological age, everyone knows
what a bear's weak points are!
Look, when a bear rises up like that,
they're gonna attack with their front paws.
Nomura-style
Bear Killing
You can avoid that stupid telegraphed punch
by ducking down and...
Stop reading things on the internet
if you can't pick out the lies!
Standing atop these narrow stairs
is one of the Five Swords, who excels in
a thrusting sword technique.
Yet you still plan to face me?
I hope you thoroughly enjoy this!
The hell?! That was a jab!
Kyo-bo has been trained in boxing as well!
Don't forget, there are two people here!
Taisha School Odachi Technique 8
Enkai
Princess Oni, you fool.
You know how many years I have sat
on the council of the Five Swords.
Did you think I would be weaker
than the beast I employ?
How underhanded!
That wasn't underhanded.
Ninjutsu is quite accepted in the Taisha school.
Ninjutsu?
Yes, when she attacked,
Hanasaka used a hidden shuriken...
to stab Onigawara's right shoulder,
and took her attack with her sword.
She used the force to spin like a top,
jumping upwards diagonally.
Then sliced at her unprotected back.
She's terrifyingly light on her feet.
Like a circus performer...
No, she's the damn ringmaster!
Returning Blade
Horizontal Right Slash
Wha?!
Taisha School Odachi Technique 11
Yousha
Now, this won't do!
What impressive power!
Combined Technique Two: Kick
A kick, but...
Dragon's Tail
So what!
Just kidding!
I've got you!
Oh?
Crane Pose
The Kashima Shinden school also has
kicking techniques, Hanasaka!
Don't underestimate me!
Not me, or...
Kikakujo,
or Nomura!
Thanks for caring!
This is the first time I've used
the magic bullet this many times.
I'm cornered!
An easy victory for me!
Now!
They're...!
You can't protect yourself from these with a rapier!
That's right!
Both of them look like they're cornered, though.
Right Armor-Breaking Stance
I can no longer overlook your actions.
As a member of the Five Swords, I will correct you!
What a strange thing to say.
Look at yourself!
Can you really say you're not swayed
by your own emotions?!
The Five Swords' purpose is to
put down enemy outsiders.
What is so different from what I am doing now
and what you have done?!
I know she's just trying to distract me.
Focus!
I cannot see the reason why a woman like you,
who terrorized the men of this school,
one day stopped altogether, and is now
turning her sword against her allies!
I am the one in the right here!
You're overthinking things.
Keep focused on one thing.
Is that all you have to say?
Oh, then I'll tack on something.
Onigawara, Kikakujo!
Now that I think of it,
I haven't thanked you for earlier yet, right?
Yes, that's right!
Wha-?!
You need to focus too, Nomura!
I'm fine.
That's right, I just need to focus on
defeating the enemy before me!
What?!
Kyo-bo! Finish him off already!
Kyo-bo!
Kyo-bo, she's talkin' to you.
My magic bullet's damage builds up on the inside.
If you ain't coming at me, should I come to you?
There it is, the stupid telegraphed punch!
There we go!
I've been waitin' for you to drop your head down!
Totally Straight Punch
Fleche
She's coming at us?!
To such an enclosed space?!
Petit bete!
Touche par dessus
It's only natural that I can fight you
in close quarters, too!
Kyo...!
Humans will reflexively move away from a blade.
But if you overcome that fear
and take a step forward instead,
your opponent will move away from your attack,
causing theirs to miss.
This means instant victory.
This is a Kashima hidden technique,
One Blade!
One Blade
We took care of them!
Allow us to assist you!
Nono, U. Baragasaki.
Good work.
Onee-sama!
Thanks.
Nomura...
U-um...
W-we should be thanking y-
Well, forget that,
could you hurry up and help me tie her up?
What?!
I might break some bones doing it myself,
but if all three of us do it it'll be real easy.
Three of us...
Doing it?!
Y-you bastard, are you serious?!
Huh?
On top of doing this to us,
you're going to do that to her as well?!
I don't think so!
You will not!
Huh?!
You won't get away with this!
You bastard!
I'll get you for this!
I'll correct you!
This won't do.
This won't do at all.
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Warabi Hanasaka's school of swordsmanship
is the Taisha School!
The "Tai" in the name refers to the four kanji read as tai:
body, waiting, confrontation, and thickness!
Wait, don't those all have something to do with us?!
I mean, your body waiting for something
thick to confront it...
Episode 6
000000000000000000000
Memorandum of a Scandal
Don't go any further with that!