Well, obviously...
Something that risks it all...
A gamble!
Yumeko.
What you said yesterday...
did you mean it?
You're up against the
student Council President.
We have absolutely no idea
what she can do to you!
Suzui-san...
You're worried about me, aren't you?
thank you so much...
But I must still apologize - that just won't do.
There is no way I can refrain, especially not
with such a feast being dangled in front of me...
It's not that I want to stop you.
I want to watch your gambling
as closely as I can, Yumeko.
Yumeko's showing me something...
You guys, why are you taking it so easy?
Do you really have time to chat?
what about your strategy?
My strategy...?
I'm talking about the gamble with
the Council President, obviously!
First, we have these special
dice that only show one side...
They come as a set of six,
with lots of different types.
Next, we have a card deck
with infrared paint.
If you look through an infrared camera, each and every card is obvious!
And now, one of my personal favourites.
Simple construction, major results.
We call it the "bedbug", and–
Wait a second!
Does that mean you're
planning on cheating?
Huh? Do I really have
to explain the obvious?
We're up against the President here.
If we can't at least bring this
much to the table, nothing'll do.
I certainly appreciate the thought, but...
I have no plans to cheat,
none whatsoever.
Eh?! Why not?
After all, an all-out gamble
against the President...
...has no room for such impurities.
Well, I had a feeling you'd say that.
If that's that, then let's
just prepare ourselves.
You're right...
Oh? Will the both of you
be accompanying me?
That woman said that
she underestimated me,
so I want to see her fall from grace with my own eyes.
And I did bet on you, Yumeko-senpai.
Suzui-san...
Mary-san, Itsuki-san...
Thank you very much.
Everyone, thank you
for coming here.
The President awaits.
Please come in.
You did well, coming here...
Pardon the intrusion, Kirari-san.
No need for a preface.
why don't we get started now?
After all, it doesn't seem like I can refrain...
...when there's such a delicious
feast dangling in front of me.
From when I first
met you in this academy,
I felt as if we had
met a long time ago...
How I've dreamt for this day to come...
Jabami Yumeko!
Ok,
ok,
ok!
Attention!
Today I, Yomotsuki Runa,
will be overseeing this gamble!
I'm glad to see you
both so fired up for it!
'Kay, let's get the formalities
done with so we can move on!
First of all, about the wager...
You said you'd bet everything,
but exactly what does that mean?
Yumeko.
do you enjoy your life here?
Oh, I do! An academy
where gambling decides all...
A victory leads to Heaven,
a loss to Hell.
Everyone embraces risks that
leave them crawling on all fours...
Such a place cannot be found anywhere else, no matter how much you search.
As it is, Hyakkaou Academy
is my Heaven on Earth.
I'm glad it's to your liking.
This is a garden, completely separated from the rules of the outside world...
The only definite truth is the survival of the fittest, decided by gambling.
I love this academy, and the way it forces anyone
and everyone to desperately struggle for survival.
Hyakkaou Academy is an
aquarium of my own design.
How wonderful.
To think that such affections
were placed upon this academy.
In that case...
It means that...
Whoever loses this gamble isn't
allowed to ever step foot in it again.
You're fine with that?
Yes.
Of course.
Th-That's...
Yume–
President!
Please wait!
something like this...
Wait! Don't you think it's weird?
If the winner doesn't even get anything, then what's the point in playing along?!
Oh, is that so? Is gambling really
something made for winning?
For people as superior
as yourself, that may be.
For others, however,
It's very different.
They take on disadvantageous
gambles for the sake of the danger.
While humans are
said to be irrational beings,
actions with such an utter lack of reason are rare.
Even though gambling bears no fruits, even though it only leads to loss...
...we still indulge in gambling. It's because pursuing such risks is entertaining.
Runa, please go on.
Gotcha!
Itsuki-chan, you got any tarot cards on ya?
Why do you ask?
We're gonna use them to gamble.
Sure, we have some of our own. But you'd feel safer if you brought yours, right?
I do have some...
I left behind those trick tarot
cards because Yumeko told me to...
What a fucking waste...!
Thank you.
Now then, do explain the rules for us.
For better or for worse, this gamble
will greatly change our fates.
So why don't we try
some fortune-telling?
This game is called
"Tarot Cards of Fate".
Twenty-two cards of the Major Arcana,
each bearing a vastly different meaning.
From these cards, three of us
will each pick one card.
The Major Arcana is numbered from zero to
twenty-one. These numbers will be our points.
However, should the card be upright for the player, it becomes a plus.
If inverted, it becomes a minus.
If the sum of all points is positive,
It's Yumeko's victory.
If it's negative, it's mine.
But still... There is just one special card.
The Fool.
This card is worth zero points,
and will be our "joker".
Disregarding all other cards, should The Fool be
upright, then Yumeko will win. If inverted, I will.
With this fated card that decides the outcome,
there will always be a chance to turn the tables.
Tarot cards are able
to foresee the flow of time.
The three cards we will hold will, in the end, represent the past, present, and future.
Let's look into the future.
just what do we think of reality?
Was there any meaning to the past?
What conclusion will we face?
Let's leave it to the cards of fate.
Okay! Finally, we have to decide the
three who get to draw the cards of fate...
True. Yumeko will be the
present, and I will be the past.
Outrageous! Saying that
you are of the past... is...
Now for the cards of future...
You, what's your name?
Huh?! You mean m-me?
I'm... Suzui Ryouta.
Very well, Ryouta.
you'll draw the future.
Huh?! W-Why me?
Oh my, that would be perfect!
Suzui-san! I ask you to do this as well!
Yumeko!
This could very well become my final gamble here at Hyakkaou Academy.
Yumeko's... going to leave the academy?
For a gamble where I may have
to part with this academy,
I'd love to have you be
of assistance, Suzui-san.
But that kind of big role...
It's just too much for me...
That's right!
It was the same back then!
I get it...
I'll draw the future.
It's decided, then.
Should we get started?
This will decide our future...
This tarot-reading of fate...
We're ready to go!
We'll start of with Yumeko-chan.
Before all else, the present!
Understood!
I'll be taking this one.
And you're fine with that direction?
I am!
Then, flip those cards!
There are only three chances to draw.
If she gets a big negative from the
start, then I can't bear to look...
The Magician, upright!
that means plus one point!
One point?
For a gamble I think that's risking everything, I think that's a pretty gloomy start...
No, this is fine.
Since each card can be upright or inverted, we can keep expecting a value of zero.
Being in the positive is
enough of an advantage.
Now keep 'em coming!
You're next, Prez!
you get to choose the past!
Yumeko, do you believe in determinism?
In fate, you mean?
As in, the belief that everything
has been decided in advance.
If such a thing truly exists,
It would be quite the romantic notion.
I feel the same.
It can't be duplicated,
and is therefore illogical.
But on the other hand, deciding that fate doesn't exist is just as illogical.
Do you know the record for a
game of roulette to land on black?
No...
Twenty-seven times.
Looking at the chances, they would
roughly amount to one in seven billion.
I'm sure this is what the dealer in charge of that roulette must have thought...
"Oh, this thing must be broken..."
After all, if that weren't the case, one could only think that something let the ball land on black.
As long as something isn't completely
impossible, there's a chance it might occur.
If one were to draw something with a tiny success rate by chance,
people would see "fate" in the works...
In the end, "fate" is merely a question of what one would call a past occurrence.
Yumeko. Just what would
you call that, I wonder?
The World... inverted?!
Its score is...
Minus twenty-one points!
That's the President for ya!
Drawing that, now?
how lucky can you get?!
Tha... that's just...
Getting minus twenty-one points now?
This is cheating, isn't–
Oh, Itsuki-chan...?
Did you even listen to
what the Prez said earlier?
Are you seriously gonna treat it like cheating 'cause you're a little in the red now?
I'm telling ya, don't worry about it!
I'm a totally neutral party! I can guarantee that the Prez's choice had no gimmicks!
More importantly, the current
score is at minus twenty points!
Are you ready, Suzui Ryouta-kun?
If you want Yumeko-chan to win,
drawing The Fool's the option ya got!
But you already get that, don't you?
Suzui...
He has to draw The Fool to win...
Isn't there a hint hidden somewhere?!
This means...!
Whoa there!
No can do! Suzui-kun's the
only one who gets to draw!
I'm not telling you to stuff it, but if I catch
you givin' out advice, you lose by foul play!
Come on, Suzui-kun!
draw out the future, would ya?
Only twenty cards left...
And out of all of them, I have to draw
the Fool, and in its upright position too...
My odds are one-in-forty!
Are you really telling me that I can pull that off...?!
Suzui-san.
Please, draw a card at your leisure.
Even if you were to lose, I'm the one
that must leave this academy.
Indeed, this is my risk alone...
my own pain to bear...
All I can do is to
somberly accept the outcome.
Yumeko...
You're wrong about that.
I already told you. I want to you watch you as closely as I can, Yumeko.
I want to be with you more, Yumeko.
There... There's a risk for me, too!
The problem is which card
I'm supposed to draw...
Those two looked like they
caught on to something just then...
He-Hey, did you hear that?! Did you hear that just now?!
So basically, there's something I missed...
That was a confession, it so was!
Something that I can use as a hint...
Did he notice?
The twenty cards left look
like they have no clues...
...but there's actually one
card that sticks out.
It's probably lip gloss
or something similar...
It's not that thick,
you wouldn't see it at first...
She marked the surface... Is it a trick where she marks a good card to draw it later?
It's not. After all, Yomotsuki's the only one who touched those cards while playing overseer...
She peeked at that moment...
Which means 'that' card...
...was The Fool!
Yomotsuki really did stick to the truth.
The President's choice had no gimmicks.
Even though she already marked the surface, she didn't draw that card!
I have no idea why she'd
do something like that...
But anyways, it's a sure
thing that that card's The Fool!
As long as it's upright, we can win!
A one-in-forty chance can become a one-in-two!
Are you gonna go with that card?
Come on, then. Flip it.
No...
This isn't it...
This is the
one card I can't draw!
Huh?!
W-What do you think you're doing?!
Whoa there...
If you say any more than that...
I have no idea why the
president would mark that card.
But there's one thing that's certain!
Whether that's The Fool or not... Whether
we'd draw based on either of those ideas...
Drawing that card has a huge risk.
It's because the President's
the one who prepared all of it!
She likes to chase after risks!
There's no way I'd just leave
the best part to someone else!
I'm the one who gets to choose!
I'll decide the risk I'm after!
This is...
This is
my
gamble!
Amazing...!
Yes,
yes!
Wonderful!
Let's both choose randomly!
let's leave it to fate!
But regardless...
In the end, it will be by your own hand!
Come on...
Let us gamble into madness...
An upright Judgement!
That's plus twenty points
and adds up to zero!
And so...The Tarot of Fate
ends with a draw!
Neither of you have to leave
the academy. Isn't that nice?
Good work!
President!
President...
I'm so... glad...
Pull yourself together, Sayaka.
Suzui-san.
Yumeko...
What were you thinking, Senpai?!
If you drew The Fool, there was a one-in-two chance to win! Why'd you throw that away?!
Well, I mean... I already said–
Sumeragi, what are you talking about?
There's no way the card with the most obvious mark could be The Fool.
Huh? But the President only ever touched The Fool!
No, no. She stacked two cards and took them.
There was another card behind The Fool.
If it really was The Fool,
then there's no way she wouldn't draw it!
No, no! You wouldn't know,
saotome-senpai, but she so would!
There's no way, don't be a moron.
Then do you want to make sure?!
Couldn't ask for more!
Come on–
What're you doing?!
I'm telling ya, not knowing
makes it all the more fun!
Now hold on a minute!
I certainly didn't expect a draw.
I really might turn into a determinist.
I feel the same!
I'm sure that a grander, more
enjoyable fate awaits me in the future!
Yumeko... You do have
quite the followers...
With that lot... Yes, the future will
become all the more interesting.
Oh, no. They aren't my followers at all.
I merely happen to
have very good friends.
Oh. Hello, hello! Did you
listen to my voice mail?
Things were amazing over here!
Yumeko and the Prez's gamble...
It's a shame you couldn't
be there, it was so interesting...
Jabami Yumeko's more
amazing than we thought.
Who knows, something could
even happen to the Prez!
Isn't that right...
...Momobami Ririka?
Private Hyakkaou Academy.
Ever since Yumeko came here, a lot of people have been changed by her existence alone...
Some changed from livestock to humans...
Others came to terms
with their aspirations...
And others were smothered in defeat.
Some gained their faith...
Yumeko...
And of course...
...others that started licking their
chops at their new prey.
As of today, the Student
council will be reorganised.
But still, Yumeko won't change...
No matter how many countless matches
went by, she continued to seek out more...
She isn't right in the head.
She's mad for gambling...
Episode 12
She's a compulsive gambler.
With thanks to all of you who stuck with us to the end!
we here at ChunChunMaru Subs are forever grateful!
and until next time...Ari Ari Ari...Arrivederci!