A Gathering of Adventurers
Good morning!
Just one sec. Breakfast is almost ready.
Run.
Huh?
Why?
What's wrong? Where did that come from?
There were tracks.
Goblins.
But you can defeat them, right?
I can't.
Even if there were a hundred of
them inside a cave, I could win.
No matter what, I'd win.
But...
There were at least ten
sets of scout footprints.
This horde definitely has a leader.
A hob... A shaman...
No, judging from their numbers,
it must be...
The king of goblins,
the Goblin Lord.
They're going to attack
tonight or tomorrow night.
We don't have time to ask any
other countries or lords for help.
A horde of more than a hundred goblins
will attack this place at once.
A goblin... horde...
Why... would they attack here?
They probably want to make
this place their stronghold
so that they can attack the town.
I'm not a platinum-ranked adventurer...
I'm not a hero...
We don't have enough people
to face more than a hundred
monsters in an open field.
I lack the strength.
I can't do it.
And that's why you're telling me to run?
Yes.
And if I go now, there'll be enough time?
Okay.
Have you decided?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm not going to run.
Because I know you're going to stay behind.
See? I knew it. You always go silent
when you don't know what to do.
You've always been that way.
They won't just kill you.
Yeah, I can imagine.
I was watching...
Yes.
Don't think that you'll survive.
You might live,
but you'll be dead inside.
So you need to run.
I told you, I won't!
Because...
I don't want to go through
that a second time.
You'll lose your home again...
And... You know...
Even if we run, if we lose our cows,
sheep, and other livestock,
it'd be...
You know... um...
I see.
Yeah. I'm really sorry.
I know I'm being selfish here...
Don't make that face.
I'll do everything I can.
Okay.
"You have to protect girls," huh?
Hey.
At least say goodbye.
I'm sorry. I...
She's a good girl.
She grew up to be a good girl.
So don't make her cry.
I'll do my best.
That's what I hate about you.
Goblin Slayer.
Wow, you're still alive.
You need something?
I apologize, but hear me out.
I have a request.
The Goblin Slayer has a request?
Wasn't he a solo adventurer?
Actually, it seems he's formed
a party with a few people lately.
Really?
A horde of goblins is coming
to a farm on the outskirts of town.
They'll probably attack tonight.
I don't know how many there are.
Man, I knew it'd be goblins.
But goblins being in hordes is normal.
Judging by the footprints left by
the scouts, they have a Goblin Lord.
Which means there's at least a hundred.
A hundred?!
A hundred goblins?!
Seriously?
No way.
What the hell?
What's going on?
A lord?
No idea.
Lords are a mutated class of goblins
that specialize in leadership.
They can be considered
the top rank of goblins.
The top?
And the horde that it's leading
will be here soon.
There's no time.
I could handle them in a cave, but I
can't handle them alone, out in the open.
I'd like your help. Please.
What should we do?
You're asking me?
Goblins, huh?
He should just handle them himself.
I'm definitely out.
Me, too. They're gross.
Hey.
I think you've got the
wrong idea about something.
This is an adventurers' guild,
and we're adventurers.
We're not obligated to listen to requests.
You need to put up a quest,
which means a reward.
Right?
Yeah!
We're adventurers!
You expect us to put our
lives on the line for free?!
What the hell?!
Long-ears, if you go out right now,
it's just going to complicate things.
I understand how you feel,
but please wait a moment.
Let me go!
Yes. You're right.
Okay, then, tell us.
How much are you going to pay us
for dealing with a hundred goblins?
Everything.
Huh?
Everything I own is the reward.
What do you mean by that?
All of my belongings.
Everything within my discretion.
My equipment, all of my assets,
knowledge, time, and...
Your life?
Yes. My life, as well.
And what if I tell you to go die?
I can't do that.
What?
There's someone who might cry if I die.
I was told that I can't make them cry.
So apparently, my life
isn't within my discretion.
I seriously have no idea what you're thinking,
but I can tell you're serious about this.
Yeah. I'm serious.
God damn it...
I don't need your life, you dumbass!
Just buy me a drink later.
Come on, that's basically market price.
A silver-ranked adventurer is saying
that he'll slay some goblins for you.
Be thankful, client.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hey, cut it out. Thank me after
we're done slaying those things.
Me, too!
I'm going to slay some goblins, too!
But only if you'll come with us again!
I'll take you on a real adventure next time!
Very well.
You'll need to buy me more
than one drink, Beard-cutter.
I'm going to need a whole barrel.
All right. I'll get you one.
You mind if I tag along on this
adventure of yours, too, long-ears?
Of course! We're a party!
Which would mean that I
must accompany you, as well.
Very well. This is a request from a friend.
But if I were to ask for a reward...
Cheese?
Yes, and if possible...
Ice crème?
Yes, they are truly nectars of the gods!
They don't belong to me,
but they're both made at the farm.
Then we must punish those foul
creatures that come from below.
That makes five.
No, six...
Inflammarae.
Though we might actually have seven...
Everyone!
The Guild... The Guild is offering a quest, too!
There is now a reward of one gold
coin for every goblin you slay!
This is your big chance!
Seriously?
One gold coin for every goblin slain?
You're okay with this, right?
It's information from a
silver-ranked adventurer.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Not to mention...
It's hard to say no when they're
that passionate about it.
Guess I don't have a choice.
You're going?
I don't care for the Goblin Slayer,
but there's a reward involved.
Really, can't you be more honest?
Why don't you just tell him
that this is all because
he's the one who slew the goblins
that appeared in your hometown?
Shut up! He doesn't need to know that!
I just want the gold coins
for slaying those goblins!
Well, I'm trying to become a Paladin myself.
If someone needs my help, I can't say no.
Well, if Bro and Sis are going,
I guess I am, too.
You're right.
Guess we'll have to go.
Hey.
What?
I haven't slain any goblins yet.
Well, we heard that it was dangerous.
But I think I should start.
Yeah... He did help us out, too.
I became an adventurer the same day he did,
so I guess this is some kind of fate.
It'd be weird if the guy who only talks
about goblins just disappeared one day.
Yeah, he's this guild's most popular
product. Everyone talks about him.
He's annoying when he's here,
but it'd be lonely if he was gone.
Honestly... I've never heard
of such a strange quest.
We're not comrades or friends,
but we are adventurers!
Leave it to us adventurers!
This is wonderful.
Yeah.
Of course, I'll be coming along, too.
It'll be all right.
Thank you.
Hey!
Here they come.
Stupor.
Sleep.
Sleep, you goblins!
Now!
Don't worry about the goblins!
Secure the shields!
Hurry! Fall back! Fall back!
Honestly, those are your shields?
How low can you get?
That's the last of the shields!
I've taken care of all the
spellcasters I can see!
All right!
All right, here we go!
Time to make some gold, boys!
Get them!
Woohoo! Look at all this gold
that's runnin' toward me!
Damn... Hard to believe there are this many.
What a pain.
Even Sir Goblin Slayer
didn't know what to do.
This is to be expected.
Man, talk about scary.
Not that it... matters too much...
But don't step out of range...
of the Deflect Missiles.
They're pushing hard.
I should've gone over there, too.
Wait, look over there.
Riders! They actually showed up!
Riders! The riders are coming!
Riders!
All right! Head for the designated area!
When you're ready, line up!
Back line, fill the gaps in the front line,
but stay behind them, weapons drawn!
They're smaller and shorter than horses!
Draw them in as close as you can!
Not yet!
Now! Take aim!
All troops, charge!
Whoa...
I-It's dead...
Pay attention, newbie!
Go on! Get in on the action!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Thank goodness I bought some armor.
That was some easy money.
Yeah, but...
This is all thanks to his strategy.
Set ambushes.
They're used to ambushing others,
but not used to being ambushed themselves.
They'll use meat shields.
Cast sleep spells, and use that
moment to rescue the hostages.
Don't bother with the
goblins that are asleep.
They'll be trouble if they wake up.
When the hordes get bigger,
they train wolves and ride them.
There'll probably be
twenty or thirty riders,
but we can take care of them
by setting up spear walls.
And you can kill them with your weapons.
When weapons aren't enough, use spells.
Also, take care of all their
capable spellcasters first.
So despite how he looks,
he really is silver-ranked.
Stupid goblins, running this far away.
Hey, how's it going over there?
What the...
Something's flying over here! Watch out!
Now we're dealing with hobs?
Nope...
That's a big'un...
A goblin champion.
Make that two.
Good. I was getting bored
with all the small fry.
These guys are much more fitting for me.
Jeez. I'm too busy counting all
the goblin heads I lopped off.
Just shut up and come with me.
Hey, step back.
Right...
Then I shall take the heads
right off their shoulders.
From here on out,
it's a veterans' battlefield!
Anyone not confident in their
skills better bow out!
Not bad...
May I get some... water?
Oh, of course!
Thank... you.
Um, are you sure you don't
need to be with them?
Well, yes...
If anything... he's more used
to dealing with these...
than with normal goblins...
Goblins...
Come to think of it, where did he go?
Oh?
You know... who he is... right?
Yeah.
Where do you think he is?
He went...
to slay some goblins.
Next Time
The Fate of an Adventurer