What? You've been real quiet.
Wh-what?
That girl with the sword,
is that kid one of the Five Swords, too?
Inaba Tsukuyo!
The Academy's strongest pigtailed girl!
The only middle-school student in the Five Swords!
She's a cool beauty that guys, girls,
and even the Five Swords are terrified of!
That's fine.
I'm gonna get my last stamp.
Wait!
She'll kill you!
She's super dangerous!
Maybe.
Too late anyhow.
I didn't even see her draw her sword,
or put it back in her damn scabbard!
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
No.
You died just now.
Episode 9
The Terrifying Blade, Inaba Tsukuyo
You died just now.
Don't worry. I didn't cut you anywhere.
But I will only stop my blade for you one more time.
What?
Seems you need an explanation.
Truthfully, the school headmaster has
entrusted me with your case.
She told me to allow you two transgressions.
However, you have surpassed that limit.
Your first transgression was breaking into
Onigawara's room in the girls' dorm.
Likewise, your second was breaking into
Tamaba's room and the bathing area.
Ignoring my summons was your third transgression.
Because of that, I have a slight cold.
Sorry about that...
Because of the nature of this academy,
I am not driven to anger by small things.
However, the girls' dorm is another matter altogether.
My attendant manages the dorm.
Attendant?
All responsibility falls on her shoulders.
The patience of the Buddha has its limit.
And I have reached mine!
T-time out!
Wh-why is a kid like you in charge of me again?
Well, there are plenty of reasons, but there are two...
...big reasons.
One, I am stronger than you.
Whoa, there!
Why're you doing all this needless killing?!
Girls your age should love butterflies!
Moths, I could get...
The flapping sound they make irritates me...
Additionally, I can't tell the difference
between moths and butterflies.
Wait, are you...
Blind, what of it?
I have good hearing to make up for it,
so do not worry.
More importantly, I'd like to continue my explanation.
Have you realized it yet?
I performed the technique just now at kotsu,
or one hundredth speed.
Kotsu
Yeah, I just barely saw it.
The Yakumaru Jigen School sword draw.
Above all, the speed of your first attack, too fast
to be seen by the human eye, has its own name:
The Invisible Blade, Unyou,
one hundred-thousandth speed.
Unyou
Which means you're...
Yes.
A fellow student.
Nomura, you can use a sword?!
Could use is more accurate.
Seeing an attack at kotsu speed
is an extremely rare ability.
Perhaps your talents were honed to
that level by intensive training.
However, I am extremely disappointed.
You swordsman capabilities are already falling apart.
You were not blessed with a teacher.
Well, you were still able to tell I was a fellow student.
Why is that?
For one, you reside on a different level of speed.
Besides destructive force and reach,
one big difference between fists and kicks
and the sword is speed.
The point of each weapon accelerates
in proportion to its length.
If, even with your bare hands,
you can face someone with a sword,
that means you must have previously lived
in that environment yourself.
From that, I can logically conclude
you also have experience with the sword.
Excellent deduction, Watson.
Thank you.
What's wrong? Finished already?
Not good, it's deeper than I thought...
No!
What are you doing?
You're going to scuff my boots.
Pickaxe Fist
Tiger's Claw
Spread Fingers
Four-Speared Hands
Kyo-bo!
There's no doubt as to why Jigen techniques came to
have a large advantage over bare-handed combat.
In the past, there was a great karate master
who had full mastership of Jigen School.
Now...
Auto-Counter: Gouging Fist
We're at the good part. Don't get in my way.
You! I told you not to follow!
You...
What're you doing?!
I'll kill you!
Yes, come at me together!
And, above all, your technique
when employing your magic bullet.
The collision on the median line of your
iliopsoas muscles deep within your core.
That is a secret technique only given
to a small fraction of students.
That is how I determined you were
a fellow student of mine!
Huh? What'd you say?
Forget that, you heard it, right?
There's some kinda commotion going on on the roof.
Yes, the Empress.
The Empress?!
I heard the name of your magic bullet
from the Empress as well.
Seems you two are acquainted.
What?
From the first day she transferred here,
the aloof Empress didn't try to get along with anyone,
but she spoke of you fondly.
It seems you have not spent time with her
since coming here,
but are the two of you friends?
Onigawara, Kikakujo, Hanasaka, and Tamaba...
In the blink of an eye, you've made friends
with the other four Swords.
Seems you are quite good at making friends,
but how did things come to...
H-hey, Nomura!
What the hell are you looking at?!
I'll kill you!
I'm so...
disappointed!
I am very different from the "Amou" you speak of.
She knew about my magic bullet?!
That means she's...
Don't!
Please, don't!
Please spare them!
Kill me and only me instead!
I cannot let...
Warabi Hanasaka, you are an arrogant soul.
Sacrificing yourself will save no one.
If you cannot bear to watch, then shut your eyes,
before I do something even more horrific before you.
What were those voices just now?
Screams!
I've never heard my voice raised before like that.
My ears hurt from hearing my own voice.
Tamaba!
Hanasaka!
The... Empress...
Amou!
Hanasaka! Hey!
Forget about me, the others...
Don't worry.
They're not hurt as bad as you are.
I see...
Hanasaka!
Hey, some--
You seem upset, Inaba Tsukuyo.
Yes, when my anger surpasses
a certain level, I smile instead.
So childish.
You too should carouse in moderation, Empress.
I can't hide anything from you.
Were you alright with just watching them die?
They weren't really my friends.
I see. Well, then...
It'd be best if you averted your eyes
from what's going to happen next.
Amou!
What is the meaning of this?!
Inaba?
Those screams earlier...
Explain to me exactly what those were!
We won't let you get away with
doing whatever that was!
Oh, no need to rush,
I'll recreate the scene for you now...
...with your bodies.
She was behind me all of a sudden...
I didn't hear her or even feel her presence!
Who is she?!
Step aside.
I will examine her wounds.
Her eyes are alright...
but the injury to her eyelids
is down to the orbital fascia.
She can't open her eyes on her own.
Is she gonna be okay?
She'll need surgery, but...
Okay.
Is there anything I can help with?
I can handle everyone here.
You take care of that.
Those girls...!
Balestra
Mist
Roundhouse Block
Amou's...
Defense?!
I have no reason to be fighting you morons seriously.
You uncivilized girls.
Foot Blade: Two-Sided Kick
Before, you could never work together,
but now, you're attacking me in tandem.
Did he bring about this change?
That's none of your business!
I can't believe it didn't work...
Even her feet are blades...
She's like the Nemean lion!
My bladed hands are a product of hardening my body,
yet you thought it was a special talent?
But that fact isn't important.
The fundamental skill is turning your body
into a single blade!
This is the ultimate form of karate,
Takemikazuchi, the Sword God!
Takemikazuchi, Sword from Body
Her whole body is a weapon!
I was wrong when I thought you were
using a style of swordsmanship...
The Swordsman Without a Sword,
Amou Kirukiru's true form
was a karate practitioner who turned
her own hands and feet into blades!
Non!
Run, you two!
Depeche-toi!
B-but if we do...
You Onee-samaes will be...
Inaba!
What?
Inaba Tsukuyo, you intend to fight me?
I have one question for you, Mozunono.
Are we friends?
Nono...
Um, u-uh...
Y-yes, we are!
I see!
As you've just heard, we are friends, and I will not
excuse anyone who lays a hand on them!
Perhaps it's because I met with him,
for I'm so bold today!
It's earlier than I'd planned, but really,
my ultimate karate...
against your sword...
Let's find out which is superior.
Okinawan Kobudo.
A style of karate from Okinawa.
There is no first strike in karate.
Of course, the pace of bare-handed combat
cannot keep up with the speed of a sword.
That is why you have your auto-counters.
In Uechi School, one of the three great schools of
Okinawan karate, the body is literally beaten into steel.
Similarly, reacting to blows
with a spear hand is done in sets.
The cerebellum memorizes behavior patterns,
but these patterns can be burned in deeper
when physical damage is incorporated into that training.
Through repetition of these excessive sessions,
these patterns were ingrained even to
the level of spinal cord reflex arcs.
In short, your Takemikazuchi is
go no sen, after the attack.
My Unyou is sen no sen, faster than the attack.
The names of both these techniques
invoke lightning, but on opposite poles.
Turning your body into a blade
and tempering it thoroughly.
It's no easy feat.
You could simply carry it like this.
So, if you still think you can beat me...
I will be very disappointed in your underestimating me.
It's almost summer,
but I feel the temperature just dropped...
If Satori is a monster, then the two of them...
Are a devil...
...and a behemoth!
Thank you for listening.
Come at me.
One Second, Three Strikes
Unyou: Flash of Light
Nono!
Too fast to see!
No, more importantly...
She broke through Amou's Takemikazuchi?!
Auto-Counter
She took damage?!
A tie?!
If it had been a real sword,
a sharpened blade, I don't know how things
would have turned out.
But what is this?
It's light and so horribly weak.
A safe, cheap, fake metal sword,
made from a zinc alloy.
A child's toy.
Swordsmen have it so difficult.
They can't fight without a weapon.
I can't get my wits about me today...
It must be his fault...
Amou!
Nomura!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
The last of the Five Swords is Inaba Tsukuyo!
She's the strongest, fiercest pigtailed girl on the planet!
She uses Yakumaru Jigen School!
She draws her blade at unyou speed,
undetectable by the naked eye!
It's so fast, you can't even see it! Be careful!
Sure, I'll watch out for it!
Episode 11
000012312312312312123000000000000000000
The Magic Bullet I'll Always Remember
000000000000000
Can you stop it with the bad puns?!