It’s over.
All of it.
Is Satou really thinking about our-
About ajin-
I thought I told you.
All we can do is trust Satou.
This will be... the last.
It will end with this.
By twelve noon one week from now,
I want you to hand over Japan.
There, we will create an independent
country ruled by ajin.
Prime Minister.
It seems the base of command has been occupied.
If our demands are not met,
with this lethal gas,
we will kill all the humans in this country!
Yes. We have plenty of reason to
hold a council of war.
All citizens should already know this, but...
I...
am very serious.
We’re stopping Satou.
We don’t have anything left-
This is no longer just my problem.
Alright!
Let’s get revenge for the old guys!
Nagai?
I won’t do it.
What did you say?
The government, which had previously issued
an official state of emergency,
has released a new statement about the danger
facing the country
in response to the ajin Satou’s occupation of
a Self-Defense Force base.
Hereafter, plans to cooperate with the
U.S. military are in the works,
and will be put into action when deemed necessary.
I got it.
Things are okay here.
Don’t worry about it, mom.
What should we do?
Mm. See you.
I’m worried. Shouldn’t we run away?
I’m scared too,
but we can’t leave the patients all alone.
Until we secure the hostages and chemical weapons,
don’t strike without a good reason.
Wait for orders from above.
Roger.
It’s just as the blueprints showed.
Right on the mark.
Just a teaspoon of the nerve gas
possessed by the ajin side
could wipe out all humans within 100 meters.
It’s that bad?
If it was scattered all over the country,
the entire population of Japan could be wiped out.
So what we confirmed from the video feed
weren't short range missiles?
Earlier...
from the commanding unit of the U.S. forces in Japan
there was an appeal for a joint operation.
The U.S. military
would make an armed intervention to deal
with a domestic terrorist attack?
-must be a violation of Japan’s sovereignty.
That’s-
Rather than a domestic conflict,
they are regarding it as an emergency in the Far East.
I’ve received an official directive from the President.
Yeah,
I’m definitely going to get Nagai.
I’m sure he can probably come up with a great plan.
And his ghost too.
Leave him out of this.
I won’t do it.
What did you say?
There’s no chance for us to win now.
It’s futile.
You’re just going to shut up and watch,
and do nothing?
If this country becomes an independent ajin nation,
that sounds like it’d be an easy place to live.
I thought you were selfish,
but I didn’t think you were truly that selfish.
For you to say such a thing...
You just want to help your fiancée!
You son of a bitch!
Nagai!
Are you really okay with that?
Of course I am!
Scum!
Id-
I know...
I am.
He’s finished.
And he can’t produce his IBM.
He won’t be any help.
According to information from the government,
the Japanese and U.S. forces are cooperating on an unprecedentedly
comprehensive stance in response to the ajin Satou.
This will factor into upcoming plans for a joint strategy
Hey, hey.
Now even the Americans have been called out.
Shaking them up isn't working?
between the Japanese forces and the U.S. forces stationed in Japan.
We’ve come this far,
so now they have no choice but
to recognize our demands.
Isn’t that right? Satou-san.
Yes.
We should be hearing from them pretty soon.
See?
This is Colonel Kouma of the Self-Defense Force.
I’ve been entrusted with the negotiations.
This is Satou.
What an honor!
To talk directly to the higher-ups
at the government.
I’ll get right to the matter at hand.
The government
is considering the safety of its citizens
as its first priority,
so we can offer you some uninhabited islands in the south of Kyushu,
or part of Hokkaido to establish an
independent ajin nation.
Yes,
we did it!
That’s awesome.
Satou-san.
I’m glad.
This is as much as we can do-
it’s an exceptional case.
Therefore,
we ask that you accept the general's request for disarmament-
But it’s no good.
What’s that?
What’s going on?
What are they-
It seems the missile has been launched!
Where is it heading?
Jeez...
Are you making doubly sure your
threats are heard?
No...
I didn’t hear anything about actually
launching them.
What’s the meaning of this?
What is this?
This is... poison gas!
I can’t believe-
-contact the-
We need info on-
Security, confirm the extent of the damage!
It was Colonel Kouma, wasn’t it?
What I want isn’t something clichéd like that.
What I want is the country itself.
This is your final warning.
This country...
Give me Japan.
You have three days before time’s up.
If the Japanese and U.S. forces refuse my demands,
come at me with the intent to die.
However, I won’t allow aerial bombing.
If a suspicious aircraft comes within three kilometers,
I will launch the missiles.
Even if this country
is shrouded in gas,
the ajin will survive.
They’re at a loss for words.
I will become the ruler of this country.
What are you doing?
Doesn't this make it war for real?
What are you saying, Tanaka-kun?
I’ve been saying from the beginning.
That this is war!
You didn’t say we’d be doing this!
I won’t forgive deserters now.
To run away under enemy fire
is against the rules.
If that’s the case, then what?
Do you plan to get us all locked up?
I suppose that’s right.
Satou-san.
What are you doing?
If you’re that worried,
I can behead every one of you.
Satou-san.
Why?
Finally...
Finally... Japan has started moving!
For that purpose, we...
For the future of ajin!
We’ve been giving our all!
I don’t care about any of that!
What’s important is whether it’s exciting or not.
Isn’t that why we’re fighting?
Satou-san.
There’s something wrong with you.
Presently,
the area within one kilometer of the bombed
prime minister’s official residence is under a blockade,
and life-threatening measures to protect against
chemical weapons are continuing.
This is bad. What should we do?
Get home, I guess.
The government has instructed all citizens to stay calm,
but signs of panic are appearing in every region.
You all go ahead.
I’ll watch the rear.
That fuck Satou,
he’s completely off his rocker.
Okuyama.
Are you sure about this?
It’s meaningless to play war games forever.
But..
what will you do now?
If Satou finds us,
he won’t let us off scot-free.
As for that, I have an idea.
Amidst continuing panic throughout Japan,
people are rioting, and hunts for ajin have begun,
putting the families of ajin at risk of harm as well.
Eh?
Already the families of ajins Tanaka and Nagai are under protection,
but the safety of Nagai Kei’s younger
sister Eriko is unknown,
and riots appear to be descending on the hospital
where she is receiving care.
Where’s Nagai Sister?
Where is she?
Let us in!
Out of the way!
Calm down!
Let us through!
Where is she?
She’s not here!
Find her!
Don't let her get away!
Eri!
Kei
Let’s go! Eri!
Don’t touch me!
Who’s fault is it?
Who do you think is to blame that
they’re after me?
Idiot! Be quiet!
Stop it!
What’s wrong with you?
Why did you come?
Here she is!
Hey, is that-
Nagai.
Ouch!
It’s Nagai Kei!
Come on, hurry up!
Should I yell?
But it would freeze Eri, too.
Hey! We got her!
Good for you!
Let’s get her!
This is an ajin hunt!
Kei!
Come out....
ghost!
Kai!
Come with me!
Shit.
This is bad!
Have you calmed down now?
Yes.
Mm.
Then, let’s go.
We can’t take you all the way to the police,
but we can drop you off close by.
But..
Wait.
Kei.
Run away with me.
Kai-san.
I saw it on the news.
Things are pretty hard, aren’t they?
Because of Satou and all them.
It’s not particularly...
It’s not related to you.
Hey, Kei!
Eri, be quiet.
But to talk to Kai-san that way?
Shut up!
Thanks to his senpai’s connections,
we can get away to India.
This time, let’s run away together.
You’re still thinking of that?
Is that weird?
I’m not
the same as I used to be.
Fighting was my only option,
and lots of people died in front of me.
It made it clear once more.
I have no need of spare emotions.
Only idiots get carried away by feelings!
Kei-
Kai, you should understand that!
You saved me, and I left you behind!
And that’s why you were in juvenile prison!
Maybe.
So, just leave me alone!
But, we’re friends.
Kei, you’re my friend.
You still...
think that way?
Of course I do.
You never change, do you.
Since we were kids...
You’ve never changed.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Ok.
Then, we’re decided on the plan
I mentioned earlier.
That guy,
he’s stupid.
Yeah,
you’re right.
He’s a total idiot.
He said you’d definitely go to where your sister was.
And so he’d definitely save you.
That’s what he insisted.
Even though you left him behind before.
There really is...
something wrong with him.
Hey...
Up to this point,
you-
I’ve done only what I had to,
and chosen only what I needed to
be a good person.
Even so,
a weird guy like him...
He’s my only friend.
What’s up with that?
Can I ask you a favor?
Eri... I’m sorry.
Eh?
It’s my fault you got in all this trouble.
Why are you apologizing now?
I’m really sorry.
It- It’s fine.
But when we were running away,
you should have kept quiet.
You were stupid to yell like that.
Huh?
That’s because you showed up out of nowhere!
Ah, Kai?
What is it?
I know this isn’t the best time, but...
I really need to take a piss.
All right, I’ll pull over.
Kei’s taking an awfully long time.
I’m going to look for him.
There’s no point.
It’s a long time for a piss.
He said to leave his sister to you.
What do you mean?
Kei...
You might be an idiot,
but your friend’s an idiot too.
Shut up.
He’s not an idiot.
You seem like you’re having an awful lot of fun.
Are they really that interesting?
Games.
The higher the difficulty level,
the better it feels when you clear the level.
Is it possible you did it on purpose?
Tempting them to turn them against you.
Tanaka-kun, that’s quite an interesting thing to say.
You thought if you did that,
your game would be more fun.
Well, it’s true that the fewer friends you have,
the more enemies there are to kill.
Satou-san,
you’re a huge idiot.
You’re not the person who I thought you were,
and I don’t understand what you’re thinking at all.
But-
The second player slot is open.
Tosaki-san.
You’d better rest.
It’s no problem.
Well, I never....
To challenge a fighter plane with a bamboo spear.
That’s our only choice in this situation.
You sound like Don Quixote.
Nagai!
Why did you come back?
Isn’t it obvious?
In order to stop Satou, you need me.
Don’t fuck with me!
Tosaki-san!
What can you do now?
I know you don’t trust me.
I don’t care about that.
But...
I will stop Satou.
That’s what I ought to do.
Target confirmed.
Enter the building.
It’s a trap!
To be continued...
Preview
Episode 25 will be aired immediately following, at 2:35 am.