Please come in.
Oh!
Why is Jabami Yumeko here?
Wait, I can't get distracted.
Oh my, please don't make such a scary face.
Try to enjoy the game.
Damn it!
This is like a dice game of sheer guesswork.
There's no skill involved.
3C - Nishinotouin Yuriko
2S - Saotome Mary
So why is the game so one-sided?
Unless I'm having an unbelievable stroke of bad luck, the only explanation is...
she's cheating!
I don't know how,
but she's definitely playing me, bit by bit.
In that case...
32 chips.
I'm going all in!
So it comes down to this, now.
That is fine.
Both players have confirmed.
I will now put in ten swords.
They're down!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
She fell for it!
Seven.
All that's left...
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
I see.
I'm concentrating my bets on five numbers.
I'll take the game in one fell swoop. She'll have no chance to cheat.
Time is up.
The betting is now complete.
We will now proceed.
Two, four, eight, sixteen, twenty-two.
I just need one of them. Please!
Reveal!
There's a twenty-two. Saotome won!
Oh dear. It landed on your number.
However, the verdict seems to be death.
My condolences.
What? Verdict?
Saotome didn't win?
Since twenty-two was stabbed by the sword, the verdict is death.
The wager is multipled by thirty, so as Saotome bet six chips,
the loss is 180 chips—18 million yen.
Counting all chips owed to Yuriko,
your balance is now -49,600,000 yen.
That is all.
Thank you for the game, Saotome.
I will inform you of the repayment process at a later date.
Someone please escort her out.
I'm done with her.
Saotome! You are disturbing
the other customers!
Don't touch me!
I could've paid the student council fee if I wanted to.
But that wouldn't have regained my social standing.
I shouldn't have played this game.
I shouldn't have been so fixated on my social status.
No. By far my biggest mistake...
was getting involved with this woman, Jabami Yumeko.
Saotome was desperate enough to play an official match?
Suzui, what is an official match?
Oh, right.
Playing official matches is the only right housepets have.
Housepets are able to challenge anyone they like, but only once.
As long as the wager is sensible,
these challenges cannot be refused.
Furthermore, housepets typically
challenge student council members.
That's why you'll sometimes see housepets making large bets,
hoping for a major upset.
Was that what Saotome was just doing?
Indeed it was.
Episode 3
Snake-Eyed Woman
Jabami Yumeko, correct?
Welcome to the Traditional Culture Research Society.
I serve as a student council member,
and also as president of this society.
My name is Nishinotouin Yuriko.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
What business do you have here?
Though do I really need to ask?
Would you like to play a game with me?
This is an original game,
invented by our society: Life or Death.
That sounds delightful!
I would love to play!
Life or Death.
We first place ten sword-shaped pieces into the cup and shuffle them on the board.
There are thirty numbered holes on the board.
We guess which holes the swords will land in and bet our chips accordingly.
In essence, it is similar to roulette and other such guessing games.
However, Life or Death has a fun rule.
If a sword is pointing upwards,
the verdict is life and you win
thirty times the amount you bet.
If a sword is pointing downwards,
the verdict is death and you lose thirty times the amount you bet.
In other words, you must pay your opponent.
There are also rules on how to bet.
Both players agree on how many chips
to bet for each game beforehand.
Within ten seconds of the dealer placing the cup down,
you place your chips on the
numbers you wish to bet on.
As such, we continue playing until either player runs out of chips
and the loser must pay the difference.
Now then, let us decide the wager.
It wouldn't be much fun to
play with small bets, though.
Yes, let us both wager 40 million yen.
Very well.
Now then, Yumeko, how many chips
would you like to bet on the first game?
Let me see...
I will bet ten chips first to test the waters.
Very well.
Both players have confirmed.
I will now put in ten swords.
They're down!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
This one!
Two.
One.
Zero.
Time is up.
The betting is now complete.
You seemed to be thinking very hard until the very last moment.
Did you figure something out?
Indeed.
The cup is ever so slightly wider on the top.
That means there is a higher chance of the swords landing on the smaller numbers in the middle.
Even though the swords
may land on life or death,
it's no fun if you do not
bet on the right numbers.
I am not a very patient person, after all.
I pray that that does not cost you.
We will now proceed.
Reveal!
Life on 17.
Death on 30.
Yumeko didn't bet on either of them.
What about Nishinotouin?
That was close!
She was just one number off!
30 million yen changes hands with just one chip on the right number!
No swords landed in nominated holes,
so neither player incurs a loss.
I was very close.
Well, let us play the next round.
You're killing me, Yumeko!
You should stop playing such crazy bets—
There is no need to worry, Suzui.
This much money is hardly enough for me to regret losing.
Huh?
In fact, this game is fun because
the exchange of chips is so volatile.
It would be a waste to quit halfway through.
Suzui, was it?
Y-Yes?
If you felt unimaginable amounts of money
change hands with a single shake of the cup,
I'm sure you too would understand.
Isn't that so, Yumeko?
Indeed.
I'm afraid I might become addicted to it.
Though, Nishinotouin,
your methods are despicable.
Excuse me?
Did you not hear me?
I said you are despicable.
I'm sure you were the one who proposed playing this game
when Saotome challenged you to an official match earlier.
If Saotome was only playing to restore her honour,
she would not have needed to play a game
with such vast potential losses.
To give a glimmer of hope to people at rock bottom and then drive them even further into despair...
You are no different to an underworld loan shark.
I do not know how good you are at gambling,
but as a human, you are the lowest of the low.
Much like a piece of shit.
Y-You insolent woman!
Yuriko, please have her escorted ou—
What is the matter, Kumagusu?
That was but some trifling jesting.
Right.
Ah, in any case, this was quite unfortunate.
I was sure a sword would
land on two, four, or ten,
but that doesn't seem to be the case.
Why two, four or ten?
I am a big fan of wordplay.
If you break up "Nishinotouin",
you get "two, four and ten in", do you not?
Do you not think about such occurrences?
Please do not disrespect my name.
Nishinotouin is an honourable family name
dating back to ancient Kyoto—
And if you consider the even numbers, six and eight are missing!
They are missing!
Just like how there is a screw missing in your head!
What a coincidence! Right, Suzui?
That's enough, you—
I'm surprised.
You are just as much fun as the president said you would be.
Oh dear, it is quite embarrassing to be praised like this.
Now then, let us continue.
How much would you like to bet?
Forty chips. I would like to go all in.
Your resolve is impressive.
Kumagusu?
B-Both players have confirmed.
I will now put in ten swords.
They're down!
Ten.
Simply winning would not be enough to cleanse my spirit.
Nine.
Eight.
Stress is the greatest enemy of beauty, after all.
Life or Death...
As the name implies, I'll have the honour of taking your life!
Five chips each on eight numbers!
She wouldn't bet so heavily if she only
wanted to bring Yumeko's balance to zero.
She's definitely pissed off!
Yumeko shouldn't have provoked her!
Two.
One.
Ze—
Nishinotouin, I apologise if I offended you in any way by what I said earlier.
I was simply saying whatever came to mind so I could bet everything on this number,
so please do not hold it against me.
Wh-Why?
Why, you ask?
Well, of course, it is because you are cheating.
She's cheating?
Indeed. Please look at the dealer's right hand.
Does she not appear to have moles?
You're right.
The person who showed us to the room also had something similar on her hand.
What does that mean?
Those moles are not natural.
I am sure they are piercings.
To have society members inflict bodily self-harm
just so you could cheat on this game...
You have some delightful methods indeed.
I dare say one of the swords is magnetic.
Since the dealer has metal in her hand,
she can control how the sword will land.
All she needs to do is slide her hand around the side of the cup
and she can place the sword down
wherever she likes, even in plain sight.
So you provoked her earlier to make sure she would cheat this round?
Wait!
I have not once bet on a correct number since you arrived.
Even in the previous game, your friend placed her bets after the cup had been let down.
How can you say I have been cheating despite this?
The best part of this trick is that you won't win hundred percent of the time.
It would take quite some dexterity for the dealer to land the sword exactly where she wants.
There could also be other swords blocking the holes, and more importantly,
since only one sword is controlled,
the positions of the others are luck of the draw.
The actual success rate does not amount to much, does it?
That was why Saotome was unable to see through the trick.
It is an unreliable trick,
but that is all you need for your purposes.
I am sure you bring great
sums of money to the table,
being both president of the
Traditional Culture Research Society
and also a member of the student council.
You do not need to win every single game.
All you need is a slight advantage over your opponent.
If you play enough, you will
slowly but surely make a profit.
In the heart of this trick lies not your cunning, but your financial muscle.
I'm sure losing tens of millions of yen is but a drop in the ocean for you.
However, I am betting all of my assets!
The stakes are completely uneven!
This is not a fair game!
Let us both feel the same fear.
I am betting forty chips.
If a sword lands on my number and the verdict is life,
you would lose 2 billion, 170 million yen.
You could lose that much money in just one game.
It is truly life or death.
Now...
Now, now, now...
Now!
Now...
Now!!
Let's lose ourselves gambling!
Look, it's time!
Come! Please reveal the board!
Y-Yuriko!
If I lose, I'm down 2 billion, 170 million yen.
Even I wouldn't be able to prepare that much money.
I could use the money the society has been collecting,
but if I don't make it back, I'll be
kicked out of the student council for sure!
I can only keep the society operating and its members from becoming housepets
because I'm a student council member.
If I lose my position, everything will be ruined.
Completely ruined!
I-I have to negotiate with her.
The swords haven't been revealed.
I still have time!
Y-Yumeko?
Excuse us.
M-Miss President! Why are you here?
This looks like quite the interesting development.
The stakes are high so we definitely want to avoid any trouble.
I will be the arbiter for this game.
Y-You do not need to trouble yourself over this.
I can handle something this trivial on my ow—
Shut up and reveal the board.
You're white as a sheet, Yuriko! Are you okay?
Yuriko!
We will now proceed.
Reveal!
Life on ten and death on seven!
I coincidentally bet on seven.
Moreover, a sword didn't land on twenty-four!
The verdict is life for Yuriko who bet five chips,
which brings her total to 195 chips.
This leaves Jabami at minus 115 chips.
Yuriko wins at 310 million yen.
The game is over!
Y-You're kidding!
Yumeko lost?
I didn't think you'd actually win that one.
You're quite lucky, aren't you, Yuriko?
I'm impressed.
On the other hand,
it was quite unfortunate for you.
You tried your hardest but you were unlucky in the end.
Was this a bear-in-the-hole play?
I must admit my defeat.
Well, who knows?
Bear-in-the-hole is an old trick used in similar dice games.
You start by making a small hole in the floor of the room.
Then you play over the hole, but you cover it with a white sheet so that the hole cannot be seen.
Japanese houses have a space under the floor,
so you have an accomplice hide down there.
The accomplice would use something like a candle to see the dice through the sheet
and then move the dice with a needle if the roll needed to be changed.
Just like that, it becomes a victory for the bookmaker.
I would hazard to say Miss President used a magnet
to do something similar just now.
She used an opposing magnet to force the sword out of the twenty-four hole.
Though from the look of things,
it appears Nishinotouin was not informed of this.
It was coincidence that a sword landed in a hole she bet on.
Truly a stroke of good luck.
But doesn't that only work if you're in a Japanese-style house with space under the floor?
You could make plenty of space above this room.
All you need to do is have the building constructed as such.
In fact, it is possible that Miss President had
the building altered solely for that one game!
N-No way!
How wonderful would it be
if that were the case?
Normally you would not even consider doing something like that,
and certainly would not go through with it.
You would have to be mad.
This academy—no, the student council president is even more than I imagined.
Oh, I know!
I want to gamble with the president!
stupid
psycho
retard
ugly
gross
worthless
idiot
not surprised
bitch
get lost!
kys
Kitty! Kitty! Kitty!
Kitty
Bottom Rank, Rank 1
Student with uncooperative tendencies
Jabami...
I heard you gambled with someone from the student council yesterday.
Yes, but I ended up losing.
Yeah, I heard that too.
That's why we're here.
Oh my, thank you for y—
What's this housepet think it's saying?
We came to laugh at you!
Who would be concerned about a kitty?
Your filth is gonna rub off on me!
Oh, I see. You refer to female housepets as Kitty, so we are cats, then?
Cats are the cutest, are they not?
Meow, meow!
I'm a gambling-addicted cat, meow!
I carelessly challenged someone from the student council and racked up a 300 million yen debt, meow!
How will I ever get my money back, meow?
I want to gamble more and more, meow.
I wonder if anyone would be my patron, meow.
Wh-What's wrong with her?
Sh-She's messed up!
L-Let's get out of here!
Y-Yumeko?
Wh-What are you doing?
Those girls did not have
much of a sense of humour,
did they, meow, Suzui?
I-I get it, so would you—
Oh, this is kind of fun.
Perhaps I should wear a tail as well?
Please stop.
Good morning, everyone.
Morning!
Looks like Yuriko isn't coming.
That's no surprise after being exposed miserably.
Even though she won!
Good morning, Sayaka.
Good morning, Miss President.
Here are the programmes for
Jabami Yumeko and Saotome Mary.
As a substitute for your debt—
Don't fuck with me!
I heard you became a housepet.
Wow, that's lucky!
No matter what anyone says—
I'll shoot!
I simply can't get enough of this feeling.
Episode 4
The Woman Who
Became a Housepet