When I was a child, I thought I'd become
an adventurer when I grew up.
I'd leave my village and defeat the evil
monsters that were tormenting the villagers.
Eventually, I'd become powerful
enough to defeat even dragons.
I'd become a hero,
a platinum-ranked adventurer.
O-Once this is over,
the three of us are going back to
the village and going to a festival!
Everyone's in the same boat!
We all have someone dear to us
and things we want to do.
To ensure that even small
wishes like that come true...
We can't lose!
We have to save the world!
Even if I couldn't become a hero...
I thought I'd be able to
become an adventurer.
If only I were able to leave my older sister,
who had raised me all on her own, behind...
I'm gonna go to the city!
I'm gonna go to my uncle's farm and
help one of the cows give birth.
And once I'm done helping,
I can go shopping in the city.
My mom gave me some money.
I wonder what I should buy.
Is there anything you want?
I'll buy you something.
No.
There must be something. I mean—
I told you, I don't want anything.
Why do you have to say it like that?
I just wanted to buy you something
since you've never been to the city...
Shut up! Just go to the city or wherever!
Why are you getting mad?
I'm not mad!
Yes, you are!
You must've been envious
that she was going to the city.
Still, you shouldn't have acted like that.
You have to protect girls.
Did you know...
that if you envy others, you become a goblin?
A goblin?
Yes. If all you ever do is dwell
on the things you don't have,
your heart and body warp
into something unsightly,
and you start trying to take
things from others by force.
So, later on,
let's make sure you apologize to her, okay?
That night, my sister made my favorite
stew with chicken and milk.
It was so delicious, I ate bowl after bowl,
but now I can't even remember
how that stew tasted.
I'm sure...
it's because I haven't
eaten it since that day.
Dozing
Morning!
Hey.
It looks like today's going to be a hot one.
I guess that's no surprise.
It's summer, after all.
Yeah.
I'm starving!
I think my uncle is awake,
so let's have breakfast!
All right.
Good morning, sir.
Morning. Were you doing your usual patrols?
Yes, sir. There were no issues.
I really don't think you
need to worry so much.
I heard that the Demon Lord
was defeated by the Hero.
I'm sure the monsters will calm down a—
They won't.
At least, goblins won't.
O-Oh, yeah?
Yes.
Oh, sorry. It took a little
longer than I thought it would.
I'll lay everything out now, so let's eat.
After breakfast, I have
to go make deliveries.
I'll go, too. I have to stop by the guild.
Okay! Let's go together.
Are you going to the city to accept a quest?
That, too, but I also need to get my gear
repaired and pick up my other set of armor.
I see.
Don't do anything rash.
I don't want to see her hurt.
I'll do my best.
You need to stop by the guild, right?
Yeah.
After I'm done with my deliveries,
there's something I want to buy,
so let's meet up later to head home.
Okay.
Hey, you.
You sure are pasty for
someone who's so ripped.
I haven't seen you around before. You new?
No.
So... you're just dropping in
on a day off or something?
Something like that.
Yeah, if you actually wanted to make
money as an adventurer right now,
you'd go to the capital.
A lot of the Demon Lord's army is still there.
They're just stragglers, so they'd be
easy to take care of for good pay.
You're not going?
Me? You can't be serious.
Bullying the weak isn't my style.
I only fight for myself.
I've got no interest in money or peace.
Besides...
Yes, all right.
I'll listen to all of your concerns,
so form a single file line, please.
I've got personal reasons.
Basically, I have no need for catchy slogans.
Is that how it is?
It sure is.
Well, see ya. I've got some
ruins that need exploring.
Wish me luck in battle.
I shall.
The stoic type, eh?
I don't mind that, though.
There aren't any... quests.
I see.
I had some extra time,
so I fixed the smaller bits, too.
How's it feel?
It's fine.
And now to repair this...
For crying out loud...
How'd your armor get so damaged
just from fighting goblins?
Were you able to get me a scroll?
Those things are hard to come by.
Keep yer shirt on.
All right.
Hey, boss. That guy's a
silver-ranked adventurer, right?
Yeah, that's what I've heard, at least.
Why does he wear all that armor?
If he wanted to be quieter,
wouldn't mithril chainmail be better?
You don't get it?
I can't say I do... I mean,
he'd be better off with a
magical sword than a scroll...
Only a munchkin would wave around a
legendary magical sword at some goblins.
He knows exactly what he's doing.
Ow!
Come on, what's the matter?!
You won't even be able to
kill goblins at that rate!
Damn it! We're going for the opening!
Go around the right!
You got it!
That sounds like a great plan, but...
You probably shouldn't say it out loud.
You're too naïve!
Oh, hey, Goblin Slayer.
I heard you almost died in Water Town.
Yeah.
By the way, are you always dressed like that?
I see...
I didn't think that warrior
was part of your group.
Ah... We were sparring with our little brat,
and we saw him staring the whole time.
An adventurer's skill with the
sword is mostly self-taught.
If you learn actual swordsmanship at least
once, you'll have a chance to survive.
Now, then...
I need to teach those girls
a bit about survival, too.
I'm sure that giant ball of energy
is starting to lose his breath.
I guess I'll join in.
Have at you!
You're always bragging
about how mighty you are,
so I'm sure you'd consider this fair game.
What?! And you call yourself
a paladin candidate?!
That's enough talk!
This isn't effective training for anyone!
We're...
We're saved...
You sure aren't holding back, are you?
Goblin Slayer!
So you're here.
Yeah. My armor needed some repairs.
You should've said something.
I didn't really need to.
How's your shoulder doing?
Huh? O-Oh, it's fine now.
They cast a healing spell on me.
I see.
Yes!
Goblin Slayer. How'd the
quest at Water Town go?
It's been taken care of.
There weren't any problems.
What are you talking about?! You almost died!
What?! A-Are you okay now?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Did you have your wounds properly tended to?
Yeah, I did.
Is something wrong?
N-No. Nothing at all...
What did you need?
Do you have a quest for me?
No, not exactly...
An adventurer from Water Town asked
me to give this letter to you.
Thanks.
No problem. It's part of my job.
Do you have an acquaintance in Water Town?
No.
It's probably from the one
who requested the job.
Oh, that makes sense.
The one who requested the job?
The Sword Maiden wrote
Goblin Slayer a letter?
But why?
Well, if it isn't Beard-cutter!
You should've at least come to
say hi if you were here, Orcbolg!
Ah, it's a relief that your armor seems to
have been repaired, Sir Goblin Slayer.
Yeah.
We're about to go get some food.
Want to join us, Beard-cutter?
You should come, too.
S-Sure.
Oh, uh, I...
I'd love to!
I'll pass.
Aw, don't be shy!
I'm not.
Come on! Let's go, Orcbolg.
Sorry to keep you waiting...
Hey.
My, you've got a lot of friends...
Yeah.
How amusing.
Jeez, if you were waiting for someone,
you should've just told us!
You're the one who forced
Beard-cutter to come.
Well, I didn't know, okay?
Um, is it really okay
for me to join you all?
It's fine.
Please, help yourself, young lady.
Yes. Food always tastes better
when you eat in a big group.
Then I guess I'll dig in.
This is great, too.
Hey, is the rumor that the Hero
defeated the Demon Lord true?
Yes, it is! We've received
word from the capital.
Apparently the Hero became the tenth
platinum-ranked adventurer in history!
That's splendid. Now we can all rest easy.
I'm sure there's quite a celebration
going on in the capital right now.
Guess we should start celebrating ourselves.
Like you need an excuse to drink.
Jeez... Maybe I should've
gone to the capital, too.
It's not as big as the one in the capital,
but we also have a harvest festival.
A harvest festival, huh?
Join me for a drink, Beard-cutter.
No, I'm going to pass today.
Why not have a taste of this, then?
Wow, it's so good!
It is.
It has lemon and honey in it.
Apparently it helps with fatigue.
I see. Maybe I should consider carrying
some with me on my adventures.
Now that training's over, it's time to eat!
It's all on me! Eat up!
Thanks for the grub!
Sounds like they've been training all morning.
Applying oneself to one's craft is a fine thing.
There have been talks recently
about opening up a training hall.
They want to hire retired adventurers.
There are so many newcomers
who really don't know anything.
Yeah...
The more they know, the more
likely they are to come back alive.
It'll give them confidence, too.
Not to mention that even
when adventurers retire,
they'll continue to live until they die.
So I think it's beneficial to everyone.
I see.
So you need to be more
careful, Goblin Slayer.
Yup, yup.
Otherwise, I won't give you any more quests.
The next time you collapse,
no more adventures for six months.
Yup. No adventuring allowed.
That would be bad.
Right?
So make sure you take
better care of yourself.
All your friends are such nice people.
Are they?
"Are they"? You mean they aren't?
They're skilled.
I have a higher probability of
crushing goblins if I'm in a party.
Someday...
What?
Oh... It's nothing.
I see.
Yeah.
Dear Goblin Slayer.
How are you doing in these hard times,
where the fire spirit continues its dance?
Under normal circumstances,
I would have sent a letter
of gratitude much sooner,
but I told myself that
I shouldn't trouble you.
Please forgive me.
By some miracle, ever since that night,
the goblins have stopped
plaguing my dreams,
and I've been living peacefully.
This is all thanks to you and your comrades.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
The Demon Lord has been
defeated by the Hero,
which should lead the world toward peace.
But many of the Demon
Lord's army still remain,
so we mustn't let down our guard yet.
I believe that the adventurers
will have to continue their fight,
but I am always praying for your safety.
Sincerely, the Sword Maiden. Sending prayers.
Ugh! You're so loud, and you
never know when to quit!
That's it! I've had enough!
Let's finish this, dwarf!
You've got some guts, long-ears.
Don't worry, I'll go easy on ya.
I'm gonna have my fire wine,
and you can have regular ol' wine.
What do ya say?
Bring it on!
U-Um...
The wise never court danger, milady.
Bring me more!
Come on! Pour me another!
All right!
What's this? Looks like you're having fun.
Place some... bets?
I'm betting on the girl. Three gold pieces.
Well, aren't you confident?
You sure you can afford that?
I'm going for the jackpot.
I'm disciplined, righteous, and have
the protection of the gods.
Wouldn't the Supreme God be against gambling?
I'm betting on the dwarf!
Then I'm betting on the elf!
Hey! That's all of our earnings from today!
Um... Are you sure we shouldn't stop them?
It won't take many more drinks
before Sir Mage wins...
Or so I'd like to say,
but Lady Ranger is also stubborn.
There's just no way to tell yet.
You say that like this isn't our problem...
Next! I'm nowhere near done!
Drink up!
One more!
What's the matter?
I came to tell you that dinner's ready,
and I wanted to know what
you were thinking about.
About the future.
The future?
Yeah.
I see.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Oh, nothing. Nothing at all.
You're strange.
You'll get grease all over you.
It's fine.
I needed to do laundry, anyway.
And I'll take a bath.
I see.
Yup.
Let's take our time, you know,
thinking about the future.
Take our time?
Yup. There's no need to rush.
Yeah, you're right.
The future, huh...
Not to mention that even
when adventurers retire,
they'll continue to live until they die.
So I think it's beneficial to everyone.
People get old and get hurt.
When they're tired, they collapse.
Eventually, everyone reaches their limit,
whether it be an adventurer or a hero.
Even if he doesn't die,
there'll come a day when he'll
no longer be able to slay goblins.
These days won't last forever.
And when that day comes, what can he do?
What should he do?
He probably doesn't have the answer.
Actually, no one has the answer...
No one has the answer.