I want to be an adventurer!
Can you read and write?
Yes, I learned how at the temple.
Then please fill this out.
How was dealing with the
manticore at the pass?
It wasn't too bad.
The Fate of Particular Adventurers
Hey, I heard that a demon lord
appeared in the capital,
and it's the perfect time to head
over there to earn some coin.
I'm sure I could at least
handle a low-level demon.
So you're fifteen and
your job is a priestess.
Yes.
I'm an adult now, so I wanted
to help other adventurers.
This will act as your ID in the guild.
There are ten ranks of adventurers,
and platinum is the highest rank.
Next is gold,
but the highest-ranked out in
the field would be the silvers.
Your identification tag shows
that your rank is porcelain,
the lowest rank for adventurers.
So I'm a beginner.
Yes.
It will also help identify you if
something were to happen to you,
so make sure not to lose it.
Yes, ma'am.
And that ends your registration.
You can find quests on the board there.
Please go ahead and find one
suitable for your rank.
Or you could join a veteran
adventurer's party and—
Hey, wanna go adventuring with us?
Huh?
You're a priestess, right?
My party's missing a priest,
but we've got an urgent quest to do,
so we were looking for
at least one more person.
Would you come with us?
An urgent quest?
We're gonna go slay some goblins.
Goblins?
Yeah, they attacked a village,
stole supplies and livestock,
and even kidnapped some girls.
We need to hurry up and save them.
Um... You're all porcelain-ranked, right?
I'm sure if you wait a little while,
other adventurers will show up...
With the four of us, we shouldn't have
any trouble dealing with goblins.
Right?
Come with us.
Make up your mind already.
Okay. If you think that I can help you.
All right! We can finally go on an adventure!
Yeah! It's great to have you!
Welcome aboard!
Now slaying goblins will be a breeze!
Calm down.
Well, if things get hairy,
I'll take care of it!
Um... Are you sure we should
suddenly barge in here?
Maybe we should go back
and prepare a bit more...
Huh? We've come this far,
and you bring that up now?
You're such a worrywart.
Goblins are as small as children,
and just as dumb, too.
They're the weakest
monsters you can run into.
I even managed to chase away some
that came to my village once!
That's not even worth bragging about.
I'm sure we'd be able to handle things,
even if we ran into like a dragon!
You're getting ahead of yourself,
but yeah, we'll eventually get there.
One day, I'm gonna be a dragon slayer!
Wh-Whoa!
Even if that idiot can't cut them all down,
I'll beat them down with my bare hands.
Don't you worry.
Besides, she's a wizard who graduated
from the Sages' Academy in the capital.
Okay, that's enough talking. Let's go.
Do any of you have any potions?
Nope!
We didn't have the time or
money to do any shopping.
Huh?
Besides, I'm worried about
those kidnapped girls.
And if we do get hurt, you'll heal us, right?
I do have the miracles of
healing and light, but...
I can only use them three times...
Hold up!
What the heck is this?
There was one at the entrance, too.
Was there?
O merciful Earth Mother,
please provide us protection
as we step into the darkness.
Come on, we're falling behind.
The other two ran ahead.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter now?
I thought I just heard a sound...
From where?
From behind us, I think...
We've only come straight from the entrance.
There's no way they'd be behind—
Goblins!
Sagitta... inflammarae... radius!
Firebolt!
I got one!
Sagitta inflammarae radius!
G-Give that back!
Get away from her!
Curse you, goblins! How dare you?!
Over here!
Take that!
Hurry and perform a healing miracle on her!
Of course!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please lay your revered hand
upon this child's wounds!
Heal!
Take that! And that!
Stop swinging that thing around!
I can't get closer!
You protect the other two!
I'll take care of these!
What's the matter, goblins?!
You bastard!
You're in my way!
Why? I used Heal, but she's
not getting any better...
You two, run!
B-But...
Ow...
R... Run....
I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me! Are you all right?
Wh-Why...
O... merciful... Earth Mother...
That's one...
And that makes two.
Um... Who are you?
Goblin Slayer.
Goblin Slayer?
He's a silver?
Are you a rookie?
Y-Yes...
I see you can talk. You're lucky.
Drink this. It'll help with the pain.
U-Um... P-Please, give it to her...
Give up on her.
She's been poisoned.
P-Poisoned?
I have an antidote, but it's too late.
Kill... me...
All right.
We might've been able to save her!
You'd only make her suffer more.
Drink.
Did you see a bigger one somewhere?
I believe so.
But...
That was a hobgoblin. Maybe they
took on a wanderer as a guard.
I'm going to go kill some goblins.
What are you going to do?
I'll go... with you...
What can you use?
I can use Heal and Holy Light.
How many times?
Three times... So I have two uses left.
All right.
What are you doing?
We have to get rid of our scents.
Get used to the smell of blood.
All right...
Eight, nine...
This is too long to swing
around in this cave.
How did this happen?
Were you attacked by a horde from behind?
Huh?
But... when we went through...
In a dark cave, if all you have is a torch,
you wouldn't notice the
shadows along the cave walls.
That over there would
catch your eye first.
It's a common mistake that rookies make.
Listen, they're not bright creatures,
but they aren't complete fools.
This horde is being led by a shaman.
A shaman?
They're powerful spell casters.
How many were in your party?
Four...
Is the last one a woman?
Looks like they dragged her in deeper.
We have to save her!
Ten.
Can you see in the dark, too?
Of course not. I just practiced.
I always aim for where their necks would be.
Practiced? How much did you practice?
A lot.
What about your sword?
It's useless now. Too much blood on it.
That was a scout. This is the right way.
Let's go.
Y-Yes, sir...
Use Holy Light from here.
Once you do, get back to
the entrance immediately.
All right...
Let's go.
O merciful Earth Mother, please bless us,
the wanderers in the
darkness, with holy light!
Holy Light!
Six. One hob and one shaman.
Eight remaining.
Fall back!
O-Okay...
Do it.
O merciful Earth Mother, please bless us,
the wanderers in the
darkness, with holy light!
Eleven.
Th-There are more coming!
But I can't use any more...
I know.
See ya.
Twelve, thirteen...
What was that?
Gasoline that I bought from an alchemist.
Wasn't very effective, for the amount it cost.
B-But inside... The kidnapped girls...
The flames won't spread too far
with just two or three corpses.
They won't die.
Are you going in again?
No.
They probably have no idea that
I'm waiting out here for them.
It's okay...
You're okay now.
Now, then... As I thought...
Eighteen.
The high-leveled ones are tough.
What's this?
Children?
They multiply fast.
If we had waited any longer,
there'd be about fifty of them,
and they would've attacked.
You were lucky.
Are you going to kill them?
Of course I am.
They hold on to grudges for life.
And the survivors of the nest learn
from their mistakes and adapt.
There isn't a single reason to let them live.
Even if there was a good goblin?
A good goblin? I guess there might
be one if you looked really hard.
But in the end, the only good goblins are
the ones who never come out of their holes.
That makes twenty-two.
They say it's a common occurrence.
Goblins attacking a village
and kidnapping girls...
A party of rookie adventurers
going out to slay some goblins
only to end up slaughtered...
Rescued girls joining temples due
to their despair after being treated
as the goblins' playthings...
An adventurer losing all of their comrades and
going home, never to be heard from again...
All these things happen
quite often in this world.
But is that really true?
I don't have the answer.
In the end, there are only
two things I'm certain of.
The first is that I'm still an adventurer.
The other...
H-Hello, Goblin Slayer.
Um, I bought some armor,
just as you instructed.
It's chain mail.
I see.
Um... Are you going again today?
I'm slaying goblins again.
Are you coming?
Yes!
Next Time
Goblin Slayer