Ack!
Morning
Yo, Amano.
M-Morning, Uehara-kun.
That free game by that Nobe
person was boring as hell.
I thought you said it was good.
No way! You actually played it?
How was it?
In the beginning, yeah, it was
a horror exploration game,
and it had me excited about all
the mysteries and foreshadowing.
I wasn't sure what to think about it
becoming a fishing game halfway through,
but since you were the one
who recommended it to me,
I figured it was worth powering through.
And yet...
The ending was just some dude
who caught a black bass,
Black bass
posing proudly in front of a fish print!
What the hell is that?!
I know! Nobe-san's games
are all great, aren't they?
In what way?
Your tastes are way too sophisticated.
That game's a total flop.
Sorry.
I actually think Nobe-san's games suck, too.
But they have, like, this
inexplicable charm about them.
I really don't get it.
For example... I know.
It's like falling in love.
It's not rational.
You're a virgin, and you're saying
that to a guy with a girlfriend.
That's not the point!
Sure, you have a girlfriend, but...
What, now?
N-Never mind that. What about you and Tendou?
What about Tendou-san?
Don't you see her often,
after what happened?
I'm actually a little bummed
by how little contact we have.
Uh, dude, are serious when you say that?
Yeah.
I mean, I see her in the
corner of my eye sometimes.
Never mind.
That's kind of amusing, too.
Just be careful not to pass each other by
so much that you completely lose touch.
Yeah.
Pass each other by?
You mean the 3DS thing?
Yeah, StreetPass...
No, damn it!
Mono-san is
requesting assistance.
Accept
Decline
Sorry, Uehara-kun,
do you mind if I play for a bit?
Fine.
Tsucchie
Why is your nickname "Tsucchie"?
I like using a name that isn't
like my own when I'm online.
My mom's maiden name is
Tsuchiyama, so I'm Tsucchie.
I use Yama-san sometimes, too.
Lame. I was expecting a cooler reason.
Shut up!
What about that "MONO" there?
Oh, Mono-san?
We've been friends since
I started playing this game.
I feel strangely close to this person.
It's kind of exciting communicating with
someone whose face you've never seen, isn't it?
Looks like you're going to need some rehab
before I can enjoy your rom-com.
Huh?
Rom-com?
Me and who?
With Tendou.
You're not going to get anywhere at this rate.
Th-That's true. I'm not even
a tick compared to Tendou-san.
Oh, no, I'm not trying to make you sad.
By rehab, I mean I want to help you
level up from being in loner mode.
Uehara-kun!
You care about me that much?
All right.
So why don't we start talking to some chicks
who like the same kinds of games you do?
Yeah?
Travel to school
Morning Homeroom
Period 1
Period 2
Period 3
Period 4
Lunch break
Period 5
Period 6
Homeroom
After School
All right. She's your target.
Her name is Hoshinomori Chiaki.
She's supposed to be a gaming
otaku loner, just like you.
N-No way.
Why should I have to quasi-hit on someone?
Just do it!
Get straight to brass tacks!
Brass tacks?!
Just go!
Tasuku!
Weren't you going to hang out with me today?
Oh, right.
Sorry.
All right, Amano. I'll be
waiting to hear how it went.
You'd better go talk to Hoshinomori!
Did I do something to deserve this?
They're totally staring at me!
I wonder what's wrong with Tendou-san.
Huh? Amano-kun?
What's up?
Are you here to see Tendou-san?
N-No, I'm not.
I'm not interested in Tendou-san,
nor do I have any business with her.
Oh, yeah?
So what brings you to Class A?
I'm here to see another girl
today, not Tendou-san.
Whoosh...
All right.
Um, pardon me...
She's completely focused.
Huh?
This game...
Ahem.
T-Tendou-san!
L-Long time no see, Amano-kun.
L-Long time no see.
What brings you to Class A?
Um...
I'm here to, well... see a girl.
I-I see.
Oh, I know! knowing you,
it's probably something managerial,
like class representative stuff.
Huh? Oh, no, that's not it.
Just do it! Get straight to brass tacks!
Brass tacks...
Oh, right!
I worked up the courage to come to Class A
so I could become friends with this lady.
What's wrong, Tendou-san?
No, no, now's not the time for that!
S... S...
S?
S... S... S...
Sleazeball!
Tendou-san!
Sorry, Amano-kun.
S-Sleazeball?
Oh, right, Hoshinomori-san...
Wh-Who are you?
I... e-er...
Th-That...
That game... It's Aegis VIII, isn't it?
It came out last week.
This is a little late,
but I'm Amano Keita, from Class F.
Amano-san, huh?
Do you like games, too, Hoshinomori-san?
Yes.
The conversation's dead.
Um...
You're from the game club, aren't you?
I'm sorry, I still have no interest
in joining the game club.
W-Wait a second.
I'm not in the game club.
I've been invited, but...
Wait, you were invited, too?
Yes.
Tendou-san invited me,
so I went to watch, but...
But the club's activities weren't really
what you had in mind as a gamer?
Yes, yes!
The game club is definitely awesome,
but they're way too glamorous for us.
Yes, yes!
I like gaming with people,
and I compete, too,
but it's not like I want to be
the best at a game or anything.
I get that!
But the game club is definitely a proper club.
So I felt bad for Tendou-san, but...
But...
Games are our lifeline,
and we can't make any compromises!
Right!
Before we knew it, Hoshinomori-san and I
were a little more comfortable
with each other.
Message from
Hoshinomori Chiaki
It turns out that the two of us were more
alike than Uehara-kun had expected.
So, what kind of games
do you like, Amano-san?
You can call me Keita
You can call me
Chiaki too, Keita
The more we talked to each other,
I'm not too picky
I also like really chill games that
feel more like productivity apps
the more I realized that our tastes
and sensibilities were the same.
Me too
It's important to be able to
just zone out and enjoy it.
Especially when it comes to games,
the games we've played in the past,
our ideals, our gaming styles...
Aye, but that doesn't necessarily
mean I like only easy games
I like hard games, too
Like RTS games, foreign
hack-and-slash games, FPS games...
We were practically mirror
images of each other.
I know
Even though I'm pretty bad at them
I'm not good, either
Oh, yeah, you like the Aegis series, right?
Yes!
Yeah, they're all masterpieces, huh?
Yes, yes!
The best thing about it is...
Especially...
...the characters!
...the music!
Except for one thing.
You got in a huge fight?
We had a difference in philosophies.
What?
I thought Hoshinomori
was a game-loving loner.
Yeah.
We got along really well, I guess.
She was a lot less condescending and more
like a friend to me than you, Uehara-kun.
I love you, Uehara-kun!
So why did you get in a fight?
If you two get along, what's the problem?
You wouldn't have let that slide, either!
Let what slide?
Chiaki says games don't need moe characters!
What are you, mental?
I don't care if she's a girl. I can never
concede when it comes to video games!
Dude...
All right, fine.
You finally made a gaming buddy.
Let's talk it over calmly later.
What?!
Are you serious, Keita?
Think of the Japanese game industry
that's taken moe too far,
compared to the foreign game industry
that's focused on gameplay and story.
Isn't it obvious which one's
got more momentum?
Th-That's the problem with you,
you narrow-minded shrimp.
H-Hang on a second, then, Chiaki-san!
Have you never played a foreign game and
thought, "Now, if only the girls were cute"?
Y-You... seaweed head!
What?!
Wait, wait, wait.
Where did that come from?
Why can't you just get along?
Y-Yes, you're right, Uehara-san.
So you'll develop a crush on good-looking guys,
but you won't accept moe, Chiaki?
Th-That's not true!
Fighting over video games is one thing,
but attacking each other's
appearances isn't good.
Amano is a virgin shrimp, though.
Hey.
So, weren't you talking about how
far you've gotten in Aegis VIII?
Oh, yeah. So how far did you get, Chiaki?
U-Um, well...
I got to the elven hideout.
Hey, that's where I am, too!
That map is one of the
best in the series, isn't it?
Yes, yes!
You never get to see a map
that's so sublime and fantastic.
I know!
And it has a way of showing off
that it's a camp of human-haters.
It really is expressive.
Yeah, yeah!
And what really tops it off is the beautiful...
But the one thing that I have to say
ruins it is the disgusting moe...
...graphic of the elf posing!
Huh?!
Seriously, why can't you stop there?
You don't get it, Uehara-kun.
We're lonely gamers with
nothing but our inflated egos.
We can't compromise
when it comes to games!
Keita's right.
There's a line that we can't cross,
even as lonely gamers.
You guys are too much work.
She's got some aura.
Let's call it a day.
Sorry to call you out for this, Hoshinomori.
N-No, not at all. It's fine.
I had fun listening to you
talk about video games.
Who cares if you have seaweed for hair?
I actually like girls with
naturally messy hair.
Huh?
R-R-Really?
I think Aguri-san might have the wrong idea.
So, come on. We're finally gamer buddies.
Let's be nicer to each other.
I-I'll make an effort.
This scene does look like Uehara-kun
is making a move on another woman.
Oh, yeah. I like your hair as it is now,
but I think you'd look even
better with shorter hair.
D-Do you think so?
Yeah.
I mean, you've got what it
takes to be cute as heck.
He could end up with hell
to pay for that comment.
A-Aguri-san...
Huh?
Misumi-kun, what's the relationship
between Hoshinomori-san and Amano-kun?
I don't really know, but they seem
to get along really well, those two.
Do they get along really well?
That is what's happening?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
She's pretty quiet today.
S-Say, Tasuku, what were you
doing in the classroom earlier?
You were watching?
I was, well...
Is it something you'd rather not talk about?
No, no. Long story short, I was mediating
a fight between Hoshinomori and Amano.
Th-That girl's called Hoshinomori-san, huh?
Then what's the deal with that Amano guy
you hang out with so much lately?
What?
We just like talking about video games.
I see.
Subject: I liked it!
Posted on: May 14, 10:13PM
Posted by: Yama-san
I got to see a side of Nobe-san
that I hadn't seen before.
It was seriously fun.
Thank you very much.
But man, I feel like his new
game played it too safe.
It didn't have any of Nobe-san's
usual crazy plot twists.
Re: I liked it!
Posted on: May 14, 10:36PM
Posted by: Nobe
Thanks again.
The Next Day
Later.
Find out about that chick for me.
Sure.
I'm curious about that really cute girl
who showed up out of nowhere, too.
Is there really someone else
besides Tendou who's that cute?
Uehara-kun.
Are you heading home?
Yeah.
I'm waiting for Aguri.
Yeah?
Is there something you want to say?
Well, maybe I'm being nosy, but did Aguri-san
say anything yesterday on the way home?
N-Nothing.
She was normal.
Okay, never mind, then.
Why is Amano worried about Aguri?
They don't even know each other, do they?
Hey, Amano, are you...
U-Um, Uehara-san...
U-Um...
Who might you be?
Um, well...
Can't you tell?
Dried seaweed.
What?!
Wh-What's your problem?!
Wait, Hoshinomori, is that you?
Yes, yes.
I-I did give her a little advice
about her presentation,
but I never expected this
much of an improvement!
Um, um...
I'm sorry.
About what?
It's a bit creepy when it's this blatant, right?
N-No, I don't think so.
You had what it takes to be cute, after all.
Yeah.
You're super cute.
Super cute...
What the hell is going on?
Aguri-san?
Um, um...
Is this okay?
Aguri-san!
I mean, even my parents and sister
were like, "Who are you?"
"Is it okay"? You look great.
D-Do I?
Thank you.
Hey, where's Amano?
Keita ran that way.
He was shouting, "Aguri-san!"
Crap! Where did Aguri-san go?
Tendou-san!
A-Amano-kun?
I'm glad you're here.
Um, I think I had some
misunderstandings the other day.
I'm sorry for everything.
What is she talking about?
No, this is not the time!
Hey, did you happen to pass by a girl?
She looked, like, ditzy and cute...
I saw someone like that heading to the
front entrance, looking depressed.
Thank you!
A-Amano-kun!
What is it?
Wh-Why are you chasing after her?
It's what you'd call relationship drama.
Relationship drama...
Aguri-san!
It's the creepy guy who's chasing after Tasuku.
Is that how people see me?
No wonder people were staring at me.
So what do you want?
Um... well...
W-Would you like to go have tea with me?
I can't shake the feeling that I've
been hitting on everyone lately.
This is awkward.
I didn't plan ahead at all.
U-Um...
What?
Is it just me, or are you
making a huge mistake?
I don't think it's what you think it is
between Chiaki and Uehara-kun.
But he said Hoshinomori-san was super cute.
Th-That was, you know,
like a figure of speech.
Uehara-kun said you're
really cute these days.
Really?
Yeah, it's true.
Uehara-san definitely loves you, Aguri-san.
Besides, Uehara-kun's too good
for that seaw— for Chiaki.
I'm totally rooting for you.
I'm going to go get something else to drink.
I managed to pull it off.
Oh, there's an event.
I think I'll invite Mono-san.
I hope nothing bad happens from now on.
Whyyyyy?!