Now, then... What's rather curious...
is this.
Could this be an object of worship?
I don't think we should
touch it so carelessly...
I agree, but we must investigate it.
Get ready.
Goblins?
What could this be?
I believe this is the goblins' home.
Look over there! That's the boat
we saw the other day.
Maybe that's how the goblins
are getting here.
So this must be an ancient artifact
capable of producing a Gate.
A magical mirror that can
invoke lost spells...
I can't even imagine how valuable this is.
So someone's been summoning
the goblins with this...
...then giving them weapons and
having them live down here.
And having that creature protect the mirror.
What shall we do, Goblin Slayer?
So it was goblins.
I'm sure that explosion shook the entire place.
If this is where the goblins are entering
and exiting, we can't overlook it.
So they're going to come reclaim it.
Oh, come on!
Give us a break already!
Goblin Slayer...
What...
What's in my pocket?
Don't worry.
There's no problem.
There and Back Again
Can you do this?
Of course I can.
Worry about yourself. Don't get thrown
into a wall like you did last time.
I plan not to.
Goblin Slayer, the preparations are complete.
Though it's sort of improvised...
That's plenty. How are things over there?
Yes, I'm ready.
Good. How many spells do we have left?
Um... I have one left.
Save it. There'll be a proper time to use it.
All right.
I have two left.
If I don't summon the dragontooth warrior
again, it'll be a total of three,
but I doubt you'd like for me to save that.
Correct. Give it a shield and
have it protect the girl.
Understood.
Would you like me to attend to the mirror?
Yes.
I probably have about two more left myself.
Save them. They'll be our trump card.
Then I guess I'll assist you
until it's time to use them.
We're pretty lucky...
We somehow have three spell casters.
Huh, I guess even long-ears has it in her
to be honest when it comes down to it.
How rude! I'm always honest!
So, what do you want me to do?
Draw them in and then take them down.
Lure in as many as you can.
I feel like you're asking a bit much, but...
Fine.
I'll do it.
At least you won't have
to aim too carefully now.
One.
Beard-cutter! Shoot all you want!
Best to take out as many as possible!
That's the plan.
That's two.
Three.
Eight.
Their numbers are making this tough!
Looks like we let too many through.
Coming from the right!
Leave it to me!
Three from the left! Four from the right!
Yeah, yeah.
Well, aren't you adorable?
I-Is it?
You honor me with your praise.
But...
How in the world is this mirror attached?
O proud and strange brontosaurus,
grant me the strength of ten thousand!
There's a huge one coming!
I'll take care of it.
Don't move away from the altar.
You got it.
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Yes! Orcbolg, I need some arrows!
Pass them on.
You got it!
Here ya go.
Yes.
Look out!
Ugh... You done yet, Scaly?
Just a little more...
I'll help you.
I thank you.
Do you still need more time?
Damn your brute strength.
Orcbolg!
He's purposely luring it
into the goblin mob.
Jeez, you're unbelievable.
Hey, long-ears, can't you
shoot a few more of them?
Shut it! Get me some better arrows, then!
Why don't you just throw some rocks?
No way!
Just one more push!
Goblin Slayer!
Face the mirror upward and get under it!
Understood!
He's coming!
Shoot a big one! Upward!
Upward? You got it!
Time to work, you gnomes!
Roll bits of sand together,
and it shall become rock!
Orcbolg, over here!
Thanks.
Goblin Slayer!
We need light!
Right.
O merciful Earth Mother, please bless us,
the wanderers in the
darkness, with holy light!
Stone Blast!
Bring it down!
Jeez...
Spin the buckets, gnomes! Make them
spin and spin and let them go!
Now that...
Falling Control!
...makes fifty and three.
Jeez... What were you thinking, Orcbolg?!
That startled me...
Startled you? That's it?
I mean... I think I'm just
getting used to all this.
Jeez...
Good heavens... Thank goodness we
had the Gate mirror right above us.
We were fortunate that it absorbed most
of the rubble, but it proved rather heavy.
Well, you definitely did most
of the work back there, Scaly.
But I almost feel bad for
the ones on the other side.
Maybe this is how people got around
way back when, eh, Beard-cutter?
I'm not interested.
We're very lucky we weren't
underneath the city.
If we were under the city,
I would've thought of another plan.
Hey.
What?
No fire, no water, no poison,
and no explosions.
Orcbolg...
What?
Goblin Slayer?
I'm glad you're safe.
I've come to ask you something.
Yes, what is it?
I will be happy to give you an answer if I can.
You know everything, don't you?
Yes. You're exactly right.
I see.
How did you figure it out?
I didn't.
I intended to ask everyone
who was in a position to know.
Everyone?
Oh... I see.
Perhaps I shouldn't have
been so forthcoming, then.
But I can't say I'm disappointed
that you asked me first.
May I ask why you suspected me?
There are several reasons.
That white... What was it called?
Alligator?
Yeah, I think that's what it was called.
I don't believe that was a random encounter.
So you're suggesting that it was planned?
At least to the extent that
it tried to chase us away,
and it also attacked the goblins.
That seems a bit paranoid.
Despite how elaborate these ruins are,
you have no precise maps,
nor any rat-killing quests,
and adventurers avoid the place entirely.
That'd be impossible without any patrols.
You seem rather knowledgeable
about adventurers.
Though I'm not an adventurer.
That would mean something
was guarding the place.
That thing is a familiar.
Is it a guardian beast
protecting the sewers?
Ironic, don't you think?
To think that the messenger of
the Supreme God should protect
the city and the city alone.
You should've known.
Killing women, ripping out
entrails on the spot,
then leaving the corpse there...
Those aren't things goblins do.
Indeed.
They bring their prey back to
their nest to toy with them.
They won't kill them quickly.
They were plotting something
using that mirror.
They are minions of the Demon Lord.
The mastermind...
no longer exists in this world.
They were disposed of in a completely
different place... by the Hero.
But...
But if the goblins were to attack,
I would just break down in tears.
I had heard about them
moving under the city.
I also knew that the sect was
plotting their revenge against me.
I would have been able to endure that.
But...
Who could I have asked?
The hero known as the Sword Maiden,
asking for protection from mere goblins?
No one would believe me...
What do you plan to do with me?
Nothing.
Because you're not a goblin.
Is that why you're not going to ask why?
If you want to tell me, I'll listen.
I wanted someone to understand.
How scared, how hard...
how painful and terrifying...
Something so horrible could
happen in this world.
There are creatures in this world
that could commit such atrocities.
I just wanted people to understand that...
But in the end, no one did.
You may have that Gate mirror, if you'd like.
You must understand...
Of all people, you must understand...
I got rid of it.
What?
That was an ancient relic,
a priceless treasure worth thousands...
There's no guarantee that the other
goblins won't learn how to use it.
We encased the mirror in concrete
and sank it in the canal.
It'll make a good bed for...
What was it again? That white thing.
You never cease to amaze me...
I daresay you might be unstoppable.
Perhaps.
May I ask you something, as well?
I can't promise you an answer.
Has something changed since you
started slaying the goblins?
Something?
If the Hero is able to slay the Demon Lord,
I'm sure the world will be saved.
But if the fifteen-year-old girl
who was attacked by the goblins
is still looking for salvation,
no one would even notice.
No matter how many goblins
are slain, nothing...
Nothing changes.
And I think that's fine.
You said you went through something horrible.
Yes.
I saw it happen, from start to finish.
Then—
So I don't know exactly how you feel.
So you're not going to save me?
No.
But...
If any more goblins appear, call for me.
I'll kill the goblins for you.
Even... Even in my dreams?
Yeah.
You will come?
Yeah. Because I'm the Goblin Slayer.
I-I...
I cherish you...
I'm done.
Thank you for reporting back to her.
Man, that was fun.
You were the one crying like a baby
after the goblins surrounded you.
You're one to talk.
Oh, come on. We survived and won.
We even got paid.
I cannot help but feel that the
Gate mirror went to waste, though.
But we gathered valuable information,
destroyed a heresy,
and did many valorous deeds.
I must say that I am overall
satisfied with our work.
I've got no complaints as long as I get to
eat something delicious with this money.
All you dwarves care about is food.
Good work, Goblin Slayer.
When we get back...
Jeez... If you're awake, just say so.
I just woke up.
I can't tell because you always
have that helmet on.
I see.
When we get back, there's
something I want to try.
Something you want to try?
Ice treats.
Ice treats?
Could I join you in tasting
this ice treat you speak of?
If you want some, sure.
It's made with milk.
Oh, sweet nectar!
Oh, s-sorry about that!
It's nothing to worry about.
Come now, Beard-cutter.
How could you not rely on this dwarf
with matters involving food?
Should I?
Of course!
Then I guess I'll rely on you.
So, how are you going to make it?
Apparently, you go like this.
Sir Goblin Slayer, if you
need to spin something,
I believe something that uses a pedal to
spin the object would be most effective.
I see. You have a point.
Goblin Slayer, I can have some, too, right?
Sure.
What about you?
I guess I'll have some.
I see. Don't kick me if
it doesn't turn out right.
Jeez, okay, fine! I won't kick you!
I won't kick you, so give me some!
Are you satisfied?
Yeah.
Next Time
Dozing