This way, dear guest.
Oh.
Jabami Yumeko?! Why?
Not now, I need to concentrate.
There's no need
to make such a scary face.
Let's enjoy our little gamble.
Shit...
In a game of chance similar to Chouhan Bakuchi, technique shouldn't matter.
Chouhan Bakuchi: Dice game of betting either odds or even.
So why am I being pushed into a corner?!
If I'm not just having a streak of horrible luck, the only explanation would be...
Cheating!
I can't tell how she's cheating, but she must be slowly building up whatever plan she has...
Then...
32 - I'll bet everything I have left!
Oh, it seems you want to finish the game right now.
Very well.
Both parties are prepared.
Ten blades will be placed within.
Come on, all are down!
Got her. Now...
I see.
I bet six chips in five different places.
I’ll finish this in one go. There won’t be an opening to cheat!
Time's up. No more bets please.
I will now proceed.
2 4 8 16 22...
just one is fine, please be a hit!
Match set!
22. Saotome has a hit!
Oh, it seems your number won.
However...
The verdict is death.
My condolences.
What? Verdict? Saotome didn't win?
22 was stabbed by a sword. The verdict is death.
Saotome-sama, having bet six chips, receives a thirty-fold minus of 18,000,000 Yen.
With Yuriko-sama's chips added, the total is a minus of 49,600,000 Yen.
Thank you for this match, Saotome-san.
I'll let you know
the method for payments later.
Somebody lead her outside, please.
Our business is settled.
Saotome-sama, you’re causing trouble for the other guests.
Don't touch me!
If I wanted to pay
that tax in full, I would have.
But if I did that,
my lost status will never return.
I shouldn't have taken that bet.
I can only dream of getting back my former status.
No... More than that...
Jabami Yumeko. Getting involved with her was a mistake.
Saotome... you were cornered enough to take on an official match...
Suzui-san, what is an official match?
Ah, an official match is only privilege given to 'livestock'.
They have the right to challenge anyone to a match, just once.
As long as the bet doesn’t involve an absurd amount, refusing a challenge is forbidden.
The challenges the members of the Student Council receive
are typically through
the roof thanks to that.
The 'livestock' aims for a big one-match comeback from time to time.
So, Saotome-san did just that?
That's indeed how it is.
Episode2
Jabami Yumeko-san, right?
Welcome to the Traditional Culture Research Club.
I am the head of
the Culture Research Club
and member of the Student Council.
NIshinotouin Yuriko.
It’s nice to meet you.
The purpose of your visit... of course I don't need to ask that, right?
How about a little battle with me?
Using this original game of ours,
'life or Death'.
That sounds really interesting, please let me join you!
Life or Death.
First, ten sword-shaped game pieces are placed within that cup and are shaken.
There are thirty numbered holes on the board,
you simply predict where the swords might land and place your bet.
Simply put it involves betting on numbers just like Roulette and Chouhan Bakuchi.
The interesting part about 'Life or Death' though...
If the sword lands facing up the verdict is 'Life' and the winnings are multiplied by 30.
If the sword points downward the verdict is 'Death' and the penalty is minus 30.
Meaning you have to pay your opponent 30 times of what you bet.
Each round has a decided bet.
The participants decide on how many chips they want to place in advance.
While the cup is shaken you have ten seconds to place the chips.
When the chip count reaches zero, the game is over and the difference turns into debt.
Well then, let's decide the size of the bet.
A small amount would be really boring, so...
Indeed, let's go with 40,000,000 Yen.
Fine by me.
Now then, how many chips should we bet to start with, Yumeko-san?
Let's see... I think I’ll see how it goes first. Ten chips.
Very well.
Both parties are prepared.
Ten blades will be placed within.
Come on, all are down!
I've decided!
Zero!
No more bets please!
Both parties placed their bets.
I see you pondered until the last minute, do you have a plan in mind?
Yes, this pot seems to have a flared base, doesn't it?
That means that, physically,
there should be a higher chance of the numbers in the middle to be hit.
Whether the verdict is Life or Death, if they don't hit your slots it'd be boring.
I'm not the most patient person, you see.
Then I will pray that your plans won’t work against you.
I will now proceed..
Match set!
17 - Life! 30 - Death!
Yumeko... missed.
NIshinotouin-san... So close! One number over and it would've been hit.
That one hit would've been worth 30,000,000 Yen...
Both players have missed; no chips will be moved.
So close, so close.
Now, on to the next one.
Yumeko,
I can’t look at this anymore!
It would be better to stop such a super risky ga–
Suzui-san.
You don't need to worry so much.
This amount of money is no problem, really.
The extreme movements of chips is what makes this gamble interesting after all.
It would be a waste to stop halfway.
Suzui-san was your name, no?
Y-Yes.
The sensation felt once such money relies on a single shake of a cup...
You would understand
If you tasted it once.
Right, Yumeko-san?
Indeed, it seems I have
become addicted to this.
But, NIshinotouin-san...
Your methods are the worst.
Pardon?
What did you say?
Could you not hear me?
I just said that you are the worst.
That official match with Saotome-san just now - it was proposed by you, wasn’t it?
I think Saotome-san would have called for a match to get back her status and pride, but...
there was no need to choose such a high-risk game just for that.
Showing a weakened human a glimmer of hope and then beating them into despair...
It’s no different from a loan shark.
I don't know how good of a gambler you are, but as a human you're the lowest of the low.
Akin to a piece of shit.
How dare you!
Yuriko-sama, let's throw this wom–
Why should we, Kumagusu-san?
It was simply a slip of the tongue, correct?
Yes.
Still, I have to say it's too bad.
Surely you bet on 2, 4 and 10 showing up, but it didn't seem to go well.
2...4...10?
I love wordplay, you know. The name NIshinotouin...
NI
Shi
Tou
Has 2(ni), 4(shi) and 10(tou) in it, right?
Have you never taken notice of such word play?
I kindly ask you to keep from playing with people’s names.
NIshinotouin is a proper, esteemed name that stems from ancient Kyoto, a lineage with–
Also!
Just counting even numbers, the 6 and 8 in between are missing.
What's inside... is missing!
Quite the fitting name for an airhead, don't you think?
So cheap!
Right, Suzui-san?
Y-You, cut it out al–
Interesting...
Just as the Student Council President said, you are really interesting.
Oh, receiving such high praise is a tad embarrassing.
Now, let's continue.
How much shall we bet now?
Everything I have left, all forty chips.
You’re certainly resolved, aren’t you?
Kumagusu-san.
B-Both parties are prepared.
Ten blades will be placed within.
Come on, all are down!
Winning normally at this point is simply not good for my mental health.
Stress is the enemy of beauty, after all.
'Life' or 'Death'...
I'll kill you  - just as the words say.
Five pieces...
If she wanted to put Yumeko under zero chips, there'd be no need for that many...
She's angry, no doubt about it!
That provocations drove her up the wall.
Two.
One.
Zer–
NIshinotouin-san...
I'll apologise if my previous remark hit too hard home.
It was all a trick to have you bet everything from the beginning.
Forgive me, if you would.
Why...?
'Why', you ask?
It's because you're cheating, of course.
Cheating?!
Indeed.
Please, take a look at that woman's hand.
There appear to be moles, no?
Yeah, that's true...
The woman who offered to guide us here had the very same markings.
What could that mean?
Simply that those 'moles' are artificial.
Piercings, I'd assume.
To hand out piercing amongst her staff for a simple cheat...
NIshinotouin-san...
You've done something marvelous, haven't you?
In at least one of those blades you've embedded a magnet, am I correct?
If the dealer's piercings are indeed magnetic, she could influence the blade from the outside.
All she would need to do is slide her hand alongside the cup.
She could then move the blade around and have it fall where she desired.
That's insane...
You provoked her earlier just to get her to definitely cheat for this round?
Wait!
Since you've come here, I have yet to land a single hit with those blades!
That friend of yours placed her bet after the cup was shaken!
How could I possibly have the needed leeway for such a thing?!
What makes this trick so marvelous is that there's no absolute guarantee of winning.
For the dealer to hit the blade
at the exact desired location would take immense control, after all.
Other blades would stray from the hole as well,
not to mention that you can only manipulate a single one - the rest you leave to luck.
The actual percentage of victory wouldn't amount to much, no?
No wonder Saotome-san couldn't see through this, either.
An 'uncertain' cheat.
Nevertheless,
It was more than enough for you.
You're head of the Traditional Culture Research Club, and in the Student Council on top of that.
Surely, you met others in this gambling room with enormous assets to use at your leisure.
Regardless of your uncertain victory for every round,
having that advantage over the other is enough.
Within dozens, hundreds of these matches, it's enough to move into the positive.
Basically, the secret behind it is no simple trick, but your own affluency.
I'm sure that losing tens of millions means next to nothing for you.
And yet I still can't call this a fair game!
I've bet all of my finances,
that's simply unfair!
Why don't we suffer together?
My bet amounts to 400,000…
If I manage to hit the right mark and it results in your loss...
You owe me 2,170,000,000 Yen.
In a single round,
you may lose that much.
Truly, 'life' or 'death'.
Come now!
Come now...
Come now...!
Come now!
Come now, come now, come now...
Let's gamble into madness!
Come on now! End this!
Come now! Raise that cup!
Yu-Yuriko-sama...
A loss will cost me 2,170,000,000 Yen…
There's no way I can prepare such a sum!
I'd have no choice but to use the money pooled by every club member....
But if we don't persevere afterwards, my position in the Student Council would be...
It's only thanks to my position this club can continue to exist,
and that the girls here are protected from becoming 'livestock'.
Without it, everything would fall apart.
It would mean utter ruin!
I-I have no option
but to settle this with her...
Before that cup is even moved...
Yu-Yumeko-san...
Pardon the intrusion.
C-Council President?!
Why are you...?!
It certainly seems as if things have gotten interesting.
It also seems that you're betting quite the amount. That tends to stir up trouble.
I'll be playing the overseer for you.
T-This is nothing that should trouble you, Council President.
Something this trivial
I can take care of myself–
Just bite your tongue
and turn that cup already.
Yuriko-chan, you look really pale! You sure you’re okay?
Yuriko-sama...
Then, here I go...
Match set!
Ten on 'death', seven on 'life'...
Seven...
the position I bet on at random...
More importantly,
It didn't hit twenty-four...?
Yuriko-sama lands on 'life' with five chips.
Her total chips are at 195; Jabami-sama loses 115 pieces!
The match is settled with 310,000,000 Yen going to Yuriko-sama!
You're joking...!
Yumeko lost?!
I wouldn't have thought you'd win this one.
You're quite lucky, Yuriko.
I'm seeing you in a new light.
And yet, that must be awful for you.
Getting beaten by a lucky punch after trying so hard.
It might have been a 'badger'.
There's little I can do now.
Well... I wonder about that.
A 'badger' refers to an old trick employed for dice gambling.
For this trick, one would poke a hole into the floor.
The gambling would occur on top of it, but a white cloth was used to hide it from view.
Under the floors of old Japanese homes there's a space, correct?
The cheater would hide in that space.
He would use something like a candle
to see through the cloth and determine the position of the dice.
Depending on the visible pips, he would poke the dice with a needle.
That would allow the pips to be in the bookmaker's advantage.
It's possible that the President had someone use a magnet in a similar fashion.
She propelled the blade stuck in the twenty-four position away.
Recalling NIshinotouin-san's behaviour, she was not informed of this.
That the other had hit was a coincidence. Truly a stroke of great luck.
But that would only work if they had a space under the floor, right?
Simply building this room on top of a space would be enough, no?
That kind of architecture would work for them.
No... It could even mean that the President had this building remodeled for that sole purpose!
N-No way...
If that is truly so,
how marvelous would it be?!
Something like that isn't simply done on a hunch,
nor would anyone do so even if the idea came to them!
Only a madman would be capable of such a thing.
This academy truly exceeds expectations!
No, that Student Council President!
I've decided.
I want to gamble against the Council President!
Quit!!
Airhead
Stupid
Lololol
Idiot
Creep
Moron
Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike...
Mike: A common name for Japanese cats.
Mike
Jabami-san...
We heard. You gambled against the council yesterday.
That is true. But I seem to have lost.
Yeah, we heard that too...
So, we came to...
Oh, thank you for worry–
What the hell are you even saying, cattle?!
We're here to laugh at you!
Who the hell would worry about a Mike?!
That 'losing feline' nature might rub off on us!
I see...
Female livestock is 'Mike'. A losing feline...
Isn't that just the cutest?!
Meow, meow.
I lost at gambling, meow.
I lost against the council and am in debt, meow.
Just however can I repay it, meow?
I want to gamble more and more, meow!
Won't anyone be my manager, meow?
W-What the hell's up with her!?
She's crazy!
L-Let's go!
Yu-Yumeko!
What do you think you're doing?!
Some people just can't take a joke.
Right, Suzui-nyan?
Okay, okay!
Oh my, I could get used to this!
Do you think I should add a tail, too?
Just forget about it, okay?!
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning!
Yuriko-chan's not coming, huh?
After such a pitiful presentation, I doubt she'd be willing to show her face.
Even though she won and all!
Good morning, Sayaka.
Good morning, Council President.
These are the contracts for both Jabami Yumeko and Saotome Mary.
Account of debt!
You turned into a 'Mike', right?
No matter what anyone thinks, I'll shoot!
This sensation...
Episode 4
The Woman Who Became Livestock
I can't get enough.