I'm sorry! It seems I had the wrong idea.
No kidding.
And here I am, hanging out
with Hoshinomori again.
Uehara-san, are you all right?
Yeah, it's nothing.
I was just moping about
how cruel the universe is.
Oh, of course.
I still don't get how Keita could
have such a cute girlfriend.
About that, yeah,
I don't get it either, but...
The world really is twisted.
Just thinking about the
time Keita was bragging
so proudly about his
relationship makes me furious.
Hey, are you sure you
weren't just hearing things?
I've never seen a man brag so
shamelessly about his girlfriend.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Let's talk about something else.
Sure.
Okay, so about Amano...
I hope he gets on a helicopter
built by Ca*com.
Glad to see you haven't changed.
All right, then, what do you think of Tendou?
T-Tendou-san?
I don't know what to say.
I don't really talk to her much
in class or anything.
I mean, compared to her,
I'm like garbage.
You two even have the same self-perception.
I do admire her, though.
We're both gamers, after all.
I wish we could be friends someday.
You legitimately need to just
go out with Amano, already.
Uh...
Where did that come from?
Wh-What about you?
What do you think, Uehara-san?
About, um, Tendou-san.
Me? What I think of Tendou?
I think she's flawless.
Until you get to know who she really is.
I knew it.
You do like Tendou-san.
Cheer up, Hoshinomori.
You're a perfectly fine woman in my eyes.
You could give Tendou a run for her money.
Sure... Thanks.
Wait...
Sorry.
I hang out with a really clingy girl, so...
I-I-I'll be going now!
Hey... Wait!
Excuse me!
Thank you very much.
He's totally cheating!
I couldn't hear the beginning that well,
but I heard everything from where
he said Tendou-san was flawless
to where he patted her on the head.
You're way too much, Uehara-kun!
Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right,
B, A, B, A, B, A, B, A...
The infamous cheat code?!
It's almost refreshing to witness.
I guess it's a bit easier in a sense.
But still, I love Tasuku.
What should we do?
Enough about me.
What about you?
What about me?
What else?
About Tendou-san.
Are you even trying, Amanocchi?
It took me a lot of work to
get to where I am now,
from when I was a total wallflower.
Here, where your boyfriend cheats
on you left and right. Got it.
Ow, ow, ow!
My point is, no matter how much better
you make yourself, that's not enough.
But in dating sims, you can set most of
the flags just by getting your stats up.
Listen, Amanocchi. Life isn't a game.
You're right.
Still, some games are a
good representation of life.
Dude, shut up.
Sorry.
Can you really even quantify human
relationships in terms of "levels"?
You don't become friends just by
racking up enough charisma, right?
Amanocchi, in this world,
one plus one isn't two.
Right...
In this world, one plus one is...
love!
Wha?
It's love!
Love, you say?
Love, I say.
Why do I feel sorry for this girl?
N-No, but first things first...
We need to become friends.
Actually, I need her to recognize
me as a human being first.
It's the same thing.
Either way, you need to talk to her directly,
or you won't get anywhere.
I know, but...
Hey, by the way, how did
you confess to Uehara-kun?
You're going there?
You're really going there?
Oh, man!
Oh, crap.
Okay, okay...
I said, "Will you go out with me, Uehara-kun?"
Huh?
I said, "Will you go out with me,
Uehara-kun," Amanocchi.
I heard rumors that Tasuku likes ditzy girls.
Besides, even if he didn't,
I think I would have ended up
saying almost the same thing.
That's pretty simple.
Tut, tut.
It's the opposite, Amanocchi.
Your most precious feelings
are always really simple.
They spill out of your mouth on their own.
So if you truly wish to be
friends with Tendou-san,
you won't have trouble saying it.
It's what you really feel.
Is that something even I can do?
Yeah, you can.
Guaranteed.
Maybe I'll give it a shot tomorrow.
I have nothing to lose.
You said it, Amanocchi.
I'm a man. I'll stand by my word!
That's it!
I'm not buckling just yet, either!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Let's stick together!
No, haven't I told you?
I have no intention of going out with you.
No, how is it any different
if we start as friends?
What do you even mean by "friends," anyway?
Do you mean "friends," as in one step below
"boyfriend" because you had to settle?
No, it's not that we have
a difference in values.
It's more that I don't
get along with you well.
So, with that said, I don't... huh?
Piece of shit!
Rough day?
Oh.
Game Club
The worst thing you can do
is give a vague answer.
You end up giving them false hope
if you let them down softly.
I see.
That's why you were shutting
them down mercilessly.
Was I that brutal?
Honestly, you sounded like a monster.
Maybe it's because you were
intent on turning them down,
but you always went in with a "no."
I wonder if it's become a habit
to be dismissive of everything.
Now that you mention it...
Oh, no, I'm not accusing you of anything.
I know. Why don't you let your gut
talk and be a little more open?
My gut?
That's right.
To me, for better or worse,
you wear this armor that says,
"This is the ideal Tendou Karen."
Even in daily conversations, you seem
to deal with them in your armor first,
and then you think about
it internally later on.
If only you could do it
the other way around...
In other words, you're saying
I should talk more openly,
and then try to smooth things over
or try to explain myself afterwards?
I think so.
I think that would be about right for you.
I see.
Otherwise, I don't see you ever
narrowing your gap with Amano-kun.
Say what?
No, nothing.
You're right.
I should be more open, and stop
going into everything rejecting it.
Stop being so dismissive...
Stop... Stop... Stop...
Thug
Check it out! She's a ten!
Let's have some fun together.
Flora
I have no interest in you guys.
Let's go, Keita.
Thug
Damn it, what a bitch.
Just get over here!
The delinquents grab Flora's wrist.
Flora
Ahh!
1: Help her
2: Run away
by yourself
Terrified, I run as fast as I can,
leaving Flora behind.
Flora
K-Keita...
Thug
What a loser!
Let's bounce.
Flora
Keita...
It's my tenth playthrough!
I've tried so many options already!
Maybe it's a sign that I'm just
fundamentally incompatible
with someone like Tendou-san.
New message from Aguri-san
New message from Uehara-san
Get some sleep for tomorrow, Amanocchi!
People judge you based on
your complexion, you know!
Don't you dare stay up all night gaming!
Nah, even you aren't that stupid!
Sorry, good night!
I'm so sorry!
Today
Hey, Amano, I heard you're
meeting up with Tendou tomorrow.
I'll round up some more people for you.
Let's get you in front of
everyone when you do it.
You're finally going to get some respect.
Although you'll be shunned
if you mess up. lolol
Don't mess it up for me!
Piss off with your "lolol"!
Send
Thanks.
Although you're putting
a ton of pressure on me.
I shouldn't be so rude to someone
who's doing so much for me.
Message from MONO-san
Let's do this
Oh, it's about the kill event tomorrow.
Mono-san must be a shy, awkward person.
Tsucchie
Yeah, let's do this
Thanks, Aguri-san, Uehara-kun, MONO-san.
I think I have a little more fight left in me.
Load saved game?
Loading the game.
1: Go home together
2: Go to Flora's place
I wonder if I'm supposed to be nice to
every girl in the game, not just Flora.
2: Go to Flora's place
1: Go home together
You aren't supposed to try to make
everyone happy in dating sims, but...
1: Let's all go together!
2: Let's go with Flora!
1: I'm worried about everyone
2: I'm worried about Flora
1: As long as everyone's happy
2: As long as Flora's happy
1: I like everyone
Keita
Please... go out with me!!
Flora
Ever since I first saw you ten years ago...
...Huh?
Keita
Huh?
No way. Is it happening?
Flora
I've been waiting to hear you say those words!
I love you!
Flora
My hero, kind to everyone!
I finally beat it.
I get it.
No matter what, you can't treat people
like crap if they've treated you well.
It's all thanks to Aguri-san and
Uehara-kun, and Mono-san.
Thank you, guys!
Even if Tendou-san rejects me,
I'm already happy as hell.
Tendou's coming to see Amano?!
You know something about this, don't you?
Uehara!
I wouldn't know. It's not like
I'm that close to Tendou.
Although I was actually the
one who spread the rumor.
And I was the one who called Tendou out.
Damn it. I told you yesterday.
I'm trying to get you some respect by having
you do it in front of a bunch of people.
That's not why I'm trying
to get close to Tendou-san.
Is he angry?
I'm sorry I set things up without asking you.
I'll call it off if you don't want it.
I mean, I'm grateful that you're
doing all this for me, but...
Listen, Amano, I'm doing this
for the sake of your future, too.
What do you mean?
Think about it.
Say you and Tendou establish a friendship.
What would people think when they
see you walking together outside?
Exactly.
That's why it's better to have some people
around when you make a friend request.
All the better if they're
irresponsible blabbermouths
who will spread information fast.
What place satisfies all those
conditions and is easiest for you?
Class 2-F!
Right after school, when there are a ton
of people and there's plenty of time!
That's the idea.
You're great, Uehara-kun!
You're so amazing!
I'm sorry. I was a fool.
The base part of this vector, AB,
is called the starting point,
Amanocchi
Normal?
Attracted to
Amanocchi likes Tendou-san.
Amano-san
and the tip of the arrow
is called the endpoint.
He's attracted to her.
Amanocchi
Tendou-san thinks, well, he's normal?
I don't think she hates him.
Comrades!!
Amanocchi and I are comrades.
Aguri
Tasuku
Love!!
Likes?
I like Tasuku.
No, I love him.
Tasuku and Tendou-san...
Likes?
Attracted to
Tendou-san
Normal?
He might like her?
Don't cry, Aguri. Don't cry!
You're a strong girl!
Now, the problem is with this girl.
Amanocchi
Hoshinomori? Chiaki?
Amanocchi says he hates her,
but they're obviously pretty close.
And she's clearly interested in Tasuku.
Likes
Tasuku
And Tasuku...
Likes
All right, here I go.
Why is this so hard?!
Hoshinomori-san was a lot like me when
I used to be a wallflower! I can't take it!
Oh! I know!
Amanocchi's after-school
friend request event!
I'll figure out Tasuku's feelings then!
Yeah.
Keita's talking to Tendou-san after school?
About what?
Doesn't Keita have a girlfriend
named Aguri-san?
Come to think of it, I've heard rumors that
Aguri-san's going steady with Uehara-san.
What if... What if Keita's love for
Aguri-san is completely unrequited?
That's it!
Keita is being played by Aguri-san!
Otherwise,
there's no way he'd call Tendou-san
when Aguri-san is already his girlfriend!
It could only be...
for money!
Keita must be paying for
all her arcade visits and tea!
He's being played by a normie!
We're of the same kind.
I need to help him wake up.
I hate to use Amano like this,
but what I told him wasn't the real reason!
Aguri will definitely be coming
to see the event today.
I'm going to hide in the crowd and
get a good look at how Aguri reacts.
My girlfriend! The one who
seems to be dating Amano!
She'll never suspect that
she's being watched
when everyone's got their attention
on Tendou and Amano.
If Amano and Aguri are just friends,
she should be happy to see him
become friends with Tendou.
However, if Aguri shows even
a hint of disappointment...
Then case closed, she's cheating!
If Tasuku really likes Tendou-san,
he shouldn't be happy to see her
become friends with Amanocchi.
That's sure to show on his face.
And if Hoshinomori-san is his
real interest, he'll look at her.
He'll be worried about what
Hoshinomori-san thinks of Amanocchi.
Which means Keita's "please be my friend"
confession to Tendou-san is his SOS signal!
Because Keita doesn't have the
heart to dump Aguri-san!
I've got it!
I've got it, Keita!
I shall rally at Class F after school today
to verify your message and find out
what that little devil is really about.
But wait a second.
If Aguri is really going out with Amano,
this event is nothing but a farce.
Then what if I see Aguri looking
guiltily at me, her boyfriend?
That would be the worst!
Although I don't things will get that bad.
* They will
But what if Tasuku looks to see how I react?
Gulp.
Checking on his girlfriend
at a gathering of cheaters...
That's totally a player thing to do.
Although I guess Tasuku
couldn't be that awful.
Man, I'm so smart, though!
I fear my own craftiness!
But, but, what if...
What if Aguri-san and Uehara-san
look at each other guiltily?
If the two are actually going steady,
they'd be freaking out
about Keita's SOS signal.
I-I guess things couldn't get that bad, right?
* They will
In any case...
...the after-school event...
...is where it all ends.
I still don't get it!
Why would Amano-kun want
to see me after school?
Honestly, the most plausible explanation
is that he wants to end our friendship.
He just wants to game in peace.
His relationship with me is
nothing but trouble for him.
Amano-kun is timid.
Maybe he didn't like all the attention
he was getting from my pestering him.
Buck up, Tendou Karen.
Even if I'm faced with
an unfavorable situation,
I shall act with dignity, true to myself.
Attack!
I'm just going to have
to prepare for the worst.
I'll respond to what he says
openly and honestly.
First, I listen attentively
to what he has to say.
And I don't need to be dismissive.
I just need to tell him what I feel.
I'm going to meet Amano-kun face-to-face.
That's all.
Okay!
Pardon me.
Is Amano-kun here?
She's here!
She's actually here!
O-Over here!
Good luck.
Uehara-kun...
Aguri-san!
Chiaki!
Everyone's here for me.
Hello, Amano-kun.
Hello, Tendou-san.
Thank you for coming here today.
It's not a problem.
So, what business do you have with me today?
Y-Yeah, about that...
U-Um... uh...
This isn't easy for me to say, but...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing. Don't worry.
Continue, Amano-kun.
I'm prepared.
O-Okay...
Prepared?
I'm just going to make a friend request.
Of course! She's prepared to reject me!
Uh...
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Hey! Uehara-kun's blatantly
avoiding looking at me!
Uh, Amano-kun?
I see.
They're making sure they don't
see me in my miserable defeat.
It's sympathy!
Yeah.
Even if Tendou-san turns me
down, I have my friends.
I already have all the happiness in the world.
Tendou-san, please...
Aguri's staring at me,
looking ridiculously guilty!
This is the scenario where
she's totally with Amano,
and she's feeling totally
guilty about this charade!
Tendou-san, please...
Tasuku's staring at me,
looking ridiculously guilty!
Which means Tasuku was a
skeevy player the whole time!
It totally proves he's scheming to
cheat on her behind the scenes!
Tendou-san, please...
Uehara-san and Aguri-san are staring at
each other, looking ridiculously guilty!
Which means Uehara-san and
Aguri-san are totally going steady,
and they're freaking out
at what Keita might say!
Tendou-san, please...
First, listen more openly.
And don't go into everything being dismissive.
This isn't like the way I'm always
turning down casual confessions.
Even if I'm being rejected,
I'm going to be completely open.
I have a responsibility to
respond with how I really feel.
Tendou-san, please...
Just as I started that sentence,
the many events of recent days
flashed rapidly through my mind.
Keita
Please... go out with me!!
Yes, gladly.
Whoops, I messed up my line a littl—