Tonight, we bring the hammer down on the last of the corporations who regard ajin
as mere animals for experimentation, who have
repeatedly carried out unjust experiments.
This is genuinely our last chance.
The board of director’s meeting will be held
in the president’s office on the top floor.
The Anti-A’s will line the sides of the 24th floor.
We’ll be located here. There seems to be
a supply room on the 21st floor.
How do they plan to arrive?
Well, shall we start our playthrough?
A suspicious vehicle!
Oy! Stop!
Take them in!
Check the back!
What’s that?
Like I said,
it’s a secret weapon.
It’s coming down!
W-Wait!
It’s an EMP.
It’s likely
that all electronics within a few hundred meters are disabled.
It’s your turn, Okuyama-kun.
Let’s give them a show.
F- Fuck.
What’s going on? Hey! Nagai!
This situation in itself is a chance.
I have an idea.
Airburst grenade launcher. Taser gun.
Blinding lasers.
All unable to be used.
Abandon all electronic devices.
Go with the usual equipment.
From here on...
it’s a primitive fight with a single blade!
Let’s start the plan.
What’s going on?
Help out-
Watch out-
Do we have contact with the Anti-As?
Communications and all other devices are down,
and we can’t tell when they will be restored.
Give us the order.
We’ll come down on them from above!
It’s no good!
With these forces, nothing will come of that.
But what about guarding the building?
You can get to the police headquarters in 15 minutes.
If our communications aren't working, run!
Yessir!
It’s too bad.
In this situation, even the insurance you prepared...
Shut up.
Gen-kun.
Huh?
Can you come here a minute?
Don’t underestimate them.
Our opponent is a squad specially
prepared to fight ajin.
But, they’re just humans, right?
Yeah.
Numbers of enemies, seven.
They’re coming.
We can’t use the flashlights either.
In this situation,
even with our shared knowledge...
Adjust your eyes to your surroundings.
Unit three,
take the direct stairs to the top floor.
Unit four,
secure the president in the meeting room.
Everyone else, we’ll make our stand here.
Don’t kill them unnecessarily.
Capture them and get them under control.
This situation in itself is a chance.
We’re going up here?
Satou likes to fight, so he’ll probably take the Anti-As head on.
There’s a high chance of getting caught up
in the fight if we take the stairs.
Don’t you think we should take down Satou while
he’s distracted fighting the Anti-As?
With the change of circumstances,
we know our enemy’s target is the president,
so this plan has a higher chance of success.
Huh?
Seems like there’s no time to waste!
Aim for the guns.
Take out their weapons!
Hey you!
Reset!
There’s no time to be scared.
Fire!
Don’t look!
Ah, shit!  They got my eyes!
Fuck!
It’s true they don’t die.
But-
they’re amateurs in combat.
Shit!
Once things get like this-
It’s coming!  An IBM!
In front of the pillar!
Like you’d understand!
He’s the source! Get him!
The mental... connection-!
Shit.
Shit!
Just as expected of the Anti-Ajin Special Forces.
It’s not just a name.
It’s him.
Take him down ASAP!
Don’t give him the chance to revive!
Weak.
You bastard!
That agility- is he a former soldier?
How perfect...  a real savage fight!
Now!  Take him in!
It’s time I return the favor, Satou-san.
Well, now!  One round is already complete!
Units one and two, go around front!
We’re under attack by the ajin!
What happened to the commander and the others?
Hirasawa-san.
Understood, we'll take care of everyone but Satou.
Old man!
It’s Manabe.
Remember it already!
Be careful.
What’s going on?
They’re pushing through!
Now it’s just the inside of the meeting room.
Let’s move!
What?
There are still more?
It brings back memories, this feeling.
Couldn’t agree more.
Shit.
We'll handle these guys.
Satou-san, you go on ahead!
Thank you, Tanaka-kun!
Takahashi!
Reset those guys over there so they can help!
I’m a little busy here!
Now... time for the last stage.
If it isn’t Nagai-kun,
I haven’t seen you in a while.
What are you doing in a place like this?
Isn’t it obvious?
Satou-san.
I’m here to stop you.
Put down your weapons.
If you don’t, I’ll kill the president.
Ehhh?
Seems like you’re different than you were
at the research facility.
Why should I be concerned about
that man's life?
If I kill the president,
your game fails.
Can you stand having your fun
taken away in front you?
Ah, so you saw through my personality.
It’s your fault
that my quiet life is all messed up!
Quiet life?
Ahaha, that’s right!
You said you wanted to live quietly!
But what is there for you
if you return to a normal life?
I’ll only say it one more time.
Put down your weapons!
All that’s waiting for you is a boring life.
I’m not interested in that ordinary life,
there’s not enough fun.
And...
Nagai-kun,  I-
hate people who get in the way of my
games more than anything else!
The one messing up my life- you’re
the one who’s getting in the way!
Back away from the weapons!
Hm?  And?
What are you going to do?
Stall until back-up comes?
Or...
is this to prevent me from resetting?
Now would bee the perfect time to shoot
me with tranquilizer.
Nakano! Get him!
Satou!
Shit!
I knew it.
It wasn’t a bad plan,
but there was one essential flaw-
I’m really sorry for all the trouble.
Every game can be hacked...
We- We did it.
At last...  Satou!
With this... I can go back to normal life!
We did it, Mr. Fireman!!
What’s... going on?
Even though he’s unconscious...
how is the ghost still moving?
W- Why?
All it takes is practice.
You’re not the only one who can let the ghost move on its own.
Well....
Practice... Practice... Practice...
Since it doesn't have much of a sense of self yet,
it's more reliable to give it orders.
Ghost!
Don’t you think you’ve gotten in a bit over your head?
What are you doing, move!
Get it.
It’s not over!  One more time!
Come out, ghost!
It seem like the ghost’s behavior and number of times it
can be sent out changes based on the ajin’s state of mind.
N- no!
Nagai!
Nagai?
Why are you-?
Shit!
Looks like Nagai-kun has more friends now too!
These guys!
I didn’t think they looked like the special forces.
Getting in our way!
Really...
everyone around here is an idiot!
Ah?  What did you say?
Why don’t you get it?
Satou-san is just playing around!
He’s not thinking at all about
the future of ajin!
An IBM...
Run away!  Hurry!
If they can’t see the IBM, it seems like
your friends must not be ajin.
How is it?
The feeling that others are dying
because of you.
Stop-
Stop it.
Please stop!
It’s no good.
This is your punishment for getting
in my way!
Ghost!
Come out!!
Pl- please!
Nagai!
Come out!!!
Nagai...  it’s okay!
Nagai-kun.
If you want a quiet life,
I’ll grant that wish.
Forever, in the darkness.
You guys take the stairs!
Roger!
Bring them under control!
Satou-san!
Over here!
Hurry!
Satou-san!
Ah, too bad...
Ahahahaha!
That was like a rollercoaster!
Aha, that’s what you’d call a free-fall.
This is...
Kimura!
We’ve secured the escape route.
From there, we can get out together.
Just as you asked,
we picked these up too.
To make these...
how many times was I killed?
I just worked for the sake of the country!
Weapons development is necessary
for national defense!
Don’t fuck with me!
How can you say such a thing after
what you’ve done to me?
Now now, Tanaka-kun, calm down.
He still has an important role to play.
It can’t be!
He’s here?
The EMP got rid of the electronic lock,
but we still haven’t gotten the analog key.
It’s important,
so you always have it on you, right?
Ah, there it is.
S- Satou-san?
We still didn't get his confession!
And what about the civil rights of ajin-
Tanaka-kun.
Rights aren’t something you can be given.
Rights are something you must win
with your own two hands.
That’s what JFK said.
Or was it Martin Luther King?
Or maybe it was neither of them.
Well, whatever.
What will really prove our power
is coming next.
Fuck.
T- Tosaki-san.
What about Nagai?
Where is he?
It’s too bad about the Anti-As,
but we’ve captured Nagai Kei and Nakano Kou.
It seems as though they were
working with Satou, so...
This will save a little face for the Committee.
Yes. That’s right.
Now, it’s time to prepare for the press interview.
Senpai, please help out too.
You are a member of the Committee.
I know that.
W-What are you do-
Let’s go.
The guy with the mustache...
Where are Manabe and the others?
No way...
To be continued...