Hyakkaou Private Academy
Approaching its 122th anniversary,
this academy is known
for tradition and status.
Showdown!
Fullhouse!
Too bad!
Thank you for the game.
Ro-
Royal Straight Flush!?
Well, you've been through a lot today.
But keep your spirits up, 'kay?
Po-
chi.
Starting today,
I'm no longer "human".
Those are the rules of this academy.
Money is everything here.
And so,
The strength lies within gambling.
Got a straight.
Ugh, you win again, Saotome.
Same as usual, Mary-chan!
So good!
Seems like today is not your day.
I am...
a 'livestock' now.
Regaining your status is near impossible.
Or so I thought...
Until she appeared.
The Woman Called Jabami Yumeko
Episode 1
Let's start today with introducing
a new transfer student.
NIce to meet you, everyone.
My name is Jabami Yumeko.
I may be new here, but I'd be happy to make friends with all of you.
She's cuuute...
Ehm...
I'd like for one of you to show Jabami-san around the academy.
Suzui-kun,
you're the class rep, right?
Can I count on you to do it?
Yes.
Suzui-san,
it's very nice to meet you.
L-Likewise.
Something good happened
since I became a livestock.
Wonderful...
This academy is amazing.
I'm glad I transferred here.
What's this?
Ehm, Jabami-san?
Yes?
Have you ever gambled before?
Gambled...?
You mean things like poker or mahjong?
I know the general idea of rules.
I see.
Gambling in this academy
Is almost like a tradition.
After school hours
lots of places here turn into gambling dens.
So, there's a lot of rich kids here
with infinite amounts of money to gamble with.
And soon they'll invite you to play...
So be caref–
Well now...
That sounds very fun.
Jabami-san!
Welcome to second
year cherry blossom class!
Where are you from?
What are you hobbies?
What do you do on weekends?
Do you have a boyfriend?
NIce to meet you!
NIce to meet you all as well.
Hello!
I'm Saotome Mary.
NIce to meet you.
Likewise, Saotome-san.
Jabami-san, are you free after school?
If you are, would you
like to play with me?
What's happening?
Looks like Mary-chan and transfer
student are going to gamble.
What? Are they going to play that?
What game should we play?
How about "Voting rock-paper-scissors"?
It's an original game we play in our class.
First, everyone in this class draw either a rock, paper or a scissor on a card.
Then the cards go into that box so we can't see what's on them.
Next we draw 3 cards from the box
and choose one card to play.
If it's a tie, we pick a card from the remaining two and play again.
If 3 games are tie,
that set is a draw.
That's one set.
It's not like a normal rock paper scissors, where you can just choose any move you want.
Trying to read the flow
of the game is the fun part.
That sounds fun! I definitely want to try it!
Okay!
That's the spirit.
Ehm, Jabami-san...
Pochi,
Go bring us some chips.
Hurry up.
Yes...
These are chips.
Each one is 10000 yen.
For starters, I've got 120 chips for you.
You can choose how many chips we bet in each set, Jabami-san.
The proof is in the pudding, so let's begin.
What's the bet?
All right then....
Let's start with 2.
In this game it's pretty rare to have 3 different cards in your hand.
Because you draw 3 cards, it's common to get double cards like 2 rocks and 1 paper.
For example if you've got 2 rocks
then it's possible that rock is the most common card in the box.
Which means there's a high chance your opponent will play rock.
So you'd want to play paper.
You have to base your
decision on this uncertainty.
Have you decided?
Let's show out cards together,
on the signal.
Rock paper scissors!
You've got your first win,
jabami-san, congratulations.
Thank you.
I'll take two of your chips then.
So, you've got the rules down, right?
Let's keep going.
Yes. Next we'll bet...
50 chips.
50?
It's 500000 yen. That escalated quickly.
You're quite a gambler, Jabami-san.
Not really.
500000 yen on a single Rps game.
Are you ready?
Rock... paper... scissors...
Huh, a tie.
Let's play another card.
Rock paper scissors!
Yay!
I win!
Oh...
I would've lost no matter what, huh?
I'm glad to have won such a big game.
Next bet?
Let's...
go with 2.
Let us begin.
Rock paper scissors!
Congratulations.
The victory is yours, Jabami-san.
What's next?
Well...
Let's bet 50 chips again.
You're kidding me.
Did she forget the last time?
Interesting...
I like that.
Well then, let's go.
Rock paper scissors!
Seems like we think alike.
Next one...
Rock paper...
Scissors!
Yay, seems like I win again!
I'll be taking this 500,000 yen.
So far she's made 1,000,000 yen.
Now, let's keep going.
Huh? What's wrong?
Don't tell me you've got cold feet!
Can't say I blame you
after losing 1,000,000 yen.
Not at all.
The game is just getting started.
Next, let's bet 2 chips again.
It's over...
One has 216 chips and one has 24.
The gap is huge.
If she's scared when she's beaten and starts betting small, no way she can turn this around.
So, let's continue...
Rock paper scissors!
Scissors.
Well, well, Jabami-san.
Seems like you've lost all your chips.
She lost that much.
What a great game that was.
Saotome-san.
Would you be up for one more game?
Huh?
Don't do it, Jabami-san.
At this rate you'll become a livestock.
Of course!
What's your bet?
What a fool.
She's digging her own grave.
How about 10,000,000 yen?
What the?
Why do you carry that much cash?!
Don't be an idiot!
There's no way you can afford to bet that much on a single Rps game.
You're...
...crazy!
But isn't it what makes it fun?
Madness is the essence
of gambling, isn't it?
Naturally, in the capitalist society money is life.
A sane person wouldn't entrust his life to luck.
And yet a lot of people go to casinos.
Because people derive
pleasure from this insanity.
And so...
Gambling gets more
Interesting the crazier it is!
Shall we gamble?
President.
Today, a new student transferred to second year cherry blossom class.
So...
We've got ourselves
a snake in our paradise...
I-I won't follow you
In something so stupid.
Don't tell me you've got cold feet.
This idiot girl...
is making fun of me!
What is she...
She just transferred in and got involved in such a reckless game.
How can she stay so calm?
High stakes game
are so exciting, right?
Does she even realize that
10,000,000 yen is on the line?
Well, whatever.
I'm gonna win, because...
21 voters out of 30
are voting to give me an advantage.
They all have different reasons for it, like increasing their social status...
Regardless, those 21 "slaves"
will vote how I tell them.
This time rocks and papers
should be the most common.
There should be hardly any scissors.
Chances that Jabami would get them are low.
So if I play the paper I won't lose.
The problem would be if I don't get paper.
Two papers! Almost ideal!
I've won! This ends now!
Are you ready?
Shall we begin?
What's wrong?
You've only got 3 cards, not much you can do even if you take it slow.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
Huh?
Everyone is working for you,
saotome-san, right?
Although based on the results, not all of them are voting your way.
10 people... or maybe 20
to ensure your victory.
How dare y–
You didn't do a good job hiding it.
In two games where
you bet 500,000 yen,
you played the same cards both times.
So it's natural for me to think
that you were up to something.
When we weren't betting much,
you mixed you cards well.
That's was a bad attempt to hide it.
You can't fool anyone
If you're not prepared to lose money.
Would you stop with
your weird smack talk?
If you intend to end the game–
No, no, no.
I wouldn't dream of it.
Because...
The it's going to get much
more fun from now on.
How the hell can she be so calm.
Is she that confident
that she's gonna win?
Nah, that's not possible.
She can't be sure of victory
without knowing what I'll play.
It's a bluff.
If I play paper now, I'll win!
Done with your speech?
If so, why don't you
decide what card to play now?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Are you done?
Yes.
Let's begin!
Rock paper scissors!
Scissors.
Scissors?
No way, can't be...
It sure can.
You can see it with your own eyes.
Now then, let's talk about winnings.
Not counting the money I lost,
I get 8,800,000 yen.
Be so kind and pay up, please.
Why did this happen...?
I wanted to put her into a debt,
why did I end up losing
8,800,000 yen instead?
What in the world...
Who the hell is this girl?
Would you be so kind as to pay up?
N-No...
Come again?
I don't have it right now...
Could I possibly ask you
to wait a few days?
Saotome...
Today was very fun
so I'll consider it paid.
Have a nice day, everyone.
I hope you'll treat me
as an equal starting tomorrow.
Jabami-san!
Suzui-san.
Something wrong?
I want to ask you something.
How did you figure it all out?
It's easy.
From the start I knew that Saotome-san was manipulating votes.
So I only needed to know what card would be the most common.
But how?
Let's say that Saotome-san
had 20 people in her pocket.
She needed to get them to vote for the same card or it wouldn't work.
But as far as I could tell
there was no pattern to the votes.
On the other hand having to remember a particular order of the voted cards would be difficult.
So they must be deciding
what to vote for on the stop.
But how?
While using my chips
I observed Saotome-san
but she didn't sign
her followers whatsoever.
So was it a sound?
No...
It wasn't it.
This means that there
could be only one way to do so.
Instead of Saotome-san, someone else was giving a signal to the class.
If this is true then there had to be a person in class that her helpers would look at.
I was watching but then
I realized something.
I thought it was natural
that people would stare at me
but that was where
I was making my mistake.
They weren't staring at me...
In truth, they were staring
at the person behind me.
You figured that out too, huh?
The rest was easy.
Only thing I had to do is guess
the sign based on your actions.
My actions? But I was behind you.
Yes.
As you know,
a hand mirror is essential for any girl.
I see...
Can I ask you one more thing?
How did you managed
to pull scissors in the last round?
The probability of drawing
one should've been pretty low...
Ah... That was a complete coincidence.
I was lucky!
No way!
You used 1,200,000 yen
to find the truth.
And you mean that you bet 10,000,000 and relied on luck to win?
Yeah, well...
Thinking about it, there was no point in telling everyone about the trick–
you could've won more
games with this knowledge.
Yet you did this...
because you enjoy taking risks.
Well...
Taking risk on its own is pretty boring.
But having big advantage
Is boring too, you know?
You certainly are special.
I've never felt that way.
I'm going to drop out of this academy.
I had a big debt.
I owed 5,000,000 to Saotome Mary.
I tried to make some money by gambling but my debt just got bigger and bigger.
Like I was swimming trough a swamp.
I give up
If I had your strength, I'm sure things would've turned out differently.
Jabami-san!
I'm truly sorry.
That reminds me,
I want you to have it as thanks.
Please.
Today I had a fun time gambling.
This isn't much to express
the my feelings, but please take it.
N-No.
I was a part of the scheme,
I can't take this.
I dislike situations where I know for sure if I'm going to win or lose.
Because it's not really gambling.
Thanks to you, I was able to play a fun and stimulating game today.
Thank you very much.
I was able to see her smile quite clearly.
There was no pity
or resentment towards me.
She just wanted to thank me because she was able to enjoy the game today.
She's not a normal girl.
She's a gambling enthusiast...
A compulsive gambler.
This is all because I lost to you!
Jabami-senpai!
Let's do it!
Episode 2
Boring Woman
Perhaps I should meddle a little bit?