I know you’re worried about Tosaki-san,
but please try to stay calm.
I won’t let you escape!
However you think about it,
picking a fight with America isn’t rational.
They’ve taken the road we expected.
Oh no!
I really hate women like you.
You picked this fight.
Kuro-chan, just once more,
please!
It really would have been best
to keep you locked up for experiments!
You should learn when
to shut your mouth!
Make no mistake.
I’m just
starting a new life.
The minister-
What about the minister’s schedule?
You mean-
Was it today?!
What were you thinking?
All our plans have gone to waste!
Ha, playing dead
is pretty fun.
Your demands were
the recognition of rights for Ajin, correct?
I can help you!
Satou-san.
He said they’d recognize our demands...!
Politicians.
Lying is their job.
The only lead we had was the minister.
Now he’s dead.
There’s nothing more to be done.
It seems like
there’s still hope.
We have one target remaining.
President Hashiguchi of Musashi Heavy Industries.
At the Board of Directors meeting
in three days, at 7 p.m.,
I’m going to kill him.
He’s giving a date and time for the attack?
Satou-san might like to fight,
but what he really likes is playing games.
This is a declaration of war.
No matter how he tries to hide,
we'll find him and kill him.
So you’re holding the board of director’s meeting?
Isn’t that pretty reckless?
What are your plans for security?
Will you be okay?
No matter what happens,
I refuse to give in to terrorists.
I am Chief Cabinet Secretary Mitsui.
In response to continued acts of terrorism,
the Cabinet has met and decided as
a result to enact a new law.
Under these new measures,
a new defensive force has been formed.
They will be called...
The Anti-Ajin Special Force.
What’s this about?
What about our civil rights?
Things are getting worse for Ajin!
Shit!
They said “Anti-Ajin Special Force”...
Can we really beat an opponent like that?
What should we do, Tanaka-san?
If we mess this up,
all of us will end up at the research labs!
That’s why I said
It’s too late. We can’t turn back.
But-
There’s no place
left to turn back to!
Now...
all we can do is trust Satou-san.
This is
the newly improved
blinding laser.
Please take a look.
It fires in 1.3 seconds,
and damages the retina, causing loss of vision.
This taser gun was also improved
to a strength of 2 million volts.
Be they ajin or anything else,
this should instantly take away their freedom.
It’s wireless?
Yes.
In a free-for-all fight, it’s easy to use,
and we’ve made it able to rapid-fire.
As for IBM countermeasures,
there’s the miniaturized impulse water cannon.
Oh, and
I’ve also prepared smoke grenades.
And last is this.
Jointly developed with a German small arms maker,
an airburst grenade launcher.
It hasn’t been used yet in actual combat,
but when we tested it here on-site,
the executioners were pretty happy with it.
Executioners?
By accurately detonating a high-explosive
projectile above a target,
we can render any cover ineffective.
Please take a look.
As for whether it’s effective,
it’s been tested on the ajin Tanaka.
The laser range finder
measures the distance to the target,
and automatically transmits the detonation distance to the grenade.
It’s an outstanding weapon.
Most importantly, you’re pleased with it.
I’ll have enough prepared for each
member of your forces.
Honestly...
I didn’t expect this much.
In a few days,
Satou will be headed to the research lab too.
Oh, that’s right.
Nekozawa-san...
Next week or so, it’d be better to head
overseas for a bit.
Ah.
Things are getting kind of tough in this country.
Satou-san,
exactly how far do you plan to take this?
Hm?
Until I rule this country.
The plan will be carried out in two days.
This is genuinely our last chance.
The field is the headquarters of
Musashi Heavy Industries.
Ooh!
Hm.
According to Tosaki-san’s information,
the board of director’s meeting will be held
in the president’s office on the top floor.
(screen- Headquarters of Musashi Heavy Industries)
The Anti-A’s will line the sides of the 24th floor.
We’ll be located here.
There seems to be a supply room
on the 21st floor.
Then when Satou and crew come to invade,
we’ll jump out and attack!
There’s nothing at all written about that.
Eh.
First we’ll be on standby?
We can’t get involved in the fight between
Satou and the Anti-As.
Oh, that’s right.
Once the Anti-As are beaten,
our plan will begin.
Shimomura-san and my team
will prepare for a close-combat attack,
and we have Nakano as back-up.
Tosaki-san,
please handle communications.
Yes.
I already have the tools prepared.
With this...
there’s only one problem left.
We need some way to get us into position...
The circumstances now are different
than with the minister.
I’ll think of a different way-
Keep your mouth shut.
Come on, Tosaki-san!
Are you still mad?
Shut up.
We follow the plan,
I’ll figure something out.
Um...
Tosaki-san.
I’m still against it.
If something goes wrong-
Shut up and drive.
Yes.
Considering the crumbling of the
Japan Self-Defense Force,
they were originally a foreign
mercenary squad?
They were passed down to me
and used by my predecessor.
Of course, with approval from the minister.
You want them as insurance in case
the Anti-Ajin forces lose?
Yes.
They’re also used to dealing with ajin.
They’re pros when it comes to fighting.
It’s out of the question.
To begin with,
your expulsion from the Management
Committee has already been decided.
With the mess from the Minister’s assassination,
they just haven’t given the official orders.
That’s why, if I get this final chance-
What is it?
Ah. Got it.
I’ll be there soon.
As you can see, I’m busy with work.
I’m sorry, but this is where I leave you.
The day this facility was attacked.
I killed the man from the Department of Defense.
The fact that they discovered Professor
Ogura's confinement-
Heh,
that really got to me.
What are you saying?
Have you already lost your mind?
Maybe.
But if I leaked this incident,
you and I would both go to hell.
Why me?
Ogura Ikuya is alive.
He really is something.
To think he’d lay hands on an American.
We don’t know anything about this.
Got it? We know nothing.
Tosaki-senpai acted alone in all of
these selfish actions.
You’re a full-fledged criminal.
Shall we go to hell together?
You want to add four people to security, is it?
Five.
Shimomura-kun will move with us.
Oh, and one more thing.
There’s still something else?
Prevent my expulsion from the Committee.
Yes, this is the security division.
Sokabe-san?
It went well, didn’t it?
I bought some for you.
Tosaki-san.
Um...
I’m sorry about earli-
You did your job.
There’s no need to apologize.
What are you doing?
Get the car moving.
Yes!
Somehow it’s finished in time.
The secret weapon.
It’s beautiful.
Hey, who are they?
Ah, it’s the Anti-As.
Reporting from 500 meters outside the headquarters
of Musashi Heavy Industries.
Less than six hours remain before Satou's
planned attack on the facility.
According to those involved, the Anti-Ajin
Special Force has already been deployed,
and security are on the scene.
Additionally, all the staff of Musashi Heavy
Industries have been evacuated, so only
President Hashiguchi and a few officials remain in the building.
Tonight, we bring the hammer down on the corporations who regard ajin
as mere animals for experimentation,
and who have repeatedly carried
out unjust experiments.
That will be
a big step towards
our hope for a new future.
We depart at 1700 hours.
Let’s give them a show today!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We’ve arrived at our post.
Roger that.
However you think about it, I don’t
think we need insurance.
Ghost countermeasures are up to you.
That’s not what you say to a genius.
If signs appear,
give us instructions at once.
However you think about it, I don’t
think we need insurance.
Yes.
If the Anti-As can’t win,
there’s no one in this country
that can stop Satou.
How grand. You even brought satellites out?
This is communications. Satellite setup complete.
With permission from the secretary of defense.
The government’s taking this seriously too.
We can finally end this idiotic uproar today.
Five minutes remain.
Satellite footage shows all clear.
Point 2. All clear.
Point 3. All clear.
Point 4. All clear.
How do they plan to arrive?
It won’t be possible to topple a building.
They can’t pull a stunt like that this time.
Our airborne defenses are flawless,
and the sewers have been closed.
This is
an impregnable fortress.
Well, shall we start our playthrough?
Roger that.
President.
Momentarily...
Ah.
Let’s get started.
Stop! Oy! Stop! The road’s closed!
This is Point 2.
A suspicious vehicle has stopped
at the roadblock!
From the front gate?!
Like a moth to a flame.
Don’t be afraid of damage.
Take them in!
Out of the vehicle!
Put both hands in the air.
Get down from the vehicle immediately!
Out!
We’ve got him!
You weren’t good enough.
Check the back!
What’s that?
Like I said,
it’s a secret weapon.
Secure the backup!
The electricity!
Switch it over!
What’s going on?
Oy!
It’s coming down!
W-Wait!
It’s your turn, Okuyama-kun.
It- It's this bad already?
What’s going on?
Confirm the situation!
All electronic devices are down!
They can’t be started up!
Power has been lost!
Shimomura-kun?
Can you hear me?
Shit.
It’s an EMP.
Huh?
They made an electromagnetic pulse weapon.
With that, all electronics have burned out.
It’s likely
that all electronics within a radius of
a few hundred meters are disabled.
What’s that?
Fire!
Let’s give them a show.
Shit.
I love it when a plan comes together.
Alright.  Anchor setting OK.
Pull the lead rope.
Roger!
What’s going on?
Nagai!
Calm down, Nakano.
First, let your eyes adjust.
Tosaki-san.
Tosaki-san!
It’s no good.
The connection’s dead.
What do we do?
What should we do?!
Nakano-kun, calm down!
According to the plan, first we wait.
No...
Let’s move.
Eh?
This time we’re electricians?
It’s called power line maintenance.
Airburst grenade launcher.
Taser gun.
Laser blinding.
All impossible to use.
Communication devices are also dead.
This situation in itself is a chance.
I have an idea.
Abandon all electronic devices.
Go with the usual equipment.
From here on...
it’s a primitive fight with a single blade!
It really gets you going!
Will this really go well?
Satou-san keeps to his word.
That will be his downfall.
Let’s start the plan.
To be continued...
Preview