This is your final warning.
This country...
Give me Japan.
This is poison gas!
The government has instructed all citizens to take shelter indoors,
but signs of panic are appearing in every region.
What are you doing?
Doesn't this make it war for real?
What are you saying, Tanaka-kun?
I’ve been saying from the beginning.
That this is war!
That fuck Satou,
he’s completely off his rocker.
But... what will we do now?
As for that, I have an idea.
Nagai!
Why did you come back?
Isn’t it obvious?
In order to stop Satou, you need me.
Don’t fuck with me!
What can you do now?
I know you don’t trust me.
I don’t care about that.
But...
I will stop Satou.
That’s what I ought to do.
Nagai-kun!
You-
It- It’s an explosion!
Could it be the Self-Defense Force base that
Satou is occupying?
All of a sudden,
it seems there’s been an explosion!
They’re really making a show out of it.
Yes.
I want to talk.
We’ve finished collecting the missiles.
Begin the search.
Roger.
Bring him in at any cost.
We can’t let him make fools out of us.
We’ll teach him a lesson.
They hate being made fools of
more than anything else.
This should make them get serious.
This is fun, isn’t it, Tanaka-kun.
You’re probably the only one who can say antagonizing
the U.S. military is fun, Satou-san.
But that lethal gas,
did you intend to let go of it?
Killing unresisting opponents with
poison gas is boring.
If they don’t come at you with the
intent to kill, it’s no fun!
This is the search team.
We’ve found Satou’s escape route.
We’ll send a support team soon.
Commander.
It’s the Pentagon.
Hello.
Yes.
All the missiles are safe.
We’re starting the search immediately.
Eh-
No, but-
If you do that-
Understood.
Very well.
What did they say?
Connect me to the Prime Minister.
In short,
the plan is to release the recovered nerve gas
underground, and render Satou powerless?
Capture Satou, and clean up this situation.
It was decided that that’s the only way.
But...
if we do that, it will take an enormous amount
of time to evacuate the citizens,
and he could escape during that-
No-
In order to avoid alerting Satou,
we can’t evacuate the citizens.
So they’re collateral damage?
Of course, we can treat it as part of
Satou’s terrorism.
He’ll become responsible for all
wrongdoing.
This isn’t about outward appearances!
How can you think about the
citizens this way?
The truth is, we have already transferred
control to the U.S. army.
We have no right to veto the plan.
It can’t be...
We have seven hours until the plan goes into action.
If we capture Satou before then,
the gas won’t be released.
That is the only option we have.
No, but...
Haven’t I said?
This is the result of your Ajin Management Committee's
failure to take care of Satou!
Back here again?
There’s no need to be on your guard.
We’re not planning to lure you into a trap.
Why did you contact us?
You took on Satou-san twice and
are still here to tell the tale.
We simply judged that this was the
only place of resistance.
We want to lend our power to stop Satou-san.
And in return?
Satou-san isn’t one to let traitors live.
Just three people on your side?
There were more at Musashi Heavy Industries.
Everyone else fled.
They said that it was insane to
fight back against Satou.
I have to agree.
Tanaka-san too?
No, he-
-stayed with Satou-san, didn’t he.
Who cares about him.
In order to stop Satou,
your only choice is to team up with us.
Like Tanaka-san said,
you’re a pretty disagreeable kid.
Be quiet, you scum.
There’s no way we can easily trust
terrorists like you!
What?
What did you just say, you bastard?
We’re only like this
because all of you wanted to use us ajin
as animals for experimentation!
What will you do?
Join us? Or no?
Hang on a minute.
Yes.
Shall we make a deal?
Senpai.
Sokabe.
A somewhat unfavorable situation has arisen.
Tell me your conditions immediately.
Tsk!!
A long phone call at a time like this?
You all.
Do you know where Satou-san is?
He should be in the hiding place underground.
Come with me.
What?
What are you doing?
Don’t dilly-dally.
Izumi-san. Welcome back!
Are we really joining forces with
the terrorists?
Yes.
We have no other choice,
and there’s no time.
This is Takahashi-san, Gen-san, and Okuyama-san.
Yo.
Genocide.
Pops!
Got ‘em!
You’ll pay for that!
Idiot!
Stop it!
Where’s Pops?
Where did you hide him?
Hey, calm down.
We let him go.
Huh?
Really?
Yeah.
He’s probably with his family now.
You got it now? Stupid kid.
What do you mean, stupid!
Stop it!
Like I’m gonna let you-
Nagai!
Look what happens with all these
ajin in one place.
It’s almost like a harem.
Yes.
Leave that to me.
Cut it out, you guys!
Hurry up and get inside!
Ah, wait a minute.
Oh!
I hope you’re happy with these.
If we do this, we’ve got to make it showy.
At present the U.S. military is closing off this sphere,
with the Self-Defense Force garrison at its center.
They plan to sacrifice all the people
in this area, and capture Satou.
Sacrifice, as in...
They’re releasing the nerve gas underground.
It’s only natural that tens of thousands of people
will be sacrificed in the process.
The plan will be carried out at 3 a.m.
About four hours remain.
Before then, we have to capture Satou at any cost!
Got it?
Yeah.
Obviously!
However, the Anti-Ajin Special Forces are
also moving to stop Satou.
We have to execute a plan that
it won’t conflict with theirs.
Then, as for a plan,
this is the map that Okuyama-san put together
of the underground tunnels in Tokyo.
Satou-san’s hideout is here.
Satou-san is calling the U.S. forces here,
and plans to fight.
In other words,
no matter who comes,
he’s getting ready to face them.
What on earth is Satou planning?
Civil rights and an independent nation,
both of those things were no good.
What’s his objective?
Tosaki-san, when you play games,
is it because you’re excited to save Princess Peach?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Sure, you need a story,
but you’re playing because it’s fun
to jump on turtles, aren’t you?
No idea. I don’t play video games.
He means that Satou’s a simple person.
He’s not a revolutionary or a tactician.
He’s just a player.
And that’s exactly why we have room
to take advantage of him.
What do you plan to do?
Bury him alive.
Tanaka-kun.
I’m leaving that enemy to you.
Ah, hold on, it’s too sudden-
Ah... I died.
You just don’t get any better
at shooting, do you.
I’m sorry I’m so bad!
Ah, we have guests.
A midnight party, I suppose.
Ah, this really gets you going!
As you know, our opponent is the strongest
armed force in the world.
We have to give them a warm welcome.
Was this your goal from the beginning?
Hm?
I mean,
to lure out the U.S. government.
And that’s why you saved me, and gathered
associates, and did all that terrorism.
Not at all!
If you know what the last boss is from the beginning, where’s the fun?
I see.
Then, this is the end?
What?
I mean, if we beat the last boss, that’s the end, isn’t it.
For a game.
Ha!
What are you saying, Tanaka-kun?
The real thrill of games starts with
the second playthough.
Excuse me.
For stepping in on your fun.
Nagai-kun, was it.
That was fast.
I’m surprised you found this place.
Even in the sewers,
you can’t hide the smell of a murderer.
Ah, it was Okuyama-kun and the others.
That certainly was beyond my expectations.
But anyhow,
it sounds interesting, so I guess it’s okay.
This is even more interesting.
The U.S. army that you’re waiting for...
By the way, Nagai-kun, do you remember?
Didn’t I tell you,
I hate people getting in my way?
Who knows.
But Satou-san,
you’re getting in my way-
I’m asking if you have a good memory!
Answer the question!
There are three ways to strike a person like Satou.
Number one- provocation.
Incoming!
Go, ghost!
Kill!
Number two- diversion.
Too bad.
You missed.
Ghost!
In a row?
You’re as impressive as ever.
Number three-
pretend we’re scared,
and run away.
Fall back for now!
Today I won’t let you go.
If we can lure Satou to this point,
then all that’s left is to explode the
ceiling, and bury him alive.
I see.
Once he’s buried alive, he can’t move no matter
how many times he revives.
Exactly.
That's our chance..
One more time, ghost!
Fight to the death to stop him!
I know that!
That bastard!
How many of those can he produce?
Nagai-kun’s black stuff- there’s a lot of it.
But even so,
he can’t bring out more than one at a time.
Shit!
It’s been immobilized!
I can’t use my ghost for while!
Hurry!
The remaining problem is making sure
Satou-san doesn't catch you, right.
With my ghost, I’m sure we can manage somehow.
Your way of planning and train of thought
is exactly the same as Satou’s,
but you have a poor endgame.
Nagai!
Oh well.
I’ll provide you some insurance.
No... problem!
Let’s go!
Is this a parting, Okuyama-kun.
It was fun playing together.
I’m sorry.
Sorry about your toys, Okuyama.
Ah, when did you get so good?
You can do anything with practice.
Shall we go?
Select ‘Continue’.
We got away, Nagai.
Just a little more.
They’re here.
Kuro-chan!
Wait.
Don’t stop him unnecessarily.
At this rate...
we’re almost there!
This kind of fun you can only have with ajin.
What?
To continue our talk from earlier-
Satou-san!
You can wait as long as you want,
but the U.S. forces aren’t coming!
They plan to do you in with nerve gas!
You’re joking, right?
Everyone’s fed up with playing your games!
What?
Burying us alive...
Satou-san!
You put some thought into it.
But... just when you thought you’ve won...
The rug gets pulled out from under you!
Alright. I’ll go contact Sokabe.
What?
No way!
Are they digging in?
We overdid it!
No, the floor-
It’s going down!
Less than 35 minutes remain.
I’ll kill... every last one of you!
Tosaki-san!
Are you alright?
Game... start!
To be continued...
Preview
Next week’s episode will air at 3:10 a.m.