Stop!
Haven't you cared for anyone in your life?
Then what about the friend who helped you run away!
I don't need him anymore.
Shut up.
Dumbass. Dumbass.
Dumbass. Dumbass. Dumbass! Dumbass!
Flight TA167 which was flying from Haneda airport headed for Naha airport,
Passenger aircraft crash lands at sea
has experienced unknown difficulties and has made an emergency landing on the sea.
I-It was Satou.
Passenger aircraft crash lands at sea
There's no mistake.
He shot the security people...
and then, he k-killed Mr. Sakurai.
T-Then the door exploded!
The murders of Mr. Wakai and Mr. Sakurai...
We the police, with our utmost dignity and pride on the line,
will track down and arrest the mastermind, Satou.
The path is still long,
but the feeling of accomplishment after all this will be exceptional.
Let's have fun!
#KamiFS@irc.rizon.net
http://kamifansubs.com
I'm Always Scared
Ogura-san.
If it's a cigarette, I'm not giving you one.
It's my telomere.
A cigarette?
Do you mean the particles at the end of a chromosome?
How do you know that?
I was aiming to be a medical student.
I bet you were aiming to be a delinquent.
Here.
I didn't come here to ask for a cigarette.
Then, what do you want?
I see...
So that's why you've not been going all out recently.
Being afraid of your pet dog means you have little courage.
It's useless to be able to bring out many if I can't even control it.
What's the cause of that?
A boy said "fatty" to the woman across from him.
What?
But, he's not a bad boy.
He just imitated what his mother usually gossips about.
As you can see in the case of the Ajin from Iowa,
the behavior of an independent IBM
is dependent on the owner's nature.
For example, if you hated humans,
that would be the reason behind your IBM acting violently.
If you want to change your IBM,
you'll have to change yourself.
Humans don't change.
That's true.
Nagai!
Tosaki-san is calling for you.
Oh, alright.
What the hell? That's so creepy.
There's thirteen targets remaining.
The enemy will appear somewhere in this list without fail.
Therefore, an ambush is the best course of action.
The problem is where to set up an ambush.
Why don't we just do it at the next target, Kishi?
We can't afford having more people killed, can we?
No.
Mr. Kishi has already concelaed himself somewhere in tight security.
Even I don't know where he is.
If Tosaki-san was in the list, we could've made you bait.
Shut up, Nagai.
Then, that leaves only one person.
That's right.
The only person who meets the condition is
the fourteenth target,
the Minister of Health, Labor, and Welfare.
What? Are you just going to give up on the rest then?!
The targets are all under security from the police, and
we don't know when or where the targets may be attacked.
We don't have any means of interfering.
But if it's the minister, Tosaki-san can figure out his schedule, and if we know that,
then we can make predictions as to where and when the minister may be attacked.
We can also figure out Satou's patterns by the time it's the minister's turn.
Yeah.
If we can do that, I'll make plans to be able to enter the fight.
I've made a list of places that the minister may
be attacked with the information at hand.
You are going to prepare a plan for each place, correct?
The remaining problem is how we fight.
There are three Ajins. We lack in number compared to the enemy,
but since we can prepare beforehand, we have the advantage of the locations.
Three Ajins? There's no way we can use Shinomura-san!
What kind of disad—
There's no way I'm letting a woman take part in such a dangerous thing!
We're not doing a sports day here!
Be it a child or an old person, we'll be using everything we can.
You!
Nakano-kun.
I'm happy, but it's not helpful.
I have no intent on slacking off on my work.
Of course this will happen!
Ok.
Let's take a break real quick.
I have to return some e-mails as well.
Is it alright being that laid back, Tozaki-san?!
Even if we rush, it'll just worsen the quality.
Even Satou won't have an easy time looking for Mr. Kishi's whereabouts.
Also, Nakano
Huh?
my name is Tosaki.
Learn it already.
Hey! What do you mean by impossible?
Weren't you bragging about being able to do anything as long as you have this?
There are limits on what can be done by certain objects.
Yo! Have you made any progress?
I give up.
I've ransacked the servers of the Ajin Management Committee as well as the ministry,
but I've hit on nothing.
Can't we just skip Kishi and go on to Iwasaki Keita?
Rejected.
I've decided to do things in order this time.
I will follow the rules.
It's the same as a game.
But if you don't know Kishi's location, we're checkmated here.
There's always tricks in games, aren't there?
Even if we don't know the location of Kishi-san, but
if we can figure out where the police protecting him are, it's fine.
Now, just hack the police department.
Isn't that even more impossible?
No. That goes into the "possible" category.
Of course, if you start from scratch, it'll take several days, but similar to the ministry,
the police department server should also have backdoors
that the engineers have created in times of emergency.
If you borrow them and can find them in the first place,
then you can enter from the backdoor and close it.
What's he saying?
If you close the backdoor, the logs will be erased, and no trace of entry will be left!
It's probably a trick.
Since they're not expecting someone to enter form the backdoor, their security will be loose...
I finished.
The escort target is Kishi Yuuji.
They've put in two groups of riot police,
as well as the transportation division and the life safety division.
It seems like the enemy can't afford to hold back either.
Where's the location?
It's inside the mountains.
Why don't you calm down a bit?
You won't last long in that state.
Yeah, that's right.
Who is it?!
It's a ghost...
There's two ways to destroy an IBM.
The first is to wait for the time limit.
The second is to hit the IBM's head with another IBM.
When two IBMs hit each other in the head,
particles containing information get jumbled up.
It's a state of melee.
The communication between the particles becomes normal in recombination.
As a result,
they offset each other.
Turn off the power during a lesson, Glasses!
It's Tosaki.
What did you say?
How was the location found out?
Yeah. I'll leave that place to you.
I'll come back immediately.
Is it about Kishi-san?
Yeah. He got killed.
The moment we strengthened our security, they turned to assassination using IBMs.
Damn it.
How was the location found out?
It's unknown.
Unless we can figure out that method,
it's useless no matter where we hide the targets.
We can't buy time.
We've lost one of our advantages.
You...
I heard that you've been skipping out on IBM training.
Our greatest strength is your IBM.
Make sure you're able to control it as soon as possible.
Understood?
It seems like you're this team's telomere.
The enemy is armed.
At the very least, remember how to handle a gun this much.
First, try holding it.
Then...
I love machines. They actually listen to what you say.
What? There's no rapidfire button?
Shut up! Just watch first.
Huh? Nothing's coming out.
Give it to me.
Here.
Thank you!
O...Ow...!
You idiot! Why are you letting it go?!
My hands hurt...
Are you a woman?!
Even if you say that, I can't help it if it hurts!
Um... Can I ask you a—
Oh, it's you, Nagai.
Do you need something?
No...
It's nothing. I'll ask later.
I heard from Manabe that you went to see him, but did you need something?
I just thought it might be better if we had body weight and height data.
But it's totally fine without them.
That's good then.
You...
Are you lonely?
Huh?
You're not?
Then,
I suppose that you might be lost.
You're worrying if your actions
that don't take into account others' emotions are correct or not.
You're wondering if you should change.
Am I wrong?
You're wrong!
I... I haven't said anything out of the ordinary.
I'm only thinking logically about what to do.
What do I need to change?
Yes... that's completely right.
Huh?
Nakano is good at gaining trust from others.
If you're in the same classroom,
he's the hero and you're probably just a bad guy.
But we're not at a school.
You're going to need to be able to throw away your ethics and emotions and make a decision.
It's true.
You can do that.
I know that already.
Is that so?
Then it's just my misunderstanding.
My father was an excellent surgeon.
He could get friendly with the patients —
he would get letters from discharged patients every year.
But that was also his greatest weakness.
When I was nine years old,
he tried to save a patient who didn't have a donor and took part in an illegal organ trade.
As a result, my father lost everything.
I won't make the same mistake.
I'm not an idiot.
How smart you are isn't based on seniority. Do as you wish.
All we will do is move according to the plan.
These are the important points in the anti-Satou plan containing everyone's opinions.
Everyone, get this all into your heads!
Yes, sir.
Nakano.
What?
Especially you.
How do you read this?
That's "shinkou."
Hey, hey.
You expect us to do this?!
We're not Ajins!
Nagai, this part was made by you, wasn't it?
And?
It's exciting!
Hey!
What is it?
Do you...
know of a good way to die?
Huh?
The professor told me!
The activation of IBM is totally based on luck.
An Ajin's IBM amount is the greatest after revival.
Sometimes, something special occurs.
It's also known as the tunnel effect.
Which tunnel do I need to go to?
The one you're going to is to "that" world.
If there's one way to activate an IBM, there is one.
It's to die multiple times.
What?
I've died a lot though...
Unless you draw tens or hundreds of times, you won't get your Hawaii vacation!
With this you can die at a low cost and automatically.
It even works when you're asleep.
There's also no pain involved.
Alright!
I guess I'll do it.
There's nothing to be scared of.
How can you die without any hesitation?
You've died multiple times as well.
But, I'm always scared about dying!
Because, in the worst case scenario...
we might not come back to life!
This is just a rumor,
but a Chinese Ajin obsessed with dying died over 2000 times.
Apparently, that Ajin is still updating his record.
Wow...
We'll do anything.
Otherwise, we can't move on.
There's no need to be scared.
You... you're amazing.
Just die already!
What? You're leaving?
Are you a child? I'm busy you know.
You're so cold-hearted, aren't you?
That's right...
there's no need to be afraid.
Do as you please!
I won't bug you anymore,
so do as you please.
I know that already.
I'm not an idiot you know.
Everyone here is an idiot.
Serves you right!
You!
There's a ton of sea—
Your friend is in a juvenile prison.
Huh?
That day...
On the day you were sent to the research facility.
He was arrested by the police.
Why are you telling this to me now?
If I were to betray you,
are you planning to use Kaito and blackmail me?
Just as you used my fiancé against me.
Your cards are only useful if you don't reveal your hand.
You don't need that friend anymore, right?
I determined it to not be a useful card anymore, so I am telling you.
Also, don't eat this kind of stuff during a diet!
He's a horrible guy.
A juvenile prison, huh...
I did something bad to Kai.
But,
thinking about what I'm going to be doing,
I guess it might be the safest place.
You're going to be in this group cell from today.
To be continued...
I Feel Like Throwing Up