Episode 13: Memories to Come
Shisogapo, Lumpur
International Airport
What's the purpose of your visit?
Well, um...
Sightseeing.
Hmph. Okay.
Have a nice trip.
Please, the list.
First, I need to find someone
with an ability to search.
I guess I'll ask their leader.
A city in the Philippines
It's got to be this one.
Now... What kind of an ability will he have...
This guy?
Let's see...
If you move, I'll burn everything including you.
You're the leader, right?
Who are you?
Um...
An ability-wielder, just like you.
Why can't I read his mind?
Um... "Why can't I read..."
He stole my ability?
Let's see...
That's right!
This really is a useful ability...
Question: How do you look for ability-wielders?
Don't think... Don't think... Don't think...
Angelo?
So that guy's sis is finding the ability-wielders
for you, huh? Thank you!
Damn you....
Goddammit!
Door, open up!
What?
Are you Angelo?
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Your ability is an sickness.
You don't have to use it anymore.
Oh gosh...
I see. You just have to look at the map.
This is amazing...
His ability to seek ability-wielders is perfect.
Northern South Africa
Earlier this morning, the UN announced that the
democratic revolutionary army,
an organization based in various
parts of Asia, had been subjugated.
The UN Chairman Brian Jackson
reported that "a young—
—man suspected to be the ringleader, and that
everyone has been apprehended unhurt."
Ouch!
For what is to come, he answered,
"We will look out for attacks from remaining forces.
There even is a useful ability like this?
I hope there will be a quick,
peaceful resolution."
It looks like there are other places
that are gathering ability-wielders...
A city in Egypt
Be careful of the One-Eyed Grim Reaper!
T-The One-Eyed Grim Reaper!
What an embarrassing nickname...
I didn't think I would be called that of all people...
What was that? That image just now...
I guess I became able to learn what
the plundered ability is without knowing it.
Big Brother, I plundered every
ability of yet another country.
I took an ability to translate languages,
and an ability to be active without sleeping at all.
That's amazing. But, don't
overexert yourself too much, Yu.
No... I have to finish off the next country
as soon as possible. Time is precious.
You're right... It may be rough, but I'm counting
on you to be done before you lose your ability.
Yeah...
An ability to make illnesses worse...?
Northern Afghanistan Mountains
The ability-wielders are all clumped up again...
To make children do something like that...
One clump only has one glimmer...
What does this mean?
What the..? No images are popping up...
What kind of a facility is this?
Carriers?
Oh, so that's what this means.
I get it. They've been infected, but the ability
hasn't broken out yet, so they're carriers.
But, I can't plunder an ability
before it breaks out...
What should I do?
Exactly. The special abilities are truly a disease.
So, before particles are spread all over Earth again,
we need to vaccinate every person in the world.
That's right...
If it's an illness, I can make it worse,
and have the ability break out.
Wouldn't that make plundering possible?
All right, that went well...
So that new ability-wielders don't show up
from countries after I leave them...
I need to plunder from all
carriers as well from now on...
Eastern India
Shoot until you're out of ammo!
Peru Republic
Well, thank you very much.
So there was someone with
an ability to heal...
I'm glad you got all better.
I'm sorry. Even if you were using your ability for good,
I have to plunder it from you...
This hand... If I put this hand on
my right eye right now...
I can regain my stature as
wielder of the time-leap ability...
With this, I might be even able to save Kumagami.
No, that's not it. I didn't plunder
abilities for something like that.
I can't allow for acts that break
human reason any longer...
I'm going to turn this world into
one with zero ability-wielders.
That is my only mission.
A city in Cuba
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Incoming call - Shunsuke Otosaka
Shut up!
SHUT UP!
Hey, are you all right?
Are you the enemy...
So are you my enemy?
Anything but my life!
That's right... Calm down...
Calm down... I shouldn't kill anyone...
Western Saudi Arabia
They have announced that they have captured
Mayor Muscle of their capital Hassan.
According to government insiders, an attack at the
mayor's mansion by the coup d'état army has started,
So I'm going here tomorrow... Once in a while, even if
I have to force myself, I should sleep a little...
and he is said to have
been captured at that time.
According to government reports, this attack has
killed at least 10 city legislators and injured 20 more.
It is necessary to rest one's body every so often...
Currently at the capital—
The government has announced this morning
that the leader of the coup d'état,
Mofsen bin Yagid, has agreed to unconditional surrender.
The ongoing combat within the capital from last year were
by a syndicate that was comprised of primarily children,
What?
What's going on?
but due to a skirmish yesterday instigated by a
mysterious individual, it seems they have suffered major damages.
What?
With that, the coup d'état forces—
Did I do this?
—agreed that the syndicate led by
Mofsen will not be further prosecuted...
This isn't good... My memory is
starting to muddle....
... for other crimes, leaving the focus now to
how the government will respond from hereon.
So I shouldn't sleep after all...
Southern Italy
What in the world am I doing here...?
Why am I in a battlefield..?
What is this?
That's right... I made a promise...
That I would plunder every last
ability in the world, and then return to her...
Her..?
Who was she..?
I'm sure she was someone
very dear to me...
But I can't remember who...
Russian Federation
Hmm... So someone with the "explosion"
ability will show up there...
I see! So you're that "Reaper"!
Then, you can die off together with our principles!
What the... Dammit...
That ability only gives people misfortune.
A city in the United Kingdom
A city in Sicily
One-eyed..?
Can it be... The Reaper?
Yeah, I'm the Reaper.
Manhattan, New York
Hello! Reaper here!
Arizona
This is too tough for me... I don't want to do this...
Who the hell came up with such a huge task,
and why did it end up that I had to do it..?
This is enough, right? I'm tired
now! Someone take over for me!
I thought of something good.
Maybe I'll just take over this entire Earth!
After all, I'm omnipotent!
I am God! I decide everything! That's what I'll do!
What is this? It's filthy.
Why is it...?
Why am I regretting kicking this thing...?
Why am I crying because of it..?
What's up with this...
I still need to keep doing my best...?
Siberia, Irkutsk
I-It's the Reaper!
Southern Cambodia
Gimme that!
Turkey Northern Research Base
Why won't any of it hit?
Is that a monster?
That's the One-Eyed Grim Reaper!
There's no way we can win!
Out of my way!
That surely defeated him!
You're kidding me! That was an RPG!
You saved us.
Thank you.
We appreciate it!
Southeastern Australia
Beijing
It's close to here...
I did it!
I finally got that Reaper!
You shouldn't pick on the weak!
Pick on the weak? Do you know who the hell that is?
I don't know!
But you can't do something like that!
That guy has a huge bounty on his head!
If I nab him, I get a ton of cash!
Even then, you shouldn't!
Then, I guess you'll have to
see some pain as well.
Do as you like! I will never stand aside!
What is that?
Of all things...
The ability of the very last ability-wielder...
was the power of "courage", huh...
But that is merely reckless valor...
You were about to die there.
You should go home.
Y-You shouldn't!
You are a girl with more than enough courage.
So, you should be on your way.
T-Then, I'll go call for help!
I'll make sure to come back!
It's all over...
I promised...
I need to get back...
It's all over, so I need to get back...
I accomplished everything...
so I need to get back...
Get back...? To where..?
I need to get back...
I must have made a promise...
Now I can spend the rest
of my life fooling around.
W-What is that?
Yu!
Are you finally awake?
Thank you for all the hard work.
You kept our promise.
Ouch...
Your life is not in danger.
But, you need to quietly rest for a while.
Okay....
By the way, who are you?
So that's how things roll...
Of course, it's understandable.
Since you plundered thousands
-tens of thousands - of abilities...
...the stress caused by all that
to the brain must be staggering.
It's a blessing that you can even talk.
I am...
...your lover.
A lover? Even though
I don't recognize you at all?
That hurts... a lot more than I expected.
Did I make you sad just now?
You did.
Because we were in the same class,
and we lived our high school lives
together in the student council.
And before you left,
you promised me that we would be lovers.
I'm sorry... I can't remember anything at all.
Those flash cards... I made those.
So you held onto them until the very end.
Did they come in handy?
So this... You made this...?
Yes.
For me, this was something like a good-luck charm...
This was the one thing I couldn't part with.
Even though it's so tattered, and half torn...
Thank you... very much.
If you were able to come back
like this because of that...
I couldn't be happier.
Did I make you sad again?
No... I'm just happy. That is all.
I don't really get it... but please don't cry.
That's impossible.
Yu Otosaka...
Welcome back.
Grave of the Kumagami family
This was a camcorder that I kept recording things
I didn't want to record for the longest time.
I will record lots and lots of happy everyday life.
And so, let's leave behind lots
and lots of happy memories!
Sounds good.
Yup!
Can Ayu be a part of that as well?
Of course!
What should I say right now...?
Please, be honest.
I'm looking forward to what's to come.
Right! Everything is going to happen from now on!
That's right!
From now on, let's fill our lives
only with fun things.