Mom-
I’ll do it all over again.
This time...
I won’t run.
Where is Ogura Ikuya?
Tell him, Myers.
It’s tough being a lapdog, isn’t it.
Nagai-kun!
What are you doing?
Preparing to move the hideout!
We only have one chance to beat Satou.
We have to ambush him when he
attacks the minister.
But...
...the only one who knows when that
will happen is Tosaki-san!
Change of plan.
We’re going to rescue Tosaki-san.
Intruders!
I know you’re worried about Tosaki-san,
but please try to stay calm.
I know that.
Tosaki-san!
I won’t let you escape!
You’ll pay for that later.
This is bad, Hirasawa-san.
They’re heading towards...
the American Embassy.
The embassy is extraterritorial.
Neither the police nor the army
can lay a hand on them there.
If they make it there,
that’s the end!
Well then,
shall we give them a show?
New Opening Song Subs will be added next week!!
At the fastest, we can make it to the
embassy in about 10 minutes.
We won’t be able to catch them.
Only if they can continue to use
the regular roads.
Go get them!
However you think about it, picking a
fight with America isn’t rational.
Where are they?
At this point...
STOP
Alright!
They’ve taken the road we expected.
Let’s catch up.
Shimomura-san!
Can you hear me?
I hear you.
Where are they?
The side street by the park ahead.
STOP
Back up!
Oh no!
What are you-?
Reset.
Shit.
We made it this far...
Help me carry him!
Hurry up!
Where’s Tosaki-san?
They escaped!
But...
they’re still close.
Nakano!
Yeah!
Security will be strong near the embassy.
Hirasawa-san,
you clean up here!
This way.
Hurry up!
Let me go.
Shut up!
Where did they...?
I only have a few real bullets,
and one tranquilizer dart left.
I can’t afford to miss.
Don’t let your guard down.
They have an Ajin on their side.
I know!
Tosaki-san!
Where are you?
Let’s go.
If we can get past here,
the embassy is close.
Do something, just take her out!
Understood.
What a waste.
I’ve smashed your knees.
You can’t escape,
or die.
I hate women like you.
You picked this fight.
Are you stupid?
Even though you can’t send
out any more IBMs...
You could have escaped.
You didn’t need to go through
all this pain.
Did you think I wouldn’t realize?
How pitiful are you?
I...
...made up my mind.
Not to run...
...any more!
The IBM concentration is...
Kuro-chan, just once more,
please!
This contract is between me and you alone.
Obey my orders.
These are...
...her memories!
How useless are you?
If you’re gonna shoot, just do it!
I don’t need an Ajin that’s of
no use to me.
It really would have been best
to keep you locked up for experiments!
What-  How could-?
You should learn when
to shut your mouth!
Make no mistake.
I’m just
doing my job.
Tosaki-san!
Nagai!
This way!
I have no other way to defeat you.
But my work here is done.
I really...
...hate women like you.
Make no mistake.
I’m just
starting a new life.
Izumi-san!
Are you okay?
Tosaki-san.
Tosaki-san!
Where are we?
On our way back to the hideout.
Hirasawa-san and the others
are taking care of the clean-up.
You should thank Izumi-san.
If not for her,
who knows where you’d be now.
What?
The minister-
What about the minister’s schedule?
Eh?
I thought you were the only one
who knew about that.
What did you say?
So that’s how it was.
Uhh..
What are you talking about?
When is it?
You mean-
Was it today?!
What were you thinking?
Why didn’t you tell Nagai?
All our plans have gone to waste!
I’m sorry.
Everything we did was for today.
And despite that-
Despite that, you-!
Eh?
It’s not worth worrying about
what’s over and done.
It’s more important to think about what’s nex-
What about my phone?
Where’s my phone?
We picked it up for you.
Come on.
Pick up.
Yes,
It’s Sokabe.
Why?
How did the information leak?
This way!
How did things get like this?
I thought you guys were prepared
for this sort of thing.
Too late for you to complain.
This way is clear.
Minister. Let’s hurry.
Behind me!
Ha, playing dead
is pretty fun.
Watch out.
If you move, you lose your head.
Congratulations.
I didn’t think
you would make it this far.
Wow, what an honor.
To be praised by the minister himself.
Your demands were
a public announcement of the experiments
and a recognition of rights for Ajin, correct.
And if they were?
I can help you!
I work as a government minister.
I can't guarantee anything,
but I'll make a proposal to the prime minister.
The prime minister?
So he’ll recognize our demands?
Yes!
If you have me,
I can expose their crimes!
Isn’t your end goal
to create a country ruled by ajin?
Sa-
Satou-san!
You’re a better politician than I expected.
Alright, if you agree, then-
Thank you.
That was a wonderful performance.
Satou-san.
Why...?
Hm?
What?
I mean,
he said they’d recognize our demands...
Tanaka-kun, don't be so naive.
Politicians.
Lying is their job.
B- but!
S-spare us!
Yes.
Yes, it’s Sokabe.
Come on, you’re all so gloomy!
We got Tosaki-san back,
and our chance to stop Satou is still-
Zero.
The only lead we had was the minister.
Now he’s dead.
There’s nothing more to be done.
But!
If you have complaints, tell them to her.
We’ve finished.
Huh?
Wait.
What’s finished?
Cleaning up tonight's mess.
If we had left it,
it would have caused a stir.
Sorry about that.
You shouldn't have to do something your salary doesn't cover.
We don’t care about that,
but we don’t know where the other
Ajin has gone.
Since it’s her,
you don’t have to worry.
I’m sure no one will find her.
Are you covering for her because
she’s an Ajin?
That’s not why- !
If you do that again,
I’ll send you to the dissection table.
Tosaki-san!
How could you?!
More importantly, what about Nagai?
I haven’t seen him around.
He’s also doing clean-up.
Using the laptop we got from
the Americans’ car,
he’s sending an email to the
Department of Defense.
The incidents with Professor Ogura,
and at the safe house...
he’s reporting Satou as the
culprit of all of those attacks.
Are you saying that Satou kidnapped me?
If I do that,
maybe the Americans will go after Satou.
They might stop him for us.
And while you’re at it,
you’ll have those two Americans
go missing, with that email
as their last trace.
You’re very crafty.
I’ll take that as a compliment.
You don’t need that word.
What?
But...
It doesn’t sound native,
but it’s grammatically correct.
If this were a test,
you’d get full marks.
Of course I would.
But,
if they don’t let you take the test,
that means nothing.
What do you plan to do?
There must still be a way.
To have all our plans fail just because
of unexpected obstacles...
[screen- New video uploaded]
First we need to get out of here.
It seems like
we’re already prepared for that.
Get out, to... where?
No idea.
You come up with something.
What do you mean?
You're supposed to be in charge.
The minister is dead,
and the Committee is about to fire me.
We also have no place to go.
It seems like
there’s still hope.
A new video from Satou was uploaded.
Did you see?
Just now, we killed the Minister of
Health, Labour, and Welfare.
Although it probably hasn’t made the news.
We have one target remaining.
President Hashiguchi of Musashi Heavy Industries.
At the Board of Directors meeting
in three days, at 7 p.m.,
I’m going to kill him.
He’s giving a date and
time for the attack?
Satou-san might like to fight,
but what he really likes is playing games.
This is a declaration of war.
If the president doesn't show his face,
we'll take that as evidence that he was
complicit in the inhumane experiments
that were performed on Ajin.
Then,
no matter how he tries to hide,
we'll find him and kill him.
Is this a joke?
All this will do is increase security!
Okuyama,
didn't he tell you anything?
Coming up with the strategy isn’t my job.
So he doesn’t tell me about that.
Tanaka-san!
You-!
Is there some kind of problem?
N- no.
Satou-san.
Why...
What's the point of lying to them like this?
It's not a lie.
This is part of our plan.
This way,
we’ll bet able to use our secret weapon.
We are reporting live from the scene.
Right now,
a joint press conference is being held
by the government and Musashi Heavy Industries
in response to Satou's recent threats.
No matter what happens,
I refuse to give in to terrorists.
Therefore,
whatever threats they make,
I won’t run or hide.
You mean you plan to-
-dangerous-
That’s quite a-
-will you do about-
What are your plans for security?
Will you be okay?
Of course, we also desire the utmost security
and we have already requested cooperation
from the government.
That is all.
You mean-
Wait a minute, that’s-
Next, a briefing from the Chief Cabinet Secretary.
I am Chief Cabinet Secretary Mitsui.
In response to the increasing threat of ajin terrorists,
the Cabinet has met and decided as a result to enact a new law.
Under these new measures,
all involved government ministries have cooperated,
and a new defensive force has been formed.
They will be called...
The Anti-Ajin Special Force.
The Anti-A-
(translator’s note: ‘tai’ means ‘anti-‘)
Tire?
What’s that?
An elite squad specializing in fighting Ajin.
It’s made up of members selected from
the SAT and the Self-Defense Force
1st Airborne Brigade.
You’re awfully well-informed about such a newly formed organization.
Ah. So that’s how it is.
Huh?
What?
What do you mean?
There’s no way
they can put together such a force
in less than two days.
Which means...
it had already been formed,
it just couldn’t act officially.
Isn’t that right?
Yes.
Up until now,
it had been illegal for such a force to exist.
But,
because of this law,
their existence becomes legal.
That’s quite a big deal.
After all,
this country is the best in the world
at putting its public image first.
And?
Are they strong?
The Anti-As.
The equipment used by the Anti-Ajin Forces
was all produced by Musashi Heavy Industries.
It’s a new, inhumane weapon.
It will be used by
what is now Japan’s strongest force.
Soon...
they might not need us.
That’s true.
I hope it turns out that way.
As long as someone stops Satou,
that’s the most important thing.
Do you really think that?
Of course not.
Do you think I could just sit back and
do nothing after all we’ve done?
Why do you think
I joined forces with you?
Yes.
That’s exactly right.
This is our last chance.
No matter what,
we have to stop Satou!
To be continued...
Preview