It's almost summer,
but I feel the temperature just dropped...
If Satori is a monster, then the two of them...
Are a devil...
...and a behemoth!
One Second, Three Strikes
Unyou: Flash of Light
Nono!
Too fast to see!
No, more importantly...
She broke through Amou's Takemikazuchi?!
Auto-Counter
She took damage?!
A tie?!
If it had been a real sword,
a sharpened blade, I don't know how things
would have turned out.
But what is this?
It's light and so horribly weak.
A safe, cheap, fake metal sword,
made from a zinc alloy.
A child's toy.
Swordsmen have it so difficult.
They can't fight without a weapon.
I can't get my wits about me today...
It must be his fault...
Nomura!
Amou!
Episode 11
The Magic Bullet I'll Always Remember
Bang!
Wow!
I couldn't tell from far away,
but now that you're up close,
you're pretty damn cute, like a girl!
Damn.
Makes me wanna kiss you.
I get that a lot.
Go ahead and try.
Nobody's succeeded.
Huh.
Oh, by the way.
Up there. Yeah, your hat.
I'll just help myself, then!
Hey! Get off of me!
You little...
Scared ya, right?
That's my secret technique.
Still a work in progress, but works for
a damn good self-introduction.
So, I've got a proposal for you.
Call it a tie, if you will.
You keep on with this and next time I'll lick you instead.
I can't have that.
Right?
Haven't even used mouthwash this morning.
Alright! A truce it is.
That's what I'm talking about!
Amou.
Glad to have you as a friend.
Let me welcome you to my school.
Let's get along!
I feel like I'm gonna have a lotta fun with you.
U-umm!
Thanks for saving me this morning...
Nomura.
Don't forget, my name's pronounced with
the accent on the first syllable.
Huh? So, Nomura?
Uhh, it's not much in the way of thanks,
but you can come to me if you have any questions!
I've got nothin' but questions.
Where do I go, what can I do...
You want a school tour? Okay!
Let's check it out together!
Yeah, thanks.
What's up?
Nomura, a moment of your time.
I will give you a tour of the grounds.
I'd like to hear more about you along the way.
Uhh, then, I'll just...
Sorry.
Already made plans for that.
We'll have to hang out later.
A word of warning.
You should only associate with those who are worthy.
I will tell you who is.
Auto-Counter
Nomura!
Not even Nomura can handle her auto-counter...?!
I thought I was done for!
Ever since that first awful time, I've kept a book on me!
Like hell you "didn't know me".
I am very different from the "Amou" you speak of.
You were the Amou who knew me all along.
Why?
Why didn't you think that I would
cut you down by coming back here?
Tsukuyo?!
What are you...?!
I jumped in without thinking 'bout it.
You're alive and well, aren'tcha?
You protected me, despite us not being friends?
Could it be that you want to be my friend?
What?!
Just so you know,
I have the right to choose my friends!
And to be honest, I don't think
someone like you would be good!
But, if you insist...
Hey now, don't get me wrong here.
I don't wanna be your friend, either.
You were in the way, so I moved you.
Wha-?!
And friends?
Friends aren't people you ask things of,
or get particular with.
You get to be friends without even realizing it,
without even thinking of what you each want.
Even if you hate each other in the beginning...
at some point, you find you don't.
And then there are some people
you wanted to be friends with,
but it just didn't go that way.
There was a split second when we were friends.
I got disappointed by a miscalculation.
Why?
You don't know?
It's because...
I hate you!
Until I get my freedom,
I'm gonna wreck the peace and quiet here!
I don't get why you do things this way...
...and I can't stand it!
I see.
Then...
you should die.
Can I really beat her?
I don't know what's going on,
but regular strikes won't work on Amou.
If I had to put together a plan,
I'd use my magic bullet, but...
that only worked once back then.
If I mess up, she'll hit me with her auto-counter,
and I don't have anything to block it...
Then, not only will I be unable to get back at her
for Hanasaka and the others,
but everyone else here will be dead meat!
He's shaking.
Nomura's tough spine is afraid of defeat.
Nomura...
No, I can't do it.
I can't find the words I should say to him.
You're overthinking things.
Keep focused on one thing.
Just how he encouraged me back then...
On Kirukiru's chest...
...there's a star-shaped scar!
Well, be careful of his "magic bullets".
That's it!
Amou's steel body is practically impervious
to regular attacks, but...
Yes, your theory must be correct, Rin-san!
Water
The human body is mostly made of water!
Protein
Water
In the right conditions,
water can be as hard as concrete,
Water
Protein
but the muscles that form that hardness have reflexes!
Water
Protein
Triggering those reflexes would drain them of strength!
I see...
That Western approach is so like you, Kikakujo!
If the reason she purposefully
defended against our attack
was because she didn't want that to happen...
Nomura! Don't lose faith!
Give it your all, that is, your magic bullet will work!
We're living proof, it worked on us!
Please take her out!
For us, too!
They used to hate him so, but now...
Is this what he meant by becoming friends?
Leave it to me,
I'll take care of her.
Nomura's...
That's a sword stance!
He may be basing it on Jigen School's dragonfly stance.
While maintaining his defense,
he aims for the shortest distance in which
he can hit his opponent.
This is likely a plan specifically prepared
for a fight with the Empress.
I already showed off my left-handed magic bullet.
I can't be stingy with it!
How hated I am.
I'm glad.
What's wrong? Don't keep me waiting.
You can come at me just like a beast would.
If you make me wait too long,
I'll get hungry for a snack.
He's fast!
Roundhouse Block
That won't work on me again.
Curbing Strike
What?!
This is the end.
Dammit!
Jump over here!
I'd totally forgotten.
Forgot you wanted to slice me up.
The two of you behind me, stay where you are.
I'm disappointed that they've misunderstood me.
Huh?
You said something that helped me,
so in return, I said something that helped you.
Still...
You're all talk.
Inside, you are afraid, which has led
to your half-hearted movements.
You cannot shake the image of
that first strike that nearly killed you,
which has damaged your resolve.
You threw away the magazine in your shirt
to show the extent of your resolve,
but that action has had a reverse effect.
As a result, she is driving you into a corner.
And what was that desperate punch
you threw at the very end there?
Had she hit you there,
that would have been the end of you.
Hey, c'mon, I'm more than just a body,
you can't say all that crap!
Are you implying I should let her cut me?
Yes.
Rock n' roll! Thank you so much for that advice!
I'm disappointed you didn't listen to me until the end.
Please listen.
She has already told you something
that will work against her.
What?!
Did you not hear me?
Yeah, but I can't believe my ears.
You really gonna make me do that?
You really do want me to die after all.
I'll do that myself when the time comes.
Nomura...
I forgot to thank you again.
I'm gonna hit her hard enough for all of you.
That includes Tamaba and Hanasaka, too;
I'll do it for everyone!
The moment of birth is the beginning of death.
Through death, the world will be as it is in our minds.
Discarding one's body provides one with opportunity.
I should've known this before.
I thought I had nothing to lose when
I got good at weaponless combat, but...
I've got too many things at this academy!
Why?
Why are you standing on their side?
Why is it like this?
Oh, Nomura, Nomura!
Even now, I want you!
I need you!
The excruciating delight I felt that day
we exchanged blows still haunts my heart!
When I was young, all I laid eyes on was gray.
Nothing was enough for me.
A tasteless, bland world without value...
Then, only the parts I cut out myself took on vivid color.
Anything I could get my hands on. I dyed in my color.
But you were so bright,
you colored everything
I had already taken into my control.
You should have been mine, but instead...
The shining light I saw that day
must surely have dyed me in your color.
Where did I lose sight of it?
If, back then...
No, or even now,
if I could cast off my pride and all...
Could we...
Could even I...
No, things can no longer go back to how they were.
I can never get that back!
If that is so, then I should...
...kill you.
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Nomura's stance is Jigen School's dragonfly stance!
You hold your left hand out in front of you
to close the shortest distance between your enemy!
It's a stance that truly works for Amou!
How will the last battle go down!?
Episode 12
000012312312312312123000000000000000000
The Girls' Machiavellism
000000000000000
Will we get any screen time?!