Good morning, Suzui.
Oh, morning, Jabami.
Oh dear. We are friends, are we not?
Huh?
Please call me "Yumeko".
Huh? Oh, right...
Um... Looks like I'm in
your debt now, Yumeko.
Oh?
From yesterday.
I won't be able to pay you back right away, but I definitely will.
That was but a gift.
Please do not concern yourself over it.
Well, I don't really see myself being able to pay it back.
Wait, no! I can't just
take your money!
flat chest
washboard lololol
ugly
Student with uncooperative tendencies
Bottom Rank, Rank 87
Kitty
flat chest
washboard lololol
scum
ugly
stupid
pussy cat
RETARD
worthless
for shame
idiot
Whatever might this be, Saotome?
Did something happen to you?
Are you being bulli—
Shut up!
This is all because I lost to you!
Come on, put on your collar!
If you break the rules,
you'll go even further into debt!
Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty! Kitty!
Hyakkaou Private Academy.
A class hierarchy exists in
this prestigious school.
Your standing within this hierarchy is determined not by your performance in academics or sports,
but by your gambling skills.
It's not your fault Saotome
is being treated like that.
That's just what people
do around here.
What people do?
Yeah.
A lot of the students are children of
influential politicians and businessmen,
so the school focuses on skills like negotiation, picking up on tells,
and being able to perform under pressure for when they need to take advantage of others in the future.
I see.
People who are good at
gambling will reap the rewards,
while those who aren't end up being the target of bullying.
There's a hierarchy system in place.
The student council monitors all of the gambling going on within the school.
The amount you pay them determines your position in the hierarchy.
Rankings are published irregularly,
and of the school's 3000 students, anyone in the bottom 100
is labelled as a "student with uncooperative tendencies", essentially a euphemism for "housepet".
Housepets are called "Doggy" if they're male,
and "Kitty" if they're female.
Oh, is that what you
were wearing before?
Yeah, but thanks to you, I was able to pay the one million yen fee to have my housepet status revoked.
That is delightful!
I extend my felicitations.
Thank you so m—
The discrimination
wasn't always this bad.
It started two years ago, when the current student council president was elected.
Momobami Kirari.
Our school is a combined middle and high school, but she only enrolled here for high school.
Then she became student council president straight away.
She gambled with the former president with the president's seat on the line.
Wow! She became the
president by gambling?
The current student council comprises only the strongest gamblers.
To be the leader of that
group is quite something.
She completely reformed the system.
That was when the student council started accepting payments whilst branding Doggies and Kitties.
People started to notice the discrimination gradually getting worse since.
What happened to
Saotome was a bit extreme,
but she did lose spectacularly despite getting everyone to work for her.
Students with Uncooperative Tendencies
Rank 81
Rank 82
Rank 83
Rank 84
Rank 85
Rank 86
Mozu Karen
Niwa Sakura
Hamada Takashi
Kuroyanagi Isai
Akita Moematsu
Saitou Shougo
It was just bad luck that it happened on
the same day the rankings were published.
Rank 87
Rank 88
Rank 89
Rank 90
Rank 91
Rank 92
Saotome Mary
Kawahara Akagi
Aoi Youhei
Hinata Yume
Katou Yui
Hirano Megumi
Oh sorry, I wasn't trying to scare you.
Good grief.
The academy sounds less and less normal the more I hear.
I'm so glad I transferred here!
Does fear not register in this girl's brain?!
Full house! I win!
Yes!
Oh, there are people gambling during lunch time as well.
Yeah.
Hey, she's pretty famous.
She's in the student council despite being a first year.
So she must have earned her position through gambling?
No, I heard she spent a
fortune to pay her way in.
After all, her father is the CEO of
Japan's most distinguished toy maker.
She has a ridiculous amount of money, and she's also good at gambling.
I also heard she's never
lost a card game before.
She's never lost?
That is amazing!
I'd very much love to play her onc—
Wait, wait, wait.
I really think you shouldn't—
Hi, Jabami.
Episode 2
Boring Woman
I'm Sumeragi Itsuki from
the 1st year Flower Class.
It's an honour to make your acquaintance.
Wh-Where did she come from?
People have been talking about you.
I heard you made a mess of
Saotome on your first day here.
I'm actually pretty good
at gambling myself,
and I thought it would be
fun to find out who's better.
Of course!
Yumeko, wait!
That's what I wanted to hear.
Dammit, I was too slow.
Why is this happening to me?
Why?
How did it come to this?
Why? Why did this happen?
Kitty, I spilt my coffee.
Come clean it up.
Hey, guys!
Sumeragi from the student council is about to gamble!
Really? Against who?
You won't believe it.
Jabami Yumeko!
Really?
Where are they playing?
I heard they're in the cafeteria!
So for our game,
would you be willing to
play Double Concentration?
As the name suggests,
we play with two decks.
With regular Concentration,
if the numbers match then it's a pair,
but in this version,
you also have to match the suit.
So even though there's
twice as many cards,
there are only single matching pairs out of all 104 cards.
I see! That sounds very enjoyable!
I'd be pleased to join you!
Okay!
Of course, we also need a wager.
Let's play with 20 of these student
council-issue one million yen chips.
Can you bet 20 million yen?
Oh...
Unfortunately, I do not have
that much money left at hand.
I would not be able to
arrange 20 million yen.
Oh.
Despite your appearance,
you're actually pretty tight-fisted.
Or do you have a debt or something?
Huh? Uh, s-sorry...
Well, don't worry about that.
I can lend you 20 million yen.
Interest-free.
Huh? B-But there's nothing in it for you.
Honestly I wouldn't really
miss 20 million yen.
Getting people interested in my family's
company's cards is much more worthwhile.
It's just a bit of advertising.
In that case, please allow me to ask this favour of you.
Okay! Looks like we've
got ourselves a game!
So just as I explained earlier,
we'll use two brand new decks.
It's our company's
mainline product, "Raclette",
the second best-selling cards in Japan!
They're designed to fit
perfectly in your hands!
Please try them out!
They're really good!
She's actually advertising them.
Let's begin. Double Concentration!
Jabami, you can go first.
Oh, thank you.
I suppose there's no point thinking too hard about the first move.
They are both four, but with these rules, this does not complete a pair, does it?
That's right.
Okay, it's my turn now.
Come on, four of hearts or diamonds!
Isn't this game a bit too hard?
Since only one card makes a pair,
there's only a 1/103 chance of finding the matching card.
That means you need to remember all of the cards that were already flipped up,
but there's no way you
could memorise 103 cards!
King of diamonds...
Ace of spades...
That's a two of hearts...
And that one is a club...
It's impossible! My head hurts!
Oh, the four of diamonds
was flipped before, wasn't it?
Where was it?
I believe it was here.
I did it!
If you make a pair then
you can have another turn.
Go ahead.
Seven of diamonds.
King of clubs.
That isn't a pair.
Oh, I remember seeing the king of clubs.
It's here!
Sumeragi's putting up a fight!
Wow, they're evenly matched.
2F - Jabami Yumeko
Yumeko has 18 cards.
1F - Sumeragi Itsuki
Sumeragi has 22 cards.
Both are going strong.
Hey, is it just my imagination or have neither of them missed a pair so far?
What do you mean?
Like, when they find a card that matches one that's already been flipped,
they always get the pair.
Huh?
Five of hearts.
This one has been flipped before!
That's exactly what I mean!
Do they remember the positions of every single card that was flipped?
Their memory skills are more or less equal.
It's just a matter of being
lucky enough to find a pair.
There are 28 cards left.
Yumeko has 36.
Sumeragi has 40.
They're still going even.
It's going to be rough
from here on out, though.
As the number of cards in play decreases,
it becomes that much easier to find a match.
The tides could turn completely.
You're pretty good, Jabami.
This is the first time I've
had such a good match.
Oh, thank you.
I'm honoured.
I need to step up my game—
Oh, I found a pair.
And this one was here.
Another pair!
Then this one...
All right!
I've seen this one too!
Would you look at that, ten in a row.
It appears Lady Luck
is smiling down on me.
She has 14 more cards than Yumeko.
If she gets any more...
Oops, that's not a match.
I guess it's your turn.
If you don't get a pair,
I'll win for sure!
Please, try your best!
That's the wrong card!
I made the pair!
With 54 cards, I have
the majority, so it's my win.
How is Yumeko going to pay back a 20 million yen debt?!
She said she didn't have the money!
I did it! I won again!
Sumeragi!
Huh?
Would you...
Would you play just one
more time with me?
I would never be able
to pay 20 million yen!
Just like you, I remembered the
positions of all of the flipped cards!
I cannot bear to take a loss like this!
Please, play me but once more!
You see, I actually
have a nail collection.
Here. Aren't they great?
This is only a fraction of
my collection, of course.
There's also a bit of
a secret behind these.
They're all real fingernails.
Oh my...
It would be so much easier
if I could just buy them,
but no one seems to
want to sell them to me,
so I've gotten most of
them through gambling.
You know what I'm getting at, right?
For me to bet 20 million yen,
I would really love your
fingernails in exchange!
You're kidding!
Betting fingernails?!
So how about it, Jabami?
Y-Yumeko, you don't
have to accept this craz—
Yes, that would be fine.
Wh-What are you thinking?
I must accept, else I won't
be able to repay my debt!
Or were you perhaps
about to offer to pay for me?
Er, no, that would be a bit much.
Great!
We'll use two new decks, all right?
You're kidding...
She's actually going to do it?
This is kind of exciting!
This is crazy!
Even at this school, there are rarely bets involving bodily harm.
I guess that's why everyone is so excited.
This isn't just a game!
Well then, shall we start?
The wager is 20 million yen for me, and all of the nails on your fingers and toes for you.
Understood.
Then, you can go first
this time as well.
Thank you.
Looks like I'm adding to
my collection today!
I'm going to win for sure, after all.
Especially since I know
what half of the cards are!
At a glance, these cards appear to be the same as the rest of them,
but they're actually a different set that I specially manufactured.
There's only one difference between these cards and the regular ones.
Above a certain temperature,
a mark will appear.
My bag is full of pocket heaters,
so after all of the cards are laid out,
the marks will remain for
another two or three minutes.
It's only a subtle sign and they fade away quickly,
so there's no way I'd be found out!
And all I need to do is remember those cards.
There's no way I'd lose.
I chose Double Concentration just to make it harder to win by chance.
If I know what all the cards are, I can win at any game, be it poker or old maid.
Memorising all of the markings was
hard work, but it was definitely worth it.
I'll be taking those nails, Jabami!
She found a pair!
What a great stroke of
luck from the get-go.
Sumeragi, incidentally,
is it true that your family
runs a toy-making business?
What?
What would be the market value for such a large enterprise?
10 billion yen? Or perhaps
even 100 billion yen?
In comparison, you're only betting 20 million yen on this game.
Don't you think there is
a bit of a discrepancy?
What do you mean?
Allow me to offer you some advice.
If you're going to be putting your family's business on the line,
it would be in your best interests to
prepare yourself for the consequences.
What's she talking about?
My family's business?
Did she realise that I'm cheating?!
Is she trying to threaten me?
It's true that it would be a huge scandal if people found out that my company made cards for cheating.
How much does she know?
Did she see the markings
before they faded away?
No, it could be a bluff.
It's no good.
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to just collect all of the pairs once it's my turn
and then pack up all of the cards
and swap them with a normal deck.
That's all I can do.
When it becomes my turn...
When it becomes...
Y-Yumeko?
This pair makes 54 in total.
It appears I have won.
What?
N-No way...
How?
I would have lost had you been just slightly more cautious.
After all...
The markings are all
the same as last time.
If you had prepared a deck that had a different set of markings on the back,
it would have been all over for me.
What?
I-Is she saying she memorised them all?
So she knew about the markings from the very first game?
She pretended not to notice
and just played the game!
And the show of despair
after losing was just an act.
But the marks all faded
away after a few minutes!
So she memorised all of
the markings in that time,
and moreover, worked out which markings corresponded to each card as they were revealed during the game?
Is that even humanly possible?
Well, that marks the end of this game!
Let us play once more!
What should we play next?
Maybe Blackjack?
Or perhaps Baccarat?
No, I don't—
Oh? I don't recall you
being in a position to refuse?
Oh, I know!
Why don't we both bet our nails?
The winner gets to tear off all of
the loser's fingernails and toenails!
N-No way...
Being the one who proposed it,
you don't mind, of course?
I've heard that it's quite painful
after having your nails removed.
The area will bleed every time it bears even the slightest weight,
and that would be happening
on both of your hands and feet.
I'm sure the daily life you take for
granted will cause you great hardship.
Simply imagining such an earnest game with those kinds of stakes
truly lights my fire!
Come, Sumeragi!
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity!
You disgraced yourself by proposing the match full of bravado,
and ended up losing
miserably despite cheating!
There is no better time to let loose!
Let us play!
All you need to do is nod.
Come!
Come now!
Quickly!
I-I can't...
I can't do it.
P-Please don't do this to me.
Excuse me?
P-Please...
Y-Yumeko? She's clearly
regretting what she did.
How boring.
That concludes my report.
What an amazing girl, beating
Sumeragi right after transferring in!
I hope she's not getting cocky over beating that weakling.
She did pay her way into
the student council, after all.
Who was the one that
recommended her again?
Be quiet.
Moving on, how should we
deal with this Jabami Yumeko?
It's fine.
Perhaps we should
play a little bit as well?
H-Hey, are you serious?
You're going to keep playing?
But I was hardly able to have any fun at all!
"Once the bell rings, gambling stations pop up all across campus."
Is that not what you said before?
Where can I find them?
You should accompany me, Suzui!
Welcome to the Traditional Culture Research Society.
You came at the perfect time.
An official match is going on right now.
Would you like to come in and watch?
What is an official match?
The verdict is: death.
Saotome, your total is -49,600,000 yen.
The game is over.
40 million yen?
I will inform you of the repayment process at a later date, Saotome.
Someone please escort her out.
I'm done with her.
They're down!
Oh dear! Please don't
make such a frightening face.
That's enough.
Shut up and show us.
If one chip is one million yen,
that's 30 million yen!
Your methods are despicable.
I'll have the honour of taking your life!
Episode 3
Snake-eyed Woman