Satou-san!
Everyone’s fed up with playing your games!
In short, the plan is to release the recovered
nerve gas underground,
and render Satou powerless?
In order to avoid alerting Satou,
we can’t evacuate the citizens.
About four hours remain.
Before then, we have to capture Satou at any cost!
Go, ghost!
Fight to the death to stop him!
I know that!
He’s not a revolutionary or a tactician.
He’s just a player.
And that’s exactly why we have room
to take advantage of him.
What do you plan to do?
Bury him alive.
You put some thought into it.
But... just when you thought you'd won...
The rug gets pulled out from under you!
W- What’s going on?
Are they digging in?
We overdid it!
No, the floor-
Tosaki-san!
I’ll kill... every last one of you-
We couldn’t defeat him?
Game... start!
This is...
Nagai! Nagai!!
What happened? Search team!
An explosion!
At point F2, there’s been an explosion
and a large-scale collapse.
It seems like below the underground tunnel,
there's an even older passage.
I can’t reach Okuyama and the others.
Nagai!
Naga-
Nakano, shut up!
Nagai!
Where’s Satou-san?
He’s not here.
Neither are Izumi-san and the others!
That way’s blocked off!
What’s going on?
No idea!
But it looks like we were done in.
That we were the ones buried?
...Which means, the problem is Satou-san.
If he’s not defeated,
he’ll come after us while we’re not paying attention.
Is it Satou?
Probably!
Then, the ones he’s fighting are...
Tosa-
Izumi-san!
Let’s go!
Kuro-chan. Please!
I'm the type who keeps my things in
good working order.
The one from earlier!
Tosaki-san!
It’s no good.
What’s the damage to the unit?
No damage!
It’s a trap.
Will there be a problem with releasing the gas?
The conditions have changed slightly, but
they’re all within our expectations.
Very good.
Then, when the installation has been
completed, withdraw immediately.
Roger.
We’ll also withdraw in five minutes.
I can’t believe...
I’m burdening you like this.
Please don’t worry about it.
This is my job-
You’re first up.
Nagai-kun. Can you hear me?
Nagai-kun!
I'm going to make you regret getting
in my way so much...
you'll wish you were dead!
Go!!
Hurry!
One down.
What?
You’re supposed to be human!
I’m a ghost.
At Musashi Heavy Industries...
I should have died.
To the right!
Three people confirmed!
They’re ajin!
Take them all in!
You kids go on ahead!
Hang in there, Tosaki-san.
The bank.
In that safe-deposit box is the proof
that you’re an ajin.
Tosaki-san.
What are you talking about?
Be quiet and listen.
The key for the safe-deposit box
is in her hospital room.
If you understand, then go.
With this leg,
there's no way for me to escape.
But, surely Nagai-kun and-
I release you from your contract.
Hurry up and disappear.
Get out of my sight!
So I’m...
...free?
Yeah.
Live as you like.
Then...
I’m free to protect you, Tosaki-san.
What an idiotic-
I won’t take orders anymore.
I was released from my contract.
Tosaki-san.
Thank you... for the new life.
Stop!
You can’t beat him!
So you’re number two.
I still can't manage...
Stop it!
I’ll let you meet your new self!
It’s Nagai.
Your game is over, Satou-san!
Aren't you a bit late?
Excuse me.
I went the wrong direction.
Commander. This way.
How’s the installation?
Complete.
Excellent.
Wait for orders.
Shit!
This is payback for earlier!
You-!
Damn-
Kuro-chan!
I’m always taking care of you.
This time I’ll make sure you thank me.
Hey, Tanaka-kun!
I’ll leave this to you.
Got it!
There’s one thing I want to ask you, Nagai-kun.
Why do you get in my way?
Isn’t it obvious?
With you around,
I’ll never be able to live a quiet life!
Ha!
You’re the same as me.
I’d rather you not lump me together
with a lunatic like yourself.
Let’s do this, ghost!
You are the same.
You want to live quietly.
I want to play to the very bottom of my heart.
But this world won’t allow that!
One more time...
ghost!
That’s why we’re doing what we
should to each other!
Of course you would, Nagai-kun.
As foolish as always.
Kuro-chan!
That’s the result of experience in
battle, I suppose.
Damn it.
You get what you deserve.
Let Izumi-san...  go....
I’ll make you pay for that time at the hospital!
Let Izumi-san... go...
What is this?
You too?
Don’t get in my way!
Less than five minutes remain.
Release the key lock.
Commander! It’s Satou!
We’ve got Satou!
Commander.
The orders were to...
use the most surefire method to capture Satou!
Do you remember my promise
at the research lab, Nagai-kun?
I said I would cut off your head.
And now I’ll fulfill that promise.
I’ll pick up your severed head,
and make you watch as a new head is created.
You will watch until you die.
You will no longer be yourself.
Then...
I promise I’ll show the new you
the best show you’ve ever seen.
First...
Eriko-chan!
Next, Kaito-kun and your parents.
And then... Tosaki-kun.
Shimomura-san, Nakano-kun....
All of them,
I’ll kill them in front of your eyes.
Just like at Musashi Heavy Industries.
That is...
your punishment for getting in my way.
No...
I...
I make promises too, Satou-san.
Wherever you go...
I will find you and kill you!
Ah.
Farewell...
Nagai-kun!
Nagai!! Nagai-kun!
Yeah, nothing good comes from saving people.
We’ll act as your pawns!
I won’t do it.
Hurry up and die.
Shut up.
It’s your fault my quiet life is all messed up.
Satou-san.
I’m sorry to have caused you trouble.
He was sick...
that’s just what happens.
I need to take a piss.
I should be the one saying that
As your immortal soldiers!
The flood phenomenon.
Send out the IBM-
You can wait as long as you want,
but the U.S. forces aren’t coming!
I only bothered with him because
he seemed pitiful and alone.
Hey, Nagai-kun.
Go, go, go!
Don’t move!
Hey, wait.
I’m-
Don't take him!
Wait.
Those ajin are under the protection
of the Japanese government.
And that woman is a human, working under me.
Satou and Tanaka.
We've already reached an agreement.
Withdraw.
So the American side gave up the plan of
using the gas just before it was time.
I’m grateful, Senpai.
In exchange for stopping Satou,
all of you will be pardoned, and free to go.
Thanks to your persistence with
your idiotic arrangements.
Tosaki-san.
Don’t forget to erase my
responsibility for my crimes.
This afternoon, within the government, the cabinet made
a new decision regarding measures concerning ajin.
After much deliberation, the National Diet has approved
a new bill making civil rights a reality for ajin.
With the enactment of this measure-
Nagai-san.
It's time for a blood sample.
Ah.
Did you see your brother again?
It's nice that you get along.
Yes.
Ah, wait.
It’s not like we get along that well.
That’s why he wanted to go out with me!
Eh, that’s something!
Isn’t that pretty awful?
Isn’t it?
That’s really funny.
Yes.
It’s been a while, hasn’t it.
What happened?
Eh?
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
I can’t believe they really exist.
Yeah.
I didn’t believe it until now.
They’re humans that don’t die.
I wonder how the hell they get that way.
Right?
Yeah, it’s almost like a game.
It’d be so much fun to have a body like that.
Ah, I had a dream for the first
time in a long time.
I can’t believe you can sleep
in a situation like this.
Even though we don’t know
what will happen to us now.
What are you saying?
Obviously we’ll start our second playthrough.
How are we going to do that?
I love it when a plan comes together,
Tanaka-kun.
When did it happen?
Right after the U.S. forces took him into custody.
They kept that fact quiet.
I'll tell you the details when you get here.
We’ll pick you up shortly.