Ability: Mind reading.
Mind reading?
Reading people's minds?
Looks like the itinerary is set.
A new ability user?
How exciting!
The location is...
Looks like a desserted side alley again.
Let's make a move.
Yes!
Yessss!
Aye aye, Captain.
Strong People
It should be somewhere around here...
Perhaps, she's the one?
Is she expecting us?
That's way too fast.
No way she's waiting for us.
In any case, let's just ask her.
Hello!
I have something to ask you.
Do you happen to have the ability to read people's minds?
Hey, she nodded.
Woah, serious?!
This is progressing way too fast.
That's amazing!
By the way, can you tell me what's on my mind?
Takajou is such an idiot!
I'm an idiot!?
Why that out of nowhere?
You guys could hear it?
Yup. Your voice saying Takajou-san was an idiot.
I heard it too.
What?
I'll have another go.
Takajou is a muscle freak!
Hey! What's with the consecutive insults!?
You guys heard it?
I've something I wish to confirm.
C'mon over, guys.
Sheesh... What's her problem.
If I were a muscle freak, wouldn't that make you a ZHIEND freak?
ZHIEND this, ZHIEND that...
ZHIEND freak?
You heard it?
I see now.
Seems like her mind reading is not limited to herself
but also to the people around.
That said, what did you mean by ZHIEND freak!!
Are you looking down on ZHIEND!?
Weren't you the one who started it?
You piece of shit!
I merely had that thought.
Don't eavesdrop the inner voices of others.
So you really thought that of me.
It's my fault that everybody is fighting!
There's no place I belong!
Let's leave this for the moment.
My inner voice wasn't heard just now, right?
Yeah.
Radius is approximately 2.5m.
Those who enter that boundary would have their inner voices transmitted to others around.
Just like the actual person saying it.
Has she always been like this?
I believe she personally thinks that.
Otherwise, she wouldn't be so rejecting.
I bet even her friends and family's thoughts are transmitted without restrain.
Leading to multiple conflicts.
The end result: she had chosen solitude.
I see.
That's really sad.
But I've never heard of an ability that is continually activated.
There must be some kind of trigger causing the activation.
Let's go find out.
We're gonna ask with her abilities activated?
That's asking for trouble.
I'll do my best together with Yusarin!
YESH!
If someone like you pairs up with Kurobane,
there won't be an end to how those disgusting fantasies would be transmitted.
You should drop the idea, too. Kurobane-san.
Okay..
That makes you the only one left.
There's also you.
Why me?
Didn't you hear her?
Everybody starts fighting.
If she's alone, that won't be possible.
Are you looking for a fight?
The reverse.
If she sees that we aren't fighting,
at least her level of guardedness would be lower than now.
I see.
You mean for us to hear one another's thoughts and not fight!?
You can't do it?
The heck's she thinking?
I'm confident we can pull it off.
She deserves credit saying those words so confidently.
Aren't we the worst combination?
Isn't this a good opportunity for us to deepen our friendship?
A chance for us to be frank with one another.
Although we may be borrowing her ability.
If you're fine screwing up, I have no objections.
Let's both do our best.
For her sake.
Good work, you two!
We'll make a move first.
All the best!
Say, Yusa-san. Let's go back first.
I don't need to read your mind to know what you're up to.
Sure!
Now then.
We also ditched class.
Wanna have fun with us?
Hey you, come over.
He'll be joining us too.
Just so you know, we won't fight.
She doesn't trust us because of what happened?
I can hear you.
The stuff I think are alright with being heard.
Aren't you reliable?
Is there somewhere you'd like to go?
It must be boring here.
I'd really thank God if we could just split ways now.
Look, you kicked him!
You got it wrong.
I was playing the straight man.
Note: This is a reference to Boke (Funnyman) and Tsukkomi (Straight man) in Manzai.
Since he was trying to be funny, it was my duty as a partner.
Partner?
That's right.
He is my partner.
We are really closed and combine well together.
Really?
You think she believes that crap?
Look! Again!
Like I said, the straight act.
Really?
Like the straight man always says, of course it's true.
The funny man will try being funny, don't take it seriously.
Is that really true?
I promise.
Right?
I'm feeling hungry.
I want to eat something.
Alright! Let's get something to eat.
There's a family restaurant nearby.
This way!
Well then, ikimashou?
What's your name?
Sekiguchi.
Your first name?
Iori.
I shall call you Iori-chan.
Keeps getting better.
Have you decided?
Carbonara udon!
Subarashii~!
Can't you just say it?
Is Carbonara udon good?
I guess hot coffee will do.
I will-
I'll have Tandoori chicken and chai.
Get him a cream soda.
Right away.
Mind reading is so convenient.
Don't just decide for me!
When was the last time you ate?
Dinner two days ago.
You haven't been home since then?
Your parents must be worried.
Well, heck it.
Let's have some fun today.
Are you serious?
You bet I am.
Where should we have fun next?
Theme park, zoo, aquarium.
The theme park!
I got it.
The theme park, it is.
The theme park, huh...
You got a problem?
Nope.
Ticket Office
It's indeed a weekday.
There's hardly anyone!
What should we ride first?
Tornado in the Sky.
Exciting and Fun
Leja Land Information
Sky plus tornado. It can't be anything good!
So Otosaka Yuu is afraid of fast and high things.
Please, how can that be~
God, help me!
What an honest lad.
But you still have to accompany us.
Because we came here to have fun.
That was so good!
Boy, it was thrilling!
I almost died up there.
Says the guy here.
Wanna have another go?
I'm in!
You must be kidding?
A really honest lad.
NOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
Next is Tower Off.
More like Tower of Death. I have a bad feeling about this.
Well, you won't really die.
You have small guts, Onii-chan.
Man, I feel like punching her.
PUNCH!
Straight act.
Straighten my ass!
Straighten your funny act.
I ain't funny.
You guys are hilarious.
Let's have a break.
Wanna have ice-cream?
Yes, please!
For a handsome guy like me, I've really disgraced myself.
This guy genuinely thinks he's handsome.
He may be handsome, but he's a scaredy-cat deep down.
What a pity.
Pity?
How dare you say I'm a pitiful man-
PUNCH!
The straight act.
Like I said, what are you straightening!?
Your funny act.
And I already said, I'm not acting funny!
At the very least, nobody in school should know about this.
Now that I know, what should I do?
Try me!
Is that the attitude of someone in need of mercy?
Don't do it.
More.
Could you not say it.
Where is your please?
Coud you please not say it.
On account of your sincerity, what more can I do?
Alright then, I won't tell anyone.
Damn.
You two really don't fight even around me.
Except for the straightening act.
Didn't I say so.
We are really closed and combine well.
Meaning, the two of you are a couple?
Impossible.
Perfect synchrony.
You two must be lovers.
No.
I think the two of you are really compatible.
Does she mean it?
Boy, she got me there-
PUNCH!
Watch it!
Straight act.
I already said, what the hell are you straightening?
Your funny act.
And I also already said, I'm not acting funny.
Hey, let's ride something else.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Are you alright?
What's with this midget?
My date is turning into a disaster.
Hey, she's only a kid.
I didn't expect you to be someone who'd say something like that.
Hey, what's the matter?
I was expecting you to be more mature.
She already apologized.
In fact, you're the kid here.
Why are you saying such things about me?
I've been putting up with you for a long time.
That's it between us, then.
Thank you up till now.
Goodbye.
How did it turn into this?
It's all your fault!
I knew it. It's all my fault.
Iori-chan!
Aren't we back to square one?
What should we do?
We chase after her. That's what!
Anyway, what do you mean back to square one?
You retarded?
Don't come any nearer!
Why?
Bad things happen when you're near me.
You saw it for yourselves just now.
It won't happen to me and him.
So please allow us near you.
No way!
You'll be jinxed!
I won't stop even if you say no.
Then, I will disappear for good!
I won't allow you to be alone.
Why?
It's futile.
Onee-chan. How did you do that?
I also have a special ability.
One that doesn't allow poor girls to be alone.
Really?
Yes.
So let me stay by your side.
I got it.
I'll try to believe you once more.
Yes, please have faith in me.
Hey you, come over here.
Now, things are back to normal.
I guess.
Thanks!
Thank you for staying by my side.
It must have been lonely.
If I'm with Onee-chan and Onii-chan,
I feel as though we can be together forever.
I came to have this ability because of my strong desire.
I had a really closed childhood friend.
One day, she started hanging out with another clique.
She stopped playing with me.
I must have done something wrong.
But she wouldn't tell me no matter what.
Therefore, I wished to be able to hear her thoughts.
Here it comes, the trigger.
I know this much.
What?
Even now, you continue to wish for it.
If you can find out that reason,
there's a high possibility you'll be able to control your ability.
Really?
You must be really troubled by it.
But before I got to hear her thoughts,
everybody started fighting.
There was no place I belonged, so I left home.
I see. I can at least grasp the situation.
Even so, knowing you, you have no solution.
That's right.
Let's think of a way to solve this!
You serious?!
Really?
I never lie.
I will do my best for you.
You can stay over at my place today.
Thank you for the meal!
Yeah, it was delicious.
Today's dinner was red as always.
When is the pizza sauce gonna end?
Shit!
Oh right.
Thoughts will only be heard if I'm in her vicinity.
No, it's nothing.
Alright then, I'll clear the table.
Tomori Nao
Calling
Oh yeah, I gave her my number.
Speaking.
It's me, Tomori.
Please come out immediately.
Come prepared.
Where to?
The home of Iori-chan's bestie.
Yes?
You must be Honoka-chan?
Are you friends of Iori-chan?
Did you manage to find her?
Don't worry.
We managed to find her safe and sound.
Rest assured.
What a relief.
I have a question.
I can tell you're really worried about Iori-chan.
Then why did you avoid her?
Well, that's...
I want nothing to do with her ever again!
Please leave!
We will leave.
But could you tell us the reason before we go?
Since you are her friends, even more so, I can't say!
Is that so?
I understand.
Actually, we're not friends of Iori-chan.
What I'm about to say is highly classified.
I ask that you divulge to no one.
There was quite a commotion in school prior to her disappearance.
Everybody was quarreling and having fights.
Yes, I've heard about that.
Her special ability was the cause.
It's an ability that transmits the inner thoughts of people in her vicinity to one another.
She possesses such an ability.
Is this some kind of joke?
We are members of an organization that gathers and supervises special ability users.
That guy and I have special abilities.
Just so you know, I'm an invisible girl.
No way!
Watch closely.
Over here.
He'll hand over your cellphone to me.
I guess that's my cue?
I got it.
Look, this belongs to you, right?
It's as you have seen.
Do you believe us?
Do powers like that really exist?
Iori-chan is also a special ability user like us.
To get her to join us as a comrade, we're secretly protecting her.
Why are you telling me all these?
We will take her with us.
She'll work in the underworld from now on.
You'll never see her again.
That's why we've come to ask you, as her best friend,
if you have any last words to say to her.
Afterall, I'm still a sentimental person.
Working in the underworld?
How is that possible?
Why not?
Because... eventually, she won't be able to move her body!
What do you mean by that?
Please elaborate.
I coincidentally overheard my mom and the rest talking about it.
Iori-chan has an incurable disease.
No way!
She's so lively and energetic.
That's why I decided to never be with Iori-chan again.
I severed all ties with her.
Compared to watching an important friend gradually losing her ability to move,
I'd rather have her hate me.
So I've to get her to hate me!
To have my beloved Iori-chan hate me most!
Hey, that doesn't change...
You call yourself her best friend?
You insolent brat!
While you were playing with the others, her illness continues to creep upon her!
Do you understand that!?
Even so, here you are, raving about how important she is to you!
Don't you dare run away by yourself!
There are still things you can do!
You will regret it for life!
Say something!
What do you think you're doing?
Stay away from Honoka.
Are you hurt, Honoka?
It was my first time seeing Tomori this agitated.
Within which, was the rage at knowing the unfortunately truth
about our newly made friend whom we spent the day having fun with.
Good morning.
Yes, morning.
How did the mind reader case go?
I cannot say.
Knew it.
Tomori forbade me to.
There's nothing I can do.
Quite right.
But it piques my curiousity.
Are you a lolicon?
Careful what you say!
I'm Yusarin FTW!
Good for you.
Settle down!
Homeroom is starting.
Since then, with regard to the mind reader incident.
Tomori and I visit her on a regular basis after school.
After hearing Tomori's outburst that faithful night,
that Honoka girl made up her resolve to stay by Iori's side.
Iori has also confronted her illness and vowed to fight till the end.
It made me realize that girls are amazing.
What's on your mind?
Nothing really.
I was just thinking that women are really amazing.
Is that so?
Maybe you'll eventually meet one.
Meet what?
One that will make you give your everything.
Me?
I bet you're going to say it's impossible.
But that's life.
You're too young to be saying that.
Yeah, quite right.
For now, we should give our best for them.
As friends.
Tomori-san!
Google~
How do you feel?
These are for you.
You're indeed amazing!
Thanks!
Look! Honoka-chan. Aren't they pretty?