Wh-what the hell?!
I was a fool to trust you even for a second!
So, what is this all about?
I remembered one thing very clearly!
I did not have a boner!
So if you get the original data,
you can provide the others with an explanation.
Take this!
Buri-buri!
Spit it out! Explain yourself!
What is that picture about?!
When did it happen?! How do you know her?!
I can't believe we've beat him this much,
and he hasn't made a peep!
Buri-buri! Buri-buri!
Say something!
Princess Satori's sword is missing!
You fool!
Oh, you did come!
But wowie, I'm surprised that
Warabi's working with you!
You really can't tell what people will do, huh!
Episode 7
The Dubious Sword, Tamaba Satori
Did she have us figured out all along?
No, wait, this is crazy!
Who brings a sword into the bath?!
I finally remember everything.
I won't fall for that again, you damn paparazzi!
Paparazzi?
I felt like someone was watching me all day yesterday.
That's how they found their chance,
dragged Masuko into things,
and slipped me a roofie, right?
Dragged him in? That wouldn't be right.
What? Then how did you...
Little Masuko was helping all along!
It was all connected!
He sure is sleeping well!
Okay!
Let's get started!
Oh, is he waking up?
You're...
What is that taste?
Sardines?
What're...
Okay, go back to sleep a little longer.
Look! You want this, the picture data, right?
She saw right through us, huh.
Ordures!
I will not forgive him for this!
Y-you're absolutely right!
This is why men need to be
corrected to coexist with us!
Y-you're absolutely right!
Everyone has to be careful around them!
I'm sure he was after your body as well, Onee-sama!
My body...
He was never after my body...
Onee-sama?!
But I must have misjudged him!
To think he was the kind of man to do such a thing!
Onee-sama, this is non-alcoholic wine!
Please calm down!
That man, ugh!
I need a refill!
That idiot!
I won't forgive him for this!
Y-you're absolutely right!
You know, I actually...
That idiot!
But I thought he was...
Y-you're absolutely right!
I won't forgive him for this!
Even so, I...
That idiot!
I won't forgive him for this!
Y-you're absolutely right!
More!
This is just barley tea...
You idiot! Are you listening to me?!
Y-yes, of course!
Besides, what do you even think of him?!
Um, uh...
I-I've always thought he was a horrible guy,
ever since that one time!
That one time?
That time when he stole your lips from you!
Nono...
That's enough. I'm going to bed.
So I get that you're a fan of mine,
but why'd you do this?
No reason.
You were just kinda annoying.
Do not get carried away with this!
Why did I cry?
What was that about?
Besides, I would never actually think he's...
I was a fool to trust you even for a second!
What do I even want to do?!
Nono...
You take care of Princess Satori.
Yep, that's the perk.
Sure!
Okay, we'll fight over here!
C'mon now, can you at least put on some clothes?
What? I can do what I want.
Not gonna be easy on me like this.
That's part of my strategy.
Calm down, Magnum ****!
Would you take this seriously?!
She's got me there.
If I keep my hips back, I can't use my magic bullet.
You fool!
Listen up! Do not take her lightly!
Ten... sou... metsu...
That drug was quick to affect me...
And Kyo-bo won't be able to join me...
However!
Don't think this will be easy!
I won't let you through.
If that man leaves us, Kyo-bo will miss him too much!
The girls' baths sure are nice.
I could do without having to see naked guys.
Oh, that's right!
Huh?
There was one question I reallllly wanted
to ask you before we fight.
Hmm? What is it?
Nomura-chan...
No way! I was ready for her!
Which do you like more,
getting stabbed or getting slashed?
Wow, you did a good job blocking!
I guess you don't like getting stabbed.
I can't react as quick!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Wow, you're good at dodging.
You're scary good at looking away when you attack.
Huh? Did I do that?
I can't predict her attacks by watching
where she's looking.
And if I look down,
I'll be too distracted to actually fight!
Dammit, she's seen through every little thing!
I don't get you at all!
I get that a lot!
But I don't understand everyone, either.
Don't worry, your all-seeing eye
makes you look like a monster to us!
Monster?
I get that a lot, too!
The first people to say that were
probably my parents...
Back then, my dad was really mad,
and my mom was crying,
but I couldn't understand why,
or how I was supposed to react.
I still don't understand!
She's getting sloppy!
A trap!
She's back to her usual self!
Alright. I think I get you a little now.
Your left hand keeps supporting your sword.
That means you're using
Shindo Munen school techniques!
How 'bout that?
One out of ten?
You're tough!
Asayama Ichiden Style
Harmony
She suddenly changed styles!
Someone like you couldn't figure me out!
You bitch...
My body's so heavy!
Ten... sou... metsu...
She went for my clothing!
There were drugs on the mouthpiece, too?!
This is bad.
At this rate...
Think it's stupid? So what!
You fool!
I will be winning this duel,
and there is no changing that!
Right Armor-Breaking Stance
Tsutsumi Hosan Style: Hatten-giri
She used technique from another school again!
It's like a mish-mosh of a bunch of schools!
Someone like you couldn't figure me out!
One out of ten?
That's it! I got it!
You're using Keishi School!
Keishi School takes one technique from
ten separate schools and fights with wooden swords.
Which means that each one of
your techniques adds up to ten!
Ding, ding, ding!
That's correct!
Okay then, I'll give you a special treat,
Satori's secret little game!
What's that?
Tatsumi Style: Horizontal Eye Attack
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Don't say that.
Nothing good ever comes from that phrase!
Nomura-chan, do you know how to play word chain?
No, I'm at my limit!
Leg swipe!
Fake her out with that...
...then hit her like this!
Taisha Style: Toppei
Too short!
Word chain?
Yes, for example...
Her grip!
She's holding the handle and her wrist!
Tatsumi Style: Makiotoshi
Shinto Munen Style:
Uchiotoshi
Like I did just now,
there are techniques in different schools
that have the same words in them!
Sword School Word Chain
There are lots, so I'll be sure to show you them!
It's no use, I can't find an opening!
You monster!
Her movements got sloppy again.
Is it because...
I'll have to test it!
Giving up?
Nope.
Figured I'd finally finish you off!
Can you?
Yeah, it's all or nothing!
Are you serious?
Umm, hey, what's this supposed to mean?
Who knows?
What's wrong? Come at me.
You monster in human's clothing.
I'll kill you, you know?
You're getting too caught up in
your desire to dismember me.
Your human nature comes out in your sword.
Your feelings might not show themselves easily,
but they're definitely in there.
There are only two ways girls react when I drop trou.
Their eyes get fixed on it,
or they focus hard on looking anywhere else,
rendering your all-seeing eye useless.
I win the bet!
Even without my strength...
I can use judo!
Taisha Style
Stolen Sword
So light and easy to use!
I'm suddenly feeling a lot better now!
The drug was spread over this end, yes?
Well, well, not to worry,
I'm only going to beat you silly!
What is it, my lady?
Where are you going?
The baths.
Yes, but Tamaba is using them at this time...
I know.
I hear everything that goes on in this dorm.
Now, as the loser,
you must show me your real face!
It's my win.
Are you sure?
See? If I let go, your precious data goes bye-bye!
So you had me from the beginning, huh?
Maybe!
Do you know what to do now?
What? Are you stupid?!
If I'm getting expelled anyway,
might as well do that and leave with no regrets.
Why are you so mad?
Is it because you were framed and tortured?
Or is it because your future plans
have totally gone to waste?
It's because you made Onigawara cry!
That was a great reply!
Humans sure are interesting!
You're a human, too, ain't you?
You're no monster.
You got mad there at the end, after all.
Huh.
I really hate you, Nomura-chan.
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Tamaba Satori uses a style called
Keishi School Kidachi Style!
It takes one technique from ten different schools
of swordsmanship to make a perfect match-up!
Just like we're a perfect match-up!
What do you mean?
You're the cute one, Omugi, and I'm the sexy one!
Episode 8
000000000000000000000
His and Crossdressing Her Circumstances
We're neither, we're just crossdressers!