What is your job?
My job is...
to protect you!
An emergency meeting?
It seems that there are investigators coming
from the U.S. Department of Defense.
We’ve been dispatched here
to investigate the circumstances surrounding the
death of professor Ogura and his bodyguard
From here on,
we’ll be fighting every second of the way.
Who do you think you’re talking to?
We don’t have time to get carried
away by a false sense of justice.
Do you know our plan?
Tosaki-san is investigating the Minister’s movements,
Right?
What should we do?
How are we supposed to get the schedule at this rate?
Don’t worry.
If we can’t get it directly from the Minister,
we’ll go after someone close to him.
Kuro-chan, please!
After Professor Ogura left the monitor room,
you went outside the barrier wall, did you not?
No way!
Are you seriously considering me as a suspect?
It’s just as I thought.
Something that should be here is missing.
I’m tired of dealing with Japan’s procedures.
This means... tonight??
Out of my way!
This woman is an Ajin!
That’s too bad.
You’d have been happier dead.
Tainaka Yoko-san, is it?
Your real father’s name is Tainaka Satoshi.
He died in an accident,
when you were 15 years old,
and your mother is Tainaka Sawako.
If i am not mistaken?
Get out.
I don’t want to hear...
those names again.
You’re registered as a suspected Ajin.
Sorry, but I can’t do that.
He...
...that woman...
Put that phone down!
Sawako!
Think about it,
We can make money from Yoko’s body!
We won’t have to work any longer!
Yes, hello?
...Mom?
Eh? [stepfather]
Yeah, that’s right.
Yes, yes, that’s correct.
You tried to sell me out...
Mom, why do you always have to listen to him?
It’s his...
It’s that woman’s fault...
I am sure...
She’s probably still with that guy.
Doing whatever she wants.
No.
Your stepfather and mother are already dead.
She tried to sell her daughter.
Serves her right.
No, you’re wrong.
There was a lot going on,
but that’s not it.
What do you know?
The police still had a recording of
the call they received.
It must have been made immediately
after you left home.
So you’re reporting an Ajin?
Yes, that’s correct.
Ajin, she’s an Ajin!
My kid’s an Ajin!
Hey... you!
That kid is...
That kid is... my child!!
-the hell...!
I’m... sorry...
Yoko!
You play that for me...
...and ...so what?
You’ve misunderstood.
It’s too late.
It’s too late!
Tosaki-san!
I’m a government official.
You won’t be forgiven for this-
Where is Ogura Ikuya?
I don’t know what you’re-
That day,
you shot the bodyguard,
and kidnapped Professor Ogura.
And you still have him confined somewhere.
Why would I do such a-
The Professor is a one of our country’s
top-class researchers.
I’ll need him to return back to the
U.S. at any cost.
If you have complaints,
tell them to Satou.
He-
Cut the crap,
Tosaki-san!
Where is the Professor?
I already...
said...
I don’t know.
It’s not that you don’t know,
you just forgot, right?
Help him remember.
Understood.
Wh- What do you think you’re doing?
Tell him, Myers.
You're most familiar with it.
It’s a dosage which paralyzes the diaphragm
and you feel as if you’re slowly choking.
S-stop i-
It’s a drug to render Ajin powerless.
If you adjust the dose,
you can cause endless suffering without death.
The building and location have changed,
but there are no major obstacles.
We can more or less use our previous Plan B,
with some revisions.
The spots to revise are as we discussed,
so please check those parts again.
Nakano.
.  I’ll fill you in later.
I know that already!
What about Izumi-san,
isn’t she running late?
I wonder if she’s eating out
with Tosaki-san.
Ah, Izumi-san, welcome back!
But, what happened to your clothes?
What about the Minister’s schedule?
Tosaki-san’s been kidnapped.
Huh?
They found out about Ogura’s confinement,
and the investigators from the Department of Defense-
I’m going to rescue Tosaki-san.
Nagai-kun!  Make a plan!
Hirasawa-san.
Hurry and prepare a place to hide.
It doesn’t matter even
if it’s temporary.
Can you do that?
Huh? Yes.
That is a possibility.
Nakano, collect the equipment.
Eh? The equipment?
Why?
Hurry up!
O- okay.
Nagai-kun. What are you-?
Sawamura-san and Kuroki-san, pack the
necessary things in the car.
Suzumura-san, get Professor Ogura.
There’s no time to mess around.
Go quickly-
Nagai-kun!
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Preparing to move the hideout!
Huh? That’s not it.
First we have to rescue Tosaki-san!
That’s right, Nagai!
If we don’t help Tosaki-san, it’s all over!
How?
Where did they take him?
Eh? Well I don’t know-
Our first priority is to stop Satou.
But Tosaki-san is-!
First of all, Tosaki-san is, without
a doubt, under interrogation.
If he talks,
they could come after us.
If that happens,
that’s the end for us.
But, come on!
Hirasawa-san!
Nagai.
Hirasawa-san.
You told me before.
Here, you need the determination to cut off ethics and emotion.
Now that time has come.
First we have to make sure we’re safe,
and after that, we can make a plan.
If you think about it rationally,
right now that’s our best course of action.
No, but- Tosaki-san is...
If the roles were reversed,
Tosaki-san would have come
to the same conclusion.
How can you say that?
Get moving.
This contract is between me and you alone.
The organization doesn’t know.
Your job is to...
protect me from unknown threats
presented by other Ajin.
Tainaka Yoko is dead.
From today, you start a new life.
First, you should choose a name.
A name?
A new life calls for a new name.
It’s best to choose something slightly
related, so it’s easier to get used to.
Then,
my real father’s last name,
“Shimomura”, and-
my mother’s maiden name,
“Izumi”.
Understood.
Let’s get going.
You’ll catch cold,
Shimomura Izumi-kun.
Mom-
I’ll do it all over again.
This time...
I won’t run till the end.
Nagai.
I’ve confirmed the location.
We can move at any time.
Thank y-
Eh?
If I were Satou,
you would be locked up for good.
In a dark,
cramped place.
But...
you’re not Satou-san.
If you can’t even beat me,
how do you plan to stop Satou?
We only have one chance to stop Satou.
To shoot Satou when he’s
attacking the minister.
But...
...the only one who knows when
that will happen is Tosaki-san!
Think rationally!
However you think about it, picking a
fight with America isn’t a rational.
We’ve finished packing the car, Nagai.
Please take everything out of the car.
Ha?
Change of plan.
We’re going to rescue Tosaki-san.
Nagai!
Nagai-kun.
With the U.S. as our opponent,
it’s the perfect opportunity to test our training.
Thank you.
There’s no time for thanks.
First we have to figure out where
they took Tosaki-san.
Minami-Azabu.
Eh?
There’s a safe house we used before.
I bet four-eyes is there.
Why are you telling us?
Aren’t you on their side?
You expect me to put that ahead of access
to prime samples for research?
If it’s Minami-Azabu, we should be able
to get there within an hour.
Let’s depart ASAP.
Okay.
Suzumura,
you relocate Ogura-san.
The location is already arranged.
Understood.
Nakano,
you pack up the equipment.
Ha!
Yes sir!
Nagai.
[screen- Schedule Alarm ;  meeting with
Cabinet Vice-Minister  ; midnight]
"If it’s a plan you want, I can do that on the go
Let’s go! Izumi-san.
Have you remembered?
I don’t know.
I...
don’t know anything.
Myers.
His heart rate is dropping quite a lot.
and-
I didn’t ask for your opinion.
Do it.
Understood.
It’s tough being a dog,
isn’t it.
How many more times
can you use your IBM?
Probably zero.
I know you’re worried about Tosaki-san,
but please try to stay calm.
I know that.
Shit, intruders!
What happened to the electricity?
What the-?
The safety, idiot!
This is Bravo One.
The living room is clear.
We did it.
Idiot.
What’s that?
Fire!
Clear the rooms.
Room C, clear
Room D, clear.
All that’s left are rooms E and F.
Alpha, roger.
Get a move on!
Shit.
I guess...
neither of us can let our guard down today.
Tosaki-san!
Ghost!
Go!
Damn!
How did they know where we were?
That doesn’t matter, our first priority is to get to headquar-
Shut up!
It’s because you let that woman go.
You’ll pay for that later.
Tsk!
You can’t even pick a decent street?
It’s about time for you to
deserve and injection too!
Where are they?
They’re still near the safe house.
They just entered the second street on the right,
but don’t rush yourself.
You guys take care of clean-up.
Roger.
Go on ahead, and...
No time for that!
I won’t let you go!
That’s why I said...!
Izumi-san!
Are you okay?
Detour to the right.
Izumi-san!
What about Tosaki-san?
We’re following him now!
Can we catch them? Nagai!
Hey, Nagai!
Shut up for a minute!
This is bad, Hirasawa-san.
They’re heading towards...
the American Embassy.
That’s the worst possible outcome.
Eh?
What is?
Why?
The embassy is extraterritorial.
Neither the police nor the army
can lay a hand on them there.
If they make it there,
that’s the end.
But why?
Just shut up!
To be continued...
Preview