We've covered a third of our list,
but so far the Japanese government hasn’t made any response whatsoever.
In any case,
the government refuses to give in...
It was too much to expect of them.
An emergency meeting?
It seems that there are investigators coming
from the U.S. Department of Defense.
We’ve been dispatched here
to investigate the circumstances surrounding the
death of professor Ogura and his bodyguard.
Tosaki-san....
Damn.
Of all things at a time like this.
Well then...
now that we have our secret weapon,
shall we dive right into the second half?
Basic training is over.
Starting today we’re moving onto the real deal.
Rubber bullets?
I said this would be the real deal,
but we can’t use real weapons.
If we died, that’d be the end.
Even so, those hurt like a bitch
if they hit you.
I’m used to pain.
There will be three people per team.
Nagai will be head of the alpha team.
I’ll be the second,
and Manabe will bring up our rear.
Nakano will...
We repeat.
Earlier,
Mr. Tadokoro Yoichi and Mr. Kousaku Endou of
Matsunami Sciences were killed.
You’re still worried about the other targets?
The suspect, under police surveillance...
Something wrong with that?
Ajin Satou was seen amidst the panic,
and after successive failures by the police, calls have
been made to review security measures.
Damn.
We don’t have time to get carried
away by a false sense of justice.
Do you know our plan?
Tosaki-san is investigating the
Minister’s movements,
and laying an ambush for Satou.
Right?
Seems like you’re prepared.
That said,
where’s Izumi-san?
I want to be on the same team as
her for training.
She’s with Tosaki-san at the
Research Facility.
It seems like they were called
there by the Americans.
Then,
you were with Professor Ogura...
I only saw him in the monitor room.
After Nagai Kei escaped,
I returned home soon after.
After that,
unrelated to the ongoing Ajin attacks,
Professor Ogura was killed by an unknown player outside the barrier wall on the way to his car.
I don’t know the details,
but I heard the opposing side was using an IBM.
We’ve received reports of that.
The corpse also matches our medical records.
It’s just...
There are few points that concern me.
Such as?
Such as,
why is the surveillance camera video missing
on the site of the murder?
That is mysterious,
but that might be the result of Satou’s explosion.
It’s also unnatural that the bodies of Professor Ogura
and his bodyguard were found at different locations.
Perhaps they got separated while escaping?
We’ve also heard that on the day of the event,
one of the research staff who was supposed
to be at the facility went missing.
That’s the first time I’ve heard of that.
Are you sure that’s been confirmed
against the staff list?
You see.
So, after Professor Ogura left
the monitor room,
you went outside the barrier wall,
am I correct?
No way!
Are you seriously considering
me as a suspect?
Let’s say, that the crime wasn’t
an act of Satou,
but rather someone on the inside.
The only one who could have murdered the professor given the conditions is you.
Tosaki San!
It could only be you.
Why do you think I would need to
do such a thing?
All I know is that,
despite the ongoing Ajin attacks,
you were outside the facility for close to an hour.
Why would you do such a dangerous thing?
The truth is,
After Nagai’s escape, my boss called me
and really got on my case about it.
I was unable to control myself,
and had to leave.
I’m sure
you too know the difficulty of being
a public official.
The proof of the circumstances is
extremely limited.
I guess,
he really isn’t connected with the
professor’s murder.
I didn’t ask for your opinion.
I’m sorry.
That was a waste of time.
Gather the evidence and we’ll return home.
Put in the request.
News Flash
After noon today,
there was an explosion at the headquarters
of Touyou Railroad Industries.
In the explosion, Director Yutani,
as well as three other victims,
were confirmed dead.
Ritori Makoto                         Toyou Railroad              James Campbell
The four victims
were all targets on Satou’s list,
In response to the government's stance,
people are calling for the capture of Satou
Among continuing panic caused by Satou,
demonstrations are being held near government offices.
Hey, did you see the news about Ajin?
Yeah. It’s scary, isn’t it.
That girl in the hospital,
she’s Nagai Kei’s sister, isn’t she?
Yeah, that’s the Ajin who was on
the news before, right?
The one who pushed someone from the roof
of a building, and ran away from the facility.
I’m worried...
It’s become a difficult world for
Ajin to live in.
Just like for heavy smokers.
If we stop Satou,
the day-to-day will return to normal.
Unlike cigarettes,
Ajin don’t harm others.
One can hope.
A secret weapon, huh.
I always wanted to try making something like this.
We refuse to give in to terrorism.
In order to destroy the Ajin organization that
is threatening our populace,
I plan to put new laws in place.
This has gotten pretty intense.
At this rate, things for Ajin are just getting worse.
Are you unhappy?
No way.
Are we really handling things the right way?
What other choice do we have?
That is...
It’s true
that outward criticism of Ajin has gotten stronger.
But I wouldn’t say it’s all bad.
We’ve gathered Ajin from all over Japan.
Guys from the ‘protest’ at the Ministry,
and groups we got through your connections.
The police can’t prevent information from travelling by word of mouth.
Everyone has come together for the future of all Ajin.
It’s too late to turn back.
Tanaka-san.
Right now I’m getting everyone
to help with assembling the bomb, but...
Ah. Thank you.
Is there anything else that needs to be done?
Hmm, clean-up, I guess.
Understood.
I’m acting as the manager,
so if anything comes up, please let me know.
Ha, this is starting to feel like an army.
That is...
What was his name again?
That’s just like you, Tanaka-san.
Huh? What’s that supposed to mean?
More importantly, where’s our main man Satou-san?
Ah, I haven’t seen him for a while.
Isn’t that obvious?
Yes.
Understood.
Mr. Kashiwagi of the Meihan Medical Center has been killed.
It seems the incident happened while
he was traveling by bullet train.
It’s our turn, Tosaki-san.
The Minister who’s the next target is..
currently holed up in the safe room
at the government building.
However, given the way the attacks on the
related companies were carried out,
I believe we ought to take additional measures.
The Minister is also being pressed to deal
with related government authorities,
and the Cabinet is trying to
get their story straight.
I’ve already inferred where they’ll
hold their private meeting.
It’s a place that important people
from many countries often use.
I thought you said the attack would come at
the ministry, or at home, or both.
I said that was a prediction at best.
And what’s more,
Nagai.
You of all people should be able to deal
with some changes here and there.
Well...
the point of the strategy was to make
use of the building layout.
Hirasawa, get a copy of the architectural blueprints,
and investigate where people will
be posted around the building.
Roger.
I will get my hands on a detailed schedule.
Everyone else, notch up your training.
Alright!
Let’s go,
Shimomura-kun.
Tosaki-san.
From here on,
we’ll be fighting every second of the way.
We can’t afford any mistakes.
Who do you think you’re talking to?
Excuse me.
No matter what you try,
you can’t capture Satou, huh.
Our sponsors have been annhihilated.
How dare you show your face here after
such continued mismanagement.
My apologies.
However,
Minister, I came to prevent the same
kind of accident from happening to-
This place is like any other shelter.
They may be Ajin,
but they won’t be able to get in.
That said,
if you were to take a trip outside, that’s a different story.
If I could get your schedule just to be sure-
Don’t make me laugh.
Like I would discuss the situation with to
a subordinate who’s about to be fired.
And besides,
you shouldn’t have the time to be
worrying about others.
According to Sokabe,
aren’t you under investigation by the Americans?
They’ve already finished their interrogation.
They have no reason to doubt me.
Through the police crime lab, we got
hold of Professor Ogura’s effects,
and have transferred control of them here.
The list of items is as I gave to you earlier.
Please allow us some time to confirm.
I see no problems.
Your detection skills are as low as ever.
As I thought.
Something that should be here is missing.
What should we do?
How are we supposed to get the schedule at this rate?
Don’t worry.
If we can’t get it directly from the Minister,
we’ll go after someone close to him.
I sent the schedule over earlier.
Yes.
I’m still at the Ajin Research Facility.
As soon as I assemble the documents-
The Minister’s secretary is examining
the documents for a new bill.
I’m also supposed to submit a report.
That’s our chance to steal the schedule.
This is...?
It will take about 10 seconds between recognizing
the device and automatically
executing the program.
Don’t let her catch you during
those ten seconds.
You mean...
Your job is to control the IBM.
Sorry, can’t you wait?
I’m sorry,
Tosaki-san asked me to hurry and confirm...
It’s the Ajins’ fault I have to do
all this idiotic work.
You ought to send it digitally.
Kuro-chan,
please!
Looks okay to me.
I’ll pass it on to the minister.
...that... that is...
What?
That’s, uh...
That’s...
a very nice watch.
It looks good on you.
Oh, you noticed?
The truth is, it’s an antique-one of a kind!
This suit is simplistic, but it’s high-brand.
And the heels are haute-couture,
so they were pretty expensive.
That’s very impressive.
If you’d like,
I’ll tell you where I got them from?
Thank you very much.
Maybe another time.
Wait a minute.
You...
are you and Tosaki-san an item?
Ha?
You’re always together,
and you do whatever he commands,
isn’t that right?
I’m just doing my job.
Just say it!
No sense in hiding things.
Our basic strategy is to shoot from behind
the IBM, which we’ll use as a shield.
The primary objective is to secure Satou-san.
To render him powerless the moment
we find him.
Idiot!
Don’t underestimate my training!
I meant to do this!
Why do I have to be.... Satou...
That’s a new record.
Now
all we have to do is wait for word
from Tosaki-san.
This means... tonight??
Damn.
What the hell is Shimomura doing?
What is it?
The investigation should be over.
Actually, we found something in
the end that concerned us.
Something seems to be missing from
among Professor Ogura’s effects.
His effects?
We suspect
it was picked up while they were in storage.
They were supposed to be left in Professor
Ogura’s car, these...cigarettes.
Oh?
Look familiar?
I don’t know what you’re talking about,
but if you want a cross-examination, you’ll have
to go through the appropriate procedures.
It’s exactly... as you say.
Well then, I’m in a hurry, so...
I’m tired of dealing with Japan’s procedures.
I’ll make you talk.
Bring around the car.
Should we really be doing this?
To a Japanese official.
Didn’t I say I don't need your opinion?
If it comes down to it,
we’ll say he was in an accident.
Everyone around here is so insensitive to death.
That woman...
she’s always been with him.
We have no choice.
Contain her too.
Out of my way!
No way, this woman...!
This woman is an Ajin!
Because I just brought one out...
Your internal organs are destroyed.
It should take a few minutes.
If the Ajin’s consciousness is lost...
the IBM is just a doll.
It’s not even good as a curio.
So that man was keeping an Ajin too...
That’s good, more subjects for
our experiments.
That’s too bad.
You’d have been happier dead.
Leave it.
We can’t afford any witnesses.
Tying him up is our first priority.
Get the car moving!
Don’t worry.
Afterwards I’ll use you to make up for what
we lost out on with that woman.
Gotta take responsibility for your mistakes.
What is your job?
My job is...
to protect you!
To be Continued...
Preview