A Day in Tendou Karen's Magnificent Life
Otobuki High School Class 2-A student
Tendou Karen begins her day very early.
It's another pleasant morning!
As soon as she wakes up,
she leaves the house for a jog.
The morning is a time of
self-enrichment for Tendou Karen.
Morning!
Good morning!
You sure look pretty, as always.
Thank you.
And so I, Tendou Karen, begin my
magnificent day with a pleasant awakening.
Good puppy!
After my morning exercise, I move
on to my early morning studies.
The tranquility of the morning
provides a perfect environment
for a busy student to study.
I have breakfast, and quickly
prepare to leave for school.
What people don't know is that I don't
fuss too much about my appearance.
I believe that what really matters
is what comes from inside.
There!
The first thing I do upon arriving at
school is socialize with my friends.
Morning, Karen!
Morning!
My principle is to commit myself fully
to what can only be done then and there.
During breaks, in addition to
socializing with my school friends...
Sensei!
I'll help carry that.
I volunteer to help the teachers.
Thanks as always, Tendou-kun.
I do so not to score points,
but because I value the special
experience that I can gain from it.
And then comes what, for me,
is the most depressing part
of the day.
Please go out with me.
I believe it is my duty to confront
the person's request head-on,
and decline with honesty.
I'm sorry.
Still, turning down someone's kindness
leaves a stinging sensation in my heart.
Game Club
After school, I head to the game club,
where I am secretly a member.
There, members gather to
hone their skills in gaming.
I am absolutely in love with the tense
atmosphere that comes about only when
everyone takes their work seriously.
When I get home, I review
and preview my studies,
get some games in to relax
as well as to gather information,
and sleep early to prepare for the next day.
Goodnight.
And thus ends another impeccable,
magnificent day in the life of Tendou Karen.
A Day in Tendou Karen's Magnificent Life
Otobuki High School Class 2-A student
Tendou Karen begins her day very early.
Wh-Wh-Why am I having a
dream about Amano-kun?
And such a disgraceful one?!
I haven't done my homework yet!
The tranquility of the morning
provides a perfect environment
for a busy student to study.
What the hell am I doing?!
I have breakfast...
Thank you.
...and quickly prepare to leave for school.
What people don't know is that I don't
fuss too much about my appearance.
I believe that what really matters
is what comes from inside.
What the heck?
My bangs won't behave!
Look at the time!
Karen, you're going to
school dressed like that?
The first thing I do upon arriving at
school is socialize with my friends.
K-Karen?
M-Morning.
My principle is to...
Oh, darn it!
Karen, are you okay?
I'm fine.
...commit myself fully to what
can only be done then and there.
During breaks, in addition to
socializing with my school friends,
Huh? Where's Karen?
I don't know.
Tendou-kun...
I volunteer to help the teachers.
I'm happy that you're offering to help,
but that needs to go to the chemistry class.
I know!
I've got this!
No, you're going in the opposite direction.
Don't worry, I'll get it there!
Via Class F.
Huh?
Why Class F?
I do so not to score points,
but because I value the special
experience that I can gain from it.
Is he not here?
He should be playing games
by himself right now.
Huh? Tendou-san?
What are you doing out here?
And then comes what, for me,
is the most depressing part of the day.
Why not?!
Am I not good enough for you?
No, that's not it.
I don't know you too well, and besides...
Is there someone you're interested in?
N-No...
Someone I'm interested in?
A-Are you kidding? Of course not.
I have no intention of dating anyone!
Dating...
N-No, I'm not picturing dating
someone or anything!
Uh...
What about my confession?
Oh, that's not happening.
Not a chance.
You're cruel!
Wait, I didn't... I'm sorry!
Jeez, why does this always happen?
Game Club
After school, I head to the game club,
where I am secretly a member.
There, members gather to
hone their skills in gaming.
Tendou.
I am absolutely in love with the
tense atmosphere that comes about...
Hey, Tendou.
Sorry!
You seem pretty out of it lately.
What's wrong?
I don't know...
Just stuff on my mind, I guess.
My mind tends to wander to
completely unrelated thoughts.
Like what?
Let's see...
Like the time I first talked to
Amano-kun at the game shop.
Or the time I got Amano-kun to
come to the game club with me.
The time he turned me down.
That he was by himself again today in Class F.
And about how he thinks
highly of the game club.
I keep thinking about it over and over.
Tendou, you've been losing your edge lately.
You're clearly not as good as you used to be.
N-No way!
You're the president, after all.
Try to keep up gaming.
That's right.
I'm Tendou Karen, president of the game club.
I have to stop being distracted
and focus on gaming.
I hope Amano-kun comes
to the game club tomorrow.
Wait, why do I care about Amano-kun?
I-It's not like we need
his skills in the game club.
And it's not like I want him to come!
B-But I guess I wouldn't mind
welcoming him, if he asks to join.
Then I'll show him the ropes
and teach him how to play...
And thus ends another day, magnificent
in a slightly different way from before.
Misumi
Karen
1 chain!
2 chain!
There! Got you back!
Not bad.
By the way, have you
heard anything since then?
About what?
About Hoshinomori-san's
relationship with Amano-kun.
Misumi
Karen
1 chain!
2 chain!
Huh?
What's wrong, Tendou—
Tendou-san?!
7 chain!
Misumi
Karen
Yay!
You got
me...
I really am getting worse at gaming.
I look so dead.
It's obvious why I'm doing so poorly.
Yes, I know why it is.
Ever since that day,
when he said that having fun is the
most important part of gaming,
there's been hesitation in
my stoic style of gaming.
Seriously, he'd better take
responsibility for this.
Wait, that's not what I mean
by "responsibility"!
It's nothing like that!
Tendou-san?
A-Amano-kun?
Yes.
U-Uh...
Um...
Hi.
Ahem.
Well, what a coincidence, Amano-kun.
Are you out shopping?
Nailed it!
There's the Tendou Karen I know!
Um...
I've been gaming all day,
and my mom yelled at me.
So here I am, outside.
Th-That's a bitter reason to leave the house.
In that case, why don't you
come for a walk with me?
Sure, I'd love to...
Wait, what?!
No way! I can't possibly
be with you on a weekend!
I'm not worthy! I mean, um...
Not worthy?
I mean, it wouldn't be good.
He's going to reject me again.
But not this time.
Why not?
Do you hate me, Amano-kun?
O-Of course not.
I mean, I wouldn't want to bother you
with more rumors going around.
Oh, I remember...
Tendou-san?
Wh-What's wrong?
Nothing... I-It's nothing.
It's nothing.
Really?
Anyway, with that, I'll be leaving now.
W-Wait!
Hang on!
Wh-What is it?
I... I was only proposing that we go on a walk.
Not that we go on a date.
So just stand tall.
Huh? Er, I don't think that's the issue...
Just come with me, Amano-kun.
Wait, where are we going?
Games
We Also Buy!
I see.
What, do you have a problem?
I told you that this is a walk
and not a date, did I not?
Well, even more than that, why are
we at a game shop right off the bat?
I've been interested in this!
This, too!
Man, which should I get?
You're already having more fun than I am.
Is something wrong?
W-Wow, you really do like
Golden Memories, huh?
No, um, that's not it!
It was on sale, so I couldn't help myself...
It's all right, Amano-kun.
You're a boy.
Please don't say that like you're a mother
who just found her son's secret magazines.
I'm not buying the game!
Oh, you're not?
Why do you seem so sad?
So you bought it, after all.
So...
This is a walk, right?
The next stop for two gamers on
a walk is, of course, the arcade.
Yeah...
"Walk."
Actually, I never knew you went to the arcade.
I guess I go on days when
the club doesn't meet.
What about you?
I thought I didn't like it, but I had a
chance to go with someone recently,
and I realized arcade games
are pretty fun, too.
You mean Hoshinomori-san?
When you say you went with someone...
We're there, Tendou-san.
Oh, right!
This will do! Yes!
H-He's talking about Uehara-kun, right?
Not Hoshinomori-san, I'm sure.
Is something wrong?
No...
The idea that you'd go to
the arcade with a girl
made me think you're surprisingly
shameless. I'm disappointed.
When you're the one who invited me here?!
I totally just tricked you into
choosing the bad option.
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
I feel like I might find a way
to get out of this slump if
I can play against him here.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'm just surprised that you'd be
the kind of person who gets
competitive in crane games.
That's true, I'm not really
interested in these kinds of...
Wait, is he still talking about...
It's a heart!
Yay!
Do you want to play the
coin games, Tendou-san?
Huh?
Hey, it's a 3x Medals Day today.
Today's Medals
3x Day
Lucky us, huh?
Sure.
Why don't we start with about 500 yen, then?
Wait...
Tendou-san?
You look like someone in your party
just wasted their MP on useless magic.
Why can't you put your
observational skills to use sooner?!
I was going to play you in
arcade games, but forget it.
All right.
It's a challenge, Amano-kun.
This isn't what I intended,
but I have no choice.
We don't have to play this
if you don't want to.
Amano-kun!
Yes?!
You've made a good choice.
Indeed, coin games are all about luck.
We can have a fair, serious battle.
You're subtly knocking my gaming skills...
This is a battle for my life...
for my reawakening!
I'm going to defeat you and
take back what I've lost!
You're way too gung-ho!
Aren't we just playing the coin games?
Y-Yeah, but...
Girls won't like you if you keep
fretting over little things!
Is it just me, or am I losing
charisma points really unfairly today?
Anyway, it's a challenge!
We'll meet here in 30 minutes.
R-Right.
All right, the game begins!
I'm going to beat Amano-kun in this
challenge and get over my slump!
Running in Eco Mode
Please insert a medal or push
the button to start the game.
The pusher games are the most orthodox.
But the popular seats are taken, of course.
Besides, they aren't good for scoring
big in a short amount of time.
He's at the seat with the lowest total?
Does he have a plan of some sort?
Wow, so that's how it works.
He's a total newbie!
That kind of threw me off,
but I won't let my guard down.
And I'm going to put an end to
my Amano-kun-ish weaksauce-ness!
30 Minutes Later
I was hoping I'd do a little better,
since it's a coin game.
Man, that was so fun, though.
Why do I feel so dissatisfied,
even though I won?
Tendou-san, may I have this coin?
Of course.
Thank you.
Amano-kun?
I want to make good use of your coin,
so I'm going to bet our challenge on this.
Our challenge?
Our coin game challenge, of course.
Huh?
Eh?
Teiou Cup
And now, the gates have opened.
Wh-Why?
Well, because it's a challenge.
But you aren't that type.
What type do you mean?
I thought you weren't interested in winning.
If it's a challenge,
you've got to win, or it's no fun!
The lead has entered the final
corner. It's the final sprint!
Yeah! Go!
Suginami Teiou is in the lead!
Suginami Teiou enters first,
followed by Uji Houjiki in second.
Too bad.
Tendou-san?
Rules for Using the Park
You turned down our invitation
to join the game club because you don't
like the way we play to win, didn't you?
Well, to put it simply, yes.
You looked sad when you
lost just now, though.
In fact, you tried to win,
right down to the last coin.
That doesn't add up, does it?
It doesn't?
Well, I thought you cared
most about having fun.
So you don't care about winning, do you?
No, of course I care.
I want to win.
That doesn't make sense.
To enjoy a game and to play to win...
...are almost the same thing, right?
I mean, if you honestly
didn't care about winning,
would there be any fun
in playing video games?
Cold
Durian Juice
Ew.
Vending
Look, Tendou-san!
I won!
Yay!
Yay! I'm in luck!
Here you go.
I won it.
Thanks.
You have good times and bad times,
and you make a big deal of it either way.
That's why games are entertainment for me.
Then why wouldn't you join the game club?
That's simply because I don't have
the tenacity it takes to win.
I see.
Hey, Amano-kun, I get really worked up
over winning and losing in video games.
The game club does.
Are we silly?
What are you talking about?
That doesn't sound like you.
To enjoy the victories and fret the losses
is the biggest thrill in gaming!
That's why, even though I admire
the game club members for practicing
really hard in order to win,
I'd never think it's silly.
I see.
Of course, I'm gutless, personally,
so I end up fleeing to other games
before I can get good at any one game.
Honestly, you keep disappointing me.
S-Sorry.
I really mean that in a good way.
All right, that's it for today's walk.
See you, Amano-kun.
Right.
That was pretty abrupt.
Well, I'm dying to
go home and game right now!
Tendou, you...
How have you gotten even worse?!
Why?!
You were finally getting good!
Why are you suddenly playing
worse than a newbie?!
Every time it starts getting fun,
I keep remembering Amano-kun's face.
It's all Amano-kun's fault!