I've prepared this. A total of 1,000,000 Yen.
You've helped me out before.
I'm not saying I'm returning the favour,
but I want you to use it.
As long as it’s in your hands,
I'm sure you can earn enough through gambling.
Thank you very much.
Even after such a crushing defeat you're still believing in me and placing your bets on me...
But I have no need for this money.
Huh? W-Why?
To tell the truth, the Student Council hasn't come to collect anything from me as of yet.
That's why I still have some money on hand right now.
What? That can’t be right.
The Student Council being merciless when it comes to debts is common knowledge...
I wonder why, myself.
Ah! I’m not certain if it's meant as a replacement,
but this was handed to me.
Hakuou Academy Student Council
Life Plan Form
Jabami
yumeko
A Life Plan Form?
Yomotsuki-san?
Yomotsuki-san.
Huuh?
Second Year, Flower Class
saotome Mary-san is asking for an interview.
Ugh... The president isn't here right now,
so I guess I’ll take care of it.
Let her in.
Saotome-san, please come in.
Need something?
I'm pretty busy right now, so keep it short.
This morning I received this
right here from the Student Council.
What's the meaning of this ridiculous text?
Huuh? Exactly what's written there.
Stop joking around!
Just what is this creepy text even?!
40 years old Senator Orida rises to
president of the Humanities Department
39 years old First child enters Hyakkou Academy.
35 years old Senator Orida rises to Vice-President of Law.
29 years old Anticipate thrid child (male is hoped for)
28 years old Orida runs for Senior Senate President, wins.
24 years old Anticipate second child (Female is hoped for)
23 years old Anticipate first child (Male is hoped for)
22 years old Graduate from Hakururi Academy, marry Orida.
19 years old Enter Hakururi University
Begin interaction with Orida Zoukou.
Become secretary of Sayama Senior Senator.
18 years old Graduate from Hyakkou Academy
Like I said, it's exactly as it's written there.
Everything in there's been decided.
Yay, clear!
Oh, you're lucky!
a diet member's wife, it says!
Still, ‘Orida’ is a filthy
old pedo so I'd totally pass.
But he has a lot of connections and plenty of funds, so it should work out for you!
It's already been arranged anyway.
Huh? ‘It’s already been arranged’?
Yup, it's all done and decided.
It's true that this school has
strong connections to political circles, but...
Assuming that this is all true, why am I getting married?
There's no way I'd marry just some guy I d–
Mike
Your opinion doesn't matter.
It's been decided.
There are a lot of ways to force people to do what they need to.
Don't bullshit me!
Who'd even abide by something like this?!
Then pay up.
Yiha! If you can't pay us back, it’ll all happen for real.
Just do your best and brush up on your man-pleasing skills, ‘kay?
Marriage... Birth...
what kind of joke is this?
This academy truly
never fails to entertain me.
Your entire life, down to your marriage partner, is decided by this.
This livestock status will truly haunt you until you die, it seems.
Episode 4
Yumeko, this is serious.
When the Student Council says they’ll do something, they will.
True. If I can't return the 300,000,000 Yen
I'll truly become cattle.
Discord, anxiety, anger and despair...
Even that familiar classroom is warped by them.
This sensation...
I can't get enough of it.
Oi, Jabami Yumeko.
You became a Mike, right?
Come with me for a bit.
Kiwatari from the Camellia Class?!
That's quite alright. Shall we go?
We’ve moved quite the distance, haven't we?
So, in what way might I help you?
Take off your clothes. Strip for us.
Shit, what are they talking about?
Ah, could it be...
that you were planning to violate me?
Huh? I never went that far.
just hurry up and strip.
I think I'll have to decline after all.
Showing my bare skin to strangers is rather unpleasant.
And also, you gentlemen are...
a far cry from my preferred type.
Fine, you bitch.
I’ll violate you, like you said.
Yumeko!
Whoa there!
Don't get in the way now.
Just be quiet and watch.
Oi...
what are you guys doing?
The fuck are you?
Hey, this is bad.
It's the Student Council member and head of the beautification committee, Ikishima Midari!
Come on, you can’t just force yourself on others.
As the head of the beautification committee I should stop that, right?
If you’re that pent up, I can take care of it for you.
Still, it won’t be for free.
We'll decide this with gambling, obviously!
There's only one bullet in the chamber.
If I pull the trigger and nothing happens,
you can do whatever you want.
If it does come out, you’ll just get riddled with it.
What do you say? Sounds fun, right?!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I don’t get you!
are you really this scared of being shot?
It's a five-in-six chance; if our positions were reversed I'd accept, no questions asked!
Reversed? That's it! Reverse!
You shoot!
If no bullet comes out be nice and go back.
If it comes out...
I probably wouldn't have it in me to resist anyway,
so you could just do whatever you want!
There are absolutely no negatives for you,
you couldn't ask for better conditions!
Anyone would agree that shooting’s the only option!
Now, shoot! Come on!
Shoot!
What are you even saying?
Are you an idiot?
I'm beat, let's go.
Ah, yeah. Me too.
Yeah, for real.
Why are you leaving? Show some guts!
are you not up for it or somethin'?!
Yumeko, are you alright?
Suzui-san... Yes, I'm quite alright.
Ikishima-san.
Thank you very much for your assistance.
I won't forget my debt to you.
I'll be sure to repay you somehow.
Don't you think there's something wrong with that girl's head?
The Student Council seems to be full of weirdos, huh?
True, this isn't a manga.
But thanks to those guys,
we can turn a profit!
We have to be grateful for that, don’t we?
Shitheads!
It's not enough.
Fucking teasing bastards!
Fucking Bastards!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Once... let's do it just once...
One in six... a one-in-six chance...
This! This is it!
Here, right now, I'm alive!
The way this feels...!
Amazing!
Jabami Yumeko, was it?
I'll let you pay me back in full...
That really cut it close.
Becoming a pet might be even more dangerous for women.
I have to do something...
Yumeko, where do you plan on gambling next?
What are you reading?
A leaflet that was handed out in the hallway just now.
A notice for the 'Debt Adjustment Assembly'?
Debt Adjustment Great Meeting
Just do your best and brush up on your man-pleasing skills, ‘kay?
What gamble are we gonna do today?
It's all good as long as you win,
but losing’s gonna be hell...
Maybe I should drop out after all.
Ladies and Gentlemen, welcome to the 'Debt Adjustment Assembly'.
I am the secretary of the Student Council, Igarashi Sayaka.
In our academy, people who lose their heads over their debts appear every year.
Thus, the Student Council prepared something
to help those in need.
That would be... the ‘Debt Replacement Game’!
You will gamble in groups of four.
The debts can be changed drastically according to the results.
If you come in first, you’ll exchange your debt with the lowest debt of the group.
The lowest with the highest.
The debt will be replaced, to put it simply.
The one with the least amount of debt gains nothing, you say?
That’s certainly not the case. For them, the debt will be erased completely.
Now, everyone. This is your second chance.
please make use of it.
Damn hypocrites…
Quite the lavish proposal, isn't it?
Could the Student Council be gaining something from this?
Jabami Yumeko!
Good day to you!
I heard you majorly lost against the Council after what happened.
Indeed. I was careless, it seems.
I see you decided to participate in this meeting as well?
That's none of your business.
Whose fault do you think all of this is, huh?
Come now, no need for that!
Aren't we friends from the same class?
So annoying...!
Debt Adjustment Notice.
I will now begin distributing
these blank forms.
Please write down the name of your creditor and the amount owed.
Most of you are Crowd Debtors, which means that you owe a debt to a non-singular entity.
Anyone would be overwhelmed by this.
Through this game,
may you unify your debt with the Student Council and aim for a second chance!
They're just returning
whatever exploited money
they have to desperate students and get thanked for it.
There's no limit to how thick those masks of theirs are.
It's more likely that the Council's...
Now, I will announce the decided pairs.
Group A.
first Year, Flower Class - Mozu Karen...
I heard she has a total debt of 310,000,000.
I really don't want to end up in the same group as her.
Second Year,
flower Class - Jabami Yumeko.
flower Class - Saotome Mary.
Saotome-san, I'll place myself in your capable hands!
Ah, shit!
am I cursed by her or something?!
Now then, let us move to the details of this gamble.
Tln: Indian Poker also known as Blind Man's Bluff
The game we have prepared for you today is
two-Piece Indian Poker.
The rules are simple.
You will be using a deck with forty cards,
having excluded all Joker and Face Cards.
Initially the dealer will deal out the first cards, so be sure to inspect them.
Following that, the second card will be dealt.
You will avert your eyes from it and
place it in front of your head.
A Public Card and a Private Card.
You will be playing with a combination of these two cards.
The strongest is a 'Pair',
composed of two matching numbers.
Right below that is the 'Mark',
composed of two matching markings.
The weakest is the 'Pig',
composed of a pair where neither matches.
Should two matching types
face each other, the one with the larger total sum is deemed the winner.
And this is where the
game becomes interesting.
We will distribute various chips with differing colours, there being ten of each.
The total amount of one's chips is of little importance.
This is because in the end, the total worth decides the winner.
The worth of each chip amounts to a tenth of the player's written debt.
Should the debt be 100,000,000 Yen, the chip will be worth 10,000,000 Yen.
Debt Adjustment Great Assembly.
The game shall constitute ten turns for all.
For each turn, a payment of one chip must be issued.
To add to that, only up to five chips may be placed for each turn.
Debt Adjustment Great Assembly.
A single one of my chips would be worth 5,000,000 Yen.
In contrast, one of Yumeko's chip would be 31,000,000 Yen!
Just how will this gap influence us...?
And finally...
We will not offer any advice for this match.
That applies to cheating as well.
In a world of loss and victory, the fault lies with the deceived.
You will be stopped upon being discovered.
However, this does not mean that all past actions will be invalidated.
This concludes our explanation.
I pray you will all do your best.
Well then, should we move along as well?
Shit...
This is the last thing I wanted to do...
Jabami-san.
a quick word, if you don't mind.
Oh?
F
Debt Adjustment Great Meeting
Group
We've been awaiting your arrival.
You'll be the dealer?
Yes.
This table will have the largest opening gap, after all.
We can't let there be any mistakes, can we?
Hey, Yumeko.
Looks like we have a connection, huh?
A coincidence, surely.
Kiwatari-kun.
Huh?
Where's your Livestock Tag?
What, weren't you listening?
The debts here are just personal statements, right?
I'm not even close to livestock;
I just said that I owe a buddy some cash.
That way, the Council pays that buddy about
10,000,000 Yen to shoulder that debt.
So if I win here and get discharged with a refund, I can cash in.
That's quite confident of you, despite there being a chance of owing a real debt.
Hah!
I've won at three of these meetings before.
There's no way in Hell I can lose to livestock like you.
It's like picking up dropped cash, that's it.
This guy's way too brazen in front of the Student Council...
Looking the other way, huh?
Something like this could end up as a huge loss for the Student Council,
but it's still just a self-proclamation...
Now, we will have you commence a
game of Two-Piece Indian Poker.
Please give your participation fee first.
Once you have inspected your cards, please lay them face-down.
As for these, please avoid looking at them and place them facing the top of your head.
Now then, Kiwatari-sama may begin as the dealer.
Let's see, what to do...?
Backing down from the start's no fun.
bet! Kiwatari, one chip.
I call.
tsubomi, one chip.
That's a given.
The lower the cost, the lower the risk.
Going the greedy route would be correct,
but we can't afford to do that.
We have to be careful and–
I call!
jabami, one chip!
Huh? What do you think you're doing?!
Do you even realise how much a chip of yours is worth?!
Backing down from the start wouldn't make
for an interesting match, you know.
I'd have to place bets eventually anyways.
Well yeah, but that's still...
I like it. Strong-willed.
Is she even right in the head?
I'll fold.
Proclamations have been completed.
Please show your hands.
Seven and eight.
'pig', correct?
Three, six. 'Pig'.
Three, NIne. Mark'.
I win this one.
Kiwatari-sama wins the round.
all placed chips go to him.
That's what you get.
We will begin with the second turn.
The dealer role moves to Tsubomi-sama.
Bet.
tsubomi, one chip.
I'll fold.
Fold.
I raise.
kiwatari, four chips.
I fold.
All participants barring Kiwatari-sama fold.
kiwatari-sama wins.
Don't you guys think you're too weak for this?
This is exactly why you turned to livestock, you know.
Fucking pip-squeaks aren't even a challenge.
We will commence the third turn.
I seem to have drawn quite the card. I'll bet.
Jabami, one chip.
Heh. Finally picking up on the challenge, huh?
I raise.
kiwatari, two chips.
Oh, just two? I may be paraphrasing,
but 'are you too weak for this'?
Please, it's fine.
It's called 'strategy'.
I'll chew up and spit out those molehill chips of yours.
Won't even stand to look at them when that happens.
Yumeko, those chips of yours are plain security for me. There's no way in Hell I'm risking those.
Is that so? Then I have no choice but to steal this victory, no?
I raise.
jabami, three chips.
Wha–
Interestin'.
I call.
kiwatari, two pieces.
Proclamations are complete.
Please show your hands.
Luck's on my side, huh?
Two and five.
a 'Mark'!
What a coincidence.
I happen to be confident in my own luck, you see.
Four and Ten.
'mark'.
This bitch...
We shall now commence the fourth turn.
Saotome-sama will deal.
It's just like Yumeko said.
I have to place a bet eventually.
If that's the case...
I bet.
saotome, one chip.
I call.
kiwatari, one chip.
I fold.
I call.
Kiwatari, one chip.
If I lose here, my life's going to end up like that ridiculous life plan form said.
19 Years old
Enter Hakururi University
Become secretary of Sayama Senior Senator
Being interaction with Orida Zoukou
Married to Orita
Male son wanted
23 Years old
Second Child is
I'll get married to some politician, bear his children, and be some diet trophy wife.
The husband climbs the ladder
all the way to Minister of Education...
Our three kids would become independent,
and I'd spend my old age with my husband surrounded by beloved children and grandchildren and no worries.
I'd live a long happy life.
Saotome Mary would reach
the utmost happiness as a woman.
She will lead a life where
she couldn't even begin to wish for more.
That's worth shit!
I decide my own life! I'm not leaving it to anyone else!
I'll... I'll get back my own life!
I raise!
saotome, three chips!
Oh?
What are you, a moron?
Did you think I'd just get cold feet and fold after adding that to Yumeko's bet?
If I win here, you'll just have two chips left.
There's no coming back from that.
I call.
Like I would.
I can see right through livestock like you.
Saotome, Yumeko...
you're in this together, right?
Come on, you're way too obvious.
In this game, you only know what card you have.
No matter what huge numbers come your way,
you'll just lose to the one-in-four chance of there being a 'Mark'.
I seem to have drawn quite the card.
Who the Hell even says that?!
Betting 155,000,000 Yen on an off chance is even more ridiculous!
And that just makes it easier.
You just bet that because you knew you had a 'Mark'.
It's obvious you're just playing it up.
That sucks for you, huh?
Whatever fucking livestock does is always gonna be seen through by us humans!
I fold!
Jabami-sama?
I fold.
Good. They've lost two pairs they could've used.
At this rate, winning'll be a cinch!
Pretty sharp, aren't you?
Huh?
Doing heinous deeds all the time must mean you become sensitive to this kind of stuff.
Regardless, I'm glad I placed my bet.
really dodged a bullet.
What are you even–
It was a 'Pig', moron!
What was that?!
Having cheating makes it quite interesting...
... It is merely a means to seize victory.
I won with just a 'Pig'!
This match has already...
Episode 5
The Woman Who Became Human
Devolved to a war of bluffs!