This could be your last chance.
Remember this fondly!
Crap, I'm gonna die...
Do I have anything left...
...I can fire at her?!
Why am I dreaming about that now?
The Empress!
Episode 9
The Day Love Died
This feels so good!
What's up?
Oh, sorry, I just felt like someone was
behind me in the shower.
Oh god, that's like, so like a horror movie!
Huh?
Wh-what?!
There was a monster in the bathroom?
There's all kinds of creepy monsters in there.
Especially when you're all in there naked.
That's not what I mean!
God, stop being ridiculous and come help us!
It was a monster that was just
a woman's head with long hair!
Just a head...
Well, that's scary.
It wouldn't be able to soak in the bath.
God!
Could you please take us seriously?!
What's going on with you?
Just woke up on the wrong side of the bed.
So I'm gonna go back to sleep.
Nomura!
Get out right this second!
Unfortunately, it doesn't look like
you're getting back to sleep.
Hey.
Huh?
Don't forget this.
Oh, thanks.
You okay?
Get it together, alright?
Wha-?!
Y-you've got stamps!
And you only need one more?!
Nomura!
Yeah, yeah! Don't freak out!
I'm coming!
He's incredible.
At this rate he'll get all the stamps.
I don't think so.
Huh?
The last one he needs is...
The Empress has left her room.
Since a few days ago, she has drastically increased
the amount of carbohydrates in her diet...
...what is called carb-loading, if you will,
and now that she is prepared, she is on the move.
Now you are informed.
Thank you.
Message to staff.
No classes today.
You're late!
Sorry, mornings ain't easy on guys.
Where's Kikakujo?
She's busy at the girls' dorm this morning.
Huh?
Apparently some things have gone missing.
U. Baragasaki was making a fuss,
and I hear Hanasaka's little bear
has gone missing, too.
Do-mo's missing?!
I think he's just off playing somewhere.
Huh.
Do-mo! Where are you?
Where are you?!
Anything over there?
No sign of him.
Our search did not bear fruit!
Could he have gone towards the school building?
I do not want to make a big deal out of this...
Why not?
Princess Satori.
If that girl found Do-mo somewhere out of sight,
she would treat him like a stuffed animal
and be much too rough with him!
O-oh no!
N-no...
Expand our search to the school!
We must find him before
Princess Satori does, no matter what!
Yes, ma'am!
You two!
Huh? Kikakujo?
If you could, could you please
help me with my search?
Wait, search for what?
A wig!
Huh?
What?
A wig?
Chouka's "Cho-kyute!" blonde hair
is nowhere to be found!
Wha...
Huh...
She hasn't been able to go
anywhere this morning because of it!
Oh, Chouka, you're so exceedingly pitiful!
We've got to find it as soon as possible!
Wait, so she...
...was wearing a wig.
I'll tell you as soon as we find it!
What "problem" should I pop my head into?
I-I was looking for you.
Mi...
I mean, S-Satori.
Oh, that's right.
'Cause I'm Satori now.
Everyone seems busy today.
Miss Inaba!
U-umm, uh...
Is this about the wig?
Nono...
Unfortunately, I don't know about it, either.
You knew it was missing?!
Yes, I heard the commotion.
Where on Earth did it go...
Shall I come with...
How disappointing.
Over there?!
Nothing!
That little bastard...
Warabi?
We haven't seen hide nor hair...
Hide nor hair
Yes, the hair was hidden!
Hide the hair
We've searched everywhere it could possibly be!
We may find it somewhere unexpected...
After all, it's been slipping off a bit recently...
Was it really slipping off that much?!
And it's no use asking people...
Do not give up.
The walls are nary without ears, nor eyes!
The walls are Mary?!
Still, if they find out we've lost it,
they could blame us for being irresponsible!
Fret not.
I will own the whole ordeal!
Let us go!
Yes, ma'am!
Why is Hanasaka going to own the wig?!
Hey, d'ya find it?
Huh?
Kikakujo?
What's up?
Oh, Nomura!
How's it going over there?
No luck!
I-in any case, merci, Miss Warabi.
Why are you thanking me?
Let's hurry and find it so you
won't have to own it, Miss Warabi!
Indeed.
But why are you going this far, Princess Kikaku?
What are you talking about?
It's all for that cute girl!
R-right, of course.
Let's go at it again with vigor!
Yes!
For Kyo-bo!
For Chouka!
Kyo-bo?
Hey, guys, you're looking for different things.
She's looking for a cub, and she's looking for a wig.
A cub?!
A wig!
Forget that, we've got to find Do-mo!
Don't make light of it like that!
Do-mo is a living being!
Chouka can't live without that wig!
You won't convince me with that
hair-splitting argument!
Alright, you two, why don't you just look for it toge...
Together...
It was a monster that was just
a woman's head with long hair!
I think I've solved the case, Watson.
Feels so good!
Masuko was so right!
That monster must've been
a figment of our imagination!
I'm so sorry I scared you!
Oh, it's totally fine!
Not again?!
Is he here?!
Hey!
Don't come in when us ladies are showering!
You pervert!
Jeez, you guys!
Bingo!
So you unmasked the monster
in the boys' bathroom!
Onee-sama!
Oh, Nono...
Who's that?
Ubaraga--
The regina delle farfalle!
Queen of the Butterflies
Chouka
Baragasaki
Just call me Ubaragasaki today...
So she's the regina delle farfalle?!
Yes, she's regina delle--
You can simply call me Ubaragasaki today!
I-I see!
Forget that, did you find my wig?
Well...
This guy was havin' a bit of fun...
Poor Chouka!
Hey! We don't have any time to be getting down!
If we don't hurry and get ready, we'll be late!
Onee-sama, haven't you heard?!
Heard what?
Class is canceled today!
What happened?
The truth is,
the Empress has gone missing.
What?!
Amou?!
Amou?
Her striking hand was less like a chop, more like...
...a blade.
But "empress" means she's a woman.
Is she really that Amou?
I'm glad he was found before
Princess Satori found him,
but her lack of movement is actually quite unsettling.
Speaking of Satori, Princess...
About Misogi...
Hmm.
It's okay!
Calm down!
B-but, i-if we don't do something...
I told you to calm down.
Hey, Satori doesn't have time for that right now.
I-I'm sorry!
I would rather be feared than loved,
if I had to choose one...
But Tamaba Satori,
you're a monster who possesses both.
I get that a lot.
Your lonesome self finds a place
where you can look down on others,
then you dye all those around you in your own colors.
There's only one copy of that photo!
How did she...
Though I can't support your methods,
I can say that it's quite interesting
how they've granted you control.
However, you've developed the need
to constantly create new enemies,
then take them out.
But you've provoked the wrong person.
Tamaba Satori.
You pitiful soul.
You have nothing at all.
No ideals, no ideas, no reasons;
you've lost sight of everything,
simply wandering towards your next enemy.
You're a ghost.
Oh, I see.
What would Nomura say?
I wanna see Nomura.
Princess Satori and Misogi's relationship
certainly seems unnatural...
My goodness, the more I learn,
the more complicated it becomes...
There was one more thing I learned just now.
The Empress left her room?
I really don't want there to be any more trouble.
There's already trouble.
Th-that's...!
Kyo-bo!
We'll come with you!
No!
Do not follow me!
Hey,
can I go now?
N-no!
I-it's a trap!
Keishi School: Quick-Draw
Matchless Return
A single strike, your intentions concealed...
Impressive.
I couldn't sense it coming.
Auto-counter
But it doesn't matter to me.
S-Satori!
You are a pitiful soul.
But I cannot forgive you.
You have nothing.
I will take everything you've built until now
and destroy it all.
I-it didn't hit, why?!
Blow darts are such curious things!
Hey.
Who're you looking at?
Move, move, out of my way!
Keep your friends close, and your enemies closer...
I'd kept her within arm's reach
to keep a close watch on her,
but I cannot believe she's tried to steal a march on me!
It is times like these when I wish I had you, Nomura!
Misogi...
Huh?
This taste...
You're sisters?
I liked high-up places.
I liked looking down on people from high-up places.
That was where I belonged.
It was my spot.
But she...
she stole everything from me...
Satori's up top!
Misogi's on bottom!
I love you!
That was the first time I knew how I looked
when I looked down on my little sister.
Since then, she acted like she was me.
Even our mother thought my little sister was Satori.
Everything she has, she's stolen from me.
My face, my name, my future...
Yet, I still...
I love you!
Oh, jeez!
I don't know how to react when you say that!
Wh-what?
Now you don't need to despair anymore, right?
I was too late!
I see you're in the middle of something;
perhaps I should come again?
What? I'm just finishing up.
And now I don't have to go find you.
These things are best when wrapped up all at once.
I see.
I want to leave this place!
Is that so?
You've made quite the mess so far.
You should be prepared to lose
at least an arm for this.
And of course, it will be two on one!
Bear Swordsmanship
Switch
Woman and Beast as One
Simultaneous Slice
Auto-Counter: Tiger's Claw
What is her body made of?!
My sword and her claws didn't cut her!
Like she's made of steel!
Bear blood stinks too much to bear.
Warabi Hanasaka, you are an arrogant soul.
Did you really think you could do
anything to me with your weak body?
Your insolence knows no bounds!
So much happened today, but this should mean
everything's wrapped up, right?
Hey.
Hey!
Huh? Yeah.
What? You've been real quiet.
Wh-what?
That girl with the sword,
is that kid one of the Five Swords, too?
Inaba Tsukuyo!
The Academy's strongest pigtailed girl!
The only middle-school student in the five Swords!
She's a cool beauty that guys, girls,
and even the Five Swords are terrified of!
That's fine.
I'm gonna get my last stamp.
Wait!
She'll kill you!
She's super dangerous!
Maybe.
Too late anyhow.
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Amou, the Empress, has finally gone on the move!
She seems really used to the field of battle!
She intentionally making an escape route
to catch her opponent off-guard!
And even when someone tries to corner her,
she comes back with intent!
With all that, she's totally got it easy!
Episode 10
000012312312312312123000000000000000000
The Terrifying Blade, Inaba Tsukuyo
000000000000000
Intent that won't be deceived by intent!