I'm sorry. I couldn't make breakfast...
Don't be stupid.
You have such a high fever!
You keep resting.
I'll call school for you.
You don't have to make dinner, either.
Stay in bed.
Roger that.
Oikawa.
Here.
Otosaka.
Oh right, Otosaka was absent with a cold.
Kato.
Here.
Kijima.
Kiyama.
Here.
Konishi.
Komatsu.
Here.
Komiyama.
Episode 6
Happy You
Did Not Notice
The ability is... collapse.
Collapse? What kind of ability is that?
Who knows?
Probably something like
"able to destroy anything they target."
But still...
The fact that it's not "destruction"
is kinda scary.
So, where's this guy?
Let's see... wait?
This is our condo complex
that is attached to this academy.
Then, isn't it natural
for someone with an ability to be there?
Is that so?
This person is in their
condo right now, you see?
Don't you think that's strange?
Why's that?
Parents will not be wielders
of special abilities,
as it only occurs during adolescence.
I see...
Which means...
The target is home sick from school,
or something like that.
Impossible!
Whoa, that's an abnormal bit of agitation.
I'm sure it's a coincidence...
What is it? Try talking to us.
My little sister...
...is bedridden with a fever.
It might be that both siblings
show these symptoms after all...
Well, we're no scientists,
so let's go visit Ayumi,
and see if she really
gained a special ability while we're at it.
Wait, are all of you going?
We're talking about a sick girl here.
Oh, right.
Then I guess I'll go by myself...
No, wait... Ayumi is a fan of Yusa...
If I bring her along,
I'm sure Ayumi would be happy.
What's wrong?
But you, fanboy, are getting in my way!
I want it to be just Tomori and Yusa!
Should I take over his body and jump
from the window to injure him or something?
I see... so that's how giraffes sleep.
That's right! Giraffes wrap their necks
around into a coil when they sleep...
Wait, there's a giraffe here?
Where? Where?
I felt it senseless for him to come with us.
Nice going, Tomori!
But, but...
He's got a full-body protector on,
so he's fine as long as
he didn't fall head first.
We have someone injured,
so please bring an ambulance right away.
Now, the three of us
can go visit the ill after school.
I'd like to buy a get-well gift,
so lets swing by a convenience store.
Yes, yes! I want to buy something as well!
I was just thinking I wanted to buy
packaged porridge packs on my way home.
Then, shall we eat the same thing as Ayumi
and have porridge for dinner?
Sounds good.
You guys can eat freely
once you get home, can't you?
If we get in the way, we can...
We should all eat together, though!
Why is that?
That's because...
I'm living away from my parents too,
so I'm all alone even if I go home.
I'm used to being alone,
but Kurobane just moved out recently,
so maybe what she says is true.
No, Yusa isn't the only one...
I swore in my heart
that I won't trust anyone ever again.
I snuck out of that school.
Her parents sold her off to scientists,
and she no longer could trust anyone
and still is all alone....
The fact I have a little sister
makes me more fortunate.
Fine. We can all eat porridge
for dinner together.
Your total is 1360 yen.
This goes over my budget.
Oh I'll pay for this.
And these, too.
Why stewed enoki mushrooms?
Aren't stewed enoki mushrooms the best?
It's perfect on top of porridge, too!
That's just your personal tastes...
well, I don't care
as long as you're paying for it.
Yes, I'm fine with that.
Um, that can of cookies back there...
can I have that?
I've never seen anyone buy that before!
It will be 2500 yen
And it's expensive!
To top it off, what is this paper bag?
but I've never seen this paper bag, either!
Thank you so much!
It's this room.
My little sister is a
pretty huge fan of yours.
That makes me look forward
to seeing her even more!
However!
She is currently in bed with a fever...
we can't get her too excited.
At the least, she will get a nosebleed.
I'd like things to be gradual,
like "Hey? Can that really be Yusarin?"
or something like that.
Then I'll have my disguise mask on.
All right! Then, can you
hang out here for a bit?
Guests? Who are they?
Big Brother Yu is home!
Oh, elder brother sir, sorry to be intruding!
I'm Nomura, the class representative!
We came here in order to visit Ayucchi
while she's sick!
I'm Oikawa.
Your little sister is allowing
me to be her friend.
It is a pleasure meeting you.
Can your brown-nosing
be more obvious than that?
You already got denied once.
Ayucchi will hate you even more if you do that!
So this is the guy
that asked Ayumi out and got dumped..?
Sorry to barge in with so many people!
Come on, both of you, let's go home!
Elder brother sir, sorry to be so rowdy!
And Ayucchi, get better soon!
Hello! Excuse me, or rather,
sorry for coming in already!
Wait! I didn't call for you yet!
I thought it was just a personnel swap....
It's Big Sister Tomori!
You got to see me again, see?
Can it be that you're now
Big Brother's girlfriend?
No way!
But you guys make a good couple...
Well... we have one more guest.
Nice to meet you.
Yu sa ri n...
She saw through me instantly!
I'll stop her bleeding!
Make sure to breathe from your mouth.
There, it stopped now.
You're right! That's amazing!
I'm so glad.
Yu sa ri n...
I'll stop her bleeding!
Should I cast my magic charm
that stops nosebleeds?
No, I think it will do the opposite
of what you intend, so please don't...
Yusarin in the flesh. Boy, was I surprised!
You finally calmed down?
I'm glad!
Oh, these are some cookies
as a get-well gift. I'll leave them here!
N-No way! I made Yusarin worry about me!
She's nothing more
than one of my classmates right now.
Don't think about it too much.
Right, right!
Her speech patterns
are starting to catch on already...
And the get-well gift from me is... this!
I love those!
Do you have an appetite?
We bought some pouched porridge.
What about you, Big Brother?
We're eating porridge, too.
Porridge for all!
Time to eat!
It's super-duper-delicious!
Isn't it? Isn't it?
Thank you for the meal!
Thank you for the meal...
Excuse me.
Thank you for the hard work.
Yes... Yes, I understand. Excuse me now...
I'm so sorry, I have to go work now!
You're talking to a current showbiz celebrity.
Don't complain.
That is exactly correct!
Please do your best at your work!
Sure! With that, I'll be going now.
Ayumi, please get better soon!
Yusarin! Thank you so much for coming!
Gratitude and thankfulness
falling like rain and hail!
Then I guess we'll clean up now.
You're not going to wash them?
You can wash this many dishes
at any point in time.
What blood type are you?
I'm washing it now.
You can at least dry them with a dishcloth!
S-Sure...
So you two really might be dating
and keeping it a secret from Ayu!
That won't happen.
You two are so compatible!
Is that how you hide your bashfulness?
You're seriously wrong.
Come now... Ayu thinks you two
are totally a great couple.
Attractive and intelligent boys
like this chump is someone
I can never be a good match for.
I think you're such a good match
that you're even too good for Big Brother Yu.
Don't be fooled, Ayumi!
Realize that all the compliments are
contradicting as she used the word "chump"!
Come on, shut up and go watch some TV.
Fine.
Wow, that was fast!
Yusarin moves at amazing speeds!
That's pre-recorded...
Oh, I see...
Here, some medicine.
You turn in for today. I'll tuck you in.
It's a good thing you
have a great big brother.
Yeah, but I'm slightly
scared of going to sleep...
What's wrong?
I had a scary dream this afternoon.
Well, if you have a fever,
it's common for you to have a nightmare,
so there's nothing to be uneasy about.
By the way, what kind of dream was it?
Don't ask something like that
because it will remind her of the nightmare!
Indeed...
Then, I'll be going now.
Sorry to have bothered you.
I am eagerly awaiting your next patronage.
I'll see her off. I'll be right back.
Really, it's nothing like that.
Please ask her what the nightmare was about.
It might be a clue in figuring out
what the "collapse" ability is.
Wait. We still don't have proof that Ayumi
is the wielder of the special ability.
It can be someone else
that lives in this condo complex...
It is true that we don't have proof.
But, the possibility is very high.
And "collapse"... I can't help but feel
that it will be a dangerous ability.
That's the same terror that I initially felt.
So, get it out of her.
This will be for Ayumi as well.
All right.
Even if her fever goes down,
make her stay home tomorrow just in case.
At present, we just have too few information.
Yeah...
I'm back.
Welcome back!
Hey, Ayumi.
Can you tell me what that dream
you mentioned earlier was about?
Well, I don't remember it well...
You can just give me a vague idea.
A dream where something breaks.
What did?
I think... the ground?
What kind of ground was it?
I can't remember that much...
It was like there were
cracks in the ground and splitting up...
Why do you ask that?
Wouldn't it be scary if that dream came true?
Ayu is the type that doesn't believe
in spiritual stories like that...
The world is full of
spiritual things, though.
The ground splitting up?
Is that some kind of a hint?
Maybe that ability is something
so horrible that it will also
rope in the person using it.
We still have too few
information after all...
What should we do?
For now, we can use the large number
of surveillance cameras set
up at the middle school
to see which way the ability is headed.
Other than that, probably just letting
the teachers know to look out for Ayumi.
The middle school has a lot of people,
so it's dangerous if something happens.
It's a lot safer at the condo complex.
I'd like to gather a bit more information,
so have her stay home again tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Should I go cast a magic spell
that cures her cold?
There it is! Yusarin's magic spell series,
#21! The spell for curing a cold!
Such a turn-off!
No, she'll get a nosebleed again,
so I'd like you to pass this time...
Yes, then I'll visit once she's better!
Yeah, that helps a lot.
36.5 degrees... your fever has gone down.
Ayu here has managed to
finish fighting the illness,
and going to do her best
like she usually does!
You didn't have a weird dream, right?
Correct.
But you're still recovering.
I think you should stay home for one more day.
It's boring to stay in bed even without a fever,
so I'd like to go to school.
There's still a chance that
your cold will relapse,
so I can't allow that as your big brother.
Suck it up, be a good girl,
and stay in bed for one more day. Got that?
I'll contact your school.
Ayu is not so easy
that you can stop her time and time again...
The grudge of the pizza sauce...
will be avenged!
Are your injuries all better already?
You mean when I was pushed off
from the student council room two days ago?
Yeah.
It's something that happens often,
so accidents of that level
can be dealt with right away.
Though, when I first met her,
it really was an instant trip to the hospital...
If I was in your shoes,
I'd never be able to deal with it all...
It really makes me slightly unsure
of whether or not Tomori should be the leader...
She is a lot more calculating
than what you're currently thinking.
Oh, she's calling us over again.
Let's hurry up and eat!
You're finally here...
Both of use were eating pasta,
so we couldn't wolf it down. Sorry about that.
How did you find the time
to twirl a pasta around your fork to eat?
What? Did something happen?
Ayumi is at school.
No, I contacted her school
and made her stay home today as well...
How was her condition today?
The fever was down...
But I was worried about her relapsing,
so I told her to stay home for one more day.
Because her temperature is normal, perhaps.
She decided to attend school from third period,
based on her own decision.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Let's go check Ayumi's condition right away.
Nice seeing you!
Um, Otosaka?
I found a sweets shop
that serves really good red bean soup.
I'll treat you some
to celebrate you getting better.
I'm sorry, but I just got better,
so I'll have to pass.
H-Hold on a second!
If right after getting better is bad,
how about we go on the weekend...
You really don't get it, do you...
you've been denied once already. Just give up!
Outta my way!
I'm going to make my way back through from here!
Oh, shut up, shut up!
I'll do something with this guy,
so Ayucchi, you can go on ahead.
Thanks, Nomu-chan.
Wait, hold on, O-Otosaka!
You don't stand a chance anymore!
Hey, wait, where are you going?
It's a shortcut.
Konishi?
It's because you showed up...
What is?
With Oikawa...
With Oikawa?
With Oikawa... I used to eat lunch all alone.
We were supposedly dating.
But ever since you showed up,
Oikawa... Oikawa...
It's as if he's completely forgotten about me!
He looks at just you all of the time!
Wait, let's talk it out!
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding!
So put that cutter knife away!
It's your fault...
That's not true!
That's why... you're going to see some pain!
Help... someone...
Someone..!
Help me!
This is... the collapse...
I guess we didn't make it in time...
- I'm going in!
- You can't! It's too dangerous!
Ayumi...
Ayumi!
Don't go! You'll get roped into it!
You there! Get away! It's dangerous!
Ayumi... Ayumi...