Nomura's supervision is my responsibility!
Non! It is my job!
C'mon, you two.
Is it really cool for you guys to keep
hanging around me all the time?
Don't you have jobs to do as the Five Swords?
I am carrying out my job as a member right now!
Pay no mind to either of us.
I don't really care, but...
You're flashin' me.
Wha-?!
Aloha!
Hello, Japan! Hello, Coexistence Academy!
Warabi is back from Hawaii!
Aloha oe!
Alo...
Nomura!
Hold it!
You bastard!
I'll correct you!
What is going on over there?
This won't do.
This won't do at all.
Episode 4
The Warabinpics are Starting!
I didn't expect a situation such as this to arise
Important:
Targets   requiring correction
Dangerous!!
while I was on my class trip.
A member of the Five Swords should uphold order,
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
not befriend a target for correction.
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Nomura caught
skipping class
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
Onigawara scolds Nomura on
the way to school for not
doing his homework
As such, Onigawara Rin and Kikakujo Mary
are both added to those who require correction,
and I will carry out their correction!
I propose this idea to this meeting of the council!
Princess Tsukuyo isn't here.
Uh-huh.
I am in favor.
Princess Satori, what is your opinion?
I don't care either way.
I mean, the opinion of a senior member is
more important than the votes, right?
That's right!
Well, let me see what you've got in store for them...
...on that special correction menu of yours.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
School Store
Egg bread, please!
One for me, too!
Two egg breads!
How disappointing.
Well then, let's get the party started.
Thank you.
The legendary festival of blood!
Hey, what is that?!
Things are getting really crazy...
Masuko!
Wait a sec, I'll get you down!
Nomura.
Wait!
I've...
...got a bad feeling about this.
Heaven knows! Earth knows! I know!
Ruffians disturb the peace of our academy!
What?
How deplorable!
Disturbing moral standards disturbs the mind!
As such, it disturbs the body!
I have no choice but to hold these events!
The Festival of Blood!
The Sports Deathtival!
Featuring Warabi Hanasaka's special coexistence menu!
The Warabimpics!
I thought so.
Right on the mark.
Of course, the main focus will be on you,
Nomura Fudo!
Jeez, she keeps blathering on...
I don't give a crap about this
Warawampics or whatever.
Hey, you!
Why're you doin' this to him?
He brought contraband goods inside our walls!
That is his sin!
Well, yeah...
Do you want to save him?
Well, then!
If you make your way through
my countless challenges, it will be so!
I will also give you my stamp for your permission slip!
That's all I need to hear!
C'mon down here!
Or do you want me to come up to you?
Hanasaka!
What is the meaning of this?!
That's right! Why are you doing this?!
You fools!
This has been decided upon
by the council of the Five Swords!
Wha-?!
Come forth, my three musketeers!
Wh-what was that?
How would I know?!
Huh? Everyone's gone.
They all just disappeared...
Who're you?
What are you doing?
Do you have any idea who I am?!
I should be saying the same thing to you.
Tsunemi Toko of the Hanazaka Musketeers
We're third years, and your senpais.
Kinue Tanukihara, of the selfsame group
We rank higher than you from our years alone.
Nico Saruwatari, of the selfsame group
And...
Council of the Five Swords Decision
Warabi
Tamaba
Even Tamaba?!
You've been ordered to participate
in the Warabimpics as well.
And we will be your opponents.
What?!
All behind our backs!
We've been duped!
Quiet!
The two of you have stayed by his side every day,
displaying affection for one of our targets!
It is preposterous that members of the Five Swords
are disrupting the peace on their own accord!
Y-you've got it all wrong!
M-menteuse!
And Nomura doesn't need violent correction!
We are taking responsibility for him
and supervising him exceedingly well!
You fool! His supervision is my job!
No, it's mine!
Ugh! Now, of all times, you're acting so unsightly?!
Stop that and start the activities!
The first game of the Warabimpics!
The game is...
This!
Try yer luck...
at Raging Sumo!
A sumo ring!
Looks real nice!
This isn't the time to be getting excited!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Listen up!
We've got to get through this first game
with all we've got!
Warabi will come to fight herself in the last game.
If that comes to be, our chances for winning
will be exceedingly slim!
Huh.
What kinds of games did she do before?
The most tragic one in the past...
Tragic?!
...was the bucket relay.
The target for correction had
a flaming torch stuck to his back,
and everyone would pass down
a bucket of gasoline in a relay.
As a result,
half the school building was damaged in a fire.
You sure you shouldn't have done
something about her before?
Huh?
What are these?
Your mawashi, or sumo belts.
What?!
You're going to sumo wrestle. It's only natural.
Make sure you tie them properly.
You can wear them over your
gym clothes if you like, but...
I said you can wear them over!
If you don't know how to tie them, we can help you.
Onee-sama!
Nono?!
Chouka!
Stop this already!
You're getting much too full of yourselves!
A war fan!
This girl...
she has two police batons!
War Fan Art
Nono-san!
You looked away.
Double Police Baton
How impudent!
You deserve...
Any more, and you'll be facing me next.
That's enough.
Nono, U. Baragasaki, lay down your arms.
Onee-sama...
The decision of the council is final.
Not even a member of the Five Swords can reverse it.
That's right!
But I will remember this moment!
I will not forget this humiliation!
Nor what you've done to my younger sister!
Now then, why don't you get over there
and put your mawashi on?
If you need help, just call for it.
Well, they usually have the second do it for you,
but I guess I can do it myself.
Huh?
Did you do that yourself?
Yup.
Nomura.
Come here a minute.
Vous permettez?
H-hold on a sec!
Sh-should I hold it like this?
Yeah, like that.
C'mon, stay still!
Turn around.
L-like this?
Spread your legs more.
Huh?
Hold it tight.
Hey!
D-don't pull it so tight!
If I don't make it tight it'll just fall apart.
Turn around.
I was slightly prepared for this, but...
I-I had no idea it would be so humiliating!
I'm exceedingly embarrassed just by watching her!
D-don't touch me more than you need!
I'll try my best.
Alright, turn around again.
O-okay.
There!
Almost done.
Put your weight on it like you're sitting down
and I'll pull it up for you.
I-I have to do it?
Yup!
That's it!
Alright!
Perfect!
Okay, you're next, Kikakujo.
I-I'll have Rin-san do it!
I'm sure she knows how to now!
I forgot.
What?!
Don't let this chance get away.
You'll go through the same thing, too.
N-no!
I cannot accept this!
Enough with that, Kikakujo!
He was going to touch you,
there was no getting out of it!
That's not what I'm mad about!
What?!
He finished me up really quickly!
Even though he spent so much time on you!
Why do you have a problem with this!?
You must have some kind of fetish
you don't want to talk about!
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?!
Now, the Thirteenth Warampics,
thanks to the help of our film crew,
will be broadcast on all in-school monitors!
Rin-san...
They look kinda good in those.
I can't believe they made Rin Onee-sama wear that!
Mary Onee-sama must be so distraught!
C-cameras?!
You're filming this?!
Non! Stop this at once!
Get out of here!
Get over here, you three senpai musketeers!
Which one of you's gonna be the first?!
Hey! Who said you got to go first?!
That's right!
What's this?
You three aren't even wearin' mawashi.
Your opponent is already above you in the ring!
What?
Above you!
Someone's there!
It's a frickin' bear!
Don't worry! He's quite the gentle bear!
His name is Kyo-bo the Brutal!
Those two things are not the same!
I thought I was gonna be fighting you three!
What are you saying?
These are my three musketeers!
Tohko,
Tanukihara,
and Kyo-bo!
What about Saruwatari?!
You brought her out like she was
the most important one!
No matter your reasoning, it's against the rules
to pit him against a non-human!
Don't lose your head over this.
If one of you can defeat Kyo-bo,
I'll let all three of you off the hook!
I get it. So that's what you're after.
That's why none of you were wearing mawashi.
Who will fight first, then?
I'll do it.
I'll, no, I'll do it!
No, I--
Pretty sure I said I'm gonna do it!
So he's not even afraid of Kyo-bo.
Ever since I've had hair down there,
I haven't lost any kind of sumo match once!
You're talking about nipple sumo, aren't you?!
Nipple sumo?!
Nomura...
Let's get... ugh, this started!
Face your opponent!
When this soda bottle hits the ground...
...the match will start!
Face off, face off!
I wanna go home so bad.
But unfortunately,
I'm the kind of guy who won't let
a threat made with violence slide!
Hakkeyoi!
Nokotta!
A tackle?!
From right in front of him?!
That was a pretty good tackle!
But that's as far as you go!
Slapdown
You're already out of strength to charge him!
No...
Nomura is only starting!
He's keeping a technique hidden for now!
A slapping attack?!
No...
That tiny sound the sacroiliac joint makes when his hand
collides with the line of the iliacus muscle...
His magic bullet!
Figured it wouldn't be that easy.
He dodged it!
No choice now.
Time for my hidden bullet!
Magic Bullet
A bullet from his left hand?! He's ambidextrous?!
Still haven't had enough?!
He pissed off Kyo-bo?!
Open-hand Slap
Footsweep
Ain't easy for you to walk on two legs, huh?
It's better if you walk like nature intended!
I'm right here.
Don't tell me he's...
It can't be!
He's going to lift Kyo-bo's huge body out of the ring?!
Don't make it harder on yourself, boy!
To build up my legs and core...
ever since I was a kid, I've been fightin' adults!
Nomura, let him go!
You're going to get crushed!
No, I'm not letting go!
I don't care how proud you are,
but dragging in innocent people...
and hurting them, too...
then embarrassing these two here,
while you watch on from high above,
are all things I just can't stand!
Nomura...
If I win, you're all going to wear mawashi!
Be prepared!
What?!
Dammit!
How exceedingly frustrating!
Hey, who tied this guy's mawashi?
What?
You got a problem with it?
No, just wanted to say thanks.
'Cause you helped me win.
Wh-what?!
When he put it down and stepped away...
He untied it?!
I've heard of this happening!
Yes, I have as well!
Tanuki-senpai, you know how to write this down?
Huh?
Kyo-bo lost by "fujomake", mawashi unraveling.
Also called "morodashi".
Nomura wins!
Yes!
Alright!
Let's keep up the winning streak in the next round!
I-I'm still reluctant to work together with you on a team!
Th-that's right.
I'm only doing this because it was
decided by the council!
Princess?
Princess!
Princess?!
Tell them all.
Yes, ma'am!
Get changed and get inside.
And...
all personnel, switch into Red Pepper Tower Shift!
Huh?!
The games are over.
This is war!
Omugi here!
Hiko here!
Nomura won the match by fujomake!
In Article 16 of official sumo rules,
If your mawashi comes unraveled
and falls off, you lose!
And everyone sees what's underneath, oh my god!
Morodashi: show it all, you take a fall!
Episode 5
00000000000000000000000000
The Love-Crazed Blade, Warabi Hanasaka