The first time I wrote a game
was back in fourth grade.
The creator has fun making the game,
and the player laughs.
I was completely enamored with
that simple, happy communication.
Before I knew it, I was a serious
freeware game developer.
Nobe's Game Room
Home             About            Projects            Forum            Contact
Freeware games by Nobe!
Please download and enjoy.
I appreciate feedback on the forums.
But if you ask me if making games
was always fun, the answer is no.
I started it as a hobby,
but with the chronic pain of creation,
Subject: Review of the new game
Posted by: Redo
Game sucks
Re: Review of the new game
Posted by: Rin
The setting is too weird. It stresses me out.
and seeing brutal comments,
I spent days bummed out.
Re: Review of the new game
Posted by: Shirura
Why did you publish this?
Re: Review of the new game
Posted by: Mikoto
It's boring.
The reason I couldn't stop releasing
more games under the name Nobe
was because there was
just one person who always
Posted by: Yama-san
I liked it! It's chill, as always!
Re: Review of the new game
had the same tastes I did,
and kept rooting for me
with respect and warmth.
Onee-chan, your writhing
technique isn't cute at all.
Huh?
Wasn't I playing a board game with
Uehara-san and the others since noon?
Yeah.
I think they left in the evening.
Huh? That's weird.
I don't remember what happened then...
Hey, Konoha...
Yeah?
I don't really like how, in manga and stuff,
the girl sees the delinquent guy
helping a puppy in the rain,
and changes her mind about him
and falls in love.
Where'd that come from?
I get what you mean, but...
Of course, I accept that it's just
a common cliché in storytelling.
And?
B-But...
I think it's cheap to tug at the heartstrings
by playing on surprises in your character.
I-I guess I'm trying to say it's
absolutely not a true feeling.
Sorry, Onee-chan, what are you talking about?
I-I'm saying...
I...
I should stick to my position that
I still absolutely hate him, right?
I'm not wrong, am I?
Right?!
Sure.
I think that's good.
I know, right?
Yeah.
I'm confused, but, uh... who is it?
Yama-san.
And I bet he's just acting
to make it look like it.
That's impossible!
No one talks bad about Yama-san.
Not even my sister.
Take it back.
I-I'm sorry?
Uh... Yama-san is a great person.
Good.
Uh...
Onee-chan?
Subject: Re: Review of the new game
Name: Nobe
Long time no talk.
Damn it!
Famitsu
Oh, right.
Konoha?
What, Onee-chan?
Uh...
Why are you so out of breath?
Your face is beet-red.
I-I was doing some light exercise.
Yeah.
Nothing suspicious, of course.
Wholesome exercise.
Okay...
So what do you want?
Oh, right.
I'm going to the convenience store.
Is there anything you want?
Oh, you're going to buy Famitsu.
Y-You got me!
Oh, yeah. Onee-chan, can I borrow your PC?
Sure, but why?
My PC doesn't seem to have the
specs I need to watch this video.
I see.
By the way, what are you watching?
The opening movie of the
new BUILD game that I lov—
Buil...?
I-I want to watch my favorite band's
new music video! Okay?
J-Just go already.
Huh?
Okay, See you.
Welcome.
Famitsu
I always knew you were creepy.
So you are a stalker type.
I'm not, okay?
But thanks for the freezie.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's just that I wanted one.
I'm just sharing because
I didn't want the whole thing.
I know what you mean.
You feel weirdly guilty when you
eat the whole thing by yourself.
Right?
Uh... Shut up, stalker.
I'm not! It's just...
I forgot my transit pass.
I was just on my way to go get it.
And that's how you ran into me?
I mean, I get that it's weird for me to go
to a girl's place by myself out of the blue.
But let me make an excuse.
Depending on what it is,
I may call the police.
Is your phone turned off, Chiaki?
Huh?
Who forgets to charge their
phone in this day and age?
Don't you play games or anything?
Huh? Uh...
N-No, I mean, how should I put it...
G-Girls like me get asked out by
a ton of boys during the summer.
It makes it hard to check my phone.
You couldn't have come up
with a worse excuse.
Wh-What do you know about me, Keita?
Your body.
You don't have the body of someone
who's out doing stuff all summer.
Look at your skin.
Wh-What gives you the right to say that?
Because I sport the same
kind of skin, I guess.
I'm sorry.
Now that you mention it,
I think I saw your card wallet.
Yeah?
Thank goodness.
I'm really sorry for
coming uninvited, though.
But don't you just spend all summer
playing games at home?
Well, yeah, but I get the feeling
this summer break is going
to be different from usual.
Different from usual?
Well, not that we have any specific
date plans or anything yet.
Really?
You're so self-conscious. It's creepy.
Sh-Shut up.
Although it's true that
I didn't need it just now.
But I guess I acted outside
of my comfort zone
because I wanted to change myself.
I wanted to gather my courage
and get a little closer.
To Tendou-san.
I mean... I know people like me tend to
make excuses out of the smallest things.
Even I think it's pathetic.
Oh, yeah. I remember I gathered my courage
to come talk to you before, too.
You seemed pretty awkward that time, too.
You know how hard it is to talk to the
opposite sex when you've never had contact
with them before, right?
I get chills just thinking about it.
See?
Although I'm glad it was you, Chiaki.
When I saw you having so much
fun playing Aegis VIII,
I totally forgot how nervous I was.
I was actually really happy.
It was like I'd found a true friend.
Although I guess that was a misunderstanding.
What's wrong?
W-Well, that was a total nuisance to me.
Have you thought about
how it feels, as a girl,
to be eyed by a gross guy
with heavy breathing?
You just shot down my tiny victory.
You're trying to break me, aren't you?
It meant I got to meet Uehara-san,
though, so I can forgive you.
Th-Thanks for having me.
Have a seat.
Oh, it's fine. I'll be leaving right away.
Why don't you have some...
Why don't you have some tea first?
Thanks.
I feel kind of bad.
Just make yourself at home.
D-Don't look, pervert!
Sorry.
I guess I should get going.
Actually, I'll allow it.
View to your heart's content.
Why the change of heart?!
I won't!
Oh, i-is it okay if I go to
my room to charge my phone?
In that case, I really should...
J-Just give me a moment.
I'll be right back.
Message from Tsucchie
Let's do this
Thanks
Message from Tsucchie
I appreciate it
Let's do this
Message from Tsucchie
Thanks
I appreciate it
Keita...
Chiaki?
Y-Yes?
It just started raining.
You might want to bring your laundry inside.
Um... Got it.
Nobe's Game Room
Home         About        Projects        Forum        Contact
A-Are you okay?
No!
Don't! Not my phone... or my PC, either!
Your phone and PC?
N-No!
Nobe's Game Room
Home         About        Projects        Forum        Contact
Nobe-san?
Mono-san?
Keita...
Y-Yes? How can I help you?
I never intended to tell you,
but I need to tell you now.
S-Sure.
As you might have realized by now,
it's what it looks like.
As you can see, Nobe the
freeware game developer,
and Mono on the social
network game, are both...
Both...
That was a good nap.
Konoha...
Sorry, Onee-chan. I was using
the computer in bed, and...
You!
Th-That's right.
Nobe and Mono are actually my
sister, Hoshinomori Konoha!
What?
Nobe and Mono are actually
Hoshinomori's sister?!
That's right.
Shocker, huh?
Well, yeah, that's a shocker, but...
Wait, what?
But didn't you...
I've been spending the past few days trying
to decide if I should help Hoshinomori,
and meanwhile, they throw this curveball.
That's Amano for you.
Konoha-san's reaction was
kind of weird, though.
It's like she didn't really
know what was going on.
Well, duh.
She isn't Nobe, after all.
So, what did you do then?
Well...
Don't you dare leave the living room.
Don't even move one step.
R-Right.
I'll be going once we're done, though.
Just stay there.
Maybe she was harassing me or something.
She wouldn't let me leave.
Yeah...
I must have waited for about ten minutes.
So, um, allow me to introduce her.
This is my sister, Konoha.
I'm Nobe and Mono.
Nice to meet you, Yama-san, Tsucchie-san.
R-Right.
I recently learned of your connection,
and I was trying to figure out how to
tell you, and I came across a bit weird.
That's it.
It was like I was talking to a
state-of-the-art bishoujo AI.
So then we just kind of said hi,
and I went home.
Something just doesn't sit right.
I can imagine.
I was really shocked and happy that Nobe-san
and Mono-san were the same person...
But I just can't see them as Konoha-san.
I just can't see her as anything more
or less than Chiaki's younger sister.
I'm being cold, though, right?
I finally got to meet the person I admire
and who treats me really well...
Of course you can't see that person as her.
There's nothing at all wrong about that!
I'd like to tell him that,
but I can't tell him the truth.
This is the answer that
Hoshinomori chose for herself.
I'm just a bystander. I don't have
the right to object to that decision.
But this is just too much.
I can't be happy for Amano and Tendou,
even if things work out for them.
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
I have to head to work.
I'm going. Later.
Okay...
I almost blurted out the truth.
I still want to root for Hoshinomori.
There's nothing I can do
if she's already told him.
I can't be happy for Amano and Tendou,
even if things work out for them.
I see.
So Uehara-kun does like Tendou-san.
I guess there's no mistake about it.
Could it be that there's another
girl who has a crush on me,
and Uehara-kun decided to back her up?
Or something?
Nope.
Nah.
Let's just accept reality
and do the best I can.
New
Dating sims
And now here I am, buying dating sims!
I'm so sorry, Tendou-san!
Found it.
What a beautiful design!
The logo and colors are so down-to-earth.
The illustration is simple, too.
And yet it's gripping.
Why didn't I bother to disguise
myself today, of all days?
Konoha-san?
Wait, was Nobe-san always like this?
Why do you keep messing with
me in all the worst ways?
Huh?
U-Um...
That wasn't me as Nobe or Mono or anything.
That was just me reacting as Konoha.
Don't mind me.
Huh?
I'm kind of confused.
You're the same person, aren't you?
I-I'm saying, I might be
angry at you right now,
but Nobe and Mono are
still just fine with you!
Right...
So you have multiple personality
disorder or something?
Yeah, that sounds good!
That's a good interpretation!
All right, let's use that.
Use that?
Think of me and Nobe as two different people.
Of course, I'm Nobe and also Mono, but...
Right.
By the way, you're technically my senpai, right?
Oh, right.
By a year.
That means I'm supposed to show
you some more respect, right?
That would be kind of awkward at this point.
We've already kind of skipped over that.
You're right.
Okay, I'm just going to keep
that attitude, then, Senpai.
Don't tell anyone I was buying adult games.
Anyone? Like?
Just don't tell anyone.
Got it, I guess.
Good.
So, Amano-senpai,
what do you think of my sister?
Why do you ask?
Is it weird for me to be curious?
It just so happened that Mono-san
and Nobe-san were actually her sister.
It's not much to think about.
This situation is a pain in the ass.
Okay, then what do you
think of Mono and Nobe?
I'm just really happy.
I seriously love your work as Nobe-san!
What's wrong?
Man, the embarrassment, the envy,
the guilt, the annoyance...
There's a huge traffic jam of emotions
happening inside me right now.
All right, Amano-senpai, would you take
responsibility and allow me to hit you once?
What?! Why?
That makes no sense!
Huh? Chiaki?
K-Keita!
Wh-Why are you here?
How am I supposed to answer that?
Onee-chan and I already
had plans to meet up here.
Oh, okay.
So that's why you went
adult game shopping by your—
Senpai!
So that's why you ran into me while I was
happily buying adult games by myself.
Wow. Ew.
Were you two ever that close, though?
Well, you know, Senpai and I talk
about my work and stuff.
Right?
Right.
Wh-What specifically do you talk about?
Um...
Wait, why do you care?
You can talk to my sister about
Nobe and Mono all you want, Senpai.
We don't keep any secrets from each other.
Look who's talking!
We got to know each other
a little better, I guess.
A scum-of-the-earth who buys adult games
in the light of day, with my adorable,
intelligent, kind sister?
It's mine.
Hello?
Yes.
Yes...
Okay, I'll be going now.
Okay.
Well, then, uh...
Later.
Okay...
Um, see you later.
What?
What does that mean?
U-Uehara-san?
Uehara-san?
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Uehara-san just blurted something out
in a serious tone, and hung up.
What?
He said,
"I've decided I'm choosing you."
Isn't that...
...a confession?!