The next time I see him, I'll kill him.
You passed!
I'll give you my stamp!
Huh?
But for me to give you my stamp,
I'll have to take responsibility for you.
What?
I will also be joining Rin-san in
supervising your behavior from now on!
I told you, he's mine!
He's my cochon!
He doesn't need two people watching him!
Well then, you can just quit!
How unsightly!
It's almost like I've run away from him.
I know what it is that has made me go so insane...
The pain I felt that day
has endlessly plagued me ever since.
Perhaps my heart and body were weakened
by that unfamiliar damage...
My chest aches uncontrollably in its desire for it.
But Nomura is not a man who will submit.
He's just the same as I.
Then I must continue until I reach him.
If he will not be mine...
then I must kill him!
Episode 12
The Girls' Machiavellism
What are you doing with that?
What, you said it yourself.
You can come at me just like a beast would.
That's all I'm doin'.
Jigen School's sword movements
are swift, as is its footwork,
and if the wielder's speed is raised to
that of a flash of lightning, of unyou,
they tread into the territory of invisibility.
But his is imperfect.
After two or three displays,
the effect loses its effectiveness.
That's when...
He purposefully exposed his vitals.
It seems she is more resistant to
piercing bare skin than clothed skin,
so that technique may work quite well with her.
Amou...
I thought you were empty...
Who knew you still had your "magic bullet".
She took the magic bullet...
and stood up!
That's right, I ain't gonna go down
just with one hit, either!
I'm not done hitting you yet!
I'll give you a special treat,
so you come at me with all you got, too!
Like this!
Not bad!
That's more like it!
It's clear now.
The last one poisoning our academy
of coexistence was...
It's unexpected, but good that it was not Tsukuyo.
Perhaps I'll show my face for the first time in a while.
For now, we'll have to think of how to punish those two.
A student's duty, first and foremost, is to study.
What is the point of those two
hitting one another without defending at all?
It hurts to try and understand.
Most of all, why do they seem so happy?
Could this be what friendship is?
I have no clue.
I can't follow.
It hurts...
I wanted this for the longest time.
I wanted a pain that would help me forget
the burning in my heart.
More! Give me more!
Look only at me, touch only me,
think only of me!
Nomura!
Magic Bullet
Auto-Counter
You really were holding back
on your auto-counter, huh?
What?
I simply wanted to do things your way.
Give it your all.
It's too early to be exhausted.
I'll give you a treat.
Be sure to fire it hard.
You don't like overwhelming victories.
You calmly see your way to a chance of winning,
while purposefully taking your opponent's attacks.
Wouldn't say it's a hobby of mine...
...to one-sidedly force someone into submission
and get them to listen to me.
Yes...
you fight not to win, but to show where you stand.
I'm feeling that for the first time right now.
Because the victor has already been decided.
Loving is losing.
Amou, can we st-
Nomura Fudo.
You are a fool.
But sometimes, that means absolutely nothing.
I will not allow a half-hearted attitude.
Finish it.
Can you tell, Nomura,
what this ringing in my chest is?
I loved you so strongly I wanted to kill you.
This is the end, Nomura.
Be mine.
Nah, I won't.
Count me outta that.
Seems it is over.
Then let me finish our fight as well.
After all, it does not seem as if you and I will be friends.
Besides, I am disappointed at
the crude use of your iliopsoas.
And in a simple punching match,
you have the physical advantage.
But that unsightly display was proof that you have
not mastered the use of your center of balance.
On no account could I abandon someone
learned in the same school of swordsmanship.
To put it briefly...
I will become your teacher and correct you!
Wait, just before you were going on about how
I'd caused someone trouble and you were super mad!
How did that suddenly...
I am not going to let that slide.
Earlier, I said the patience of the Buddha has its limit,
up to three strikes, if you will.
I will be using that interpretation here.
Sure, but...
Oh?
You do not want to make me angry.
Besides...
it benefits us both.
Obedient students will naturally earn leniency.
And you want this from me, yes?
The carrot...
...and the stick!
He has to accept her offer!
The stamp he wanted so badly
has fallen right into his lap!
It's not a bad deal for Nomura.
But...
This is really bad!
Inaba doesn't know...
...that Nomura's not the kind of man
to nod his head in this situation!
I refu-
Ten... sou... metsu...
Masked girls!
Satori's girls?!
Stop, you guys...
You don't need to worry.
Yukino has come.
On school grounds, call me by my title.
I am the school headmaster, after all.
Ten...
Sou...
Metsu!
All of you, disperse.
Oh, well, except for you.
What're you...
Isn't it obvious?
You're expelled.
Expelled?!
Yeah, seems like it.
Isn't that weird?!
Well, nothing I can do.
Not after I went and did all that.
That's not what I mean!
You're a guy who hates being forced into things,
it's weird that you're just accepting it!
I'm used to that stuff.
But...
After all the help you gave me, I went and wasted it.
Are you really okay with this?
Eh, I won't get woken up early
by Onigawara's shouting anymore,
so that's a relief.
She's already riding a bicycle!
Looks like Kyo-bo's doing well at the animal hospital!
At this rate, it looks like she'll be
the first one to fully recover.
Nope, it's me!
Nomura!
I didn't think you'd come all this way to visit me.
Nah, not here to visit you,
more just here to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
Was that rumor true?!
You're getting too worked up!
It's good to see you better, but don't hurt yourself.
Heard you were the one who had it the worst.
Forget about me, Nomura, are you really...
Take care.
Nomura...
Could you leave?
Sorry, but I dunno what expression I should make.
It ain't something you should make
based on the situation.
Put on whatever expression you feel like putting on.
Really?!
What can I say to that sour reaction?
Sure does fit you.
Hey, Nomura.
Who am I to you?
The girl who tried to slice me up in the bath.
Ain't no other.
I see!
You really are funny, Nomura!
Let's play again sometime!
If I feel like it, yeah.
Whoops.
Sorry, go on in.
Um, uh, well, er...
B-but...
No need to worry about me.
I'm on my way out.
Take your time.
U-umm, Miso...
S-Satori!
Huh, is that how it is?
I-I'm sorry, I, I...
It's okay.
Whichever's fine.
Call me what you want.
I'm me, after all.
Please reconsider, school headmaster!
Nomura Fudo's actions were
all to stop Amou's rampage,
they were all to preserve the peace of our academy!
We will guarantee you of that!
Expelling Nomura is a mistake!
No matter what you say,
I cannot reverse Nomura's expulsion.
Never thought you'd be waiting for me.
Really?
I had not heard your answer to my offer to teach you.
Thanks for the offer, but you heard why
I can't be your student, right?
My, that is disappointing.
So you intend to leave this place, like the Empress.
Wait, what does that mean?!
So you haven't heard.
She gathered up her belongings
and has already gone to the airport.
Where are you going?
You know you're not allowed to leave the grounds.
Doesn't apply anymore!
I'm gonna be expelled!
That isn't true.
Until the paperwork is completed,
you are still a student of this academy.
Unless you have a permission slip
stamped by all five Swords,
you are not allowed to leave.
You should hurry if you're going to
run after her, my pupil.
Headin' out?
Why are you here?
'Cause I didn't think you'd leave.
Just came to ask why.
Thanks to that I got forced into being her student.
I just wanna run away from it all.
Wanna run away with me?
Do not get me wrong.
I will do as I wish.
That is all.
That is why you should be yourself and do as you will.
If you have anything you wanna tell them,
I can pass it on.
Let's see.
There was one thing I didn't get to say back then.
Nomura is mine.
Apologize to them for the misinformation.
Especially to those Five Swords.
Hey, now, when the hell did I become yours?
From the moment we met, you have always
been mine, deep within my heart.
Bang.
You're late!
Look at you! Goin' on a date?
Y-you idiot! This is what I normally wear!
Huh.
Finally got to see you in casual wear!
You've got a good eye for fashion.
H-huh, w-well anyway, were you glad you went?
Oh, Amou, huh...
It's fine.
We understand each other well enough now.
I was a little reluctant, but I don't have any regrets.
Hey, so about getting expelled...
You know, I actually...
That's right! About that!
Hold it right there!
Kikakujo!
Rin-san, I am exceedingly disgusted that
you would try to sneak ahead of me!
You idiot! You just took much too long to get ready!
A-anyway! Let me explain about that!
No matter what you say,
I cannot reverse Nomura's expulsion.
Just kidding. Gotcha.
Wha...
Th-the school headmaster was joking?!
I've never heard her joke before!
Well, considering your words,
I will say that was the true circumstances.
In exchange, the two of you need to
tightly hold onto his reins.
So Nomura, you can stay at the Acad...
What?
Nomura Fudo!
Like the other men, you must choose
to either coexist with us here,
or leave this academy!
Make your choice!
Nah, I won't.
We're all here, might as well have some fun.
Welcome back!
Good to have you back!
The view from the outside is pretty great!
Not half bad.
Oh, Aichi Coexistence Academy!
My beautiful alma mater!
I'm back!