Tendou-san, please go out with me.
Yes, gladly.
Load
Load which game?
Load this game?
See, that's him.
Seriously? Him?
Man, I know I shouldn't say this, but...
I seriously can't see him with her.
They ran away again.
Connection lost.
Your opponent
has disconnected.
The match will be terminated.
Damn, I'm jealous.
I wish I had a hot blonde girlfriend.
Hey, idiot, not so loud.
Uehara-kun, I've decided to stop
indiscriminately blowing up normies.
I have no idea what you're talking about,
but I'm glad that this terrorist
has changed his ways.
But man, you're getting an
insane amount of attention.
The horror...
You say that like it's got
nothing to do with you.
This is partly your fault, Uehara-kun.
I know. I'm sorry,
but who could have predicted
that you'd go beyond being friends
and actually start a relationship?
It's a miracle.
Well, I guess.
But Tendou-san likes Uehara-kun...
Or so I thought.
But man, at this point, I have no idea
what to talk to Aguri about anymore.
Did something happen with Aguri-san?
"Did something happen"?
The guy she likes is with Tendou.
The guy she likes is with Tendou-san?
Never mind.
Later.
Morning.
Take your seats.
The guy Aguri-san likes, that is,
Uehara-kun is with Tendou-san...
So he was cheating!
That's why he doesn't know
what to say to Aguri-san!
Of course.
It's easier for them to hang
out together at school
if people believe Tendou-san's dating me.
I think I'll ask her to let me
rescind my confession.
It was a mistake to begin with, anyway.
S-Sorry!
Huh?
Are you okay, Amano-kun?
You look pale.
S-Sorry, Tendou-san.
I'm in a hurry right now.
Um, so...
Later!
I'm sorry, Tendou-san.
Hey, over here.
What do you want?
It's about what happened yesterday.
You know why Tendou-san's
doing this for you, right?
Well, yeah, sure.
I mean, she's doing it for me,
so I should hope so.
All right, then.
That was a godly move, though.
Well, it was spectacular in a sense, but...
You put a huge check on that little
devil who was preying on you.
Little devil?
Never mind, it's nothing!
W-We're enemies, but I don't care
to hurt you more than I need to.
F-Forget about it!
Aguri-san was a great person,
but she wasn't your girlfriend.
That's all.
Right...
Well, yeah, she's not my girlfriend.
I see.
You've moved on that far already, huh?
Of course I have.
She isn't my girlfriend, after all.
Of course!
I like that quick, clean change of heart.
Right...
Damn it!
Die in a fire, Amanocchi.
I'm truly sorry!
Sorry, don't mind me.
I'm 20% just kidding.
That's a pretty low just-kidding ratio.
What do you expect?
I can't be happy-go-lucky after
confirming that Tasuku's cheating.
Uh...
Don't you think it's a bit
of a stretch to decide that
Tasuku's cheating on you just because he
was staring at you with a guilty look?
Why else would a guy look so panicked after
making eye contact with his own girlfriend?
T-True...
Everything's gone downhill
for me ever since I met you.
That hurts.
You say that like I'm jinxed or something.
But Tendou-san and Hoshinomori-san
both met Tasuku through you, basically.
B-But it was Uehara-kun
that egged me on at first.
Although maybe it was to use me
as a cover for his cheating.
I think he sees you as a real friend, yeah.
Maybe he was never a real friend.
Maybe he was just using me.
Damn it, you're so negative! It's annoying!
What do you want to happen
with Tendou-san, then?
Well...
I guess I should tell her honestly
so we can break up properly, huh?
Who knows?
I have no idea.
O-Of course.
I think what's important
is how you feel, though.
Anyway...
Are you really going to let someone else
decide something this important for you?
I'm sorry.
Please forget I asked you for advice.
All right.
Gross! What the heck?
You just noticed?
I didn't taste a thing.
Scary what relationship problems
can do to you, huh?
See you.
Amano-kun contacted me out of the blue.
Why does he want to meet me on the rooftop?
Does it have to do with our relationship?
Stop. Stay calm.
I don't want Amano-kun to see me like this!
I wonder if that confession
was some kind of mistake.
That actually makes more
sense in a lot of ways.
I mean, it's just... weird.
Why would he confess to me?
I'm scared to see Amano-kun.
Sorry to call you on such
short notice, Tendou-san.
Tendou-san?
Um... Do you actually hate me, Tendou-san?
N-No!
Then why won't you face me?
Because...
Wh-Why don't you?
What?
You want to stop dating me, don't you?
I-It's fine.
I understand.
It must have been hell for you
ever since you confessed.
It's not hard to guess
from the face you made.
Th-That was...
Forget it.
You don't have to tell me. I know.
You want to take it back, don't you?
You don't have to worry about my answer.
It wasn't that I was l-lying, but I kind
of got caught in the moment, too.
No, this isn't what I want to say.
Uh, well... first, I'm glad.
About what?
I mean, I'm glad you don't
seem to hate me or anything.
W-Well, of course I don't hate you.
Th-Thank you.
With that said, I have to
ask you something imposing.
This is it.
If it's okay with you, would you
please go on a date with me?
I mean, we can go whenever you're free,
wherever you want to.
Wait, what's going on?
What else? I'm asking you out on a date.
I understand that, but...
We're in a relationship now, right?
Y-You're right that there are going to be
a lot of hardships in this arrangement.
I mean, the attention I get...
Also, I don't stand a chance
against Uehara-kun.
I'm obviously going to lose.
But as a gamer, I think it's wrong to disconnect
before it's clear who the winner is.
Tendou-san?
F-Fine.
Let's go on a date.
Sure.
We're in a relationship.
Of course we should go on a date or two.
It's not like we have a choice.
Okay, well, this comes a little late,
but even though I'm not very mature,
I look forward to our time together.
H-How courteous.
Thank you. I, too, hope for a good, long...
S-Still, you'd better not go overboard.
Things have to be done in order
in a relationship. Got it?
O-Of course.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Y-You'd better.
A-All right, let's disband for today.
Yes, sir!
Get home safe, Tendou-san!
A-Aye.
Wait, this isn't right!
This isn't the relationship I had in mind!
But I can't ask him to change his tone now.
I can't let him get any closer to me...
I'll lose my mind!
So this is the famous facility
frequented by the normies,
Around 1.
O-Okay, let's go in.
Yes, let's.
There are arcade games on the first floor.
Y-You're right.
Shall we leave that to be our main dish?
Then, uh, let's start with...
Um, let's see...
Uh...
Let's just look around and
do whatever seems fun.
Okay?
Right.
It's so fun here, huh?
I-I'm glad to hear that.
It's weird. I've never even gotten
this excited in PE class at school.
I know what you mean.
It must be the difference between
it being mandatory or voluntary.
I'm sure that's part of it, but...
Wh-What shall we do next?
Let's see...
Then again, all the
interesting sport attractions...
Pool
I guess all that's left is the
floor with the arcade games.
There's a huge pool there.
I'm not so sure about that...
Why don't we go check it out for the heck of it?
I'm sure they have rental swimsuits.
I see.
You don't want to see me in a swimsuit, huh?
That's obviously not true!
I was just kidding.
I mean, um, how should I put it...
You shouldn't show the likes of me.
It's in the best interest of humanity
to keep it out of anyone's sight...
I, uh... eh?
You wouldn't want to go on a
date to the pool with me?
I have betrayed humanity.
Thanks for waiting.
Uh...
Wh-What do you think?
Oh, crap! I just lost a life!
Thank you very much.
That's way too weird of a
comment on my swimsuit.
You look good in it!
So much so that I don't want to bother
making pedestrian comments about it!
Would you at least start with a pedestrian
comment like, "You look good in it"?
You look good in it!
Well done.
Stop that!
Gotcha!
That's cold!
Why don't we do that, too?
But if we do, we should
establish some clear rules.
R-Rules, huh?
How about this?
The game is turn-based,
with the attacker only getting to
throw water once in each round!
Switch sides after the attack or after
ten seconds, whichever comes first!
The first one to get
the other's hair wet wins!
Tendou-san's kind of a pain.
Here we go, Amano-kun.
Okay, bring it on.
Damn!
My turn.
I'll use all my time to confuse the enemy.
Now!
Shoot! She baited me.
A rush!
I-I lose.
I win.
Stop it already.
Take this!
Hey, that's not fair!
Maybe we should go to the arcade games now.
Right. Let's do that.
Hey, girl, are you by yourself?
Wanna hang out with us?
Keita!
Uh...
Hey there, kelphead.
What is it, beansprout?
I-I guess I'm going to have to help you out.
Bah, she's with a guy.
Rats.
Look, Tendou-san's there!
I noticed.
Hello, Tendou-san.
H-Hello.
Wait, wait, wait, this is crazy!
I happen to be right here with the person
I'm technically in a relationship with!
Huh?
So you're on a date, right?
I-I can see that, obviously.
So how can you let this situation continue?
I-I suppose I shouldn't have interfered
in a date between two people
who are in a fake relationship.
What do you mean by "fake"?
Are you done?
S-Sorry.
Even given the circumstances...
It's fine.
But why are you here today?
Oh, right.
I had to come since my sister
invited me, but we got separated.
My kid sister's so cute. I'm worried about her.
Why don't we help you look for her?
I'm sure your sister must be
looking for you about now, too.
Th-That would help a lot...
I'm not in a hurry.
I guess I should help.
Keita...
No, I can help by myself.
Amano-kun doesn't need to help
look for your adorable sister.
Wait for me on the floor with
the arcade games, please.
Y-Yes, sir! Standing by, sir!
Very well.
Off you go, Amano... uh... Private Amano!
Yes! Godspeed, sir!
Wh-What is dating, anyway?
All right, Amano-kun,
it's time for the main dish.
So why is Chiaki still with us?
Oh, wow!
Um, it looks like my sister
went home already.
Wait, never mind that!
Do you really understand why she's
bothering to go on a date with you today?
Huh?
You're not getting anything good
out of this day, are you?
You might as well do
something nice for her in return.
What are you trying to say?
I'm giving you a chance, Keita.
A chance to make her happy
in a video game challenge.
Say what?
You just want to game, don't you?
N-Not really...
A game challenge!
That sounds fun!
Four-player fight together!
This game's highly luck-based.
It'll make for a good challenge.
This is my first time playing the arcade
version, but you're going down, Keita.
I'll make you regret choosing this game.
Go!
J-Just giving you a chance.
That's what you get for picking hard
mods when you can't even handle it.
Come on, Amano-kun.
Don't give up.
R-Right.
Not bad, Hoshinomori-san.
I'm going to win.
You're not bad either, Amano-kun.
I'm getting used to the controls now.
Bomb Roulette!
Too bad for you, Keita.
That item has a 50/50 chance of blowing
up either you or everyone besides you.
It's hard to use on this map.
Thanks for the info.
I see the goal!
I'm going to win!
All right, now!
U-Um...
I'm sorry.
It's just that the way
you lost was so hilarious.
So then...
You weren't angry at my patheticness?
Why?
You didn't use the item at the end
of the race in order to win, did you?
Sorry I don't take competition seriously.
Whichever way it went, everyone there
would have enjoyed the game more.
I like that about you.
I admire the way you don't ever go easy on me.
It doesn't sound like you're
complimenting me at all.
If you went easy on me just to let me win,
I don't think I could have enjoyed it.
I just don't know any better
than to take the game seriously.
I know.
But that's exactly what I like
about you, Tendou-san.
By the way, Tendou-san, are you playing
that game that just came out, Fire Tactics?
Yes, of course I am!
That's right, I wanted to talk about it.
Have you gotten far in it?
I'm...