Ikishima-san.
I don't recommend that you pull that gun's trigger.
Huh?
Begging for your life after all this?
Don't you get boring on–
That gun would be mine.
Please take a look at the muzzle.
There's a red mark sticking to it, isn't there?
I just so happened to completely
fill that barrel with lipstick.
I loaded three bullets.
That means that there is a
three-in-six chance of accidental fire.
That makes it fifty-fifty.
Not to mention that you're carrying a one-sided risk–
Nothing, huh?
I was lying.
In truth, I didn’t load a single bullet.
Huh? You serious?
Sheesh...
On that note, even if something as simple as lipstick were clogging the barrel,
the gun would have fired without issue.
I don't give a shit. Come on, let's get on with it.
Ikishima-san, why did you approach me
and propose this gamble?
Huh?
That's obvious.
For the thrill!
It's because the thrill of betting your life feels so good!
I wanna get shocked by the kind of
thrill you don’t just get anywhere!
It's not enough...
Stuff like cash doesn't make me feel anything...
It doesn't matter how much I win or lose.
It doesn't matter...
My left eye is totally blind.
Why do you think that is?
The President took it away from me, as payment for my debt!
Ever since I was a kid I felt out of place...
Victory and praise...
Even fear...
Even the times I really cashed in at the academy...
Not one of them made me
happy from the bottom of my heart.
Now then...
The amount you lost comes to 300,000,000 Yen...
Do you have any way to pay, I wonder?
Huh?! There’s no way I'd have anything like that!
Really though, gambling’s so fucking boring...
It doesn't matter how much my debts pile up,
they don't even make me itch.
I see.
That fearlessness of yours is what
makes up your gambling strength, is it?
For someone like you, rather than money,
I'd like to make you pay with your life, but...
You really don’t strike me as someone
who’d be enamoured by men.
Are you even a fit for a life plan, I wonder...?
Oh, I know...
The other side...
Have you ever seen the dark side of the moon?
Huh?
You haven’t, of course...
Pictures of it do exist, but I’ve never laid eyes on it myself…
Should everyone be deceiving me,
then there just might be an alien base there...
I can't even fully deny such fantastic delusions.
What are you talking ab–
Now that I think about it,
I've also never seen the other side of an eyeball.
I'll buy your left eye for 300,000,000.
What colour does the other side of an eye have?
Where are the nerves and how are they connected?
What about the scent? Does it bleed?
I want to know.
Not through information, but through experience.
This girl...
She doesn't see me as a human being.
Let’s have the removal surgery take place tomorrow.
We have classes to consider, so after school should be fine.
You bitch, you’re fucking nuts.
You fucking pervert!
President!
Heh. Not bad.
I understand now.
Indeed, I've never seen someone gouge out
their own eye out of their own volition.
It wasn’t too interesting, was it?
You’ve done well. You may leave.
You bitch!
I carved my
eye…
e-
eye out!
That's what you said you wanted, right?!
Be happier!
Of course. As I said, I'm satisfied. Good work.
Now I get it...
Pain!
This pain is what true gambling is about!
President, one more time!
Let's gamble one more time!
You don't have any money left, right?
And you’ve already shown me what I wanted to see.
If there’s no obligation, there’s no point.
I've still got another eyeball, right?!
I’ll bet 300,000,000 so let's gamble again!
Midari, join the Student Council.
I'm not fucking interested!
more importantly, gamble with–
If you join the Student Council...
I’ll do you the favour of killing you one day.
It was the best...
The inside of my head went numb...
I finally understood the reason why
people throughout the world gamble.
We hate pain. We’re scared of dying.
That's why it's so good.
Right Yumeko? Isn't it the same for you?
Well, I do wonder...
Don’t go acting all ignorant now!
I told you, right?
I understand because we’re the same...
The President may be the best woman,
but she won't take me on no matter how long I wait.
I expect great things from you, Yumeko!
The second round’s starting.
How do I lay them out?
Unlike the first round where we had no hints,
yumeko and I have reliable, shared information.
The way we laid out our cards during the first round.
Mine?
Ikishima’s?
Yumeko’s?
I just have to reuse one of those line-ups.
I can trust Yumeko
with understanding that these three options are the only ones I can think of.
Still, the problem is...
I only remember Yumeko’s and mine;
they’re the only ones I paid any attention to!
Wait a second…
Isn't it normal to not remember them all?
I'm not someone who can just memorize the order of five cards for three different people.
If Ikishima remembers any cards, wouldn't it
be mine over Yumeko’s, just as a standard?
But Yumeko’s different.
There’s no doubt that
yumeko remembers every single card.
I've decided! I'll reuse Yumeko's card
line-up from the first round!
I'll say it just one more time.
Mary, join the Student Council.
Would it be alright to ask you about something?
What might that be?
You can ask anything.
It's about the livestock system.
Turning humans into livestock is more than cruel...
Why is there a need for it to go this far?
Beautiful, aren’t they?
But even for fish this adorable,
It’s survival of the fittest.
If I were to gather the weakest of the weak,
what do you think would happen?
Even among them, fish of a much weaker class would be born.
And sometimes, even the weak fish may steal away the stronger one’s prey...
Then, what if they were humans?
I want to see that.
It's incredibly intriguing to me.
Huh?
I should tell you in advance.
It is guaranteed that I end this gamble with a draw.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! What’re you saying, huh?
The risks of gambling are the ultimate pleasure.
that's what makes us the same, right?
You want us to kill each other, right?!
‘Kill each other’, eh?
It really is a good thing you
agreed to play only three rounds.
You're joking, right?
Whoever loses, dies. Don’t you want to give it your all, just to feel that risk?
No. As of now,
I don't feel even a sliver of fear.
After all, I have faith in Suzui-san.
Tche! I’m loading six bullets!
If you think you can get a draw, just go ahead and try!
If you say so.
As long as Yumeko catches on to what I’m thinking, then…
Please!
You’re ready, right?
Show them.
Yes!
Five to three! Yumeko won!
She got all five right?!
They don’t even have a sign, so how did she do that...?
There's no way it was a coincidence.
The aim to get them all right and the risk to
get them all wrong are basically adjoined.
She took the risk and just went for the results!
Yu-
me-
ko...
You’re exactly the kind of woman I thought you’d be!
Ikishima-san, I trust that you’ve
mentally prepared yourself?
I’m ready! Aim carefully!
A one-in-two chance...
There's a one-in-two chance that a bullet comes out!
Something like that… it doesn’t even begin to compare.
I...
I'll die!
Nothing, huh?
It would seem so. This is my gun.
The second chamber also has no bullet.
Aren't you afraid of pulling the trigger
and getting in a shot?
You sadistic bitch!
No. After all, it was obvious that this was my own gun.
Huh?
The bullets have their own weight, no?
Six bullets make a difference.
This gun barely weighs a kilogram, correct?
A single bullet should be about fifteen grams.
That much of a difference is enough.
Of course I'd realize.
Yeah, that's right. Of course you'd get it...
Like Hell you can! What kind of senses do you have?!
But... I still realized it.
That's nothing a human could do.
If this goes on, I'll definitely lose...
Yumeko really is amazing!
She completely read my mind!
'Kay. Roger that.
Suzui. We're moving into the third round.
For the next round, I'm 'reusing' again.
We can get a whole line-up!
What is this?
This is cheating, isn't it?!
W-What is this...?
This is cheating! Cheating!
Yeah, yeah. Just line them up already.
Stop messing around! Lives are at stake here!
There's no way–
Suzui!
Line them up already!
If you don't line them up in
ten seconds, I'm killing Yumeko!
10.
9.
8.
You're kidding, right?
If they do something like this, Yumeko's going to...
7.
6.
5.
I have to line them up...
It's no use. I can't think of anything!
If I can't, then...
Great.
Yumeko...
Ikishima-san. You've gone and done
something awfully dull, haven't you?
This is your punishment.
I have loaded two bullets.
You, you know. You're the best!
I had the wrong idea about you!
Someone who gets off on risks like me?
No!
You're on the scheming side!
the same kind of person as the President!
If you're loading two, then so am I!
No way... Why now, of all times...?!
Yumeko. You're ready, right?
Show them.
How boring...
Huh?
Were you aware?
suzui-san is right-handed.
And yet today, for only the first two rounds,
he arranged the cards with his left hand.
And on top of that, the sign on the wave-line card was reversed.
Considering that, only one answer comes to mind.
The projection we've been seeing thus far has been mirrored,
meaning that left and right have been reversed.
Still, the third round shows his right hand.
That being the case, only this round has no such reversal.
With all that in mind,
it's rather odd that Suzui-san managed to match my line-up in the second round.
The arrangement should have been reversed, after all.
But that wasn't the case.
Which would mean...
Our positions... were reversed as well.
We were both looking at a reversed projection.
A trick this worthless should not be able to deceive anyone.
Please keep your ridicule to a minimum, if you would.
Suzui-san's hand was exactly what I expected.
This trick can't be used anymore...
So she's completely gotten the upper hand, huh?
Looks like I couldn't hold a candle to her from the start...
Yumeko...
Congratulations.
It's your loss!
Why...?
They're all wrong?!
I never would've guessed! I never thought
someone like you would ever show up...!
I can't hold back anymore. It's your turn.
Flip those cards, Yumeko!
I've been looking for so long...
For the woman just perfect for me,
someone just like the President...!
Please, dominate me! Just like that guy you string along...
Come on, let me join the fun...
I wanted to get fucked up by a girl just like you!
I'm leaving it all to you, come on!
Dominate me... everything about me!
Hurry up... turn those cards!
I'm begging you, make me cum!
It's you! It can't be anyone else!
Anything else is just masturbating!
If it's not you, I can't feel the same
pleasure as I did that day!
Shit!
Yume...!
Predictable to the end, aren't you?
It was obvious from the start that you intended to lose.
Why else would you agree to
letting Suzui-san be the dealer?
You weren't even certain that we didn't share a 'sign'.
No. Please, wait...
During the first round,
the only reason you even pulled that trigger was your lack of caution for the impending danger.
Well, that much I can let slide...
But this is just plain atrocious.
Wait! Hey! Don't turn any more over!
This trick was made for the purpose of being found out.
Take this wave-line card...
How about adding one more wave?
Should the card happen to be turned upside-down,
no one could tell the difference, no?
There is no conceivable way this was all made to win at gambling.
Then, why?
For you, winning would equal...
Being killed.
Those are the conditions for your victory.
Yumeko missed every single one!
the third round's a draw, too!
That's weird... my plans didn't go through...
How does that add up...?
Why did you load two bullets?
You just had to load none and get the right cards.
Loading two and getting nothing just raises the chance of getting shot...
That's simple.
These guns can load up to six bullets.
by loading two, four empty chambers are left.
That means that a five-point difference would certainly result in a discharge.
By that logic, having all five cards miss would
guarantee that there would be no draw.
I do believe that was your line of thought.
Had you managed to land a correct card or two on a whim,
there would be a chance of me being shot.
Something like this isn't gambling...
It's nothing more than a worthless game
without a lick of victory or intrigue.
Not long ago, you stated that you and I weren't the same, no?
I completely agree.
Gambling is fun because both sides receive a taste of pain, after all.
And yet you try to keep all that pain to yourself?
The answer is not that you enjoy gambling.
You're just someone begging for death!
The kind of person I despise more than anyone.
If you'll allow me to speak plainly...
You piss me off!
What the Hell is that...?
She was aiming for a draw, even though she'd risk dying...
She's fucking nuts!
She's way more than I ever imagined!
She's something that goes above my ideals...
Yumeko...!
You're... my Goddess!
This was a waste of time.
Yumeko! P-Please, wait!
Y-Yume...!
I-It can't be anyone else!
Just one bullet's fine! I'm begging you, give me pain!
Episode 7
I refuse.
What did you just say?
What, couldn't you hear me?
I said that I refuse
to join the Student Council.
Could I ask for a reason?
Was the treatment of livestock too unforgivable?
Did you always have such a strong sense of justice?
I have no obligation to answer that.
Goodbye.
Yumeko... does she seem a little down?
Suzui-san?
Yeah?
Would you like to go to a sweets buffet?
Huh?
The coin will decide who treats the other.
Tails, my treat. Heads, and it's yours. What do you think?
W-Well, um... I'm cutting it close this month, so...
Can't I ask you for this?
I get it! I'm a man, I'll do it!
Thank you so much!
Now, then...
I'm begging you... tails tails tails tails tails...!
Do you mind... if I ask you something?
Huh?
During that gamble...
why did you continue reusing cards despite catching on to that trick?
What? Why do you want to know?
Please,
I simply want to hear an answer.
Um, well...
There wasn't much time left,
and I couldn't think things through...
But I guess, in all honesty...
I thought that you'd realise that I had
no idea how to deal with that situation.
I kept thinking, 'It'd be great if she noticed'...
I'm sorry!
I know I was supposed to give it more thought
since lives were at stake back there, but...!
I see. I do believe I understand.
Tails. Suzui-san, it's your win!
Alright!
I'm safe...
Thank you very much, Suzui-san.
Huh?
Thanks to you, it turned into quite the fun gamble!
'Sense of Justice'?
Being so wrongly sized up
just pisses me off all the more...
The reason's obvious. She doesn't
even see livestock as human beings...
She thinks of them as a lower race!
And that means...
She made a fool out of me!
Don't look down on me...
You'll definitely pay for this!
Long time no see!
Thank you, all of you!
Of course there's a connection...
So,
so,
so
wonderful!
When that time comes...
Episode 8
Love-Dancing Woman
I'll have you form an idol group with me!