Shanna is best girl.
momobami
The Momobami Clan.
As soon as you show weakness, they'll devour you to the bone.
My family was defeated in a conflict within the clan,
momobami
and ever since, our very names have been stripped from us.
How many more generations will suffer as we have?
momobami
I may have heard the answer, but I don't remember it.
For one raised since birth as mere livestock,
the thought never occurs to question one's station.
Momobami
H-hey...
And, so...
Hello there.
I simply couldn't believe that someone would talk to me like that.
I brought presents for all the children,
but I had one left over.
You have beautiful hair. It looks nice on you.
That was my first compliment—no.
That was the first time someone had looked at me like I was anything other than a garden stone.
I didn't know how to express my gratitude, so all I could say was this:
"I will do whatever you say."
Listen to me.
This mark is not engraved on your heart, you know.
Your heart is yours alone.
You mustn't give it up so easily.
For the first time in my life,
I owned something.
She would occasionally visit the estate, and whenever she did,
she looked my way.
Although we didn't speak,
those moments of joy were enough to make my days exciting.
But for some reason, every time I saw her, she appeared more and more gaunt.
And then, one day...
Huh?
She, too, was defeated in a Clan conflict,
and was devoured.
Until she was broken.
My life simply returned to the way it was before.
However,
I had realized that I was livestock.
I'll make them pay for what they did to her.
I'll take back what they stole from me!
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
In my story of wonderful thrills I'll
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo
Live
ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
momobami
I, Batsubami Rei, will win this presidential election,
and rise to the top of Hyakkao Academy—and the Momobami Clan itself.
Rise to the top...
So, revenge against the Momobami Clan was your goal all along?
But could that horrible story really be true...?
That's the clan that brought up our president, y'know.
That's about what I'd expect from them.
Right?
momobami
.......................
Well, Jabami-san.
momobami
.......................
That is my purpose in life, which you won.
momobami
.......................
Will that suffice?
momobami
.......................
Yes. I finally got a chance to see your face.
What will you do?
What do you mean?
Now that you've heard my story, what will you do?
Let's continue the game, of course!
You little...
Wait. Doesn't this mean...
Terano isn't involved in this gamble, is she?
So it would seem.
I was certain she was calling the shots here.
That bitch!
How dare you trick all of us like this?
It was our mistake.
We became too accustomed to having them as a slave to the clan.
After all, we grew up together.
That was our weak point.
Very well.
Let us continue the auction.
W-wait a moment!
Where did all those votes from your "sponsor" come from?
You never once appeared in the rankings, did you?
The rankings are not updated in real time.
Yesterday, a large volume of votes moved to Batsubami-san by way of a gamble.
We were most certainly aware of that.
A gamble?
It was authorized, of course.
The bet was on whether or not Rei could become student council president.
Naturally, all the participants entrusted their votes to Rei in order to win.
Ballot Box
So, to satisfy the terms of the gamble,
Rei used those votes to compete in an election match.
I see.
How very election-like.
No matter what the bet may be,
as long as all players consent, the gamble is legal.
That's fundamental.
But when did they lay the groundwork for this?
Ever since we transferred,
I've seen girls acting strangely flustered.
Particularly those at the bottom of the academy's hierarchy.
I see.
I knew that we couldn't make light of swing votes
at a school with over three thousand students,
but the idea of creating a ballot box never occurred to us.
Nor did the idea of livestock baring its fangs.
The auction is hereby resumed.
current bid
Let us begin with one vote.
Fuck this!
This auction is over!
Calm down, will you?
Erimi-san, how much would we lose if we stepped away right now?
Ten votes.
It's no big deal if we split it among ourselves,
but even if we quit, the auction will keep going.
And if Rei ends up getting all the votes from Yumeko and the rest...
The election will become much more difficult for us.
We've got no choice but to stay, huh.
Indeed.
We have ten votes.
I've just got to bite the bullet.
But, to reclaim what we lost...
We can't compete among ourselves.
The only ones here I can work with are my fellow council members.
We have twenty votes.
current bid
That idiot!
Thirty votes.
Do I see any more?
So this is how it goes.
Nobody here can trust each other.
If they don't want to give up their votes, they need to keep bidding.
Their only chance to back out was when they received the invitation.
Once they started bidding, there was no escape.
current bid
The bid is currently thirty votes.
Any others?
This is a chance to make a huge profit.
L-let's be calm, guys.
We need to work together.
Suzui-san, we would be suspected of collusion if we did that.
What we have to watch out for most of all, right now,
is Batsubami-san ending the auction.
While in possession of all those votes.
Isn't that right?
H-hold on! If this keeps up...
You don't have enough votes to bid, so shut up.
What do we do?
There's no point in raising the bid any more.
But, if we don't keep playing, we won't get our votes back.
We'll lose votes if we compete, too.
In any case, cooperating with them is entirely off the table.
Dammit.
The bid is currently sixty votes.
current bid
Do I see any more?
Damn. I'm out of ammo.
I can't sit idly by and let Batsubami collect more of our votes.
We have 99 votes.
Well, do I see any more?
Then it's sold for 99 votes.
We're playing right into Batsubami-san's hands.
We can't escape even if we try.
We're trapped.
Yes. It's like an antlion's trap.
The more we struggle, the deeper we fall.
That's exactly what this auction is.
Falling deeper as we struggle and bid,
yet falling still if we do nothing.
What a wonderful hell this is.
She's done for.
Hey, Saotome. If this keeps up—
I know.
But even all of us work together, we can't win.
Right. There are more players, in another room.
Is everyone ready?
Let us proceed to the next lot.
Well, it's about time I began.
Huh?
Yumeko, what are you trying to do?
We have 101 votes.
Are you quite sure about this?
Yes!
winning bid
Then it's sold for 101 votes!
Time for the next lot.
current bid
Let us start with one vote.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's happening?
She's finally made her move...
Jabami Yumeko.
But what's the point of doing that?
Sold for 101 votes.
Just what are you planning,
Jabami Yumeko?
Let us move to the next hundred.
current bid
We'll begin with one vote.
Does anyone wish to bid?
It would seem the joker has finally entered play.
Then you knew, and still let them swim free?
Isn't it true that you haven't told any of the other children?
Our votes needed to be centralized, anyway.
This simply moves up my plan.
Is that so?
Did you ever suppose that the joker might win, though?
Even if it may win, it remains the property of the Clan.
Terano, surely you remember.
Whoever wins this presidential election will also become leader of the Clan.
Are you insane?
Part of the clan, yes, but a Batsubami?
Does a joker not flip the status quo on its head?
If not, then it's no fun at all.
Now I'm certain.
With someone like you at the top, both the academy and the clan will fall to ruin.
Pardon the interruption,
but falling to ruin in an fun and amusing manner could be nice too, don't you think?
current bid
Does anyone wish to bid?
Let's move to the next hundred, then.
Do I see any bids?
What is Yumeko trying to do?
Buying time?
But for what?
There's nothing we can do with all these 101-vote bids.
current bid
Sold for 101 votes.
Again?
But something's changed.
Indeed.
The first two bids were placed quickly,
but the second two were delayed.
Is she trying to see how we play it?
Or rather, she's looking to see how we react to her suicide bids.
To be more precise...
Sold for 101 votes!
winning bid
Now, let's proceed to the next hundred.
current bid
I finally got an answer!
Huh? That wasn't Yumeko?
Sold for 101 votes.
Let's move to the next hundred.
We'll begin with one vote.
current bid
Would anyone like to bid?
All right,
I entered my bid right away.
The bid is currently one vote.
current bid
Any others?
Anyone?
Doesn't look like it.
Wrap it up already.
current bid
Sold for one vote.
Oh, wow! I won the lot with just one vote!
This is absurd.
Were they all afraid she'd bid 101 votes again?
Again?
A second time?
current bid
Auctioneer!
Unnecessary delays impede the progression of the game.
I did it!
It can't be.
current bid
Hey, Yumeko. You can't keep all that profit to yourself.
We're all free to bid, Mary-san.
You're right.
Inconceivable.
How can this be? Election monitor!
I suspect foul play.
The participants are colluding with each other!
current bid
Huh?
Actually, I haven't seen anything of the sort.
B... But!
Hey!
Hurry up and move to the next lot.
You never know—I might drop a bid.
I've got enough left.
The next hundred votes.
Get a move on, will you?
This can't be!
current bid
Batsubami-san...
We're not colluding with each other.
We understand each other.
Huh?
For us to win this gamble, we need to not compete among ourselves.
None of us trust each other,
so what do we gain by not competing?
T-there's nothing, obv—
There is something.
"My biggest fear is that you would withdraw from the gamble."
After I mentioned that, our stalemate ended and we started bidding.
Indeed—we made sure you collected enough votes to not turn tail and run.
That confirmed it.
We could have a conversation through the gamble!
I used a series of deliberately useless 101-vote bids.
current bid
Or, to be more precise...
She's looking for an answer.
Indeed! We completely understood each other!
To profit by not competing with each other.
The Momobami Clan members in the other room and I!
Y... you're lying!
current bid
It's sold!
Auctioneer, what's your move?
I don't...
have any... left...
current bid
As Batsubami-sama no longer possesses any votes,
the Hundred Votes Auction is hereby concluded.
This was always a pretty risky gamble.
That's right.
I tried to use gambling to my advantage,
and I was swallowed up once again.
It's over.
I'll return to those empty days...
Hold on.
Hm?
Don't give me that shit!
I don't care what you lost in some gamble.
Stop acting all enlightened just 'cause your little pile of votes got taken away!
The real gambling hasn't even started yet!
She's right.
You still have something, no?
What?
You still have something you can bet.
That life's purpose you showed to me.
Everything you have is right here!
The fun part is about to start.
You think...
this is fun...?
That lady... what the Momobami Clan did to her...
Gambling...
you find it fun?
I find it fun.
That single shining moment when you've bet everything you have.
Gambling is my  life's purpose.
I don't need anything else.
She's crazy.
This woman is insane.
Batsubami-san!
Please, free yourself from gambling for revenge or for other people's sakes.
Bet something you own, for your sake alone.
If you do, I'm sure you'll find gambling fun.
Something... I own...
Your heart is yours alone.
That's right.
She wasn't just a pitiable victim, devoured by the clan.
She had bet everything that she had, pure and simple.
In this gamble.
This mark is not engraved down to my heart.
Yes! My bonds were not tied by anyone else,
but by myself!
Now is the time
Your heart is yours alone.
to break them!
Jabami Yumeko, I accept your challenge.
I'll bet everything I have in this gamble!
Naturally!
In that case, I need to answer your wager by betting everything of mine.
House Jabami.
The name of House Jabami is equivalent to Batsubami Rei's life, valued at three billion yen.
That's wonderful!
Batsubami-san, is that okay with you?
Yes!
Can she just do that?
If Yumeko loses, she'll...
Yumeko'll turn into a Batsubami.
Suzui, you know you can't stop her, don't you?
For this gamble, Batsubami Rei will wager three billion yen,
and Jabami Yumeko will wager the Jabami name.
You're fine with a simple coin toss, right?
It's time!
Let's go all in!
So, you identified with her?
Not that I mind.
That was quite the wait!
Momobami Rikira,
I never thought you  would challenge me.
Let's do this.
I, Komabami Nozomi, will take you on!
The game that will decide our fate is...
Gin rummy!
Rei?
Pick up the brush.
bami
Why?
Someone bound by imagined chains
has now severed those chains.
It was quite fascinating, you know.
bami
What? The Jabami name against three billion?
She really gambled with that?
I mean, it's a shock that she gave up that three billion to begin with.
So, what happened?
Don't tell me Yumeko-senpai lost her own name.
The result was...
Huh?
Yumeko-senpai won?
Oh, that's good to hear.
Hey, Yumeko-senpai!
Oh, dear. I've lost again, haven't I?
Let's go again!
No way. She's lost so much.
She's been like this all day.
I think she might have lost all the votes she won from the auction.
Wait, wait, wait.
Senpai, you can't do this!
In the end, perhaps the joker in this election was Jabami Yumeko all along.
Damn you, Kirari.
You should gamble with me too, Sumeragi-san.
I've retired from the election.
Actually, if you keep losing votes like this, you're going to retire too, Yumeko-senpai.
YEAR 2
HANA CLASS
Oh, dear.
Good morning.
Go... good morning!
Huh?
W-was that...?
This suits her better, doesn't it?
Even invisible chains
cannot keep a person bound forever.
Today is the first day
Episode 12:
The Null Woman
of her very own life.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo, sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii