There are too many mysteries in this tower.
Miss Igarashi is my opponent in this game,
but the Tower of Doors itself is also an opponent.
Don't you understand?
Your life hangs in the balance,
and any wrong move could be suicide.
Instead of living on in total ignorance,
wouldn't you rather learn everything, then die?
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
In my story of wonderful thrills I'll
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo
Live
ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
Chairwoman.
Here are the election match applications that arrived today.
Oh, is something wrong?
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
These votes are moving so slowly.
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
The top ten have accumulated around 40% of all the votes.
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
But the other 60%, about 2,000 votes,
are still totally scattered.
Ah, that is true.
The election still has a long way to go, though!
Suppose so.
And I'm sure the student council are holding onto a bunch of stock votes.
Stock votes?
Having their little birds gather up votes for them, like in cormorant fishing.
And when the time comes...
I see!
Because they don't possess the votes themselves, those won't be reflected in the rankings.
When everything comes down to swing votes...
things are bound to get even stormier.
Hyakkao Academy Middle School
Affiliation
3rd Year, Gerbera Class
Female
Furigana
Full Name
Sayaka
Igarashi
Middle School Report Card
Subject
Japanese
Category
1st Semester
2nd Semester
Final Grade
Grade
Point
Language knowledge, understanding, and technique
Speaking and listening ability
Writing ability
Reading ability
Knowledge and understanding of quantities, diagrams, etc.
Sayaka Igarashi.
Far and away the best grades in our high school, to say nothing of our middle school.
So? Why did you request to meet with me?
To demand I put you on next term's student council, perhaps?
Th-that's not why.
P-please,
Please make me your secretary!
Oh? My secretary?
It's not a bad job,
but surely there are other ways you could put your intellect to use, no?
I saw you gamble the other day.
It was beautiful.
Not only did you, a first year, gamble with the student council president,
but I can't even begin to imagine the time, people, and effort
that were sacrificed just to reach that moment and make those bets.
And then, you were ready to throw it all away in a single move.
I'll never be able to gamble like that for my whole life.
That's why I want be by your side, so I can watch you from up close.
Please, let me stay...
Hm?
Um...
Was it really you who did that?
Ah, I'm sorry!
Why did I say that?
I understand perfectly.
I'll be in touch.
You can leave now.
Why did I say something like that?
How could I have been so rude?
I just don't understand.
I spoke without thinking.
How could I have done that?
You know,
I find you fascinating.
You're hired.
Start coming every day, from now on.
You'll be the student council secretary.
Igarashi, secretary?
Is she serious?
U-um...
Is there a problem?
You only want to be my personal secretary?
O-oh, of course not...
I'm glad.
But...
I see. Then there's no problem, is there?
I look forward to working together, Sayaka.
Everything the president has said to me...
Where I was, and what I felt, when she said it...
I remember it all.
I can keep adding to my collection of beloved memories.
If I can just defeat Yumeko!
This problem can be solved with high school level math.
If:
Then:
The answer is 2.
Win.
That's my only option.
Which does not belong?
The second floor looks the same.
Now I know the structure of the tower.
In Yumeko's best-case scenario, she's still on the third floor.
She might get to the first floor this turn.
But I don't care about where Yumeko is.
I've got to focus on the problem in front of me.
Which does not belong?
Now I can get to the first floor.
If it isn't Miss Igarashi!
You're finally joining us.
Considering how precious each turn is, you sure took your time.
I could never be so leisurely!
Don't let your mind wander!
Each turn is just five minutes.
I need to climb down.
Giving up is out of the question.
She's not here?
Why?
Has she already been here, and she's climbing back up?
That can't be it. Not with the way the tower's built.
More importantly, both flowers are still here. You can't win if you don't take one back.
Could this mean...
I've won?
Even though my turn has started,
Yumeko still isn't here.
She's taking longer than I expected.
Descend and ascend the tower as quickly as possible, without making any errors.
I thought I should focus on that...
I know what the source of my unease is.
There are unresolved mysteries in this tower.
Why did the central door turn into a wall after we'd passed through it?
Why do the numbers on the vertical doors change each turn?
Until now, I've turned a blind eye to those mysteries.
But if it really were possible to move between the first and fifth floors in one turn...
What if Yumeko used the central stairway to get ahead of me?
No... the lilies are still here, so that can't have happened.
The answer for the central door is 120.
I'll open it. I can't go on if I don't confirm this.
Still a wall... So, we can't use the central stairway.
In that case, where is Yumeko?
Struggling with the problems?
No, she'd never be that stumped.
It's Yumeko's turn.
The displays on the outer doors are changing here, too.
They're still showing angles, and the relative positions haven't changed.
It's as if...
Here we go!
Well, I've finally arrived.
Miss Igarashi, you got here quickly.
But it's still just a one-turn difference.
I'll turn the tables, just you wait.
Um... We're supposed to take this flower back to the fifth floor, right?
Is something the matter?
Oh, no, no, no.
My apologies.
It's nothing.
Yes, yes!
Like you said before—let's have a fun gamble.
Yes!
Let's have a fun gamble.
Well, if you'd excuse me.
It's my turn, so I need to solve a problem.
Right. Let's both do our best!
From now on, I won't make a single mistake.
How could I?
Yumeko... I won't let you overtake me.
Two moves to checkmate. The answer is 2.
My courage is coming back to me. I'm totally in the zone.
Right now, I could solve any problem!
I always found it strange.
I despised gambling, yet I longed for a girl who was infatuated by it.
Until now, I just wanted her to look at me, and only me!
But now, from this day on,
I'll be able to become the president's favorite!
You were fast, Sayaka.
You got all the problems right, then?
President...
Miss Igarashi, you got here quickly.
You got all the problems correct, didn't you?
Miss Igarashi, congratulations on reaching the finish line.
Either of us could easily have won.
Such a close game, wasn't it?
I was one misstep away from losing.
Oh, Miss Igarashi, you dropped your lily.
Here you go!
Not that you need it, of course.
Sayaka, open your eyes.
You lost.
I... lost...
That can't be true.
I played perfectly, didn't I?
I considered everything I could think of.
We both messed up on the first turn.
I opened the central door for no reason.
On the following turn, you went on ahead of me.
Left behind, I had two choices available to me.
First, to open the floor hatch labeled "2" and hope you made a mistake.
Second, to open one of the outer doors.
Now, the issue is, which option would I choose?
You realized that the numbers displayed on the outer doors changed after the waiting period, right?
They were clearly showing angles.
They rotated sixty degrees clockwise.
That made me think.
The moon is quite beautiful tonight, isn't it?
I thought there might be a better view from the top of the tower,
so I wanted to get another look at it.
The numbers had rotated twice since we entered.
For the second turn, the moon should have been around "78".
With my heart pounding in anticipation, I opened the door labeled 78.
However, something strange happened.
The moon had suddenly disappeared.
Why did that happen, then?
It's simple.
It wasn't the numbers that had rotated—
it was us.
The Tower of Doors rotates.
Every five-minute waiting period, the tower rotates precisely 60 degrees!
The Tower of Doors rotates only while we're gambling.
How absurd, how lovely,
how terribly romantic!
Heh. I'm glad you like it.
Now, what's so important about the tower's rotation?
Does it have an effect on our game?
Oh, yes, it has every effect!
On the first turn, when I opened the central door, we found a wall.
What could this mean?
Knowing that the tower was rotating, I came up with a theory.
That is, the central door was impassable because its position had changed since we arrived.
And thus, there was one part of the tower that rotated, and one that did not.
Yes, indeed!
There are two  towers.
The outer tower rotates, while the inner tower stays still.
On the first and fifth floors, the inner tower has an opening the size of a door.
On the sixth turn, I climbed to the fifth floor using the central stairway.
That's why I reached the finish line before you, Miss Igarashi.
That's ridiculous!
There's no logic to your story.
Why did you open an outer door?
You had no grounds to assume that would provide a hint.
No... More fundamentally,
even if you knew that the tower was rotating,
that might just be for show, and not affect the game at all.
The president designed this tower, so the possibility is high.
Oh, of course not!
I never thought that could be the case.
Why would she design such a massive feature and not utilize it for the gambling?
You give me too much credit, Sayaka.
Even I'm not that capricious.
Well, you're right that there was no justification for what I did.
But that's just how it is.
Yes, that's right.
This is
gambling, after all.
How?
How can these two understand each other so well?
This brings us to the end of the game.
I'll now declare the results.
The Tower of Doors has been won by Yumeko Jabami.
I know why I lost.
I clung too much to logic.
I didn't want to lose.
I wanted to become the president's favorite.
I focused on the options that I thought were fastest.
On the other hand, Yumeko tried to see the big picture.
As a result, she was able to make the seemingly irrational decision to open one of the outer doors.
Now then, it's time to pay what you owe, Sayaka Igarashi.
This was a message to me from the president.
Choose whichever door you'd like.
It's time to jump.
She finds someone who runs purely on logic boring.
She doesn't want me anymore.
The president is faithful to her own desires.
I'm too different to ever hope to understand the inner workings of her mind.
But that's why I wanted to be by her side.
It's finally here.
This is the first time someone will jump from the the tower that I created.
I'm an ordinary person.
It's only natural I wouldn't draw her attention.
All I can do now is follow the president's wishes, until the very end.
Sayaka, you will die a complete and total stranger to me.
The president and I are total strangers.
Secret!
Quotes
from President
The president and I are total strangers.
President...
I find you
fascinating.
You are my one true love,
President.
W-why!?
We're going to die—the president's going to die!
A safety mat under the flowers...
I've never jumped from such a high spot before!
If I knew it would be this much fun, I'd have done it a long time ago.
But, why?
The Tower of Doors belongs to me, after all.
So I have the right to take part in the first jump, don't I?
S-still,
this is much too dangerous.
Even if there's a safety mat.
If I did get hurt, then I suppose I'd have had it coming.
And, you know what?
I needed to make sure you didn't land in a dangerous position.
Didn't I tell you?
If you found the solution, you would live.
The door you chose at the very end read "5" in Braille.
Since you needed to fall five floors, that door was the solution.
If you chose any other, you'd be dead.
I'd rather not dive off without thinking.
You didn't even realize, did you?
You thought you were going to die anyway,
so you didn't need to think about it.
But somehow, you knew.
Just like always—
you knew something you hadn't even begun to consider.
Why, then?
Because you're irrepressibly rational.
No matter how trivial,
no matter how insignificant it might be,
your mind always seeks after logic.
I find you fascinating.
Sayaka Igarashi.
Now that we're strangers, I'll make you an offer.
Would you become my secretary?
How about it?
We can negotiate the terms.
P-president?
This is crazy.
I don't even know why I was playing that game anymore.
It's beyond my comprehension.
But...
Sayaka.
You don't think you can understand me, don't you?
Same for me.
A girl who reveres logic, who's constrained by logic...
Who, even with death close at hand, banished her emotions and made the logical choice.
I don't understand you at all.
You're my exact opposite.
But that's all right with me.
That's what I like about you.
Yes.
Episode 10
The Logical Woman
I'm at your service.
I can't understand her...
But I still love the president.
She lives in a world beyond reason, beyond anything I could imagine.
That's the world she shows me.
You'll take the job, then?
Wanting to be her favorite is contradictory.
I love her because she keeps me guessing.
I simply want to be by her side.
To stay by her side forever.
Well, one of the two stakes for this gamble has now been resolved—jumping off the tower.
As for the other...
Heh. We had the same thought, in the end.
One's feelings for another person...
can't be outlawed.
Batsubami!
Um... This girl says you helped her too.
Hey.
R-right.
So, we were thinking, and...
That is against the rules.
I'll be honest with ya.
We're in a pickle, aren't we?
Damn it, away games really suck.
We don't even know how many votes the student council has.
You're right. At this rate, Kirari will keep the presidency.
That's true. However...
Isn't it about time for her to make a move?
Terano, that is.
Oh, yeah!
But she can be hard to predict, too.
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class                Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class                Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class                Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Full Name
Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class
Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class
Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class                Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Right, right.
Hyakkao Academy High School
Election Management Committee
Committee Chair
Student Council Presidential
Election Gamble Application
Details about the requested
election match
Location        Year, Class                Full Name                                   Votes Held      Desired Date/Time
Rock-paper-scissors, lotteries.
Gambling is pretty dreary if the votes aren't flowing.
This could be...
—————————————
ABSOLUTE
NEUTRALITY
Nyah hah hah hah...
YEAR 2
HANA CLASS
Man. I didn't know what was gonna happen for a while there,
but I'm glad you're safe, Yumeko.
Thank you, Suzui.
Oh?
Ballot Box
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo, sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
We'll now begin the Hundred Votes Auction.
Nyahahahaha!
Let me off the hook!
What, so you're just handing out votes?
Now, show me!
Your resolve, and the reason why you're here!
Episode 11:
The Woman Who Bears the ✕