Reporting in.
Yesterday, an election match was held involving Yuriko Nishinotoin.
How can this be...? I was playing... perfectly...
Miss Yuriko! Miss Yuriko! Won't someone... please...
Oh, dear. Giving up so soon?
How pathetically fragile.
Nishinotoin was defeated, and all her chips were given to Inbami and Yobami.
It stinks!
This whole thing stinks.
Ａｂｓｏｌｕｔｅ
Ｎｅｕｔｒａｌｉｔｙ
They're testing our absolute neutrality.
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
I'll live, live, live, live a story of wonderful thrills.
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo ikiru ikiru ikiru ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Here we are.
Thank you for taking me, Suzui.
Why did you need to be here?
Look! It's an invitation to gamble.
after school today in Lounge 7.
An election match will be held
To the Esteemed Yumeko Jabami
This is...
I'm very thankful to Kirari for the chance to gamble so often.
Who gave you this letter?
Oh, I just can't wait!
This way.
You're Rei Batsubami, from yesterday.
Why are you here?
I am simply showing these ladies the way.
This is Miss Miri Yobami and Miss Miyo Inbami.
Our blood relation may be distant, but this is the first time we've met, isn't it?
Yumeko Jabami.
That's right. It's nice to meet you.
So they  are Yumeko's relatives.
As you are here as well, that means...
You received this letter too, Yumeko.
Oh, my! We can all gamble together, then.
Please don't go too hard on us.
Miyo, no need to act humble.
This woman is our enemy, you know.
Come now, that won't do, Miri.
We're all members of the Momobami Clan.
Let's swear on our family's pride to have a fair and proper match.
Yes, let's! I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so happy to meet you, Yumeko.
I am too, Miyo.
Your turn, Miri!
I will now take my leave.
Oh, you're finally here.
Runa Yomotsuki?
Why is the head of the Election Management Committee here?
I'm just here to supervise, like any Committee member would.
Though, having said that...
Honestly, I kinda wanted to meet the pair who brought down Yuriko.
I see.
Under the supervision of a neutral  Election Management Committee member,
Yuriko lost the gamble fair and square.
Isn't that right?
Yes... of course.
So if you two are gonna play Yumeko Jabami and I'm the dealer,
I've got to watch you very carefully.
I would like nothing more than for you to do your duty.
It's quite reassuring to have the chairwoman as our dealer.
All right! Let's get started, then.
So... The contestants are Miyo Inbami, Miri Yobami,
and Yumeko Jabami. Any objections?
I'll do it!
I'll enter this election match too.
If those two are okay with it, then that's fine.
I don't mind.
Suzui!
I'm so happy.
Let's savor every moment!
R... right.
There's something fishy about this.
I hope I can help Yumeko just a little by entering.
All right. To keep things fair, how about we play the game I brought with me?
Fine by me.
Okay! The game you four will be playing is...
Nim Zero!
There are four types of cards.
The deck has ten cards each of zeros, ones, twos, and threes, for a total of 40 cards.
Each player is dealt a hand of four cards.
Then, in order, they each play a card.
If you play a card that increases the total sum to more than nine, you lose.
But that would just leave it up to chance, so you'll be placing bets like in poker.
So even if you get a bad hand, you can bluff your way to victory.
We'll play three rounds. The loser will distribute all the votes they bet to the other players.
Um... I only have one vote...
Don't worry! For this election match, you can borrow as many "service chips" from the Committee as you need!
However, each service chip corresponds to 24 hours of service to the Student Council.
Each chip is 24 hours?
You'll have to obey any and all orders during that time. Keep that in mind.
Well, then? Do you agree to those rules?
That is fine by us.
Risk is the key to gambling. I'm so excited!
Do you agree?
I... I agree.
Okay!
Wonderful! I'm sure the girl who brought us all together will be pleased.
Who was it who sent those letters, then?
It was the vice president!
This is one hundred votes.
If you can guess which hand the chip is in, I'll give you these hundred votes.
Now choose, Mary Saotome.
Time to start playing Nim Zero!
We're finally starting.
Let me just say something. I'm in a position of absolute neutrality.
To ensure fairness, I'll be using a new deck for each round.
And I'll deal the cards randomly every time.
First I'll cut 'em a few times...
Suzui!
Huh?
Pick a number between 20 and 30.
U... um... 21.
Okay, I'll stack 21 cards face-down here
and then riffle-shuffle 'em together!
And here's the deck!
Wow! This is a great hand!
Having two zeros in this game is huge.
Now for the betting. Everyone, put one chip in the pot.
Yumeko will go first. Then we'll rotate counterclockwise.
Hm, what to do...
I bet 30 votes.
Huh?
I call.
Wonderful. That's what I like to see.
Small bets are boring.
What we need are bets that could end your life in a second.
Well, Suzui, it's your turn.
If you use 30 service chips, you're giving up 720 hours of your life to the Student Council.
What'll it be?
Damn... I call!
Lovely!
This is a contest.
I just have to win.
That's the best way for me to help Yumeko.
I'd get lonely being the only one to sit the round out.
I'll call as well.
She bet 30 votes without using service chips!?
Things will be more interesting this way... right?
Okay! Now that everyone's bet 30 votes, we'll start the first round of Nim Zero!
Alrighty! Let's start with Yumeko.
Uh, Yumeko? You there? Hello?
R-right! Let's see...
I'll play a three.
Mm, mm. That's a standard play.
Two.
The key to this game is most likely the zeros.
As long as you have a zero to play, you can't lose. So I need to avoid forcing Yumeko to play a zero.
In other words, I need to prevent Miyo and Miri from making the total equal nine.
My two choices are one or three.
Either way, I'm leaving things up to chance.
I play a one.
That's probably the right move, seeing how Miyo didn't back down from betting 30 votes.
I called because I had a good hand.
Miyo must have done the same.
So there's a high chance she doesn't have a three.
I play three.
What?
Zero.
I play... a zero.
I suppose I lose, then.
Huh?
First round complete!
Miyo loses!
Oh, dear. Well, I did all I could.
What? Her hand is way too weak! She clearly should not have stayed in the game.
Well, Miss Yomotsuki? Let's play the next round.
You betcha!
Make sure you give me your cards back. Don't want to let anybody cheat, now.
We're telling you to gamble with us and lose on purpose.
Pets need to listen to their masters' orders.
I know that your brother's a house pet too.
Brother and sister both house pets? That's hilarious.
Leave my brother out of this!
Why, you little!
What? I'm free to treat a house pet however I want.
I am well aware of the rules at this academy.
However, are we not also free to be considerate toward everyone?
Um...
W-why'd you just let her go?
And let go of me, already.
Your lips are much too lovely to be...
What's your problem?
...sullied by harsh words.
You two are victims, in your own way.
Gambling changes people.
It is a ghastly poison.
It's not against the rules for a gamble to be this lopsided?
As long as both parties agree,
and as long as gambling is involved,
they are free to bet whatever they wish.
Of course, this is not a gift.
I have one condition.
If you win and acquire these hundred votes,
we will fight together in this election.
What?
A winner cannot be bound by obligation,
so I will simply follow you around.
That is the compensation I require.
And if I lose?
I have no intention of taking your vote.
However, if you lose, you will join me to fight together.
It's a good deal.
No matter what, the student council presidency will be within your reach.
Now, choose.
Huh?
If you want to ask someone to do something, you should take off that mask!
You really are the spitting image of the president.
But I can tell from your lack of self-confidence that you're a different person.
You're twins, right?
The president is a twin... Play my cards right, and I could make some money off that piece of info.
I--I won't be moved by threats.
You need to choose! Right, or left?
I know what to do.
I refuse.
You can't trust someone you hardly know to have your back.
I don't care who ordered you to do this.
Tell me what you really want!
What I... want...
I don't want... anything.
Oh, is that so?
Then we have nothing further to discuss.
Goodbye.
Hm?
You can't.
This is an offer
you can't refuse.
What?
Hello, Suzui? What do you want?
Saotome! Are you still at school?
Yeah, why?
Please help me!
Yumeko is dying!
What's going on?
I don't know. These Momobami people told me to get someone with a lot of votes.
I'll be right there.
O-ow...
I can't refuse, huh?
Now I get it.
Not bad.
You've got some guts.
Yumeko!
Saotome!
This has got to be poison.
During Yuriko's election match with these two,
she collapsed and was taken to the hospital.
The doctors said her symptoms were the result of some kind of poison.
How very awful. Do you have proof we had anything to do with that?
Although it is true that the Inbami and Yobami family trades are both in pharmaceuticals.
We can save or kill people at will.
Episode 3:
This Woman Should
Not Be Touched
Of course, that alone is not enough to lay the blame on us.
Aha! You two are so candid.
What have you been doing!?
Hnyah?
You knew these girls were dangerous. You Election Management people are supposed to prevent this!
Hmph. Sorry, no can do!
It's 'cause I'm the dealer that my hands are tied.
What?
I was watching carefully, but I didn't see anything suspicious.
That means she was exposed to the poison before coming into this room.
If the dealer starts making calls based on out-of-game activity, that'd damage my absolute neutrality.
Anyway! We need an ambulance, quick!
Oh, would that be wise?
The most difficult and important part of poison treatment
is determining which poison was used.
If that takes too long to find out, the patient might very well end up dead.
In any case.
Now that Ririka is here, let's continue the game.
I do not possess any votes.
I gave them all to Saotome.
Hmm.
In that case, Miss Saotome.
Would you care to join?
If you replace Yumeko in our game and win,
I'll give you this serum.
And if I lose?
I will simply take your votes.
You do have quite a few of them, don't you?
So this was all part of your plan?
If I win this gamble, you're going to have to let me punch you.
I'm gambling, just like you wanted. No big deal, right?
I-I... I am...
Oh, whatever. You can't even decide that for yourself, can you.
Everyone's being real cute today.
Sit down. I'm taking you on.
Oho? How frightening.
Allow me to add some new rules before we begin.
First, this serum will be considered equivalent to one hundred votes.
Second...
Anyone who folds, or causes the card total to break nine,
will prick their finger on these needles.
That... that can't mean...
These needles are coated with the same poison afflicting Yumeko.
I assure you, I won't budge on either of those rules.
Ooh? I see, I see.
So basically, folding is impossible.
Even if you get a bad hand, you can't fold.
So, does everyone agree to those rules?
Stop beating around the bush. I've had enough drivel. Let's get started.
If this is the only way to save Yumeko...
I'll do it!
Nyahaha! You could've hesitated a little.
Ah... how pitiful.
People can't make the decision to wager their own life with no hesitation.
These two aren't even being reckless... they're entranced.
They're swept up in a noble daydream about saving their friend.
That foolishness will simply result in handing over all those votes.
Gambling is a dull distraction. In the end, brute force always wins out.
All you have to do is establish dominance over the rules themselves.
Alright, I'll deal the cards.
Let's do Miyo this time. Pick a number.
Nineteen.
Okay then, nineteen it is.
Time to begin round two!
Are you all mentally prepared?
Your lives are on the line this time, after all!
These people are insane!
To hell with their family business.
To hell with absolute neutrality.
I should never have entered this game... but...
Suzui...
Do you have a moment?
Do exactly as Mary tells you.
If you do...
then you're sure to have a good time.
What was it Yumeko saw?
Let's start betting.
Miri, you go first.
I bet 30 votes.
My hand is... weak!
This lack of zeros is fatal!
If the total reaches nine
I'll lose for sure!
I call.
Suzui. Show me your hand.
Huh?
Uh... okay.
Hey, wait a sec!
What?
That's obviously cheating!
If you make it that obvious, I've got no choice but to stop you.
I-I'm sorry.
Well, that said, I can't stop you from having an accident.
Like dropping your cards by mistake and showing them to everybody.
That works, Suzui.  Show everyone your cards.
Huh? What did you...
I told you to show everyone your cards.
Get a move on. I've got to win.
Saotome is probably not being deceptive.
But she is simply trying to lower the risk that she gets poisoned.
And for that, she needs a scapegoat.
Saotome's goal is to force this boy to lose.
That's not right!
Yumeko told me to do what Saotome said.
I have to believe in Yumeko,
and trust Saotome!
That is
my gamble!
Wow, that's some determination!
Oh, my.
Vice President.
This match...
I can win it!
I raise you 100 votes!
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
If I'm poisoned... we won't have enough antidote!
I raise you 10,000 votes.
Yumeko, I...
Come, let's defeat Miss Saotome together!
Episode 4:
The Connected Women