Please...
please let me handle this!
I will eliminate anyone who poses a threat to you, President.
You mustn't do that.
Being devoured by an invasive species can be quite entertaining.
Yumeko...
Please, please churn up my tank even more!
I don't understand.
What goes through your mind?
President.
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
In my story of wonderful thrills I'll
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo
Live
ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Good morning.
G-good morning!
It's Batsubami!
So cool!
It's time for the Presidential Election News Flash you've all been waiting for!
Nyaha!
You know who I am—
Election Committee Chair Runa Yomotsuki!
We've got a whole bunch of special guests with us today!
Tada!
Election
News Flash
Who will be our next president?!
Vote Holders BEST 10
-----------------------------------------
It's the top ten vote-holders in the election!
Let me introduce them.
Tenth highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
2nd Year, Hana Class
Ryota Suzui
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
Nobody could have predicted his meteoric rise from being a house pet!
2 Votes
4 Votes
7 Votes
9 Votes
11 Votes
13 Votes
/
It's Ryota Suzui, with 13 votes!
Ninth highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
She hasn't made any waves so far,
1st Year, Hana Class
Nozomi Komabami
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
3 Votes
5 Votes
8 Votes
10 Votes
13 Votes
15 Votes
but she's got a solid foothold in the rankings.
/
It's Nozomi Komabami, with 15 votes!
Moving right along.
Eighth highest!
She may have recently lost at Nim Zero,
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
/
.
1st Year, Kikyo Class
Miyo Inbami
Votes Held:
0 Votes
4 Votes
7 Votes
11 Votes
14 Votes
18 Votes
21 Votes
but she's still got a ton of votes left!
/
It's Miyo Inbami, with 21 votes!
Sadly, she couldn't be with us today.
Too bad!
Seventh highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
2nd Year, Botan Class
Ibara Obami
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
/
4 Votes
9 Votes
He grabbed a bunch of votes in the Greater Good Game.
13 Votes
17 Votes
22 Votes
26 Votes
/
Despite his rough demeanor, he's got a sharp mind.
It's Ibara Obami, with 26 votes!
Sixth highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
2nd Year, Hana Class
Yumeko Jabami
She's steadily climbing the ranks.
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
11 Votes
22 Votes
33 Votes
43 Votes
54 Votes
65 Votes
It's the rising star of this election,
/
Yumeko Jabami, with 65 votes!
Fifth highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
Same as before, he's got the most votes of all the guys.
2nd Year, Hana Class
Rin Obami
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
12 Votes
24 Votes
36 Votes
48 Votes
60 Votes
72 Votes
/
It's Rin Obami, with 72 votes!
Fourth highest!
She's high up in the rankings, as always.
What do you think she's plotting with the vice president?
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
2nd Year, Hana Class
Mary Saotome
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
17 Votes
34 Votes
51 Votes
67 Votes
84 Votes
101 Votes
It's Mary Saotome, with 101 votes!
/
Third highest!
This YourTube idol recently put on a stunning performance.
She's on her way to fame and fortune!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
2nd Year, Momo Class
Yumemi Yumemite
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
22 Votes
43 Votes
65 Votes
86 Votes
108 Votes
129 Votes
It's Yumemi Yumemite, with 129 votes!
/
---------------------------------------------------
2nd Year, Momo Class
Yumemi Yumemite
Votes Held:        129 Votes
Yumemi!
Second highest!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
She really is something special.
3rd Year, Tsubaki Class
Terano Totobami
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
28 Votes
56 Votes
84 Votes
112 Votes
140 Votes
168 Votes
She's been busy racking up votes.
/
It's Terano Totobami, with 168 votes!
And, last but not least, the highest vote-holder is none other than...
Our very own Student Council President Kirari Momobami, with 255 votes!
ELECTION
NEWS FLASH
3rd Year, Hana Class
Kirari Momobami
/
.
Votes Held:
0 Votes
43 Votes
85 Votes
128 Votes
170 Votes
213 Votes
255 Votes
/
That's our president for you! Since the election began, nobody's topped her!
Well, how about we ask our guests what they're excited about in the rest of the election?
Okay!
Let's start with Terano.
Got anything to tell us?
I have no need for excitement.
When this election is over,
I will be the one with the greatest number of votes.
That is all.
Oooh! A spine-chilling declaration if ever I heard one!
Now, who should go next...
Oh, it's gotta be her!
Yumeko!
Oh?
Mind saying a few words?
Let me think...
I just want to have fun gambling with everyone...
But since so much is at stake,
I'd love to participate in the greatest of gambles,
on this, the greatest of stages,
with the greatest of opponents.
A game to make temperatures burn and blood seethe—
the ultimate gamble!
Would you join me...
Madame President?
Oh, dear!
We have a gambling invitation right before our eyes!
Hyako Academy Student
Council Presidential Election
Student Council
Presidential Election
News Flash
I take it you were not satisfied by our tarot game the other day?
I'm ready to go whenever you like, even right this minute.
Well, that might—
Shut up!
I won't stand for this, Yumeko Jabami!
You are a pestilence.
You drag people into dangerous games for the sake of your own pleasure.
H-hey...
Sayaka, you know this is a live broadcast, right?
Yumeko Jabami, you're a—
Please Stand By
You seduced them all with your wicked wiles,
distracting them until they lost.
You drive people mad,
rob them of their dignity—
you're a pestilence that brings people to ruin!
A pestilence...
Is that what I am?
Yumeko...
President!
This girl needs to be thrown out...
expelled from Hyakkao Academy.
This girl...
is going to destroy your beloved academy!
Throw her out?
Throw her out, you say?
Sayaka...
You've always had a way of striking right at the heart of an issue.
But do you remember what I said?
You mustn't do that.
I don't have to tell you, of all people, the reason why.
President...
If I'm able to beat Miss Jabami at gambling,
if I can slay the woman who aims to wrong you,
might you look upon me favorably?
Well, I would be impressed if you were able to do that.
Miss Jabami, please gamble with me.
Oh, my, you're inviting me right away?
Yes, I'd love to!
However, this will be separate from the election.
We won't be betting votes.
Wh...
We'll bet our lives.
Are you quite serious about this?
Miss Jabami...
Isn't that what you really want?
To risk your life in an all-consuming gamble.
You're right.
I'm very grateful for your offer.
However...
I humbly refuse.
Wh—why?!
Surely you don't have cold feet.
Miss Igarashi, please be calm.
Please Stand By
If you want to have a truly stimulating gamble,
that won't be enough.
Betting your life?
That's boring.
Aren't there things more important to you than your life?
For instance, memories, status,
or your feelings.
All that constitutes your relationship with Miss Kirari Momobami.
If you lost them, you would become total strangers.
Only then could you say you'd bet everything.
How interesting!
You'll let me be the dealer, won't you?
Thank you very much!
In that case, what shall I bet?
If we're talking "everything" ,
then I suppose I should promise to never gamble again if I lose.
Of course.
Anything else, and the stakes would be unbalanced.
You're fine with this arrangement, aren't you, Sayaka?
Yes.
There's a game I've been wanting to play.
The stage was built for precisely this occasion.
A tower that represents both beginnings and endings in the journey of life.
It's called...
The Tower of Doors.
Never thought Sayaka would end up playing against Yumeko.
It's no fair!
If it's not for the election,
I wanna play with Yumeko too!
I've never seen Igarashi participate in gambling before.
I highly doubt she's capable of beating Yumeko Jabami.
Oh, really? You don't know about Sayaka?
Right, you're a grade above us.
Right, right.
Back in middle school, everyone knew her as a genius.
She was always getting first at the national college mock exams.
Jumping over the high schoolers—makes ya sick.
But, you know what?
I never thought of her as a genius.
English
Grammar
and Usage
All she did from morning 'til night was study.
It was obviously way more than she needed to.
So, why did she do it?
She didn't have a particular goal.
All she wanted was to be "number one".
What's so clever about that?
Studying, really?
That's hard to imagine, these days.
Oh, really? I don't think she's all that different.
She's just changed her target.
She's still got that crazy drive to be number one.
Wonderful!
You weren't exaggerating when you said it was built just for gambling.
It hardly seems to have any practical use.
Right?
I'm rather fond of it, too.
Now, then.
We're going to move up from the first to the fifth floor.
There are two ways to ascend in this tower.
The first is to use those ladders.
The other is...
the central stairway.
This certainly is a long staircsae.
Really makes me feel my lack of stamina.
The are no doorways to other floors along the central stairway.
You can only go to the top floor.
Don't worry, though.
We can start the game as soon as we arrive.
This is the fifth floor.
It's the top floor of the tower,
and where the game begins.
The rules of the Tower of Doors are exquisitely simple.
Move down to the first floor,
then climb back to the fifth floor.
The first person to accomplish this wins.
You will retrieve one of the lilies on the first floor as proof.
Every five minutes, you will each have the chance to open one door.
In order to open and progress through a door,
you will need to solve the problem it displays.
You will take turns answering.
After a five-minute wait, there will be five minutes for Yumeko's turn,
then five minutes for Sayaka's turn, and repeat.
The doors in the walls lead to the outside, right?
Yes, that's right.
The floor hatches lead to ladders to lower floors, then.
However, unlike the central stairway, they do not go all the way down to the first floor.
The central door leads to the way we just came.
Those are all the rules.
I cannot afford to lose.
I'm the one who meets with the president.
I take the biggest volume of her orders.
I manage her schedule and entertain her guests.
I arrange her meals and receive her words of gratitude.
If I lose this game, I lose all of that.
If I lose...
I'll be reduced to a mere passerby.
I'll be longing for her from far, far away.
Surely you didn't think that would be allowed, did you?
If you're able to keep longing for me,
then you'll remain connected.
It would mean you hadn't bet everything.
So, how about we raise the stakes?
Since we're playing in a tower, after all...
Let's have the loser jump through this door.
If you find the solution, then you survive.
If not, you die.
You'll need to bring your wisdom to bear,
and stake your life on it.
P-president...
Only then will you take on the ultimate risk for this bet.
My relationship with a corpse cannot be restored.
We'll remain total strangers...
forever.
Sayaka, you would die a complete and utter stranger to me.
What do you think?
I see! I'm perfectly fine with that.
Sayaka? What about you?
Are you dissatisfied?
You can tell me anything.
No, I could never be dissatisfied with one of your decisions, President.
I just...
can't wait!
The greatest of gambles and the greatest of risks—just as you desire.
I wonder how you'll look upon me when I've won, President!
I exist solely for the president's sake.
I've given up everything in service to her.
If she still won't look my way,
that simply means I did not try hard enough.
I will achieve victory here,
Episode 9:
The Woman By Her Side
and become the president's favorite!
Before we start,
let me give you a hint.
In the Tower of Doors, the correct answer may not always be the solution.
Only she who truly understands the meaning of the answer
will be able to reach the solution.
Now, then...
Let us begin.
These are...
the problems.
First, the five-minute waiting period.
Try your best to solve the problems.
In this game, whoever reaches the first floor and returns to the fifth floor faster wins.
If what the president said is true,
then the outside doors are just decorations.
We can move down through the floor hatches.
So, what about the central door?
Using the central stairway,
we can complete the game in two turns.
That would certainly be the fastest way.
But... it can't be that simple.
The screens changed!
This sequence...
Five minutes have elapsed.
Time for Yumeko's turn.
Going first can be a real puzzle.
There's so much I still don't know.
That said,
this one is altogether too important to pass up.
It can't hurt to try it out.
We had the same thought.
Whoa! W-what was that?
I've finished answering.
Huh? What did you do?
Did you really just...
I wouldn't want you to look at my answer and copy it, would I?
So I devised a small countermeasure!
This little bitch!
You're too tense, Sayaka.
You won't stand for Yumeko taking the lead, will you?
It'll open.
This is the only possible answer, after all.
Wha... th... a wall!?
Did she get the answer wrong?
No, the door definitely opened.
That means...
Too bad.
That answer may open the door, but it won't allow you to move forward.
It was correct, but it wasn't the solution.
I see.
That was my mistake, then.
Yumeko's turn is over.
The door will now close.
Sayaka, it's your turn.
I knew from first glance what these numbers were.
They're hexadecimal numbers.
Numbers 0 through 9, then letters A through F are used to express numbers 0 to 15.
It's a form of notation used in computer data storage.
The numbers on the outside doors were a hint.
This is what the screens displayed during the wait.
In decimal notation, that'd be this.
This room is circular,
and the doors were displaying angles.
When the displays on each door changed,
the numbers simply shifted.
The angles between each door didn't change.
That confirmed that the alphanumerics displayed were hexadecimals.
We need to answer using the numbers 0 through 9,
so converting to base-10 notation was right.
What I don't know is the "solution".
On Yumeko's turn, the central door displayed "12c".
In decimal notation, that's 300.
Oh?
Is that what you've chosen?
When the waiting period ended,
the numbers on each door changed.
However, the numbers on the floor hatches haven't changed at all.
The number 1 is the same in both hexadecimal and decimal.
Is it not right to be unchanging?
Just as it is with my loyalty to you.
What if I'm wrong that consistency is the solution?
Could that be too simple?
What's Yumeko doing?
What kind of expression is that?
Is she sneering at me for being on the verge of making a mistake?
I'm scared.
If I lose, my relationship with the president...
Sayaka?
You don't have much time left.
I recommend you answer quickly.
President...
Why am I getting spooked?
I'm playing a game.
I have to trust in my reasoning and ability.
All I can do is believe in myself and bet it all!
It opened!
Dear me.
Looks like I've been left behind.
I did it!
Well done.
The door will close when your turn is over.
You should start climbing.
Alright!
What is that?
This is...
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
This ladder connects the fifth floor and the third floor.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
TL Note:
This is too
blurry to read.
There were two floor hatches.
The number on the door I didn't choose was... two.
The unchanging displays showed the solution,
but they also showed the number of floors they spanned.
There's no way for me to access this ladder from the fourth floor.
It's impenetrable.
If Yumeko makes no mistakes for the rest of the game,
then I'll lose, no matter what.
No!
I'll be forgotten by the president.
That's the one thing I can't allow.
Please, God,
don't let Yumeko choose the door that says "2".
I'm acting like a fool!
Praying to a higher power other than the president... Hoping Yumeko would make a mistake, no less!
It's not as if I've lost all hope of winning.
We still don't know the structure of the lower floors.
I've got to give it my all!
If I mess up because I'm preoccupied with what she's doing, then I'm finished.
Focus.
I need to focus.
I can do that.
Yumeko, it's your turn.
The displays have changed again, I see.
When the waiting period ends, the displays on the outer doors change.
Clockwise, and systematically.
A simple hint about hexadecimal notation.
And a distraction.
Only the floor hatches actually lead up or down.
That's why Miss Igarashi chose a floor hatch.
It's exceptionally logical.
Despite limited time and information,
she made the most rational decision.
Do you keep Miss Igarashi by your side because of her extreme rationality?
Oh, of course not!
Rationality, really?
That's not what's good about her.
Or perhaps I should say that it can't be expressed using that word.
I'm sure you'll come to understand what I mean by the time this game is over.
I'm looking forward to that.
Well, then!
You've chosen an outside door, I see.
Let me warn you—
there are no passageways or ramps along the outside of the tower.
It's just as you saw from outside.
This is hardly a rational choice.
There are too many mysteries in this tower.
Miss Igarashi is my opponent in this game,
but the Tower of Doors is an opponent as well.
I want to taste every nook and cranny.
You've so generously prepared this tower for us.
If I don't relish its smell, roll my tongue over it, and suck it dry,
then I can't truly say I enjoyed it!
You understand that your life is on the line, don't you? That one wrong move could mean death?
Instead of living on in ignorance,
wouldn't you rather die, knowing everything?
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo, sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
How magnificent, how lovely!
I won't make any mistakes from now on.
It's bizarre. There's no logic to what you're saying.
It's still very possible.
Jump.
I need to report my adoration,
Episode 10:
The Logical Woman
President.