This match...
...is one we can win!
I raise by 100 votes!
Oho!
I see.
She's betting high to try to save her friend.
Even I didn't think things would go so perfectly.
I call.
Call.
Gambling is a dull distraction.
The best way to make people do what you want is brute force.
That's right, Miyo.
Everyone's bet 100 votes. Time to start playing!
Round 2 begins now!
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
I'll live, live, live, live a story of wonderful thrills.
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo ikiru ikiru ikiru ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Fingers... eyes... lips.
When we were little, it started as our secret language.
When we were separated into different Houses, it was no longer just a game.
If our families found out, we would face much worse than a scolding.
We were completely closed off.
This was the only way we could speak freely with one another.
Episode 4:
The Connected Women
Miri and Miyo really creep me out.
Always talking about something, but never saying a word.
Yet, that skill of theirs is particularly useful when it comes to gambling.
Torn apart by a succession struggle, those two sisters devised a perfect method
of secret communication.
Undetectable to ordinary eyes.
I'm quite jealous that they stayed so close after being separated.
Rin-san, we're plenty close.
Between those sisters and Jabami Yumeko...
I wonder who Lady Luck will smile on.
Rei, what do you think?
I find gambling rather baffling, I'm afraid.
You never change, do you.
He deliberately showed everyone his hand.
A weak hand, with no zeros at that.
How foolish can one be?
Three, two, zero, zero.
Indeed. Three, three, two, zero.
We both have zeros.
Our numbers are on the high side,
But we can win.
Okay, let's start with Miri-chan!
If I can bring the total to nine on my turn, Suzui loses.
I can open up by playing a three.
Then you can adjust as needed, Miyo.
That's a good idea...
...but I have a better one.
Three.
Our first play is a three. Now for Suzui-kun!
R... r-right.
Suzui.
Play a one.
Why?
Just do as I say. So we can win.
All right. In that case...
Is that really what you want, Suzui-san?
Huh?
Saotome-san is trying to sacrifice you
to make sure she wins.
That's why she made you reveal your hand.
But, you know, if you lose this game...
You will die.
Ah! How about this?
If you ignore what Saotome-san tells you,
I'll provide you some antidote as a gift.
Enough for both you and Yumeko-san.
What?
You're risking your life because you want to save her, right?
With this antidote, you could save Yumeko-san,
and you would no longer need to risk your life.
Nor would you need to play along with the cajolery of that coward.
You have no choice but to betray her.
There's nothing to fret about.
Come, let's bring down Saotome-san together.
No, thank you.
What?
No, thank you!
Oh, does it bother you to condemn Saotome-san to death?
In that case, I can provide enough for her...
No!
Your way would be no fun at all.
And that's not what Yumeko wanted.
It's not what I want!
Second card is a one! The total is four!
How disappointing.
You have him well trained, I see.
Allow me to enlighten you, then.
The weak are exploited until the day they die.
Oh! Third card is a two. The total is six!
We're almost in the danger zone!
Why a two?
Due to our turn order, we are unable to make Saotome lose this round.
Let's first focus on killing Suzui.
With the total at six,
if Saotome plays a one or a three, then Suzui will lose.
The only way to avoid it is by playing a two.
But Saotome's best play is a three, since it raises the total the most for Miri's turn.
Well, Saotome-san?
It's your turn.
What were you saying, just now?
Who was being exploited?
The weak, you see—
Tell me.
Who are "the weak", here?
Why, you two, of course.
You've been forced to bet your precious 100 votes,
and your life is in danger.
And we are only betting the antidote we already have.
That's the difference between the strong and the weak.
That may be right.
But you've got one thing wrong.
We're in Hyakkao Academy. The weak ones here...
Are you two!
Fourth card is a two! The total is eight!
Drat. She's lucky.
We'd have won if I had a one.
I have no choice.
Fifth card is a zero! The total is eight!
Sixth card is a one! The total is nine!
Seventh card is a zero! The total is nine!
Next is Mary-chan! If you don't have a zero, you're dead!
Miri has no more zeros.
If I have to take another turn...
I'll lose.
Obviously I have one.
Eighth card is a zero, and the total is nine!
Next up is Miri-chan.
Got any zeros?
I don't.
W-we did it! We won!
Round 2, complete!
Youbami Miri loses, and must pay 33 votes to the winners!
Since we can't split up one serum,
if that's how you want to pay,
how about you give 'em one each?
This is the antidote?
Great! This will do fine.
But there's something else you need to do, right?
The loser needs to prick their finger on these needles.
Miyo, I don't have any serums left.
Please bring me one.
How do you use this thing? I need to give it to Yumeko soon...
Huh? What are you guys talking about?
You still have another round of Nim Zero to play.
You can't spend your chips while the game is still going on.
No using those serums until we're all finished!
You can't...
No arguing with the dealer.
It will be a little while before the poison takes effect.
Finishing this game will be a piece of cake.
More importantly, we need to teach Saotome a lesson.
About the taste of death.
Yes.
Now, it's time for round 3!
I'll deal the cards.
Right now, we have two serums.
If either Saotome or I lose this round...
We'll lose our serum and get poisoned.
We won't have enough antidote!
Suzui?
Right.
This foolishness, again? He must have a death wish.
Let's start the betting!
Suzui-kun, how about it?
I bet five votes.
I raise you 300 votes.
300 votes!?
Is she trying to make up for her prior loss?
I raise...
10,000 votes.
What?
Nyahahaha!
10,000 votes?
That's 240,000 hours, you know! You'll grow old at this school!
Is there a problem?
Not at all, not at all!
But if you lose...
You'll have to retire from the presidential election.
Miyo.
Saotome's goal is clear. She wants us to fold.
Now that she has a serum, she has no reason to play.
What should we do?
She's obviously bluffing.
You're right. If her hand were strong, she'd have made a reasonable bet.
In any case, this girl called us weak. She needs to die.
I call.
Dumbass.
Call.
Okay! The bet is 10,000 votes. Let's begin!
Suzui, play a two.
How?
How can she make that face?
The total is two!
Saotome should be paralyzed with fear by our absolute force.
She's a total weakling!
Second card is a three! The total is five!
How can this be?
Only the strong can smile like that.
Third card is a two! The total is seven!
Even if Saotome had a great hand, Suzui definitely didn't.
She should be in deep water right now.
Miyo.
It's bad that she played a two.
With the total at seven, I can only play a one.
If I do, Suzui will play a one, and then it'll be your turn with the total at nine.
If only I had a two, we'd have a chance.
Didn't I tell you?
You two are the weaklings here.
We should have been able to win.
Miri and I have good hands. We both have zeros.
With our bond, we should have been able to win!
And yet, we're the ones under threat right now.
It's all her fault!
Oh? Did you finally notice?
Did you not realize something was up?
Were you not at all suspicious
about the way the dealer dealt the cards?
What do you mean?
She used a Gilbreath shuffle. It's a famous trick.
You take a deck of cards that alternate between the four suits, spades, hearts, clubs, and diamonds.
You cut it at random, and pile up as many cards as you like in a stack.
Then you riffle shuffle the two stacks.
The deck order appears to be random,
but in reality, every four cards will contain one of each suit.
It's the same as this game, right?
That means that the 16 cards we were randomly dealt contained precisely four cards of each number.
Why do you think I made Suzui reveal his cards?
Because I wanted to win for myself?
Too bad!
Wrong answer!
By knowing Suzui's cards and adding them to my own, I determined what the other eight cards were.
In other words, I knew exactly which cards you two had.
You guys never had a chance.
What?
Suzui, do you notice anything
if you add my cards to yours?
Huh? Um...
Th... there's a trend?
Right. We have all the twos.
So the choices you two could make were limited, which made you easier to predict.
Our victory was certain from the moment the cards were dealt.
Although, Suzui... You believed in me.
Thank you.
Y... you too.
Anyway, you guys were from the Momobami Clan? That's really something.
Betting 10,000 votes on a gamble you can't even win...
I sure don't have the guts for that.
Ahahaha! Ahahaha!
Ridiculous!
A special shuffle...
Doesn't that mean the dealer planned the whole thing?
It's unfair. What happened to neutrality?
Huh? You still don't get it, do you.
You're saying I wasn't neutral?
You better watch your mouth, child.
I was dealing the same way the whole time.
It's your fault for not noticing, Miyo-chan.
In any case, I used this dealing method to prevent uneven distributions.
It wasn't to put anyone at a disadvantage.
W-well, that said, anyone who doesn't notice has a pretty lethal disadvantage!
You put so much faith in poisons and brute force that you neglected your powers of observation.
You said that I planned the whole thing,
but isn't it natural that the dealer gets to set the rules?
It's my job to set the rules so that anyone can win!
Even if some players use a weapon like poison.
You can't use brute force to stop someone from wanting to gamble.
Anyone can take anyone down.
That's my absolute neutrality!
That school rule is the cornerstone of my existence!
If someone dies in this election...
I'll just create a game that even dead people can win.
Now, let's get back to the game.
Miri-chan, it's your turn.
Oh? You don't look so good.
Poison getting to you?
Hurry up and play a card.
Let's get this over with.
Fourth card is a one, and the total is eight! It's time for the climax!
I can't... There's nothing I can do.
But...!
A one! The total is nine!
Zero! The total is nine!
Alright, Miri-chan! Your turn!
If I play this, Miyo will...
Onee-chan will lose!
Miri,
play a three.
What?
If one of us has to lose, better you than me.
After all, I'm more talented.
It would be a bigger problem if I were eliminated from the election.
Come on. Lose, Miri.
Lose, and prick your finger on the needles. Let's get this over with.
Do you not want my antidote?
Hurry up, Miri.
Three! The total is twelve! Youbami Miri loses!
What's up, Miri-chan?
Oh, dear. She fainted. What should we do about the punishment?
Does it matter? The game is over, anyway.
What are you doing?
I don't want to hear "But you were merciful then!" next time.
Saotome Mary.
Next time, I will  kill you.
Bring it on.
She's looking a lot better.
She should be all right now.
If you two hadn't won, she would have been in serious danger.
The antidote seems to be working properly.
Honestly, I was worried about that.
I will now take my leave.
Thank you, Batsubami-san!
We didn't know how to apply the serum by ourselves.
Oh, I am simply glad I could be of service.
Goodbye.
Saotome!
Thank you so much!
You're the reason Yumeko is still alive!
I-it's not like I could just let her die!
Y-yeah.
You really were a godsend.
Yumeko never ceases to amaze.
You know what she said after she collapsed from the poison?
She told me that if I called you there, I'd have a good time.
Huh?
Even though her life was in danger, Yumeko just...
This is Yumeko we're talking about. She must have noticed the Gilbreath shuffle.
But she didn't know that I'd notice,
or that I could use that to win.
Yumeko is willing to bet even her own life.
She's a genuine gambling addict.
But I'm not like that.
If anyone's worthy of being student council president at this insane academy...
Hey, everybody!
Thanks so much for coming to see me today!
I've been waiting for this, Yumemi!
Did you all bring your votes?
Yes!
Come again soon!
Showdown.
The table has two, two, ace, seven, six.
Joumaru-sama has two pair, aces and twos.
Momobami-sama has two pair with aces and twos as well, but her kicker card is a nine.
Because her kicker is higher, Momobami-sama wins.
I couldn't come close. It was like I was under your thumb from start to finish.
Oh, my! Good luck!
This is so dull, Sayaka.
Why do you partake of this nonsense?
Is there no one who will sincerely try to take me out?
Well, how about us?
Oh?
Finally, a bit of fun.
Hey! Batsubami-san!
Hi there. Thanks for the other day.
Suzui-san?
Yumeko's gotten a lot better.
Thank you so much.
Th... that's quite alright...
U-um...!
I'm, um... the one you rescued yesterday.
Ah... you're...
You were like a prince...
Oh, no, I didn't mean!
Thank you very much.
Please take this, if you like!
Cats.
I only thought of the Momobami Clan as frightening,
but you're a kind person, Batsubami.
Second Year
Flower Class
Jabami
Yumeko
The election is going to get even
more heated from now on.
And I know you're going to jump right into the thick of it.
Yumeko, I don't know if you can hear me,
but you're the only one I'm going to tell this to.
I'll only say it once.
Yumeko, I...
will become student council president.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
What does singing mean to you?
This is simply exquisite!
Things have finally gotten interesting.
Let's have some fun.
The Woman Who Changes
Episode 5: