I call it—
the Finger-Cutting Guillotine!
Guillotine?
Each player places a finger in the hole.
Then we take turns cutting one of these twenty strings.
All it takes is one string.
Just one, and the blade falls... along with your finger.
You don't know which string will be the one.
Whoever pulls their finger out first loses.
It's a game of chicken to see who can leave their finger under the blade the longest.
Whoever gets cold feet first loses the gamble!
Well?
You're free to accept or refuse.
It's no use.
Yumeko can't resist.
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
I'll live, live, live, live a story of wonderful thrills.
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo ikiru ikiru ikiru ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Hyakkao Private Academy.
The school prides itself on 122 years of tradition and class.
However, at this prestigious academy, there is an absolute hierarchy of students.
Your rank is not determined by grades or athleticism
but by your gambling prowess alone.
Most students here are caught up in
the cycle of winning, losing, and betting.
But I met someone motivated
not by money or fame,
but by her desire to gamble itself.
Yumeko Jabami.
Ever since she arrived,
the gambling at Hyakkao Academy has become noticeably crazier.
And right now, at this very moment,
Yumeko is letting herself be consumed by her gambling lust.
Miss Jabami. Miss Ikishima.
What is your response?
You have the right to step away from this gamble.
My game is so horrifying that they can't even speak, I suppose.
Hah...
You did spook me.
My mind went blank there, too.
Oh? Well, if you're that frightened, I guess I have no choice...
The game will—
Let's do it!
I've been waiting for something like this!
Extreme in its simplicity,
yet extreme in its strategy!
I've always wanted a gamble like this.
The rules are great, but this machine is really something.
It'll slice you apart as soon as you slip up, no bones about it.
Ouch!
Oh, wow.
I just brushed it and it drew blood.
Heh heh heh. You've got this thing damn sharp!
Yumeko, look at this!
Isn't it wonderful, Suzui?
Uh... yeah...
Hey, look at me!
What?
What's with these two?
Could they really not be afraid of my game?
That's unthinkable.
Losing a precious body part is a fundamental human fear.
Very well. Let us begin, then.
Yes.
Let's do it.
With your affirmative responses, I officially recognize this gamble.
Can you even call this gambling?
It doesn't matter how lucky or smart you are. All you need for this game is reckless abandon!
But neither Yumeko nor Ikishima will pull their fingers out so easily.
H-hey, wait!
What?
You're the one who rigged up this guillotine.
So don't you know which string is connected?
If so, it's hardly a fair game.
If you don't have anything useful to say, keep your mouth shut, kid.
Kid...
The string that connects to the blade
can easily be changed by opening this box.
I'll have the dealer switch the string.
That will satisfy you, no?
Understood!
But now,
it will be possible for you to determine who wins.
Miss Mushibami.
Yes?
Rest assured, that is altogether unthinkable.
The Election Management Committee
takes pride in its absolute neutrality.
If not, our jobs would be meaningless.
Please do not insult the Election Management Committee.
Hmph.
How very trustworthy.
Well, fine then. Let's get started.
Right!
What's the point of being so careful when nobody's gonna sneak a peek anyway?
Peeking takes away half the fun!
Ah, it's been so long since I've felt this...
Heh. It's unusual for Yumeko to flaunt her distaste for someone.
Not that I blame her.
Do you understand the situation?
In just a few short minutes,
one of our fingers could be dancing in the air.
Preparations are complete. Please come in, everyone.
Ahaha!
I'm getting tired of waiting. Let's go!
Miss Yamata?
Yes?
Did you do a thorough inspection?
We won't be able to fully enjoy the game if you didn't.
I most certainly did!
If the blade falls from that height,
amputation will be unavoidable if it hits.
Heh heh heh. Just what I wanted.
They're going to start.
Now, then, everybody.
Place your chips, and insert your fingers into the guillotine.
That blade is the real deal.
Does Mushibami really know what she's doing?
Does she know how dangerous—
I apologize for the wait.
The Finger-Cutting Guillotine game will now begin!
Let me go first!
You don't mind, do you? I can't hold back anymore.
Sure. Go ahead.
Our odds are the same, no matter who cuts.
Then, Miss Ikishima, the first move is yours.
Heh heh. Thanks for that!
Which one'll be it?
Our fingers are riding on this one little moment—I've gotta think it through.
This is too much, Yumeko.
I'm so happy I get to gamble with you again.
Is that so.
Heh. Don't worry!
We're on equal footing now. Same one-in-20 chance to lose a finger for both of us!
Let's feel the pain together!
Ah!
Huh.
Guess it wouldn't happen on the first try.
I see. That was a miss.
You may take your finger out at any time, if you wish to surrender.
It appears no one is surrendering.
In that case, Miss Yumeko Jabami, the second move is yours.
Okay.
There are quite a few strings left, but I shouldn't be careless.
The moment of truth could come at any time.
Heh. True that.
You'll really pay for it if you're looking away when it happens.
Right?
Well, here goes.
Oooh!
Guess that wasn't it.
Even though the odds are still low,
these girls cut their strings without any fuss.
I've heard about Yumeko Jabami already, but...
You—your name was Midari Ikishima, correct?
Huh?
Why did you join this game?
Why?
I heard that you lost to Yumeko Jabami once already.
So, the reason you'd risk a finger just to gamble with Yumeko Jabami...
Could it be revenge, by any chance?
Revenge...
What?
Yeah... it might just be.
She got me so hot and bothered...
Now I need some real bullying.
Huh?
Hey, it's your turn!
I'm not gonna complain, even if you snip the right one.
You're the one who made this all happen, after all!
No need to remind me.
Dammit! Another miss, huh!
Haha! This is the best!
Heh. It sure is great.
The danger steadily increasing as we take our turns—it's sublime.
What, you think so too, Yumeko?
We really do have a connection!
Oh, I don't know about that.
I see.
At the very least, these girls have the nerve to keep up the bravado.
I wonder how much longer they can hold out.
I'll be watching from a position of safety!
Because this guillotine, you see,
is designed to never really amputate anything!
There's an iron plate in this platform that stops the blade from falling all the way down.
Best of all, it's not actually cheating!
The blade still falls—even if it doesn't reach our fingers.
The dealer must have noticed when she inspected the machine,
but since it's not a violation of the rules, she'll stay quiet.
That bluster about "absolute neutrality" seems to be real.
And as a result, there's no way either of you can win.
If they can hold out until the blade falls, they might manage a tie.
But can either of them withstand a terror that increases turn by turn?
Damn, I got it wrong.
Yumeko, please! Cut the right one, already.
I will do my best.
I wonder which one it is.
But if I may, why do you possess this wonderful device?
You must have had it before coming here.
Oh... good point. What do you normally use this thing for?
Torture.
That is the Mushibami family business, passed down through the generations.
Torture? In this day and age?
It is needed in every age.
When you hook someone up to this little beauty and start cutting the strings one by one,
They'll happily tell you whatever you want to know.
I wonder how long you two will last.
Wow. There really is a job for everything, isn't there.
But that makes things easier.
Huh?
If someone did to you what you do to others as your profession...
You'd have no right to complain.
Especially since you proposed this gamble yourself.
It's not that you don't mind losing a finger,
But that you have accepted it as a potential necessity.
Isn't that right?
What?
Miss Yamata?
Yes?
You did remove it for us, right?
Hm?
Oh, most certainly! That is my job, after all.
I'm glad to hear that.
Now I can enjoy the game with no reservations.
Hey, whatcha talking about? Don't leave me hanging.
Huh?
Now, let's continue.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
What did she say just now?
"Did you remove it?"
This device has no removable parts...
What?
Ugh! Another miss, huh!
But that's real interesting.
Torturing people is your job?
That means you'd have no qualms giving my finger...
giving me the torment I need!
I love it! It's your turn, Mushibami!
Give it to me already!
It's all you! Go ahead!
Go, go!
Go! Go!
Go!
Episode 1:
The Women Who Went
All In Again
Let's go all in!
That was turn six, Miss Mushibami. A miss.
God, I can't get enough of this!
The more strings we cut, the bigger the thrill!
Quite right.
My wager was 100% safe.
I should be watching my opponents tremble in fear from a position of safety.
That's how it's supposed to be!
How did they find out about the iron plate?
Or is it just a bluff?
Is the dealer in on it?
I have no way of erasing these doubts!
I came up with this game in the first place.
If I ask a question, I'll be admitting to my trick.
I've been hoisted by my own petard!
Ikishima, it's your turn.
What?
Oh, right, yeah.
H-here I go, okay.
Ahahaha! Ahahaha!
I get it now, Yumeko!
I had it wrong before. We all take on the same risk!
This is so much fun, isn't it!
Indeed!
I don't understand. How can you keep cutting the strings?
You could have had the game canceled as soon as you saw my trick!
Even if you were just bluffing!
The reason you didn't must be that...
You truly want to do this...?
Your turn, Miss Mushibami.
Hey, don't tease us too much...
W-what's with them?
Come on!
It's your turn!
What's the matter with this school?
Huh?
Hey, what's your deal all of a sudden?
Why would you start crying about the game you came up with?
Mushibami...
That's why I wanted to stop this.
This gamble would never faze either of them.
Particularly Yumeko.
Because she's...
A gambling junkie.
The world runs on ups and downs.
appu daun wa yo no tsune
I won't let one bad hand get to me.
kuzu hiitatte doujinai
What's essential is to have a strong mind.
kanjin nano strong na mind
To outwit, and survive.
dashinuite survive
I'm either gonna end up in Heaven or Hell.
ikitsuku saki wa heaven or hell
There's just one rule in this world: the winner is always right.
kono sekai no ruuru tatta hitotsu shousha koso ga seigi
A woman's got to have guts.
onna wa dokyou
Gotta keep him tantalized.
jiresaseru no aitsu wo
I'll do anything I can; I'm the compulsive gambling queen!
yareru koto nandatte yaru atashi wa kakegurui no kuiin
Think you know my game; you doubt me.
omitoshi sore you doubt me
Make your read and let's showdown!
yomikitte rettsu showdown
Deal with the devil! I'll see through you and make you mine
deal with the devil misukashite atashi no mono ni suru
from a single hair to your everything.
anata no kami no ippon made zenbu
A million dollars? I say "raise". You're trembling, boy.
a million dollars? I'd say raise furueteruwayo bouya
I won't let you off this ride.
orosase wa shinai wa
Deal with the devil! Ah, the excitement.
deal with the devil uhhhnn koufun
I can't get enough of these thrills.
tamaranai wa suriru
I won't let anyone touch this money.
dare nimo sawarasenai kono money
A million dollars? I'd say "raise".
Come on, grit your teeth, start shaking, get excited! My heart.
saa come on kakugo kimete furue takabure my heart
You really look like you want it; you're still a baby.
hoshigaru you jane mada beibii
I won't lose to anyone.
dare nimo makenai
Let me feel it. Love me, honey.
kanjisasete love me honey
I plan to dissolve the Student Council.
I will resign the Student Council presidency and hold an election.
Are... are you insane?
Holding an election
after the council has suffered a string of defeats by Yumeko Jabami...
You would all but abandon your position of power.
It is sheer folly!
Heh heh.
Yuriko, you think you're in a position to criticize?
How amusing.
Sheer folly...
is precisely my intent.
What?
Hyakkao Academy...
is an aquarium of my own construction.
A beautifully cyclical, closed-off world based on the law of survival of the fittest.
But someone has appeared who is distorting its beauty.
They are devouring my aquarium.
This person has brought enlightenment even to those who know nothing but the tank.
If left to fester, the distortion will grow,
and may become too large to handle.
So I want to stir up the waters even more.
They're here.
If you would excuse me.
As everyone has arrived, I have shown them to this chamber.
Stop right there. We are in the middle of an important meeting.
Regular students are not allowed here without permission.
Yes. I am well aware of the rules.
Who... who are you?
It would not do for someone of my status to be introduced first.
Allow me to introduce:
Miss Terano and Miss Yumi of House Totobami.
Miss Sumika of House Warakubami.
Miss Miyo of House Inbami.
Miss Milaslava of House Honebami.
Miss Nozomi of House Komabami.
Master Rin and Master Ibara of House Obami.
Miss Miri of House Yobami.
And finally, Miss Erimi of House Mushibami.
I am here to facilitate the school lives
of these ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Rei Batsubami.
P-president, who are these people...?
This will be a pain to explain...
Could you please explain it instead?
These ladies and gentlemen are all relatives of Kirari Momobami, the head of the main family.
Their extended family consists of House Momobami and its many branch families.
All of them have
come to this academy as representatives of their families.
"Momobami" also refers to the "Hundred Devourers".
Together, they form the Momobami Clan.
Welcome to my academy. And...
To a presidential election in which only the fittest survive.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
The Student Council Presidential Election has begun!
They all have "bami" in their surnames.
I have always...
...utterly despised you!
Episode 2:
The Women of the Momobami Clan