Student Council presidential election news flash!
Student
Council
Presidential
Election
News
Flash
#1
Student
Council
Presidential
Election
News
Flash
#1
Election Management Committee
I'm Yomotsuki Runa, head of the Election Management Committee, and I'll be your host!
Hyakkao Academy Student
Council Presidential Election
Now, it's been one week since the start of the election.
I want to make the remaining time even more fun and exciting.
So I'm going to tell everyone which folks have the most votes right now!
Vote Holders
Number 10!
This girl beat a bunch of Student Council members right after transferring.
2nd Year, Hana Class
Jabami Yumeko
She's this election's rising star.
It's Jabami Yumeko, with 13 votes!
Number 9!
This girl might look aloof, but she's working hard to earn votes.
2nd Year, Rindo Class
Honebami Miroslava
What could her true intentions be?
It's Honebami Miroslava, with 17 votes!
Number 8!
The election had just begun when this girl trounced the head of the Traditional Culture Club, Nishinotouin Yuriko.
1st Year, Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
It's Inbami Miyo, with 21 votes!
Number 7!
This girl might put a curse on you if you gamble with her!
This girl might put a curse on you if you gambled with her!
3rd Year, Momo Class
Warakubami Sumika
It's Warakubami Sumika, with 40 votes!
Number 6!
Could this girl be the next first-year president after our current one?
1st Year, Hana Class
Sumeragi Itsuki
It's Sumeragi Itsuki, with 50 votes!
Number 5!
This guy's got the most votes of any boy at Hyakkao Academy!
2nd Year, Botan Class
Obami Rin
Doesn't seem like he wants anyone to start swooning, though!
It's Obami Rin, with 62 votes!
Number 4!
This girl was just a housepet not so long ago.
2nd Year, Hana Class
Saotome Mary
I can't believe she's doing so well!
It's Saotome Mary, with 101 votes!
Number 3!
This YourTube idol aims for the
stars, even in this election!
2nd Year, Momo Class
Yumemi Yumemite
Share videos, not votes!
It's Yumemite Yumemi, with 109 votes!
Number 2!
Not many high schoolers can radiate this much poise!
3rd Year, Tsubaki Class
Totobami Terano
I wouldn't be surprised if she's the one who ends up in the president's chair!
It's Totobami Terano, with 133 votes!
Wow, they've all got abilities far beyond their age!
But there's one student who's leaps and bounds ahead of all the top players at Hyakkao Academy, and that's...
N-n-n-number 1!
No introductions necessary!
It's our very own President,
3rd Year, Hana Class
Momobami Kirari
Momobami Kirari,
with 216 votes!
Oh, boy! Who else but our President could collect that many votes in one week?
Election Management
Committee Chair
Well, the only one with anything real to lose in this election is the current president, after all.
So I get why she's fighting so hard.
That said, the election is far from over!
Every student still has a chance to win!
That's all for this broadcast, folks!
Until next time!
Adieu!
The broadcast is over.
Thank you for watching.
Ugh, I'm bored.
Why won't the president give me any service chips?
I told her I'll do as many hours of service as it takes.
Hey, give me a few of your votes...
The ever-dreaming YourTube idol
with twinkling stars in her eyes
Yumemite Yumemi
The ever-dreaming YourTube idol
with twinkling stars in her eyes
Yumemite Yumemi
I've always shared
your content
because I wanted
to support you.
But, to be honest, I
want to be your
only "favorite".
Please, smile.
Your starlight is radiant...
I've always shared
your content
because I wanted
to support you.
But, to be honest, I
want to be your
only "favorite".
Please, smile.
Your starlight is radiant...
"Is this a dream?" I pinched my cheek.
"Touch me and find out." I could tell from the warmth of her skin that this was real.
I'm as cute as always!
These are pretty good.
Aren't they?
Yeah, but
don't you want to be a Hollywood actress?
What?
Like that girl.
You think you've got time to screw around in a bikini?
It's okay!
The fastest way to become an actress is to switch over after you've mastered being an idol.
You really think so?
Not that I care,
but Japanese actresses in Hollywood aren't all that rare these days.
You telling me they were idols before?
Of course they weren't.
They got there 'cause they had real skills.
All this idol crap... isn't it just an excuse for your lack of talent?
You're so harsh, Midari-chan.
Maybe it's how you show affection.
I'll do my best, step by step.
Okay, then. Enough about that.
Let's get this "Beautification Chair-for-a-Day" meeting over with.
Right!
What is that eyepatch bitch's problem!?
She's a total fucking amateur,
but she's talking shit like she knows anything!
You really think anything your little brain could think up would be news to me?
Yumemi...
I need more votes.
I don't want to be student council president.
But if I'm going to hold influence over the next president,
I need more votes.
They need to be convinced I was the one who put them in power.
I will  win an Academy Award.
For that to happen, I need this academy's support.
But we've taken all the votes from your fan club already.
If you want to obtain more
will you start gambling?
That, or I find more fans... right?
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
I'll live, live, live, live a story of wonderful thrills.
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo ikiru ikiru ikiru ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
What's so funny?
You could tell? I'm impressed.
Heh. It's just Kirari, from yesterday.
All in.
Hmm?
Fold.
All in.
Unbelievable.
Going all in pre-flop, five times in a row...
Now I see what you're after.
You can make your opponent fold right away by going all in,
but all you get is the ante.
You're risking everything for a low return.
It's a foolish strategy, no question.
However, because you have far more chips, we can only bet against your all in by going all in ourselves.
In other words, you're forcing us into sudden death in every round we play.
This isn't about poker skills at all. It's about whether or not you can do that kind of gambling.
Isn't that right, Kirari?
Things have finally gotten interesting.
Let's have some fun, shall we?
How very like you.
All right. If that's how it is, then...
I'm out.
What?
I'm not obligated to play along with this kind of game.
At least, for the time being.
Let's go, Sumika.
That surprised face she made.
Even Kirari can be cute sometimes.
Priceless!
Her strength is in the way she lets her emotions show.
Hm? What do you mean?
What's most important to her is whether or not she's being amused.
She craves pleasure at all times.
That's why she's unreadable.
If you think so, that must be right.
Well, I understand Kirari now.
It's time to investigate the other one.
Yumeko-chan!
I missed you so much!
Yumemite-san!
Itsuki-chan, Suzui-kun, long time no see.
R-right...
Long time no see...
What brings you here today?
Well! You see, I have a favor to ask you, Yumeko-chan...
I want to bring the Dreaming Creaming Sisterz back together!
Yumemite-san, um...
Please! It's just for one day!
One day?
It'll be a one-day-only reunion concert.
We'll gather tons of fans and gamble with them!
It'll be lots of fun!
We'll split the winnings equally, of course.
Please, please, please, please, please!
That does sound fun.
I'll make out way better with Yumeko there too.
After all, more people means more votes to get.
What?
No way!
Hey, look!
There's no way!
Seriously?
But why?
No way, no way, no way!
I'm a huge fan of her!
Why's she here?
Hello, everyone.
That's the Hollywood actress...
Natari...
Episode 5:
The Woman Who Changes
Kawaru.
Uh... who might that be?
What? She's a super famous actress!
Oh, my.
Um!
I'm a huge fan!
I own all the TV shows and movies you've appeared in!
Your work in Mistral  made me shiver.
And in the dark heroine you played in Gamble Hole  was totally groundbreaking.
I want to become an actress like you!
You're...
You're Yumemite Yumemi-san, an idol, right?
No way... Natari Kawaru knows about me...
It's like a dream come true...
Please don't misunderstand.
I don't know anything about Japanese idols,
nor do I care to learn.
But this is an election.
I've researched my rivals.
Rivals?
Hold on a minute!
"Rivals"...
Are you participating in the election?
Most certainly.
W-wait, wait, wait,
I've never heard about a Hollywood actress at this academy!
Well, of course you haven't.
Let me introduce myself.
My real name is Warakubami Sumika,
and I'm a member of the Momobami Clan.
I came to this school to gamble.
Natari Kawaru is from the Momobami Clan?
That... that can't be...
Hold on.
According to that news flash this morning,
the one with the most votes right now is the president.
Second place was Totobami Terano...
If she wanted to avoid competing with members of her Clan for votes...
Then the reason Natari Kawaru is in this classroom is...
Let's play a game.
Jabami Yumeko.
O-okay.
But is that quite all right?
I only have thirteen votes.
Perhaps if you were to gamble with someone in possession of more...
No need to worry about that.
Those people won't last long, anyway.
In the end, only members of the Clan will be competing for supremacy.
You think so?
I'm not surprised. She's a Hollywood actress.
For her, a lowly high school idol might as well not even exist.
Maybe I should just be grateful she noticed me at all.
But...
I'm going to walk the red carpet someday.
Which means Natari Kawaru is an opponent I must defeat!
What kind of game shall we play?
As for me, I'd prefer poker—
A performing arts showdown.
How about that?
And please allow me to join in.
Oh!
You'll have a chance to win my 109 votes,
and we'd be competing on your turf.
Surely you won't refuse.
Then let's have...
Jabami Yumeko and Yumemite Yumemi against me.
With that one condition, I'll accept.
Those 109 votes are certainly alluring, but they're not worth the extra effort.
I'd like to decide this in a single match.
I'm fine with that.
How much is she going to denigrate me?
Just you wait.
I'll make you pay attention to me.
I accept that condition!
It's decided, then.
Yumemite
Yumemi-sama
Waiting Room
What on Earth do you think you're doing?
A three-part performance contest in front of a hundred people?
Let's Win T  is Thing!
h
You're up against a world-famous actress.
Competing against her in performing arts is just suicide!
Yumemite-senpai,
you don't actually care whether you win or lose, do you?
Your real goal is just to have the performing arts showdown with Natari Kawaru.
Ah...
You're totally right.
Yumemi...
I can't help it... I'm her fan.
She's who I admire, who I want to be... I want to catch up to her someday.
I'd be honored just to gamble with her,
and a performing arts contest is beyond my wildest dreams.
But, you know...
I'd feel even better if I won!
Ehe...
I have no intention of losing.
The election match you've all been waiting for is finally here!
We have with us today
Election Management Committee Chair Yomotsuki to explain the rules.
Good to be here! Nyaha!
What's this? I hear that all 100 tickets sold out instantly!
Of course they did!
After all, you'll get to see the  Natari Kawaru gamble.
Oh, but not to worry. No matter how famous she might be, I'm still absolutely neutral!
I did get her autograph, but I'm not gonna play favorites.
I'm so jealous!
All right then, let's get right to it!
This is Active Station—or "A-Stay" for short.
Let's start!
I'm two pair.
What's that?
♪A two pair maiden♪
What's happening?
Look at that.
♪In love, you can only go all in once♪
Why?
The vice president's trailing her.
Hey, you. I told you not to follow me!
You've been shadowing me all day!
But we promised!
We'll fight this election together.
I'm keeping my promise.
Please keep yours.
Just how dumb are you?
You put Yumeko's life in danger and forced me to play your game.
Now you're telling me to keep a promise?
I can't make a promise with a dumbass who can't even think for herself!
I can't accept you as an partner and start gambling alongside you.
At least, not the way you are right now.
The resolve to pick out one hopeful path from uncertain and unlimited possibilities with your own volition.
That resolve is the core of gambling.
I'm going to have you gamble.
If you win, I'll accept you as my partner.
♪I'm two pair (I'm two pair)♪
♪A two pair maiden♪
♪In love, you can only go all in once.♪
That was Dreaming Creaming Sisterz with "Two Pair no Otome".
It was very cute!
That was quite the compelling opening act for today's A-Stay.
Now, let's turn our attention to Chairwoman Yomotsuki for another explanation of the rules!
Yooouuu got it!
Today's game is a three-round performance contest!
Round 1 was designed by The Dreaming Creaming Sisterz,
DreCreSisterz
Round 2 by Natari Kawaru,
Natari Kawaru
and Round 3 by the Election Management Committee.
Election Committee
Obviously we need the game to be fair, but other than that, anything goes!
Whoever wins this match gets all of their opponents' votes!
There are quite a few ways to interpret "performance".
We need to pick a type of performance that we can beat Natari Kawaru at.
It's got to be singing.
As a professional singer,
you intend to fight her on your own turf, then.
With no regard for your pride.
Yes!
I will  win, no matter what it might take.
Heh heh. Your confidence in victory is truly admirable.
After all, if it turns out our opponent is thinking the same thing...
If both of you are certain you'll win, one of you will turn out to be a liar.
The risk of your determination being exposed as a lie... it's simply exquisite!
I'll gladly help any way I can!
No matter what methods you use, Yumemite-san!
I can't lose at singing. I've earned my fair share of experience, too.
Just like you have!
Now, our next piece will be performed by Natari Kawaru-san.
She will be singing "Amazing Grace".
She's in a league of her own, isn't she.
Beautiful...
She's clearly been trained as a singer.
A long time ago, my teacher told me something.
"Perfect technique is the foundation."
"Real talent is built on top of it."
Huh?
Why did I remember that just now?
That was Natari Kawaru-san with
"Amazing Grace".
Braaavoooooooohoooooooo!
Now, everyone. You can now use your smartphones to start voting!
That was wonderful, Natari-san!
Song is performance.
I truly believe that.
A song conveys the feelings trapped inside music and lyrics.
Songs enchant us with worlds of our own creation.
During a performance, there is no Natari Kawaru.
The actress only contaminates the stage with her presence. All that is needed is the role.
By the way...
What does singing mean to you two?
Is it simply a way to show yourself off with a pleasant song and a cute little dance?
Natari's singing was definitely several times better than I'd imagined
it was beautiful.
Even so...
Counting
Votes
even so, I  will win this contest.
This hardly seems fair...
No matter what, Yumemi needs to win!
But, I'm surprised Yumeko would be okay with this...
I bought 'em off!
I bribed 80 of the 100 audience members to make sure they vote for me.
Bribed
ibed
Bribe
Bribed
ribed
So even if worse comes to worst, I'll still cruise to victory!
Counting
Votes
We've just finished counting all the votes!
Counting
Complete
All righty, let's announce the results!
The result of round one, "Natural Voice", is...
Natari       Kawaru
DreCre             SisterZ
Dreaming Creaming Sisterz got 8 votes, and Natari Kawaru got 92!
Wow, that's a difference of 84 votes!
Natari Kawaru absolutely crushed it!
You're really...
underestimating actresses.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
I will fight by myself.
If you don't pass, there's no doubt...
You were acting, all that time?
Episode 6:
The Hollywood Star
A-amazing!