These ladies and gentlemen are relatives of Kirari Momobami, the head of the main family.
They are all part of the Momobami Clan.
Episode 2:
The Women of the
Momobami Clan
The Momobami Clan?
What on Earth...
I'd like to thank you all for coming.
Drop the act.
You announced that the winner of this election would become the next Momobami leader.
So it's only natural that the adults would panic and send us as representatives.
After inheriting the Momobami leadership,
you quickly gained control over this academy as its student council president.
You centralized control over the debts and liabilities of both current and former students,
exerting immense influence on the political and economic establishment.
And so, the student council presidency at Hyakkao Academy has become a position of tremendous power.
Control of this academy is control of the nation.
And yet, you have chosen to abandon your position and wager it in an election.
To make the winner leader of the clan, no less.
Essentially, this election is a winner-take-all succession struggle
for both Hyakkao Academy and the Momobami Clan.
Do you find it amusing, Kirari? Watching the branch families run helter-skelter.
Yes, very much so.
I expected as much.
You take what we all wanted with ease,
and then you relinquish it and provide us with a chance to acquire it.
I have always...
utterly despised you!
What's going on?
I can't keep up. What's happening with the election? Momobami? Clan leadership?
The one thing of which I'm certain is that our president's academy is on the verge of being devoured by this family!
This is completely impermissible! All sense of order at the school will be lost!
She is correct, President. Please reconsider.
Well, if that's the president's decision, so be it.
No use trying to stop her now. But if this interferes with my career, I'll crush her.
Sounds like fun! I'll give it a shot.
Not that any of these girls will be better than Yumeko, that is.
There's even a grade schooler!
This is ridiculous.
Calm yourself, Yuriko.
If you want to preserve the status quo, then all you need to do is win.
Sayaka, the same goes for you.
The opportunity is yours.
After all, everyone has an equal shot in this election,
and it will be decided with gambling alone.
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love, hate, love, hate.
suki kirai suki kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
I'll live, live, live, live a story of wonderful thrills.
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo ikiru ikiru ikiru ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Announcing the Student Council Presidential Election
To All Students / Hyakkao Academy High School Division
Runa Yomotsuki, Election Management Committee Chair
Hello, everybody!
I'm the head of the Election Management Committee, Runa Yomotsuki!
Did you catch our poster?
I'm going to explain everything now, so pay attention!
If you miss something, you might end up a house pet!
First and foremost! You won't be using ballots in this election.
You can only make and receive votes through gambling.
Any other exchange of votes is prohibited.
So, no need to announce your candidacy!
Everyone is a voter, and everyone is a candidate! The election will run for 30 days.
You can gamble however and with whomever you like.
The person with the most votes at the end of those 30 days is the winner!
Well, everybody? Are you ready?
From this moment onward, the student council presidential election has begun!
These are the chips, huh.
Looks like a toy.
I see; each student gets one chip.
Each chip is a single vote, and you can gamble with them.
It's too bad we can't buy them with money.
Right when I'd managed to save some up.
Manyuda transfered me everything he owed.
Take a look!
Three billion yen!?
I was all excited about using this money to gamble to my heart's content.
Even with all that money, you haven't changed a bit, Yumeko.
Hey, you shouldn't be flaunting that.
Never know what kind of morons you'll attract.
Mary!
Stop with the hugs.
You've got that three billion yen all figured, but what about the other prize you won?
I have no need for a person's life.
If I can keep gambling, I'm satisfied.
I transferred Manyuda's life to a suitable person.
Oh. Sumeragi, then.
She must be happy about that. Seemed like she was pretty attached to him.
Exactly.
Yumeko.
I doubt your head will ever come down from the clouds, but let me give you some advice.
You shouldn't take this student council president election lightly.
Haven't you heard? A whole bunch of weirdos have transferred in just in time for the election.
From what I've heard, they all have "bami" in their surnames.
"Bami"?
Yes. Same as the president's name, Momobami.
There's no way that's a coincidence. You should really be careful.
Yumeko, your surname has "bami" in it too.
Do you know anything about this?
Hm... I suppose they could be distant relatives.
Anyway, what a massive school! Everything's so extravagant.
She's giving up both the academy and the family leadership.
Kirari sure is generous.
You're not the rep, though, Ibara.
Shut up, Yumi. I'm here to support him. Right, Rin?
I'll do my best.
So, whoever earns the most votes becomes student council president.
It is an election, you know.
And that one winner becomes leader of the main family.
Erimi?
Be that as it may, I do not recommend trying to eliminate us Clan members first.
Not only do you run the risk of a plan backfiring, you will be painting a target on your back for us.
Should wait 'til there's fewer people in the running.
And don't go telling us about it.
I know that! I was just...
Shut up!
I hope you have not forgotten our pact. Until we topple Kirari, we will not fight each other.
I will kill anyone who stands in my way. Remember that.
Don't worry. We all understand.
So, how should we handle the Jabami girl—Yumeko Jabami?
Jabami? Is that a branch family?
Rei?
Very well. Yumeko Jabami is the second-born daughter of House Jabami, a fringe branch family of the Clan.
Soon after transferring to Hyakkao Academy, she defeated five student council members by gambling.
That is the information I have gathered on her.
Wow, she's impressive!
It may be a fringe family, but the fact remains that she is part of the Clan. Isn't that right, Rei?
Yes, Miss Miyo.
Should we include her in our pact?
That will not be necessary. You are free to engage or ignore her however you wish.
Oh? That means we can go after her, then.
Rei.
Understood.
They sure got started right away.
Well, I guess these are just toys to most students.
Not to the students at the bottom of the school's hierarchy.
However small it may be,
they still have a real chance.
What are you going to do, Yumeko?
I'm going to use my vote to gamble with the president, of course!
I figured.
I'm so excited!
In that case, you'd better earn a lot of votes.
You can't challenge her with just one or two.
Oh, I don't know about that.
There's so much power in one of these votes that even a single one cannot be ignored...
At least, that's one view!
Yumeko's plans are a mystery to me, as always.
Does she want to become student council president?
What about you, Saotome?
What are your plans for this election?
I'm...
Saotome?
I don't know. And it's none of your business.
I'm leaving for the day.
Did I say something to offend her?
I wonder...
You are Yumeko Jabami, correct?
Yes, I most certainly am.
I am here to invite you to an election match.
To gamble? I gladly accept!
Yumeko, you should be careful. This must be one of the transfer students that Saotome...
Are you from the Clan as well?
That—
I apologize. My name is Rei Batsubami.
I am here to assist the ladies and gentlemen of the Momobami Clan.
Will you be gambling with me today?
Will I be... gambling...?
Certainly not. Your opponent will be someone else.
I will guide you.
Great!
Yumeko! Boy, have I missed you!
It was Ikishima?
She invited me! Told me I'd get to gamble with you!
Pleased to meet you.
This is Miss Erimi Mushibami.
Mushibami? Then she  is one of them.
Miss Mushibami, thank you so much for inviting me.
You're actually pretty great.
Sorry for calling you a grade schooler.
You will have the pleasure of being the first I eliminate, lowly underling. Alongside Yumeko Jabami, that is.
It appears all the players have arrived.
I will now take my leave.
I am Inaho Yamato from the Election Management Committee.
I will be managing this game space.
Why do we need a manager?
Anywhere there is gambling, there must be a Committee member.
Voting is strictly regulated, so it is necessary for a Committee member
to be present at all gambling sites until the election is over.
Dammit, who cares? Let's get this show on the road!
You've got something good for us, right?
I believe it will satisfy you.
You're not going to turn tail, are you, Yumeko Jabami?
Of course not! I'm excited to see how we will be gambling.
Hey, doesn't this put Yumeko at a huge disadvantage?
Rest assured, you are free to decline after you hear the rules.
Don't worry. The game I've prepared is fair as fair can be.
Let's do it!
Our jobs would be meaningless.
She got me so hot and bothered.
Hey, what's your deal all of a sudden?
Why would you start crying over a game you came up with?
You can't just end it after teasing me this much.
Shit! If this ends, how am I gonna get off!?
Shut up.
What? I can't hear you!
Shut up! You think I'd let myself lose to an lowborn brat like you!?
Now we're talking. Y'know, I might be into that kinda thing!
How can you cut so easily?
Only three strings remain! Your turn, Miss Mushibami!
I can't.
I can't believe we haven't gotten it yet!
We've got some real shitty luck.
Oh, but the longer it takes, the better the game, no?
What the hell is with them? There's only three left.
How can they keep their fingers in when the blade will fall within three turns?
This is crazy. Will they really...
not pull their fingers out until the final string is cut?
I just can't take it anymore. I can't...
Miss Mushibami... I hardly think this could be the case,
but you're not thinking of pulling your finger out, right?
You said it yourself—
torture is the Mushibami family business.
And you wanted to see how long we could last.
Yeah, true! That's what you said!
Since torture is your family business, this must be preaching to the choir,
but this Finger-Cutting Guillotine causes fear to build up as the strings are cut.
Nobody can endure the steadily increasing terror.
It's a physiological reaction so powerful as to make anyone abandon their pride and convictions.
Which means...
Now we're at the essence of it! Now the fun truly begins!
So, why are you dawdling?
Pick up those scissors, if you would be so kind, and make that terror real!
She's right.
No human being could possibly keep their finger under the blade until the final string.
House Mushibami's torture is infallible! If such a person really existed...
My family... the Mushibami family business would be undermined!
Looks to be another miss!
Oh, this is good. Oh, this is good!
You're great. I think you can take me all the way.
The move is yours, Miss Ikishima!
I know. Let's all come together!
Freak.
Anyway, there are just two strings left.
The game will be decided within the next two turns.
I'll prove it! When it comes down to one string, you  will pull your fingers out.
You have to!
This inescapable terror... is the cornerstone of my family!
I'm in heaven!
Get it wrong! Keep this going until the last—
Game over! As all the strings have been cut, we have a result!
Miss Mushibami removed her finger, and is thus eliminated.
Miss Ikishima cut two strings at once, in violation of the rules, and is thus disqualified.
Accordingly, the winner is Miss Yumeko Jabami!
Miss Jabami earns two chips!
The hell were you thinking, cutting two strings at once!?
Why the fuck did you design this thing to not cut off any fingers!?
I thought... I thought I could finally make it happen with Yumeko... But you screwed it up!
Dammit! God fucking dammit!
Yumeko! Say something to this piece of crap!
The only piece of crap here is you, Ikishima.
Do you have any idea what you did?
W-what do you mean? I was sharing the risk with you guys, just like you told me...
You cut two strings.
Those one-in-twenty odds slowly increased over a stretch of happy accidents, eventually reaching one-in-two.
It was like a miracle brought by God himself.
And at the end of it all, we reached the ultimate choice.
Yet you trampled on that final moment.
Even though we weren't scared at all by that stuff about amputation and inescapable terror...
Never show your face to me again.
You disgust me.
W-wait a minute!
Why... why is the iron plate still there?
Didn't the dealer say she removed it?
That was just a bit of insurance.
After hearing the rules, I thought it would be unfortunate if the device contained something like that iron plate.
Fortunately, there was also a rattle to the table the guillotine is on.
But we were able to play the game without any difficulty, right?
That was thanks to the dealer, Miss Yamato. She removed the pads from the table feet.
Indeed! One of the pads was damaged,
so I removed them all to ensure the table was balanced.
I'm sorry that you misinterpreted my words.
But I wanted you to feel what we were feeling.
That's why... that's why I...
Miss Mushibami.
The pride and conviction you showed us at the end were truly magnificent.
Let's have fun gambling again sometime.
Yumeko Jabami. This girl is part of the Momobami Clan, no doubt about it.
And I have no doubt either that our clan
will consume itself at this academy.
How long has it been since we had a casual conversation, I wonder?
Terano... Yumi. I hope you two are well.
I'm doing great! That's all I've got going for me, after all!
The Clan would never come together like this under other circumstances.
Quite right. However, I was a bit surprised to see you had brought Rei along as well.
This school is your territory. Who would be foolish enough to waltz in without some insurance?
But can they  really be counted on as insurance? House Batsubami was expelled from the Clan.
They are outcasts. I hardly think they would work on your behalf, even out of malice.
They wouldn't work on your behalf, either.
That's what's good about 'em. Right?
An ill-conceived scheme would simply dig my own grave.
I have merely thrown in a joker whose actions will be unpredictable.
Nothing more or less.
How interesting. I've always liked that about you, Terano.
Wow!
At any rate, the game is already afoot.
There can be no stopping it. This academy will fall to ruin, just as you wanted.
Miss Yuriko! Miss Yuriko! Won't someone... please...!
This is so stupid.
Everyone's still dancing in the palm of that girl's hand...
You're... the president? No, the vice president?
You are Mary Saotome, correct? I've been looking for you.
We have matters to discuss.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
In a trance.
Do exactly as Mary tells you.
Gambling changes people...
It is a ghastly poison.
Episode 3:
This Woman Should Not Be Touched