Shanna is best girl.
100 Vote
Auction.
..Auction
100 Vote
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election.
.                            Management Committee..
Management Committee.
.      Please bring your invitation.
I was right.
Nobody else in our class got an invitation.
We were the only ones.
I see.
I wonder who the sender is.
By the way...
What will you do, Yumeko?
I'll attend, of course.
Of course you will.
Maybe we should wait to decide until we look into who the sender is.
Really?
All I care about is whether the gambling will be exciting.
You say that, but if you don't know who you're up against,
you could wind up being poisoned again, or something.
That's one of my treasured memories.
Oh, right!
What about Saotome?
100 Vote
Auction
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
This gamble will be held under the auspices
of the Student Council Presidential Election
Management Committee.
Please bring your invitation
Yes, I received one as well.
Could it be the vice president again, then?
Nope.
Definitely not.
Huh?
Well, the organizer of this event is most likely
someone from the Momobami Clan.
That's the most plausible explanation.
We're midway through the election, and votes are moving slowly.
They must be starting to feel the heat.
So, what will you do?
Uh... me?
I'm sure Yumeko must be raring to go.
Preparations for the auction are complete, Chairwoman.
Okay!
Let the organizer know.
Right!
What an unexpected surprise.
I never thought something like this would happen.
Suzui Ryota
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Suzui Ryota
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Suzui Ryota
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Suzui Ryota
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
2nd Year
.Hana Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Votes
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Votes
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Votes
Komabami Nozomi
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes
Votes Held
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes
Votes Held
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes
Votes Held
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Sumire Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Votes
Votes Held
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Inbami Miyo
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Obami Ibara
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Obami Ibara
Votes Held
Votes
1st Year
..Kikyo Class
Obami Ibara
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
In my story of wonderful thrills I'll
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo
Live
ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
It'll be all right, Suzui-san.
We'll know as soon as we enter.
W-what are you doing?
Shut up. I'm staking her out.
Nishinotouin-san,
Ikishima?
You two were invited too?
Not just us—the entire Student Council was, too.
However,
it would seem we're the only ones who decided to attend.
Not like you had a better choice, after losing on the first day of the election.
You lost on the first day too!
And I only lost because of foul play from Inbami Miyo.
At this rate, it's not just my seat on the Student Council that's in danger—
the future of the Traditional Culture Club is, too.
What?
Suzui! What should I do to make up with Yumeko?
Huh?!
The way things are, Yumeko might not play with me ever again.
Help me out, will you?
I'm not sure what you want me to do...
Suzui-san?
Whomever have you been speaking to?
What?
Uh... Ikishima—
I can't see anyone.
Y-Yumeko, the other day we—
Let's go, Suzui-san.
Hey, I'm begging you, Yumeko. Please...
Let me off the hook, Yumeko!
Mary-san!
No hugs.
What a beautiful theater.
Vice President?
So you're attending, too.
Nishinotouin-san...
Thanks for the game, the other day.
Can you really take part in the auction if you don't have any votes?
No need to worry.
I won my votes from the Traditional Culture Club.
You won  them, did you?
I see.
That must be how Ikishima got more votes.
Oh, my!
Batsubami-san?
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you very much for attending the Hundred Votes Auction today.
Unfortunately, it would seem that not all who were invited are attending.
Gathered here now
are those fine ladies and gentlemen who know no fear.
For today's auction, I, Batsubami Rei,
will be your auctioneer.
So, does this confirm that the organizer is from the Momobami Clan?
Now, let me introduce our monitor for today.
I will be your monitor today.
My name is Yamato Inaho.
You, again?
Let's have a good game again, Yamato-san.
I would like nothing more.
Getting right to it—I'll now explain the rules of the Hundred Votes Auction.
Wait.
Oh?
Is something wrong, Saotome-san?
If you're putting hundreds of votes on the line here, then someone must have them.
Who is that?
Do these votes even exist in the first place?
The sponsor must remain anonymous.
However...
The votes most definitely exist.
Who could pull together so many votes in such a short time?
Other than the president, just one person.
Your sponsor must be Totobami Terano, then.
The sponsor's anonymity is a condition of this gamble.
As long as you consent to the terms,
then the gamble is valid, even if the sponsor's identity is not revealed.
Isn't that right?
Yes. You are quite right about that.
I get it. I'll give it a rest.
Much appreciated.
Now, let me return to explaining the rules of the Hundred Votes Auction.
First, the auctioneer will place hundred vote
lots up for bidding.
You will be using your votes to make bids, as well.
Whoever places the highest bid will win the hundred vote lot.
current bid
However, all votes placed as bids will be paid to the auctioneer,
winning bid
and will not be returned to you.
S-so, if you don't win the lot, you lose everything you bid?
Each participant will make their bids using their own individual terminal.
Unlike ordinary auctions, you will not know who places each bid.
Additionally, each participant is free to withdraw from the auction at any time.
If you withdraw, your participation ends then and there.
That's it for the rules.
current bid
In that case, the Hundred Votes Auction
shall now begin.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
let us start the bidding for the first lot of one hundred votes.
current bid
We'll start with one vote.
It's like they're just handing me votes for free.
We have ten votes.
Wh—ten, already?
I only have 13 votes to begin with...
Do I see any more?
Of course not.
Under these rules, any votes you bid get subtracted from your winnings.
In other words, the more the bidders compete with each other,
the more the sponsor stands to gain.
So, unless you're a hopeless idiot—
We have twenty votes! Anyone else?
current bid
What!? Who made that bid?
Calm down, Mary-san.
Gambling is boring when only one person puts their hat in.
You're the only one who believes that.
I never said I made the bid.
Don't be so smug about that!
current bid
We have thirty votes!
Hey!
Yumeko's totally right.
We came all the way out here, after all.
What's the point if we don't gamble a little?
If I can put Yumeko in a good mood,
I'll definitely get out of the doghouse!
Damn idiots, the lot of them.
Dammit. Don't do anything stupid again, will you?
We have eighty votes! Any more bids?
Then it's sold for eighty votes.
You understand now, right?
I was the one who made the first and last bids.
winning bid
So, despite losing the hundred votes,
the sponsor took in 130 votes from all of our bids.
They want us to fight among ourselves.
Saotome?
What is it?
You're saying we shouldn't compete.
But how about we pick an order and let everybody win once?
That won't do, Suzui-san.
This is an auction.
Collusion among bidders all but assures the sponsor's loss.
As the custodian of these votes, I would have no choice but to withdraw.
If you'd like to win, you will need to compete.
Y-You're right. I'm sorry.
Now, let us begin the bidding for the second lot.
winning bid
current bid
We'll begin with one vote.
We have ten votes.
That ten votes is my bid.
Anyone else who bids will be fighting against me.
I won't back down. Keep that in mind if you want to bid.
current bid
We have twenty votes.
Is anyone listening!?
Well, are you ?
We came here to gamble.
Right, Yumeko?
Eyepatch bitch...
What's the matter, Mary-san?
Huh?
I have no idea who you might be talking to.
current bid
The bid is currently twenty votes.
Do I see any more?
Well, if Yumeko's not going to get involved, this round might go well.
current bid
We have thirty votes!
Anyone else?
Forty votes.
We have forty votes!
Anyone else?
What?
Huh?
You, again?
That wasn't me!
Was it Yumeko, then?
Oh, no. It wasn't me.
Well, then! Do we have any more?
current bid
Fifty votes.
Seventy votes.
We have seventy votes!
Eighty votes!
Do I see anyone else?
current bid
Then it's sold for eighty votes.
winning bid
What on Earth is going on here?
This is crazy.
At this rate, none of us will gain anything.
I was the one who won that bid.
Nishinotouin-san?
Hold up. What do you think you're doing?
Like I said before, this auction—
Be quiet.
There's something strange about this auction.
But, in any case,
there's only one way to prevent people from bidding.
And that is by bidding.
Bidding so high that everyone else loses interest in competing.
I see.
Thanks to you,
I've realized how to beat this gamble.
Is everything all right?
winning bid
Then let's move to the next hundred vote lot.
Excuse me!
May I have a moment, please?
I would like to speak with Yamato-san.
Oh, you'd like to speak with me?
Yes... Yes.
Very well, then!
Thank you very much.
winning bid
Jabami-san, is there a problem?
Oh, no. I'm enjoying this game from the bottom of my heart.
What about you, Batsubami-san?
current bid
I am merely the auctioneer.
I am in no position to enjoy the gambling.
Now, is everything all right?
Let us move on to the third lot, then.
We'll start with one vote.
I have an announcement.
This time, no matter how much anyone else bids, I'll bid 99 votes.
If you don't want to lose your votes, then don't bid.
Unless you'd like to go down with me, that is.
We have ten votes.
Is there anyone else?
We have twenty votes.
Wha—! That can't be.
Now, the current bid is twenty votes. Any others?
current bid
Then it's sold for twenty votes.
winning bid
Saotome, weren't you going to bid 99 votes?
Oh, I lied about that.
I did lose ten votes, though.
But now I know.
The auctioneer is cheating.
winning bid
Cheating?
I announced that I would bid 99 votes no matter what, not that I would keep bidding.
If anyone wanted to beat me, then they'd be trading a hundred votes for a hundred votes.
There would be no point in bidding.
Yet someone bid twenty votes.
Who do you think would do that?
Um...
It wasn't me!
winning bid
Try to remember.
Neither the auctioneer nor the election monitor ever said the six of us were the only ones bidding.
There was someone else bidding, besides us, whose goal was to deliberately raise the price.
In other words...
You were participating in the auction!
A simple task, but one with incredible results.
winning bid
Essentially, all they needed to do was keep the bidding going until the sponsor made a profit.
Color me impressed, Saotome-san.
winning bid
You're right.
I was participating in the auction.
However, I was not in violation of the rules.
I was putting my own votes on the line, just like all of you.
No, that's definitely weird!
No—Batsubami-sama is correct.
Nothing in the rules of this game prohibits the auctioneer from participating in the auction.
What the hell!?
But I understand your concerns.
From now on, I won't participate.
Will that be all right?
Well, that's fine.
Doesn't make up for the first three rounds, though.
Thank you very much.
winning bid
Is everyone else fine with that?
current bid
In that case, let us begin bidding for the fourth lot.
Batsubami-san won't be participating from now on.
Does that mean Saotome's plan will succeed?
All right.
current bid
We have ten votes.
Ten votes is the current bid.
current bid
Do we have anyone else?
Suzui, huh.
Come, now, anyone?
We have thirty votes.
That's the only explanation...
current bid
We have forty votes!
Fifty votes.
Sixty votes.
At this rate, Yumeko's got no choice but to notice me!
current bid
We have seventy votes!
Hold on.
Can you all stop screwing around, for once?
I'm sorry, Mary-san.
Gambling just isn't fun when only one person's in the running.
Yumeko, will you ever...
But...
I finally understand.
Why we've all felt uneasy.
Huh?
This round, I bid forty votes.
Someone bid thirty votes before me.
Is there anyone here besides me who would prioritize gambling over acquiring votes?
I bid seventy votes, Yumeko!
There isn't.
So there must be someone, besides us, who bid thirty votes in order to raise the price.
But there isn't anyone...
Suzui-san, there's another thing that the rules didn't mention.
"The participants must all be able to see each other."
That can't be...
Yes, there's someone else.
Another participant, in a different location!
Nyahahaha!
This has gotten interesting, hasn't it?
Damn, they realized, huh?
Here I was thinking we could earn a little more, Rin-san.
This is why I told you to hold off for a bit.
S-Shut up, Mira.
Why did you let Ibara-san have the terminal?
Heh. Sorry about that.
This is no laughing matter.
You could have just ruined Terano-san's whole plan.
I'm not surprised it was Jabami Yumeko.
current bid
I will not deny that there is another participant.
What else  have you...
Shall we end the auction, then?
current bid
Of course, I cannot return the chips that you have bid.
How could we stop now?
This is where the fun part begins.
Batsubami-san, don't you think it's time we put an end to this farce and started gambling for real?
Surely you didn't intend for this game to end with no risk to you, did you?
current bid
What... do you mean?
I've been thinking about this for a while.
On whose behalf are you acting?
I said before that I have no duty to answer that.
current bid
Perhaps it's not that you won't answer, but that you can't  answer.
I'm not sure I follow.
Because both the sponsor and the organizer are you.
Jabami-san,
I'm sorry, but it would seem you have almost no votes left with which to bid.
current bid
Whether you're right or not, has the question not lost its relevance for you?
Oh, I don't know about that.
Jabami-sama!
We have delivered the items you requested earlier.
With the consent of all those present, it is possible to amend the rules.
current bid
Thank you.
Yumeko...
Batsubami-san, there is three billion yen here.
That's from the formal match with Manyuda-san!
Please let me use this to win this round's hundred votes.
current bid
You could buy as many votes as you like with this money.
However...
No matter how many votes you earn, if you don't put your heart into it,
you'll get crushed underfoot like an ant.
There is nothing to be enjoyed from a gamble with you, as you are now.
I want to gamble with the real  you.
A gamble with real risk!
Not just a hundred votes!
current bid
You've hidden yourself behind that mask for so long—
I want to bid this three billion to win your everything!
current bid
Now, show me!
Your resolve, and the reason why you're here!
I'd expect nothing less from Jabami Yumeko.
current bid
Well done.
If you'll go that far, I can't back down.
You are correct.
I was the one who organized this auction.
current bid
Episode 11
The Woman Who Bears the ✕
Take a good look.
This is my...
raison d'être!
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo, sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
It would seem your joker has entered play.
Even a house pet will bare its fangs.
Nothing's started yet!
Now is the time for severance!
Episode 12:
The Null Woman