I did not expect you to reach out to me first.
What is it you want from me?
Jabami Yumeko.
Let's gamble!
As you wish, I will gamble with you.
nozomidoori ni kakete ageru
I won't go easy on you.
tekagen wa shinai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Who will be first?
saisho wa dare?
Moderation is boring.
hodohodo ja tsumannai
It's all or nothing.
subete ka zero ka
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Love
suki
Hate
kirai
Let's have some fun.
tanoshimimashou
It feels good when you indulge.
nomerikomu hou ga kimochi ii
In my story of wonderful thrills I'll
suteki na suriru no sutoorii wo
Live
ikiru
We won't lose anything of importance.
ushinau mono wa takaga shireteru
We may lose our tomorrow, but not our whole future.
ashita wo nakushitemo mirai ga nakunarutte wake janai
If you want to dream, you need to be world-weary.
yume wo miru ni wa shirisugita jidai sa
Come here, and gather round.
oide yo kono yubi tomare
I prefer to love until there's nothing left.
aishikiru sore ga watashi no tashinami
Here you go! Eat up, Manyuda-senpai.
I peeled them by hand,
so I'm sure you'll enjoy them.
Sumeragi...
Leave me be.
For your own sake.
I failed. I lost everything.
My status at this academy, my parents' confidence.
I don't even own my life anymore.
Your life?
Oh, you mean this?
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Yes.
Because you have that Life Plan, my life belongs to you.
Hah! Why are you acting so complacent? It's not like you.
This is nothing but a pile of paper.
Someone controls your life. So what?
Put some wins under your belt and turn the tables.
It's no reason to give up on your ambition!
You're a fool.
I had no right to walk the high road.
I know that now.
There's no reason for me to fight.
Oh? Well, in that case...
You wouldn't mind submitting to me for the rest of your life, then?
It must be so shameful to serve someone
you looked down on that much.
I'll be sure to run you ragged as long as you live.
You're right...
This is how it should be.
What, is that really it?
Did a single failure bring you this low?
Is this really the extent of your ambition?
What's wrong with you?
I don't want to see you sulking.
Sumeragi-san, there you are!
Yumeko-senpai?
Mira!
Terano called you over, too?
Yes.
Damn, this must be a big deal.
Won't just be a little tea party.
Well, who knows what she's got in store for us.
Well, well. If it isn't Jabami Yumeko!
What's going on, Terano?
You bringing her in after all?
No.
Gotcha.
You want to fight with Momobami Kirari, right?
Then the logical choice is to join us.
Let's bring her down together!
I'm sorry. I can't accept your offer.
Drop it.
If she simply wanted to fight Kirari, she would be doing so now.
Yumeko appears to have a plan of her own.
I have agreed to Yumeko's proposal.
What would that be?
You saw the news flash from the other day, I'm sure.
Kirari is accumulating votes far faster than I imagined.
3rd Year, Hana Class
Momobami Kirari
The endgame is easy to foresee.
Votes can be bought and sold.
The well-funded will soon be scrambling to buy them up.
If we enter the game at that stage,
our financial disadvantage will prove fatal.
Without enough votes, none of us will even be able to compete.
She's exactly right!
So, let's all gamble together!
If we play a high-risk, high-return game together, we can pool all our votes.
Jabami Yumeko and Sumeragi Itsuki are both at the top of the current rankings.
You'll find no better opponents.
I went ahead and decided which game you will be playing.
What do you say? Ibara. Miroslava.
Very well.
Fine by me.
I'd love  to play against them.
Is this everyone who'll be playing?
Not quite. There's one more person.
Manyuda-senpai!?
Wait a sec! Hold on!
That's the former student council treasurer, Manyuda Kaede, right?
Isn't he a loser who's ten billion in the hole?
Doesn't that go against the whole goal of pooling a bunch of votes?
In the interest of fairness, both myself and Yumeko each chose two people.
We needed one more person for this game, anyway.
Deal with it.
Heh. Filling seats, huh.
Fitting treatment for a failure like me.
Do as you please.
I don't care about this election.
Huh?
I don't like your attitude.
Okay, okay, I see everyone has arrived.
I am Uru Rumia of the Election Management Committee.
I will be presiding over this game.
Your voice kinda pisses me off.
People often say that.
Now, now, today's game has been planned and sponsored by Totobami-sama.
There are five players.
Huh?
I get Yumi and Rei, but you're not playing either, Terano?
Have you forgotten our pact?
I have no intention of taking votes from you, yet.
Huh?
The name of the game you will be playing is...
The Greater Good Game.
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Greater
Good
Game
Let me explain how the game works.
First, we will show each of you, one by one and in order, to another room.
In the other room, there will be two boxes: the personal bank box, and the tax deposit box.
To begin with, everyone will be provided with five coins.
You are free to deposit them in either box.
Tax
Once everyone has deposited, I will count the number in each box,
Greater
Good
Game
and distribute coins for the next round.
The coins in each player's personal bank
will be counted towards their overall total.
However, the coins placed into the tax deposit box
T
a
x
will be doubled, then divided in equal parts and distributed to all players.
Paying taxes enriches the whole country,
and improves everyone's quality of life.
That's why you want to put your coins in the tax deposit box.
I see!
By the way, when you say "all players",
does that include people who didn't put coins in the tax deposit box?
Yes! Even if you didn't pay any tax at all,
you'll still receive coins from the tax deposit box.
It's free money, so to speak.
That's ridiculous.
Nobody will pay any tax at all, then.
You may be right.
But people who don't pay their taxes are quite a nuisance, right?
Before each round, you will have time for a discussion.
If at least three players are in agreement during that time,
you can eliminate a player from the game, one time only!
The eliminated player will be excluded from the game, and all of their coins will be confiscated.
You can put your coins in the tax deposit box... or you can try to outwit your fellow players.
Regardless, you should aim to accumulate at least 40 coins over five rounds.
If you acquire 40 or more coins, you will be eligible for these prizes in votes.
1st Place                  100 Votes
2nd Place                    30 Votes
3rd Place                        3 Votes
4th, 5th Place                0 Votes
You only have five turns, so if everyone puts their coins in the personal bank box, you won't have nearly enough.
Wait a sec.
Prizes?
Who's gonna hand those out?
Me, of course.
I told you, didn't I?
I have no intention of taking your votes.
I will offer up every one of my 133 votes.
You'll be snatching votes from the bookmaker. Easy as can be.
To oppose Kirari, I need more people with large numbers of votes.
Even if they're not on my side.
That said... what I don't  need is dead weight.
One last thing...
Any player who does not accumulate 40 coins
1st Place        100 Votes
2nd Place        30 Votes
3rd Place          3 Votes
4th,5th Place        0 Votes
by the end of the game
will need to give Totobami-sama all of their votes!
1st Place        100 Votes
2nd Place        30 Votes
3rd Place          3 Votes
4th,5th Place        0 Votes
Aha! Hey, that's crazy, Terano!
What happened to all that generosity?
Our goal here is pooling votes.
To do so, certain arrangements are required.
Hah!
Always got a trick up your sleeve, don't you.
Fine, then.
Seems I'd like to play this game after all.
I'd feel awful to sit this one out!
I have no objections.
This is starting to get exciting.
I don't care.
How about you, Sumeragi-sama?
I'll play.
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
Everyone has agreed to the rules, how lovely!
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
In that case, let us begin.
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
T
a
x
1st Place                100 Votes
2nd Place                30 Votes
3rd Place                    3 Votes
4th, 5th Place            0 Votes
Time to start the Greater Good Game!
This turn order has been established by drawing lots.
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Now, you may begin the discussion for Round One.
We're supposed to have a discussion, but... we don't have much to discuss yet, do we?
Ehe. Then let's just confirm.
Everyone will put all of their coins in the tax deposit box, right?
What?
If everyone pays their coins in tax, we're sure to acquire at least 40 coins.
More importantly, we'll all get first place!
What are you on about?
That outcome would be almost as bad as everyone losing.
If everyone came in first, 500 votes would be required for the prizes.
But Terano only has 133.
So everyone would only get 26 votes.
However, if you outmaneuver everyone else to reach first place, you'll get 100 votes.
I can't imagine nobody would give in to that temptation.
Sooner or later, we'll start trying to outwit each other.
It's inevitable.
Oh, dear. How very tragic.
There's no way Yumeko didn't think of that already.
Yumeko was making sure of something.
The goal here is to sabotage everyone else while keeping yourself alive.
It's a game of treachery!
Okay! The discussion period is over.
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Sumeragi-sama will be the first to invest her coins.
This way, now. We will show you to the other room.
Sumeragi
Tax
What should I do?
I want to get first, but I definitely don't want everyone to lose.
It'd be sheer folly to put everything in the personal bank right away.
Anyway, for now I'll aim to win!
What?
I had a lot of fun gambling with you the other day!
We both put everything on the line—
Standard Account
(With Debt Schedule)
Date   Summary      Name of Payer              Deposit (Yen)             Net Balance (Yen)
Received
Iwata Kei
Kazakami Mai
Okamura Kouya
Minato Tomohiro
Yanagida Takashi
Animinami Saki
Ueno Yui
Sakurada Hiroko
even Sumeragi-san bet everything she had.
Hyakkao Academy
Student Council
Life Plan
Sumeragi
Itsuki
It was a truly wonderful experience.
Let's have fun gambling today.
You never cease to amaze.
You have a lot of nerve to say that to me.
Huh?
Just like you said, I bet everything—and I lost.
I'd like to ask you something.
You have an ardent passion for gambling.
Sometimes, you send an opponent to the depths of despair.
Do you feel any remorse
for the people whose lives you've ruined?
Yes... I suppose...
I feel some remorse
about the fact that I don't feel remorseful.
Are you serious?
You know the fate of a person who's fallen to the depths of despair!
And despite that,
You still feel nothing!
Do you know what it looks like, too?
When a person sinks into despair.
Rei.
Please excuse me.
Hey, we're trying to play a game here, you two.
Chill out, Batsubami.
Manyuda,
enough grumbling already.
If you've got a problem with Yumeko, then knock her out of the game. Right?
Right.
If you would do that...
I'd be glad.
Let go of me.
Itsuki     Sumeragi
Miroslava     Honobami
Yumeko     Jabami
Ibara     Obami
Kaede Manyuda
Sumeragi Itsuki-sama has finished.
How was it, Sumeragi-san?
Uh... There wasn't really anything noteworthy about it.
Just two boxes in a room.
Not that! She's asking which box you put your coins in.
You didn't put 'em in the personal bank, did you, now.
What do you want me to say?
Nobody wants to become a target for elimination.
I'd always tell you that I put them in the tax deposit box.
Really, though?
There are times when you can tell someone's lying by the way they answer.
Hey, Manyuda!
You've known Sumeragi for a while.
What do you think?
Don't involve me in this.
Play this out among yourselves.
Hehehe. Alright, then.
Honebami Miroslava-sama has finished.
Jabami Yumeko-sama is next.
Okay!
Yumeko-senpai!
We... can win, right?
If we both get knocked out of the election today...
Sumeragi-san...
For some reason,
I think something thrilling is going to happen.
All players have finished deposits for Round One.
All that remains is to announce the results!
Now, I will double the number of coins in the tax deposit box and distribute them to you.
20 coins were in the tax deposit box.
Double 20 is 40, and 40 divided by 5 leaves 8 coins per player!
Oh, dear!
If everyone put their coins in the tax deposit box, there'd be 25.
We were 5 votes short!
That means...
That's right, Sumeragi-san.
It would appear there is a traitor in our midst who didn't put any coins in the tax deposit box.
Now, you may begin the discussion preceding Round Two.
I knew this was gonna happen.
Who was it who betrayed us?
You can get ahead of the rest by putting your coins in the personal bank box,
but if nobody puts their coins in the tax deposit box, everyone will lose!
Yes, everyone's fully aware of that.
Let's expel them. We'll expel the traitor and continue the game with everyone else.
We can start competing for the win after everyone has 40 coins!
I'd love to do that if we could, but how are we gonna find out who the traitor is?
Shall I make them talk?
Torture may be House Mushibami's area of expertise, but there are things I can do.
Give me five minutes per person, and I'll find the truth.
W-what is this girl talking about?
How dumb can you be?
You only have a 1-in-5 chance of finding them.
I'd rather not be tortured despite being innocent.
Worry not. I will ascertain the truth.
You don't get it, do you, Mira?
How do we know you're not the traitor, in the first place? Idiot.
W-wait, please, calm down!
Ah, this is the true thrill of this game.
"There's a traitor in our midst."
"Someone didn't pay their taxes like they promised, and they're lying about it."
"They're acting like they're innocent."
"I paid my taxes like I said. How can this be allowed?"
"Am I really going to lose?"
"I don't believe it."
"I can't forgive it."
"It's unfair."
This is the true essence of the Greater Good Game.
When a person feels something is unfair, they can't even trust their neighbors.
Well? Can you face that unfairness and still trust each other despite it?
Why did you choose this game?
This game is a microcosm of the presidential election.
You team up with others to accomplish your own goal,
all the while thinking of how to outwit them.
Rei, of all these people,
whom do you think is most smeared in falsehood?
I find that question difficult to answer.
I see.
How about this?
We're not able to determine who the traitor is right now.
In that case, all we can do is prevent treachery itself.
I have an idea!
Does anyone have paper and a pen?
I-I have some.
What's this about?
On each of these pieces of paper, I've written a number between one and five.
Please take one, everyone, and put coins in the tax deposit box equal to the number you get.
Why should we?
What's the point of this?
I see! So that's what this is.
If everyone puts their number of coins in the tax deposit box,
if the traitor puts all their coins in their personal bank,
we can see who they are from the amount missing from the tax box.
Sumeragi
Tax
Honebami
Jabami
Tax
Exactly!
There's still a risk people evade one or two coins' worth of taxes,
Manyuda
Tax
but we'll be able to avoid any big betrayals.
All right! Everyone has finished their deposits for Round Two.
I'll now announce the results.
Wonder how it'll turn out this time.
The amount you all paid in taxes was...
Thirteen coins!
Rounding up, you will each receive six coins for the next round.
Thirteen... coins?
Y-Yumeko-senpai, what does that...
Hmm, this is a surprise. I thought the total of the numbers I'd written was 21.
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
S-show us your papers, everybody!
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Of the 21 coins that ought to have been paid in tax, only 13 were actually paid.
Which means...
The number of traitors has gone up!
The total in the box couldn't be 13 without at least two people evading taxes.
What are you people doing?
We're all going to lose this game if we don't work together!
Hey.
Did you expect that this would happen?
That two or more people would be traitors.
Yes, of course.
Those pieces of paper were basically bait.
When a fish bites a lure, the more it splashes around, the easier it is to locate.
I did what you said because I believed you. Did you trick me?
It was all to expose the truth.
Now we know that there are currently multiple traitors, right?
Ah, is that right. Now I get it.
You were lying to all of us.
I guess honesty doesn't pay, after all!
How can they let this be so unfair?
We don't need liars like you!
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
Obami     Ibara
Manyuda   Kaede
Calm down, Ibara.
What Jabami Yumeko wants to say is this.
The two traitors are working together.
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
What?
It is not very wise to turn traitor when we already had a traitor among us.
Our coin allotments decrease,
and the risk of everyone losing goes up.
However, it's a different story if they're working together.
By paying tax at certain times and evading tax at others,
they can manipulate how many coins are allotted.
It's difficult for any more of us to turn traitor with two traitors already active.
For the traitors, it's a strategy for near-surefire victory.
The only way to disrupt it is for us to expel one of them.
Aren't you two the traitors, then?
You need to trust each other to work together.
You two are both members of that clan, so you're the most suspicious.
When would we have time to team up?
We only learned about this game after we got here.
Did you really not know before coming?
Couldn't you have coordinated in advance with Totobami-san over there?
With Terano? You think I'd do that?
Thus does discussion leap around. There will be no end to the accusations.
Sumeragi     Itsuki
Honebami     Miroslava
Jabami     Yumeko
What they need now is a decision.
But they're consumed by feelings of unfairness,
so they simply level accusations at each other.
This is the society we live in!
Now, let me see you get further and further from the goal!
Ah! I've had enough.
This is ridiculous.
Manyuda-senpai, do you have anything you'd like to say?
I'm sure you could—
Shut up already, Sumeragi. Leave me alone.
But... let me give an objective evaluation.
Judging from the circumstance, the traitor is...
Episode 7
The Treacherous Woman
Jabami Yumeko.
If you desire it so much as to writhe, I will give it to you.
notautsu hodo ni motomeru no nara ataeyou
You will need to avail yourself of even your despair.
zetsubou sae kate ni shite shimau
Now, come to me!
saa oide
If you offer your body and soul, I will answer.
mi mo kokoro mademo sashidasu nara kotaeyou
Tragedy will be overwhelmed by pleasure.
higeki mo etsuraku ni nomareru
Consumed by an excess of pure carnal desire,
amari nimo sekirara na retsujou ni ukasarenagara
Eventually you will live wishing only for a moment of titillation.
yagate shibireru youna shunkan dake wo negai ikiru
O soul that burns with desire, raise your glass.
aa katsubou suru tamashii yo, sakazuki wo kakage
Sing an ode to such joy as will break you.
kowareru hodo kanki no uta wo utaou
Simple acclaim will never satisfy your cravings.
kassai dewa michitaru hazu mo nai uzuki
It's maddening enough to bet on.
kakeru hodo kuruoshii
You in love with that glasses boy?
If I've got to die, I'll bring you all down with me.
Result
I'm taking you along.
Oh no, I'm gonna lose!
Episode 8:
The Winning Woman