Nuke
Fansubs
Presents
...Eri's Escape
...Harima's Lullaby
...The Fake Bride
Although Tenma's ahoge says
clear skies with clouds on the horizon
Note: "Ahoge" literally means foolish hair. It is a lock of hair sticking out from the head.
Nakamura's beard says that
sunny days are coming right up!
I was giving up...
Somewhere in my heart...
Was I... wrong?
Was I being weak?
I don't know.
It appears that I was one step too late.
I shall request for Masaru's aid.
Lord Yakumo! I humbly request that we order some sushi!
Huh? I thought we were going to have hot pot tonight.
Fine... I'll bring the groceries in. Give me a minute.
I thank you deeply! Your kindness will not be forgotten!
Eh?
Nee-san, I'm back...
Huh? She's gone...
Damn it. This is starting to get out of hand.
I'm supposed to be delivering the manuscript right now!
Excuse me, where are we headed?
HUH!? Uh, I mean... I'm not sure either.
I'm really sorry... Making you go through all of this just for me...
Hmph, you better be sorry.
But it this really okay? Didn't you have a marriage interview?
The truth is, I know that if I go, I'll probably be forced to marry against my will.
That's the kind of person my father is.
What? Was she planning on accepting it all along?
But why?
I was giving up...
Somewhere in my heart.
Was I...
Wrong?
Was I weak?
I don't know.
But... right now, what I see in front of me is...
HUH?
Ah.. Um... Uh...
Just now, that was...
What the... What are you doing, Tenma!
And the other person in the car was our... I'll text message her!
There's a ton of food, so don't hold back, Asou-kun.
That's right. Mikoto is always causing you trouble, Asou-kun.
No, no, I don't believe that she has ever caused me much trouble.
When did I cause any trouble?
Ahaha, why did you raise your voice, Mikoto?
You're being rude!
By the way, you look a lot older than I thought you'd be, Asou-kun.
How sweet of you to come all the way here to deliver a forgotten item.
What a thoughtful high schooler. Students like that are rare these days, eh Asou-kun?
You're doing this on purpose, right? RIGHT?
Suou Group
Safety First
Ahh... That's enough teasing to last me a lifetime...
I see. It would be troubling if you were to become inept at romance due to all of this teasing.
And who's fault do you think that is?
However, it seems that your relationship with Asou-kun is proceeding smoothly...
Oh, excuse me. I apologize for intruding upon these matters.
Ah, can we just change the topic already?
Besides, how come even Sawachika's people know about my private matters?
They are things that Ojou-sama often talks merrily about, after all.
Hm?
Yes. Stories, such as how her friend abuses her charm to mislead other men, one after another.
Yet, she is highly talented at pretending to be uninterested in relationships and making men's imaginations run wild.
Indeed, there are plenty of stories.
That woman...I'm going to kill her...
Did you catch a cold?
Ah, no.
She replied.
Note: Tenma is reading what the phone says.
I heard about it! Seems like you're going to a marriage interview!
It sounds fun so I'm going too! Oh, your assistant is really amazing!
He keeps calling me Ojou-sama. Okay, see you!
What? Just what is going on? That idiot...
Huh? Uh...
What's wrong?
Uh, well, apparently, my maid somehow mistook that girl we saw for me and took her away.
Let's go after them right now!
What?
Isn't it obvious? I'll go break up that messed up interview.
Huh? No... Why is this person...
Come on! Quickly!
Why is this person... trying so hard...
Tenma-chan getting married? Like hell I'd let that happen!
Like I said, I'm not Eri-chan. I'm Tenma.
Huh? Tenma?
Huh? Another text message from Miko-chan.
Eh... So Eri-chan's interview is against her will...
Huh? Then why is Masaru-kun taking me to the interview?
Oh no! Don't tell me that he mistook me for Eri-chan! Although it's quite understandable...
I guess I have no choice but to act as Eri-chan's substitute.
I'll go screw up this stupid interview!
Oh, that's right. I have to tell Yakumo.
Note: "Toro" is the type of tuna with the highest fat content.
Sis'll be late
Leave me the toro.
I'll stop them for sure!
Damn it. A flat tire now of all times...
There's nothing I can do...
What's up with this marriage interview? Even if it's Tenma-chan, I doubt she'll go along with it...
But what if the other guy falls for Tenma-chan's cuteness and insists on it...?
Damn it!
I guess he's cold after all...
This was the only blanket on the bike.
I said I was cold, so he gave it to me.
Ehhhh? Two people using the same blanket? That's so embarrassing!
But at this rate, Worker-san will catch a cold...
What should I do...?
Huh? What's up with her?
She's been fidgeting for a while...
Don't tell me that she thinks I'm going to do something to her!
Ah. It's possible. She's so arrogant and full of herself...
After all, she always mistakenly thinks that she's cute and that all of the guys will fall for her.
How annoying!
I'll try talking to him first. The blanket can come after that.
Um, Worker-san, when did you start working at Mikoto's house?
Huh? Oh, uh, yester... I mean last year.
You look pretty young... Are you a university student? Do you have a girlfriend?
Huh? Well, no...
Eh-heh... Really? What a waste.
HUH? What the... Is something wrong with her personality? I swear she wasn't the "eh-heh" type of girl...
Is she trying to trick me into something?
I'm sorry, bringing up a topic like this so suddenly...
Was it a bother?
No. It's fine.
Um, do you have any goals or things that you want to do in the future?
Huh?
What should I do...
I can't say anything about the manga or Tenma-chan.
Yes, I do. Although I'm working at Suou-san's place for now, I'd like to finish up the project that I'm currently working on.
Alright! The perfect lie!
A project? Are you an architect?
Something like that.
Um, in times like that, did something such as social customs ever become an obstacle for you?
Hell yeah. One's annoying me right now.
Huh?
Uh, I mean...
I won't lose to them. With these hands of mine, I'll defeat anything that stands in my way.
You're strong, aren't you.
Yes, I am strong.
What is the difference between him and me?
What can I do to become strong?
Should I just behave like a man?
Am I supposed to be more mature?
What should I do... to fight against this world?
Indeed...
Indeed, I have run into things like social customs.
They really are painful.
However, if thinking about it doesn't help, then I just stop thinking about it.
I just take it all in...
But even so, I still continue to laugh.
What... What the hell am I doing, talking seriously to Ojou...
Amazing!
What?
Huh?
Geh!
Um, I'm afraid that you'll catch a cold.
What's up with her?
Something is very wrong with her personality. It's seriously unnerving. What's she trying to get at?
Is it a bother for you?
Huh? Uh, no, not at all.
Actually, I've been really depressed lately.
But, thanks to you, I've regained some will to fight.
Can I ask you to do something?
Sure.
Can you come with me to the marriage interview?
Huh?
Of course, you'll only be pretending. It's just to make the other side give up.
Okay...
I know I should be solving this problem by myself, but...
For now, can you lend me a hand?
This girl...
Well, I guess it's alright.
Thank you.
What in the world am I doing...
Huh? She fell asleep! She says what she wants to say and then she just falls asleep! This is why rich people are...
Hmph, for the rich Ojou to say something like that...
For a moment, you seemed like a decent person.
Just for a moment back then...
Besides that, this girl is too careless.
Not that I have any interest in her, of course.
Hige, you're the worst...
It was really just a moment, wasn't it?
What? The other party is late?
We're in luck. Let's do this.
Got it.
You'll pretend to be the other guy. Converse with me, and we'll break off this engagement.
Afterwards, we'll meet upstairs.
Okay.
What a bother... I'm too nice of a guy.
I guess Ojou is still...
I have been waiting for you.
My name is Sawachika Eri.
It is a pleasure to meet you. Let us discuss our future marriage.
It's okay. That person is with me, after all.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Well, Eri-san.
You look gorgeous!
Mother...
Can I speak with you for a bit?
Please, just a moment is fine.
I see.
Tenma-chan has already accepted her role.
Okay, I'll finish this before Ojou comes.
Um.
What are your interests?
I have an interest in manga.
Huh? What is this?
I feel like I've just been badly ridiculed.
What I just did was pretty rude...
No, I must strengthen myself and finish the task.
I'm sorry. This incident has caused trouble for you, didn't it?
It's fine, mom.
It's not your fault.
You're forgiving, aren't you? I...
Mom, don't apologize!
How forgiving....
Uh, what about your interests?
Ze Wubic's Kube, I gwess.
The Rubik's Cube, I guess.
Ohohoho! I'm always like this, so the interviews will never work out for me!
Heh, how about it? There's no way you'd like a horrible woman like this. Let's hear you break off the engagement!
Please marry me!
This interview, if you really don't like it...
It's fine, mom.
I'll be okay.
I see. Then everything is fine as it is?
I guess I couldn't do it after all.
We're all in the same class.
You're with us too, Tenma.
Girls are the best!
Switch the pitcher.
Mikoto, you aren't all that cute, are you?
I... got rejected.
He's an idiot for rejecting you.
Deliver this for me...
If you can't swim, then say you can't swim!
Sorry.
We have to win against 2-D.
Take this!
Stop it! It's cold!
Mother.
Sorry, Eri-chan.
This'll become something you did,
but I have to do this here.
Ah, my shoulder itches.
A country bumpkin?
And now... this!
Note: "Para para" is a type of Japanese dance that has preset movements with everybody doing the same moves at once.
Para para?
Heh, if I go this far, then...
He's copying me!
Sawachika.
Eri-chan!
Eri.
That's right.
Mother, I...
I still want to stay with everyone after all.
Wait, Eri-san!
That's right. It's not like me to be giving up.
Ohoho! My hand slipped while we were playing.
How convenient. My forelocks were starting to become a nuisance anyway.
He's a difficult opponent. Sorry, Eri-chan. I might lose.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Huh? What're you doing?
Worker-san! It's fine! I--
Hm, so the meeting is cancelled... I understand.
Iori, where's all the toro?
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Timer
Floof
Translator
DeiLight
Typesetter
Rina
Editor
Meltingice
Karaoke
Rina
Encoder
Meltingice
TL Checker
Cairan
Rina
Quality Control:
DeiLight
Meltingice
Fansubbed by Nuke Fansubs
http://www.nuke-fansubs.com
Visit us at #Nuke @ irc.rizon.net
Many fansubbers were enslaved and worked in a sweatshop under our timer, Floof, in order to bring this episode to your hard drive. If you do not approve of sweatshops, please send 4 cents to Floof. Yes, that is double the amount we normally ask for.
Hey, Kuuta-kun hasn't been very popular lately.
I guess that even 3 meters becomes ordinary once you're used to seeing it.
Hey Kuuta, settle down!
Yagami Zoo
Suou Group
Safety First
Suou! Not showing up when you were the one that invited me to practice is...
The truth is...
What?
Yaku-- Tsukamoto-kun is going to an arranged marriage?
Tsukamoto-san and Ojou-sama are currently headed for the meeting.
What? Hanai went after them?
It was merely a jest. They are more than 500 kilometers away.
Nakamura-san, that's some naive thinking.
For you to go to an arranged marriage meeting with Harima... I'm sure it's tough for you, Yakumo-kun.
I, Hanai, will save you! Wait for me!
This is getting tough.
Oh, there's a temple over there.
Snacks from left to right: Roll bread, Pokaron, Melon Bread, Tea, Fried Chicken
It's already pretty late. Good thing I brought enough food.
Is someone there?
Oh, it's just a blanket.
Ah, it's so warm, it's so warm, it's so--
Is something there?
Hel--
It must have been my imagination...
Why is there a red panda here?
No, I must concentrate on protecting myself here.
Against large opponents like this, I should bring them down with a low attack and go for the temples!
Wait, it was never standing in the first place.
Damn! I can't attack properly if it's not in the same stance as a human.
What should I do?
It stood up!
The finishing blow!
Kyuu.
Lovely.
What a good rest.
Can you fix it?
Yeah. I used some parts from the bike over there...
Beard!
Beard?
Uh, nothing.
Anyway, are you hungry?
Yeah.
We didn't notice it at night, but there was a lot of food right beside us!
That's great.
I found the tools I needed too. This is quite a helpful temple.
Last night, Kuuta-kun, who escaped and caused a large commotion, has returned safely.
He's wearing glasses now and is very popular!
Ah, it's so cute!
Yakumo, Sarah, make sure you attend the clubroom's big clean up today. Santa is coming.
Next time on School Rumble Ni Gakki,
The Temptation of the Part-Time Job.
The Temptation of the Class.
The Temptation of the Celebrities.
The Temptation of the Part-Time Job.
The Temptation of the Class
The Temptation of the Celebrities
Penguins are sad beings, aren't they?
Of tradition and trust
The Suou Engineering Store.
Come fast!
The order for a giant tree,
See you next time!