I'm back!
Welcome back, Nee-san.
How's the preparation for the Christmas... presents...
They're going well, I guess.
Everything's perfect!
The Temptation of the Part-time job
The Temptation of the Class
The Temptation of the Celebrities
Jingle Bells~
School Rumble is now
preparing for Christmas
Hm? Was there a problem?
A problem? Of course! Why didn't you tell me that worker was Hige?
You would feel uncomfortable if you knew you were living under the same roof as he was, wouldn't you?
Besides, you mistook him for someone else at first.
But, thanks to that, we ended up sleeping together...
No way! I didn't hear of this!
How did it feel?
Well, nothing really.
Like this?
Eh?
Don't tell me it was like this!
Wait a second! Nothing happened! Nothing!
Ah, trips really make you more liberal after all, don't they?
Hey, where and how did you sleep together?
Eh? It was... in a vacant temple.
In a vacant temple?
Wrapped in a blanket...
Blanket...
Could it be that the two of you used the same blanket?
The two of us... used the same blanket.
We had no choice! We didn't have any money and it was cold and dark!
True, true. In that situation, you would indeed sleep together, wouldn't you? It couldn't really be helped.
So? What actually happened? I won't tell anyone else.
Nothing actually happened!
Really? Nothing at all?
What's with that look on your face?
Ah, Takano? I guess I lost. She didn't confess. I guess you know her better than I do, after all.
Just a minute! What are you people betting on?
A kiss.
A passionate kiss that happens when you give yourself into the atmosphere.
I got nothing. What a disappointment.
Unexpectedly, she's a chicken.
Coward.
You pop out of nowhere, and all you have to say is that?
Now, about the part-time job.
Part-time job?
You stayed over at Mikoto's house, right?
You have to repay her the favor.
Ah, right. That's...
Every year at this time, Mikoto's family offers part-time jobs to people.
Eh?
It's decided.
Make sure you show up tomorrow.
Note: Sign says "Yagami Station."
Now that I think of it, this is the first time I've had a part-time job.
I'm a bit nervous.
Alright, part-timers! We're starting soon!
Note: The back of their jackets say "Suou Engineering Group."
Wait, Akira hasn't come yet...
Why the heck are you here?
That's what I was going to ask!
I was asked by Akira...
I was asked by Suou...
to come...
I fell for it! What are those two plotting?
How am I supposed to face him looking like this?
Next, please unload the ornaments that are in the back of the truck.
We'll be decorating the tree. Please work in your groups.
Ah, no! I have to listen to the explanation. Concentrate...
Make sure to ask if you don't understand something.
Alright then, let's get started on today's tasks.
But what should I do if I don't understand something?
I can't possibly ask Hige for help.
Hey, did you see that girl with the blonde hair? Is she a model?
Yeah, I wonder why she's doing a job like this...
She's really cute!
Hey, I'll carry that for you.
Eh?
It's pretty heavy, right?
No, I'm fine.
Is this your first time doing this?
Yes.
I thought so.
I'll teach you a few things.
Thank you.
Alright, it's time for a break!
It's food! Food!
Hige, may I sit next to you?
Part-time jobs are pretty interesting.
I was wondering what I was going to say to Akira and Mikoto at first,
but it looks like I'll manage.
Hm...?
What?
Nothing.
If you have something to say, then say it!
I said that it was nothing, didn't I? Stop pestering me!
Hey, you were the one who...
...deceived me...
But Hige actually managed to change some things for the better.
Maybe I should be grateful.
Still, he should have told me who he was.
I mean...
Huh?
What? You couldn't say what you wanted to say either.
Then again, I guess it's better than someone who just speaks randomly.
But,
I will have nothing to do with you anymore.
Sorry.
He really is the worst after all, this Hige.
Note: Green advertisement says "English classes."
Pink advertisement says "Credit."
Hmph, I've finally realized it. Being around you always causes trouble between Tenma-chan and me...
Eri-chan!
Huh? Tenma?
Note: Sign says "YAGAMI Tourist" and
below it says "Trip to Izu"
You're working part-time too?
I'm meeting with someone.
My premonition was right on!
Ojou is a jinx. There's no doubt about it.
It's pretty rare to see you working part-time, Eri-chan.
Yeah, it's my first time.
How is it?
It's quite interesting. More so than I expected.
I see. You're so talented.
Mikoto introduced me to this. Also, for some reason, Hige is here.
Eh, Harima-kun? That's awful.
He really is the worst, that Hige.
You think so too?
Of course.
He's violent.
Yeah, yeah.
He's rude.
His feet smell.
Yeah, yeah.
And I've never seen him wear anything other than his school uniform.
I'm in the worst possible situation again!
Not to mention that he'll go after any girl he sees.
You should be careful too, Eri-chan.
Eh?
I've already said that it's a misunderstanding, Tenma-chan!
Somehow, I doubt that.
But that time when he came over...
I don't know what happened, but did you confirm your theory?
Eh? Now that you mention it, he might have been shouting something back then...
Although he's quite the outrageous guy, I doubt he'll do something that's completely unreasonable.
Huh? Is Ojou covering for me?
I've got no idea what's going on, but nice one, Ojou!
She's right, Tenma-chan. Everything that has happened is all a misunderstanding!
I'm here.
Akira-chan, you're late!
You were meeting with Akira?
You came here on purpose, didn't you?
What do you mean?
Ah, I hate you all!
Good morning.
Huh?
No one's here.
Hm...
Did I misread something?
Ah, it's from Takano-senpai again.
Good morning, Sarah.
You are currently in the clubroom of the old building, correct?
Eh?
A perplexing mystery and a wonderful present are waiting for you in the classroom on the second floor.
Make haste.
Is this the place?
I'm coming in.
Is this... the present?
Ara?
I can't get out. This isn't good.
Sarah?
Eh?
Yakumo!
Were you called here by Takano-senpai as well?
What are you doing?
Stop!
Huh?
You fell too.
Signs: Floor, Ceiling
Considering how old this building is, we probably broke through the ceiling of the first floor.
My feet are dangling.  It's a good thing that we didn't fall.
You were called here by Takano-senpai too, right?
Yes.
Christmas approaches. Fellow comrades, this is a challenge from your boss, me.
What could it mean?
We have no choice. Let's ask Takano-senpai.
~~Young one who can yet drink~~
Takano... senpai?
Yes?
What exactly are you doing here?
The Penguin Emperor...
It is a sad creature that gazes at the sun no matter how empty its stomach gets.
So basically, while you were playing around here in a penguin costume, you carelessly...
Here is my challenge.
Figure out how to get out of here.
Go.
It's from Nee-san.
Hello, Nee-san.
Ah, Yakumo? What are you doing right now? What's for lunch?
Um, I'm in a situation that makes it very hard for me to answer...
I'm on the second floor of the old school building, and there's a bit of trouble--
Really? I'm close by, so I'll come pick you up!
See you!
Nee-san, wait!
Is Senpai coming?
Yes.
I have a feeling that there's going to be a fourth hole in the floor soon.
Don't say that!
But considering the situation...
Yakumo, I'm here!
Ah, it's a penguin!
That was quick.
Nee-san...
Aren't you all the same? Say something earlier!
Is there anyone else we can rely on?
Oh, that's right. Yakumo, try calling for that person.
As long as you're here, he'll come for sure.
That person?
Reach him with your mind.
With my mind?
Where there's a will, there's a way. Try your best, Yakumo.
I guess it didn't work.
That's strange.
That reminds me... He said that he's getting new glasses.
Well, no wonder Hanai-senpai didn't come.
Eh? Hanai-senpai?
Were we wrong?
What should we do now?
Let's try calling Eri-chan and them.
Eri's at a party.
Mikoto's on a date with Asou-kun.
I see. That means that they can't come either.
But if no one comes to rescue us...
No! You'll die if you fall asleep, Yakumo-baachan!
Okay.
It's over for us...
Sarah-baasan!
And finally...
Hey! Why is she so big?
Because I'm a penguin.
By the way, no one has questioned my reason for being a penguin.
Rather than that...
How naive.
Why do you think I'm wearing this?
Don't tell me that you could have gotten out since the beginning?
SFX: Go go go go
This will make for a pleasing story.
Those interesting yet humiliating figures of yours...
I'll capture them all with my camera.
It appears that I have won this game.
You're a bit closer than before.
Now we've really run out of saviors!
We might be stuck like this until New Years.
That's...
If there's someone doing something in the classroom directly below, he might notice us.
On the first floor? During winter break?
Yes. For example...
For example, there might be someone who, although he has to finish a 120 page manuscript right away, got locked out of his own house, freeloaded at a classmate's place, got kicked out right away, and helped with an arranged marriage, made no progress on his manuscript. While being frustrated without any new ideas, he tumbled into the old school building to work on his manuscript.
For example, there might be someone who, although he has to finish a 120 page manuscript right away,
got locked out of his own house, freeloaded at a classmate's place, got kicked out right away,
and helped with an arranged marriage, made no progress on his manuscript.
While being frustrated without any new ideas, he tumbled into the old school building to work on his manuscript.
Text: There's no way someone like that exists.
There's no way someone like that exists.
Isn't that...
SFX: Go go go go
San-- Santa-san?
A gymnastics mat.
We're saved.
I wonder who that Santa was.
That's a trivial matter.
Yeah, he saved us. That's what matters.
Christmas has just begun.
That's right.
*Sneak sneak*
It's a good thing that I kept my part-time costume on.
Damn. Now I have to find a new place to work on this thing.
I definitely sensed Yakumo-kun's aura...
As I was saying, today is Christmas Eve.
Let's set off some fireworks here.
But look at the time.
Don't give up.
Oh, Harry, you...
Hey, what are you doing about tonight's party?
Who knows? Perhaps you should ask Tougou.
Hmph, the fun is in the surprise.
Oh, you always say that.
Tell us!
But it's lovely how he keeps it a secret.
There's no way. We're not cool like Harry and him...
I-- Idiot!
Are we not men?
If they can do it, there's no reason we can't!
Well said, boy.
Huh?
When a man stops walking, death is the only thing that awaits him.
If you don't want that to happen, then keep running.
Run recklessly. Recklessly!
Since you've realized your own weakness, I'll join your consultation.
I see. I understand now.
Alright, allow me to test the extent of your will, men.
There is a dance party at my house tonight.
Those who I've recognized as men are allowed in.
Are we really allowed to go?
As of now, you are only half a man.
If you want to come, then make my heart boil!
Note: Sign says "Yagami Station."
You're turning him down? What a waste.
Don't mess with me. What's that macaroni bastard trying to do?
Store
May I survey you for a moment?
No.
First of all, it's not like we'll die...
Shall I read your palm?
If we don't have girlfriends during Christmas...
Please, give me a minute to allow me to pray for you.
You! Do I look that miserable to you?
Well, it's in times like these that the dry crevices of your heart should--
They aren't dry!
I'll go, damn it!
Yoshidayama-kun!
We'll be reborn as good men and we'll show that Tougou!
Why are we all dressed up like Harry?
I guess... it's because he's cool?
And there's a limit to how low Nishimoto can go, you know!
Indeed.
Hm, you've reached this conclusion after all.
Tougou!
However, you are all making a great mistake.
Appearance alone will not bring you closer to us.
So we have to act like them too.
But what...
Harry-kun rides a motorcycle, right?
Maybe we should copy Harry-kun's favorite phrases as well.
Indeed.
That's your favorite phrase.
What about speaking in English?
DAS!
You really are an idiot.
What an awful potato... Interfering with your beauty...
Oh, you...
It's a joke.
Huh?
Amazing.
What kind of magic trick was that?
Here is your WAS set.
Stop right there, young lady!
It's an awful potato! We'll handle this...
The burgers are bad too!
The juice as well!
Give me back my lunch!
Hey, Nara, Nishimoto.
I've thought of something.
We're better off being ourselves. I'm sure of it.
Bravo!
Tougou!
Not following someone else's path, but cutting open your own path is what a true man does!
All of you have just become gentlemen!
Note: Amigo means "friend" in Spanish.
Hurry on to my party, amigo!
Eh?
Is this a dream?
No. We've been reborn!
Let's go all out tonight!
Okay. I'll be there right away. Bye.
Some urgent business has come up.
Ehhhhh?
Harry, you're leaving?
Don't worry. Tougou will keep you entertained.
Note: Bambino means "child" in Italian.
That is correct! Be at ease, Bambino!
Alright, let's have enough fun to make up for Harry's leave!
Huh?
It's as you see.
Apparently, everyone had some urgent business to take care of.
By the way, this tastes pretty good.
Haha, it does!
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
This is a dance party!
Let's dance!
I guess he's right. We practiced for it, after all.
I didn't get closer to any girls this year, but it was fun hanging out with you guys.
Yeah. Merry Christmas.
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Timer
PsycTint
Translator
DeiLight
Typesetter
Rina
Editor
Meltingice
Karaoke
Rina
Encoder
Meltingice
TL Checker
Cairan
Quality Control:
DeiLight
SSephirothT
Meltingice
Fansubbed by Nuke Fansubs
http://www.nuke-fansubs.com
Visit us at #Nuke @ irc.rizon.net
Nuke Fansubs' Timer, PsycTint, is offering his personal services
to the public. If you want to use him for any reason at all, you may do so by sending PsycTint a flaming bag of poop.
When it comes to Christmas, it has to be curry, right?
Yes, Karasuma-kun!
Next time on School Rumble Ni Gakki,
Here and there, it's all Christmas!
Dash for Christmas!
Break apart, Christmas!
Here and there, it's all Christmas!
Dash for Christmas!
Break apart, Christmas!
Christmas curry is the best!
Penguin Emperor,
Genus: Emperor Penguin.
Raising a child
is a tough job!!
See you next time!