It's been two weeks since I started flying.
There's no sign of land today, either...
Turbulence?! Not good!
The Southern Rainbow's 2-C!
The Mysterious Island's Yaakumo!
The Seven Seas's...!
School Rumble
is currently on winter break.
The super elegant and gorgeous
dream cruise.
This feels great.
But Sawachika,
bringing the whole class along...
You really go all out when you're set on something, don't you?
It's more fun with more people.
This ship is too big for its own good anyway.
I just thought, "Winter break is almost here. Why not go somewhere warm with everyone?"
Ichijou! Whenever it is, wherever it is, we can't forget about training, Ichijou!
Yes!
Hey, Tsukamoto.
Huh?
Come to think of it, is Karasuma not present?
Uh, yeah...
We should have forced him to come along.
But Karasuma-kun said he's visiting his relatives.
Oh, on that note, where's Harima-kun?
Eri-chan, what happened to Harima-kun?
Eh?
He was with us when we boarded the ship, right?
Where did Harima go, Sawachika?
Why would you possibly ask me?
I have no idea where Hige is.
Regardless, he's probably enclosed in a dark place and scared.
I finally got the chance to go on a dream cruise with Tenma-chan.
Why is the deadline for the thirty-page, special spring edition, appendix the day after tomorrow?
One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two.
Hmph, this reminds me of the blue skies of California.
Hey, are you sure it's in this direction?
Hmph, wait just a second.
There are no mistakes in my calculations.
Okay.
Let's go, partner!
Huh? Crap!
Ah, it seems like it thawed just fine.
This is pretty heavy.
Hey, can someone lend a hand?
Hige?
Leave the tuna to me.
Crap! I rode in a tuna fishing boat before, but all I did on it was draw manga.
I give up! I give up!
Geez. "Leave it to me," he says...
Masaru, take care of it.
I see. You handled the tuna well.
Well done, Masaru.
Big Catch
Amazing! The tuna is done!
I'll go check on things. I'll leave this place to you, Masaru.
You only need to watch straight ahead.
Don't look away to the sides.
Ah... I'm useless as usual...
Hey, what's that?
Isn't that Tougou and Harry?
They actually came.
Eh? You knew about this?
"If you don't mind, we'll head over in a canoe."
"We'll meet in the southern seas."
Southern seas... Sounds like a place where typhoons start.
Amazing!
All the way from Japan?
Oh, great job, both of you.
Huh?
Hey, you guys! Look! Straight ahead!
Rocks! This place has reefs!
What happened? Ahhh! Help!
Reefs!
Reefs, which have broken apart the hopes and dreams of countless sailors throughout history! Reefs!
A normal sailor would probably turn back now.
Why didn't anyone see it?
However, Tougou is here!
It's made with tuna. Try some.
Not even a siren's song nor a kraken's assault will cause us fear!
I shall then.
Masaru, what are you doing?!
Hey! There are reefs to the left, damn it!
Turn right!
Now, come! I will overcome you and reach El Dorado!
Go for it, Tougou!
We're out of luck. It seems like the engine broke down.
We're not getting any wireless signals either.
Are we out of ideas?
The cellphones won't connect either.
I wonder why?
We're probably in a special area of the ocean.
We're in a place where electromagnetic abnormalities occur, like in the Bermuda Triangle.
B--
Bermuda...
It seems like there is no choice but for us to seek help.
Nakamura, Masaru, be careful.
Save us!
Hurry up!
Goodbye!
1 Hour Later
Save us!
The Japanese cat series
in Shakujii Park.
I'm sorry, Yakumo-kun. There were still things I wanted to say to you...
I was saved?
Yakumo-kun?
Yakumo-kun! Why are you here?
Who... are you?
What am I...?
And where is this?
Yaakumo.
You--
At any rate, where in the world am I?
Although it's my first time here, this place feels familiar somehow.
I'm not going to say anything. I'm not going to say anything.
What are you doing here?!
I don't know. You're mistaking me for someone else.
Someone else?
You... understand Japanese?
I am Laala! I have lived in Japan before!
You look exactly like someone I knew from back then.
I thought you were him.
You want to go back to where your friends are, right?
Then go consult the queen.
Fellow Villagers!
The message of God has arrived.
Praise the Lord!     Praise the Lord!
That's Queen Eeri.
I imagined something like this, but...
Yaakumo should be here!
Tell her to hurry up!
The people here seem sort of menacing...
It seems like the preparation for this year's sacrifice was delayed.
She's the sacrifice this time.
What?!
Wait, wait, wait!
I don't know what's going on, but I'm not going to sit by and let this happen!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
Nonsense like sacrifices have no place in this scientific day and age!
Following the sudden turn of events,
we will show the rest of this show with dubbed voices.
You've done a terrible thing.
Now the village will be destroyed by the demon beast, Devil Tusk.
Then allow me, Hanai Haruki, to defeat this Devil Tusk!
As you wish, Hanaai.
If you want to save Yaakumo, head to the Kuuta Panda Forest on the night of the full moon,
and slay the demon beast, Devil Tusk.
This Kuuta Panda Forest is where the sacred protector of our village, Kuuta Panda, sleeps for long periods of time.
It's said that if our village met with calamity, it will awaken again.
Calamity?
But this has now become the place where Devil Tusk dwells.
I see...
This is bad!
Devil Tusk is coming!
It's finally here.
Just what kind of monster is...
Hanaai, I don't think...
I--I--I--I--It's fine!
L--L--Leave it to me!
Damn!
I won't let you hurt Yaakumo-kun!
Hanaai! Kuuta Panda... Kuuta Panda is...
Yaakumo-kun, don't believe in gods! Believe in me!
Those eyes... Where have I seen them before?
Could the key to moving this god be...?
Kuuta Panda awoke!
The village has been saved thanks to you, Hanaai.
Thank you.
No, it wasn't much.
Um, Hanaai...
My father told me to marry you.
Eh?!
And then forever on this land...
Yaakumo-kun?! This is too sudden...
Hanaai?
Thank you, Yaakumo.
Goodbye, everyone!
Goodbye!
Hanaai... Take care.
I dreamed that Yakumo became Yaakumo.
Eh? Yaakumo? I had one like that, too!
I--I was the queen!
Eh? Really?
Why the hell was Hanai in my dream?
Seriously...
Hey!
Huh? Hanai? Is that Hanai?
Hey! Hey!
You're right! It's Hanai!
What happened?
Ahhh! It's Hanai!
So he has been flying since two episodes ago.
Perhaps he can save us.
Yes! You managed to revive Kuuta Panda! This is nothing for you!
Hey! Hanai! Hanai!
Well, what a coincidence! I would never have expected to see you guys here.
What were you doing up there?
What I was doing? Well, I wanted to go back to Japan,
but the kite wouldn't really obey my orders properly.
In other words, you were stranded on it.
Bingo!
Along the way, I arrived at a mysterious village,
revived Kuuta Panda,
and defeated Devil Tusk.
I can understand if you can't quite believe me right now though.
Anyway, what are you guys doing here?
This ship hasn't moved at all since I saw it.
Note: "Stranded" and "I see" are said in a similar way, so there is a pun here.
Could it be? You guys are stranded, too? Ah, I see...
Ahaha! Just kidding!
Ahahahahaha--
I'm right?
1 Hour Later
Who would have thought all the food is gone...
Is it over for us?
No, Imadori-san, don't give up.
Let's think about something fun.
Something fun...
One, two.
Then there's the number three.
Like this, three fell on its side.
Mama! The number three looks like breasts to me!
Yeah, breasts, breasts.
Gah! Why?!
Why you... You pervert!
Hey! What are you all moping about?
Stand up! Never give up!
You have too much stamina...
I feel weak.
I haven't eaten a thing for a whole day.
This is exactly the kind of time when I want to be of use to Tenma-chan, but...
Isn't it getting sort of cold?
Yeah, you're right.
1 Hour Later
It's okay, Yakumo.
Onee-chan is with you.
Even if help never arrives, as long as I'm with Nee-san...
I said all that... but I'm still hungry.
No way! Karasuma-kun?
That couldn't possibly happen.
But even if it's an illusion, I'm happy to see Karasuma-kun.
Eh? What? What is it, Karasuma-kun?
Yes. I see. You're telling me not to give up.
I got it, Karasuma-kun. I won't give up.
Harima-kun.
That's right, we can't give up.
Let's do whatever we can.
Everyone...
Thank you, Karasuma-kun!
Alright!
I'll go check the engine.
Then I'll go too.
I'll go fish for food.
Yeah!
We'll make it move with love! Let's go, Ichijou!
Eeeh?!
What is it this time?
Damn!
It's a whale!
W--Whale?!
Here it comes!
It's over!
Everyone, get down!
Imouto-san, quickly!
We're done for!
Eh? A song?
Who would have thought that the whale fell in love with Imouto-san at first sight?
Thanks to that, it's saving us right now.
Yeah, everything turned out just fine.
Whale-san! Keep it up!
Alright! To Japan! Let's go!
South Pole
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Translator
DeiLight
TL Checker
alchemist11
Karaoke
Rina
Timer
PsycTint
Editor
Typesetter
Encoder
Meltingice
Quality Control
SSephirothT
Ojou-sama!
Who might you be?
Next Episode
Alone...
An old album...
An unchanging roof...
Aren't You Romantic, Harima-kun!
A changed self...
Is that really okay?
You're Appearing in Jingama, Harima-kun!
Alone...
Come on, Harima-kun!
Raising a child
is really hard work.
He has become
so magnificent.
See you next time!