Tsukamoto Tenma is a cyborg.
More than a friend...
Yet, not a lover...
Before that...
By gathering everyone's courage, Collision Combination, Unprecedented...
1 plus 1 is 2
2 plus 2 is 4
Unprecedented Robo
Dojibiron!!
Ichijou's Home
Nee-chan, Nee-chan!
Today's the Dojibiron ofukai! You didn't forget, right?
Note: "Ofukai" is a term that is used when people who come to know each other through the Internet meet up in real life.
Hm? Ofukai?
I guess you're right.
Sorry, Onee-chan's worn out from her part-time job, so let me sleep today.
What?
Hmph, whatever.
We'll be playing in the room.
What? You're inviting him over?
Of course, I'm the coordinator.
Hm, the elementary schoolers these days are really something.
I don't need it. I don't need it.
You meet lots of people you don't know on the Internet, don't you?
What if someone weird comes?
It's Dojibiron Blue, the one who's always writing to us.
Hm... He's the guy that's pretty friendly with you, right, Kousuke?
How old is he?
He just uses hiragana, so he's probably younger than I am.
Really? That's fine then.
Make sure you keep it down.
I know, I know.
Alright, Onee-chan's going to sleep for a while.
Okay.
Coming.
Eh, I--Imadori-san!
Ichi-san, will you go out with me?
Eh? Uh... But um... Is it really alright that it's with me?
Ichi-san... No, Karen...
It seems like I've lost to you.
Take this!
Ah, so that's what you did... What should I...
Owww... Huh? Huh? A d-dream?
Hey, Blue, you lost.
Why did I have a dream like that?
Awww. Wait, wait. That last one didn't count.
But it was a nice dream.
Alright, let's go for another round.
You really don't know when to quit.
Note: Imadori mistakes "oujougiwa" (knowing to give up) with "ogyougi" (manners).
They're really noisy.
Huh? Why? I have good manners.
I said you don't know when to quit!
Hey, Kousuke! Keep it down a bi--
Alright, it's time for a comeback with Unprecedented mode.
This!
Hey, Nee-chan.
Huh? Nee-chan?
W--W--W--W--Why?
W--Why is I--Ima...
What's wrong, Nee-chan?
He's Dojibiron Blue.
Ahh!
What?! Imadori-san is...
But you said he was younger than you are!
Before that, why do you know his name?
W-Why? Because he's a guy in my class!
No way! This hilarious guy?
Nee-chan's so lucky.
W--Wait, first...
Huh?
We have to do something!
Do what?
I don't know! Do something!
There, there.
Ahh! The dirty clothes are everywhere!
Who cares? It's just dirty clothes.
Just come help me already!
Hurry up and fold them.
Put them away! Put them away!
Ichi-san, what about this?
Um, that goes in the bottom-most drawer.
What are you doing, Imadori-san!
Well, I thought I should help out, too.
Wait, why do you have such a big one?
That belongs to my mom!
Wow, Ichi-san's mom has a nice body?
I found Ichi-san's pajamas.
G--Give those back, please!
Ah, Ichi-san, aren't these dumbbells a bit too heavy? I can't lift them.
You're lying! You're lying! They're only five kilos!
Target
Hm, your target is the first half of the forties?
A bit more and your diet will be a success.
Keep it up.
Target
Stop looking!
You're the worst, Imadori-san!
Hehe, I got called "the worst" by Ichi-san.
Stop it already!
Nee-chan, forget about that and let's play pretend Dojibiron.
You'll be Pink, like you always are.
Oh, Ichi-san's Pink sounds pretty strong.
Ichi-san.
It's okay. Just do it like you always do.
I'd like to see that Ichi-san as well.
Imadori-san...
Then... Then just for a bit...
Yay!
Collision!
Combination!
Dojibiron!
Episode Thirty-four:
The Massage Monster Ryuusan and the Hidden Trap in a Three-Night, Four-Day Field Trip - Second Half.
Whoa!
Choosing the phantom in the thirty-fourth episode... You know your stuff!
Ahhh, a massage after a bath is the best.
My body...
Keep it together, Squad Member Kousuke!
Damn it, I'm mutilated after the massage...
Muahahahaha, you're next.
Oh, this is where Ryuusan jumps in!
I'll suck your fighting spirit out, too.
Momi, momi!
Note: "Momi, momi!" is "Massage, massage!"
What should we do, Squad Member Karen?
I won't let you!
Take this! Unprecedented Hammer!
Ohhh, you have some skill, Dojibiron.
As expected of Ryuusan. He's tough!
One plus one is two.
Two plus two is four.
If one more were to come out,
Five! Five, five, five!
Doryaa!
Soyaa!
I'm sorry about the ruckus today.
However, if you told me beforehand that you were coming, I would have been better prepared.
Come by again, Blue.
Sure. I'll be back, Kousuke.
Don't cause trouble for your sister.
Ah, shut up.
Hey, Nee-chan, why don't you go out with Blue?
Just kidding!
Huh?
Hm...?
Hey, Nee-chan, isn't this mask the one that Blue brought over?
Huh? But I thought I just saw Imadori-san put that in his pocket...
The sound recording and angle are both set.
Alright, we're good to go.
All that's left is to turn the camera around.
Thank you. You came to help even though it's winter break.
Don't worry about it. It's just some good will from a fellow band member.
It's cold out here. You can go back to the clubroom if you want.
I'm fine. This is the only time I'll have to look at the stars anyway.
Next year will be our third. Are you planning to go down the astronomy path, Yuuki?
Eh?
Note: High school in Japan is split into Social sciences and Natural sciences. She says she can't take the astronomy path because she is part of the social sciences group.
I like the stars, but I'm a social science student.
I see.
Wow, it's freezing.
It has really gotten cold today.
I brought some snacks.
Hm? Did I tell you about today's meeting?
I asked him to come lend a hand.
I see.
Whatever. Let's eat.
As expected of Sagano. You're quite the thoughtful one.
Well, I am the daughter of a Japanese cuisine restaurant owner.
Voila!
Well, now that we're all warmed up,
let's begin this year's telling of love stories.
Eeh? Since when did that become a tradition?
Think about it. If three girls are gathered in a place like this at the end of a year,
what else is there to talk about?
Hey, I'm here too, you know.
They didn't hear me at all...
Then what about you, Sagano?
Hehe, it's about time you asked.
I've matched up a total of ten couples this year.
It's a new record.
You're so sly.
That's one part of you that has never changed.
Well, you haven't changed much either, Ichijou.
Do you think so too? Somehow...
While I was sitting around doing nothing, the whole year passed.
That's not true. Lots of things must have happened to you too.
Like when you sang in front of Imadori-kun, and when you called Imadori-kun to your house.
N-No! That was Kousuke's doing.
It's okay. The fact is that Ichijou tried her best.
What about you, Yuuki? How was your year?
Hm?
I... didn't really do anything in particular.
Watching you people shine brightly along with the stars... I guess that's all I can manage for now.
But man, it really has gotten cold. I'll go buy some coffee.
Eh?
You all want some?
Stop.
Oh?
Leave that to us.
You two should just wait here.
These chances don't come often.
This might be my eleventh.
Right?
That was sort of a weird misunderstanding on Sagano's part.
Really? I'm quite fine with it.
It's okay. I'll pass.
I guess that didn't work.
I don't like that air of confidence around you.
No, no. Despite what you may think, I'm actually quite the naive guy.
I know what you're like. You're very conscious of the public eye, and you desperately try to conduct yourself properly.
Even so, you're still dishonest and insincere on the inside.
Hahahaha, that's harsh.
So that's what I look like to you.
Just because I'm a plain social science girl doesn't mean I want to be looked down upon.
Did... something happen today?
What do you mean?
I don't understand you at all.
That part of you is really cute.
Those words... You've said them to Sawachika-san as well, right?
Well, it wasn't only to Sawachika.
Every girl in love is beautiful.
I can see that.
That's why you're taking those pictures, right?
Nope. It's the opposite.
I wanted to capture that beauty in my pictures.
But they never come out properly.
I'm a lucky guy.
I'll live on knowing that no one but I can see that beauty and I'll always have it all to myself.
You seem to be trapped in a spiral today.
A spiral of sound and light.
Stop that dubious fortune telling.
H--Hey, Suou!
Come on, let's go over there.
Hey!
Ah, I found a star.
Yeah. It's so far...
Hey, what do you think of the new chief?
Eh? U-Um...
I think he's fine. He's pretty handsome, too.
It's a huge step up from the perverted old geezer we had.
Although his taste in clothing is debatable...
Yeah, it's black.
Maybe the black is part of some cultural dress?
Isn't black fine?
Heh heh...
What?
Well, you know...
Yeah...
Tenma, don't tell me it's love at first sight?
W--W--What?
I'm thirsty.
Ah, I'll go make some tea.
Hey, just a minute!
I don't like her.
She's quite cheeky for a newcomer.
How can she seduce her superior?
Text: Saboka
I think it's time for the customary welcoming for new members of the Cyborg Department.
I'm Tsukamoto Tenma, a newcomer at the cyborg department, commonly known as Saboka.
Sign: Currently Boiling
I've only been allowed to prepare tea so far, but
with this 10,000 yen per 100 grams of tea,
Note: 10,000 Yen is about $100 USD.
I'll win over Chief Karasuma's heart!
Get out of the way!
The truth is that I don't have any memories from over half a year ago.
In other words, I have amnesia.
Without a single relative, I drowned in loneliness.
That was when Yakumo-oneechan held out her hand.
Yakumo-oneechan is probably the oldest,
so I affectionately call her Onee-chan.
This is the super ojou-sama-like Eri-senpai.
This is the extremely large-breasted Mikoto-senpai.
This is the cool, tomboy-looking Akira-senpai.
It feels great to be surrounded by these people. I'm trying my best!
This girl is...
Tea Serving Chart
Names from left to right:
Sawachika Eri, Suou Mikoto, Tsukamoto Yakumo, Tsukamoto Tenma
Hey, Chief, let's have dinner at the hotel tonight.
I spilled it...
Hmph, go remake it. While you're at it, make one for me too.
Eri-senpai...
Pushing people around just because you have some extra cash...
Take this! And this!
What in the world was I doing?
Well, whatever.
This time, I'll make Chief Karasuma drink my tea of love.
Chief! Eri-senpai! The tea's ready!
Chief, how do I write these documents?
Getting all cocky just because your breasts are a bit bigger...
Take this, and this, and this!
Again?! What was I doing?
Could it be because of something in the past that I don't remember?
No way!
Hehe. This time, I'll make sure you drink it.
The tea's ready, everyone!
G-Gyooo!
Even Y-Yakumo-oneechan!
I--I believed in you!
N--No, this is... I had no choice...
It's the customary welcoming party for newcomers.
W--What part of that is...
Ah, Tenma!
So this is the rumored bullying of newcomers at Saboka!
Left: Cyborg Department
Right: Cyberterrorism Department
Hot...
Tenma-chan's tea...
Should we do it?!
What?
Should Sabaka have a welcoming party too?!
Note: "Sabaka" is the name for the "Cyberterrorism Department."
Why the hell did I end up as your superior?
No matter how you look at it, you two should obviously be in the cyborg department!
That's... so mean...
You... made Ichijou cry!
That bastard, bullying around my dear Tenma-chan...
Unforgivable!
Huh?
*Sweat* *Sweat*
Not you, you dumbass!
W--Wait, Lala-san, he's choking!
What's wrong?
Akira-senpai.
Yo.
I see... So that's what happened.
I'm a clumsy, stupid turtle.
Heh, that's not like you at all.
Eh?
The girl I know as Tsukamoto Tenma is...
...a good girl who's always cheerful, overly energetic,
and has enough overflowing vitality to share with other people.
No way... That's just a show.
Whatever it is, you cannot deny the fact that everyone is motivated by that vitality.
See?
Ah, Yakumo-oneechan. Everyone!
Tenma, I'm sorry.
We meant it as a joke. My bad, my bad.
Come on, you too.
Um, ahem... I-It was our fault.
H--Huh? What's going on? My eyes are watering for some reason.
Yes. It was peaceful up until this point.
However, there is something I must tell her,
even if it means ripping apart that moment of happiness.
Tsukamoto-kun.
Chief K-Karasuma!
There is something I must tell you.
I'll never forgive you, Karasuma. What the hell are you trying to...
Chief Harima! Hurry up and finish your work!
Shut up! I'm doing something important her--
What's going on?
Something has infiltrated the network! It's trying to destroy the network!
Everyone, move out.
Understood!
Hold it, that's my department, you know!
Roll call.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six!
Seven.
Again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six!
Seven.
An unprecendented crisis presses upon us.
You are the only ones who can remedy the situation.
Let's move.
Understood!
Wait, damn it! I said that's my job!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I've been waiting for you, my dear cyborg girls.
Professor Hanai!
Today will be the day I delete you all!
Go, my minions!
No!
Hey, don't sting me there!
Um... This is quite troubling...
No! Please, stop it!
Bring it on!
E--Everyone!
Tsukamoto-san...
Surmount our...
Deaths and...
Go.
Everyone... really liked you.
TENMA!
I'll carry on the spirit of your lives.
Now I can fight with determination.
Hold on, Tsukamoto-kun.
There is something I must tell you before the final battle.
Could it be... about my forgotten past?
Your socks still don't match.
I haven't screwed up in so long!
Then just what actually happened to her in the past?
Could it possibly be that time?
No, I want to go back!
Damn it, do you have no self-awareness as a cyborg?
Come with me already!
Ah!
Eh? She's pretty cute.
Eh?
Could that be what caused her amnesia?
Yup.
Well, it happened after I, the genius, modified her, so she was fine but...
she went missing afterward.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Unforgivable.
Eh? What?
I'll never forgive you...
...for toying around with a maiden's pure heart!
Note: "Otome" means "Maiden"
Tenma's maiden circuit is responding! It's activating the Su--bot!
Lowest Underground Level
Third Hanger
This moment... It has come at last.
Final Decisive Battle Weapon
Suga-Robo
Now... is your time.
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Translator
TL Checker
DeiLight
Cairan
Timer
Meltingice
Karaoke
Rina
Editor
Meltingice
Encoder
Typesetter
Meltingice
Quality Control
Valorbreak
SSephirothT
Special Thanks
[G2]Abarnes
H--Hey, you're still not finished buying stuff?
Come on, just keep it up for a bit longer.
Huh... I wonder whose toy this is?
What's that supposed to be?
Who knows?
But it looks lonely.
Alright. Time to go for another round!
Think a little bit about the guy carrying the bags!
Let's go eat some ramen. Let's go eat some ramen.
I don't need any. I don't need any.
Yakumo, is the soba done yet?
The "Three Who Were Slashed" End-of-the-Year Super Special is about to start!
Yes, it's done, Nee-san.
Nothing beats this on New Year's Eve.
Soba. Soba.
...It's Sukuran.
......It really is Sukuran.
.........I said it's Sukuran!
Yakumo, you too!
Soba. Soba. Soba!
The man's name is
Suga Ryuuhei.
A member of the basketball club,
and Asou's close friend.
See you next time!