This is Yuurei-chan and Otama-chan.
Behind Yuurei-chan, there is always Otama-chan.
The two are always together.
Aren't You Romantic, Harima-kun!
You're Appearing in Jingama,
Harima-kun!
Come on, Harima-kun!
Harima Kenji
Jingama's spring edition
special thirty-page appendix,
is earnestly being worked on.
Damn.
Thanks to the whole drifting incident on the ship, I didn't get any work done on the manuscript.
I'm terribly sorry. Please give us one more hour.
W--Why?
Your manga is too realistic.
Go draw me something that I can actually publish next time.
That's easy for you to say.
But I didn't root it in reality this time,
so it'll probably be fine.
Come to think of it, Imouto-san sure is late.
She said she would be here before six o'clock.
Oh, she's finally here.
Uh, sorry, Imouto-san, but can we quickly get start-
Hey there!
Te... T-T-T-T-T-T-Te...
W--Why is Tenma-chan here?
Harima-kun, open up!
Yakumo couldn't make it so I'm here in her place!
I brought some snacks.
I can come in, right?
Oh. Yeah, o--of course.
I'm coming in!
I--Itoko's shoes!
Huh? What's going on?
I-It's nothing. I just haven't moved around much recently, so I'm getting some exercise.
Ah, I see.
Alright, I'm finished.
Wow. Harima-kun, you live in a pretty nice place.
I... I guess so.
Do we have a guest over, Kenji-kun?
Eh?
Is someone there?
N--No way! It must be the television!
The workroom is over that way.
I'll go make some tea, so wait here for a bit.
Sure.
That was way too close for comfort.
Who would've expected Tenma-chan to show up all of a sudden?
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity.
I--Itoko!
You said that on purpose, didn't you?
I seem to be an annoyance here, so I'm going out for a bit.
I'm leaving the two of you alone. Try your best.
The two of us alone together...
S--S--S--S--S--Sorry it took so long, Tsuka--Tsuka--Tsuka--Tsukamoto.
Amazing! You can see Yagami High School from here! Ah, you can see Yagami Bridge, too!
Isn't it romantic, Harima-kun?
I... I guess so.
Damn it, my heart is racing.
It really makes your heart race, doesn't it?
I mean, it's my first time ever being a manga assistant.
I have to try my best.
I... I see. That's right.
Is this the manuscript?
N--No, you can't!
Eh? Why?
W--Why, you ask?
A pro's pride doesn't allow him to show people unfinished works that he's not happy with.
I see. That is truly the way of a pro. How admirable.
Yeah, I'm just going to clean it up a bit. You go sit down and have some tea.
Sure, I got it.
This is bad. If she sees this, she's going to get everything. My feelings are blatantly obvious in here.
Tsukamoto, is Imouto-san busy with something?
I don't really know either, but she just said she was busy.
I see.
That's strange. Imouto-san didn't sound like she was busy during the phone call this morning.
I mean, this is the really intellectual Imouto-san we're talking about.
Wouldn't she have told me beforehand if something had come up?
Alright. With this, I'm probably safe.
But it sure was a surprise.
What was?
You really can't judge a book by its cover.
I never would have thought that you were drawing manga.
Yeah... I guess so.
You know, I was really touched by the last manga you drew.
Eh?
I guess I have a better opinion of you now, Harima-kun.
I... I see! This is just like a dream!
Harima-kun, you're wonderful.
I think I'm in love with you.
I wanted to be by your side so much that I forced others out of the way just to come here.
So that's how it was.
Alright, now since it's settled, I have no choice but to attack.
But then again, it's sort of embarrassing to suddenly confess to her since she just arrived.
I should indirectly show her some signs.
Alright!
Okay. I'm counting on you to be my assistant, Tsukamoto.
Yay!
I'll first give you a brief overview.
This is a story of a man and a woman who were aboard a cruiser that met with a storm and drifted off.
I see, I see.
This is the main character.
Yeah, yeah!
And this is the heroine.
Yeah!
Do these two remind of you of anyone?
Hm?
Ahhh!
T--These two are...
Y--Yes, they are...
The two who appeared in the last manga!
So this is a continuation of that story!
Yeah... That's right.
I guess there really is no way but to say it directly to a thick-skulled girl like her.
Hey, Tsukamoto.
What?
A work often unwittingly shows the personality and thought process of the author who created it.
Hmmm? Is that so?
This manga is like that as well.
This is my very soul.
Tsukamoto, this main character is me!
On top of that, I'm in love with this heroine!
And this heroine is none other than--
Who the heck?
How are you doing, Kenji-kun? Did you successfully manage to confess to Tsukamoto-san?
Go mind your own business!
Really, don't call me at the worst possible time.
Wow, Harima-kun's ring tone is the theme song of "The Three Who Were Slashed?"
Eh?
Mine is, too.
R--Really? What a coincidence!
Yeah!
Oh no!
What... What's wrong?
There is a special episode of The Three today!
It has been showing for over half an hour already!
Whatever shall we do?! If we missed the beginning, we wouldn't be able to follow the plot!
That's right! Yakumo might have recorded it!
Really?
Wait, I'll text her.
Yes! Look!
A blunder, there
was not, Nee-san.
Oh, that's Imouto-san for you! She's always prepared!
What a relief. I'll lend it to you later, Harima-kun.
Yeah, thank you!
Were you playing outside, Iori?
I asked Nee-san to go help Harima-san with his manga today.
I've been thinking about it for a while, but isn't Harima-san...
Did Karasuma show up at Tsukamoto's party?
Eh? Oh, right. After the party, he came to our house directly instead.
I see.
Text: Mellow Mellow
I'm really pumped now!
Could it be that Harima-san loves Nee-san?
But Nee-san is completely oblivious to that fact.
I wanted Nee-san to look at Harima-san more.
It's not good to be naughty.
This is...
Nee-san during her middle school years.
The best episode has to be episode eighty-nine:
"Goodbye, The Three! The Evil Flowers of the Roads of Kamakura in Full Bloom!"
Yeah, yeah! Mangoku's fight was the best!
But you can't forget about episode forty-three.
Oh, "Lovesick in Nakasendou While Shouting, 'Come on! Come on!'," right?
That really brings a tear to your eye.
Yeah, yeah. The guest appearance of Kiku-chan was a really nice touch, too.
I didn't expect it, but Tenma-chan really knows her stuff.
We're totally compatible with each other.
But I had no idea.
Who would have thought that you are a Mangoku fan?
I didn't think that you're a Mangoku fan either.
We're really compatible with each other, aren't we?
Te... Tsukamoto...
You're annoying! Stop calling me over and over!
Uh, Tazawa-kun? This is Mitsui.
Huh?
You sound pretty terrifying.
How is it going?
Uh, yeah, well...
I'm counting on you.
Please make sure you bring it tomorrow morning.
I'll try.
The chief has high hopes for you as well.
Don't let us down this time.
Try your best then.
What's wrong?
They're pressing for the manuscript.
When's the deadline?
Tomorrow morning.
Oh no! We have to hurry!
No, it's okay even if I don't make it in time.
Eh?
That's right. Now that you recognized me,
I need nothing more.
You can't give up, Harima-kun!
You have talent.
Besides, I really want to see your manga appear in Jingama.
Tsukamoto.
Since it has come to this, I'll keep you company until the very end!
Note: Tenma says "tsukiau," which literally means "to keep company with." However, it can also be interpreted as "to go out on a date."
Date...
The Harima Family's
You... You'll be with me?!
Yeah! Let's try our best!
Alright! Let's give it our best shot!
Yeah!
Onee-chan power.
You haven't changed a bit, Nee-san.
Title: The Lost Yuurei-chan.
This picture book...
Everything will happen after I finish this manga.
There's no need to rush.
We can take our time to work on our relationship after this is done.
That's what it means to go out with someone. Right, Tenma-chan?
Hey, Tsukamoto.
What?
If we finish this before daybreak,
do you want to go take a bike ride along the coastline?
Coastline?
The view of the morning sunrise above the ocean is beautiful.
Yeah, sure.
R--Really?
Color... Color...
How... How can this be?
I'll have to redraw it all!
I'm not going to make it in time like this!
Huh? Did I do something wrong?
No, not at all. Thanks a bunch.
Then what should I do next?
Eh? Uh, well, try sharpening some pencils for now.
Okay.
But I really understand what this main character is feeling. A one-sided love is really painful.
Eh?
Although when the time actually comes, it really is hard to confess your feelings, isn't it?
That... That's true.
That's why he might think it's fine just to be able to be by her side,
but it won't work out in the end unless he puts it into words.
He needs to be brave.
Sorry, Tenma-chan.
Even though you said you'd be with me...
It's really unmanly of me to not say it clearly to you.
I have to confess properly to Karasuma-kun, too.
Wait for it, Tenma-chan. I'll properly confess to you.
Tsukamoto.
Huh?
The truth is, I...
am sort of hungry.
Yeah.
I guess I'll go order some food.
I'll cook us something!
Ehhh?! No, it's fine!
Don't be so reserved.
No, that's not the point here...
Huh? Where are the condiments?
Huh? I don't know...
I have no choice. I guess I'll have to ask Itoko.
It looks like things are heating up.
If it's the condiments you want, then they're under the sink.
Oh, thank you.
Tsukamoto, the condiments are under the sink...
Wait, how the heck did you know?!
Did... Did she put a bug somewhere?
Let's eat!
Yeah, let's eat...
I guess I pretty much failed.
No, you didn't!
Thanks for the food...
I sort of want to wash away the taste.
Let's drink something.
How in the world is she capable of making something that awful?
It's almost an art.
However!
We both ate the same thing and shared the terrible taste!
This is a slight variation of the meaning of "going out!"
I made some coffee, Tsukamoto.
Huh?
Ah, I found it.
Title: The Lost Yuurei-chan.
This is Yuurei-chan and Otama-chan.
Behind Yuurei-chan, there is always Otama-chan.
The two are always together.
During mealtime,
"I don't want any more."
"Yuurei-chan, don't leave it unfinished."
During playtime,
"I want this."
"Yuurei-chan, that's the girl's toy."
Even when everyone is going on a trip,
"I want to go that way."
"Yuurei-chan, everyone is going this way."
"It's fine. I want to go that way."
"If you want to be with everyone, Otama-chan, then you can go with them."
"Will you be fine by yourself, Yuurei-chan?"
"Yes, I will be fine by myself."
Otama-chan has a lonely expression on her face.
But she won't say anything.
"I don't care about Otama-chan anymore."
Yuurei-chan trudged off on her own.
For how long do you plan to sleep, Tenma-chan?
Although, as a result, I made some decent progress.
Speaking of which, I've been in a similar situation before.
Now that I think about it, that was when everything started.
I love you.
From that moment on, you were...
I think this is going a bit too far, Pervert-san!
Sign: Pervert-san.
I've since worn sunglasses and grown a beard.
I've become a different person so I can move closer to you.
A lot has happened.
But this long drama will soon come to an end.
The finale of our relationship shall be a happy ending!
Wait, this is no time to be getting excited.
Work, work...
I can still eat lots more!
More food!
Really, she can't be helped.
Come on, Harima-kun.
N-N-N-No! I'm not that kind of guy!
T--Think about something else! Something else! Something else!
Come on, Harima-kun.
Go to Hell!
O--Oh crap!
I'll be your opponent this time.
I love you.
Yuurei-chan trudged off on her own.
Yuurei-chan trudged on and on.
"Ah, there are some flowers."
But there was no one behind her.
"Ah, it's a shooting star."
Still, there was no one behind her.
Yuurei-chan went home alone.
Even when she got home, there was no one there.
Even during mealtime, playtime, and cleaning time, she was alone.
"Otama-chan, where did you go?"
Yuurei-chan went to look for Otama-chan.
She asked the worm on the flower,
"Worm-san, Worm-san, where did Otrama-chan go?"
"Yuurei-chan, I'm so hungry that I can't move."
"I'll give you my food then."
"I saw Otama-chan gazing at the flowers."
"Thank you, Worm-san."
She asked the twins by the seashore,
"Hey, hey, did the two of you see Otama-chan?"
"Look, we only have one toy."
"I'll give you mine then."
"Wow, thank you."
"Otama-chan was looking at the shooting stars over there."
"Thank you, the both of you."
She walked and walked. Although everyone knows about Otama-chan, she is nowhere to be found.
"Where did Otama-chan go?"
Yuurei-chan finally cried.
The tears fell one drop after another, forming a puddle.
"Otama-chan, where did you go?"
Is this really okay?
Don't you love Harima-san?
Meltingice
Raw Provider
Translator
DeiLight
TL Checker
alchemist11
Karaoke
Rina
Timer
PsycTint
Editor
Typesetter
Encoder
Meltingice
Quality Control
Kruge
SSephirothT
Fui~~
Hey! Wait...
Next Episode
Wow, being a manga artist's assistant is really tough work!
Wait, Tsukamoto, didn't you just sleep the whole time?
It's because of this kind of hard work that the finished manga is interesting.
The manga's not done though.
Next time on School Rumble Ni Gakki:
Sesame-- Huh?
Duwaaa!!
No, that's not it!
It's a period!
The next episode is finally the last one.
In which direction will Harima's love go?
Note: "Taiga" literally means "big river," but can mean "epic" when used to describe an entertainment production.
The schoolyard Taiga anime,
Sukuran, is finally going to end!?
See you next time!