How is it? Did you finish the manuscript?
It's no good, Oyaji!
The rudder isn't working!
Fool!
You can go and weep after we've hit the shore!
G-- Got it!
I've done it, Oyaji! The engine's alive again!
H--Hey, look at this!
It's huge!
It's over! We're done for!
Men of the sea do not show their weakness.
It is exactly in times like these when men...
Laugh!
Oyaji...
Let's go, sailors!
Yeah!
Full speed ahead!
Laugh!
Boy, have you found your dreams on land?
Master...
Dash for Christmas!
Break apart, Christmas!
Here and there, it's all Christmas!
School Rumble
is already prepared for the season
The Christmas Festival
is currently on display!!
Hey, are you alive?
It's time to wake up.
It's nice that you've cooled down, but seeing Santa collapse on the street during Christmas is an eyesore.
I finished it.
Hey, don't get up so quickly.
I finished it... The manuscript.
It ended up being 20 pages.
You... What are you planning to do with that?
Heh... What else?
Although lots of things have happened with Tenma-chan...
SFX: Mellow mellow
You'll... be the first...
How bright.
Alright girls, it's almost done.
I wonder if it baked properly? How exciting!
Akira-chan, what did you make?
Something that would fit nicely inside a room.
By cooling it right after it was put in the furnace, cracks will appear, which further refines the creation..
Let's take a peek!
So this is what they call the "Aohibi" of the Oobori Souma Yaki from Nakamura of Fukushima Prefecture's Souma City.
One, two...
TL Note: "Aohibi" is type of Japanese pottery called "Oobori Souma Yaki", originating from Nakamura of Fukushima Prefecture's Souma City.
We did it! It's finally done!
It's a lucky charm.
Tenma, that's...
That's right. It's a Christmas present.
Hello?
Hey, Tazawa-kun?
How is it? Did you finish the manuscript?
Yes, I just finished.
What a relief! Alright, bring it over right away.
Eh? I'll bring it after I show someone.
What are you talking about? You won't make it in time if you do that.
Eh?
It's the end of the year, right?
The printing centers are up to their necks in work.
But... it's only for a moment.
You can't! You won't make it if you do that!
The chief is evaluating you too, so don't let us down!
It's not an exaggeration to say that your future rests on your work that's getting published this time!
Mitsui, phone call from the printing center. They're telling you to hurry the manuscript over.
Okay, got it!
Alright, so bring it over right away, okay? See you.
My future, he says?
I've never even thought about it. Did I ever have something like that?
Someone like me...
Why did I start drawing manga anyway?
I'm horribly bad at using my head.
Compared to those who were aiming for prestigious universities,
and those who were working hard on their art or music,
I thought I had no choice but to rot and wither away as I watched them from afar.
Do I have a future?
Get it
to the publishers
immediately...
If it's about Tenma-chan, then doesn't she have all the time in the world to read it afterward?
Hey, me! If you want this chance, you have to grab it now!
Sorry... Tenma-chan.
This snowfall will likely continue until midnight.
Furthermore, certain areas may see tremendous snowfall, so please be aware.
I'm back!
I was worried for a moment, but I managed to make it.
It ended up being sort of big. I wonder if Karasuma-kun will like it?
Eh?
Sorry. This was the one thing I couldn't give up after all.
Ten-- Tsukamoto.
What business do you have here?
You are forbidden from entering here, remember?
Going as far as lying about how you couldn't get into your apartment...
I don't even know what you're thinking anymore.
I... I can't.
I can't make her read the manga to convey my feelings.
It's hopeless.
If I mess up, she'll misunderstand again.
Misunderstand?
What am I afraid of?
Compared to the crappy life I had before encountering manga and this girl,
this is nothing!
Not to mention, there's nothing more important for me to protect.
Right, Kenji?
Tsukamoto... the truth is...
I've been drawing manga.
Go! Break me apart!
Liar.
Eh?
It's a lie! No matter how I look at you, you just don't seem like the type to draw manga.
No, I actually drew it. Here, look.
First of all, why are you even telling me this? How am I involved?
Well, Imouto-san was involved in various ways...
Yakumo was?
Please read it, Nee-san.
Is it true?
Ahem... It was interesting, I guess.
Alright!
Has spring finally come for me?
All that's left is to bring the manuscript to Dankousha.
It's a manuscript for Jingama, Nee-san.
Really? It's appearing in Jingama? Amazing!
I'm looking forward to it, Harima-kun!
Due to the extreme amount of snowfall, all lanes on the highway have been closed.
What happened?
Local blizzard at Yagami City
This just in. It seems that Yagami City is experiencing a local blizzard.
Let's hear from the reporter.
Ah, Iori! Look at what you've done!
Reporter Eiwa-san?
I'm on scene right now. Like the reports say, Yagami City is currently experiencing a tremendous amount of snowfall.
So far, there have been no reports of injuries...
I'm going to make it there on time no matter what. For Tenma!
Tenma's Curry Plate
Tch, there are too many obstacles.
Turn, damn it!
I love you, Tsukamoto!
Harima! Faster, Harima!
For the sole girl who he is devoted to in this world.
Ride on, Harima Kenji!
That was...
That was fun.
A skiing trip from time to time isn't too bad.
Senpai, didn't Kenji-kun just pass by?
What in the world is that idiot doing?
Hello?
The tea's ready, Nee-san.
That Harima-kun...
He should have said so from the beginning.
Now I look like an idiot for hating him.
I don't think so, Nee-san.
If you really hated him, you wouldn't say something like that.
What business have you here?
You are forbidden from entering here, remember?
Going as far as lying about how you couldn't get into your apartment...
I don't even know what you're thinking anymore.
A normal person would...
Is that so, Harima-kun?
A normal person would have been like this.
That unnatural tension causes relationships between people to go awry.
However,
However, no such thing exists between Tsukamoto Tenma and Harima Kenji!
no such thing exists between Tsukamoto Tenma and Harima Kenji!
For two people who are so divided, their relationship is unbelievably natural!
Nee-san...
That part of Nee-san is probably what Harima-san...
Yes? Eh? Miko-chan?
Huh? What's wrong?
Harima-kun is?
WHAT? Harima-kun was riding on my curry plate?
Yeah, I was really surprised too.
Anyway, Takano told me not to worry about it and to leave it to her. I wonder what she's up to?
Nee-san?
Sensei...
Get in the car.
Bring your sister.
I've already heard most of the story. She drives a bit recklessly though, that girl.
I don't do such a thing, Osakabe-sensei.
Dankousha
Alright, we will have a few words from the president shortly,
so please enjoy Dankousha's end-of-the-year conversational party in the meantime.
Man, what is Tazawa-kun doing?
The party has already started!
Dankousha End-Of-The-Year Conversational Party
What the heck?
Why did Santa fly in on a plate?
I didn't hear about an event like this.
Hey, someone call security!
Editor-in-Chief?
Is that a manuscript?
That Santa... He wrecked the party... The Chief's going to kill him!
Seems like he's finished reading.
I can't accept this.
Take it and go home.
You bastard, why!?
K-- Karasuma!
You... again!
I heard about what happened from Takano-san.
Calm down.
It looks like they're here.
Tsu-- Tsukamoto...
Merry... Christmas... Karasuma-kun...
Thank you.
Nee-san...
Don't tell me... The thing that I rode on was Tsukamoto's...
She made it.
Editor-in-Chief?
That manuscript...
Ahh, I can't publish this.
It seems like this manuscript was meant for only one person in this world to read.
You've got some good friends.
Tsukamoto...
Tsukamoto, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Tsukamoto.
All I wanted was to see her smile.
I wanted Tenma-chan to laugh.
That's... all I wanted.
Harima-kun.
But I...
I'm sorry, Tsukamoto.
Tsu-- Tsukamoto!
I'm really sorry... about the plate.
I misunderstood too.
Harima-kun, let's make up.
Sure.
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Timer
Floof
Translator
DeiLight
Typesetter
Valorbreak
Editor
Meltingice
Karaoke
Rina
Encoder
Meltingice
TL Checker
Cairan
Quality Control:
SSephirothT
Meltingice
The sun will always shine after a storm, eh, boy?
Merry Christmas.
Collision Combination! Dojibiron!
Let's go, Pink!
Got it!
Next episode, Unprecedented Robo Dojibiron!
More than a friend.
Yet, not a lover.
Before that...
But what a surprise! Ichi-san's mom is so...
More than a friend...
Yet, not a lover...
Before that...
a giant curry plate.
Tsukamoto Tenma makes,
It is about 5 feet in diameter.
It can fly as well!?
See you next time!