I love you.
Harima Kenji.
His chance has come!
Sukuran's last episode
is now starting~ is now starting~
Is this really okay?
Don't you love Harima-san?
T--That's...
You finally managed to find someone you love.
Are you sure this is okay?
B--But Harima-san loves Nee-san...
"That's why I wanted Nee-san to get to know Harima-san more."
Is it really okay for you to be so understanding?
Yielding your loved one to your sister... Will you be satisfied with that?
In the end, you are still alone.
And will always be alone.
Are you okay with that?
I--I'm...
You've said it before, right?
"I'll definitely fall in love with someone."
I thought that perhaps Harima-san was the one you were talking about.
Just what will it take to move your heart?
What do you see deep within yourself?
Yaa...
mo...
Yaamo...
Yaamo, where are you?
Nee-chan.
Yaamo!
What's wrong? Why are you mad, Yaamo?
How many times do I have to say it? Stop calling me Yaamo!
My name is Yakumo! I don't like being called childish names!
Especially by Onee-chan!
Ya... Yagu...
See? That's what I mean! That's why you're always made fun of by the other kids!
Sorry... Yaamo...
Stop calling me Yaamo already!
Yaamo.
I'll help you with your art homework.
It's okay. Everything you touch always turns into a failure.
Don't worry, don't worry. Here, give me it.
I was doing fine before too!
I'm sorry, Yaamo. I'm sorry.
Yaamo, it's clay next? Are you making a lion?
No! Definitely not!
Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. Your Onee-chan is good with clay.
It's okay. It's okay. I'm just about to make it into a cool lion.
Huh? What?
I told you... Onee-chan, you idiot!
Uh... Um... The book got dirty, so I wanted to make it clean.
Onee-chan, why do you always come near me?
Eh?
You can't do anything and you always get in my way!
Yaamo?
Don't come near me!
Eh?
I don't need Onee-chan!
I--I'm sorry. You know how the suits become clean if you wash them? That's why...
That's enough already!
Yaamo, here, I'll lend you my game.
It's the one you like, Animal Cro--
Give it back!
The book that Dad gave me...
No more... Someone like Onee-chan...
Dad!
Dad, read me this book!
Yuurei-chan finally cried.
The tears just kept falling, forming a puddle.
"Otama-chan, where did you go?"
"Yuurei-chan."
Yuurei-chan opened her eyes and saw Otama-chan in the puddle.
"Otama-chan! Are you in the water?"
"I'm always with you, Yuurei-chan."
When Yuurei-chan turned around, she saw Otama-chan sticking out of her.
Otama-chan was simply invisible and was always behind Yuurei-chan.
"Was Otama-chan by my side all this time?"
"That's right. I'm back, Yuurei-chan."
"Welcome back, Otama-chan."
Thus, with the two of them even closer than they were before,
they were surrounded by the many new friends they had made.
Why...
does Onee-chan always come near me?
I'm sorry,
Yakumo
You can't do anything...
Yet you always care for me...
Nee-chan...
The two of us were eventually left with only ourselves...
Nee-san must have been lonely too.
But Nee-san has always been kind...
and caring toward me.
Nee-san is the most important person to me.
That's why I wish for Nee-san to be happy.
Those words of yours... Are they the truth?
We'll meet again.
I love you.
This is almost...
exactly the same as that time.
Karasuma-kun...
No, there's a very good reason for this!
Y--You were sleep talking, and you said, "Duwa!"
Duwa?
Yeah, yeah, then you went for a full nelson.
Huh? I did?
There's no possible way I'd do something like that!
Liar!
I speak the honest truth!
H--Huh? Wait... I think I remember something...
Something like this happened in the past...
Um...
Ahhh! I remember!
Could it be that Harima-kun is the Pervert-san from that time?!
I'm right, aren't I? Confess!
Yes, you are.
It's just as you say.
I'm sorry I hid it from you until now.
I am the Pervert-san from that time.
You are after all!
Uh, no, wait! I am indeed the Pervert-san from that time, but I'm not a real Pervert-san.
That's a misunderstanding.
Lies! All of it!
Please, listen to me!
I know anything I say now will sound like an excuse,
but the reason I hid my true identity from you
was not because of guilt.
There's another reason behind it.
Another reason?
Yes. Your... I wanted to be by your si--
Dankousha
Man, what is it this time?
Yeah, hello?
Tazawa-kun? How are you doing?
Uh, fine.
I'm begging you here. We've been waiting all night.
By the way, did you hear? Something big happened.
Apparently, Nijou-sensei was involved in an accident.
The whole company here is in a riot over the news. What a shocker that is.
But that aside, keep it up on the manuscript. Bye.
Did something happen?
Eh? Uh, nothing.
Karasuma-kun...
No... Something did happen.
Tsukamoto, keep a cool head when you hear this. The truth is...
Karasuma was in an accident.
Let's go, Tsukamoto. To where he is.
How is this possible?
I'm stuck like this and forced to face a situation that I couldn't even dream of.
What... What should we do? Karasuma-kun...
Don't cry, Tenma-chan. Tears don't suit you.
Don't worry, Tsukamoto. He'll be fine. I'm sure of it.
Karasuma... If you make Tenma-chan cry once more, I'll never forgive you.
Let's ride! Hold on tight!
Nee-san, are you okay?
W--Why... am I...
I got a call from Harima-san and...
But thank goodness you only had minor injuries.
What about Karasuma-kun?
I'm right here.
Tsukamoto-san, are you okay?
K--Karasuma-kun...
Give me a break. I can understand your panic, but riding your motorcycle in the middle of a storm?
Quiet. I had no choice at that time.
Damn! Stop!
T--Tenma-chan!
F--For the moment, we made a safe landing.
But getting away with these injuries after a truck sent you flying is quite something.
As if I'd lose to a truck...
Our fighting spirits aren't even close.
Although, in terms of just fighting spirit, you've changed my opinion of you for the better.
At any rate, it's a good thing that Tenma-chan's fine.
That's right, what about Karasuma?
He's fine. He's currently talking to Tsukamoto-kun.
I see. That's a relief.
I guess this is as far as my love goes.
Be happy, Tenma-chan.
What a relief, Karasuma-kun! You're alive! I'm glad you're safe!
I--It's a relief that you're so healthy too.
Yeah... But Karasuma-kun... Weren't you in an accident?
Yes, I was.
I met Zico.
Eh?
The new term starts today, right? Really...
But you really go all out when relationships are involved, don't you?
It's over already.  Everything is.
Stop spewing nonsense and go to school already.
No, I'm never going to school again!
Shut up and go.
S-Save me!
Everything...
is over.
I came to this school because of Tenma-chan.
I have no regrets.
Hey.
Harima-san, what happened to your arm?
You know.
Was it a fight again?
Let's hear the story of your awesomeness!
Note: Withdrawal
The festival is over.
I see. It's over.
Hey, Tsukamoto.
Good morning, Tenma.
Good morning!
What did you do during your final break?
Did something interesting happen?
You know, it was incredible!
Tons of things happened.
Ah, Harima-kun!
Wait a minute!
What the...
What happened?
It's a harsh situation... For him, too.
Why are you running away, Harima-kun?
W--What do you mean, "Why?"
Now that my true identity is exposed, there's no way I can face Tenma-chan anymore.
Hey, I heard you met Zico.
Zico
Yes. I got his autograph, too.
Incredible.
Let me take a shot of it as a souvenir.
Zico
Okay, say "cheese."
Didn't you know?
The seventh of January is Ichijou's birthday.
Oh, is that so?
Speaking of birthdays...
Episode nineteen of Dojibiron: "The Enjoyable Birthday - The 2.29 Monster," right?
Wow, as expect of Ichi-san.
Damn it!
Hey, have you heard? 2-C's Takano said that Harima's running away with a secret photo of Tae-chan.
Are you serious?
Damn! I want a look!
As a gentleman, I can't overlook this one.
We cannot bear to see the saddened face of a lady.
Why the hell is every damn person here chasing me?!
That's an admirable running ability. One that makes you worthy of being my opponent.
Shut up! Don't get in my way!
Secretly taking unseemly pictures of a beautiful woman's figure...
What a deplorable action for a man.
Say whatever you want.
Harima-kun!
Don't... Don't come!
Why?
Why do you keep trying to avoid me?
You wouldn't see me when I went to visit you in the hospital either.
There's obviously no way I could see you!
You... Now that you know my true identity...
True identity? Whose?
Whose? Mine.
Huh?
Wait, what? You don't remember?
Remember what?
Well, yesterday's...
My memory is fuzzy for some reason...
I think something happened then...
It's okay. It's nothing you have to force yourself to remember.
That's a relief. I thought something was wrong with me.
How's your injury?
O--Oh, no problem. A light scratch like this is nothing.
Thanks for protecting me.
I'm really grateful to you, Harima-kun.
It wasn't all that much. Really.
Let's continue getting along, Harima-kun.
S--Sure.
Oh, that's right.
Label: The Three Who Were Slashed
Here.
The special episode of "The Three Who Were Slashed" that I promised you.
Let's enjoy it together again sometime.
Yeah, let's enjoy it together again!
See you!
Okay.
It's not over.
I can still keep going!
COMMENCEMENT
What happened, Tsukamoto?
Did something happen between you and Hige?
I'm not completely sure, but the issue is settled.
Hey everyone, I've got big news!
Apparently, Harima is finally dropping out--
Won't happen.
W--W--W--Won't... Won't happen!
Resetting is complete.
EXCURSION
COMMITTEE SELECTION
EVERY GROUP
EACH SELECT
ONE REPRESENTATIVE
Alright, it's finally been decided that the third term's excursion will be to England.
I'd like to figure out the committee members for it.
Too much trouble.
More importantly, let's decide on groups.
England, huh? Sounds pretty extravagant.
This will be the first time I board a plane.
I want to eat their sandwiches!
Okay, settle down. Stop your selfish ranting.
Hey!
Allow me to be the representative for the excursion committee!
Did he come back from the South Pole on a kite?
What are you looking at?
Amazing.
Could someone let me down from this kite?
Wait, that's not even possible.
Hey, my classmates!
When one speaks of the third term, one must think about excursions!
Let us polish our unrefined manliness with the drill of a gentleman!
Oh.
Someone!
Let me down!
Leave it to me!
Make a hole in the kite!
I failed.
Bravo! Bravo!
We shall rehearse the important parts of the pillow fight.
Text: Pillow Fight
Excursions are all about pillow fights, aren't they?
Oh, Nishimoto!
It's not like we're in a Japanese hotel.
Our male students are all idiots.
Akira-chan!
Wait!
Help!
Get a hold of yourselves, you crazy buffoons!
Mai-chan, calm down.
Label: The Three Who Were Slashed
Tenma-chan...
Karasuma-kun, aren't you looking forward to the excursion?
Yes.
It's already the third term.
It came pretty quickly.
Yes.
When I was a young child, I always thought that being a high school student was something in the distant future.
But right now, I'm passing the days one by one and getting closer and closer to becoming an adult.
Although I'm living through wonderful days right now,
I wonder what the distant future is like?
In your future, there will be me, your close friend.
That won't ever change.
Ever.
Right?
Yes.
We'll always... Forever.
Listen, Yakumo!
The excursion is to England! England, you hear?
Seeing UFOs at Stonehenge with Karasuma-kun...
Taking pictures with the palace guards at Buckingham Palace...
Looking at mummies in the British Museum...
And eating lots of roast beef and apple pies with Eri-chan and the others...
There's so much to do!
You're really looking forward to it, aren't you, Nee-san?
Hey, Dad...
Why are these pages all blank?
You see, these blank pages are magical pages where you're free to draw your future.
Magical?
What kind of future will you draw, Yakumo?
Even now, the smile from then still warms my heart.
And it always will... Forever and ever.
Even though it was expensive, Nee-san went and bought a new--
Property of Yagami Library
Keeping this book is forbidden
I... I have to return this.
Do it, Mangoku!
All the support that was received,
is greatly appreciated!!
Translator: DeiLight
Translation Checker: alchemist11
Timer: PsycTint
Raw, Editor, Typesetter, Encoder: Meltingice
Quality Control: SSepirothT, Kruge
Episode 26 Credits
School Rumble
will keep on running.
DeiLight: Translator, Typesetter, Quality Control
Cairan: Translation Checker
alchemist11: Translation Checker
PsycTint: Timer
Floof: Timer
Rina: Typesetter, Karaoke
Valorbreak: Typesetter
desani: Typesetter
SSephirothT: Quality Control
Kruge: Quality Control
Meltingice: Raw, Editor, Timer, Typesetter, Encoder, Quality Control
Thank you to everyone who has
worked on School Rumble Ni Gakki!
Finish.