He's... coming...
The Black...
Phantom!
Hmph, go back to your mom's place, kid.
You're still no match for the G Phantom.
My next prey... is an unfamiliar face.
Will you be enough to entertain me for a little while, Crimson Maiden?
She is constantly accelerating and preventing me from catching up.
Looks like I ran into a crazy woman.
It seems like this'll be one night that neither of us will forget, right, baby?
They're here!
Those two cars are amazing.
I've never seen anything like them.
What? She's speeding up at this point?
What lies ahead is a series of unpredictable left and right turns, known as the Yagami Winding.
It's the Door of Death that has swallowed countless drivers.
Does she have no regard for her life?
Unless... she's a true soul reaper.
The soul reaper's scythe is the phantom?
Damn it...
This joke isn't funny.
Hmph, you're on!
I'll follow you straight to the depths of Hell!
She yielded the path?
No, she slipped.
Has she become unable to endure the sea's wind blowing from the right anymore?
It looks like your light frame became a disadvantage.
Eat this!
Phantom Turn!
The... The morning sun?!
I see.
The moment of sunrise.
She planned this far.
There's still someone like you in Yagami...
This is why I still cannot graduate from the streets.
How many times do I have to tell you? Huh?
S--Sorry, Sui, I wanted to feel like I was a part of the match.
Your muttering in the back is annoying, you know?
Go get a license if you want to drive so badly.
It's great that we made it in time for the first sunrise of the year.
Yeah.
Year's First Dream
Lion Dance
New Year
Sukuran is already
in New Year's mood.
We will protect
Japan's traditions!!
It suits you, Nee-san.
Thank you, Yakumo! It fits perfectly!
I want to show it to Karasuma-kun.
I wonder if Karasuma-kun will go to the first temple visit of the year.
K--Karasuma-kun, Happy New Year.
Please take care of me this year too.
Happy New Year to you too, Tsukamoto-san.
Your kimono suits you very well.
R--Really?
Yes.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I didn't know you were this beautiful.
O--Oh, you're always joking around.
It's true.
Tsukamoto-san, close your eyes.
Karasuma-kun...
N--Nee-san? Wait a minute. What's wrong?
Nee-san! Nee-san!
Harima-kun!
Where is this?
What's going on?
Why am I here?
Harima-kun!
Tenma-chan!
I'm so glad, Harima-kun!
I finally... I finally found you.
Tenma-chan...
We'll always be together from now on, Harima-kun.
Y--You've finally accepted my love...
What bliss!
It's as if this is all...
A dream.
Wait, it was a dream. Damn it.
What kind of first dream of the year was that?
They say that the first dream of the year will come true.
Could it be that the dream I just had...
Alright!
If so, then it's time to go pray at the first temple visit of the year!
I'm counting on you, God!
Whoa, something very nice just happened!
It's the promised bra steal!
This is what swimsuit sumo is all about!
It's no understatement to say that this is a fight for which the girls put everything on the line!
Oh, Kenji-kun.
Youko-san. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year. Take care of me this year too.
Got it! Me too! See you!
What a noisy guy.
Wow, there are so many people!
I won't be able to find where Miko-chan's performance is located...
Are you okay, Tsukamoto-san?
Karasuma-kun?!
Left Stand: Starch Syrup
Right Stand: Fortune Lottery
Be careful. It's hard to move in a kimono.
You're right! It's hard to move! Hahahaha...
A--Are you here to visit the temple, too?
Yes.
Ah, if it's okay with you, do you want to go together?
Hey, hey, what's this supposed to be?
Isn't something slightly wrong, God?
What the hell's with the dream coming true?
Huh? Right now?
"Go help you," you say...
But the Suou Group is putting on a performance here today.
This is troublesome...
Ah.
Well, it'll probably work out somehow.
It's crowded no matter where we go.
Yes.
Tsukamoto-san, watch your step.
Eh? Oh, thank you, Karasuma-kun.
Is it okay for me to be this happy on New Year's Day?
I never would have thought that I would go to the first temple visit with Karasuma-kun.
Karasuma, you bastard. I'll never forgive you.
Today will become the anniversary of your death.
Harima-kun.
Ah, how fortunate.
The Suou Group is about to put on a performance, but something came up and I have to run.
Can you take my place until I get back?
Huh?! Why should I do that?
Ohhh. So Harima-kun is the type of person who forgets previous debts once the New Year rolls around, huh?
Okay, I'm counting on you. Thanks.
Oh, take care of me this year.
Ah! Hey, wait!
Damn you, Suou.
"Take care of me," huh?
I've got things to take care of...
What? It's done with two people?
I hope the guy in the back didn't wait long.
There we go. Sorry for making you...
wait...
W--Wait a minute! Why are you here?!
I don't know! I'd like to know that myself!
Geez, that Mikoto... Stirring things up so early in the year.
I shouldn't have accepted this job.
That's my line!
While I'm doing this, Tenma-chan and Karasuma are...
Wow!
It just moved.
It's huge!
This is my first time seeing one.
Hey, did you kids come to see the lion dance?
Yeah.
My mom told me to come and get bitten.
I guess I don't have much of a choice.
Work with me until Mikoto comes back.
Tch, don't act all high and mighty, idiot.
They talk in lion dances, huh.
They have quarrels, too.
This is my first time seeing one.
You're getting better, aren't you?
Hmph, keep quiet.
Ah, what good are sacred teachings.
Oh, a lion dance, huh?
It really feels like New Year's.
Hey, Kousuke, why don't you go get bitten?
Eh? N--No thanks, I'm fine.
It eats people?!
Interesting! There are beasts like that in Japan, too!
I'm borrowing these!
H--Hey, wait!
I'll get you this time!
Lala-san!
Note: The lion dance originated in China but other Asian cultures have their own variations.
That's not a wild beast! This is a traditional Japanese event called the lion dance.
So that's how it is.
Then why does it bite people?
It's been said that good things will happen to you if you get bitten by the lion in the lion dance.
Something good already happened to you, didn't it, Nee-chan?
Thanks to me, you managed to come to the first temple visit with Blue.
Hey, Kousuke!
Save me, Blue!
What are you saying?
Tch, if things went properly, I would be all love-love with Tenma-chan right now too.
What the heck am I doing?
Even though I had such a good dream...
Really?! Is that true, Karasuma-kun?
T--That's... Tenma-chan! And Karasuma!
Damn!
I really want to save Tenma-chan from Karasuma's evil grasp right now,
but there are too many people here.
Ah! Look, look, Karasuma-kun! The lion!
Amazing! It's so big! This is my first time seeing one.
Tenma-chan... You're too cute after all.
I got it! If I bite Tenma-chan, we can secretly...
I love you.
Harima-kun...
I love you
A secret love inside a lion.
This is it!
Yay! I got bitten!
Imadori-san, good things will happen to you this year.
Huh? Harim--
I--Imadori-san!
You did it! After getting bitten so much, you'll have a great year!
O--Oh crap. It'll be too late if they reach the streets.
If it's come to this...
Hey, Ojou.
Huh?
The lion dance is supposed to go on the streets as well.
The visitors seem happy, so do you want to go outside for a while?
I--I guess so, if that's better...
I got it. Now that it's been decided, let's go.
Mama, that.
Ken-chan, don't look.
Hey, I get the feeling that we're getting weird glances.
It's just you.
What will be your order?
One melon soda.
That was really great, wasn't it?
Sorry for the wait.
Hey, are you really sure about this?
Are you even listening, Hige?
Sir?!
What a beautiful sunset.
I watched fireworks with everyone last year.
Damn it, that Karasuma bastard!
Is he planning to do it here?
Tsukamoto-san.
Huh? What is it, Karasuma-kun?
Close your eyes.
Karasuma-kun...
Like I'll let you!
I'm going to eat you!
Tsukamoto-san.
This.
I just bought it.
I think it will look great with your kimono.
Your kimono suits you very well.
T--Thank you, Karasuma-kun.
Please take care of me this year too.
Sure.
Hey, I'm basically finished over here.
Alright, then come do this one.
Yeah, yeah...
But this is one huge kite.
What are we supposed to do with this?
You'll see.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Geez, why do I have to go through this on New Year's Day?
That's why I've been apologizing to you the whole way.
It's fine already.
Hey, Hige.
Huh?
Please take care of me this year too.
Sure.
Kite Flying
Wow, it's flying.
Amazing! They're all up so high!
There are lots of different kites.
Hey, Hanai-kun.
I would like to participate, too. Can you lend me a hand?
Hm? You should be able to fly a kite on your own.
It's a kite that can't be flown by one person.
If it stands out, it'll be good for the reputation of our school,
and you'll score a point against Tougou-kun.
I see. Allow me to aid you!
Hey, Kenji-kun.
What? I'm not helping.
Oh? That's quite the attitude from someone who hasn't paid this month's rent.
Hey, Mikoto, is that samurai-like one a kite as well?
Note: A "yakkodako" is a kite that is shaped like a footman.
That's a type of kite called the yakkodako.
Ah, the one over there is up pretty high too!
Is this for real?
They really are up pretty high.
Amazing! Amazing! They're battling kites!
Alright then. It just so happens that I felt like settling my score with you this year.
Tch, don't start playing their game.
You're a blockhead as always.
He landed a good one.
You bastard... Now you've done it!
Hey, hey, that was Takano-kun just now--
Oh, he went for a kick!
What skill!
I won't lose!
Bring it on!
Wow! Wow! It's a big battle!
They're idiots.
Yeah. They are.
Damn it! Give up already!
I can't do that! You should be the one stepping down!
Takano-kun, the time has come to use "that!"
Are you sure?
Let's go, Harima. From three times the normal height.
What's he attempting to do?
With three times the normal amount of rotation.
Let's go! Sure kill!
A Hundred Famous Poems Card Game
Hyakunin Isshu is a game where you listen to the reader's poem, then pick up the card with the last verse of the poem.
So we just have to pick up the card?
Translation: Just like the boatman of the strait of Yura who lost his rudder and floats aimlessly,
Yura no to wo wataru funabito kadzi wo tae
the path that my love will take is unknown as well.
Yukue mo shiranu koi no michi ka na
I got it!
I--Imadori-san!
Did I do something wrong?
Well, it's fine. It's New Year's anyway.
Japanese Badminton
Note: "Hanetsuki" is Japanese Badminton.
Hanetsuki?
Yeah. You hit the birdie with that paddle.
If you drop the birdie, you get punished by having your opponent scribble on your face with ink.
By the way, I won't go easy on you.
Hm? Well, let's try it.
There's no more space to draw on.
Nooo! Yakumo, avenge your sister!
Eh?
She had a bad opponent.
Really... You can't do anything well, can you?
I will...
What? You want to play too? I was hoping you would.
Oh, that's Yakumo-chan for you.
W--Wait a minute now.
W--We're switching players, too. Therefore, he can take the punishment.
Eh?
Huh?! Why me? Are you an idiot?
Well, I wonder who was the one who pushed me off a cliff on New Year's Day?
Brace yourself.
Alright, feel free to besmear him with ink!
T--That's how it is, Imouto-san.
T--That's...
What's she getting so desperate about against a underclassman?
Beard.
You're good, Yakumo!
One more round!
What are you getting so worked up about?
Who cares? Hige takes the punishment.
Damn you! That's enough already!
I'll draw then!
New Year's Resolution
Graffiti: Take down Ichijou
New Year's resolution!
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Translator
TL Checker
DeiLight
Cairan
Timer
PsycTint
Rina
Karaoke
Editor
Meltingice
Encoder
Typesetter
Meltingice
Quality Control
ValorBreak
SSephirothT
Swimsuit Sumo
Sign: New Year's Swimsuit Sumo Tournament
New Year's is all about swimsuit sumo.
W--Will girls really come?
You bet. You can expect to see lots of porori too.
They're here!
Huh?
T--Tougou?
Hmph. So this is sumo, a sport derived from a national sport symbolic of Japan's history.
The day this becomes an international sport comparable to soccer draws near!
Allow me to introduce my passionate comrades.
Hey, Brother!
Tennouji!
Kuuta-kun!
Now, release your strength!
Go!
New Year's is definitely about nothing but swimsuit sumo!
Hm? That's...
Next Episode
Ichijou! Skate! Let's go skating!
Ah, it can't be helped. I guess I'll tag along, too.
Why are you here?!
Next time on School Rumble Ni Gakki:
Dream Jumbo,
Dream Jump,
Dream -- Press.
Dream Jumbo
Dream Jump
Dream Express
X
You tricked me!
A member of the Tsukamoto family,
Iori.
Iori's footprint,
which one is it?
See you next time!