Didn't we promise not to see each other anymore?
E--Even if you say something like that now...
Ahem... Fine then... Just for a second...
It'll be fine... for sure...
See? It's going like it always does...
I... ATE... TOO... MUCH...!
This always happens at the end of every New Year's.
If I were to meet Karasuma-kun during the third term like this...
You're too fat.
That's what he'll say to me!
I've made up my mind!
Starting now, I'm going straight into a super diet!
I'm sorry. I made pizza mochi for lunch.
I'll make something with fewer calories for Nee-san...
Huh?
Thanks for the meal!
Dream Jumbo
Dream Jump
Dream Express
X
If you're talking about the
most graceful activity on ice,
then it has to be figure skating.
If you're talking about martial arts on snow,
then it's probably mogul skiing?
Oh. Hello? Miko-chan!
Huh? The four of us on a skiing trip?
I'll go! I'll go! I'll definitely go!
Are you going with Suou-senpai and the others?
Yeah. Tetsu-chan and the others were supposed to go, but they ended up catching colds.
It's quite the coincidence since you were saying how you needed to exercise.
Yeah. I'll burn some calories and shape up while skiing.
Alright, I'm going!
Have a safe trip, Nee-san.
It's okay. I'll be fine if I keep myself warm.
Yagami
Stationery
Thank you very much.
I ended up buying it.
I got some new screentones.
This stuff's pretty expensive.
I'll have to use it sparingly.
A thirty-page special appendix for the spring edition.
Go draw it with your hot, passionate soul!
Yeah! I'll draw it!
What did you say you will draw?
Hey! Don't just appear like that!
Can you stop bugging me?
Oh, that's a good reaction.
Alright, once more.
Huh?
We're taking a night bus to go on a ski trip.
So what?
Tenma is with us.
Very good.
T--Tenma-chan is going skiing?
I--I want to see her...  I want to see Tenma-chan in her magnificent skiing gear.
I really want to go! But...
I have to finish the thirty-page special appendix for the spring edition!
Not to mention, I don't have the money to go to the ski resort.
T--The right thing to do here is to go far away and pray for Tenma-chan's happiness.
Have fun for me too.
Interesting...
Hey, I'm back, Itoko.
Oki
nawa
Y
a
y
I went on a trip to Okinawa with Youko. We'll return in 3 days. Take care.
Yay! Sooki soba! I'm so excited!  Keep it up, Kenji-kun.
What the hell?! Don't screw with me!
Man, they locked the damn door again!
Just kidding. As if I'll make a fuss...
I am a man who learns.
Expecting something like this to happen, I secretly got a duplicate key.
You'll
pay
for
this
Since you're reading this, you must have secretly made a duplicate key. You'll pay dearly for this when I return.
Nooo!
Now we have the number one competitor from the Shoutou district, Fukuda Kyoko.
Let us watch the figure skating performance that she intends to give to win the title of "Skating Queen."
There it is! An amazingly stable Biellmann spin.
How impressive! She's not shaking at all!
Wow! Wondeful! She's still spinning. She's still spinning! And she's still spinning!
I wonder how long she can continue spinning like that.
I will skate this year...
And she has finished!
I will skate this year!
Fukuda exits the ring with a beautiful smile on her face.
What should I do?! What should I do?!
Ichijou!
The early morning snow feels great, doesn't it?
It really does.
It will feel even better if you wrap yourself in it.
You go do that.
Huh? Where's Tenma?
Yay!
This feels great!
Huh? What's wrong with you guys?
You're good at this, aren't you?
Eheh, I have to be good enough to teach Yakumo, you know?
Onee-chan, help me!
Oh, Yakumo, you're such a klutz.
I guess there's a surprising talent in everyone.
Tenma, how's this?
Eh? What's wrong, Akira-chan?
What a weak reaction.
Wow, you're great at jumps!
We're from the Mogul Circle in Otowadai.
Here they come!
It's a heart!
He's pretty skilled.
Hm...
How was it? Did my feelings get through?
If it's okay with you... Huh?
The girls left.
Eh?!
Hey, w--wait for us!
Only gentlemen have a chance at flirting with us.
However, their skiing was not bad at all.
Oh, that's too bad. Just skiing well isn't enough.
Tsukamoto's current character is somewhat different from her usual character.
Are you sure this is okay? Karasuma-kun will be shocked if he saw you like this.
He's not here, is he?
Good evening.
K--Karasuma-kun.
Why are you here...? Why are you a snowman...?
Hey. It's quite a coincidence for us to meet here.
What? Are you challenging me?
Tenma's reaction was quite acute, too.
It's okay, it's okay.
Welcome to the
Yagami Ski Resort
Karasuma-kun...
He saw me for sure! He heard me and now he hates me!
You reap what you sow. You're at fault here.
I only wanted to see what it was like to act like a mature woman for once.
Like I said, you don't have to wear it!
You're really helpless, aren't you? I'll lend you a hand just this once.
Really?
Alright, we'll all jump off at the same time, and appeal to Karasuma-kun by making the characters "daisuki."
Tenma will do the "dai" and Mikoto will do the "ki."
Will we really be able to jump that well?
Hey, isn't mine the most difficult?
What are you talking about? It's the same as the last jump.
Okay, Karasuma-kun is here.
I have to do it.
Watch me, Karasuma-kun.
Ready, go!
Karasuma-kun...
These are...
These are my feelings!
Text: You're too fat.
You're too fat.
Note: Because Tenma dropped her hat and her poles, the words "I love you" became "You're too fat."
Indeed, I may be too fat...
Karasuma-kun! That's not what I meant!
No, it's okay.
I was vaguely aware that it was my fault for succumbing to New Year's gluttony.
I would like you to look at my feelings this time.
Ahhh, I said it was all wrong--
Text: Thanks
See you.
You're awesome, Karasuma-kun...
It's getting cold.
Let's head back.
Everyone, it's good that you're all here!
This was quite shocking. Lala suddenly said that she wanted to learn how to skate.
Hmph. So Lala will finally make her debut on the skating rink.
This is my first time skating!
I get to skate with Imadori-san so early in the year... Thank you, Lala-san.
But the memories sure come back now that I stand on top of the ice.
The years of my youth that I spent together with the blizzards of Alaska.
How does it look? Does it suit me?
Please change into something else right now!
Why?!
T--This... is not a sport for humans!
Ah... Ah... Please don't let go.
There you go. Loosen up a bit more.
I got you.
Oh, Satsuki-chan, you're being taught by Harry-san?
Wow, Ichijou-senpai looks like a professional skater.
Hehe, that's not true.
Huh? What are you doing, Lala?
Could it be that you can't skate? I guess there's no way that a gorilla can handle human sports.
Imadori...!
Hurry up and teach me!
No can do.
I'll teach you if you manage to come over here.
Come on, come on.
I'll kill you!
SFX: Depressed
I've finally discovered your weakness, Lala. You are powerless when you're on ice.
I'm so hungry.
You really worked hard this morning, didn't you?
On that note, Ichijou-senpai, you're good at any sport, aren't you?
No, I just come here with Kousuke from time to time.
No way! You were the best one on the rink!
Why? I tried hard, too. Why haven't I gotten any better?
Hey, I just found this.
Yagami High School Pair Figure Skating Tournament...
Ah, it seems like this starts today.
There are some pretty extravagant prizes.
There are!
The first place winner gets a set of the newest models of a washer and dryer?!
Alright, I'll participate, too!
Senpai?
Um, I just thought... I'll go test my abilities.
That's how my rival should be!
Okay, we'll both go!
That's some big talk coming from someone who can't even skate.
However, there is a single way for an inexperienced person like you to take first place.
R--Really?
Nee-chan, where are you going?
Nee-chan, I have P.E. tomorrow!
Nee-chan, I'm hungry.
Nee-chan!
A dryer... If we had that, we wouldn't have to hang our clothes anymore.
The Yagami High School Pair Figure Skating Tournament will now begin.
Would the pairs of competitors please gather in the rink.
Lala & Imadori Pair
Hey, Imadori, can we really win like this?
Yeah, leave it to me.
Dryer... Dryer... Kousuke, Onee-chan will try her best!
Karen & Tougou Pair
Hmph, let's fire up this place.
How about going with me? It's still not too late.
E--Even if you say that, I really can't.
I'll drown you in humiliation, you gorilla-woman.
First off, we have the pair of Ichijou and Tougou.
Ichijou gallantly skates into the rink.
Her experience is apparent.
We can expect a good rating.
Oh?
Could this be... Kobayashi-sensei?
Ah... I did it!
That's right! This is definitely the illusionary Alaska spin!
Tougou has displayed a bold move right off the bat.
By himself, that is...
That's not good. Ichijou is left to drift around on her own.
They have completely forgotten about the "pair" part of the competition.
U--Um... Tougou-san?
Unfortunately, the Tougou and Ichijou pair is disqualified.
Hmph, it seems like an island country can't yet appreciate my performance.
Kousuke... I'm sorry.
Next is the pair of Lala and Imadori.
I wonder what kind of performance we can expect her, whom is from Mexico.
Watch me, Ichijou, Tougou!
My appearance shall be reborn!
It's our turn now. Let's go, Lala.
We'll leave the spectators dumbfounded.
Lala-san, that's for speed skating.
It's an easy mistake for beginners to make.
You tricked me, Imadori!
Idiot, idiot, come and get me.
Stop, you!
Wait, wait!
Hey, you should give up.
What in the world...? Lala has gone barefoot.
She's also gaining a tremendous amount of speed.
The finishing technique looks like a gyroplane.
Ah, this is against the rules as well.
Bravo, bravo!
To tap into lucha libre for inspiration... Even I did not expect that.
I think it's time...
we headed back.
O--Oh crap. I lost to the kotatsu and dozed off.
Why... Why am I outside of the kotatsu?
I'm going to catch a cold.
My legs won't go in.
Something is in there.
What is it?
Just now, that was... I-I-I-I-It couldn't be...
Ahhh, no way... That's not possible.
Even if it's from his point of view...
Cut it out.
But wait, think about this carefully.
His height is...
What do you want?
No... It can't happen. I mean... I mean, it's a kotatsu.
Could it be...? No...
Pyo... P--P--P--P--Pyo... Are you Pyotr?!
W--Why, Pyotr?
Why the kotatsu?! How?!
When did you...?!
Help.
An important friend.
"Help," you say...?
C--Could it be? With their sharp senses, the animals felt Tenma-chan's danger and came to tell me?
Help.
Did she run into a snowstorm at the ski resort?
Or do the devilish claws of flirting guys draw near?
I can't be sitting here.
I'm going to save you right now!
Tenma-chan! Stay safe!
Onee-chan?
Yakumo, are you okay?
Here, I made this.
A rabbit?
Here.
Thank you, Onee-chan.
It feels nice and cool.
Really? That's great.
Onee-chan...
Imouto-san.
Hey, Imouto-san, are you okay?
Wake up.
What a fever.
Anyway, I'll need to find a place for her to sleep.
This should be fine for now.
But this was pretty shocking.
I never thought something like this would happen.
Well then, I should get going.
I have to hurry up and continue working on my manga...
Iori?
Thank you.
It feels nice and cool.
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Translator
DeiLight
TL Checker
alchemist11
Karaoke
Rina
Timer
Encoder
Editor
Typesetter
Meltingice
Quality Control
SSephirothT
Meltingice
Next Episode
Going cruising in the southern islands you say?
I guess I have no choice. I'll have to go too.
Next time on School Rumble Ni Gakki:
The southern rainbow's 2-C!
The mysterious island's Yaakumo!
The seven seas's...!
Now that you mention it, is the guy with the glasses still flying on the kite?
The Southern Rainbow's 2-C!
The Mysterious Island's Yaakumo!
The Seven Seas's...!
Hanai Haruki, currently riding the
jet stream and heading east.
He's scheduled to come flying into
invade America's mainland next episode!?
X
See you next time!