School
Rumble
Ni Gakki
School
Rumble
Ni Gakki
School Rumble is starting!
...It's Sukuran.
......It really is Sukuran.
.........I said it's Sukuran!
Tonight's contents are
over the top, as always
Your nightly companion is
School Rumble!!
The illusionary, blue Damask rose.
It is said that, upon sticking it onto the ear of the person you love,
your love will be fulfilled.
Mahou Shoujo
Magical
Mai
Something suspicious!
Damn!
Fire!
Hahahahahaha. How unsightly, Mask Kamen-san.
However, this will save me some time in calling that person out.
What?
That person gets in my way quite often.
I'm Ootsuka Mai.
I'm a Taurus, and I have type A blood.
There's a little secret in my home.
What is it, you ask?
Good morning, Papa, Mama.
Good morning, Mai.
Note: "Buenos dias" is Spanish for "Good morning."
Buenos dias.
How about it? Shall we run together?
It feels great.
Uh... I'll pass.
Is that so?
You're awake?!
It's time to eat!
Okay!
We have potatoes, too!
These two are my papa and mama.
They are actually the king and queen of a magical country.
Mai-chan!
That's...
the illusionary, blue Damask rose!
It's okay. Use it as you please.
Really?
Yup, yup.
I'm going.
Got it. Be careful.
Note: "You don't want to eat any more?"
Yoo don wan nu eet an moor?
Yes. I'm completely full.
Mai-chan, Mai-chan.
To whom are you planning to give that blue Damask rose?
Isn't it obvious? Mask Kamen-sama.
Ah, but I wonder where I should go to find him?
He always shows up out of nowhere whenever we're in a pinch and then flies off.
This is a problem.
Give it back!
Ha! What's yours is mine. What's mine is also mine.
Right, Yoshidayama?
That's right, Imadori-kun.
Hey, give it back already!
Nara's getting a bit too full of himself.
Yeah, too full of himself.
Oh no. The bully is getting bullied again!
Mai-chan, that should be, "The bullied kid is getting bullied again."
I guess you're right.
Right, check.
Left, check.
Tada!
Charm up, my Mai dream!
Yoshida, you hit him once as well.
Got it.
Stop it!
That's enough.
Note: "Mahou Shoujo" means "Magical Girl."
Even little evil deeds will not stay unpunished. Mahou Shoujo, Magical Mai elegantly appears!
You're not a young girl at all.
A good percentage of her is already an adult.
Really, brats these days...
Uh, Mai-chan. Don't forget we're dealing with kids here.
Now is the time to indiscriminately punish!
Uh, Mai-chan, that's not--
Magical Flash!
Damn it!
Stop wearing white panties, old hag!
That's quite some nerve you've got there.
Mai-chan, I think that's enough for today.
Who's there?
Dun-dun-dun-dunh!
Come on, let's go.
You're going to ignore me?!
What are you doing here, Tsukamoto-san?
Uh, I need to buy something, so I'm doing a part-time job.
Part-time?
My job's to deliver that letter to you.
Eh?
I've powered up quite a bit, and it's pretty tough, you know.
Eh? Ah! They slipped off again!
Oh, so that was padding.
I'm slightly busy right now, but be prepared to be awed by my presence sometime in the near future.
Later. Hahahahaha...
Nee-san, isn't that the way villains laugh?
They're always such lively people.
So? What's the letter about?
I wonder.
T--This is...
Dear Magical Mai-sama,
It feels especially cold today as the chilly weather pierces the body ever so deeply. How are you faring right now?
Oh, by the way...
I happened to capture your dear friend, Mask Kamen-kun!
If you wish to save him, it would greatly please me if I could trouble you to visit my magic castle.
From, the Great Demon King, Ponchie-sama.
This saves me the trouble of looking for Mask Kamen-sama, but...
Man... Why are my enemies always so adult-like?
It can't be helped, Mai-chan.
I mean, you're a high school Mahou Shoujo.
Note: The appeal of Mahou Shoujo typically wears off after elementary school.
That's true. I mean, look at Tsukamoto-san. During her elementary school years...
Milky Change!
Marshmallow Tenma appears!
She was like that.
Although both of you were actually young girls a few years ago.
I don't have the guts to change occupations either.
But if you were to continue to age like this...
My Mai... What was it again?
No! That's an absolute no!
With this rose, I'll definitely do it by tonight!
Go Mai! I'm going to resign for my marriage!
Ponchie's Magic Castle
I have a bad feeling about this.
It really does feel like a trap. Do you want to go ask?
That's right. It's a trap.
Who might you be?
It doesn't matter.
Nothing will be solved if you keep running away.
Do you not think that, sometimes, the courage to jump into danger is necessary?
Especially for the current you.
That may be true.
Alright. Two newcomers.
Designation
No. 1
Tennouji-chan. Guide them to table number three.
Actually... Maybe some other time.
Number
Isn't this really bad?
There are lots of strange things here and there that are improper for Shoujo manga.
Ahhh!
What are you planning to do to her?
Mai is seriously taking this magical girl thing too far.
She's already a high school student, yet she's still running around pretending it's her fate to be a magical girl.
Normally, you'd get sick of doing it.
There was someone called Marshmallow Tenma, right?
Hmmm?!
As I recall, that girl was the same age as Mai.
Is this for that girl's sake?
There is no use for two magical girls around here.
You... really do think of her...
Does that girl know of your feelings?
Argh, that girl... is really fired up for some other guy.
Geez, don't scare me like that.
Sorry.
So this castle was built just recently, and you were doing the final round of inspections?
Yes. I designed... this castle.
Ehhh...?
However, due to budget cuts, there are many inconveniences.
How's the earthquake resistance?
That's fine.
Hmmm...?
Are there any secret passages that lead outside?
Yes, there are.
Alright!
Get out of my way!
Go for it, Mai-chan!
Note: "Paku" means "Munch."
Paku, paku, paku, paku, paku, paku.
Note: "Gottsuandesu" is the Sumo Wrestler's version of "Gochisousama."
Gottsuandesu.
Whoa! What's going on?
Whew, we're finally out.
Where's this?
Ah, Mask Kamen-sama!
Uh... Can't you do something about that costume?
What right do you have to comment on others' fashions, fool?
Well, it's at least not something a decent person would wear.
A man's loincloth is a medal!
Shut up, Hentai Kamen!
No! I'm the Great Demon King, Ponchie.
You brat...
You have quite the attitude, young lady.
I've got a hostage here.
Hey, don't tie people up with your loincloth!
Ah, don't mind it. We're both guys anyway.
I do mind!
Keh, what a baby.
You can go first.
Wah!
Ah! Mask Kamen-sama!
Whoa there!
Don't flail that weird thing around!
Oh, were you guys in the middle of something?
Hehehe, I checked the management office, but no one was around. So I came up here.
Oh...
Karasuma-kun!
Are you with these guys?
Huh? Ah! Why are you here?!
Wait, the balls.
Tsukamoto-san.
Huh?
That outfit is wonderful.
Tenma-chan...
Hmph, it seems I have become a comic relief.
But...
Mai! Let's settle this!
Like I said, stop using this angle, damn it!
Pursue me if you want to save Mask Kamen!
Why, you perverted bastard?!
There they go.
I guess I'm not getting paid.
Tsukamoto-san.
Eh?
There's something you need to say to the Great Demon King, isn't there?
I also need to talk to him about the current condition of the castle.
That girl caused quite a riot as well as a lot of damage.
It will... probably be over very soon.
Shall we wait together?
Nee-san, I'll go back first, but take your time, okay?
Got it!
That outfit suits you.
Ah, this is--
Ah, no! Not at a time like this!
It's becoming loose! This is so embarrassing!
It's alright.
I know a good store.
Thank you.
The whole thing became foolish, but I'll be ending this my way.
Do as you wish.
Heh.
That's enough!
You came.
Let go of Mask Kamen!
Sure! That is, if you retire from being a Mahou Shoujo.
Eh?
Isn't it simple?
You don't have to be unreasonable.
You also wanted an excuse to stop, didn't you?
It's right in front of your eyes.
Not to mention, it's to save someone.
You're not a young girl at all.
A good percentage of her is already an adult.
It's not a bad deal at all, right?
I...
Don't give up!
Huh?
You can't give up!
What's wrong with fluttery clothing?!
What's wrong with high school students?!
Are you a pervert or something?!
Mask Kamen-sama!
That's right! All I have to do is beat you to a pulp.
Hah! I guess I have no choice. I was trying to be nice, too...
Loincloth, extend!
I'm not the Great Demon King just for show!
Sorry, it doesn't seem like I can save...
Magical Mai!
Mask Kamen... sama
You...
Why?
Like I said, stop using this angle already...
You're no good at confessing either, are you?
If you were left with some lingering regrets in this world, it would leave a bad aftertaste.
Even so, it doesn't mean I've become your buddy or anything.
Just for today, I'll express my gratitude.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're actually a nice guy.
Being praised by a cat doesn't make me happy.
Who's a nice guy?
Be stuck into his ear, Blue Damask Rose Ascension!
Ack!
Mai-chan! That's not how you're supposed to stick it!
You're supposed to stick it onto his ear like you would a red pen!
No way!
Yes way! Not to mention that the way you did it is enough to kill him.
That's a technique that assassins use!
What should I do?
I think I've got the basic gist of what's going on.
It's the magic of love or whatever, right?
But you're making a mistake.
Even if you were to steal away someone's heart with magic, it's not real!
I know that.
But...
It's alright.
Those feelings... I accepted them.
Oh, he's alive.
It's a great relief that you're fine!
You're the one who did it, you know.
Magical Mai. As I am right now, I cannot keep your feelings.
Huh?
To me, whose mask bears the burden of both my body and soul,
you are too dazzling.
Farewell.
Um... At least... your face...
Even if it's just one glance.
Please.
Since you've said this much...
*Gulp*
Although, to this day, I have never revealed my face to others,
I will answer to your feelings.
Dasu.
Ahhh! That bastard! Compensate me!
And thus, Magical Mai defeats the evil in the world and protects the love and peace of Yagami City.
Go, Magical Mai!
Fly, Magical Mai!
Your future is bright!
Probably.
Um... Maybe.
It's absolutely bright for sure. Right?
How was she? Mai-chan, I mean.
I'm quite confident about it.
No way.
Aha. You're right.
I guess it really isn't Sukuran, is it?
Raw Provider
Meltingice
Translator
TL Checker
DeiLight
Cairan
Timer
Meltingice
Insert Karaoke
Rina
Karaoke
Meltingice
Editor
Encoder
Typesetter
Meltingice
Quality Control
desani
SSephirothT
Text: Go All Out Basketball Brigade!
Reach the goal!
Go All Out Basketball Brigade!
All your friends have fallen.
Only you remain standing.
Hahahahaha.
It's time for you to pay your tributes, Drive-san.
Drive...
This trap has sealed your fate!
What?
Not yet...
Something like this isn't enough to erase my...
No... Our fighting spirit!
Heh, we'll strike back!
Our fighting spirit... I'll slam it all into you!
Roar! Exploding...
Galactic Bomber!
Drive, it's not over yet.
Huh?
That is correct.
We didn't just simply come back, you know!
We are the envoys who are here to lead you to hell.
You guys... Those bodies...
It must be Death Gate's doing.
Huh?
For you to know his name... You're not an ordinary person.
We were right to prevent you from moving around first.
Marippe...
I'm sorry, Drive.
I took advantage of everyone's kindness and dragged you all into this fight.
Even when I tried to tell you the truth, it wouldn't come out.
The truth is...
Shut up...
I'm really sorry.
Shut up already!
Stop apologizing over and over again!
We're comrades, aren't we?
Drive...
He's right.
Huh?
You're being too distant, Marippe.
Beautiful things always come with thorns.
There were some calculation errors, but they've been corrected.
Everyone...
Beating bad guys into the ground...
needs no reason!
You won't be acting stylish for much longer.
Drive!
Marippe!
Pure Evil Combination!
Transform!
Bring it on!
Complete!
We're even bigger with all five of us together!
T--This is...
How are you feeling? Totally paralyzed in fear, I suspect?
Drive!
It's over, Drive!
Wait!
Don't leave us out.
We can still fight.
You guys...
You Galactic Bomber losers... How do you plan to fight in that condition?
Like this!
Barrier.
What?!
It's futile. Hahahahaha--
Marippe!
Drive... Everyone... I dispelled his barrier with my power.
Now's your chance to attack him!
Damn you!
That's as far as you go.
Brilliant Rose.
Eeeh?!
Come on, Drive!
Yeah!
Entry angle is eighty-five degrees.
Got it!
Go!
What?!
Eat this!
Sure kill!
God Shining...
Blast!
We turned it around!
Hehe, it's thanks to you guys!
Marippe...
You idiot, this is the time to laugh.
The most important thing is that everyone is safe.
Everyone...
Drive, thank you.
Y--Yeah.
Ah, Drive is blushing.
Just like I predicted.
Note: "Ca va?" is French for "How's it going?"
Ca va?
This is Go All Out Basketball we're talking about. How do you plan to fight me with those weary bodies, voila?
That's...
You're Death Gate?
Note: "Au revoir" is French for "Farewell."
Yes, au revoir! Hohohohoho!
How is it? I thought it might be okay. Hahahaha...
Obviously not.
Right. Of course.
Next Episode
New Year! New Year!
Happy and embarrasing "first dream of the new year" date!
If the lion danced, it would gulp you right up!
Kite flying! Kite flying!
Cool! Cool! A hundred poems that will break your bones!
Note: "Hanetsuki" is Japanese badminton and "Sumi-nuri" is to spread ink.
Hanetsuki! Sumi-nuri! All black!
Year's First Dream
Lion Dance
New Year
Hurry up! Come! Come, New Year!
The next Sukuran is
currently judging bring-your-own episodes
Is the next episode
going to be Sukuran?
See you next time!
Go all out! Go all out! Go All Out Basketball Brigade! Go all out!