Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Passengers for Japan airline flight 136,
please go to gate number eight.
Be polite, Atom.
You are the representative of Japanese robots after all.
Mr. Beard, take good care of Atom.
I'm coming with him, so don't worry.
-That's why I'm worried. -Is that so? What?
Here, let's go, Teacher.
Hurry. Bye!
Here.
-You are a robot! -Yes.
Don't you know that the Robot Law says that robots can't go abroad on their own?
I do know.
What are you saying?! Atom is officially invited to Gravia country
to participate in the inaugural ceremony of the president.
Look here. He has a special permission from the minister!
Please pardon me. Please pass by.
Wow, Mr. Atom, I'm a robot too. Please tell the president of Gravia
that robots all round the world are proud of him.
Yes! I'll tell him that for sure.
-Good bye. -Say hi to the president!
I hope nothing happens.
The Robot President
There it is, Atom. That's Gravia country.
That is the country in which the world's first robot president has been born.
It's boring to wait for an hour, even though this is a VIP room.
Gosh, they shouldn't be treating guests like this.
Ah, Teacher, someone's coming.
Are you Mr. Atom?
That's right.
I'm sorry I'm late. Please come with me.
But what happened to you? Is that a fashion trend in this country?
I have no time to explain. I'm sorry, but please hurry.
It's dangerous!
Take it!
Teacher! Here, hurry!
All right!
Here, get in this car. Hurry.
This way.
Please wait a moment.
The president should be safe, right?
Hmm, then, let me go back.
-A double role? -How convenient.
I'm bit busy. Let me introduce myself again.
I'm the presidential secretary, Ambiguous.
I went to pick you up upon the president's order,
because bad guys were after you.
Eight invitees all over the world have been killed already.
Who in the world are they?
They are the ones who are trying to ruin the inaugural ceremony of the president.
Did Atom arrive safely?
Yes, Mr. President. Don't worry. As you can see, Mr. Atom is safe.
Welcome, Atom.
I'm Atom. To whom may it concern.
That's what you write in letters. I'll have to teach you how to greet people when we go back.
I've heard about you very much.
Thank you for coming. I'm the president Larg.
I'm Atom.
I'm that famous teacher of Atom's...
You are Mr. Beard, right?
My real name is Shunsaku Ban, and that's a nickname.
I have to have a conversation with Atom, so please guide him.
Yes, sir.
Sir, we have prepared the thing you like, that thing called "sushi."
-This way. -What an honorable happiness.
Here, come in.
-In fact, I called you because I have a favor to ask you. -To me, Mr. President?
Stop calling me "Mr. President." We are all robots.
-Call me Larg. -Okay, Larg!
So you have a favor to ask me?
Yes. I became the world's first robot president,
thanks to robots in this country; they voted for me.
Robots are happy that I got elected,
but there are humans who don't like that.
I do understand their position.
Because robots were created by human and for human.
But that's now a long time ago, right?
Yes. Of course, robots aren't human's slaves anymore.
That's right. We are human's friends.
But we still can't say that robots are the same as human beings.
There are several limitations.
That's why robots all around the world are counting on you.
There are people who have grudge against me.
I think they are the ones from the Deadcross Party.
Deadcross Party?
They are the ones who attacked you.
I'm getting a threat to resign from the position
before the inaugural ceremony
-after two days. -You can't give in to those guys!
You are the hope of all robots in the world.
I'm going to protect you for sure.
Thank you, Atom!
As robots' representative, I will for sure...
Shoot... Larg.
I'm going to make you see how a robot cannot surpass human beings.
We are operating that plan next morning. I'm not going to allow failure this time.
We the Deadcross Party, no matter what,
have to stop the birth of the robot president.
Humans are the owners of robots. And!
we the Deadcross Party will rule this country!
Hails for the Deadcross!
Wa, wait a minute.
Let me accompany...
Hey, hey! My legs. You are too fast.
Mr. Ambiguous, are you all right?
Ah... Man. Thank you. I'm fine.
Where is the president going?
Morning jogging.
I told him it's dangerous because the enemy's after him,
but he doesn't cease to greet the people every morning.
Then, let me accompany the president.
Please, Mr. Atom.
Larg!
-Hey, Larg. -Hi.
-Hello! -Have a nice day.
-Everyone likes Larg. -I was made as a politician robot.
Look at these feelers. Isn't it shining?
This means that many people are trusting me.
These feelers can convert trust into energy.
So the more trust I get, the more stronger I become.
And more hatred from the opposition.
Here he is.
He's here. He's with the kid called Atom.
Good. Start the plan.
-Hi! -Hi.
Hello, Larg.
-Hello. -Who are you?
This is Atom from Japan.
Nice to meet you.
What happened?
Ah, over there!
You are the Deadcross.
Atom, what happened, so early in the morning?
Teacher! Take Larg to his residence!
All right! Here, Mr. President. Let Atom take care of this, and let us go.
Atom, be careful!
All right, I won't lose!
Sir, they are trapped.
Good. Let Great Robo take care of Atom and get Larg!
Yes, sir!
Good!
Here I come!
It's done!
Ah, that's right. President Larg is.
Mr. President!
-What happened? -Mr. President and Mr. Beard are in that rocket!
What?
That's a problem. We have to follow them.
-Atom, get in here. -Okay!
-To where did they take them? -Don't worry.
There is a small tracking device on Mr. President's suit button.
They are heading north.
Good, let's go!
Mr. Beard, are you all right?
-Here... This is? -I'm not sure,
-but this must be the Deadcross headquarter. -Welcome.
Mr. President.
Welcome. The one from faraway Japan as well.
What are you going to do with us?
I only ask of one thing. Resign from your post!
What if I say no?
Let me show you something interesting.
-Th... This is all... -Robot friends. How harsh.
Robots who don't obey me will all become like that.
Now I know who you are.
Sir Hatler who was exiled abroad for opposing
the acknowledgment of robot rights!
As expected, you are a smart robot. What you said is correct.
But if you disobey me,
I'll make you friends with that scrap iron. Copy?
Declare that you are resigning from the post tomorrow at the inaugural ceremony!
This is my last advice. Do you understand?
Dang... What is he? How bragging!
Ah, that is?
That is an old castle in which Sir Hatler, a former noble, used to live in.
Ah, Teacher!
Teacher!
Don't come, Atom!
This is a trap.
It is designed to emit high-voltage current as soon as you touch this cross.
What?
Atom, if you don't want to become a scrap, go back to Japan.
Shoot... How mean!
If you don't obey me, Mr. Beard won't survive.
Go back to Japan immediately. Quietly!
All right?
Teacher, wake up!
Stupid, you think you can escape this castle safely?
Ah, what are these guys?
How insistent. They won't quit.
Ah, shoot.
Energy's low.
Atom, go! Hey!
Atom!
Hmm, even if it's a robot of million horsepower, without energy, it's a mere scrap.
Atom, for me...
Larg, did you give up now?
Even if I die, robots all around the country won't forgive you!
You can say that for now.
I won't lose. I will come back for sure.
You will become a wooden doll from now on.
I will remodel you to act upon my orders.
He gave up and left.
We have to rescue the president by tomorrow morning no matter what.
Before that, we have to rescue Atom first.
Where is Atom?
Stupid. Are they still around?
If you want to see him that much, I'll let you.
Mr. Beard!
Ah, Atom!
Remodeling Larg is done.
Larg's electronic brain is paralyzed completely by magnetic power.
So he's in hypnotic state. Larg, come here.
You are my servant.
Yes, sir.
Atom, wake up. Atom.
How can you be like this...
The watch Doctor Ochanomizu gave when we left Japan.
What is this?
We can contact Doctor Ochanomizu with this watch.
Ah, this is Mr. Beard. Is Doctor Ochanomizu there?
It's me. Is something wrong, Mr. Beard?
No, nothing. The Deadcrosses are a trouble,
Mr. Ambiguous is cut in half, and I've been Jesus for 10 hours.
I don't understand what you are saying, but like I worried,
there seems to be opposing ones for the robot president.
Yeah, that's right. Thanks to them, Atom's like this.
Oh... Atom, poor boy...
All right. Let's take a look. Please open Atom's chest.
Okay.
Hmm. So there doesn't seem to be a problem with the electronic brain.
I think only the IC has been damaged due to lack of energy and impact.
So Atom can be fixed?
There is emergency energy in that watch.
The problem is the new IC to replace the old one.
New one? Doctor, there's nothing here...
There are tons of broken robots here.
-All right! Look for the one that fits Atom. -All right.
Go, Larg.
-Make a speech of what I tell you. -Yes, sir!
I can't wait to see robots' faces all around the country!
Not that one! To the right!
Yes, yes, yes. Do something with your beard.
Yeah, yeah. There!
Good. Insert energy. He will move.
This is it.
Oh, Atom.
-Yeah! President Larg! -President Larg!
Then, let us hear the inaugural speech of President Larg.
Do you understand, Larg? You will make a speech of what I tell you.
Here, hurry, Atom.
Stop!
Where is Deadcross?
I'm a robot.
I'm a robot made by human beings.
Does a robot deserve to become a president?
Robots are tools made for human.
Stop it, Deadcross!
-You bastard. -It's too late!
Larg, can you hear me?
Robots are tools made for human.
Larg!
He will only listen to me!
Larg, your electronic brain has been paralyzed. But you can overcome it!
Because you are the world's first robot president!
Robots all around the world are counting on you!
Atom. Electronic brain. Robot. President...
I don't know. Ah... I don't know!
Think of it, Larg.
You are the robot president elected by everyone!
President?
President.
There's no use. Powerful magnetic power is covering his electronic brain.
Think of it!
I am...
Larg! Wake up for all of us!
President Larg!
-What happened? -What's wrong?
Larg! Larg! Larg! Larg!
Larg... Little bit more.
I'm the president. The robot president.
Larg!
Shoot... He got out of hypnotic state.
Dear robots in the world,
We have suffered for a long time as humans' slaves.
But half of the world's population is robots.
Dear human friends, we can't live without you.
But that's the same for human, too.
We want to make a world
in which we can share both sadness and happiness.
As humans have hearts, robots do too.
We will start understanding.
We will be able to become friends!
President Larg...
Larg...
Dang!
Stop! Deadcross!
All robots should die!
Larg, I'm going to blow you up along with the residence.
Stop it!
It's too late!
Teacher! Mr. Ambiguous! Catch me!
Hail for the Deadcross Party!
Thank you, Atom. All thanks to you.
That's not right. Your will overcame the evil.
Please visit again, Mr. Beard.
Will you come pick me up with one body next time?
Of course. What?
-Good bye! -Bye!
Good bye, robot president.
A mysterious rocket fallen from Mars.
The one aboard was a headless robot Damdam.
Skunk! You stole the head, right?
But Damdam started hunting to find his head.
Damdam, you shouldn't break robots! I don't want to fight you!
Next on Astro Boy, "Damdam's Neck." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Damdam's Neck"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
Inside my waist
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together