Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Ochanomizu.
The second Mars Resource Investigators will finally depart from this space station tomorrow.
It was a good decision to call Atom.
He put up with severe training very well for a month. Now I can relax.
Doctor Moss, I'm glad you feel like that.
Atom will successfully carry out his missions as one of crew members.
Ochanomizu, there is one thing I haven't told you.
Oh, what is it?
I'd like to send Atom as a captain, not as a crew member.
As a captain?
I don't want to repeat the same mistake again.
As you also know, two years ago,
I organized a big resource investigation team and sent them to Mars.
However, as soon as they arrived there, crew members had disputes over themselves
and an unfortunate incident of leaving people behind in Mars happened.
I do know that the first plan failed with that incident.
Then, therefore the captain should be...
Robots like Atoms would be good!
Robots?
Yes. I'd prefer robots that don't reveal emotions.
However, Atom is still only a kid...
It's all right. He will do a good job with it.
-Atom. -Doctor.
It is here. It's the Chris spaceship that will head to Mars tomorrow.
Adventure on Mars
Wow, Atom. It looks good on you.
-Doctor, I'll do my best! -Be careful.
Yes, sir!
I, Commander Ketchup, have something to tell Dr. Moss!
Go ahead.
I strongly oppose nominating a robot for the position of captain.
It's not only me. Crew members are opposing as well.
We don't want to get orders from a robot.
-I won't excuse any more arrogant comments! -But...
It's about time to go now.
Mars investigators, please gather at the lobby.
Here! Go.
Salute to the captain!
Hello, everyone.
Dear crew members, I'm Atom, the captain of Resource Investigators.
I am a robot,
-but let's do it well together! -He did it.
Salute!
Five minutes before takeoff!
There is a vibration in energy condenser.
Pardon?
If we don't fix it, it will lead to an accident.
Ah! It's true.
I'm surprised. He knew it even before looking at the meter.
Ah, the final check has been completed.
Lieutenant, what about magnetometer?
What do you mean?
Sensitivity of magnetometer is 0.001 second off.
There's no way that can be possible. I checked it carefully.
Lieutenant Ketchup, please check it again.
-We don't need to. -Please do!
Lieutenant, as the captain said, it is 0.001 second off.
What?
Way for robot captain. Electronic brain sure is precise.
Main engine ignition!
Main engine ignition.
This is Atom.
Captain, there's a stowaway in engine room.
Pardon?
Captain, it's this guy.
He's wearing the same uniform, but he doesn't have a crew number.
-Take this kid out of the spaceship right away. -Captain!
Main engine is working now. We can't open the hatch.
Please. Please take me to Mars.
There is my brother left from the first investigation.
Please. I want to see my brother.
There are capsules only for the crew. Please get off.
Captain, we can't anymore.
Robot is a robot, after all. It would never know of human emotions!
You...
30 seconds before ignition.
-Everyone, get in the capsule and wear seat belts. -Now it's over.
Good!
Get into my capsule.
Five seconds before ignition! Captain! You shouldn't be standing there!
...Two, one, ignition!
According to the record, your brother Lieutenant Rencon
had a fight with his captain after suggesting that they should change
the Resource Investigators base to a defense base.
But why did your brother say such things?
Brother detected the Earth's danger.
Crisis of the Earth?
But no one believed him. Please read this.
When he was abandoned in Mars for not following the captain's order,
a man who used to follow my brother gave this to me.
It's a journal.
"We will be arriving in Mars soon."
"I'm excited to be involved in this meaningful work of investigating resources."
March 4th, An encounter with strange UFO?
"This is the second time I saw it."
"Strange UFO..."
There are sketch and impressions on the next page.
Big, egg-shaped, and whitely luminous.
"It's a weird shape I've never seen."
"Besides, it feels bad because it looks like it's watching us."
"I had a bad feeling, so I reported it to the captain, but he ignored it."
It is up to here.
He must have felt dangerous after encountering that UFO again after this.
He must have suggested that defense base because of this as well.
UFO. What an odd shape.
Captain, please come to the bridge! Magnetometer is getting distorted!
Magnetometer is?
Ah, we won't be able to keep the route then, Lieutenant Ketchup.
We check the meter. There's no problem.
Then...
We don't know about the cause at all.
That's right. The cause might be outside the ship.
Outside?
Captain, something's glowing near the crater.
-What? -As expected.
Something strongly magnetic like meteoric iron must be stuck on the ship.
Good! I'll go outside and check.
Lieutenant. Bring energy cassette capsule from my room.
It's about time to change. Hurry!
Whom do you think you are ordering? You are only a robot.
Hmm, this one's an used one.
Good.
That's it.
This is...
it's not a meteorite. This is the ship Lieutenant Rencon saw.
Anyhow, I should get it off.
Huh? Energy meter is warning.
There's not much energy left. That's odd. I just changed it.
Anyhow, let's hurry.
Wait.
Ah! Energy is...
Gone...
It's a problem. I have to do something.
That's right! If this is a spaceship, I might be able to use it.
Good!
It's dead. Why this?
No more. I have no strength.
Energy has finally been emptied.
Huh? Energy in my body is...
Energy meter is going up.
This crystalline must be the source of energy.
Maybe...
Good. I think I can charge.
So sadly, Captain Atom has passed away through an accident.
Now I, Ketchup, will be the captain!
Salute to Captain Ketchup!
Lieutenant Ketchup, Captain Atom has just come back.
What?
Oh, captain did?
-Captain! -Captain.
-Captain. -Everyone, I caused you to worry.
There was a luminary in the ship, so I was able to survive.
Captain, what is this?
He's an alien. With high intelligence.
An alien?
He even has a mouth.
Captain.
Lieutenant, I have something to talk with you. Come to my room.
Okay.
What is that you want to talk about?
Do you know about Lieutenant Rencon?
Pardon? Is that what you want to talk about?
What's wrong?
Nothing! It's nothing.
I've heard about that man.
Lieutenant thought the Earth was threatened by lives of other planets.
That's why he fought with captain.
No way!
Sorry?
Alien is after the Earth? That's a nonsense.
In the spaceship that Lieutenant Rencon must have seen, there was this alien with gun.
So what?
I don't care about aliens or spaceships.
I've seen many things like this.
But...
Is there any concrete evidence that they are after the Earth?
Evidence?
That's right. A concrete evidence that they are after the Earth.
That is...
I just feel like what Lieutenant Rencon said is true.
How foolish. Please don't call me for such useless talk.
It's the Mars base that the first team built.
Lieutenant Rencon...
-How lucky. -Pardon?
No, it's nothing. Let's go!
Huh? What is this sound?
Lieutenant Ketchup! I'll entrust this to you.
As expected, it's that alien. Then the opposing one is...
Lieutenant Rencon! If you are there, please answer!
I'm Lieutenant Rencon. Who are you?
I'm the captain of the second investigating team.
Captain? Then there must be crew members.
Your sister Cavitt is here, too.
What?
Ah, Lieutenant!
It's dangerous!
Lieutenant, hurry up and... Hood...
-Lieutenant, -I'm fine.
Call everyone and fight them. It will be a big trouble if we just leave it.
I heard it from Cavitt. So they are after the Earth?
I perceived with the base's radar that they head to the Earth from time to time.
They showed up almost everyday here, but they finally have started attacking.
They started it as I was patrolling.
Dang it!
-Shoot, you said you were Atom? -Yes!
They are going to head to the Earth soon, making this their base.
Get everyone!
But the base is more than 300km away.
Use this radio.
Lieutenant Ketchup, it's me, Atom.
-Where are you? -At the point 2428.
Aliens have attacked. Lieutenant, please bring the crew members and come here.
That story again?
Why wouldn't you trust? Aliens are in front of my eyes!
I'm here to investigate for resources.
I have no time to listen to your imagination talks!
I'm only here to carry out missions.
What are you talking about? Lieutenant Ketchup, come right away!
I refuse to.
Lieutenant Ketchup!
Earth people are still so carefree.
This one and that one...
-Right, those guys... -They are headed to the base.
Who would have built it?
Lieutenant Ketchup, there is a trace that someone once lived here.
Lieutenant! There's an alien attack.
What?
-I can't believe it. -Captain, you were saying the truth.
-Stop talking and let's go fight! -Yes, sir!
Cavitt!
Cavitt.
Brother...
-Cavitt. -Brother...
We have to bring them out.
Shoot, monsters!
Ah, Lieutenant Ketchup!
Dangerous!
Captain!
Take everyone and go back to the Chris ship.
Hurry!
We won't lose...
Is that a command ship? If we shoot that down...
Good!
I will fight as long as my body lasts.
One ship remaining.
Lieutenant Ketchup!
What are you doing? Get aboard!
-I'm fine. Depart. -Sorry?
-We can't leave the captain like this! -Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
Get everyone into the Chris ship...
Captain Atom!
There's no more strength to bring the command ship down.
I have no more strength.
Lieutenant Ketchup,
Captain Atom.
It was me who gave you the used-up energy capsule.
I was wrong.
Lieutenant Ketchup...
Lieutenant Ketchup, you...
Ken's father is an air-traffic controller for satellites.
It's an important job of keeping the space shuttle traffic.
Ah! Satellite has been hijacked! Space shuttle will hit the Earth!
No way. We can't stop it even with million horsepower.
Ken! Cut the engine of the space shuttle!
Next on Astro Boy, "SOS on the Space Shuttle."
Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "SOS on the Space Shuttle"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together