Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Sultan, who got expelled from his country for living an extravagant life,
spitefully builds a giant robot called Pluto.
He ordered Pluto to defeat seven strongest robots in the world,
including Atom, to become the greatest robot on the Earth.
Right now, upon the order of Sultan, who has held Dr. Ochanomizu hostage,
Pluto asked Atom for a battle.
Good job, Pluto!
The Greatest Robot In The World (Part Two)
Atom! Atom.
You.
You did it?
Ah!
This is the oilfield base.
There will be a big accident if you fight here.
Atom, come!
Pluto, get over here!
Bring it on.
Ah, how awful!
I'm going to rip your arms and legs off.
Atom, go back to Japan.
You once saved my life earlier.
That time, since you pressed the button on my chest,
I was able to reach my master and survive.
I'll let you live once since you saved me once.
However, I won't forgive you next time.
What about Doctor Ochanomizu?
I'll take responsibility for his life.
All right, it's a promise!
Atom, I'll leave the match with you for my last joy.
My name is Hercules!
I've been waiting, Pluto.
I'll teach you which one is the greatest robot on the Earth.
Come!
What a confidence! How suitable it is for your name!
Let me finish you in ten minutes!
I see. So Pluto's vulnerable point is that
he can't use both his arms when he's flying.
I'm coming!
One more time!
Here I go!
That's going some.
Here, let me give your weapon back.
I don't need this!
I won't get the weapon I once lost back!
How are you going to fight without a weapon?
In the old days, Trojans chose to die rather than to get pitied by an enemy.
Pluto! The real match begins from now on.
Do you think you will be able to endure my special electromagnetic wave?
Look! I am the greatest robot on the Earth!
Fifth one.
The next one is Epsilon.
Good kids, stop crying and listen.
This Uncle Epsilon has to say goodbyes to you now.
We don't want you to! Why?
Why do you have to?
-Don't go! -Of course I want to stay here as well.
However, if Pluto comes...
I'm a photon robot. The source of my energy is sunlight, which is infinite.
I won't get defeated that easily.
-Uncle, don't go. -Kids, please do understand.
I won't let you go.
Don't go, Uncle.
I'm not going to lose for these kids.
No, I'm going to win no matter what.
I can't rescue Doctor Ochanomizu unless I defeat Pluto.
What am I supposed to do?
You can do it if you obtain a million horsepower as well.
Go ask the Ministry of Science to remodel you right now!
I'm against it.
Dad.
Doctor Ochanomizu would be against it as well.
Atom only has 100,000 horsepower, but he's got wisdom.
Doctor Ochanomizu said similar things.
If you use that wisdom well, your horsepower could increase tenfold and hundredfold.
Atom, a righteous robot indeed can be the greatest robot in the world.
Ah, that's right. When you were all out,
there was a call for Atom from Australia.
What?
It was from a guy called Epsilon who takes care of kids with no parents,
and he said he wants to borrow your power for defeating Pluto.
Pluto? Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
Robots do forget from time to time.
Epsilon.
Why did you pick a day like this?
Because you are a photon robot.
You won't be able to get solar energy because of this weather.
How mean...
Taking advantage of your enemy's vulnerable point is also a good strategy.
I'm coming.
How swift.
Uncle Epsilon, where are you?
Uncle!
Hold on, Pluto!
Where's Epsilon?
Kids, tell me.
I need sunlight...
Atom.
Pluto! What are you doing?
I was born to fight, and to win.
-What? -Hold on.
Ah, you are...
I'm Doctor Abura who built this Pluto.
Atom, I ask you one more time to fight with Pluto.
-Location is Mt. Aso in Japan. -What about Doctor Ochanomizu?
Whether you win or lose,
I'll let him go once the fight is over. So don't worry.
Good.
It's here! Here!
Atom! You shouldn't fight this guy!
Pluto is designed to self-destruct if it gets broken, so the opponent would get destroyed as well!
I investigated it!
Shut up, you blabbermouth.
Atom, let's finish this battle today.
Pluto, do you really have to fight?
Don't ask the same question over and over again. I was built to fight.
I'm coming, Atom.
All right!
Coming!
Atom!
-Ah, Pluto! -Atom won.
Pluto won't get defeated with this!
-Atom, trouble. -Pardon?
It seems like Mt. Aso has started to erupt.
Nearby towns will be covered with rains of fire.
Doctor!
Make a mountain with big rocks on top of possible eruptions spots.
Atom, hurry!
I'll try!
Atom, what are you doing?
It seems like it's going to erup. Help me!
Pluto, what are you doing? Can't you feel this danger?
I was built to fight.
I don't want to use my energy for anything else but fighting.
Pluto, I'm glad I don't have million horsepower like you do!
Even if I only have 100,000 horsepower, I know what's most precious in this world!
Please save as many people's lives as possible.
Ah... It won't work now.
Pluto!
Atom, I'll help you.
Thank you!
Sultan, do you see that? They are working together.
That is the true figure of robots.
Doctor Ochanomizu! The tremor has stopped.
Oh, the earthquake has stopped, too. Now it won't erupt.
Pluto!
Yay!
Atom, I did such thing for the first time in my life.
It's a good thing, Pluto!
What are you smiling at?
Pluto! Come fight atom! Let's settle this!
No. I don't want to fight with Atom.
What? How come?
Atom is a great robot. It would be a disgrace for me to fight Atom.
What are you talking about?
Fight Atom to become the greatest robot on the Earth!
Sultan,
Allow me to fight Bora instead of Atom.
Abura, what in the world...
It's the greatest robot of the world, Bora, with 2 million horsepower.
2 million horsepower?
Without defeating this, Pluto wouldn't be able to be called the greatest robot on the Earth.
For what did you built such thing?
Here, fight it, Pluto. Fight, Bora!
Pluto! You shouldn't!
It's dangerous!
Pluto!
I was built to fight.
That's right! Then Pluto! Get rid of that monster!
Atom, say hi to Uran.
Pluto!
Atom, I won't forget you.
P... P... Pluto!
There's not even a scratch.
Bora! The next one is Atom!
Energy is going to run out.
Good!
Atom,
Pluto.
Atom.
-Thank you for defeating Bora. -What?
Sultan, do you understand now
how stupid it is to measure who's the strongest?
Abura.
Oh, you are the servant robot who used to take care of me.
What in the world happened?
In fact, since Sultan wanted the greatest robot on the Earth,
I disguised as a human robot scientist to build Pluto.
But Sultan started harming other robots with Pluto.
I built Bora to teach him of his foolishness.
Sultan, being the greatest robot in the world isn't about being strong.
It's about being wise and righteous
like Atom, who only is of 100,000 horsepower.
Do you see it, Sultan?
Doctor Ochanomizu, Atom, you've done a lot.
Everyone was a great robot...
Doctor, why do they fight?
The strong one desires to brag about its strength.
However, in the end, it will ruin itself as well with that strength.
However, Atom,
I believe one day in which
no one fights will come some day.
Neither robots nor humans.
Near the mountain of fire
Pluto, burst into fragments
on the floor of sea of clouds and the earth,
You have walked with me
the path I shall take with no hesitation, no doubt,
and no hatred, and then disappeared.
Montblanc, Morse the 2nd,
Blande, Gezihit,
Hercules, Epsilon.
When are they going to bring judgment
on people who have created and destroyed lives
for their own desire for power and control?
The Gothem Gang running through the city.
They destroy buildings and robots one by one.
We have to stop that robot gang no matter how!
To where are you going to take Jump?
All right. I'm going to disguise as a dog and save him.
When I was chasing after Gothem, one shows up in front of me.
Ah! Atlas!
Next on Astro Boy,
"Atom vs. Atlas V, The Gothem Gang." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Gothem Gang"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together