Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
So Boss, we are destroying that White Planet vehicle, right?
That's right. We have to stop it from winning six consecutive times, Kill.
We have to let Black Devil win this year's Equator race.
All right, Boss. I'll take care of it tonight.
The Vehicle, White Planet
Koichi, pull the lever slightly.
Yes, sir.
Push the throttle as much as possible.
Yes, sir!
-Atom, is the spin output enough? -Yes!
-No problem. -Good.
This is a great racing machine. We will win this year as well with this.
Doctor, thank you.
White Planet is like my brother.
I could hear compliments for it as many time as possible.
I see. Since the deceased father of yours, once my colleague, made it,
it could really be called as your brother.
Koichi!
The meal's ready.
Mitsuko, White Planet will win this year for sure as well.
Doctor Ochanomizu guaranteed it.
What if it doesn't win? Then it's all your fault for driving it bad.
How can you say that?
Stop there, Mitsuko.
Doctor, please rest yourself here tonight.
-Please? Is it all right? -Please? I ask you, too.
It's fun since it feels like I have both father and brother.
Doctor, tell us more about our father.
All right. Your father was an outstanding engineer...
Ah, White Planet is...
It's dangerous! Get down!
Brother, it's dangerous. Don't go!
Le, let me go. White Planet is...
Mr. Koichi, I'll get White Planet.
Ah... White Planet is dead.
Who did this to White Planet? Give it back!
Give White Planet back to me.
Ah, I can't participate in the race anymore.
I'd rather than lose White Planet!
Brother, don't be too upset. I'm worried more about you than White Planet.
Stupid!
Mitsuko is a fool.
Don't you know how much I love this White Planet?
Doctor, is there any way we can fix White Planet?
Um... I'm afraid it's difficult.
An electronic brain used for White Planet is the problem.
It's a machine that is as elaborate as human. There is no extra in the Ministry of Science.
Is that so...?
That's right, there's one way.
Atom, could you lend us your electronic brain during the Equator race?
Huh? Then I'm becoming a robot car?
Here, White Planet is almost recovered. Here, Atom.
Now we have to transplant your electronic brain. Are you ready, Atom?
Yes! I'll do my best!
Doctor, I have something to tell you.
We are in Polynesia. It is the starting point of the Equator race.
This race is a race that goes around the earth
running straight through the oceans and mountains.
However, if one gets more than 2km away from the equator or flies more than 5m above the land,
one will be disqualified.
Now the rock band Roberts has showed up!
When this song is over, the race will begin.
Also, this race will be broadcasted all over the world
via tracking satellite #194.
Now, it will start in 10 minutes!
Strong racers from all over the world has arrived after the preliminaries.
Huh? What has happened?
White Planet, the winner for last five years, hasn't arrived yet.
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
What a way for White Planet.
Black Devil will win for sure this year.
No, no way.
Ah, it has appeared. It's White Planet.
The greatest machine for another victory is now here!
Kill, Kill!
Ah, yes! Boss.
Do you know where White Planet is?
Bo, Boss. I don't what happened. I did destroy it for sure.
All right, change of the plan.
Do you copy? Mark White Planet completely.
Yes, sir!
Doctor Ochanomizu,
I was able to participate in this race thanks to you.
Atom, let's do this.
That's odd. Mitsuko's not here to cheer.
Is she still mad?
Now the countdown has begun.
10, 9, 8
7, 6, 5, 4
3, 2, 1, 0!
All machines have departed!
Oh! A collision. What an early accident!
Machines in collision start to burn. The course is in chaos.
With Black Devil at the head, King Cobra, Magic Bus
and High Spider have formed a leading group.
White Planet, a winner candidate, seems to be in confusion.
Oh! White Planet has escaped barely.
As expected, Atom. Great response.
Melanesia
Melanesia, the leading group is above the Melanesian Ocean.
Black Devil, who won last year's second place, is at the head.
It's a hovercraft type.
Next in line, King Cobra. Praises for its tenacity.
Magic Bus and High Spider are next in line.
White Planet, who's catching up, is still behind.
It had a bad start after getting in the accident right after the start.
Sumatra
Problem. The video has been cut off from the satellite 194.
-What's wrong? -Contact space administration right away.
They can't broadcast what we are doing.
Way to go, boss.
Good, let's move on to the next plan. Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Dear viewers, We are very sorry the video has stopped.
The tracking satellite 194 for this race has been bombed by something.
What happened?
What a trouble!
The Indian Ocean
Somalian coast
Submarine Victoria
Black Devil will soon appear.
Ah! Boss, it's here!
Good. Good work, Black Devil. Keep it up.
I'm going to smash White Planet.
Boss, we shouldn't be discovered.
-Ah, that's right. Good, go under! -Yes, sir!
Gosh, you guys!
Do you copy? When White Planet arrives, come up and attack it.
-Get ready to fight! -Yes, sir!
It's here, here!
Here, get ready to come up. Come up and destroy White Planet!
Yes, Boss!
Stupid, I told you to get ready to come up.
Ah, hey!
Who told you to go under? You have to come up! Don't go under!
We didn't do anything.
Hey. Something passed by above us right now, right?
Yeah, I saw it too.
-Hey! It's dangerous. -You wait and see.
Was he still alive?
Take this!
Ah! This octopus was a robot?
Wow, it's gone!
Huh? The octopus isn't here. It's alive. Good, let me hurry.
Energy is...
Huh? Atom's position is fixed.
Ah! What a trouble. Atom's SOS signal is on.
Boss, there's a problem.
-Mecca Octopus is all messed up. -Oh, no!
Now I can't forgive this. Next plan, next!
Amazon River
Bottomless swamp
The Andes Mountains
It has finally caught up. Pretty good.
What about this?!
Don't bring it up. How's this!
Did you give up?
What?
I'm upset.
I can't give way that easily.
Good, then...
Kid, why don't you give up...
Huh? It's not here!
Ah! I'm done!
Shoot, I'm going to finish it no matter what.
Gosh!
I did it!
Ecuadorian coast
Kill, what a clumsy one.
Chase it down!
Galapagos Islands
Ah, good.
White Planet is at the head.
Huh? Th... That is...
It's a nuclear torpedo!
Mr. Koichi! Be careful!
Nuclear torpedo is going next in line with White Planet.
At the course P, 120 degrees west longitude, it will explode in three minutes.
Change the course!
Hey, was it you that has been interfering, Atom?
If I speed down here, I won't be able to win.
That's right! I can pass through the course P point at 120 degrees west longitude a minute before!
Good.
Was it wrong?
Atom, you won't be able to interfere anymore. Take this!
Mr. Koichi, Ah!
Good, here!
Atom... You wait and see.
It doesn't work now.
Now I've reached my limit!
The speed is... By itself... This machine...
It's moving by itself.
What in the world is happening?
If I don't do anything... Something...
Mr. Koichi! Mr. Koichi!
Dang,
Please, run for me.
Please let's just get over this one.
Ah! You shouldn't be driving it so roughly!
Huh? Atom. What are you doing there...
No. Why would you drive it so roughly? Are you going to destroy Mitsuko?
What?
When Mr. Koichi's father
built White Planet, he made an extra electronic brain.
That electronic brain was preserved safely as a robot.
No way that robot is...
That's right! It's your sister, Mitsuko.
Mitsuko told us secretly and said she wanted to be White Planet.
Did she?
So Mitsuko sped up that much
beyond her limit to save me.
Thank you, Mitsuko.
In Gravia country, a robot has been elected as the president for the first time in the world.
Congratulations! President Larg.
But the Deadcrosses that hate robots will...
It's dangerous!
Giant robots and assassins start attacking.
Don't lose, President Larg!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Robot President"
Look forward to it!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together