Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
It's so crowded.
No robot could beat that energy.
Mari!
Uran.
-Where's your mom? -She's making her way there.
Wait! Hold on! It's mine.
Hey! Who's pulling? This is mine!
Mari's mom!
Uran's mom. Robots also come to place like this?
-Hey, Uran, would you like to go upstairs? -Let's go.
-Uran, you are the same as escalator, right? -Why?
Well, you are a robot.
My dad told me that robot is a machine.
Then what is human?
Human is human.
Wow, amazing!
Mari, look! This robot looks great.
-It's weird. -What is?
Well, Uran's a robot as well, right? Same as this toy!
I'm different from this robot. This is a toy!
The same.
If you say so, humans also do have same things.
No. There isn't anything same as human.
-There is! -Nope.
There is!
Stop!
Hey, stop!
What's wrong?
Don't run!
Uran.
I found it!
I got it!
Look, Mari's the same as this.
Cockroach!
Was there an earthquake?
Uran's God
We can never stop Uran.
Well, I'm thankful we were able to be forgiven by compensating.
It's still yet to be organized.
That must be Mari's dad.
Don't ever let her hang out with my Mari!
Yes... Okay.
-What's wrong? -Uran.
How dare she compares my daughter to a cockroach? She hates it the most!
But humans are the same living things like cockroaches.
Stupid! Don't put humans and cockroaches on the same line!
Then should robots be put on the same line with escalators and toys?!
Uran.
Anyhow, this is a fight between kids.
I think they are all the same.
What?
Humans, cockroaches, and robots... They are all the same once they are disassembled into atoms.
Well, well.
No way! Humans are treated the same with robots and cockroaches?
What in the world are you guys teaching your kids here?
Well, even without teaching, Atom's pretty smart.
Rather, he teaches me.
My gosh. I don't want to talk to you anymore!
I'm very sorry.
Why do we have to apologize?
This society is unfair for robots.
Especially, Mari's parents think humans are the most outstanding ones.
How come?
Because robots were created by men.
-Then who created men? -Well... That's...
I don't know about that.
I heard God created men.
God. Where's God, Atom?
I don't know.
Where is God... That's a difficult question.
Even you don't know, Dr.Ochanomizu?
Well, God is in a man's heart.
Where? Show me!
Uran, stop it!
Doctor always pretends to know about things, but he doesn't know anything.
There are things even he doesn't know.
-I'm disappointed! -Stop it now, Uran.
God. I want to meet God.
I'm going to meet him and ask why he created humans.
All right. I'm going to go find God!
But where can I meet him?
-This is "Gods of the World", right? -Thank you.
Gods of the World #1. Christ.
In the beginning of A.D. years, Jesus Christ was born.
Nazareth's craftsman Joseph's fiancee, Mary, was conceived by the Holy Spirit
and gave birth to him in Bethlehem.
When Jesus was about 30 years old, he was baptized by John the Baptist...
Gods of the World #2. Buddha.
About five centuries B.C., Buddha who appeared in India
unraveled the secrets of the universe
and started teaching and spreading those secrets.
After his death, the religion developed according to each generation and area...
Gods of the World #3. Muhammad.
Muhammad, who founded Islam religion,
was born in the prestigious Quraish family.
In 610 A.D...
Hinduism Hindu is a Persian word for Sindu in Sanskrit.
Originally, river, especially India's...
Zoroaster.
Zoroaster was from the 7th century B.C.
to the 6th century B.C. It's India's ancient...
Huihui. It's a fire-worshiping religion.
It believes fire is the source for all lives.
I didn't know there were so many gods.
Besides, it's not scientific.
Robot's God wouldn't surely be like that.
Would there be Robot's God for Uran?
Jesus Christ,
Allah,
Buddha,
God of grains,
Bodhisattva,
Greek gods,
Hindi gods,
Amaterazu Oomikami,
Gukai,
Countless number of
human gods on sale!
Teach me, Uran's God.
Where are you?
-Are you looking for God? -Yes...
Ask Doctor Oz in the Children's Land.
Children's Land?
Doctor Oz?
Here, here.
"Ask Anything to Dr.Oz"?
I ask Dr.Oz a question.
Why do rabbits have red eyes?
Why have you come to ask such lame question?
That is because blood vessels inside rabbit's eyes show.
Huh? What are blood vessels?
Blood vessels are tubes that carry blood.
Next one.
What's your question? Ask.
Where is God?
-God is... -What's wrong?
God is... God...
-Whatever. Ask me another question. -I thought you knew everything.
There is nothing I don't know.
Then answer me!
There shouldn't be anything I don't know.
Then answer me now!
I think there isn't anything I don't know.
You are losing your confidence. You don't know the answer.
God!
What is this, I expected too much.
What's wrong? Are you angry?
I am God.
What are you talking about?
I'm omnipotent. I know everything. Therefore I'm God!
Stop joking and answer me!
-It's broken. -No, I'm not.
God doesn't break down.
He's so persistent. If you are God, then show me the proof!
I rule over everything in the Children's Land.
Even humans cannot defeat me.
This is the proof.
It's scary!
It's so scary!
Problem! Computer's out of order!
All right!
What? God? I'll stop this!
This is the power of God. I am God!
Atom, help me!
My gosh, Uran.
Where is she?
That sound is...
-Atom! -Uran!
See? Isn't my brother great?
He can't beat me. I'm God.
You are still saying that?
There is no one who can beat Atom!
You disgraceful robot! How can you not fear God?
I'll show you my power!
This place is...?
Uran!
Uran?!
I see! This is the Adventure Land under the Children's Land, right?
However, it's different from that spider that deals with children all the time.
It moves upon my will.
What is this?
You are a robot.
If you acknowledge me as God, then I'll let you out.
Ridiculous!
It hurts. What are you doing?
No!
They aren't normal butterfly robots.
They will absorb your energy like they suck honey.
Atom! Help me!
That's Uran's voice.
It's underground. All right!
Stop it!
Hey!
-Atom! -Are you all right, Uran?
What is all this fuss about?
This computer at the amusement park
suddenly started torturing me saying "I'm God."
I'm God.
God's power wouldn't stop here.
What? God? You are a computer.
I'm great. I'm God!
I'll go ahead and cut your power supply now!
Do you think you can make it here?
I'm definitely coming!
It's now the Magical Land from here.
Atom!
Uran!
Help!
Stop!
Don't interrupt me.
Atom!
Uran!
Atom, this is space.
This is only a trick!
Punishment for disobeying God will be huge!
This is the Chamber of Mirrors.
Atom.
-Uran! -Atom! Where are you, Atom?
Uran! Where are you?
Over here! Come quickly, Atom!
This is odd. I feel like I'm losing my energy whenever I break a mirror.
Atom! Where are you? I'm scared.
Uran! Don't move! You'll get your energy taken away!
Then I'll find her with my hearing ability.
Atom! Where are you? Help me!
-Uran. -Atom.
This sound is...
It's the sound of a computer. It's under this.
All right, Uran. Step aside.
This is the main computer room.
We are finally here.
Something's wrong with you!
I'm God. Are you trying to blaspheme God?
Are you still talking about that?
Cut your power supply and get yourself fixed.
I cannot let anyone touch God!
I'll cut it for you.
You see? No one can approach God.
It's a barrier.
Atom!
Stop it. It's no good. You can't break this barrier.
Shoot... If I only had some more energy...
You understand, Uran? This time, we will bump against it together.
Okay.
I told you it's no good.
Atom! Are you all right?
You should be running out of your energy now.
I'll finish you now.
Uran, step aside.
How is it?
What are you doing to him?
Uran, stop it!
Uran!
I don't have any more energy now...
What's up? Are you done now?
Crush it at once.
If you crush him, I won't stay still!
How's this?
Uran!
Uran! Step aside!
Wh, wh, what are you doing?
Right now!
Now is the chance.
Power switch is...
Stop it. Stop.
This is it.
Stop it. Don't... Don't turn it off!
I'm God! God! God...!
Go, God...
You did it!
Why would a computer delude itself into God?
Then, it must have caused a problem as soon as it was asked that question.
It doesn't seem like it's Uran's fault this time.
That's right! I was only looking after God.
God cannot be seen with our eyes.
Since He cannot be seen, humans revere and fear Him.
Poor humans. They can't see their own creator.
Since we were created by men, we can see them with our eyes.
Who created me?
He's right in front of you.
Dr.Ochanomizu?
So my God is Dr.Ochanomizu?
God... Well, theoretically, yes.
What?
See? It's better to not know about God.
I see.
-I see. -Uran!
What are you doing? Let's hang out.
Hey, wait.
-Mari, let's hang out over there. -Okay!
I told you you shouldn't hang out together!
-Kids are so simple. -Pardon?
It seems like only adults are swayed by other things.
Kids never discriminate against robots or humans.
Yes...
By the time they grow up,
robots and humans would be equal.
Dr.Ochanomizu, I finally figured out the cause of that computer's breakdown.
This cockroach was stuck in its machine.
A cockroach? This is why it became God?
We were chased by a cockroach all day long.
A gang invades the space airport R-45!
The satellite patrol is dispatched!
However, there is a huge secret about Captain Tsukioka.
Next on Astro Boy, "Space Airport R45"
Even though she is bit mischievous
Innocent smile on her face
Uran
Everyone's calling
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
Uran
When you are around
We always have fun
She likes her brother Atom
And she likes songs and dreams
Uran is like an angel
Everyone's calling