Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
We will now enter the populated joint area in about 20 minutes.
Good. Air traffic control satellite 110 inducement beacon reception standby.
Yes, sir.
SOS on the Space Shuttle
Transport ship Orion 108 has entered the control area.
The regular ship has come back. Open the communication circuit.
Yes, sir!
This is control satellite 110. Thank you for your effort during the long trip.
Welcome back.
Hey, Nao. Now that I hear your voice, I feel like I have finally arrived at the Earth.
It was a long one this time.
Nao, thank you for your effort as well.
For someone like us whom you never know when will return.
Couldn't you count on machines for sending signals?
Ah, that can't be accepted.
If there's a mistake, then there will be a big accident.
-Take care of us next time as well, Nao. -Of course.
-Robita, please take care of inducement. -Yes, sir!
What's wrong, Ken?
You haven't gone to school yet?
No... I don't want to go to school.
You always say that after a holiday.
Here, if you don't hurry, you will miss the shuttle.
Dad, until when are you going to keep working as an air traffic controller?
-Why do you care? -Nothing.
I just hope you would work on ground.
This place is bit lonely, but it's a very important work.
If you don't study hard, you won't be able to succeed me.
I don't want to succeed you.
This is amazing.
I don't know what's what. Tamao's glasses are awesome!
Shibukaki, give them back to me.
I can't see anything without glasses.
Ken's here.
Really?
-Give them back. -It's not me.
Here, I'll give them back.
Huh? Where? Where did you put them?
Ha ha. He's here. He's here.
-Hey, are you commuting from a satellite? -Alien!
-Isn't Earth's gravity bit heavy for you? -Are you all right?
He's here.
-Gosh! -What are you doing?
Space traffic lights don't need bags, right?
-Give it back! -Take it if you can.
-What are you doing? Give it back! -Take it!
You zero gravity kid, fly here with no gravity.
What are you doing? Give it back to me!
It's coming!
Alien! Space traffic light!
Stop it!
Fly to the space!
-Are you making fun again? -Atom, don't interrupt me.
Ken's father is an air traffic controller.
-Stop it, Atom. -But Ken,
Don't mind my business!
You are going to become a space traffic light anyway when you grow up, right?
How dare you come down to the ground?
-Flying, flying. -How is it? Are you watching this?
Amazing. Quick one. It's good.
Good, it's perfect. Isn't Ken here yet?
Wait, give me my bag back!
Give it back!
-All right! -Ken's bag is here!
Give it back. Give it back to me!
Attack!
Space traffic light.
What is it.
What is an adult doing here? That's expensive.
Let me go! Naoto! Osamu, help me!
It's scary...
Run away!
Hey, kids!
You are Ken Hoshiyama, right?
Mister, do you know me?
-Your dad is ill. -Pardon? My dad is?
Here, get aboard.
Shibukaki, what happened?
Atom.
Naoto and Osamu have all abandoned me and left.
What happened?
Ken's bag. What happened to Ken?
-He blew me and took Ken. -What?
He's a villain for sure. He blew me.
Good.
-Mister, the direction is different. -Shut up!
Mister, did you fool me?
Over there!
Good!
Ah, wait. Hold on, Atom!
Take me too!
I was struck hard. I have to repay it!
Well, well.
Amazing. Hey, Atom, try flying faster.
Yup!
No, no, no. Fly slower. I can't breathe.
You told me to go faster.
By the way, that car is headed this way, right?
Yes, it is.
Did you bring him? Hurry and get aboard.
To where are you taking me?
No, no!
Let me go!
Hey, Atom.
You are sure, right? There's only a port for personal rockets.
I heard a sound from this direction for sure.
Dad!
-It's that small rocket! -Atom, chase it!
Chase it and get rid of it!
No.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, you must have missed it because of me.
You will figure out the destination if you ask the control center about that rocket.
Okay. That would be good.
What's wrong?
An unexpected small space shuttle is approaching.
Small space shuttle?
Personal shuttle must have been lost again.
Well, following the protocol, activate the defense system.
Yes, sir!
Approaching shuttle, this is a route only for cargo ships.
Go back to private route.
No change. It's headed right to us.
Can you hear? If you approach more than this, we will fire.
Fire if you want to.
What?
But after you see this.
Ken!
Dad, help me!
Are you still going to shoot?
I have some business there. Can you open the entrance?
Ken,
Dad!
Your job is not over yet.
So what are you going to do with this?
Well, you just have to lead the transport ship
Carolina 3 to a bit different place.
What? Carolina 3?
Yeah, it contains much pladium.
If we get that much of pladium at once, we will make a fortune.
I will never do such thing!
Robitas here only listen to what I say.
Kill me if you can!
Dad!
Eyes... I can't see anything.
The next one is your son. I'm not going to go easy.
Please hold that!
Then, listen to what I say.
Carolina 3 has entered the control area.
What do I have to do?
You are quick to understand.
Lead Carolina 3 to the third evacuation point.
They told us to wait at the third evacuation point.
Is there something wrong?
They told us to take precautions since there is an epidemic.
Good. Move to the third evacuation point.
Good job.
Then, we won't need robots anymore. Destroy them.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
What about these ones?
Hold on. We will hold them hostages at a time of need.
Then I will go to Carolina 3.
-You keep a close watch. -Yes, sir!
Captain! Small shuttle is approaching.
It must be the quarantine ship. Prepare docking.
Yes, sir!
We've caused you trouble.
Don't move!
They are pirates!
Who in the world are you...
Hey, something's coming this way.
Kid, stop it!
Atom!
Atom?
Good!
Shoot! It doesn't work!
It's coming here.
-Ken, -Dad!
Atom.
Don't shoot!
I surrender!
Good, two of you, get in the storage!
Are you all right? I'm Atom.
Oh, you are Ken's classmate... Thank you, Atom.
Atom, there's a trouble.
Transport ship with pladium is being attacked.
What?
I have to go save it. Where is that?
Atom, take this radio. Let Ken give you directions.
All right.
Atom, please get rid of bad guys.
Okay!
Atom, can you hear me?
Carolina 3 is at SSW 7 o'clock direction!
All right. Roger!
It's that. Good!
Do you think you will be all right after you do such things?
Get off at the place we tell you immediately.
Don't you know it's dangerous to not go on the route we are told to?
Stop talking and move!
What is that sound just now?
Atom!
Computer
is broken now.
Look at you. Now you won't be safe either, huh?
Where in the world are these guys' boss?
Huh?
It was almost over. Atom, you wait and see!
Stop!
Atom. Atom, there's a problem.
An unattended transport ship is approaching.
That's a shuttle from the Moon.
Since it's on the settled route, it won't stop if possible.
Ah, Carolina 3 is falling.
No way!
-Dad, Carolina 3 is falling. -What?
Atom's supporting it, but it's hard. What shall we do?
Calm down.
-But what should we do? -Be calm, Ken.
First of all, look at the right side of the panel.
I'm looking at it.
Push the DIZ switch on the top right.
-Change the screen. -This one?
How does it look, Ken? Is Carolina 3 within the safe area for re-entering?
No, Dad. It's falling sharply from the green orbit.
What? Then it will explode with pladium.
-Huh? If that happens... -A great disaster would happen.
No. It's too heavy.
What should we do? It will soon melt.
Ken! Is Carolina 3's main engine moving?
Yes!
Then no matter what it takes, raise the ship head up.
I see. Atom, can you hear me?
Supporting the entire ship is difficult, even if it were for you.
But...
Make the ship head point upward. Can you do it?
All right!
-How's it? -No change yet.
It started to move up, Dad!
-Change the screen to L3! -Okay!
Command Carolina 3.
Stop the main engine.
If you don't do it, Carolina 3 will be lost in space.
Prepare to stop the main engine.
But the computer's broken! How?!
Stop it no matter what it takes. Twist open the panel!
Dad, Carolina 3 is back in track.
Let Atom escape.
Atom! It's done! Now get off.
Switch off the main engine.
Bring fire extinguisher!
Atom.
Are you all right? We are safe thanks to you.
No, I just did what Ken told me to do.
Ken?
I heard the story from Atom. You did a good job. Thank you.
You saved life.
That is...
If Atom weren't there, I wouldn't have been able to do anything.
And... Are Nao's eyes all right?
Yes, they are fine. I am yet to retire.
Is that so? You have a great successor next to you.
Do you think I can succeed him?
You finally have some interest.
I didn't know how important what dad does.
I'm sorry about this morning.
Well, what was it?
Since today was a crazy day, I don't remember anything.
That's right! We have to report it to the police. We also have to repair Robita.
It seems like we'll get busy.
I'll go to school well from now on.
Shiny in space, Rainbow Comet.
Amazing...
The 3-3 class astronomy club is going on a field trip by rocket.
Huh? What happened? Rocket's getting dragged to something!
It's Crystal! Atlas, you are here.
Next on Astro Boy,
"Atom vs. Atlas IV." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Atom vs. Atlas IV"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together