Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Hello, everyone in the Earth. This is the spaceship Titanic.
It has been ten days since we departed from the Earth.
The Moon Tour with 450 passengers is very comfortable.
We are traveling through the course very smoothly.
Mr. Nishiyama from Aurora firm, how does it feel like to be aboard?
It's the best.
Bring the drinks! The most expensive one!
This couple is the happiest one that won the raffle of 500,000 couples.
How is the space honeymoon?
It's a problem.
The designer of this space passenger ship, Doctor Kanda
and the Minister of Science Doctor Ochanomizu are here.
-How comfortable, Doctor. -Thank you.
This is all thanks to my teacher, Doctor Ochanomizu.
Ah, meteor!
Meteor is approaching!
But everyone in the Earth, please don't worry.
The latest automatic barrier device of this Titan ship
will bounce this meteor off!
Captain, computer's not working!
What?
Shift it to manual operation.
It won't work, Captain! It's too late to shift now.
The Fool Ivan
Announcement to passengers. Titan ship will soon explode.
Please get on the assigned life-ship and evacuate to Lagrande's satellite base!
Doctor! Doctor Ochanomizu!
Atom...
Doctor Kanda! Where did Dr. Ochanomizu go?
He went to the life-ship with the crowd. He will be fine.
Help!
I don't want to die!
We don't have enough life-ships. Can we do something?
Help me.
There should be extra life-ship beside the engine room.
-Oh. -Hurry!
-Hurry, Atom! -Okay!
-Thank God. -Ah... It was close.
Ah, thank goodness.
Ah! The rudder instrument is broken.
What?
We won't be able to reach Lagrande's evacuation base like this.
Honey!
Can we not survive somehow, Doctor?
We are willing to pay as much as you want. Isn't there any way?
We can reach the Moon if we keep traveling like this.
Let's get off at the Moon and think about it.
Huh? Moon?
What are you going to do there? There isn't atmosphere anyway.
There will be a base camp.
Outside temperature is -200℃.
- -200℃? -It feels like I'm freezing just to hear the words.
Let's shoot a rocket and ask for help.
The Moon base camp might sense it.
It's strange. It's broken.
No way! Try again!
It doesn't work no matter how hard I try.
Ah, it's over now. We are all going to die.
-What is that? -Huh? Is there something?
It's like a ghost.
It's staring at us.
-I'm scared, honey. -It might be alien.
I'll check the situation, Doctor.
-Be careful, Atom. -Okay!
You monster! I'll figure out who you are.
Huh? It's a dead tree.
Huh? What is that?
It's ice. Ice.
...It's like this.
-All right. That's air. -Really?
Air must have frozen for sure.
We have arrived at a crater with atmosphere.
Hey! Atom!
Is that so? Do you want me to bring that ice into the life-ship?
Gosh!
It won't work. Since this rocket has some heat,
it melts when it gets closer here.
Doctor, there is the list of people who's gone missing.
Doctor Kanda and Atom, and Nishiyama Narika,
Tarui Hutoshi, the executive of a company,
TV announcer, newly-weds, and a 14-year-old boy. Total of eight.
However, we are sending out communication wave
around 100,000km radius of the explosion spot, but there's no response.
Besides, even if they did escape with the life-ship, they must be out of air by now.
Please be alive. Atom, Kanda.
It's hot. It feels like I'm in sauna.
-It's hard to breathe. -I'm hungry...
No! We will be out of air within an hour.
Then! Then we will be suffocated!
-Honey! -Ah, Noriko!
Suffocate? Gosh! That's not possible! Are you telling me to die in a place like this?
What should I do? Please do something. Do something!
Everyone, get out.
Air in this life-ship is all mine. There's none for you!
-That's a pistol. -How did you get such...!
You don't need to know. Get out!
Nishiyama. You used to be in a gang.
Stop that kind of threat here!
It's dawn.
The Moon's dawn.
Frozen air is starting to melt. It's vaporizing with solar heat.
We are safe!
We are safe! According to this gas analyzer,
the amount of oxygen in this air is almost the same as the Earth's.
Yay!
Honey! We are safe now!
-Us too. -Yes.
It's colder than I thought.
Ah, but I can bear this much.
Cold air tastes good.
This is the Moon!
How impressive! How could I express this feeling!
-What is it? -Ah, it's grass!
This is...
Wow, it's amazing. It really grows fast!
I see. A day at the Moon is the same as four weeks in the Earth.
Plants grow within that hour
and when the night falls, it becomes -200℃and everything dies.
Before the night falls and air freezes,
we have to fix the broken part.
Okay!
Help!
What's wrong?
It's a monster!
Monster?
-It looks like a male human. -I'll go check!
The monster's that one!
Stop!
Huh? I missed it.
It's a rocket.
It's a very old looking rocket.
It's an old cassette player.
My name is Minya Mikhailovna.
Flying officer of the Soviet Union.
Female voice.
I safely arrived at the surface of the Moon with the probe rocket Ural.
Unfortunately, it fell from a cliff
and the rocket fell into a deep crack.
I was safe fortunately, but the rocket was heavily damaged.
Besides, the communication device was broken.
I decided to die. And that was the moment.
I saw some air bursting like smoke along with dawn.
I jumped out and started shedding tears of joy.
Then, my life as Robinson Crusoe began.
Ivan the robot does the tough works.
Ivan is the first human-like robot of the Soviet Union.
I acquired underground water with the help of Ivan.
I pumped air to the rocket and saved it as liquid oxygen.
So I could survive somehow.
However, Ivan.
I want to go back to the Earth! To the Earth!
One day, I discovered something amazing.
It's diamond.
I'm going to be rich!
However...
It's not worth anything in this Moon.
I gave that diamond as earrings to Ivan.
My body weakened day by day. I got disease.
Then today, I felt that my day is coming.
Ivan, we will soon part.
It's the last order. If I die, bury me in that hole.
This is my report.
If a person comes here later, the diamond valley...
How poor. How lonely must that one had been?
Ivan!
I'm Atom. I heard your story. How lonely.
Ah! What are you doing?
Don't mistake me for Minya.
I'm not doing it!
I'm a robot like you. So get off of me!
I see. You are glad to see a person after a long time.
But!
This is not a time for this!
Hello!
Ah... I'm hungry.
You are wrong for suggesting such trip!
I shouldn't have married you if this were to happen!
There are fruits! Fruits!
What? Fruits?
What a disgusting color.
It might be toxic.
Toxic?
-You try first. -Why...!
It's delicious. This one's good.
Where have you been?
Over there. There are tons over there.
Good!
Hmm... A rocket from 30 years ago.
All right. Let me tell everyone.
Then! Let's do it again!
Huh? 30 years ago?
Yes. And that pilot survived after such an effort.
We can do it too!
We gave up a long time ago.
Yeah, efforts won't pay off.
When the night falls, everything freezes.
But it's too soon to give up.
We might be able to discover new things.
That pilot also discovered the valley of diamonds
Di!
A!
Mond!
Diamond?!
What about diamonds?
Give it to dogs or something.
That's right. It's not worth anything here.
Odd... It should be perfect.
Shoot!
-Doctor! -Yeah!
-Wow! -Yay! We did it!
Doctor!
There is a response to our communication wave.
What?
It's from the Moon! There was a response from the Moon.
It's me, Kanda.
It's Ochanomizu! Ochanomizu, is everyone okay?
Everyone! Rescue rocket is on its way to the Moon!
-What? Really? -Is the rocket coming for sure?
We fixed the buoy, so we were able to communicate.
They will be here by this evening at the latest.
Ah... Atom.
We are safe!
-Safe. -We are safe!
Honey!
That's right. You said there were diamonds.
That's right! Where is the valley of diamonds?
Teach us, Atom!
I only know of two that became Ivan's earrings.
-Where is that robot, Atom? -No!
Those diamonds are Ivan's.
-Please, Atom. -No...
We can all be rich. Please, Atom.
Please take us there!
Please?
Tell us, Atom!
No! I don't want to take Ivan's!
Move away!
Here, Atom. Guide me.
If you don't this one's chest will melt in a second.
All right! I will.
Oh, this is an old robot.
Is that one called Ivan?
Atom! Go tell him to give us diamonds.
Move quickly!
Ivan, where are your diamonds?
Diamonds. Those shiny things.
Those you used to wear here.
Atom, what is he saying?
He buried those diamonds with Minya's body.
Kid, dig it.
No!
-Ivan buried them with sincerity. -Shut up!
Here. Dig, dig!
-This is a grave. I don't want to rob a grave! -Dig!
No! Don't dig.
How sad would it be for Ivan.
Snow.
-It's suddenly cold. -Here! Let's go back.
It will be dangerous if we don't go back quickly. We will freeze.
We still have enough time until sunset.
What are you talking about? It will be late if we don't go back now!
What? Go back when diamonds are in front of my eyes? You go back!
-Yoshio, hold onto my legs. -Okay.
Here, you, too.
Shut up! How many times do I have to tell you?
I can't help it. Let's go.
You don't have to be in such flurry. We have enough time to dig and go back.
It's all mine.
I found it!
Wow, two egg-sized diamonds.
I could buy anything with these.
You! What are you trying to do with me? Let me go!
Hey, let me go! Hey!
I have no time to sleep.
The sun will set if I act so slow.
Sunset. Help!
Help!
Ah, help me! Help!
A big earthquake is coming to Shimoda town.
But that was a lie of the robot called Thor.
That's weird. Robots can't lie.
Thor looks after Kozue, who has problems with eyes.
Why would you lie?
Ah! This time, a big earthquake for sure...
Next on Astro Boy, "The Robot Who Lied." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Robot Who Lied"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together