Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Orbit correction 0.029.
Power save, checked.
Orbit correction, 0.027.
0.028, 0.029. Check.
Orbit correction complete.
Power save 0.000001.
Destruction index N0.03...
plus minus 0.001.
Energy circuit check complete.
Resistance minus 0.09%.
Ready to launch!
Dear scientists who have come to represent UN,
welcome to the rear surface of the Moon.
What I'm about to show you now is the first experiment of
the Antiproton cannon I completed after investing more than ten years.
As you all know, the Antiproton cannon is an ultimate weapon with the biggest destructive power,
and that power is an essential factor for further planet developments.
Please see and check that power today;
I'd like to get an official permission from UN to use this as soon as possible.
Since we are only testing this today, I decreased its power level to 1/60 of its original one.
5 seconds until launch.
4, 3, 2, 1.
0, Launch!
All right! Success!
The crack is getting bigger.
Astro Boy vs. Atlas VIII "Proton Cannon"
Atom, the base at the Moon's surface is in danger.
The crack is reaching its front surface. We have to stop it before it does!
The surface base!
30 seconds until explosion.
It worked!
Thank you, Atom. I'm glad I brought you.
Anyhow, Colonel Dovrof,
Even though it's the Moon's rear surface, isn't your target decision bit absurd?
It's easy for tremor to spread through the Moon's strata,
but the power of Antiproton cannon was too big.
That's right. Antiproton cannon is too dangerous.
No, this isn't the originally intended way to use this.
If we take this to asteroids or outer planets, we can destroy them easily.
And if we take them back to the Earth,
mankind will never have to suffer any lack of resource.
That is the true way to use this Antiproton cannon.
However, if this is abused, horrible thing would happen.
That's right. Mankind would go extinct immediately.
We have to think carefully about this.
I think we have to take some risks in order to see advance in science.
Colonel Dovrof!
I think we have to have a full discussion at UN or a dangerous object like this.
All right! Now I know it was good-for-nothing to call you in!
UN Secretary General Gervezolde
declared the prohibition against using the Antiproton cannon
until the specific countermeasure gets set up.
Now it's finally over.
Ochanomizu! There's a big trouble!
Mr. Secretary General. What happened?
Dovrof took the Antiproton to Jupiter!
What?
Such cowards. Rejection?
If I show you a real test,
then even the stupid scientists would know how to appreciate the Antiproton cannon.
Velocity level: 100%. Target: Jupiter's satellite Amaltea.
Waruprogis! Were you alive?
Atlas, I've heard about your active work. Wow, you've grown up well.
The Atlas I made was a kid like this.
You rebuilt yourself, right? Way to go for the robot I built!
This is all because of the Omega factor I inserted.
So what? You tried to destroy me anyway.
You also tried to kill me, right?
Well, forget about the past. I called you for a reason.
You must have heard about the Antiproton cannon Colonel Dovrof developed, right?
I heard that Dovrof has gone to Jupiter.
So?
We are going to steal it.
If I only have the Antiproton cannon, world conquest isn't impossible.
How does it sound, Atlas?
I don't need such thing. Bye.
Wait!
So Atlas, I heard there is this beautiful female robot.
Livian?
As expected. Livian used to be my maidservant.
Maidservant?
Today's Livian isn't the same as before.
She was reborn, just like I was.
She's not your maidservant!
Okay. I get it. So please take this sword away.
Now that I think about it, Livian was nice to Atlas in many ways.
Gis! Surely you aren't planning to do something to Livian, right?
N, No way. I'm not interested.
Pass me the transmitter you called me with.
What are you going to do with it?
Give it to me!
All right, all right. So stop this.
This is it.
Thank you. Be thankful that you are still alive!
Huh? Me? Jupiter?
Atom, you are the only one who can stop Colonel Dovrof now.
Please help me!
Great velocity is needed to chase him.
It's impossible for human to do it.
All right. I'll take off right away.
Use this when you need me.
I'll go to wherever you are. Do you understand, Livian?
Atlas, you didn't even know that it's a hypnosis equipment and gave it to Livian.
Livian, it's me. I'm your master, Waruprogis.
Baron Gis.
That's right. You remembered it well.
You will now move upon my word. Do you understand, Livian?
Yes, sir.
All right. First, escape from that place.
30 seconds until launch. All equipments fine.
20 seconds.
-Atom, -Doctor Ochanomizu!
Be safe.
Okay!
Five seconds until launch.
4, 3, 2, 1
0!
Gis! Where's Livian?
Are you concerned about it?
Livian,
As you can see, I held Livian as hostage.
Gis, what are you doing?
I won't forgive you.
Try taking a step.
If I press this, Livian will explode.
Then Livian will become powdered to the point that it's impossible to restore her.
But Atlas, I really want to have this Antiproton cannon.
You should go to Jupiter and steal the Antiproton cannon.
If you want your Livian back, you should follow my order.
Gis, you bastard!
I don't care what you say. Are you in or not?
All right. I'll get you that thing you want.
However, I'm going to put a surveillance so you don't do anything stupid while I'm gone.
It takes 43 light-minutes to get to Jupiter from Earth. How are you going to watch me?
I'm going to have the tachyon receiver from my crystal.
Tachyon? You have the quantum that's faster than light?
Do you understand? Don't you dare lay your finger on Livian!
I won't let you go.
Good Atlas, you finished building tachyon equipment.
After getting the Antiproton cannon, I'm going to...
Oops, this one can send my sound as well.
Just passed the Mars orbit. I don't see Dovrof yet.
I'm separating the first energy tank!
It's Jupiter.
I see Colonel Dovrof's spaceship!
Waruprogis, can you hear me?
Look, Jupiter is before my eyes.
I'm sending you the video through TV camera planted in my eyes.
I'm going to take the Antiproton cannon now.
Watch and see!
That's good. Can I see everything you do?
That's the same here.
However, as long as I have this, you will have to obey me.
Livian! Hey, Livian!
Yes, Master.
You look better in that outfit. Bring some more drinks.
-How dare you! -Don't worry.
If you bring the Antiproton cannon, I won't lay a finger on her.
I just asked her to do the things she used to do.
Waruprogis. I'm not going to forgive you.
You surely can't do anything to me over there.
Colonel Dovrof. Target is Amaltea. Distance is 2.2 space miles.
I got it. Satellite Amaltea: 150 km diameter.
Ready to launch Antiproton cannon!
Ready to launch Antiproton cannon.
We are ready to launch.
Full power output.
Target: Amaltea.
Power output: 10, 20...
That one is...
Colonel Dovrof! I came here to ask you
to stop the Antiproton cannon test upon Dr. Ochanomizu's order!
Do you think I'm going to stop here?
Leave right now.
Or else I'm going to let you be another test object for Antiproton cannon.
Then I have no choice! I'm going to destroy Antiproton cannon!
What?
Stop it! What are you...
Who is it?
Atlas.
Atlas, what are you doing here?
Atom, don't touch this Antiproton cannon. It's mine.
What? I can't let you do that.
I will take it by force!
What happened?
Atom! Don't hide! Let's fight!
Atom, stop!
What is that?
Are you all right? Let's check the launch progress!
Atom, what a disruption.
Stop!
Where are you, Atom?
Stop there!
Take this!
Atom, where are you?
Since you are brothers, it's difficult to distinguish a winner.
Brothers?
There was a little gang called Skunk, right?
He stole the blueprint of Atom
and I built Atlas based on that blueprint.
So you guys are brothers based on the same blueprint.
But...
Atlas has the Omega factor I invented.
Omega factor?
He's not the same as a can like you.
Atlas has a heart and mind that are closer to those of humans.
Well, they are beyond humans'.
So why does Atlas do bad things to humans?
I told you; they are beyond humans'.
Atlas is looking down upon humans.
60 seconds before launch.
58, 57, 56...
I'm going to destroy whoever that interferes with my plan.
Atlas, stop it. Atom and you are brothers!
What?
Both of you were built from the same blueprint!
What's wrong? I'm leaving first!
4, 3,
2, 1, 0. Launch!
It's Antiproton cannon.
All right! It's better than what I expected.
Atlas. Atlas! What happened?
Atlas.
Did you get the Antiproton cannon? Hey, Atlas!
Surely you didn't fail, right? Hey, Atlas!
Livian!
Hold on. Give me back my explosion equipment.
Livian, I won't forgive you.
Atom, welcome. Good job.
It's nothing.
I'm thankful that you are safe.
Atom... was my brother?
The huge artificial sun invades the Siberian Railway and New York.
Who is controlling such dangerous object?
Great Britain's Sherlock Holmespan started his investigation.
But Mr. Holmespan hates robots.
My arms and legs don't move because of the attack from the artificial sun.
Mr. Holmespan! Please help.
Next on Astro Boy, "The Stolen Sun" Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Stolen Sun"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together