Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
-Atom, be careful. -Okay!
How is it? Isn't it amazing?
With this, I'm going to watch the Rainbow Comet clearly.
Astronomy club students of Ochanomizu Elementary School for observing Rainbow Comet,
-Please go to gate seven. -Let's go!
-Be careful. -Good bye!
Atom.
Yes?
At a time of need, you can communicate with me with this.
Okay!
At a time of need?
Then, you mean...
No, as you all know,
today's activity is only for the kids' club on a holiday.
As an adviser, I need to be ready even for the smallest chance of...
A machine will only circumnavigate the course
calculated with computer, so it should be fine.
But Mrs. Shibukaki, is it really okay that a teacher doesn't accompany them?
My kid said that students should go by themselves for the sake of education.
They have grown up this much...
I'm late. Is everyone aboard already?
Are you worried, Mr. Beard? you don't have to worry.
But...
-It's all right. -Not that.
Good bye!
Atom vs. Atlas IV: The Menacing Comet
How beautiful the Earth is.
You are admiring at last?
I was on a space cruise ship last week as well.
I'm already tired of looking at the Earth from space.
-What? Shibukaki's eating already. -What do you care about when I eat my own food?
I'm going to eat, too.
I'll have instant noodles.
Space meals taste really bad.
Gosh! Meal time hasn't come yet!
Sorry.
Even Doctor Ochanomizu said that you shouldn't
break the rules of Astronomy club!
Yes, because in space, a small fight can turn into a big accident!
Where is the proof that I ate already?
Look at Shibukaki.
Ha ha. Good for you.
Ah, it's a satellite.
That model was shot out in the 1900s. It's now expired.
But it's still orbiting.
Kenichi, isn't it time for you to study?
That's right. Everyone! Get back in your seat.
Okay.
Everyone, before we arrive at comet and study,
let's practice putting on spacesuit, except for Atom, just in case.
Okay.
-How do you close this? -Huh? There's no button.
That one is...
Ah! Mine wouldn't let my neck out!
Those are pants.
Are you done? Then, to become used to it,
let's study in spacesuits for a while.
A comet is a celestial body within the solar system.
It is made of frozen gas and small dust.
It wanders around space normally,
but it gets closer to the solar system, drawn by the Sun's gravitation.
And as its ice melts into gas by the Sun's light and heat, it falls.
That's called a tail of comet.
Rainbow Comet we will observe from now on
is famous for having a beautiful seven-colored tail.
Is Shibukaki listening well?
That gas shows colors because of that ice's ingredients.
Tamao, since it is controlled automatically, I told you not to go there...
It's all right, all right.
What is that sound?
Jump!
Was that you?
Ah, the noodles are running away. Stop! It's hot.
Gravitational stability device's switch is turned off!
What is this.
Hey! That.
It's my meat! Hey!
I won't let anyone take my food away.
Ah, soup...
No!
It hurts!
We are running on this smooth course.
That's nice.
I once wished to drink whiskey
as I take a spacewalk, even for only one time.
Didn't you say you wanted to go because you were worried about students?
Well, my worry as a teacher was of course the first reason.
About where are you now?
Their rocket will now approach the Moon soon.
Rainbow Comet is just approaching the Venus orbit.
Ah, it's Rainbow Comet.
-Huh? Where? -Which one is it?
It's beautiful as if space's jewels have been gathered together.
It's beautiful...
How beautiful...
What is it! What's up?!
What in the world happened?
The machine's working on its own!
Ah, it's a problem.
What's wrong, Atom?
I don't know.
It's certain that it is getting off the course.
What? Hurry and take it back!
Hand gear won't work, either.
For real?
Minister!
Ochanomizu Astronomy club's rocket is bit weird!
What?
What is that?
Ah, that is...
It's gone.
It's been a long time, Atom.
That voice is from Atlas! Then this place is...
That's right. It's my castle.
It's the castle of the one who will soon become the ruler of the Earth.
You are still saying that?
What did you do to my friends?
I won't kill them.
Atom, do you now wish to follow what I say?
I told you I don't want to be involved in bad things!
Bad things? It would be bad only to humans.
But I want to be on good terms with humans.
How foolish. Human colleagues won't do any good.
Atom, let me show you something interesting.
Wow, it's a huge hat.
For who is it? Huh? I think I've seen it somewhere.
That's right! It looks exactly like mine. Someone...
-Atom! -Shibukaki, where are you?
I'm here.
Over there.
I heard a voice.
Shibukaki!
Everyone got super bigger.
And Shibukaki became smaller.
Ah! What is it!
Would you like to try? Now Shibukaki isn't scary anymore!
It looks like you've noticed. Good, let me show you more clearly.
I don't like it.
Ah, Tamao.
If you don't join my side, then I will make your friends into a piece of rice.
If you join my side, I'll return them to the Earth.
Now, what's your answer, Atom?
Atom. Atom!
Atom! There's no response here, either.
Tamao, you know what will happen if you become smaller, right?
Even if you ask like that...
You! Stop there!
Pervert!
I'm going to crush you!
-Help! -Help me!
Make them small! How dare a girl hits me!
They won't only get smaller.
After an hour like this, they will disappear from this world.
Atlas, stop it! I'll listen to what you say, so stop it!
Are you guys all right?
-Is everyone okay? -Yes.
Put on your seat belt!
-Atom? Atom's not here. -Jump isn't, either.
Huh? What is it?
It's the Moon. But that's odd.
What's wrong? What is that?
Oh, the rocket is!
What? They are safe?
But something's weird.
I calculated the distance between the course, and the rocket is right beside the Venus.
What?
Wh, wh, what did you say?
Surface temperature of the Venus is 430℃. They are in trouble!
Atom! Atom! Atom!
Atom, you are finally my colleague.
Atom!
Atom! Atom!
Jump.
Atom!
Doctor!
Oh, is it you, Atom? The rocket's headed to the Venus.
What? Venus?
You don't have to be surprised. If you use my castle,
you can freely move around even this vast space.
You were going to let this rocket be involved with the Venus from the beginning!
I just wanted to let you guys watch Rainbow Comet leisurely.
I'm going to save them!
Stop him!
Take it!
How is this?
Stop, Atom!
You made a great mistake to think that you can escape from me!
To where are we headed?
Ah, it's Atom.
-Atom! -Atom, help us!
-Here, supply energy. -Thank you.
There's no place to hide since we are in space.
Atom! What are you doing?
Ah! Zero-saver!
Atom, I won't make pranks anymore. Please don't use the ice!
If you are going to keep insisting on escaping...
That's right!
How's this?
Atom.
Look at what zero-saver can do!
Ah, Atom's gone.
Why would you reject me so much?
Good, Atom! Then, keep in mind
that you are the enemy of me, Atlas, from now on!
Atom balloon in sky.
But it's a scary bomb that attacks children.
Huh? I'm not the culprit.
Gosh! How can they do that to Uran as well?
All right. I'm going to find the real culprit.
Balloon bomb, I'm coming for you!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Devil's Balloon." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Devil's Balloon"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together