Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Wouldn't it be great?
Uran playing the piano?
Uran's friend
started learning piano since only three months ago
and already has mastered Chopin's song.
But wouldn't it be too much for Uran?
No, it wouldn't be. It's better to start childhood education as soon as possible.
Have you forgotten what happened at the musical instrument store earlier?
That's why she needs to get some emotional education by learning piano.
Then I think drawing is more apt for Uran than playing the piano.
Even after you see that?
That's your face Uran drew.
That is...
Whether she excels or not,
drawing is the best for developing one's mind.
No, it's piano.
Drawing!
Piano!
Dad, Mom, why are you guys fighting?
Where's Uran?
Uran has already gone outside to play.
Give my bicycle back.
How noisy. I'm going to give it back to you soon.
How does it move?
Move it!
Wow, it's running. Yay!
Uran and Uran
What is that?
Robotting tournament begins today.
Robotting is that battle between robots, right?
I wanted to watch it in person.
Yeah? Let's watch it.
Mom will scold us again if we don't go back early.
It's only for a while.
Uran!
Uran! No!
Atom!
-Teacher. -No way!
I did hear robotting is popular among students lately,
but I never expected you to be into this as well!
It's not true, Teacher.
I don't need excuses!
I don't like the fact that they are making robots fight each other and getting pleasure out of it!
Give me your autograph!
Give me your autograph.
From the beginning, robots weren't built to do this kind of...
It's not good for your education!
Don't step on my beard!
Teacher.
-No admittance is allowed from here. -Don't come in!
Closing the door. Get away!
Leave it to me.
And you?
I don't need greetings.
Wow, it's really big inside.
Do you understand? It's excused only for today, to find Uran.
But since this place is so huge, it would be hard to find her.
You've waited long enough. The first match of today.
Red team, the Mongolian tiger Genghis Khan Nabe!
Blue team, the German emperor Joringin!
-What's wrong? -Get rid of him!
-Good job! -Get rid of him!
-Push forward! -Teacher.
Yeah? Well... That is...
Joringin Type AK108M
Electronic brain damage 32%
Energy converter damage 90%
The 2nd, 4th engine damage 75%
All right, destroy it.
-Doctor Ikisugi! -Oh, President.
Your fighter is too persistent!
It always fights until it gets broken down.
Aren't you going to program it to finish the match moderately?
But isn't getting smashed a cause for such popularity of robotting?
Even so!
If robots become scrap metal after every match, there's no profit!
Don't worry about that. Sandwich, come here.
It's a black leopard robot!
Show your ability to the president.
It's split into two.
This is the 1/2 system I developed.
If you apply this system, you can get two bodies out of one robot.
I see.
Even if one robot fighter gets broken down
One more fighter can participate in another match?
If one gets broken down, you make two out of that remaining one,
and if that one gets broken down, you split the other into two...
-What are you doing? -Stop it!
I'll wait outside.
Even though it's only a show, this is too much.
There's something odd.
What is it? What is that girl?
Uran!
You are mean!
How can you attack an opponent who cannot move?
Are you a true robot fighter?
Uran's in danger!
She blocked it! She's really strong.
Uran!
Whatever!
-Amazing! -That's amazing.
-Uran, stop it! -Atom, did you see it? I'm strong, right?
That girl would gain some popularity.
Hey, bring that girl in.
No way!
You are going to let this little girl be in robotting?
I'll give you a lot for the down payment.
It's not about money. I can never allow it as an educator, you fatty.
Whatever your thought is, we have to ask her own opinion.
How is it, Uran? You are surely going to be a big star.
I don't mind doing it.
No, Uran! You saw it, right? If you lose, you get scrapped.
But you don't have to lose.
Anyhow! No matter what you say, I'm not going to allow it!
-Do you understand? -Let's go, Uran.
I'm not going to give this huge profit up with that.
If there's one more Uran, it would work.
Call Doctor Ikisugi!
Robotting? No way!
Uran, go to piano classes on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
And drawing classes on Tuesdays, Thursdays and Saturdays.
Then when am I supposed to play?
-Until you get calm personality. -Of course.
It's no fun.
Miss?
Have you snuck out?
But it's boring.
Miss, haven't you ever wished to have two bodies of yourself?
Of course.
If I have two bodies, I can make one study
and make the other one do what I want.
Let me accomplish that wish for you.
Is that possible?
This is the robotting stadium.
Of course. I'm the training doctor for robotting.
I fell in love with your fight.
Well, it's not that great.
You have a potential to become a star.
That's why I decided to give you the 1/2 operation.
1/2 operation?
Lay down here?
It's scary somehow.
It's all right, all right. You don't need to worry.
Or do you not want another self of yours?
What are you doing?
I'm only inserting a special device after disassembling.
I'm really sorry.
Yes, I'll send her back when she returns.
I'm home. What's wrong, Mom?
Uran ran away from piano class.
Where did she go?
Maybe... I'll go find her!
Atom needs to learn about manners as well.
Is it a day off?
I thought she would be here...
A heckler's here!
Is it ready yet? Atom's here for her.
Yes, it's almost done.
Hey, Sandwich, chase Atom out.
So this is not the place.
What are you doing!
What is it? How unpleasant.
I did it.
But there must be something since this kind of one is after me.
Do you have any business?
-Didn't my sister Uran come here? -No, not that I know of.
Since today's the day off, no one comes here.
Is that so...
Come back again tomorrow. You will be able to see an interesting match.
I'm home.
Atom, you are late.
I've looked many places, but Uran wasn't anywhere...
-Uran's already home. -What?
Mom scolded her a lot. She's quietly sleeping in her room.
Is she? Thank goodness.
Your electronic brain is linked with the 1/2 system device.
Whenever you want to become two, it splits anytime.
Split!
Come back, come back.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
Bye!
Jump.
Good morning, Jump.
Uran, you don't have time to play with Jump from today.
You have a drawing class today. Get your energy and go ahead.
Yes, of course I know.
Jump, I'm sorry I can't play with you.
Split!
Wow, you look the same. You are my double goer.
You are my double goer.
Wow, she speaks in the same way as well.
Dad, mom and Atom wouldn't be able to notice who's who.
Anyhow, you are my double goer, so please go to the drawing class with this.
How dare you! You are my double goer!
You are the fake one I made so I can go to robotting.
You should go to drawing class!
Even though she's bit mischievous,
Innocent smile on her face
Gosh!
Uran
I'm the real one!
Gosh!
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
Uran
You are my
copy! A replica!
Atom wouldn't notice.
But I can notice.
Uran is like an angel
I'm the real one for sure.
This is not going to finish like this.
-All right, let's play rock-paper-scissors. -That's good!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Draw, again!
One more time!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Gameran, who won the third place in World Robotting.
Let's choose this one. He is known for smashing the opponent.
Would it be all right for Uran?
Let's go with the story that the other Uran takes revenge if Uran gets defeated today.
I see! That's good.
It's going to be popular for sure. Jackpot!
Today's main event!
Blue team, Gameran, the third place one from World Robotting!
Red team, great strength from the small body.
Our rising star, Uran!
I'm not going to stand it if she loses, after making me do this boring stuff!
Uran, what's wrong? Go ahead and draw.
She's behaving.
Since I'm here today, she won't be able to escape.
I'm going to prove my strength!
What, this is...
It's odd. I can't put forth my strength.
No... What's wrong?
Doctor Ikisugi!
What happened?
I think her strength has halved as well.
You stupid! You always do stupid things.
What's wrong, Uran!
Shibukaki, what's up with Uran?
No. It's nothing. Nothing...
What a skill. You were watching pocket TV again.
What! Uran's in robotting!
Huh?
Hey, Atom! Uran's in trouble.
Uran!
Atom, you should get to the stadium right away.
Okay!
Atom!
Uran! Are you trying to run away again? Stop!
Uran!
-Atom, help me. -What happened, Uran?
So, I was into two,
There was a bubble,
Rock paper scissors, will get smashed!
-Stop it now! -Poor her!
Stop it!
So full of wounds... Poor me...
-Ah, it's Atom! -Atom's here to save her!
What an interesting development.
Gameran! If you defeat Atom, you will get famous!
Defeat Atom!
You did that!
Let me take your mask off!
Atom!
Help!
Atom.
-I'm sorry, Atom. -It's over now. Let's go back.
It's all done. Now it's fixed.
I hope Uran stops causing troubles after this incident.
But it's the best for her to stay healthy.
Hmm, maybe a sports class would be adequate for her.
What's wrong, Uran?
Sometimes my legs move in different directions.
It's the habit from when you were split into two.
Well, it will get better soon.
If you behave.
SL of the mountain valley is Sakura's treasure.
But does this move?
What a storm! SL, please rescue everyone!
Next on Astro Boy, "Dash in a Storm!" Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "Dash in a Storm!"
Even though she is bit mischievous
Innocent smile on her face
Uran
Everyone's calling
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
Uran
When you are around
We always have fun
She likes her brother Atom
And she likes songs and dreams
Uran is like an angel
Everyone's calling