Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Everyone, Atom is always wearing boots, right?
Let's take them off for a while.
Look.
Atom's legs are sleek like a girl's legs.
That's right. Atom's legs are that of a girl in fact.
Only Dr.Ochanomizu knows about this secret.
There is a story related to this.
A sad story.
Astro Boy's First Love
So before I was born?
That's right. There is another robot blueprint that looks exactly like you.
So to speak, it's your original form.
It's the beginning product.
Dr.Tenma put off that blueprint
and kept it in the safe at the Ministry of Science.
After that, another real blueprint was made
of which you were born from, and the other one got forgotten.
So it has been kept in that safe ever since.
And we found out about this recently
that that blueprint got transferred to another country by a spy.
Yesterday, we found out that
it is hidden in an underground fortress of the Grota Republic.
Anyhow, it's the Ministry of Science's fault.
I have to take the responsibility and step down from the position of Minister.
That is...!
-Resigning... -Won't solve the problem.
Exactly, Atom. If the beginning product
gets built with that blueprint,
then it becomes a serious case.
It's equipped with a neutron bomb.
If you press a certain area of that robot,
that bomb can go off.
So that robot is a bomb?
That's right. I made useless stuff according to the government's order.
However, that blueprint got rejected in the end,
and I was able to make you based on that robot's robot parts.
So why did you call me?
Atom, we don't have much time left.
I know it will be hard, but go to that fortress in the Grota Republic and get that blueprint back.
-Of course, this is a secret mission. -Steal it.
I have to rob it?
Since we are getting ours back, it's technically not a robbery.
Since it's bothersome to have troubles with the Grota Republic,
you shouldn't have the appearance of a robot. Disguise as a human being.
Now you look like a Grota person.
You shouldn't use your power. Pretend as if it's heavy.
Passengers who are about to board the Grota flight 482...
Atom, I trust you.
If that blueprint turns into a robot,
it will be irreversible. Please...
Next stop is Suriri.
Passengers who are getting off at Suriri,
please get a physical at the station.
After getting off, please line up and move to the checkpoint.
Hey! I forgot my suitcase.
You... You saw me!
Please. Let me go.
Nope. If you saw me, I can't do that.
-How come? -Whatever the reason!
-You are a robot, right? -That's right. You too?
No, I'm...
You beat me with this kind of strength. You are surely a robot.
What a strange kid. Why would you disguise yourself as human?
Be quiet. Answer my question first.
-Do you live nearby? -Yes.
Then you must know where the fortress is?
Y, yes...
Take me there. Not to the front gate, but to the back gate.
Should I crawl out of here?
No, you will get caught by laser beams.
You don't know until you try.
-You were safe? -People will soon come here. Let's run!
It's impossible to go through this.
That's what I told you. Do you really want to get inside?
Yes.
-We can enter through the entrance. -But there is a checkpoint, right?
It's probably possible.
Stop!
What, it's Ryoka.
Yes, I'm back.
Hold on! What's that robot?
Let's take it to Dr.Ryndolph.
What, another research material? Go ahead!
You should have told me that you live in this fortress.
Well, since you got in without a problem, you don't need to be so angry.
That's true, but...
Then, let's separate here. Thank you for many things.
Hold on! Now you have to do something for me.
What?
-I... Don't have any friend. I'm alone. -There are so many people around here!
I wanted to have a robot friend. Please.
All robots in this fortress don't speak, and don't have emotions.
So I've been very lonely...
You feel loneliness? You are a high-quality robot, huh?
Tell me your name.
I'm Atom.
I'm Ryoka! Dr.Ryndolph built me.
Dr.Ryndolph?
He's the one who takes care of robots in this fortress.
Hide!
It's me, Ryoka.
You saw it, right? How could I become friends with such kids?
I have to finish my work before I get caught, and then get out.
I'll help you.
Ryoka, then you will get in trouble with that Dr.Ryndolph.
Atom, I don't want to part from you.
Then let's go together.
Hurry, cut those cords inside the wall!
Done!
Thank goodness. Thanks to you.
Where are you going?
There is a safe in there, right? I'm going there.
Ryoka!
Atom!
Dr.Ryndolph!
Ryoka! You did something stupid. You traitor!
Doctor, I'm sorry, but...
You will get punished later. Now, Ryoka, come back through that hole.
I have to take care of that intruder.
Don't do anything to him! Don't!
Don't do anything to him?
He's a spy, breaking into this fortress.
He must be after the safe. You must want that blueprint in there, huh?
But you are too late.
I've already built a robot based on that blueprint.
A robot with a neutron bomb is here.
There. It's right before your eyes.
It's Ryoka!
Y, you are...
Now! Come back, Ryoka! Immediately!
Atom... I'm sorry!
Your life ends here.
This will be generous for a spy.
How does it feel like to head down to hell?
There is a magnetic barrier around that dome. You won't be able to get out.
Now a long, long journey will start.
You will fly toward the sun
and hit the sun with a rocket.
How does it sound like? Isn't it a great funeral?
I'm not going to go through this!
Morse code!
Ryo...ka.
Ryoka!
You were still outside!
Ryoka.
I told you to come back.
Then go ahead and die with that spy.
I will activate your neutron bomb!
Ryoka. You will explode with that rocket after an hour.
Even if you are gone, 100 exactly same robots are about to be built.
Stupid!
Ryoka! What are you doing?
All right. Magnetic barrier is gone.
Atom!
Ryoka.
Did you break it? Thank you!
Run. Rocket's going to explode soon!
I'm leaving with you.
Dang!
Shoot them down! Emergency attack!
You should stay low.
Atom!
Dr.Ryndolph, give me the blueprint back.
This one?
Here!
I don't need this! Look!
I already have this many robots being completed.
I'll let you have Ryoka! I don't need it!
You won't be able to complete it!
Help!
Here, Ryoka. Let's get out.
Atom, you should go by yourself.
I won't last any longer.
Doctor has turned on my switch already.
Here's the detonator. Inside my brain...
Within 30 minutes, the neutron bomb will explode.
Now I can't stop it.
Ryoka!
Hurry and run. I was meant to be like this.
Atom, you were a great kid.
I'm not going to forget you. Goodbye! Hurry!
Help. I'm going to die...
Dr.Ryndolph.
I'll help you. Instead, remove the neutron bomb from Ryoka!
That's not possible. Ryoka's entire body is made of bombs.
Why did you turn the detonator on?
If you didn't, Ryoka would have lived in peace.
Atom, there are only 20 minutes remaining. Why wouldn't you run?
I have to stop your explosion.
Doctor, you can disassemble bombs, right?
Disassemble... It's impossible.
Try! Now! Here!
If you don't, then you will die as well.
Ryoka, go lie on the workbench.
10 minutes, Atom.
You won't be able to run away. You will be killed.
Ryoka, I'm going to stay here until the last moment. I'm going to watch you.
Why?
Why? Why would it be?
I don't want to part from you. You are beautiful.
Humans might call this is the "liking" of someone.
I'm not sure whether I will make it on time, but one remaining possibility
is to disassemble her from head to waist.
However, if I do that, I won't be able to put Ryoka back.
I burnt the blueprint already.
Doctor, it's all right. Please go ahead.
Ryoka!
Atom, I like you.
I love you too.
One minute remaining.
20 seconds.
It's over.
I'm glad the blueprint is gone.
Atom, good job.
Dr.Ochanomizu.
This is the last part of Ryoka.
It's the former you. Its structure resemble yours.
Doctor, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it? I'll give you any kind of prize.
Can I exchange my legs with Ryoka's?
What?
I don't want to forget Ryoka.
I think it'd be good if I could become one with Ryoka...
Please, Doctor. Please get me those legs.
But this is female legs.
I'm a kid, so it doesn't matter.
You said you would give me any kind of prize.
That's true, but...
Ryoka, we will always be together.
This is my secret.
Please keep it a secret.
Good-bye!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together