Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Who attacked the car?!
Rage of the Sphinx
You guys are...
What are you doing? I'm just a traveler!
I never did anything to you!
So you guys are not going to go away easily...
What? It just exploded like a gas bomb.
Huh?
What was that right now?
As soon as I arrive in Mexico...
Why woud such weird guys attack me?
Dr.Ochanomizu told me it's not that dangerous
since I'll just be helping the excavation research.
There is a tent!
Excuse me!
What, a kid?
I'm Atom, a robot from Japan.
Because of a car accident, all my clothes got burnt. Do you have any extra clothes...?
This kid surely is a robot.
Sir! Stop being violent!
Shut up!
This is enough for a robot to wear.
Are you going to beat me? Interesting.
What would happen if a robot beats a human being?
Don't you ever come again!
Sub, you have a bad drinking habit.
Shut up! You have a problem?
All right, just go to sleep.
You said you are Atom? What are you doing down here?
I'm looking for a guy called Mushu Ampair.
-Mushu Ampair? -Ampair?
If you need Mushu, then I can't just leave you like this.
Nopo, guide him.
You know Mushu Ampair?
Well, to put it simple, he's our employer.
So what are you guys doing here?
-Excavation. Of archaeology. -Archaeology?
That's the famous pyramid of Mayan culture, right?
That's right. We are investigating the inside.
Again? Who in the world are you?
It's me who stopped you. I'm Sphinx.
Atom, I have a business with you.
Sphinx? Right, you are the guardian of pyramid.
Do you really have to go to Mushu Ampair?
Of course!
As I expected. I can't help it.
You are our enemy!
What?
Why would I be your enemy?
Because you are trying to help someone like Mushu Ampair.
Why would Mexican robots only do things that are hard to understand?
Go!
Let's fight again in a few days, Atom!
Mister, wake up.
It was close.
Sphinx was here. I just chased him out.
He was here already? They must have been anxious.
Welcome, Atom. You must be tired, coming all the way from Japan.
You are Mushu Ampair, right?
Have a seat first. I heard what happened.
People despise robots in this country.
I heard you were in trouble.
I think you heard it from Dr.Ochanomizu, but in this country,
something called Mayan Civilization used to exist and prosper.
It's a native culture, but it left wonderful ruins.
There are ruins of a chapel,
observatory, and treasure temple.
What I'm trying to excavate this time is one of the tombs of the kings.
There are king's crown and various academic data inside there.
What I'd like to ask you is
to fight the ones who try to interrupt that excavation.
Then, that Sphinx?
That's right. That's the obstacle.
So... How did it find out about me?
The rumor that I'm going to hire you is all spread around.
He must have been waiting.
Sphinx is the guardian of the pyramid.
He doesn't like it to be excavated.
But... What I met was a robot.
First of all, let me introduce you my men.
We will divide in two teams and wait near the pyramid.
Nopo, be careful. He might attack you again.
Okay!
There it is!
Wait! That's...
That's just a cat. Poor cat...
Sir, we will soon be arriving at the first camp.
Hey! Is anyone around?
Shoot...
Wiped out. Did Sphinx do this?
This footprint is not of Sphinx. It's that robot that looks like a crab.
It's the crab man.
We got attacked by the crab man.
-I'm worried about the second camp. -Let's hurry!
Who is the crab man?
It's a monster which people in this town are afraid of.
It comes out during the night.
Ah, Mushu Ampair, over there!
Man...
I'll go and check!
This is that tent from yesterday. Then the crew members are...
-Hey, Robot. -Ah! You okay?
-We got attacked by the crab man. -Our entire tent got destroyed.
I don't want this kind of dangerous work anymore! I'm going back to the town.
Wait, you can't do that.
Ah! Mushu Ampair.
In fact, the first team got wiped out.
So while this team remains safe, let's begin the excavation.
I called in Atom from Japan to let him guard and cover for us.
What? This is our bodyguard?
He looks like a kid. Can he protect us?
I heard about his powers from Dr.Ochanomizu. You don't need to worry.
Let me explain about the excavation. Please come down.
There are gangways at the east and west side of this pyramid. Those are entrances.
From those, there is a downhill path that's about 50 m long that is connected to a chamber.
That chamber is the chamber of messenger.
Our objectives are waiting there.
If the path is blocked due to cave-ins or something,
we will get Atom's help to break through.
You understand? Then let's go ahead with shovels.
-This is the entrance. -Wow, it's super dark. Scary.
Everyone, let's go inside!
Amazing. There are pictures all over this wall?
Because of this pyramid,
an ancient culture could remain like this, without getting destroyed.
Roof falls!
Watch out!
-Is everyone all right? -That was close.
Hey, thank you.
The hole is blocked now.
Now the shovels and pickaxes will prove useful.
I'll go outside. Go ahead and dig.
Ha! Ordering us around?
Hey! Robot kid! Hurry and work!
Okay!
I think I sprained my ankle.
Are you all right?
You should go outside and take some rest.
We will do this.
I'm sorry, but I'll do that.
Fresh air!
All right. Put your hands up. Don't move! Don't!
Dang. Who are you?
I'm Jose Perez. Mushu Ampair, I know about your plan.
You are trying to ruin my brother's experiment, right?
What in the world are you talking about?
Don't pretend you don't know! I'm going to stop you.
-This is great. -That kid is doing all the work.
It's good to have a robot around.
Mushu Ampair, remove this tent and pull your team out immediately.
If you don't, the I'll shoot...
Thank you. Thanks.
Who is this one?
I don't know. Probably some thief from around.
Sir!
That robot kid dug the hole in the blink of an eye.
All right! Sub, tie this man up and watch him.
Yes, sir!
Let's go.
Be careful.
Atom, good work.
Sir, from smoke to smother. I don't think we can get inside.
Another dead end?
What do you think?
Underground water must have filled up the lower path.
By looking at the distance, if we just pass this, we would reach the room.
Atom, please go in the water and figure out the way.
All right!
As expected, this is the chamber.
Ah! Crab man!
If you must fight, then I won't hold back!
Another roof fall?
It seems like Atom is fighting with something on the other side of the water.
Then, Sphinx?
Dang, it's hot.
I'm getting tanned thanks to you.
Don't come!
-Gunfire! -Something happened to Sub.
-Ah, it's Sub. -Sub.
Hey, Sub, wake up.
He's dead.
Sphinx did this.
This one doesn't have a single scar.
Did Sphinx just leave him like this?
Odd. Sphinx didn't do anything to me.
He's got some luck.
Bring him in as well. Someone bring him!
Let me go! I can't be inside. Stop!
Shut up!
Atom, what did you do? Ther is the chamber across the water.
There were about 10 crab men, but I finished them!
All right. Let's all go underwater. The chamber is right in front of us!
I don't want to! Don't go into the chamber!
How annoying. Go in!
This is the chamber.
This is the chamber for sure.
There's nothing. It's the same as earlier, after getting robbed.
There is no mummy in this coffin.
Mushu Ampair, is it true that
there is a chamber that's not known to people yet?
Of course. But it's not that simple to find it.
Chambers like this got robbed 100 years ago. There's no way something would be here!
Nothing expensive is here!
Hackvan! Stop it.
This pot is very valuable archaeologically.
Hey! I came here because you said there would be treasures down here.
I did not come here to find some clay jars!
Both of you stop!
There are treasures here. Surely I didn't see something that's not there.
Atom, did you find something?
Some kind of mechanical sound... In this pyramid?
That's it, Atom. Lift that floor!
Okay!
No! Don't do that!
This is...
Gentlemen, let me show you something that's more fascinating than ancient culture.
-Huh? -What is this?
Is this also a part of Mayan ruins?
Brother.
Mushu Ampair! What's going on?
Ask that man for the reason. He knows everything.
This is my brother Dr.Don Perez, frozen here.
He always used to predict.
That a nuclear war will destroy this world.
He wanted to keep the records of this civilization for our descendants.
So he chose this pyramid to keep such records.
Besides, he tried to go into hibernation himself
to explain it to people in the future.
You know about it, right? If you freeze a person,
that person can survive for years, in a state of suspended animation.
My brother tested that on himself.
He's asleep now, without knowing anything.
To meet those people in the future. And you guys are...!
That's right. We are here to find that power source, uranium.
Villains! I'm never going to let you have it!
Hold on.
Sphinx.
Atom, you again.
Watch out!
Go upstairs!
Stop!
Let's get out with uranium while all this is happening.
You cold-blooded...!
Shut up. I'll take care of you with this frozen one.
Wait! You shouldn't do that.
-How come? No pity is needed. -No! You can't touch this!
He's a great man. As a same scholar, I tried to help you rob the tomb.
I'd like to apologize to this great man.
Shut up!
Stop...!
He's useless now, anyway.
Freeze.
Ampair, you are under arrest for murder!
I've been trying to find your misdeed,
and now I finally got one!
Nopo, who are you?
-We are from Mexico City Police Department. -Back! Watch out!
How dare you try to fight this Hackvan?
Here!
No! Don't aim that!
All right, Atom.
So why did you disrupt Ampair so much?
We are guardians to protect Dr.Don Perez.
Those crab men were tanks to provide oxygen and water.
And... I have the role to protect this pyramid from people who try to harm this.
I see. That's why you attacked those tomb robbers?
I... I should have told you the story earlier.
Forgive me. I will fix you no matter what.
Hey! Wait! I'm still here!
Surely he can't get out now.
This uranium is all mine.
Even a car is waiting for me.
Nopo, Atom, Sir Ampair.
Stay with that frozen man forever.
For thousands of years!
Dang...
Teach me one thing. How did you get out?
Have you forgotten, Hackvan? He told us.
There are two entrances in this pyramid, in the east and west side.
Nopo! I'm going to go back to the pyramid and try to fix Sphinx!
Atom! Before you go back home, stop by Mexico City!
All right!
To Grota Republic to find the blueprint of the neutron bomb robot.
I fell in love with Ryoka, whom I met there.
I'm a robot, and it's weird to have such feeling.
We snuck into the underground fortress together,
but the villain, Dr.Ryndolph turned on the switch of the neutron bomb.
Ryoka, surely you are not...
Next on Astro Boy, "Astro Boy's First Love"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together