Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
How lucky. Seagulls can go anywhere they want to go.
We robots can't go abroad without permission.
Hey! Watch out!
What is this? There's a letter inside.
Wow... Who threw this away?
It's a letter inside.
"Please come save me. My dad's working crazily."
"From Rumy of Pochom-pochom Island"
There's no such thing as Pochom-pochom Island.
But a letter came in.
-Isn't this somebody's prank? -Maybe it is.
Humans love to be mischievous
unlike us.
Prank... Do you really think so?
It seems possible that there's that island somewhere...
Help!
Rumy in Pochom-pochom Island
I have full energy.
If I come back until the next dawn...
All right, let's go!
It's a patrol car.
Let's follow the ocean current.
Let's go!
Ah, it's the bottle!
So I was right about the direction. Thank goodness.
The Big Dipper looks so close.
I start to see the Southern Cross as well.
I'm almost near the equator.
I only have half my energy now. Well, I traveled 3,000 km.
Ah! I see a light! I'm sure it's that one!
Huh? There's no one.
Ah, light!
My head is dent now.
Excuse me, where am I?
Wh, who are you?
I'm not anyone suspicious. I'm looking for Pochom-pochom Island.
Pochom-pochom... Oh!
Do you know?
Pochom-pochom is a huge sea snake with fire-marble eyes.
A huge sea snake?
No one can come back alive. No one can get rid of it.
Anyone who gets rid of it will become the warrior of this island. My warrior!
So it's that one who chased me just now.
What?
Pochom-pochom is near here?
So that light is a sea snake?
Then Pochom-pochom Island might be an island where that sea snake lives.
I don't have much energy left. I'll come back tomorrow night.
I'm losing my energy.
I'm finally here.
Atom, if you don't wake up, you will get tardy.
My... Look at your head.
What in the world happened?
Tell me! What did you do and where?
Mom...
I won't tell your dad about it. If you do it again, then I don't know what will happen.
Thank you, Mom!
If you sleep in class, you will get laughed at by robot student.
Atom!
Atom.
An important robot shouldn't sleep in class.
Atom!
-Is Atom asleep? -Yes.
How can he spend all his energy in class?
Does the school make students engaged in labor or something?
Well...
Because of the fog tonight, I can't see very well.
Let me make my hearing power 1,000 times better. Will I be able to hear something?
I hear something.
Wait!
-It's a kid. -Look after me.
Is this... inside the stomach of sea snake?
We also got eaten.
-This is his stomach? No way! -It's a room.
Be quiet!
I'm sorry, but you have now disappeared from the earth.
Please work here from now on.
If you try to escape, I will kill you right away!
-No! Help! -I have children in my country!
Work!
Stop complaining and work.
If you show good attitude, I might send you back to your country.
Your dead body, of course.
Watch out!
Thank you. You just saved my life.
He even makes old people like you work?
Sh, come hide here.
I got caught while traveling with my baby daughter and wife 10 years ago.
10 years?
They are digging a secret vein of ore.
First they used robots, but they were of no use since they got rusty because of salinity.
So they started to capture humans and make them work.
Even humans die after working here for about five years.
My wife also died, leaving us behind.
Grandpa.
My daughter works in nurse's office,
so I make this bump from time to time to meet my daughter.
Let me introduce my daughter to you.
God, please let people find this letter.
Rumy, your dad is injured again.
What? Again?
Dad!
Rumy. Don't worry.
I wanted to introduce you to someone.
-He saved my life. -Rumy?
It's you who sent the bottle with a letter.
What? You got it?
That's why I came here to find you.
-God! -Kids, they will get suspicious.
But... You have come all the way here, but there's no way to escape.
I'm serious. Unless there's some miracle, we can't escape this place.
There is one way.
-What? -Really?
It's all right. It will work out.
Can you breathe?
-Yes, I'm fine. -Hold on!
You can't wear boots in hospital!
Somebody come here!
Catch that nurse!
They jumped into a vent. How stupid.
Ah! That one's a robot.
-Let the sea snake out! -Yes, sir!
I know what you are!
Shoot...
One more!
Where are you?
-Where are we? -This is the ground you've always wished to be on.
Oh, I see the stars.
It's all right. It's only my head. Look. Searchlight eyes.
Since we got rid of all sea snakes, they won't be able to kidnap us.
I don't know how to thank you.
We are free now.
Cold and fresh air.
Dad! Look at this.
Seashells. Real seashells.
Yes, they are real, Rumy.
This is palm tree.
This is... a flower!
Grandpa, now you know that I'm a robot, right?
Once you go back to your country, let the police know about that submarine base.
Of course. Why don't you come with us?
I can't. I'm not here with a permission.
You even violated the robot laws to be here...
It's that one from yesterday.
He's with an old man now.
It's good to not have strangers in this island.
Well?
There is a girl as well.
Thank you.
Well... I...
Oh, I see.
Rumy wanted to thank you.
Thank you.
Ah, Ru... Rumy...
I'm actually a rob...
Oh! Pochom-pochom.
-Pochom-pochom. -Pochom-pochom!
It's you who got rid of Pochom-pochom?
Ye, yes.
Warrior!
Savior.
That's...
Warrior. Warrior!
Now people of this island can live peacefully.
Warrior, please stay in this island forever.
I...
I can serve you as my master all my life.
-Ah! -What's wrong, Warrior?
My. I have to hurry and go back.
I have a favor to ask you.
I will listen to everything the warrior says!
Please take care of these two.
All right. Follow me.
-Hey! Atom. -Yes!
Yesterday wasn't enough for you?
Atom, what are you doing? You fool!
Wake up. What are you doing? Open your eyes!
Atom, where do you go every night?
No, nowhere...
Don't lie to me!
I'm sorry. I was outside for a while...
I knew it. I know everything.
Dad's going to watch you tonight.
Atom, we are both saying this because we are worried about you.
Huh? This is!
He went out again? You stupid!
Dad, Mom, I'm sorry.
But I will make this my last one.
I can't take it anymore!
What's wrong?
Uran, go to sleep.
How dare he fools his parents? He's having fun at nights.
Something must be in his mind.
What are you talking about? You have to strict about educating...
That's right!
What is it, Uran? You shouldn't yell like that at night!
He went out to find that Pochom-pochom Island.
No way. He went abroad without getting permission?
Well, robots also do want to spend time in a beautiful island.
Uran, what are you talking about.
Do you understand? The 9th robot law.
A robot that travels abroad without the permission of the Ministry of Robots
will be sentenced to be disassembled.
That's right. It's a serious offense.
Dad, I'm sure he's Peter Pan.
I want to be his friends forever.
Me too.
-Hey! -Warrior.
Where have you been? I was worried.
Are both of you well?
-Yes. -My,
Try to think of a way to get out of this island.
We should borrow a boat and go to the place where liners pass.
No! I don't want to go back.
You are the warrior of this island.
But I have to take Rumy back.
Besides, I also have a country to go back.
I'm coming with you.
I can never part from you. Never...
Let's get ready to depart.
I'd like to ask your name.
It's Atom.
It's because of those two.
Hey! Capture those two! Hurry!
-Stop it! -Warrior, don't disrupt.
Capture them!
Stupid!
Run!
Shoot!
Atom...
Atom left me...
Atom... Leave.
It won't work without a boat.
It's the queen.
I gave up.
Go back to your country. I'll give your boat back.
Really?
Thank you.
Thank goodness. Now we can finally go back.
Let me get the boat ready.
Back!
Atom's mine. He's mine forever.
Rumy, wake up.
Where are you going?
Don't tell Rumy that I'm a robot.
-...Dad. -Oh, you woke up.
That person. Atom? What happened to Atom?
Yes... He... Well...
He was stabbed to death by that woman.
Poor Atom. He was kind and strong.
That's right. He's in my class.
I'm surprised to hear this.
After the investigation on that terrible submarine base was over,
I've been searching all over the world to answer my daughter's wish
which is that she wants to see Atom's school.
But it's quite hard to publicize Atom's deeds.
That's right. Since there is that robot law.
My daughter thinks that Atom is dead,
and Atom doesn't seem to want to let her know that he's a robot.
Hey! A cute girl is here at school.
Yeah? Where? Where?
-Really! -It's for real.
Where is she from?
She's pretty. Atom, do you know her?
N, No. I don't.
Then please say hello to Atom. I won't meet him.
That's probably better for him as well.
-Rumy, sorry to keep you waiting. -Dad.
So this is the school Atom used to attend.
That's right. Take a good look.
Rumy.
Goodbye.
Antiprotone cannon that shatters entire star.
Atlas attacked, searching for this cannon.
Stop it, Atlas. Antiprotone is needed for space development!
But it turns out that Atlas did such thing because he was threatened by someone.
That's because Livian had been held as hostage!
Next on Astro Boy.
Astro Boy vs. Atlas VIII. Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Astro Boy vs. Atlas VIII"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together