Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Wolf! Wolf's here!
Where, where?
Dang it. That liar boy fooled us again.
Wolf! Wolf's here! Help!
Do you think I'm going to be fooled again?
It's true this time! Help!
The liar boy who used to lie all the time
finally got eaten by the wolf.
Good! Good job, Atom.
But there is a moral in this story.
Does anyone know what it is?
-Yes. -Yes!
-Yes! -Me!
-Yes... -Shibukaki!
What moral does it have?
Umm...
When you lie, you have to do it well.
Isn't he stupid?
What? Those who laughed, you wait and see!
Hey, Shibukaki!
You cannot be like that.
Umm... What do you call it,
if you keep lying all the time, you will pay dearly one day.
Lying is the start of a theft. You shouldn't lie.
Well, Atom is fine.
Robots are designed to not lie.
Okay!
Good! You are dismissed!
What would happen
if a robot could tell lies?
The Robot Who Lied
Miss!
-Here. -Thank you, Thor.
What would it be?
It's a shell.
Wow, it's a pretty shell.
-Really? Is it really pretty? -Really. It's so pretty.
What color is it? White? Blue? Or pink?
Blue.
It's clear like the color of the ocean.
Blue...
My eyes, will it not get cured forever?
Doctor told me it will get cured. It will.
Really?
-Of course! -Thor!
Thor, bring Kozue in. There are visiting students.
Welcome to the crust lab. How lively they are!
Um... About that big earthquake that is about to happen near the East Sea...
Ah, the one in the newspaper? It's all right lately.
Is that so? I'm afraid of earthquakes and lightnings.
Thor, I have to host the visiting students.
-Could you go to the measuring room instead of me? -Yes!
Oh, is that a robot assistant?
Yes. He's a smart assistant. He helps a lot.
I'm surprised. You look exactly like Atom.
Atom?
Atom! Atom!
Yes!
Hmm, it really does look like him.
This is amazing.
So the cause of an earthquake is
the slanted or cut crusts
of the Earth.
This is because the crusts all over the world
-is moving all the time. -Gosh, it's boring.
Hey, let's go see the computer in the measuring room.
-What? If we get caught, the beard one will scold us. -Yeah.
Huh? Are you afraid of the teacher? I can't hang out with cowards.
Ah... I'm coming. Coming.
-Atom, are you going to keep pretending you are good? -I'm coming too.
Who is it over there?
Am I imagining things?
-How nice. -Let's ask them to let us in.
Yes, this is Minamizu Crust Lab.
Yes, abnormal uplift is continuing for a month.
This is the ocean floor of the Izu peninsula.
According to computer prediction, a big earthquake could happen today.
All right. If that information leaks, there will be great panic.
Keep it a secret until we have a solution.
Okay. I will never tell.
Oh my gosh! Gosh!
Terrible!
-Big earthquake. Earthquake is coming! -Earthquake is coming! Earthquake! Trouble!
Wh, wh, what did you say?
Are you sure? Mr. Doumoto. Bi... Big... Earthquake...
Who said such thing?
Assistant robot.
He heard us talking with the Weather Service on the phone!
Thor. Thor!
Thor isn't here.
To where?
He flew out.
What?
Earthquake is coming! Earthquake!
Big earthquake!
Earthquake is coming!
Hey, did you hear it? Earthquake is coming!
He's an assistant at the crust lab.
-Run! Help! -Help!
Earthquake is coming! Earthquake!
Everyone!
Then, Mr. Doumoto, it's a mistake that a big earthquake is coming, right?
Atom, go down to the town and quench a fire.
All right!
Do you understand? Don't let it catch that gas tank!
If that explodes, Shimoda town will be exterminated!
Mr. Fireman, did everyone evacuate?
-Yeah, evacuation is complete. -Okay!
Good!
Go!
What? You never let out such warning?
Mistake? Assistant robot's? Gosh! Dang it...
Make immediate arrangements! Arrest the robot called Thor!
The earthquake warning was a mistake.
If anyone finds the assistant robot of the crust lab, please report.
Where in the world that robot has gone?
Catch that one!
Yes, yes!
Catch that robot.
-Thank goodness. You sure should be appreciated. -I'm glad I could be a help.
Ah, it's that one! The one that lied about earthquake!
-It's that robot. -That robot!
Are you the one who spread the rumor?
No! It's not me!
-It's you for sure! -It's for sure.
It's not me. You are mistaken.
It's not me!
Thor!
Thor! Wait!
Ah, Thor!
You! You are under arrest.
Stay still.
It's not me!
He's resisting. You can shoot him.
Good!
He's running. Shoot! Shoot him!
Ah, I found him.
Thor!
Why did you make such terrible lie?
Let me go!
Where did he go?
What is it?
Ah, it's dangerous!
Really.
Hey! It's dangerous. What are you doing?
Tracks are crooked inside that tunnel, because of landslide.
What? Really?
-It's true. -Thor! I found him!
I won't lose you this time.
Thor, why did you...
Thor!
Hey!
Thor, stop.
What?
I went inside and checked. It was nothing.
So... Where is the other one?
He went out to the other exit already.
Ah, that boy! What is he doing?
Thanks, Kid.
Dangerous!
No!
That's right, Thor!
What happened?
Where did he go?
-Ah, the liar robot has returned. -It's the robot that spread the rumor!
Thor, come here.
Yes!
-Thor... -What in the world happened?
What a mystery for a robot to lie!
Teacher, I'm responsible for what happened.
What did you say?
Let me tell you why.
Teacher! Thor is...
-What did you do with Thor? -Atom, I turned off the energy switch now.
Teacher, come over here. Atom, too.
I lost my wife a year ago through an accident.
My daughter Kozue lost her eyesight in that accident as well.
Her eyes cannot be cured with current medical techniques.
My assistant Thor is Kozue's best friend.
A robot that cannot lie would tell about Kozue's eyes.
She already lost her mother; if she hears that she also lost her eyesight,
I thought she would get shocked and abandon her life.
So I made a decision.
I decided to fix Thor's discrimination circuit
and made him tell opposite things.
This one worked.
Thor kept telling my daughter that she will get cured for sure.
So my daughter could gain hope and stand back up again.
I see. There was such story.
But Mr. Doumoto,
I do understand your feelings, but it's dangerous for robots to not make correct decisions.
He's right. It has made the worst result.
I'm responsible.
I'll tell the truth to my daughter.
I'll fix Thor. Help me.
Ah... It's over.
Huh? Is nobody here?
Thor?
Thor was here. Thor, wake up. There's a phone call.
Energy switch is off. A robot would never take a nap.
Miss.
-Thor, there's a phone call. Take it. -Okay!
Yes, this is the crust lab.
You must be that assistant that lied?
You won't do it.
Put me through the manager.
Hey, what's wrong? Speak!
Thor, what's wrong?
Danger! There's a sign of a big earthquake!
You again? I won't get fooled this time.
Hello! Hello!
Thor.
Shimoda police? A big earthquake is coming.
Please evacuate people!
Hey! Are you still trying to spread such rumor?
I'm going to smash you!
Hey! It's not a lie! Hello!
Miss, please evacuate!
It's horrible! A big earthquake is coming!
Everyone, please evacuate. You should go up that hill.
I have to let townspeople know from now on. Please hurry.
Mr. Atom, please take care of my miss.
Isn't he stupid? Nobody's going to get fooled now.
Atom, Thor's discrimination circuit has been fixed, right?
Yes.
Then the earthquake is coming for real... Oh my gosh.
Danger!
Everyone, a big earthquake is coming!
Please evacuate to the emergency evacuation place!
Earthquake is coming! Hurry, everyone!
-You liar robot! -Are you going to fool us again?
This is true! Please trust me. Big earthquake is coming! Please evacuate!
This is a lie.
Get rid of him!
-He's trying to make us fools. -Please!
Please trust me!
Big earthquake.. is coming.
-Whatever! -You liar robot.
Ah! Earthquake!
Save us, save us...
Atom, get out! Help people evacuate.
Yes, sir!
Hurry!
That's right, Thor...
Thor! Thor!
Thor!
Poor Thor. It wasn't your fault.
Thor! Thor!
Thor, are you all right? If you are there, answer me!
Isn't it Thor there? Thor, right?
Thor, are you all right?
Huh? Answer me if you are okay, Thor.
I'm okay. Don't worry.
Thank goodness, Thor.
I still have some more rescue work to do. You should stay in a safe place.
Be careful.
Teacher, Atom lied.
Atom didn't lie.
Atom imitated Thor to calm Kozue down.
Atom is a great robot to be able to imitate someone.
Atom's a good boy.
Mountain cabin in snowstorm.
I came here to ski with my parents.
A girl came for help when everyone was asleep.
You are Horett?
Aliens that suck up the Earth's water.
Several discuses invade the Earth!
Horett, what happened in Alsore?
Next on Astro Boy, "The Girl from Alsore." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Girl from Alsore"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together