Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
What is that sound?
This sound is...
I hear it outside.
Yes, let's amplify my ear ability.
It's a footstep. Someone's coming.
Hey! Wake up!
Help me.
You are a girl...
-A discus, it's coming to get water. -A discus and water?
It will be a disaster. Let everyone know.
Wait a minute. I'm Atom. Who in the world are...
My name is Horett. I'm from Alsore.
Alsore?
Be aware of the discus with the cross mark on!
There must be some reason. Let's go inside the cabin first.
Who are you!
-It's dangerous. Run away! -Huh?
What are you doing so suddenly?
Atom!
Shoot!
Horett!
Where did everyone go?
The Girl from Alsore
Yes. Who is it? So early in the morning...
Doctor Ochanomizu.
Ah, it's Atom. Are you going to the ski resort?
Yes. I have a question.
I don't know anything about skiing.
It's not about that.
The girl I met last night told me she's from Alsore. What's Alsore?
-What? Alsore? -Yes.
Wait, that's... Ah! It was the name of a planet.
The name of a planet?
But I don't know the details. Let me look into it.
You don't know either?
I'm not an expert on planets. So where is that girl?
Hey, Atom! Hello! Hello!
Gosh, Atom. He just left after asking his questions.
Alsore is the name of a planet.
Brother!
There's a problem!
Uran, what's wrong?
-Come here, there's a problem. -What problem?
Atom, I told you to go down the stairs one by one. How rude.
Why are you looking at me?
With the appearance of mysterious objects, paranormal activities are taking places everywhere.
Please take a look.
The government recognized the seriousness of this and held a Cabinet meeting.
They tried to explain this and prepare for any emergency.
Discus, discus is coming to get water.
Aliens are invading.
Horett. That's right. I have to go see Horett!
Where are you going?
Atom, we are going to go ski, so come back!
It's sucking up snow on the mountains.
Ah, the cross discus.
Be careful of that cross-marked discus. Be careful!
Horett might be caught in that one. Good!
You, to where did you take Horett?
You guys are robots, huh?
We don't have to go easy on robots!
Horett, where are you? Horett!
Atom.
Horett, you were here?
You've been on my mind.
Thank you, but I was wrong.
Earth people will never forgive us.
Explain the details.
As you said, discuses are taking water away.
However, we can't stop robots and discuses that are already working.
Humans started their attack!
Here, Horett.
Let's hurry.
What do you mean robots and discuses moved on their own?
The 12th planet of Alsore always lacked water.
We came to the Earth to ask for water.
But this is a theft.
My mission was to meet the president of the Earth and ask to share water.
However, when we got close to the Earth, robots turned odd.
It wouldn't listen to my commands.
Everything got bad.
I got out and arrived at the Earth sooner than them.
To let you guys know.
But now it's too late.
Stay put here. Don't go anywhere.
Where are you going?
I'll discuss this with Doctor Ochanomizu!
That's what happened.
Horett is not a bad one.
You should let the Defense Department know.
-It's too late, Atom. -Huh? Too late?
The hunt has begun over there.
The hunt?
There was an emergency command that they can kill anyone that's not from the Earth immediately.
Pardon?
So Atom, this is the observation picture of Alsore planet...
What a temper.
I still worried about this one.
The light of this Alsore planet is weird.
It has gotten ten times brighter in a month. This is maybe...?
Horett!
Ah, here!
Atom!
What happened? I told you to hide.
I'm sorry. I'd like to meet the president and apologize.
Not now. They started searching through mountains to catch you.
Ah, the police dog is coming.
Reconnaissance plane.
We have to hide!
The dog is near.
Hey, doggy! Over here!
Huh? Dogs must have found it. Let's go!
Right, over here!
Huh? Where? Where did the dogs go?
Wow, there's no one today. I can ski all I want!
-Something's wrong. -All humans must have ran away.
TV said a mysterious object is coming over here.
It's a problem. We should evacuate too!
Uran! Let's go back!
Go back...? Not that simple...
Here, Uran.
I don't want to. I can finally ski since it's empty.
Ah, it's the one TV talked about!
Uran, Honey, run!
Wait, Honey!
Dangerous!
-Atom. -Atom.
Gosh, please be more careful!
Stop it! Stop sucking the water up!
Hey, stop it! Stop!
All right, then!
This is...
I see. This discus is a tank for saving sucked water.
Hole... It has an automatic recapture system, too?
Then there's nothing I can do.
No matter how much I break, it repairs again.
The cross-marked discus.
I see. It's this one. This one's controlling all the discuses.
Where is the control room?
This is it! This is the main computer.
Take it!
As expected, this is the heart.
This is...
What is this crystal?
The main computer is getting protect by the crystal.
If I step inside, I would get torn to pieces.
That's right. I should turn in the same direction the tornado goes.
Yeah, this was it.
I did it!
Huh? It's odd.
It feels like the temperature is going down.
This is it.
This machine was the temperature regulator of the discus.
This was ordering other discuses to suck water up.
Then...
I did it! Water in the discus froze and increased in volume and the discus burst.
Ah! The cross-marked discus...
Now Horett doesn't have to be chased.
-Doctor Ochanomizu. -Ah, Atom.
Doctor, I took care of Alsore's discus.
It's all right now. Please stop the hunt.
Ah, how nice. So... What about the girl called Horett?
She's waiting for me in a safe place.
In fact...
Listen carefully, Atom.
Atom.
Atom!
Horett.
Atom.
What's wrong?
I took care of the discus. Robots aren't coming anymore.
Thank you, Atom.
Horett, but since there are no discus, you must not be able to go back to your planet.
Would you like to come to my house?
No, I'd like to go back. Everyone's waiting for water.
This planet is beautiful.
It has a lot of water and light.
Horett, in fact... To tell you the truth...
Pardon?
Your, your planet Alsore is now gone.
Atom.
It exploded two days ago.
I'm sorry?
Ah, Horett.
Horett!
Horett, you can now live in the Earth.
-You can come to my house... -Thank you, I...
I will show you how I really look.
Atom, I was disguising as a human
to not surprise people,
but I don't need this anymore.
Atom, please bury me here.
Horett, why?
Ah!
Her body's melting.
Something came out of here.
This is a plant.
I see. Alsoreans were plants.
After One Year
How is it? It's better than last year, right?
Dad!
Uran! Don't ride it like a bulldozer.
Hey, Dad. Where did Atom go?
Atom?
Isn't he around?
No, he's not.
He's the one who wanted to come back here.
He went somewhere by himself.
Horett.
How beautiful.
Atom!
Ah, it's Uran.
Horett, I'm leaving. I'll come back next year again.
Let's see every year.
Uran!
Giant robot Pluto, with million horsepower.
The villain Sultan is trying to destroy all famous robots of the world.
Pluto, it doesn't mean anything to become the strongest robot in the world.
What are you doing? Give Uran back!
I'm coming for you, Pluto. Screw million horsepower!
I'm not going to lose to you!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part One)." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part One)"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together