Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Once upon a time, a very wise fisherman
picked up a small pot at the beach.
When the fisherman opened the lid,
a very big devil came out of that small pot.
A hungry devil tried to eat fisherman right away.
The fisherman who was taken aback said,
"Did you really come out of that pot?"
The devil showed his power to that fisherman.
"Smaller!"
The fisherman was planning to put the devil back into the pot if he had gotten smaller again.
However, the devil noticed.
"Surely you can't drink all that ocean water up even if you were capable of everything, right?"
The devil who got angry by the fisherman's words started drinking ocean water.
"Hey! More! Drink some more!"
And the fisherman got rid of the bad devil.
A righteous person's wisdom can outdo any kind of violence.
The Devil Garon
It might be a meteor.
An object that fell on the northern Alps at about 11:20 P.M.
caused a forest fire,
but the fire department is putting it off.
The fallen object seems to be a massive meteor,
and Doctor Ochanomizu's team is heading to the site.
Doctor.
So this is the place.
Atom, investigate whether there is any radioactivity.
Yes, sir!
There is faint radioactivity.
But it's not high enough to affect human body.
It's quite heavy. It dug a lot.
The depth is about 120 meters.
All trees have fallen in a radial shape due to the falling shock.
Atom, go down and dig the meteor out.
Yes, sir!
Dr.Ochanomizu, would it be all right for a mere robot to dig it out?
Don't call Atom a "mere robot," Dr.Amanogawa.
Atom! Don't break or destroy the meteor!
Wow, it's buried really deep. It must be down here.
It's still got some heat.
It has been heated up since it passed through the atmosphere.
Huh? This isn't a meteor? Someone built this.
-Wh, what is that, Atom? -I have no idea!
Dr.Ochanomizu, this isn't an earthly matter.
I haven't seen anything like this before.
Interesting. This is really interesting.
I hope something weird doesn't happen...
Dr.Ochanomizu.
It opens here. It comes off.
It's even more confusing after disassembling it.
It's like a jigsaw puzzle.
Doctor, this and this go together
And this and this. Huh? Dr.Ochanomizu.
Atom, could you assemble this with your computer?
I'll try it, Dr.Ochanomizu!
It's all done, Doctor.
I didn't even use screws and they fit well.
This seems like a robot.
-Robot? -Robot?
Why? An assembly robot fell from space?
For what?
Who in which planet sent this to earth?
This is getting really interesting.
It's not interesting to me.
Dr.Ochanomizu.
This part doesn't fit anywhere in that space robot.
So it doesn't fit anywhere.
This might be... some kind of recording tape.
Atom, could you translate it with your computer?
I'll try!
Promised Garon.
-Garon? -So that one's name is Garon...
We will send it to Megaropa for sure.
This can kill plusters
and renovate all matters in your planet.
From the king of Yura to the minister of Megaropa.
Kill plusters?
It sounds like it can kill some kind of creatures.
Garon must have fallen to the Earth
due to some kind of error that happened while it was being transported.
We've picked up a ridiculous thing.
However, I'd like to test it to see how it works.
No way! Garon must be disassembled.
We don't need a robot that kills or renovates
something on the Earth!
Disassemble it?
It makes no sense to destroy such precious science data.
But we don't know what kind of harm it would cause to humans!
We can always disassemble it when it happens.
It's only a robot.
If it doesn't follow our commands, we can disassemble it then.
It's easy for you to say that.
Atom, keep Garon accompanied.
Okay.
Dr.Amanogawwa! What do you think you are saying to Atom?
I'm going to disassemble Garon no matter what. We don't need Garon!
Robots like Atom are necessary for this Earth.
So you are a robot just like I am.
Dr.Ochanomizu, it seems like we have completely different opinions.
That's right.
I'm heading back.
Go ahead.
I'm ashamed to know a scientist like you!
I'm going to get Garon no matter what!
The Ministry of Science won't allow you to!
It seems like there's going to be a storm. Come inside the tent.
Okay.
You had a fight with him?
He's as stubborn as a mule.
Atom, please disassemble Garon later.
Garon isn't a robot we need for humans.
Atom, are you okay with thunders?
I'm all right. What about you? Are you scared?
Me? I don't mind such thun...
I hate thunders.
Ah! Dr.Ochanomizu!
-Atom, did you see that? -Garon moved!
Garon! You came to Earth by a mistake.
So please go back to your original form quietly.
Or else people on Earth will get in trouble!
Do you understand what I'm saying, Garon?
Dr.Ochanomizu!
Atom!
What are you doing? You are so violent.
Stop it, Garon!
Wait!
It's got a power to change an entire planet.
Perhaps I cannot fight against it.
That's right! Put Garon in this hole...
All right!
It turned surrounding rocks into magma
with the heat wave it emitted itself.
Dr.Amanogawa, a disparate matter reaction
was caught in the radar 200 meters up front.
It's him for sure.
Garon's been buried.
Hurry!
Stop it!
I'm going to knock Ochanomizu down for sure with this.
We are going to disassemble it and transport it, all right?
-Be careful! -Yes, sir!
Even magma has cooled down around the area where Garon fell.
But Garon cannot be seen.
It must have gotten deeper underground.
Please continue to be on guard.
Where in the world has Garon gone to? It's been 20 weeks already.
Garon! Look at this island carefully!
This island is deserted. There are only palm trees.
Go ahead and renovate this place as you please.
Make it look like the planet you used to live in!
This is amazing. Go ahead and film this!
Record it as it is.
This is beyond expectation.
We can see how a far-end planet looks like on this Earth.
This is!
Doc...Doctor.
Look at the rock Garon has renovated.
This is amazing. This is platinum.
Garon, you really are amazing.
It has turned this deserted island into a platinum island.
With this much platinum in my hand, I could do anything.
What is this smell?
Doctor, something's wrong with the air.
Analyze the atmosphere. Hurry.
There are 70% of nitrogen and 20% of ammonia included in the air!
-What? What about oxygen? -Only 0.2%
Oops... It has renovated even the atmosphere like that of the planet.
Garon, stop it.
Garon, where are you? It's a command. Come out!
I can't breathe...
Doctor, no more! Let's go back to the plane!
I was foolish. Even though it was trained,
a monster is a monster...
Almost every living thing was wiped out.
The suffocating gas that occurred at the southern ocean is spreading fast.
Three islands have already been affected and there are numerous victims.
Passenger liner Gloria which was sailing nearby also has lost its contact.
There's a possibility that it has also gotten affected by that gas.
Atom, this is urgent.
This gas will affect the entire Earth very soon.
We have to find out the cause.
As a robot, you are fit for this job.
-You understand, right? -Of course, Doctor!
Dr.Ochanomizu! Seagulls carcass!
The poison gas seems to be near. It's getting thicker.
Ah! I see the island.
It's a strange island. It doesn't look like Earth.
Ah, there's a collapsed one!
This is Dr.Amanogawa.
What? Dr.Amanogawa? Why would he be in that...
This is Garon's deed for sure!
There's a trace that Garon has melted with a high heat wave.
Isn't Garon nearby? Be careful, Atom!
Yes, sir!
Garon!
Garon! I finally found you!
Garon, so it's you who are emitting this poisonous gas!
Stop it right away!
Stop it!
No... No! You can't do such thing!
It's for the world peace. I can't help it.
A hydrogen bomb? No way.
Even Garon would be finished if we use hydrogen bomb.
But the radiation...
The army has decided already. They probably started the countdown.
Then what would happen to Atom?
Atom! Atom, hurry and run.
A hydrogen bomb missile is flying there!
Ah, I hear the missile sound.
Doctor! The missile has turned into gold.
My gosh. There's nothing that can defeat that monster?
It's only one thing.
Our best air force is charging in right now!
Doctor, it's no use to fight against Garon.
-Please stop the attack! -But...
I have an idea.
You have something wise in mind, Atom?
Doctor, in one of fairy tales, there is a story in which
a fisherman who was about to be eaten
by the devil defeats the powerful devil with his wisdom, right?
I'd like to test that!
All right! Atom, try then. I wish you luck.
Garon! Listen carefully!
You were probably planning to renovate even the atmosphere of this island,
but there is one important thing remaining.
Would you like me to tell you what that is?
It's gravity! The Earth's gravity!
If you want to create a planet like the one you used to live in, change the gravity as well!
Change the gravity for even one minute!
He's really going to do it. Can he really change gravity as well?
As expected, Garon can do it.
Only for a minute! Change the gravity!
Doctor, Garon's focusing on changing the gravity right now.
Why did you ask him to do it?
If the planet's gravity is smaller than the Earth's, then the gravity there will decrease.
I did it!
Hey, Atom, what happened? What's wrong?
Dr.Ochanomizu, can you hear me? It's all over!
Atom.
The part of the island with decreased gravity was cut out; I can't even find a trace of Garon.
I see. So that's what happened.
If the gravity decreases only on that island,
the air gets lighter there and goes up.
Then, the surrounding air is driven toward there like a typhoon
and whatever that is on that island goes up in sky.
It's like launching a rocket; it goes right up to the stratosphere.
With that force, it gets out of the Earth's gravity zone and directly flies into space.
But wouldn't the atmosphere of that place continue to fly away to space?
No. I told him to change it only for a minute.
Garon decreased gravity only for a minute.
Atom's wisdom won against force.
Good job, Atom.
But Doctor,
If Garon were delivered to the right place, he would have used his power rightfully, right?
Now you know how fearful it is to use your power incorrectly.
The fire fighter robot Woo.
The nurse robot Lilli.
The welder robot Pitato.
They were all abandoned by human and were sent to junkyard.
They can still work though.
And a big fire breaks out in the space factory.
Cheer up! Now is the time to show your power!
Next on Astro Boy, "Hurry, You Three Second-Rate Knights"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together