Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Where is it?
What have I done?
Atom vs. Atlas III: Crystal of the Desert
Hey, you guys, can you tell me where am I?
Someone sucked my energy
That is why my head is blurred and cannot remember anything
Do you want Energy Cassette?
Can you speak human language?
Yes, I can speak human language and other 18 animal languages
Well, so you are robot, too?
Yes. My name is Drop III. I'm doing officer here
So what is your name?
Nice to meet you. I'm Atom
Well, I found you because the airplain crashed...
Did the airplain crash?
Can you walk?
Sure, I can walk
Ok, then, follow me, I can share my Energy Cassette
Hey, Candy
No, my name is Drop, not Candy!
Sorry. So Drop, what are you doing here?
I told you I'm the officer. I'm protecting birds or animals that are living here
Why?
Because they are at the edge
If I don't protect them, every animal will die
Well?
What happening here?
Wh-What?
Well, at last, this place is also dried up completely
This place is...?
This place had really clean water recently
This place was our oasis
Sorry guys. You guys were really thirsty, right?
This place was a water fountain, right?
Yes, but river and Oasis are drying up rapidly
Before was filled with blue view, but these days, every field and flowers are dying
Let's go, Atom
Gosh, I can't walk anymore
Be firm. Look, that place is my office.
Come in
I can't get in
You have such a big body
Well, I will bring you Energy Cassette, so thrust your hand
Well, is it okay?
This is too small for me
Don't be rude. This is my spare
But this cannot fit to my socket
Then, I will search for another one
Hmm, where did I put away?
This is not the one I'm searching for
I found it! This is what I was searching for
This is too old. You can't use it
No, this can fit
This was my summer gift from last year
Yes, it works for me
I will try
Water!!
I found underground water
You did it! I will honor you!
Thanks, Atom. You are good robot
I remember that I came here to research this desert
This place had lots of trees one year ago, but
it changed to desert suddenly, right?
Yes, that's why all animals are dying
The Organization of International Protection sent many flights
to search for cause, but
No one came back safely
Then, I came here for this time
When I reached to the sky, I met the strange thing
Then, I was shot down suddenly
I remember until there
Hmm, the attacking monster may relate to that one
What is "that one"?
In the middle of desert, there is a hole
A hole?
That one!
Ah! Something is falling there. I'll go to see
Take care yourself
Well
It's too hard
I'm surprised
That's strange. My Laser Blast doesn't make damage
Humans! Real humans!!
Who are they?
Welcome
Well known robot hero in the world
I heard about you
I'm Libian. This is my castle
This is Atlas's and my castle
Did you say Atlas?
I fought against Atlas before, so you made Atlas?
No, I'm robot, too
I'm a friend of Atlas
Atlas!!
Atom
Atom, I know you are coming to meet me again
Doctor Ochanomizu asked you to come, right?
Why you know that fact?
I know everything
That's why I welcomed you
So the reason why the airplain crashed was
your sword absorbed energy
You're right. You didn't forget the power of this sword
Don't worry. I'm not gonna do anything now
Also, I have other powers now
I show you where you are now
Crystal, my castle
Look! Is this wonderful?
This castle can go everywhere including the earth and behind the moon
Also, this Crystal can dive into ground
So that is you who killed water and field
and turned it to desert
Yes, you are right. I did it
That is because my castle use a lot of water
But because of you, many animals are died by thirst
Using magnetic fly dries inside soon
So I have to use steam to give moisuture
Because I know why the water exists
Robots can live without moisuture
Yes, robots don't need, but...
humans need moisture. They will become mummies
Why are there so many humans?
They are my slaves, and I'm their master. I command them to work here
I use ultrasonic to control humans the way I want
I talked you about one thing before
I will control over every human one day
My dream comes true soon
If I become a master, I'll stop those stupid wars
But because of your dream, many animals are dead
It's just little bit of victims
I'll give a world that animals can live. And I will make a new world
Do you think it is great?
I don't know
I think it's bad thing!
You kidding. There's no reason for robot becoming a master.
You are robot, too
Atom, let's work together to become a master of the earth
No, I don't wanna help for bad job. I wanna go outside
I wanna go back to home
You stupid. If you wanna go back, just try!
Atom, you can't go outside. I have an idea
What is your process now?
Yes, sir. 95% now. A little bit more
Atom's new body
And he will become my brother with this form
Where is Atom now?
Yes, Sir
Atom, you are searching for exit?
Even though you search for exit, you cannot go outside
Please let Atom go
No, he can't go away
I will give him a new form. After that, he will work here forever
You said you just wanna invite Atom here
Why you can think such an absurd idea!
Absurd idea?
I'm the king of the world. I can do everything I want to do
Every robot and human will be against you
It doesn't matter if...
you are around me, Libian
Me?
Yes, when I knew that you were destroyed by Master Walbologis
I was surprised that I had bloodthirstiness toward him
A that time, I realized you are my most precious
I give my every strength to remake you
Libian, please stay with me forever
No! Don't get close to me!
You are scary and different compare to other robots
When you were made, I heard that you had some kind of factor...
Maybe that's because of that
Libian
Please, go away from here
Libian, if I lost you, I will become alone
Atom!
I listened to everything
Atom! Get away now!
This castle is steadily far away from the earth
Maybe somewhere behind the moon, Atlas will remodel you
I will tell you secret pathway. Come this way
And you?
Get away! I'm going back!
There!
Sorry
Got it
You such a...!
Really? Well!
He can't go out
Libian, don't push that bottom. This is my command
Libian!?
You stupid!
Go back to my castle, Atom
No, I don't want!
I cannot be helped
This is your end
There!!
No, please stop, both of you!
Stop!
You guys both will die
Atom, look at this!
My eyes are being dizzy
My electric brain will break!
3D Vibration Wave! Your body will be apart!
Libian!?
Libian!!
Libian, I will make you again
Atom, our fight isn't finished yet. Don't forget next time!
Equator Race around the Earth
Cool machines from every contry will appear
My friend, Koichi, will be in the race with white planet plain
What is it? Big octopus and bottomless swamp disturb his race
That's Skunk! I'm not forgiving you guys!
Next is No. White Planet. Enjoy!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together