Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Dang it!
It's dangerous! Shoot...
The Great Adventure of Little Robot Sam
Isn't it cool? Super Zero.
Yeah, how lucky for him to not get hurt shooting all that.
That's why Tom Stanton is so great.
I'm also going to be an action hero like Stanton soon!
Honk, honk!
Hey!
You could never do it.
Kids! The draw for the set tour has begun.
If I get selected, can I meet Tom Stanton?
-Wow, let's go! -Let's go!
Numbers 2015, 2092, 2208, 2301 have been drawn.
Wrong again.
-No way! -Is it yours, Uran?
I missed it only by one.
-Let me see, I'm number 2297. -I'm 2298.
-2299. -I'm 2302.
Then...
I'm 2301.
Ah, really!
I'm in!
-Atom, we are friends, right? -Huh?
If you don't mind...
Can you give me that number? I can pay you as much as you want.
Even if you say that, I only have one winning ticket...
Ah!
I'm sure you are going to give it to me, right? You are my brother.
-Uran! -What a kind brother you are.
It's fun.
Wow, an antique robot.
This is a doll. I'm for the role of robot.
-It's Tom Stanton! -It's the real Tom Stanton!
-Super Zero! -How nice!
Only for five minutes. No autographs, and only pictures.
Don't push! Keep the line! Help!
I can't see him!
Good.
Sexual harasser!
Wh, what is it.
It's time for Mr. Stanton to go shooting!
It's over now, over!
No way.
Those in the set tour, please come this way!
I've hid well.
Scary face.
It's hot.
-It's like a sauna. -It's so hot!
-Who is that? -Well.
It's that car.
There's a surveillance. We can't go in.
But I'm going to see the real action!
Hello.
It's simple.
Unlike what I expected, it's messy inside.
Where are they shooting?
Shooting will begin.
Are you ready?
We will shoot now. Ready,
Start!
Good. Okay.
Your turn is over.
Good job, Mr. Stunt mini robot.
Huh, what's this?
Mr. Stanton. Please standby with the makeup for the next scene.
Here! Wash and fuel this.
All right! Shall we begin then?
Ready, go!
Ah, it's the town.
Cut! Okay. It was the best acting, Stanton.
Shall we shoot the love scene with Amazones now?
Super Zero. I can't live without you.
Me neither.
Hah... So there was this kind of manipulation.
Where is that small robot earlier?
You really are made well. I could never see you as a robot.
I will be trapped inside here again?
Your turn isn't coming back for a while.
Ah, please...
Ah, I'm running out of energy...
There it is.
Who are you?
I'm a robot as the same as you are. I'm Uran. Hi.
-Uran? -Come out.
-I'm Sam Stanton. Call me Sam. -You really do look alike.
I was made to act as a double for Tom Stanton.
So all the dangerous action scenes were done by you.
That's my job.
That's mean.
He didn't do anything but he became a popular star.
But... If people find out it was done by a robot, they won't like it.
Are you fine with this?
No. I'd like to watch the movie I'm in even if it's only for once.
You haven't seen the movie you are in yet?
When my turn is over, I get to stay here.
Gosh, that's not fair!
All right! I'll take you then.
No, I can't. I will get scolded if they find out.
It's all right. Count on me.
So, who shall I date next?
It hurts...!
Oh, there was a person. I'm sorry.
What are you! What are you going to do to Sam?
What? An action star?!
You...!
-Would Mr. Stanton be okay? -Leave that kind of guy alone.
What happened, Mr. Stanton?
I've never been treated like this!
Oh my gosh. We got that robot stolen!
Pardon?
If people find out about Sam, my popularity is over.
Huh? Please find him back!
Hold on!
Someone must be here.
This is space!
I'm going to crash!
What, it's only a toy.
Ah, cut! Cut! Cut!
Hey! You can't enter the zero gravity studio on your own!
Hey, somebody get that kid out of here! Hurry!
-Is this the room with no gravity? -We shoot all the space scenes here.
Ah! There she is. Hey! Grab her!
-Ah, it's the manager. -He's on the bad side. All right.
Turn off the zero gravity switch!
I'm sorry!
Catch her! She's a thief!
Let's go out first.
-Ah, what is this? -It's a giant shark robot.
It's the next opponent I'll fight in the next Super Zero movie.
Amazing... It really looks real.
He's here.
What? You got the Stanton robot stolen?
That little girl ran away with it, thinking it's a doll.
If the world finds out about that robot, Stanton is over now!
Get it back no matter what!
Ah, yes! She wouldn't have gotten out of this studio yet, so I will for sure!
Assign more emergency staff!
How many times did I tell you? The set tour car has gone back already.
But she really didn't come back yet.
She might be missing, so please let me look for her inside.
You can't! I told you already!
All the guard robots are keeping the gate.
Something will turn out if we get to the gate.
I found her! She's here!
They are coming.
She's here!
-Come over right away! -What are you doing?
Let me go!
That voice is Uran's!
Hey!
Uran!
-Let me go! -Ah, she's a robot!
There!
Atom, thank you.
I was worried. What trouble did you cause again?
No, I just saved this poor robot.
You... Tom Stanton!
No, I'm Sam Stanton.
What? She ran away? You stupid!
Find him before the secret leaks out. If you can't bring him back, get rid of him.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sam Stanton.
Wow, this is an elaborate toy.
No, Dad. I told you he's the real Stanton.
Isn't Stanton a celebrity? You shouldn't lie.
Dad, you don't know. Let's go, Sam.
Well, it would be better for us to move if he just think of you as a toy.
You have to return him to the set after we watch the movie.
I know!
Sam, let's play in my room.
We are currently looking for Sam's whereabouts with robot dogs.
We will find the culprit by tomorrow no matter what.
Find him before people see him. It's confidential!
You don't have to be so anxious, right?
We can always make a new robot.
You stupid!
Super Zero series
is popular because it is known that you act without stunts.
Is it all right for you to get caught for lying?
After all, the only things you do are shooting love scenes and holding signing events.
If you feel angry, then try shooting at least one scene without a stuntman!
It's all fat.
Sam, let me show you something cool.
Wow, it's for my size.
-Here, this is the prince outfit. -Can I put this on?
I've wanted to try this kind of role.
Let me introduce you your partner.
She's a pretty princess, right?
Umm... I can't dance.
-How was it? Wasn't it fun? -Yes.
This is more fun than actions.
Robot dog has stopped!
-What? Where is it? -This is Atom's place.
Get him back by tomorrow morning for sure.
-Bye. -Bye!
Ah, that's right, Uran.
What?
Get him back to the set after you watch the movie.
All right!
-Then, Sam, bye! -Bye!
-It's too early to watch the movie, right? Shall we go for a walk? -Yes.
I can't believe such a broad world existed.
What are you doing to Sam?
Wait!
How annoying.
Sam, are you all right?
I'm used to this.
It's a robot dog.
-What? You failed again? Stupid! -I have nothing to say.
Anyhow, call her in. I have a good thought.
All right? Don't let them be on videos.
Congratulations!
You've been invited to the special premiere of the latest Super Zero series movie!
The invitation will soon be delivered. Please come.
Wow, it's from the movie company. Sam, how great!
Are we there yet?
It must be around here... This is next to the set.
Ah, there it is!
This theater is nice.
-It was built a while ago. -Let's go in.
-There's no one. -I'm here to escort you.
It's a weird theater.
Uran went inside with Sam.
Of course, she didn't notice that this is a set.
-What a big theater. -I don't know, it's my first time being here.
-It's too dark. -Maybe the movie has begun.
What? This is not a theater.
I'm going to make both of you into scrap metal. Begin!
What is this!
Open the door!
Uran! Uran!
Where did she go? Did she go to the movies by herself?
Huh?
This is from that shooting set.
Are they here to get Sam back?
No! What are you doing?
What is this? What in the world is happening?
That one is a prop robot for the previous movie.
What is it doing in the theater?
Open it! Open!
Sam, you should escape here, hurry!
-Uran, what about you? -I...
Ah, it's the switch.
Thank you.
You stupid! He ran away!
Chase him!
Is this really a theater?
-This is the set I've been staying. -What?
Sam. Sam, where are you?
Uran!
Atom, help me.
Hey! Let Uran go!
Atom!
Are you okay, Uran?
Gosh. We didn't do anything, but they attacked us.
They were probably trying to get rid of me before the secret gets out.
What?
-Dang, Atom's here. -What should we do?
Let's meet the manager here and talk about it.
-Atom! -Uran!
Here, the Mega Jaws is coming.
This is a sewer.
What is that?
Uran, come over here.
It's a shark! What is it doing here?
It's Mega Jaws for the next movie.
It's coming!
Atom!
You did it, baby!
Enormous strength. All right, with my leg jet...
-What happened! -It has disappeared.
It's because you tried to get rid of them!
-It hurts! My, it hurts... -So it was like that.
-Atom. -Sam!
Now I know all about your wicked plan!
Please forgive us.
We thought the popularity for Super Zero might go down if people find out about Sam...
If that happens, my life is over.
We could forgive you with certain conditions.
-We will do anything! -Please, spare me!
"The Great Adventure of Mini-mini Prince" -Sam Stanton for the leading role
The Premiere
Let me introduce you the big star you already know, even though this is his debut.
Mr. Sam Stanton!
The movie you are about to watch is a fantastic musical.
It's the one I've always wanted to work on.
Please enjoy it.
Uran's idea worked.
A rocket escaped through buildings.
Ah! Livian is on board!
Memorial circuit has been broken down due to explosion.
Miss Livian, for what have you come to teach?
Glaciers in the North Pole started melting, and there's a huge chaos in the world.
Atlas, is this your work?
Next on Astro Boy, "Atom vs. Atlas VI"
The King in the Ice! Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "Atom vs. Atlas VI"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together