Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
The Monster of Kuraken
Yes, this is Ochanomizu.
Aren't you Pipi? How are you? Still the same?
Pipi.
Now fish will soon come to spawn. So it will get busy.
Huh? Fish!
Pipi lives in the ocean ranch.
Atom, say hello.
Pipi?
Pipi is a robot built for protecting sea animals.
You look after fish?
Wow, it must be fun.
But it's about time the monster of Kuraken comes here.
So it's dangerous.
-A monster will come? -We call it "monster",
but actually it's the tidal current that comes during the spawning season.
That's not right! It's different this year.
What is?
Well... That is... Something's different from any other years.
Ah, again!
Doctor, something must have happened again. I should go.
Hmm... What would that be?
Since she's being nervous like that, it surely isn't an average thing.
Is it a big deal for that tidal current to come?
It's called jet stream; the cold ocean current of the North Pole
comes by crossing over the Pacific Ocean.
So it's like a storm?
And at the spot where the cold and warm current meet,
tremendous amount of plankton, which is a food for fish, outbreaks.
Is that why there is an ocean ranch in Kuraken area?
Since I'm worried about Pipi, would you like to go visit her
and learn about some ocean ranch works?
Okay! I wanted to be there.
Huh? What is that?
Amazing. It's a submarine volcano.
I should be near Kuraken seas now.
Huh?
Wow... How awful. What would have happened?
Is this the effect of that jet stream called as the monster of Kuraken?
Hey, Pipi! Where are you?
Poor boy. Hold on.
Thank goodness.
-Thank you, thank you. -Huh? You can speak?
Yes! Pipi taught me how to talk.
I came to meet that Pipi. Where is Pipi?
Follow me.
Over here.
Pipi! Pipi!
Pipi!
Hey, Atom. Thanks for coming.
You are a mermaid?
Yes. It's easier for me to move underwater in this form.
Wow, it's amazing.
Anyhow, Atom, take a look at this.
Jet stream?
No. Sharks attacked.
Sharks?
Nothing like this has happened before. But this year, sharks came here three times.
Tons of spawns taken.
All right! If they come again, I'll chase them out.
It's about time for the monster of Kuraken to come.
That's the monster of Kuraken?
It really looks like a storm.
-No way! Sharks are here again! -What?
Stop it!
I won't forgive you!
Now the sharks are gone. Come out.
Hey! Are you all right?
-It's been horrible. -They always invade with a current.
Pipi! Trouble. Problem!
The forest of golden corals is in danger!
-What? -Golden corals?
It's where fish spawn every year. It's a precious place...
We have to restore it!
What's the forest of golden corals?
It's where corals with gold grow.
How beautiful. I never knew such place existed.
Yes. It's a secret.
If it gets out, people will come in flocks and get rid of this precious spawning plce.
You must have been attacked many times.
We have to finish this before fish come.
I'll help!
Please put those pieces here.
Percentage of gold in corals: 72%
It's a rare bonanza.
How amazing. It's a mountain of treasure.
Hey! It's nice to see you again. I'm Kim Samgak.
I'm the grandson of grandson of grandson of that famous scientist Hu Manchu.
I discovered the forest of golden corals in the Kuraken seas.
It's an amazing discovery. It's all mine.
Bring in the gold-collecting robot right away!
This is the collector robot I made. It's of good performance.
I earn money easily.
Huh? It's the sound of an engine.
Ah, it's blocked because of corals... All right!
Attention! An object is approaching. Danger! Danger!
What is it?
What? That's Atom!
He always disrupts people. I don't like him. Destroy him!
Ah! Submarine!
Hold on!
How shabby. I'm running away too.
Stop!
Stop the engine. Turn on the chameleon tool!
What is this, too easy.
Hey, Atom! Are you all right?
There was a suspicious submarine. It must have collected some corals.
It disappeared all of sudden.
Ah, the forest is dug up like this.
It's that one!
-What was that light? -Let's go check out!
Ah, what is that?
-It looks like shark teeth. -But this is too big.
It's here. Here. It's here!
-Really? -What is here?
Fish are here to spawn. Atom, we are going to get busy.
All right!
This is a bed for fish spawns.
It's pretty.
More of them will come.
And this coral forest will be full of fish.
So you won't be able to take any rest until eggs hatch?
That's right.
A current! Sharks will come!
-Pipi! We have to protect everyone. -All right!
You!
Atom, good job!
You can't be here!
Is there any place like an island?
Ah! A fishing boat is passing by. All right!
Hey, what's that?
Let's go!
Sharks!
Hold on, the weather forecast didn't say that there would be a shark rain.
My!
Come here!
Go!
Ah, shark again.
-What a cooperative shark. -Another shark after a clear day.
Is it over now?
What is that?
Atom!
-Atom, wake up. -Atom.
That is?
What is that?
I can't miss my golden corals. I'm going to come back with a map.
Trouble! The ground has moved!
Stop the bullcrap and do the investigation right!
Trouble! The ground is coming up!
If you don't do it seriously, I'm going to feed you to sharks.
Danger!
Wh, wh, what is this?
-Danger! Danger! -Is this a submarine earthquake?
Luka, help me. Let's go home.
Okay!
I hope it gets better soon...
There is a golden coral piece.
I'm going to claim this island mine right now!
Is it a sea snake?
It's not a sea snake. It's a sea dragon!
My submarine's broken now.
This is a monster. So there was a real monster of Kuraken.
I don't need gold. I give up. Goodbye!
Since a great amount of electric current flew through, it passed out.
-This will be fixed soon. -Thank goodness.
Ah, Pipi!
-It's done now. -Atom, she woke up.
A huge monster moved.
All right. Let's go now!
What is this organism?
It looks like a stingray.
Why is this so big? It would at least be 1,000 meters.
That dug ground is the trace of this one.
Stop it! Fish spawns are...
Watch out! You can't handle him.
Leave this to me.
You!
Easy!
Atom, are you all right?
What a great shock. That's an electric stingray monster.
I have a good idea. Let's go back home!
Hurry! Over here!
A powerful dynamite.
We will feed this with corals to that monster.
Yeah? It must have some weak point inside.
All right!
It won't work.
Hurry, kids!
Stop! You guys should hide behind that mountain.
Don't come out until I get rid of that monster.
Pipi! I failed.
Besides, the monster now knows there are fish here.
Stop! Stop! Don't come!
Stop! Stop!
Luka! Watch out!
Watch out!
Atom, what should we do? We will all get eaten.
All right, there was a submarine volcano nearby, right? Let's finish him there.
But how are we going to take him there?
We will all do it together!
Huh?
I'm going to take kids and him.
A bait? But that's...
Since there is at least a possibility of getting rid of that monster, let's try it!
I see. Then I will be staking out in crater.
Kids! Run this way!
The second group.
All right. If I take this rock away, magma will come out.
Hurry, hurry!
-Luka, you can do it! -Pipi, are you all right?
There! A little bit more!
Kids! Let's pass by that crater as fast as possible!
Atom! We did it!
All right! Move!
This way!
How cute.
Thanks to you, spawns hatched out safely as well.
Thank goodness.
You guys should also continue to grow no matter what happens.
Bye!
Atom, thank you. Please say hello to Doctor Ochanomizu.
Now I'm prepared for any kind of situation.
-Atom, please come visit us again. -Okay!
Bye!
A glass bottle was found by the beach.
"Please come save me."
"From Rumy of Pochom-pochom Island"
I flew to that island that's not on the map without telling my parents.
But I got attacked by a marble there,
and got my head horns damaged.
Next on Astro Boy, Rumy in Pochom-pochom Island. Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy. "Rumy in Pochom-pochom Island"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together