Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Kid, sign this document.
Then you can be the happiest kid in the world.
"With no year limit and no payment, it will be possessed as an asset..."
What does this mean?
Good kid, good... Okay!
Tobio!
Dad, I'm here...
Robot Circus
Now, it's all set.
This is the gift from this trip. His name is Tobio.
You have to get to work right away.
Chief, it's a small robot.
Yes, but I'm sure we can use him for something.
Cassy, you take care of him.
I'm busy. I have to practice tightrope-act and ring-of-fire act.
I also have to take care of robots.
That's right. Teaching this one is going to be a hard work.
He doesn't seem to be smart.
Ha ha ha...
I know how to think...
How dare you talk back to Tornedo! You are only a newbie.
He's the best one in this group!
Tornedo's turn now!
Okay, I'm coming.
He's a robot, too, right? Does he get beaten as well?
We hired an inventor to make Tornedo with a high expense.
He's a specially-made robot.
He's way above you.
Come, you will see once you take a look.
Ladies and gentlemen, a midair play with thrill, speed and suspense!
After passing through a 50,000 volt current,
will he be able to reach that golden end?
Do you know? Around that ring,
a high-voltage current is flowing.
Wow!
Only the one who can calculate the time precisely
can catch that end of the ring.
Poor robot,
that's only a fake act.
You've waited long enough! The next one is our biggest celebrity,
Mr. Tornedo!
Look at his chest!
The world's most precise clock, the one that can measure 1/10000 second,
"The micro-second meter" is installed.
That's amazing!
Do you see? Now that you know,
don't you dare disobey the orders of Tornedo and I!
Hey, newbie, are you working hard enough?
Yes!
You are not putting much effort. Make it more shiny.
Cassy, the newbie must be doing all right, right?
He's cleaning the white lion over there.
A white lion? Is there such thing?
What is this white one?
I'm cleaning the black-striped dirt.
You fool! It's tiger's stripe! You are fired! Fired!
Yes, fired!
You stupid!
Uh-oh, it increased!
What a useless... Ha ha ha...
Make sure you don't tear it.
You always fail because of too much strength.
Yes.
Hurry and load it in conveyor. We will begin!
Okay!
Ah, hold on, hold on. What is this with a skirt?
You always have your own way. Dang it!
Ah, this will do. Hey, load it in conveyor.
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey! Stupid! You stupid!
Load the robot! You stupid newbie!
I'm sorry...
He caused trouble again...
You stupid moron!
Who breaks this important robot?
I'm sorry...
Yesterday you broke a motorcycle, and a trampoline the other day.
How many more thing do you have to break?!
Stop it, Chief!
Move! I'm going to discipline him!
He's trying his best. He breaks stuff because he works too hard.
If he continues to do this... I'm going to be broke.
I shouldn't have brought this useless stuff!
I'm going to make an orangutan or something after disassembling this! Come here!
Wait! Wait for only three days.
Three days?
I'll teach him for sure in three days.
Dang! Fine, I'll give you three days.
If you fail to do so, he's going to become an orangutan.
That clown is still a kid robot.
It's embarrassing. In the near future,
the Declaration of Robot Rights is going to be valid.
A place like this is old-fashioned as expected.
It is the same for Japan.
Speaking of this, what happened to that infamous son robot of Doctor Tenma?
It's been missing.
Hmm... A good output, a good electronic brain...
I've heard that it's a high-performance robot
that no one's ever been able to make.
Uh-oh, it's already time for the meeting. Let's go.
The news from Japan is being broadcasted.
After Doctor Tenma has gone missing, The Minister of Science...
Doctor Ochanomizu! You are going to be appointed!
I've heard that already...
What's the matter?
You seem to have been deeply in thought since a while ago.
That robot looks exactly like him.
With who?
With Tobio. Doctor Tenma's son.
Tornedo!
What are you doing! The audience is waiting.
Chief, I'm in a bad condition.
I haven't received Overhole for 5 months already.
Hold on until this tour finishes. Besides, in tonight's performance,
there's Mr. Capone from Chicago.
All right, Chief.
Ladies and gentlemen, you have waited long enough.
The biggest celebrity of this robot circus, Mr. Tornedo is here!
That clown received a fairly good response from the crowd.
Thanks to Cassy.
Ah,
Something's wrong!
It's broken! 1/550 second late!
What?
No! You shouldn't fly!
It's dangerous, Mr. Tornedo!
Ah!
Tornedo... You are in big trouble.
Ah, Mr. Capone!
It was embarrassing, Hamegg.
Cheer up, it's not all your fault.
Yeah, but if I noticed only a second earlier,
I could have helped Tornedo.
That's too much!
He's going to cancel the contract of the tour.
You mean we have to pay penalty fees?
Without the 50,000-voltage act,
Hamegg's circus has no merit.
Th..Then... I'm broke!
Mr. Capone,
If there is an actor who can perform the voltage act,
are you going to accept our team?
Of course, but do you have such robot?
Yes, I do.
You... You...
It's this one.
This little one? Are you sure?
I'm sure.
It's possible if he practices.
Hmm, but it could gain more popularity if a small robot like this performs it.
But this kind of newbie...
Let him do it, Hamegg! I'll teach him.
Hmm, anyhow, I got him for free. He's a little one and he's broken...
How's it, Chief? Why don't we make him do it?
If the voltage act is back, then the contract is still in the place.
All right! Let's do it!
Instead, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
After the tour in Chicago,
Please let go of him.
Ah, fine, whatever!
That's it, Mr. Capone. Thank you!
It's troubling my heart a bit. It's the same.
That robot...
Hello, please put Japan's Ministry of Science on the phone.
Hello, the Ministry of Science.
This is Ochanomizu.
Would you give me a data on Doctor Tenma's son?
The one on Tobio who died on a car accident.
Hold on.
Tobio Tenma, 9 years old at the point of death.
Height: 135cm
It's that kid!
Huh?
Where did the circus team go?
The train runs for Chicago, Chicago.
Robot Circus train runs.
Life in Circus team is fun.
Robot Circus, tan tan tan
Hmm, tan tan tan
Wait, stop!
Look where you are flying!
One more time.
Okay!
Ah! It hurts!
I'm sorry.
Chief, are you all right?
You guys... Are you trying to get me killed?!
Do you want me to do this?
I beg you, please don't beat me!
You can just be crushed or something,
but if this Chicago tour fails, I will be broke!
I'll make sure to be able to do it by the first day.
Here, Chief, go to sleep.
If you fail this time, you are going to be an orangutan!
Keep that in mind!
Hu...
I'm sorry, Cassy.
Go to sleep.
But I still have some practice...
It's all right. I'm tired, too.
Why are you being so nice to me?
I don't know, but
I must have some interest in you.
It's a good feeling. Back in long time,
I feel like I received such attention from someone like this.
Where are you from?
I don't know, but it feels like
a nice person had always been next to me.
If I were a normal child,
I would say that they were my parents,
but there are no such things for robots.
Yes, I am a robot.
I always cause trouble
to Cassy because of my mistakes.
You are different. I'm not sure what it is,
but you have big strength and wisdom that other robots don't have.
Do you think so?
Be confident. You will be able to do it tomorrow.
We came a long way for Chicago, Chicago.
Robot Circus is going to be held.
Please, check this one out.
Robot Circus, tan tan tan
Tan tan tan
Animals all seem out of heart today.
It's because the chief didn't
give us enough injection of energy.
Shut up! Ever since Tornedo
broke down, I'm all broke!
If you can't move, maximize your output!
If you do such thing, it will break us!
Enough with talking back! You only have to endure it.
Look, he's already energized!
Cassy, I don't know, you seem nervous.
It's all right. I'll give you a good one.
They are the shoes I wore on my first performance.
Wow! Thank you!
How is it? Do they fit?
They fit perfectly!
It looks quite good on you!
Yes, I'll do my best!
You can do it.
Then, the next stage is the famous
50,000-voltage current act!
Are you the chief?
As you can notice.
I want to see a robot called Tobio.
What business do you have with him?
I'm a Japanese scientist Ochanomizu.
I'm here to protect that kid according to the International Robot Laws.
Ah!
No! You have to stop that!
He did it!
This is a treasure I found.
Good! He did it!
What's wrong? Stop it right away!
Ah! What am I going to do?!
Amazing!
What a robot!
I've never seen a show like this!
This is the masterpiece of Doctor Tenma.
"The Mighty Robot" we've been dreaming of.
Amazing! Amazing!
Ha ha ha...
Look, all components of this kid are all Japanese.
I'll take it.
You fool! Look at this.
This kid and I have a contract.
Chief! You promised!
You said you would let him go if he succeeds with this act.
You can never trust a verbal promise.
You are sly. You are a liar!
Shut up!
Stop talking and wash him!
Fine, fine.
Come here.
Are you trying to ignore the Declaration of Robot Rights?
Do you think you can lock him under such paper?
With that person,
you must go back to Japan.
He's the only one who can make you happy.
Cassy, what's up? What are you doing?
Trust me.
So... Oh, this would work.
Show me your arm.
I have to do it quickly.
Good, you.
Do you know the true value of that robot?
He can fly in space,
and under deep oceans.
Wow! Now that I've heard that, I can't let him go even more.
Wh..What an evil man!
You are worse than a robot!
Wh, What just happened?
What?
Ah... The gas container suddenly exploded...
Poor thing!
Hah, is this the best robot in Japan like you told me about?
What an idiot...
Hmm... Oh! You are here!
Hey, I've been waiting.
Good.
You are okay.
Hello, Doctor!
When I first got the call, I thought I was dreaming.
But I was surprised at those pieces.
I thought you were all broken for sure.
I worked hard to find things that would look good on you.
Here, we cannot let others see you.
I won't forget about you.
Me neither.
I won't forget you, the small one yet with powerful strength.
Then, since this guy is an atomic boy,
Atomic?
Why don't we call this kid "Atom"?
Atom...
Atom! Fine! Good! It's a good name!
Bye, Atom.
Bye, Cassy.
We can meet again, right?
Of course. Take care!
Bye!
Cassy!
I liked you, Atom...
Next on Astro Boy
I'm Atom. After coming back to Japan,
I decided to go to elementary school.
I'll be in third grade.
My teacher is the bearded man.
I made many friends.
One day, silly Shibugaki boys
went to a theme park that hasn't finished its construction.
Big trouble! My friends are in danger!
Next on Astro Boy...
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
A machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together