Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
There is a telegram.
"We wish good luck for the red team in the burning planet." -From Yamato base of Venus Investigators
"Don't lose to the red team. We are here."
-From the crewmen of the third space tanker
My, my, what is the minister doing? Is he still working by himself?
This year's over in two hours anyway.
Ah, it's me.
There is a visitor for you, Minister.
I told you not to let anyone in because I'm busy!
-But he's insisting... -Hey! Doctor.
What, it's you.
What's up with that response? I looked for you for a while.
So, you have some business?
No, I don't have "business," but...
Why don't we have a toast as we listen to the Watch-Night bell?
♪♪ Together during the New Year's Eve
♪We stay up all night long♪
Whether you stay up or not, you do it by yourself!
-No more phone calls or visits for me. All right? -Yes, sir.
I have to hurry.
Ah, there's no time.
Then is it almost done?
I have to complete it by New Year's Day no matter what.
I can already see Atom's surprised look on his face.
♪Few more nights, then it's the New Year's Day♪
Tomboy Uran
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Atom.
Why do we say "Happy New Year," by the way?
Now, the next is the New Year's Day food.
We have to go pay respects after watching the video greetings card as we eat the New Year's Day food.
New Year's Day is a busy day, huh?
I studied it with the video book called "New Year's Day for Dummies"
published by the Ministry of Science.
Here, honey.
-Who would it be? -I'm getting.
Atom, Happy New Year!
Doctor Ochanomizu, Happy New Year!
-Ah, Doctor, you are here. -We were going to go say hi to you later.
I couldn't wait. I brought some new year's presents.
-Atom, this is the new year's present for you. -Huh? For me?
Wow! Amazing! It's a big new year's present.
-Open it. -Okay!
-It's a robot girl. -She's Uran. She's going to become your sister from today.
-What? My sister? -Is, is that true, Doctor?
Great!
I've always wanted a sibling.
I got much help from you last year after all.
Think of it as an award.
How nice, Atom.
She has a cute sleeping face.
She's my sister!
Here, wake up, Uran.
Even though she is bit mischievous
Innocent smile on her face
Uran
Everyone's calling
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
When you are around
We always have fun
She likes her brother Atom
And she likes songs and dreams
Uran is like an angel
Everyone's calling
Ouch, ouch. What a mischievous girl.
Uran, come here.
Let me introduce you to your family.
Uran, I'm your mother.
Umm... I'm your father. Nice to meet you. Congratulations.
Uran, what about greetings?
Father, mother, good bye.
You should say "Hello," Uran.
I didn't have enough time to train her, since I was in a hurry.
This is your brother, Atom.
Nice to meet you, Uran!
Nice to meet you, Atom.
Who calls one's brother by his name?
Atom's older than you. He's your older brother.
Ah.
Airplane!
-What a tomboy. -Let me take her outside.
-Wow, there are lots of people. -We are in downtown. Isn't it crowded?
That's a recent popular 3-D movie.
What are you doing? Gosh!
Ah! Don't do it, Uran. That's a holography.
Do you understand? Since you were just born, you don't know anything.
So you have to listen carefully to what I say.
I'm responsible for you as your brother.
Do you understand, Uran?
Uran?
Uran!
How is it? Does it look good on me?
Hey!
I got scolded from the New Year's Day thanks to you!
Is that so?
If you keep behaving that way, I'm not going to take you to the New Year's party.
What is that?
Classmates gather at Mr. Beard's house and play together.
I'll introduce you to friends, so you have to be polite.
I don't want to go to such a place.
Where are you going, Uran?
I don't want a brother who nags a lot.
Ah, it's dangerous!
What's wrong?
Somehow I feel happy.
Lady, are you alone?
Is there no one to be with you on this New Year's Day?
That must be very lonely.
Instead, let me give you an awesome New Year's present!
New Year's present?
Yes. Let's go to Dream Islands together.
There are lots of fun toys and games.
Here! Let's go!
Oh! Atom.
Teacher, Happy New Year.
Happy New Year. Everyone's waiting.
-Huh? Are you alone? -Pardon?
I heard it from Doctor Ochanomizu. You have a cute sister now?
Yes, well...
Hey, Atom. Don't hide it. Hurry and introduce her to me.
That's a bit...
You didn't bring her?
No...
What a fool!
How can you leave your sister who was just born?!
-A big brother shouldn't do that! -But...
No "but"s! Get Uran immediately!
If you don't bring Uran, I won't let you come in!
No matter how far away you are, brothers and sisters are...
♪The strong ties will never be broken♪
♪Facing each other♪
♪For 100 years and more♪
♪A mom and a baby hugging...♪ -What a nice tune!
-Huh? Where's Atom? -He went out a way earlier.
Being a big brother is a tough thing.
Look. That's the ship called Dream headed to Dream Islands.
-We are getting on a ship? -Of course.
You don't have to worry.
You can always come back if you want to.
-But I have to call my mom. -Me too.
Fun New Year's Day at Dream Islands!
Hammel, is the ship ready yet?
As you can see.
If we use the special sound wave from my flute,
it's a piece of cake to fool young robot's electronic brain.
Good job. Move it to the island right away.
To where in the world are we going?
If I don't go back, my mom would be worried.
Not yet? We are not even close to Dream Islands at all.
You can see now. That's Dream Islands.
In that island, you guys will be remodeled as slave robots.
Atom, haven't you found Uran yet?
I've looked for her but...
Is that so? As expected, it's the robot traffickers, then.
What are robot traffickers?
It's an international syndicate that kidnaps child robots
and sells after remodeling them as slave robots.
Robot UNESCO once warned...
-Then Uran too... -Hmm.
Atom! Uran's in danger!
Find her on your own. She's your precious sister.
Yes, sir!
They have been stocked.
Hmm, start sorting them right away.
There are orders from all over the world and space asking for cheap robots they can use and throw away.
I want to go home.
Daddy, Mommy!
Crying won't do it.
What are you going to do with us?
Shut up and go into that room!
Electronic brain: IQ 160. Power: 5,000 horsepower.
Locomotion ability: Class C. No special power. For simple labors.
Good, remodel it for Saturn development.
Classified as A-5.
Next!
Service robots, classified as C-3.
Office work robots, classified as B-2.
Next!
What are you doing?
Don't! Gosh!
I'm strong, huh?
Electronic brain: IQ 150. Power: 50,000 horsepower.
Wow, this one's good.
Good, this one could sell expensively if we remodel it right.
Classified as S.
I don't see her no matter how much I look for her.
Where in the world did Uran go?
Now the only place left is the ocean...
I'm going to find you for sure, Uran!
I want to go home!
Hey, what's wrong?
Be quiet!
What's wrong?
That's the switch.
Let's all run away.
But would it be okay?
It's all right.
I'm scared.
Then are you going to be sold away to somewhere far away?
Look at Uran. She doesn't cry. Let's go!
Ah, stop.
-There's infrared detector. -I don't see anything.
My dad is a bank guard robot.
So my eyes are fit for that just like my dad's.
Here. Be careful.
Wow. You have an unique ability.
Something's there. That's odd. There should be no islands near here.
Flying object approaching.
Put up disguising shield like always.
Artificial island, go below the water surface.
Disguising shield up!
Huh? That's odd. I saw an island shadow around here for sure...
Ah! That's my brother.
When did you guys...!
Brother!
-Here! -I just heard something.
That's odd. Am I just making things up?
Get them!
Brother! Over here!
I don't see anything...
You won't be able to escape this island.
Here! Go back quietly!
No! I don't like you! Gosh!
Stupid kid.
It's to set an example! Make her into scrap metal!
Brother, help me.
This is...
Uran, I'm coming!
Brother!
Uran! It's okay now.
What is this? Go away!
You want to fight?
Good work! Yeah! There! Get rid of him!
-Uran! Run with other kids. -Okay!
You guys, I won't let you go!
What is this!
Take this!
Ah, that's the power house of this artificial island.
-Help! -Help me!
-How is it? He's strong. -Wow.
Of course. He's my brother.
Uran.
Brother!
Atom, good job.
-First achievement of this year. -It's nothing...
Huh? Doctor, do robots blush too?
Atom has such device.
Looks like he has become Uran's real brother.
-Where is Uran? -She went to see the kite-flying contest.
Help!
Looks like she's going to make you go through some more sufferings, Atom.
Pardon? Yeah...
Brother!
Racing driver Robio
fell in love with Robiet, sister of his rival Chebolt.
Stop fighting. Poor them!
Next on Astro Boy. "Robio and Robiet." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Robio and Robiet"
Even though she is bit mischievous
Innocent smile on her face
Uran
Everyone's calling
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
Uran
When you are around
We always have fun
She likes her brother Atom
And she likes songs and dreams
Uran is like an angel
Everyone's calling