Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Minister, I have a bad feeling about this. If this kind of robot gets built,
it's like having the devil's child.
This is not the devil's child.
They found out that I made you.
Now I can't stay in this Ministry anymore.
Tobio, let's go to America together.
You will be free as well if we go to the States.
Yes, Dad.
Atom vs. Atlas
East-northeast, there's a fog 400-nautical miles away.
It's moving slightly toward the South.
There are icebergs from Ohotsuku around there.
The fog must have been from that.
Passengers, dinner preparations have been completed.
Please come to the dining area.
What have you done, Tobio?
The cover is open.
You broke the tap. Hurry and stop it!
It's hot! Oh! It's boiling hot!
I can't believe this. I'm soaking wet.
Tobio, how many things in this room do you think you've broken so far?
12!
Correct!
Listen carefully, this Ship Toritonic has a rule to not have robot passengers aboard.
And yet I have you here, through special measures.
Ah, shoot!
Tobio!
I've told you enough. I'm fed up with you.
I'm sorry...
Don't make a move anymore from here!
I'm going to go and have dinner by myself.
Hello, Doctor.
Hello,
Where's your son?
Umm... Well... He's still in the room.
I'd like to have dinner with him.
Oh.
Tobio, come here. Let's go to the dining room.
Ok!
Go do that one, got it?
You fool! Who burns the payload?
Steal valuable stuff first and then handle other stuff!
I've taught you many times already, you stupid!
You see, Atlas? Look at this carefully.
This is called money; it's the most important thing in the world.
If you have this, you can do anything.
I'm trying to raise you as a mature villain because
the goal is to get your hands on this treasure.
Next training!
Now you are going to attack that market.
There will be a lot of cash. Bring all of it.
Ro...Robbery!
You...You are... You are a robot!
I'm human, Mister.
Idiot! These are receipts!
Can't you even distinguish between money and receipts? Idiot!
It's done for today. Study harder!
Did you get scolded again?
Shut up!
Come here, I'll wash you up.
But what did dad say?
That I'm a stupid fool.
That I can never become a human being!
That's right, you are not human. You are a robot.
Dad told me that if robots keep making mistakes like I do,
they will all get disassembled.
He told me he would forgive me because I'm at the level of human beings.
Atlas, what you are doing is weird!
I don't know what to say, but it's scary. Stop it.
It makes me sad to see you breaking and attacking living things.
I must get trained by dad, though.
If I don't, he told me I cannot be human.
Master's calling. Let's hurry.
Can we talk again tonight?
Hu hu, but in secret.
It's whiskey.
Yes, Master.
You are saying that it's at the level of a human being because it has the Omega factor?
It only makes mistakes!
Whatever, screw that Omega factor or whatever!
Are you trying to find fault with my Omega factor, Skunk?
Baron, you told me that if you install that,
then the robots would obtain perfect human emotions!
That's irresponsible.
You can't even distinguish. That proves that it's like a human being.
Only living things could attack or kill other human beings.
It's an impossible thing for a robot to do.
That's the effect of the Omega factor. Do you understand?
It's resembling human at a hair-raising speed already.
It's resembling especially you!
That one is not on the same level as that kind of robots!
Is it delicious?
Yes!
Is this your first time in the U.S.?
Stop shutting your mouth and answer, Tobio.
It's my first time.
Uh-oh, you are a robot, right?
Y..Yes... In fact...
I thought it was your son! It's really well-made.
It's my first time having dinner with a robot!
-Robot? -Who brought it aboard?
You are not supposed to eat peels. Eat only the fruit; spit it out.
Ah, I'm sorry. I'm really...
Stop it!
Okay!
Get out!
Dad, I'm sorry!
You are not my son! Don't call me your dad!
You are a robot!
Get out!
You are not my son! Don't call me your dad!
You are a robot!
Hey, kid,
Yes?
I saw all of it. It's not your fault.
His way of teaching was bad.
Dad is always... I'm not a kid anymore...
I see, poor thing. You got abandoned by your parents.
Abandoned?
Yes, you got abandoned. So you are free now.
You can go to places you like.
Really?
But I don't know where to go.
That's a problem.
Then, would you like to go to the place where I am at?
Huh?
I'm a leader of a circus group.
A robot circus!
If you come to our group, you would be a hero!
Other collegues are surely going to be happy to have you.
What do you think? If you feel like it, come visit my room.
We can write a contract.
Con...tract?
Yes, it's a certificate that you and I are going to become a family.
Kid, can you write letters?
Good, good. Come, if you'd like.
Robot Circus
♬Tan tan tan
♬♬Tan tan tan
Atlas, since you are strong, you are not supposed to attack weaker ones.
Why not?
That's called being a gentleman.
What's a gentleman?
I'm a woman, and you are a man. It applies even to robots.
Mom must be a woman, right?
Yes...
Livian, would you be my mom?
Me?
Yes. It's scary to have only my dad.
I feel like I can't do this by myself.
If you are with me, I feel happy.
Poor Atlas!
You!
Staying in this place.
Stop wasting your energy with that slave robot!
Work!
I repeat,
There are gold bars worth of 50 million dollars under the bottom of Ship Toritonic.
I'm going to sink that ship.
Your mission is to go under that sunken ship and take those gold bars out.
This ship is in this ocean current now.
I'm going to explode an iceberg in the upper region and sink that ship.
I got it, boss.
Captain, there's something on the left side.
It's approaching!
It must be some ice.
There's an ice field coming from the left side.
Look!
There are so many!
What is this?
Captain, it's approaching with the current!
What in the world is happening?
Turn right, with full-speed.
Kid, sign this document.
Then you can be the happiest kid in the world.
"With no year limit and no payment, it will be possessed as an asset..."
What does this mean?
Well, for example... A kid doesn't have to worry about it.
Hurry and sign this!
Good, good boy, good...
Now it's done.
You are mine. No matter what others say, you are mine!
Ouch!
You stupid robot!
Passengers, please put on a life vest.
What's happening?
It's an emergency! An iceberg!
Iceberg?
All right, go!
A huge iceberg is approaching!
Avoid! Hurry!
Left 5 degrees!
Don't escape on your own! Please follow the directions!
Tobio! Where are you? Answer me!
♬♬
Something's breaking the iceberg!
An angel saved us!
It's a miracle!
Right now! Get out of this current!
Who are you?
I'm Tobio
I'm Atlas.
Nice to meet you!
Shut up! You are inturrupting me!
I was going to steal the money when that ship got sunken.
You made me work in vain under the ocean!
Stop it!
You totally interrupted me.
Why did you do such thing!
I don't know...
Who told you to do it?
You... We've met each other somewhere, right?
There's nothing about you in my memory folder.
But I've seen you for sure.
I know you as well. I don't know why, but...
Stop bragging!
Ah! What are you doing!
I can't let you go like this. I'm going to destroy you.
Learn!
You escaped.
Wait!
I'm going to smash your arms!
How is it? You must have felt it, huh?
If I only had energy...
I'm going to cut your throat!
Atlas, you shouldn't attack weaker ones. You are a man, right?
Be ready to fight me next time!
Thank you...
Tobio, where are you!
Dad!
Where have you been?
Here, come here!
Dad...
You made me look for you!
Stay inside here!
Tobio!
Is Tobio not here?
Dad...
Tobio, I'm sorry. You are my child!
Da..Dad... I'm here... Help me...
Tobio,Tobio, Where are you?
Tobio, Tobio...
Please forgive me. I was a fool.
If he cannot be found after all this search, is he under the ocean? Or...
Ah... I was being foolish. Tobio!
Huh? Livian, I won't forgive!
That's an expensive...
What a stupid robot!
I'm going to disassemble you!
So you would look like monsters up there! In the ugliest form in the world!
Please forgive me!
Forgive you? You are a robot!
I'm the real parent! It's my call to decide! Come here!
Livian?
Livian, where are you?
Livian!
Yes?
You! When did you come back?
Livian!
I've told you that you cannot come into this room.
Livian... What did you do that?
I disassembled it because it did stupid things.
What are you doing?
Atlas became weird.
What kind of guy it is! It cannot be fought back anymore.
Atlas...
Livian...
You and I are together forever...
Next on Astro Boy
A splendid robot circus
Robot elephant's pyramid
Celebrity Tornedo's performance.
The audience sends a big applause for such performance.
However, I keep doing silly things... Hamegg always makes scary faces.
I don't want to be in this circus anymore...
However, Coach Cassy encourages me.
But one day, there's a big trouble in the circus group!
Next Astro Boy episode!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together