Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Greenland Nook
Welcome to this end of the North.
Dr.Ochanomizu.
Dr.Grude. I brought Atom like you asked; what do you need with him?
Please listen to this dying old man's will.
What are you talking about!
That's right, Dr.Grude.
Your paper on the influence of cosmic radio emission on glaciers was very interesting.
Further study will be...
I don't have time to talk about that now.
I'm a descendant of the Vikings.
The Vikings?
The Vikings are of the Northern Germanic race
who used to agitate entire Europe from the 8th to 11th century.
Their energy and courage are famous historically.
A thousand years ago from now, Erik, the king of the Vikings,
reached this Greenland and served Odin the God.
It seems like he buried gold with Odin's body.
Gold?
During World War II, the Nazis tried to get that gold,
but they couldn't find it.
I don't need such gold, but I'd like to find my ancestor's ruins...
In other words, his holy land...
-Dr.Ochanomizu, -Yes?
My colleague is coming tomorrow.
I told him about you guys. Please help us.
In order to find that holy land locked up in snow and ice,
I need your help, Atom.
Dr.Grude!
Doctor! Dr.Grude!
The Devil's Place of Odin
Hey, a strange ship is approaching.
-My, it's the Vikings' ship! -Huh?
-Vikings? -Vikings!
Lower the sail!
Stop rowing!
Anchor complete!
Crew members are also dressed up like the Vikings.
What's wrong?
Are you Dr.Ochanomizu and Atom?
That's right.
I'm Captain Crowd of this ship Viking.
I came here to pick you up after hearing from Dr.Grude.
I see.
What a great ship.
Let's go to Odin's holy land.
Great engine.
I wondered if it was moving only with a sail and paddles.
There are times when we only use the sail.
However, in order to overcome the fierce North Sea, we need an engine.
-Saint Elmo's fire! -It's Saint Elmo's fire.
But it's odd for them to appear in groups.
Maybe they are the envoys of the Grim Reaper.
King Erik said, "Anyone who intrudes this holy land
will be cursed with death."
Dr.Grude told me to investigate these three places thoroughly.
The first one is this tundra's...
Avalanche!
-Atom! -Okay!
I was surprised.
What is it?
-Snowman? -You saw it.
Captain Crowd, who in the world was it?
Please forget what you saw.
And don't ever enter this place again.
Long time ago, the Vikings often used to land on this tundra area.
The area under this cliff is the first place. Atom, please take a look.
Okay!
Be careful, Atom!
I'm all right!
Frozen!
Everything's frozen.
What is that?
What? Old Norse is written on a slate?
That's right!
So what did it say?
That gold is in the North and that only Grara will be able to find it.
Grara? What is that?
I need more details. Let's move to the second location!
There are traces of the Nazis.
This is the second location...
Ah! There is a slate!
Something dangerous might happen if we get closer.
-Atom, please magnify and read it. -All right!
It's the same old Norse.
"Gold is in the West from here, and only Grara will be able to find it."
Grara again.
Move! Move away!
What are you doing? Stop it!
"Gold is in the Southeast where the river is from,
and only Grara will be able to find it."
There's no such thing as river.
I've looked from above, and there's no river nearby.
There must have been one a long time ago. It must have frozen.
-Captain, do you have an old map? -Yes, I do.
It's this one.
This is it! It's the Izuri River.
Izuri River?
Even if we were to trace it back, where in the world is it?
North from the first location. West from the second location.
This overlapping location would be our destination.
Doctor, there is a description about Grara this time.
What?
Odin the God's holy descendant.
The one chosen to guard gold.
That is?
Dad!
Javi!
Let's finish the fight tonight.
As you wish.
I have no business with you now. Go to your father!
-That's Javi. -Javi.
Dad!
I would have responded to fight you even if you didn't hold Javi hostage!
You learn to doubt people in a civilized society.
Crowd, I have your eyes, arms, legs.
This is the time to give up!
Is that the only thing you want to say? Come!
Dad, please win.
In case of emergency, I'm going to fight!
Wait!
Stop killing each other!
Atom, don't come!
What is that?
Don't interrupt!
This is not a simple fight. It's a holy duel!
We are descendants of the Vikings
who settled here after following King Erik.
Zakro here is the king of the Vikings of this land.
I also have the right of succession.
That's why we've been fighting until now.
There shouldn't be two chosen ones of Odin the God!
We are fighting to determine the only chosen one!
If you understood, then move!
How is this!
What about this!
Sir Zakro is going to win for sure.
-Sir Zakro. -Zakro.
I'm not going to miss it! Be ready!
-Sir Zakro! -Dad!
Dad!
Atom, don't make such faces.
I took this throne with a just duel, following custom.
It's a stupid custom.
Shut up! Don't you ever say that again.
Odin's custom is everything we the Vikings have.
Crowd, you can take the name of Grara from now on.
Zakro, you are a true warrior who fought well.
Javi, you must be happy to have such great dad.
Javi, be strong. And some other day...
Grara, I see.
Grara means the chosen king.
Odin!
I'm the new Grara. Are you ready to follow me?
I'm heading to the Holy North of Odin.
I'm going to take one attendant.
I'm coming!
Javi, you are still a kid.
But I volunteered first. Take me according to custom!
All right, then!
Odin!
Odin! Odin!
Only I, Grara, can enter the holy land.
According to the map, there should be a sulfur spring nearby.
What's a sulfur spring?
It was dangerous.
This is a sulfur spring.
Near fumaroles, such sulfur spring
and intermittent spring get created very often.
It's really hot, so be careful.
Aurora is lighting our way ahead.
-I've never seen such thing. -It's like it's calling us.
It's magical...
Doctor!
Atom!
Atom! Are you all right?
Hey! Answer!
Javi!
Javi, you can do it.
Hold on.
Hold on to my leg.
Hey! Don't slack off! Hurry!
How dare you.
Oh, you were safe.
Javi and I were worried.
-Beautiful... -It's dazzling.
Useless. Let's hurry our way.
-The holy land should be around here. -Let's go by that foot of the mountain.
Remains of a ship.
So the Viking ship was here a long time ago.
-Then, is this the ship that King Erik was aboard? -No. This is too small.
Dr.Ochanomizu. Let's go further.
We are finally here at the holy land.
This must be the ship that King Erik was aboard.
Saint Elmo's fire!
You can't intrude into this place.
It's the holy land.
I feel like humans are not allowed to enter.
What are you talking about? I'm going in!
-No! I'll go first. -Atom.
I'm not human. I'm a robot!
So you don't need to worry.
All right! Go ahead!
But if you lay your hand on Odin's body or gold, I won't forgive you.
I know.
What?
Are you doubting Atom?
I'm just like this. Don't worry too much.
Atom.
Atom!
-I'll go by myself from this point on. -But...
Only Grara will be admitted!
Atom! Atom!
Atom.
What is this?
Is this the gold King Erik brought?
I'm a space probe called Odin, flown from a planet thousand years ago.
Space probe Odin?
I learned the Earth's language from this robot.
When I arrived on the Earth, I was broken and couldn't move.
I was found by a person,
but they didn't have civilization and didn't know how to fix me.
Besides, they started calling me God and worshiping me.
So that's Odin the God?
That's right. I just met this robot.
If you disassemble this and use its components, I'll be able to get out of here!
The Vikings' holy body.
Gold. Holy land.
It was a space probe from some planet!
Odin, if you want to get a repair, I'll take you anywhere!
Let scientists fix you!
No. I won't allow other people to fix me.
I'm going to fix myself. That's our rule.
How ridiculous.
I've waited for thousand years for this day to come.
What are you doing?
Give me that robot back!
Doctor, Atom!
Atom!
The circuit went wrong.
Beautiful.
Captain Crowd!
I won't forgive you! I won't!
Little bit more...
Crowd! What happened on the ship?
Javi, you can use me now.
Crowd...
-Here, to the rock. -Leave me and run.
Doctor! Hide under the rock!
Now it's done.
-It should be fixed now... -Watch out!
What is that?
-That's what gold was. -What?
Captain Crowd got hurt trying to save me from that monster!
All right, take a look at this!
Where has Atom gone to?
Captain Crowd. Wake up!
Atom's back.
I've waited... Thousand years...
Dr.Ochanomizu! It's all fine now!
Oh, Atom.
Good job, Atom.
Crowd met his death as a Viking.
I'm going to be a great warrior like my dad and Crowd.
Captain Crowd.
Sail! Sound a gong!
Mexico is called the Egypt of Central America.
The pyramid is an important key to solving the mystery of Mayan Civilization.
There are mysterious people in the excavation team of Mushu Ampair,
but I as well participated in as a bodyguard.
I'll be fighting with robot sphinx.
But what we saw inside the pyramid was...
Next on Astro Boy, "Rage of the Sphinx"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together