Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Is it complete!
Yes.
I'm going to call you Pluto. Look!
There are seven strongest robots in the world.
Montblanc of Switzerland.
Montblanc is the best robot in Switzerland.
He's a mountain guide robot, but he's the strongest in power.
Next, Atom of Japan.
Atom's small, but he has seven powers
and he has a strong sense of justice.
Next, Norse the 2nd of Scotland.
A noble scientist made him.
Norse the 2nd has a high sense of pride and has the strongest destructive power.
Next, Turkey's Blande.
Turkey's robot king Blande
is a strong one that is stronger than his friend, Montblanc.
His martial arts is the best in the world.
Next, Gezihit of Germany.
It's Germany's masterpiece, a robot detective Gezihit.
Next, Hercules of Greece.
Like its name, it is after a hero in Greek mythology.
It is a warrior that with chivalry.
The last one is Epsilon of Australia.
It's a kind robot that works in orphanage, but you shouldn't be fooled.
It's the best in the world when it comes to momentary battles.
It has the swiftest techniques.
Do you understand, Pluto? You have to get rid of these robots one by one.
When you finish all of them, Pluto, you will!
You will be the champion of all robots as the biggest robot on the Earth!
The Greatest Robot In The World (Part One)
Do you have any business?
Are you the best robot in Switzerland, a mountain guide robot with 100,000 horsepower, Montblanc?
It's not 100,000 horsepower. It's 135,000 horsepower.
What are you doing.
One.
Next one is Japan's 100,000-horsepower robot Atom.
Atom went out with friends to hang out.
-Where did he go? -I don't know...
Then please tell him when he comes back.
If this giant robot called Pluto comes here,
tell him not to deal with him!
Pluto?
He's the one that destroyed Switzerland's special robot Montblanc with no mercy.
Ah, I saw it on TV. What would that be?
I don't know anything, but I have a bad feeling.
Is that robot strong?
I think it has at least 150,000 horsepower.
-But Atom's stronger! -Uran.
Uran, Atom wasn't born to show his strength off.
All right? Tell Atom not to deal with him.
Please!
Here you are.
-What is it? -It's Uran.
Uran, get down! You tomboy!
I'm going to spank you.
Honey, that's not Uran.
-Is Atom there? -What are you?
Who are you?
I'm Pluto. Where's Atom?
Atom's not here!
Don't lie. Give me Atom.
Here I am!
I'm Atom!
You are not Atom.
I'm Atom! Would you like to see my 100,000 horsepower?
I don't deal with the ones that I'm not ordered to deal with.
-I'm telling you I'm Atom! -Stop it!
Gosh, I'm annoyed.
If you are the real one, you must have seven powers.
You fake one. Why would you do this?
Confess!
-Wait. -What are you doing to Uran!
Uran?
Yes, Atom's sister.
Atom's sister?
Atom had a sister like you?
You shouldn't stare at girls like that.
What a funny girl.
What? You have a weird horn!
You are way behind Atom.
-How dare you. -Dare me if you can.
Why did you call yourself Atom?
Atom wouldn't deal with someone like you!
What?
-Atom won't fight you! -Why not?
Umm... Because Doctor Ochanomizu told him not to.
I don't care about that. All right, then. Uran is my hostage.
Tell Atom to come by himself if he wants to get Uran back.
I'm going to Scotland now.
Give Uran back!
Dad! Mom! Police officer! Kidnapper!
Shut up!
Uran.
Huh? Uran?
That Pluto guy went to Scotland?
Yes, that's right.
I'll go rescue her!
But Doctor Ochanomizu told you not to deal with...
Master, the radar caught
a giant robot approaching from 30km South.
It must be your friend.
No. It seems like my enemy.
Enemy?
You know that a super robot in Switzerland called Montblanc was destroyed, right?
That Pluto or something was the one that destroyed...
That Pluto is coming?
Yes. To fight me and destroy me.
What in the world is that robot?
I don't know.
How dare!
Norse the 2nd, Scottish pride,
let him see your power!
-For our honor. -Stand against it.
And destroy it, and bring its head!
I'll disassemble and investigate it.
I'm Pluto.
I have no grudge against you, but my master has ordered me to destroy you.
I also have an order to defeat you.
Get lost!
I'm sorry it's the opposite way.
How great. But the match begins now.
I'll disassemble you down to screws!
Two are done now.
Five more, then Pluto will be the strongest in the world.
Atom, welcome.
You are Pluto, right? Where's Uran? Give my sister back!
She's inside my chest. If you want to get her back, you should defeat me.
All right. I'm coming!
Hold on.
Kid, let me take care of this one.
Who are you?
I'm Turkey's robot king Blande.
I'm here to revenge for my friend Montblanc.
Kid, you should stay back!
Don't be in such a hurry, Blande. I'll take care of you first, as you wished.
But before that...
Ah! Uran!
She might be broken if he fights such a big one.
Uran, are you all right?
Atom.
Are you going to run away, Blande?
I'm scared...!
Pluto.
Blande?
He's now a scrap metal. But he was a formidable opponent.
Atom, would you press the switch on my chest?
Then, the master will come. If he doesn't, I will be destroyed.
My hands are completely broken, so I can't press the button.
Please.
Thank you, Atom. The next one is you.
Why do you want to fight me?
Because I was made to fight.
I don't want meaningless fights!
No, you will get to fight for sure.
Doctor Abura.
I gave you that much money to make Pluto,
and now what is this?
I didn't order for such trash!
Stupid!
Do you understand? I asked you to make the biggest and strongest robot in the world!
The best in the world means!
It cannot be defeated nor destroyed!
If it gets defeated, I'd rather destroy it!
That's right. Let anyone that defeats Pluto
go to hell with Pluto!
I thought you'd say that,
so I set up a self-destruction device.
If it gets broken, it will explode.
What? Say things like that ahead of time!
That sure is a good one that goes along with him.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a robot detective from Germany, Gezihit.
-I'm Atom. -Wow, his entire body is made of gold.
It's a special alloy called zeronium.
I have a favor to ask you about Pluto.
Pluto?
I just talked with Doctor Ochanomizu.
Starting with Montblanc,
Pluto destroyed three robots including Norse the 2nd and Blande.
We cannot let such dangerous robot be active.
I'm going to arrest him for sure for the honor of robots.
So Atom, if you find Pluto, please call me immediately.
All right!
According to Doctor Ochanomizu's analysis, Pluto seems to have million horsepower.
A million horsepower?
You don't need to worry. I'm going to arrest him for sure.
Someone must be here. Excuse me.
Pluto!
Are you Gezihit.
You are under arrest.
Stupid. That kind of warrant is of no use to me.
I'm going to catch you with the honor of German robots.
My body is made of zeronium.
Infrared rays or magnetic force won't work for me!
Gosh!
It all bounces off.
It's an electromagnetic blocking beam.
He doesn't have that beam on his feet. All right!
I told you it wouldn't work on me!
You.
Germany's best robot detective Gezihit
was found destroyed in front of Jungbremen's house.
It's Pluto again.
Uran, you almost ended up like that.
With this, I, too, like Gezihit...
Let me ask Doctor Ochanomizu to make me a million horsepower one.
Huh? Doctor is calculating something.
It's here. For sure.
Doctor Ochanomizu.
Now three more, then Pluto will be the robot champion in the world.
That's right.
Is this the secret lab for controlling the monster robot Pluto?
-Welcome, Doctor Ochanomizu. -How do you know my name?
If someone were to discover this place,
there would be no one but you, Doctor.
I caught something on my radar, so I thought you were here.
Then we could talk faster. Hand over the robot murderer Pluto!
What kind of business must the doctor have in that castle?
It's Pluto!
It's Pluto's hideout?
Here! Bring Pluto here now!
What are you talking about, after visiting so suddenly?
Shut up! There is no set time and place for justice!
Give Pluto!
If you insist...
Let me introduce. This is Pluto.
Doctor Ochanomizu, I am
Chochichochi Ababa the 3rd who used to be
the king of Sultan in arabic region.
I've heard of it.
You spent tons of money enjoying luxurious things
and was kicked out of the country for that!
Ah, whatever you please.
But I've been admiring to become the king of the world.
But since it's impossible, you tried to make the world's best robot?
Wow, you are quick to understand.
No way! You cannot let robots fight for that kind of foolish desire!
Abura!
I have a feeling that Atom's with them together.
I see. It's a bait.
Ah, it hurts.
Huh? What is this sound?
Alligator!
What are you going to do with me?
Help!
It's the voice of Doctor Ochanomizu!
Ah, it doesn't taste good.
Let me go!
Atom,
Doctor this alligator is a robot. But Atom, how did you get here?
I have a favor to ask you. Make me into million horsepower one.
What?
If I have a million horsepower, I wouldn't lose to Pluto.
Do you understand, Atom? If being the strongest is important,
then wrestlers would be the happiest one in the world.
But that's not how it is.
Even if you only have 100,000 horsepower, you can save the world by using it well.
It's Pluto!
Atom.
Here, Atom. Fight with Pluto.
No! Atom. Your strength isn't for such lame things.
Stop talking nonsense!
My precious nose!
How dare you...!
Wait! Both of you, go fight outside.
All right. I'll go anywhere.
But don't touch Doctor Ochanomizu!
I swear to God.
Atom,
Atom, I want to ask you something. How's Uran?
Why would you ask that?
It's nothing.
I just thought Uran would be sad if you get destroyed.
Hurry!
All right!
Pluto! That's a rock! Be clear!
Gosh!
Another horn!
Good job, Pluto! Make him into a powder!
Pluto continues the battle.
Next one is the 400,000-horsepower robot Hercules of Greece.
Pluto goes over to the kind robot Epsilon.
How sad it is for kids to not have Epsilon!
Stop it, Pluto!
All right, let's fight in Mount Arso.
Next on Astro Boy, "The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part Two)." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Biggest Robot on Earth (Part Two)"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together