Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Astro Boy
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Astro Boy
Atom vs. Atlas V: The Gothem Gang
No. Do you understand? Listen carefully.
Turn around three times, clap your hands, bow down and do a handstand!
That's not right. It's not about wagging your tail.
Look at me!
Like this!
You have to do this.
Uran!
But this dog is stupid.
You are going to get him killed. Jump cannot do things like that.
But even Uran can do it!
Robots are different from living things!
How come? Robots even have eyes and mouth!
Jump can only do things like standing on two legs and waiting.
You really can't do anything. Learn the handstand at least!
Do you understand? Until you learn how to do it, I'm not going to let you in the house!
Jump,
Jump, I'll cut you some slack. Come in.
Seriously!
Uran! Uran, don't do that!
-If you hit him that strongly, it will hurt! -But...
Look here.
I don't like Jump. Throw him away!
That's too pitiful.
-What's being pitiful? -It's being miserable.
Then, who's more miserable? Me, or Jump?
Jump is the dog I, Tobio, used to adore.
After Tobio died,
Jump didn't used to tag along with me who came in place of Tobio.
And he finally became friends with me after a long period of time.
That's not Uran's business.
Right, you are a guard dog, right? Then pull your guard duty at night.
Okay? Please, Jump.
What is this animal?
Should we step on it?
Wait.
We'll play with it for a while.
Honey?
Stop that habit of reading newspapers while you charge your morning energy.
But doesn't every human dad do this?
There are things you should learn from human and things you shouldn't.
Mom, Jump's gone.
The kennel is completely smashed, too.
Uran, are you not going to say good-morning?
But it's not the right time for such...
Once you wake up in the morning, you should greet people.
Good mor?
Say it right.
...ning.
Mom, good morning.
There is this huge footstep on the yard.
Something must have happened last night.
Brother? You should say good-morning!
There is an article. "The Motor Gang Robots Conquers the Town"
The motor gang robots?
It seems like a group of 20-30 of them ride motorcycles at nights
hitting and breaking everything they see.
They call themselves Vikings.
They are robots of unknown address; it's not even certain where they were produced.
They can only work to break stuff.
-Why can't we catch them? -Well, they seem to hide in the mountains.
Okay.
Hello.
Last night, it flew into our apartment window all of a sudden.
Jump...!
He's hugely hurt.
The motor gang robots must have done this.
It's scary.
All of this was assaulted by the motor gang robots?
Poor Jump. Would he be able to live?
Doctor will cure him for sure.
I can't stand it anymore! I'm going to finish them next time I see them!
-You shouldn't, Atom. -Why not?
The motor gang robots are bullies, right?
If you have fights with them, that would make you look like you are one of them.
But if we just let them go, they will commit more serious crimes.
-Revenge for Jump! -No!
Atom, you've always moved with the permission of Dr. Ochanomizu, right?
...Yes.
I called the Department of Science a minute ago.
They said that Dr. Ochanomizu is on a business trip abroad for a while.
Man!
Hello? Pet Robot Center? Can I get a pet robot?
A guard dog one. I'm going to prepare for those motor gangs.
However, there are neighbors around here, so I want one that doesn't bite everyone.
Also, I want one that doesn't bark loudly
but sings with a beautiful voice.
Also, I want one that cleans its house itself and washes its own clothes.
Honey?
We are not hiring a housekeeper.
Oh, is there a perfect one for those?
That's great. Get me that.
Uran!
Enough with playing with dog!
Why don't you go to hospital and have a look on Jump?
This one's way better than Jump.
He dances well and he can even play cards.
It's already night.
You should go back to a guard dog post. Go back to your house!
You guys...!
Guys!
It's dangerous. It's a chopper from the press.
Run!
Freeze!
Don't show me a light!
Atom, what is this? The picture on this morning newspaper!
I'm sorry.
Atom, did you join the motor gang robots?
I didn't do anything bad! It's true.
You probably want to say that robots don't lie, right?
But until I get the full account, you are grounded!
-Don't go anywhere! -I'm going to Dr. Ochanomizu...
Shush!
He's on a trip.
-Do not even make a move. Understand? -Yes.
Gosh, robots always behave as they please.
Right, I must not move because I'm Atom.
If I am not Atom... If I were another robot...
Don't laugh. I'm being serious here.
Here, go ahead.
Fine, now it's done.
You look exactly like a dog, Atom.
-Can I go call mom? -No! It's a secret to mom and dad.
Then, I won't tell. Give me just a dollar.
What kind of a dog has money?
This stupid dog, it's not running away before us.
It's standing even more still.
It doesn't matter. Crush it!
This...!
This dog...
Hey, did you all see?
This dog is being rude.
No more cutting some slack on it!
Tear it down!
How is it!
It's a bomb.
For you!
How is it!
Dang it... Combination Gothem!
We are going, puppy.
Come!
That's right.
It's a footprint. He ran.
He's gone.
Hello, Uran. It's me.
Atom, where in the world are you? It's so late.
Dad... I'm in trouble.
Come back right now!
Yes! Um...Where's Uran?
Uran went to the vet's.
The vet's?
-Jump is dying. -Huh?
-He can't live? -It seems like it.
They called, so Uran went out running.
I'm sorry. I'll be back soon. Hold on for a little more.
Atom!
Jump, you cannot die!
Doctor, please insert some energy into Jump.
Honey, it would be too hard on him.
Living things are different from robots.
They cannot come back to life once they lose life.
Then make me another one again.
Don't you understand?
Living things aren't like robots. It can only live one life.
Life is that much precious.
Ah...I plead the god of robots.
Please listen to Uran. Give me my Jump back.
This...
This is Queen Livian who used to live with Atlas. What in the world...
Hey, this is going to be your grave.
I'm over now, but I'm going to take you down as well.
Melt!
It's hot!
This place will be filled with magma.
Fine, then...
Take it!
Those gangs were my men.
To make faithful warriors for me,
I kidnapped football player robot
and inserted omega factor into them.
But then they betrayed me.
They disobeyed me and rebelled.
They even kidnapped Livian and ran.
Atom, thank you for saving me. I'll take them.
It's because you inserted omega factor in them.
Shut up!
Omega factor is necessary for them to become perfect robots!
Then why wouldn't you put omega factor inside Livian?
The truth is,
that you think omega factor has a bad effect, right? Atlas?
I owe you one. I'll cure your injury.
It's fine. I can ask Dr. Ochanomizu.
We will come to a conclusion one day.
However, a debt is a debt. Tell me any of your wishes.
Can you really make anything?
-Of course. I'm like a god. -Then...
Can you make a pill for curing a dog?
What did you say?
Who are you!
Inject this.
He will surely get cured.
Are you a robot? What are you doing here?
That doesn't matter. Inject this. It's not too late.
Here.
Tell Atom that I don't owe him anymore.
Yay! It worked!
He's alive again.
Jump!
It's a mercy. It's a good thing.
Atom.
Look, Jump is back again!
That's good, Jump. I'll get cured soon, too.
There is a strange rumor around here.
The one that destroyed the motor gang robots turns out to be a dog.
This is a picture proving that.
Have you all heard about Black Jack?
He's the world's best doctor who succeeds with all kinds of surgery.
Doctor Black Jack and we
came to the 15th century world through time machine.
What awaited us there were wizards and monsters.
Doctor Black Jack, this will change the history.
Next on Astro Boy. Black Jack's Mission. Look forward to it!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together