Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Livian...
How can I...
I see. I was locked up in this ice by Atom...
Livian!
This is because you told Atom needless stuff.
Livian, I'm telling you that no matter how much
you oppose me, I'm going to carry my wills out.
Atlas!
And I'm never going to let you go.
Atom vs. Atlas VII: The Runaway Subway
-What a speed. -It's 180 kilometers per hour.
-180 kilometers per hour? -What, you didn't know that?
But is it all right for this to run so fast underground?
You don't need to worry.
The control center called UATS sends out orders
and computers in these tubes make decisions
to give out orders of GO or STOP to the subway
and to control the speed of the subway as well.
So there's no driver of this subway. Doctor Ochanomizu's team developed this.
Tamao, there are many subways in Tokyo,
but there is only one spot where the subway comes up the ground.
Do you know which station and line that is?
-Well... Where, where, where? -That is...
Point 512 of this X-17. Right before the last station.
Teacher! You cannot say that first!
It feels like flying!
-It was great. -It was amazing.
Thank you for riding with us.
This is the last station of X-17. Make sure you have all your belongings.
I'm going to get rid of Atom.
My plans have all been interrupted by Atom all along.
Well, to think about it, Livian,
you started defying me since Atom showed up.
I cannot take it anymore! I'm going to defeat Atom this time for sure.
I'm going to fight him fairly under the same condition. You don't have any problem, do you?
Atlas!
...So the transportation network of the city of Tokyo is at its peak
by reaching both underground and ground.
You! Shibukaki.
Are you not going to listen to your teacher?
Then the next is...
-Teacher! Atom's not here! -What?
-He was here just now. -Did he go to toilet?
Stupid! Why would Atom go to toilet?
-He must be loafing around since he was bored. -What?
Anyhow, wait here.
Atlas!
Atom! It's the same sword.
I made it to fight with you.
-Here, Atom! Take your sword! It's a duel!
-I don't want to! -What?
I don't want to fight!
-You coward. -Coward?
No matter what you say, I don't want to fight!
Even if you don't want to, I'm coming!
I'm coming for you!
He drew the sword.
Good work. But the game is over now.
Take it, Atom!
Atom, you are out of energy.
Teacher!
How's this, you fool!
You bad one. Take this!
Atom, don't fight this hack.
Leave him to me.
Don't interrupt me.
-Teacher! Are you all right? -You sure touched me well.
As long as I stand here, you won't be able to lay a hand on Atom.
Oldie, get out. You will get hurt.
Oldie? How dare you.
I'm in my beautiful forties. Let's have a fight...
Teacher!
This is nothing. I'm good at fencing...
Atom, there's a disturber. Let's postpone the fight.
All right, Atom? Listen! I'll be back in three days.
And I'm going to defeat you for sure!
Coward.
Come back!
Don't run away, Atom.
In three days? This is not a time for this.
Atom would be safe in the vault under the Ministry of Science.
But why is Atlas so obsessed with Atom?
That's why, Dr. Ochanomizu.
We really can't predict what he's going to do.
As his teacher, I thought Atom should never fight
such a guy!
Here's the vault.
Wow, it doesn't feel like we are 60 floors underground.
Here it is.
This vault contains confidential documents of the Ministry of Science.
-The blueprint of Atom is here as well. -My blueprint?
Do you understand, Atom?
You wouldn't like to hid, but be patient for three days. You have to stay still.
You have any problem?
No, but... Atlas called me a coward.
You don't need to be ashamed of that. You shouldn't fight such robot.
Am I not right, Doctor Ochanomizu?
Yes, you are right.
I won't mark you absent for classes, so don't worry.
Read books or something.
Now I feel relieved.
What are you doing? You haven't found Atom yet?
I've installed detectors in all places he might show up, but...
All right, keep looking.
Today's the third day.
That Beard and Doctor Ochanomizu must have hidden him for sure.
But where?
Why isn't Atom coming to school?
He is hiding deep down the underground.
-Deep down the underground? -Oops, I'm not supposed to say that.
What is it? You said you wanted to take the subway first.
Deep down the underground... Isn't Atom already on it?
No. Atom's in a state of emergency now.
What state of emergency?
Oops, I don't know. What was that?
Let's go.
-Take me, too! -Nope. The one who doesn't go to classes can't.
Shibukaki, you mean person. Pig, stupid!
What? You little...
Is that so? So Atom is deep down the underground.
Subway is complicated.
Don't get it wrong. We are going to take that X-17.
Then it would be at the 10th basement floor.
That's it! Hurry, hurry.
The first carriage is empty.
Wow, this is awesome.
We are at the station.
Oh my!
What a speed.
-I'm not kidding. -It just passed by the station!
What's happening? Why isn't UATS working?
-There's no manual brake. -It's completely automatic.
Then how am I supposed to stop it?
My! Tamao, do something!
This cannot be true. This cannot be happening.
But this is reality.
What should we do? The train and the machine themselves
have no problem at all.
It wouldn't be good if they had one!
It's going to crash!
Quickly release the first carriage!
Emergency evacuate everyone on X-17.
-It passed by again. -We have to get off this station, though.
It's now the third time passing by. What should we do, Kenichi?
That's the train ahead of us!
We are going to crash like this!
-Hurry and change the point! -Yes, sir!
-We are crashing! -Help!
Ah, it has joined the W-3 line.
-Is point moving on its own? -It seems like it.
Emergency evacuate people in all lines of the subway.
Ah... Wouldn't it be too late...
There is no way but to count on Atom now!
Atom, can you hear me?
The train has entered the S-6 line now.
Okay!
It seems like it's getting faster.
It's 200 kilometers per hour already.
It keeps speeding up!
-Why wouldn't it stop? -What's so great about UATS?
Ah! That's Atom.
-Atom! -We count on you!
-We are safe now. -Atom!
What's wrong, Atom?
-Atom! -Atom!
Atom, what are you doing?
It's weird. My energy is gone when I get closer to the subway.
What?
All right, this time for sure!
Atlas.
Atom, you won't be able to do it.
What?
That subway has the non-energy device on.
Non-energy device?
It absorbs all energy within one meter range.
Your 100,000 horse power and UATS energy as well.
What?
For what are you doing all this?
Isn't it obvious? I did this to bring you out!
What a coward!
You are a coward for hiding.
Atom, be ready!
Atlas, how can you think of such scary thing...
The train has entered the H-15 line.
Ah, there's a train coming from the front!
Go backward immediately!
I did, but the train is running at the speed of 300 kilometers per hour.
We will get caught up soon!
Did you hear that, Atom?
Yes, Doctor.
Please do something.
Atlas, get away!
If you want to go, then defeat me.
Stop!
Atom, wait!
We are crashing. Get away!
-Atom. -Atom!
The train has evacuated to the C-30 line.
Thank goodness.
Ah, the train is now in the K-45 line.
Oh, no. There is a train that hasn't evacuated yet.
If only I can stop this.
Take it, Atom!
Stop!
The train is back to its original X-17 line.
400 kilometers per hour?
If it keeps speeding up, it will be broken.
Look at that. It's a problem.
It's heading to the last station building!
How can I!
It's not like the station building can be moved.
Are you all right, Doctor?
It's over now.
That's right. If the evacuation of other trains is over, cut the power off.
Yes, sir!
It doesn't work! It doesn't stop.
What happened?
Even after cutting the power off, the train's not stopping!
Call the fire and police department. Dispatch them to the station building.
Yes, sir!
Hurry!
All right.
But would it work?
But this is the only way to save people's lives.
Atom! Atom! Listen carefully, Atom!
All right!
There are only 30 seconds left. We count on you!
Are you running away?
It's over now.
Atom.
Atom1
God,
we did it!
We are safe.
Atom did it.
We are safe!
-Atom, good job. -Thank you.
Livian, get away.
If you don't...
Atlas, let's go back to Crystal.
Livian, you...
Atlas, Crystal is your castle. I'm with you, too.
Atlas.
This is Africa's robot safari park.
There are tons of robot animals.
But a real elephant got shot by bad hunters.
Poor baby elephant Pura lost her mom.
Let's go back your family.
At that moment, a big elephant robot starts acting violently
and the safari park is turned upside down.
Next on Astro Boy, "The Little Elephant Pura." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Little Elephant Pura"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together