Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
You guys! Stop it!
Stop it!
-Atom, stop the two of them. -Yes, sir!
-Stop it, Shibukaki. -Shut up!
No! Gosh!
Hey! Kenichi, Shibukaki. What is the cause of this trouble, huh?
But Shibukaki keeps saying
that the winner of this year's Japan Grand Prix Race will be Chebolt!
There is no one who can beat Chebolt from Yani Motors.
Isn't that right, kids?
What? Robio from Izio Motors is way faster!
That's right!
Wh, what? Robio would lose at once.
-What? -Stop it!
Teacher! Who do you think will win?
Pardon? What... Me?
Hmm. Well. Robio's a great robot racing driver,
but Chebolt also has a great ability.
So, which one?
Make up your mind, Teacher!
Hmm... So you know,
The winning one will win and the losing one will lose...
Wow, what great weather today. Right, I have some laundry to do.
-Teacher's so mean. -Then, Atom.
Who do you think will win?
Yeah. Which side are you on?
I... don't know anything about that.
But I don't care who wins the car race.
No way.
Robio will definitely win.
-How come? -I'm with him.
What?
Look, my Robio bank.
My Robio paper holder...
my picture of Robio,
with authentic autograph.
So you're a big fan?
He talked to me. I'm going to watch his race tomorrow.
I'll take you with me.
Look, that's Robio.
How is he? Isn't he awesome?
Yeah, he's great.
But it must be dangerous to drive with a car like that.
I wonder it if it has a
collision prevention computer..
Wacing cars are not ordinary cars. You knows nothing.
Robio and Robiet
He broke the record of 10'04 per round. Good, Robio!
With this condition, he won't lose to Chebolt.
I'm going to make him cry this year.
Good job, Robio!
Today's test drive is over. Come up!
Yes, Father.
What a beautiful person.
-Excuse me. -Yes.
Where is the room for Yani racing team staff?
It's the last room after turning left.
Thank you.
-And... -Sorry?
You are...
-Ah, I'm... -Robiet!
What do you have?
You are Chebolt!
You are Robio.
-What do you have with my sister? -Sister? Then you are...
You are Mr. Robio?
Now that I think about it,
you tried to do something to my sister since you don't think you can win the race, huh?
No! I was just...!
Don't do that. I only came here to call you guys upon dad's request.
Step back, Robiet!
I'll have to see how great this "Hope of Izio" is.
I'll have to have a fight.
What's wrong, Robio?
Brother.
You guys are the fool brothers of Yani!
That would be you.
What? You want to fight?
Stop it!
Shut up! You stay still.
Brother!
Let me introduce Robio to you, too. He's super handsome.
Robio, it's me who you should fight.
Ah, stop it. Don't do that, Chebolt.
Stop it!
Who are you?
I'm Atom. Robots shouldn't fight each other.
I don't care who you are. Step back if you don't want to get hurt.
Stop it, Ox.
I'll finish the rest of this fight during the race.
Ox, Mosquito, Robiet, let's go.
I'm really sorry.
Robiet.
Mr. Robio, step on it like you are having a race.
No, Uran. We are not in a race now.
It's boring.
Atom, I'm sorry about today.
I'm sorry I got you into the fight.
No problem. But why do robots from the Yanis
and the Izios don't like each other so much?
That is...
It was Doctor Haruzo Izio, Japan's top car engineer,
who made me born into this world.
I had brothers called Lard and Drill.
One day, we were having a walk.
Drill.
Brother!
Drill, what are you...
If we don't do it, then they will do this to us.
Robio, since you were just born, you wouldn't know about this,
but these are the enemy of our family.
The enemy of our family?
We have an unique characteristic.
We become aggressive when we encounter certain type of robots.
-Why in the world! -Well, you'll see soon.
It is a characteristic we the Izios get born with.
Then... I...
Then that enemy...
It is robots of Natta Yani, the rival of our father, Haruzo Izio.
Man, we missed it.
We should have stepped on those tin cans of Izio.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'm going to beat Robio in this race.
I'll look forward to it, Chebolt.
-Count on me. -Dad.
It's a call from the Science Minister, Doctor Ochanomizu.
What? Ochanomizu? Gosh. He's going to give me lectures again.
Mr. Yani! It's already been more than ten times that your robots have caused troubles!
Oh, is that so? Then, how many times did Izio robots cause trouble?
Ah, that is... I also warned Mr. Izio as well.
If you keep causing problems, I also have a thought, you know.
Excuse me, but did my robots kill people or something?
Did they destroy buildings or something?
It was only a fight between robots.
That's why! Do you understand? This is my last warning.
If your robots have a fight again, I'm going to disqualify
you from Japan Grand Prix Race for negligence.
Mr. Yani! Mr. Yani?
I'm so sick of it.
The Izios and the Yanis have been enemies for generations.
But why would even robots hate each other?
It is programmed into their electronic brains.
So they can never be on good terms?
Well, there's one hope.
This is robot's register card.
Every new born robots are to be registered at the Ministry of Science.
-Ah, this is Mr. Robio. -That's right.
And another one. Let's compare this to Robiet's.
With Miss Robiet?
Look. Interestingly, even though they have different looks and sexes,
-they have the same structure. -That's true.
How can they be so similar when they were made by different people?
Long-lasted rivalry is a scary thing.
-They now have a resembling technology. -So what would happen now?
This cannot be proven scientifically,
but robots with the same structure
could be drawn to each other by the resonance effect of electronic brains.
So Mr. Robio and Miss Robiet, too?
There could be a possibility.
So if the two of them could get closer,
the Izios and the Yanis who used to hate each other could get closer.
Mr. Robio and Miss Robiet...
Robiet.
No, you can't. You are destined to be enemies.
Dad, it seems like Robio's going out.
He must be excited to have a big race ahead of him.
I have to forget about her.
She's my enemy.
This place is...
"Natta Yani"
This is the house of Natta Yani. How did I end up here...
I have to go back. If someone sees me, I'll be in trouble.
Ah... The one who's playing the piano is... Robiet!
Who are you?
It's me, Robiet!
Robio, how did you...
I don't know.
Ever since I saw you for once,
my electronic brain doesn't seem to be able to forget about you.
-That's strange. -Pardon?
I... couldn't forget about you either...
Robiet.
Robio.
Who is it?
Robio! What is the Izio robot doing here?
You surely didn't think that you could go back safely
after stepping into the Yanis' place?
-Don't do that. -You, step back!
Brother, leave this to me.
Stop it! I have no intention to fight you!
Are you scared, Robio? Let me show you the supersonic power of my horn!
What's wrong, Robio!
All you Izios can do is running away!
I'm not going to lose you!
I don't want to fight, but now I can't help it!
Be ready!
Robio, take this!
Robio!
Robio, Robio!
I'm sorry, Robiet. I didn't mean to...
Step back, Robiet!
-Step aside! Step back! -Stop it now. Stop it!
Robiet! Are you defending the enemy?
I won't forgive it!
It's dangerous!
Robio!
Robiet...
Ah, Robio. Robio!
-Miss Robiet. -Ah, Mr. Atom.
-How's Robio? What about his wounds? -He's all right.
Since Doctor Ochanomizu is looking after him, he should be fine.
Ah, this happened all because of me...
How is he, Doctor Ochanomizu? Will Robio be able to recover?
Since the important electronic brain is fine, he will recover,
but it will take time for him to fully recover as a racing robot.
No... That can't be.
There are only three days left until Japan Grand Prix Race, so...
Robots aren't your tools!
I warned you that something like this would happen some day.
Reflect on your fault this time.
Th, that...
If Robio can't make it, then send me to the race.
Atom.
Are you sure, Atom?
I mean, you could learn racing skills in one day, but...
I would be thrilled if Atom could go in place of him.
I'm going to surprise the Yanis.
However, I have a favor to ask you.
Ah, of course, I'll pay you full...
If I win the race, please let Robio and Robiet marry.
Wh, what? My Robio and that Yani's daughter?
That's the condition. If you can't accept it, then I won't participate in the race.
Th, that is...
I see.
Ah, Mr. Robio.
-Are you all right now? -No, I'm not fully recovered yet,
but I got a special permission to go out to cheer for you today.
All right? You are replacing Mr. Robio, so you can never lose.
Pressure isn't good... But I will do my best.
Atom!
Atom. Now, it's time.
Okay!
Good luck! Yani will get crushed...
Natta Yani!
Haruzo Izio!
-Oh, it's Atom. -Go Atom!
[Go Atom] Play, play, Atom!
[Go Atom] Gosh, I'm embarrassed.
Play, play, Atom! Play!
Wait, Shibukaki. Weren't you a fan of Chebolt?
Mr. Chebolt, let's do our best.
You would be the right enemy of mine.
Do you understand? We have to stop Atom from winning.
Here, go!
While fans from all around Japan are watching,
Robot Grand Prix race finally gets started.
Start!
Each car gets into the most difficult course, the hairpin curve.
Accident breaks out so quickly!
Chebolt gets out.
He's at the head, going past other cars at an instant.
Oh! There's one more car. What a great speed.
It's Atom! Atom has caught up.
As predicted, it's a competition between Chebolt and Atom.
Next is the second stage, underwater hazard!
Who is it, interfering this race?
Atom, you cannot go further.
Mosquito from the Yanis.
Take this electronic torpedo!
Ah, it's so bright!
Shoot...
Mosquito.
It looks like Atom's behind. Chebolt's Red Star is running alone.
What happened, Atom? Is he out already?
The course now takes place in a desert, with Chebolt at the head.
Wh, what is that?
What is this tornado?
Chebolt, I made it specially for you.
You are!
Izio's Lard.
-You can't go further! -Drill!
Great distance between Mr. Chebolt.
It's odd. There was no such tornado around this area.
There must be something again.
Stop it!
-We are in the middle of the race! -Shut up!
Your race ends here.
Ah, Mr. Chebolt!
Take this!
Stop it!
Atom!
Mr. Chebolt, continue the race. Here, go ahead!
What?
-Hurry! -All right!
Stop!
Stop it! If you keep planning mean things, I will fight you!
Shoot... Atom!
You!
Gosh...
Now!
It's about time to come back.
-Teacher! -Oh!
It's back! Will Chebolt be at the head? Will Atom?
It's Chebolt! And Atom!
The winner is Chebolt with Red Star.
Yes! We did it!
Dang it...
Good. Good job, Chebolt.
-Everyone, this race will not count. -What are you talking about!
Because...
My brother and Izio's robots interrupted the race.
The one who saved me was
Atom!
Wh, what?
Mr. Chebolt, are you okay?
Atom, I wanted to fight rightfully with you.
Mr. Chebolt!
You shouldn't come!
Chebolt...
-Brother! -Ah, Atom!
Chebolt.
How funny. Now I'm the winner.
What are you talking about? I'm the winner!
-Good. Then, let's settle this down ourselves! -As I wished.
I'm going to make your Red Star into a scrap!
Same for you!
Stop it!
Dad, stop it!
It's dangerous, Robiet!
Stop, stop it!
Robiet, step back!
Robiet!
Stupid! Robio, step back!
-Robio. -Robiet.
Ah, Ro, Robio...
Ro, Robiet...
Robio!
Robiet.
-My Robio... -My daughter Robiet...
What a tragedy.
Mr. Yani, Mr. Izio, you are the most foolish people in the world.
Your foolish fight turned both of them into like this.
-What must this sound be, Doctor? -Huh?
This is a sound of artificial heart.
Then Robio and Robiet's artificial hearts did...?
Robio and Robiet are together now.
-Forgive me, Robio. -I'm sorry, Robiet.
Their hearts will be together forever even if their bodies disappear.
I will be undertaking a very important job.
I was selected as the captain of Mars investigators.
Good. I'm going to do my best.
Ah! You are Cavitt! You can't hide in like this!
Space men start showing up one by one.
Save the Mars base!
Next on Astro Boy, "Adventure on Mars." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "Adventure on Mars"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together