Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
The Stolen Sun
London
Sherlock Holmespan Investigation Office
I see, so this is the artificial sun that's scaring the entire world.
But a scientist who can create such matter...
Reasoning again, Wacchin?
The investigation is over.
It's Doctor Ochanomizu from Japan's Ministry of Science.
Then Sherlock Holmespan, you are going to Japan by yourself?
Yes. Right now.
You can take this assistance if you want...
A robot? I refuse.
I'm not that old to get help from a robot.
My pride wouldn't let me do that.
My Holmespan family of tradition wouldn't either!
Is that so? Robots aren't that bad.
I hate it.
All right, then.
Ah, that's right, Wacchin.
There is one thing your robot assistant can do.
What is it?
As you already know, my house is a mess since I live alone.
Can you make it clean my house?
What? Cleaning for my assistant?
It suits robots. It doesn't have to think.
My, my.
You must have gotten even more hatred toward robots after that happened.
Tokyo
He's been watching us like that for an hour.
Who is he?
Doctor, let me go and figure out.
Huh? No. Hold on, Atom.
Someone must be coming.
Looks like it's a real guest this time.
I'm a private detective Sherlock Holmespan from the U.K.
As I expected, it seems like someone's after you.
So, Doctor Ochanomizu, would you tell me the story?
The reason you made the artificial sun.
Surely you are not going to deny the fact.
It has already been investigated that you are related to the artificial sun.
You are being rude!
Shut up! How dare a robot disrupts a conversation?
But...!
-It's okay, Atom. -Huh?
I'll tell you, Mr. Holmespan.
What you said is correct.
I made that artificial sun a long time ago.
There used to be a plan to develop Pluto earlier.
In order to develop extreme environments like that of Pluto,
you need a source of strong heat and light.
So I created that heat and a light source from plutonium energy.
That's the artificial sun.
However,
when I finally finished building the artificial sun after three years and five months,
the Pluto development plan got cancelled.
How come? It's such a wonderful plan...
It's money.
They found out that it would cost them more money than planned.
And the artificial sun
I built got forgotten.
When I started noticing, someone had already stolen it.
So that's what happened.
That's right. Who would that be?
Well, there is a clue.
Doctor Ochanomizu, I'm sorry, but please take your clothes off.
What?
Take my clothes off?
The enemy's after you. So I have to disguise myself as you...
But...
Hurry!
Stop it!
Stop your violence!
Shut up! You robot!
This is amazing. A private detective is a robot.
What? Me? A robot?
Look! This is a prosthetic hand! I'm human!
Prosthetic hand?
That's right. When I used to work for the British government,
I sneaked into a villain's storage to save my colleague.
But that was a trap.
Tons of dynamites exploded and my body was blown up with the storage.
I was heavily injured.
At that time, my doctor was abroad to attend the Doctors' Assembly,
but stupid government. They let a robot doctor take care of me.
Machine is a machine.
It doesn't understand human heart.
They ripped my body apart.
So your body is?
The blood of my historic Holmespan family flows in this head only.
So the only original body of yours is your head?
That's right. But I'm human!
I'm a man of the Holmespans that
has achieved a long history of Great Britain.
I see...
Here, Doctor. Take your clothes off.
You should disguise yourself as me and take doctor to a safe place.
But...!
Don't talk back to me! Robots only need to listen to man's orders.
All right, now the disrupter is gone.
The only thing left is a body.
You are here.
Yes, yes. I'm coming.
Who is it? Why are you here so late...
Shut up! Doctor Ochanomizu.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to come with us.
That's... It should be fine now.
-Doctor, that's... -Huh?
Ah, that's maybe...
Atom, news. Turn on the radio.
Okay!
I repeat.
In the sky of Kasumigaseki, Tokyo, a sphere with strange light has appeared
and people are getting panicked.
Doctor,
Ah! Cars!
Doctor!
It's all right. Everyone has run away leaving their cars behind.
Atom, we have no time to delay.
Yes, sir!
My gosh. Gasoline caught fire.
-Let's escape to the tunnel. -Okay!
Doctor!
Thank goodness.
Doctor, I'm sorry. You should run first!
What are you going to do?
I'll try to break that artificial sun!
What? Even if it's you...
Atom!
The entire Tokyo will be a mess.
I'm coming!
Energy... My energy's drowning...
I safely retrieved the artificial sun.
How do you think, Doctor Ochanomizu?
What are you going to ask me to do?
I want to order you to make a stronger one than that artificial sun.
What?
Using that, I'm going to develop and rule over other planets as well as the Earth.
That's my plan.
What are you?
This was in the tentacles of the artificial sun.
This one is Atom!
The atom motor must have gotten broken due to high heat; he doesn't even twitch.
Now it's decided.
Even Atom I trusted is like this now.
All right, I'll cooperate.
That's a satisfactory answer.
So you are my partner from now on, Doctor.
Let me prepare a room for you.
Well, the entire universe will be ours if you work with me.
Relax and take some rest.
This is weird for Doctor Ochanomizu to obey so easily.
He might be planning something. Watch him carefully.
Yes, sir!
Doctor Ochanomizu. I mean, Mr. Holmespan.
Please. Would you change them to other robots' arms and legs?
It might not move accordingly,
but I think it will be a help to you.
Shut up! I have no intention to get a robot's help!
So this is the controller. In a way...
Controlling is my work.
It seems like he would listen to any kind of order.
Ah, I'm Ochanomizu who built the artificial sun.
Yes, I do know, Doctor.
So would you listen to me?
Yes.
All right, then. I will order you.
Send the artificial sun out to the stratosphere right away.
Yes, sir!
It worked. It's going up.
Doctor Ochanomizu! You can't act on your own.
What's wrong?
Boss, the doctor was controlling...
What happened, Doctor?
I can't let villains like you use the artificial sun as you please.
You are not Doctor Ochanomizu!
You finally noticed.
Of course!
I'm a British private detective,
Sherlock Holmespan!
Now!
Don't miss him!
Shoot... Chase him!
Hey, controller robot,
I have a favor to ask you.
Okay.
I want to have your arms and legs...
Let's exchange with mine.
Please. I beg you.
All right.
Thank you. So could you can a welder for me?
Don't miss him! Don't miss him!
Capture him!
Legs... My legs...
It's over now.
Shoot... When I got shot on my back, it must have ruined the circuit connected to legs.
He wouldn't be very much far away!
Don't miss him!
Shoot...!
Over there!
There he is.
How dare you fool us as a doctor.
Wait!
Huh? You are...
Atom.
Controller robot!
Retrieve the artificial sun to crater!
I can't move right now.
Stupid. You changed your arms and legs with Atom.
How useless.
Let me go! Don't do anything useless! Let me go!
-Ah, that's! -Huh? What is it?
My... I got rid of it but... That controller robot.
No, no. That robot cannot move.
-What? -I exchanged my arms and legs with his.
What did you do? Shoot... My plan's ruined.
Who in the world is controlling that artificial sun?
Piano controlling melody is in my memory...
Shut up! Mind your own business.
Get off. Get off!
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
You useless robot!
Then I'm going to wait until night and destroy that controller!
All right.
I'm going to sneak into that controlling room no matter what.
Mr. Holmespan. Let me carry you.
Shut up! I'd rather die than get help from a robot!
Ah! Mr. Holmespan!
Shoot... Dang...!
Here! Hold on to me.
Stop it! Stop.
I don't have a power to fly nor a million horsepower,
but I have a courage to fight against a bad one!
What?
-Mr. Holmespan. -Hmm.
Atom,
teach me the controlling melody of the artificial sun you remember.
Pardon?
I used to be a genius pianist when I was young.
I should be able to play some music for the controller.
Okay! Mr. Holmespan.
-Mr. Holmespan, here. -All right!
Holmespan!
-Catch him! -It's Atom!
-It's Holmespan. Don't miss him! -It's Atom!
-Okay then, Atom. -All right!
All right. I'm going to play until my arms get numb.
You will never be able to enter the room!
Shoot, Holmespan!
This is...
We did it, Atom. We did it!
The artificial sun has finally flown up to space, out of stratosphere!
We did it! We finally did it.
And my dream's gone as well.
Mason!
Mr. Holmespan!
Mr. Holmespan, Mr. Holmespan!
No...
He got shot in his head.
The only remaining part of him... His precious...
His original body...
He got shot in his head.
I will not forgive!
What?
I won't forgive you!
Don't come! Don't!
Don't come!
Robot Hospital
Doctor Wacchin, I wasn't able to be treated by you again.
I'm all right.
I changed my last body part, and now I'm a robot completely.
Holmespan.
Well...
I'm proud to be a robot.
Robot is just like man...
Well, there are robots that are better than men.
Atom?
The blood of our proud Holmespan family...
Holmespan. Tradition isn't about blood.
It's about that proper pride in your heart.
Thank you, Doctor Wacchin.
Thank that proud child robot Atom.
Some unknown package has arrived at Ochanomizu lab.
A disassembled robot was inside...
The assembled robot keeps repeating the words "Aurora Looks".
I visit Penguin Land with Mr. Beard to solve that riddle.
But there were Black Looks who were
after robots.
Next on Astro Boy. "Black Looks". Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Black Looks"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together