Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Huh?
No!
Cut the power!
The Birth of Atom
2030 A.D. Tokyo
Quiet, Jump!
May I help you?
Kid, is Doctor Tenma here?
Yes, he is.
My name is... Skunk
...and?
Doctor, you are the world's most prestigious scientist of robot technology.
However, today you have failed yet again,
but since you've tried to make a robot with a human heart,
you've had four failures...
As the Minister of Science, don't you find this embarrassing?
Shhh, be quiet!
So what business do you have with me?
This is a circuit called 'Omega'.
If you place this inside the robot's electronic brain,
it will give it human emotions.
As you have wished, exactly like a human being.
Ha ha...
I have no intention in using such things!
Even if you suggest it, take it back.
Are you sure, Doctor? It would be such a waste.
You don't know what it is capable of...
Enough! Now quickly leave!
Kid, your father is... really stupid!
No,
he is not a fool.
Dad, you are not a fool; you are great, right?
No, Tobio, I'm the worst scholar.
With all of this technology,
why am I still unable to create a robot like a real person?
Dad, what if you make a child robot?
A child robot?
A child robot! That's it!
Why didn't I think of that?!
I'm going to re-design Robot 5 into a child robot.
A child robot!
What are you going to do with such a thing?
After all, this is a kid's show isn't it?
No more chatting! It's an order of the Minister.
We will begin right away.
Oh, it's Tobio...
Dad,
you promised to take me to the theme park today.
Yeah, what? Ah, right. I did, didn't I?
I'll wait at the porch.
Daddy's busy today. Let's go next time.
We can't go? It's always like this.
Let's go next week for sure.
No, I want to go today.
Hang on for a while.
I want to hang out with you.
I said next time. Go back home.
Let's go, Jump.
Go back to house first, Jump.
Go back!
Daddy, you fool.
What? Tobio went out?
by himself in a robot car?
It's dangerous! A kid cannot possibly drive a robot car!
Ah!!!
Tobio!
God, please save Tobio.
Dad,
Tobio!
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Umm...
Dad, it's about that robot you are making now.
Name it "Tobio" in place of me.
I want it to be the coolest, strongest robot in the world.
All right, all right. I'll do that. So hang in there.
You have to do that. Promise?
I promise.
Thank you. Please love it, and instead of...
Tobio... My one and only Tobio!
Step back.
Minister, I have a bad feeling about this. If a robot like this gets built,
I think it's would be like having a devil.
I think it's good to halt this plan.
Flying in the air with a million-horsepower,
and having laser and machine gun...
Isn't it like a new weapon?
Miss Honda, it is for me to decide whether it will be a devil or an angel.
What do you mean a weapon, it's my son.
Hu hu hu... Ha ha ha...
How's my alpha and omega, Skunk?
Ha ha... As you can see...
Look,
I can surprise Tenma with this.
In a robot he built,
I installed this Omega I invented.
This would make the world's best android.
I'm going to make it this time for sure. My dream...
It's a complete robot that resembles a human being.
Ha ha...
Tenma, stop that research now.
I do understand you However, this robot is dangerous.
But Minister!
But this is only harmful to people.
Okay, Tenma? Get rid of this robot by tomorrow night.
Minister!
What is this!
Tobio,
Tobio! Tobio!
It's dad. Please call me "Dad".
Would you call me dad?
Da...d.
Tobio,
You are my child!
You completed in the end.
If this gets out, you would get in trouble.
I'm taking this kid to my house. I'm goint to raise him as my son.
Do whatever you want; file a suit or something.
Namu...
I'm Tobio, Dad.
Yes, you are starting to remember.
Window.
Say "Sorry".
Sorry.
Chair
Ah, it hurts...
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Help yourself.
You are not supposed to eat forks.
I can fly.
Wow, flying! Flying!
Bird
Jump, come here. It's Tobio.
Jump, come, come.
Jump,
Tobio, what's up?
Tobio, wake up.
Tobio, what's wrong? It's getting worse.
He suddenly fell unconscious and is not answering.
What if we carry him to the Ministry of Science and check?
That wouldn't be possible!
It's a secret that that kid is in my house.
I can only ask you and engineer Ushiyama.
Okay. I'll be on my way.
He did it.
That robot?
From what I heard over the phone, D circuit seems to be causing the problem.
Then... It's going to explode again, like the number 4.
Just in case, bring the robot disposal car.
Doctor, if that kid explodes in the town,
it's going to create a big problem.
I think it's best to disassemble it this time.
Don't do that. Honda, you are a woman.
Don't you think it's cute? You are a girl after all.
It's only cute on the outside.
It's a robot inside. A million-horsepower monster!
Should we play games?
Let's go.
Someone's calling me.
Someone's calling from far, far away. Who could it be?
Maybe it's another me.
Good, it's the birth of a prince.
The world's best robot with the Omega factor.
You will be the ruler; even human beings will follow you.
Right! I'll name you "Atlas."
Atlas! The ruler of the earth! Ha ha ha!
Livian! You take care of Atlas.
Yes, sir.
However, he will be in charge of education. Don't forget.
Heh heh...
Take it.
A...tlas... Here, come here.
Ah!
Cut the power supply.
Why am I in a place like this?
Stop.
Don't destroy him.
He's going to explode!
Stop the car. Don't touch the switch.
Stop it. The computer is...
Ah!
Oh my, it's out of control!
Somebody help!
Help!
Dad!
That!
Help!
Because of a shot-down helicopter,
there was a fire in a mansion at #15.
What is that?
A robot is flying in the air. Between buildings.
He's helping people.
Ah, robot flies away.
Where is he headed?
Ah, it seems like he's chasing the criminal car.
How is it!
Tobio,
Since you've made this mess,
people would find out that I made you after disobeying what they said.
Then I cannot stay in the Ministry of Science anymore.
Tobio, let's go to the U.S. together.
You will be free as well, if we go to the States.
Yes!
You are a good kid. Let's have fun together.
Jump, come here.
Come here.
Let's go.
How is it? He's my son.
Livian,
Is my name a "Devil's child"?
No, your name is "Atlas."
That's weird. Dad said so.
What is the devil?
Next on Astro Boy
I'm Atom...
I'm leaving to the States with my dad by ship.
An iceberg!
It suddenly came to us.
Everyone's in danger.
When I was fighting with all my strength, the one that appeared in front of me was...
You... You are...?
Next episode: [Mighty Fist Atom]
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together