Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Do something!
The radiator is broken.
I wish the repair shop was near.
Boss! It's Department of Machinery! It's exactly like you ordered!
Ha ha... A component
could be fixed or something.
There are only robots working here.
Even if we get caught, they can't do bad things to humans.
We've been on a tough road.
Let's see what we can take.
Must be awfully powerful
when it's complete.
Look!
Frankenstein
You can't move it!
It's scary! Let's run.
Don't be afraid. Let's look around.
It's a robot factory.
What is this sound?
Let me see.
Wow...
What in the world has happened?
Wake up! What happened?
Fran...ken...
Franken?
I see. Then, that weird sound was Franken's...
Franken... It's a space pioneer robot.
Oh my!
He's not completed yet!
If that kind of robot uses violence to people...
Doctor, I'll go find him.
Please.
Find Franken no matter what
and make him join us.
Will that kind of monster listen to us?
Listen, a newly made robots
are like babies.
So it will listen to the first one it hears from.
All right, hurry!
Stupid! Be careful!
Huh?
Bo..Boss...
Wow... This one's a treasure!
Bo.. Boss...
Stop it!
Franken! Listen! I'm Skunk.
All right? I'm your master.
Do you understand? I'm your master.
Ha ha... Franken...
Bravo.
Sign it! Hoshizora Misako!
Hoshizora Misako's really popular.
I cannot believe she's a robot celebrity.
The famous robot girl Hoshizora Misako's
completely changed look...
That's bad. Do you have something against her?
But there's no way that someone would be against Hoshizora Misako.
I didn't know a robot would be destroyed like this.
This must be Franken!
The jewel... The diamond is gone!
Diamond? Would a robot steal a diamond?
I don't know!
Anyway, Atom, something happened!
Huh?
Robots have become criminals.
But...
I told you robots are dangerous.
Inspector Tawashi, you shouldn't say that!
No! It's too late after it has affected human beings!
It's a big trouble!
Franken's crime against jewelry shops and banks
has a possibility to get even worse.
The police will continue to look for Franken
and with this opportunity, they submitted
a bill against an incomplete robots to the Congress.
There already are citizens unplugging
the robots to prevent a possible crime.
They started to guard the shops.
Everyone, please be careful and be on your guard.
Inspector Tawashi!
Unplugging every robot?
Isn't this too much?
No, if the other robots make troubles,
there would be a huge riot.
What a fool... It's tragic for robots.
That's right. If you look at Franken...
I can't...
Shut up! Stop complaining!
No, it's like what Atom said.
I'm sure Franken is being controlled by someone.
What? Being controlled?
Even if it's incomplete, there's no way a robot
would rob jewels and money.
I'm investigating broken channels in Franken.
If I figure that out...
No, we cannot wait anymore.
What a waste of time! I'm going to find it for sure.
We didn't do anything. Manager!
It's not good to unplug!
I'm a robot cook, so there's no guest visiting me anymore!
Here, unplug me!
My... I didn't do anything bad!
The firefighting job for saving peoples' lives
are taken over by robots, and
I haven't been happy about this.
Now, we are not going to get help from you machines!
Stay in a storage!
It's not your fault, but it's for my business.
I want you to take a break.
Robots have dropped down to a corner
due to lack of gas?
Now the work is easier. I never expected that.
Everything is due to Franken.
Hey, Atom!
Atom, wait! I called you many times.
What's wrong? You look tired.
Ah, it's Shibukaki.
This little 1st grader! You are a robot, too.
If you don't apologize, I'm not going to leave this.
So I've been saying sorry...
Stupid! If only the word "sorry" was going to work,
there would be no need for the police station.
Stop it!
It's Atom. Don't disturb us. Get away!
No! It's my father.
What?
Good. I'm going to tell the teacher.
I'm going to unplug you!
If there are two dangerous robots in this school,
We cannot be off our guard. We cannot study well.
Th..That is...
What, are you trying to beat me?
Ah... Atom.
Interesting. Beat me.
Atom, stop...
You know what happens if a robot
lays a hand on a person, right?
That's right, it's only a machine. You robots!
Hey!
Stop! Both of you!
Tamao... Ratting on...
What did you say?
People and robots are equal!
You cannot fight
with this kind of thing!
Atom, cheer up!
What is that?
That's right! There was a strange sound from Franken...
Good! Let me raise my hearing ability up to 1,000 times...
Ah! Franken's sound!
Here's the sculpture of Rodin.
You are late! 3 days have passed from the day you promised!
We are very sorry.
I thought I was going to lose my million dollars!
But it's a good artwork!
He he... Yes...
Now our Gallery Shibukaki is going to gain some fame...
I don't know whether it's Rodin or Rodung,
but Dad, you bought a fake one before as well, right?
You don't recognize the million-dollar worth masterpiece!
Sir, are you still sleepi...
Sir!
It's Franken for sure!
Good.
Ah... a forgery! My son's got a standard, so...
Ah! My jewel!
It's Franken, right?
Don't be violent, Franken.
Hold on!
What an amazing... Huh?
Are you all right?
Don't come near. Hands in the air!
I... I...
Jewel... A million-dollar jewel...
Ah! It's this one! He's crazy about the sculpture...
Ah... Jewel...
Atom! You did it in the end!
No, it's not me.
Shut up! If it's not you, how come you are here?
Huh!
Dad!
Atom, how can you...
No... I'm here because I heard Franken...
Don't make excuses!
That's right, you were in the same side with Franken.
That... It's not fair...
Atom was arrested for being an accomplice of Franken.
After that, after the interrogation in the police,
he was released for the lack of evidence,
but considering the public's panic and increasing distrust for robots,
he was ordered to be unplugged
by Dr. Ochanomizu.
Doctor, please unplug me.
Atom...
Sorry, Atom. Please forgive me.
While we are doing this, Franken is...
Franken... Why... Why do we have to go through this...
Mom...
Franken...
Oh, Franken... What happened, Franken!
Ferocious Franken is heading to the center of the city.
People around that area should evacuate soon.
It's the worst situation...
Repeat, ferocious Franken
is heading toward the center of the city.
Atom, People around that area...
Atom, wake up!
Doctor Ochanomizu!
Atom, are you awake?
Atom,
Atom, you are the only one who can insert
this remodeling circuit to Franken.
Franken!
Help!
What are robot firefighters doing?
Call the firefighters!
They should know!
All robots are unplugged.
My, at a time like this!
What are you going to do? There's no more people.
Plug the robots back!
Franken!
It's Atom and Franken!
Aim Franken!
This remodeling circuit!
Ah... Franken...
Franken, is what you did a good thing?
It's bad thing, right?
Wow, it's fixed!
Franken became a good robot!
Good, let's clear ourselves from a false accusation!
Franken, would you tell us the place of the gangs that used you?
Skunk! It was you!
Skunk!
Wait!
I'm late!
Franken!
The gang boss has escaped.
Atom, well done.
It's not that robots are all bad.
You should know this.
Of course!
Right, Inspector Tawashi?
Hmm...
Everyone, let me tell you one thing!
It's human who used Franken.
To tell the truth, it's human's fault
for leaving the Department of Machinery only to robots due to their laziness!
You should be ashamed!
It's exactly what I said.
It's good. Good. Well done.
Doctor Ochanomizu!
You should let your parents
know about your work.
Yes, sir!
Next on Astro Boy
#13-13 Sasagaya, it's a scary ghost mansion.
5 boys get abducted continuously.
Who is that there? What... It's a cat.
What? On November 19th,
Something scary is going to happen?
To Be Continued...
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together