Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Wow, the seeds sprouted.
My tulip. Please grow up quickly.
My precious tulip...
Wait, you!
Yo!
What's up with "Yo"? For what reason did you bring this junk...
I found it. Atom,
- Who do you think you are? I... - Uran!
Atom, come here!
Something's going on!
Yeah? Is that boy Atom?
What's up? A car accident?
That's not it. My tulip is...
- Atom, come with me for now. - Pardon?
Wait a minute. Who in the world are you?
- Ah, sorry, I'm detective Locke. - Detective?
- Hurry. I tell you the details later. - But I have homework...
Wait, me too!
Huh? This is not a car.
It's a time machine. A used one.
Time...
What is time machine?
Please have a seat first.
Hey, you don't have to come.
- Compensate for my tulip. - Tulip?
Yes. If you don't give me a new tulip, I won't get off.
Oh... I'm sorry.
I'm still not good with driving time machine.
The next is...
Black Jack? That's a weird name.
Major Operations by Black Jack
Oh my!
Is Doctor Black Jack here?
You should use a door! What are you going to do with my omelet?
Gosh, I did it again. Sorry!
What brought you here?
Are you Black Jack?
Right, it's this face. The best surgeon in history.
I have a favor to ask you.
What are you going to do with Pinoko's omelet?!
It's urgent. This patient needs you.
What is this? All of a sudden?
You crushed your car in my house and you didn't even apologize.
Ah... I'm sorry. I'm not good at driving.
Doctor! The fate of a country depends on this! Please!
Come later. It's time for me to drink wine.
If you like wine, I can get you 15th century Moravian wine anytime.
But can you pay for my surgery?
The charges for my surgery are...
I know.
I'll give you Moravian gems as much as you want.
Anyhow, please get in.
What is this?
It's a time machine.
I'm telling the truth.
I'm going to take you to the past, back to 600 years ago.
A time machine? What a fool.
Doctor, look at this!
That's odd.
So this is time machine. It's like a science fiction.
Yes. It is a science fiction.
A science fiction?
What a fool.
This is Atom.
Nice to meet you.
Atom is a robot for justice.
- A robot! - I'm sorry I'm a robot.
What a fool to ask the doctor for the surgery of a robot!
- Are you a nurse? You are still a kid. - How rude! I'm 21 years old.
Hold on, please be quiet.
I'm a time patrol agent, Detective Locke from 23rd century.
23rd century?
With this, I freely travel around future, present and past,
chasing around criminals.
So you are a detective from future.
Yes. Are you interested now?
My only interest is in money.
In fact, I was chasing a criminal who stole a time machine
to a country in 15th century.
But I did such a poor job with driving...
And that was the prince of that country.
I quickly moved that prince into the castle.
He was seriously injured.
If the prince dies, the history will get changed.
Because in the history it says that the prince lives up to 80.
Anyhow, I have to make the prince live.
So you came to my doctor?
Yes. I researched who's the best surgeon in history.
Then what about Atom?
Please have a look at this.
In fact...
There is a pack of villains who is after the throne.
Their leader is a wizard called Goa.
He found out about the prince's injury and is planning to invade the castle.
So I want Atom to fight against him.
Because robots don't fall under a spell.
We are here.
This is Moravia of the 15th century.
This place is...
- Fire arrow! - It's over there.
Atom, I entrust Goa to you.
Please come with me, Doctor Black Jack.
- Fine, then I, too,... - Uran, get inside the castle. Quick!
Ah! You shouldn't run away. He's not the devil.
Freeze!
Atom, are you all right?
They are toads and rats.
Everyone thinks they are the devil.
The soldiers are all hypnotized.
Hypnotized?
I see. Maybe he's just a hypnotist, not a wizard.
We drove out the devils.
Oh, thank you so much.
- This is Atom who did such job. - Hello!
The castle owes you one.
No, it's nothing.
Everyone, please get out.
I want to confirm my pay first.
Yes, all right.
This is the key to the treasure room.
Once the prince is healed and the wizard is gone
and maintain peace for this country, treasure won't be necessary...
I won't trust you until I see it with my own eyes.
- I will go see it. - Uran wants to go, too!
Uran!
I'll begin the surgery. Everyone, get out.
- I want a necklace. - Princess crown!
- It's an unpleasant place. - I'm here. Don't worry.
- Gosh, it scared me. - A bat...
This is the entrance to the treasure room.
It's amazing!
Pinoko!
This is...
It bothers me.
I'm worried.
God, please save the prince.
Everyone! Everyone!
My gosh! Pinoko is... Pinoko's...
Uran, what happened?
The treasure room... The water poured out...
What? Pinoko?
- That...That is... - What is it!
We certainly installed such trap to prevent thieves...
but we haven't been using it for years.
Then...Who...? Someone opened the floodgate on purpose?
- Where does that water flow to? - To the river in the valley...
All right!
S..Spell...
Open it! Open it!
Open this window!
Open it! Hey!
What is it? It's loud.
Doctor Black Jack?
Yes.
Boss sent a letter.
I'll read it: "Pinoko's here."
"If you want her back, stop the surgery right now and get out of this country."
What? Pinoko?
"I have something to tell you about this, so come to me right away."
"Puko will guide you."
That's me.
"If you don't follow what I say, Pinoko will be offered to the devil."
"From Goa of the Devil Army"
Goa of the Devil Army?
This is the proof. Here.
It's Pinoko's bow.
Puko, lead the way.
Um...What about the surgery?
I put him under anesthesia. It's okay to leave him like this.
What is this?
It's a magic broom. Please get on.
That's amazing. What a spell.
Where did Pinoko go?
Pinoko might not be safe...
That's Doctor Black Jack.
Where is he going? Good!
Ah, that's...
Doctor, this way.
Ah! Doctor!
Pinoko!
Welcome, Black Jack. I'm Goa the Great Wizard.
I want to ask you one thing. How did you know we were here?
I'm a wizard. I know most things.
I have only one goal.
I want to become a king of Moravia.
And starting from this country,
I want to make the whole Europe into a magic continent.
What a fool.
Wh, What did you say?
Probably!
You are just fooling the people of this country with your cheap hypnosis.
You...!
He went this way.
Huh? That's odd. But that seems like a robot.
A robot in this era?
What's the matter!
There's a big trouble! Atom's here.
Atom?
Saucy little one.
Doctor!
Pinoko!
No.
Don't move. If you move, I'm going to crush her.
Doctor Black Jack!
Atom, don't move.
Black Jack, if you stop the surgery of the prince,
I'm going to let all of you go.
I swear.
- What, are you serious? - I don't make a lie!
Fine, hold your hand out.
It seems like you are telling the truth.
I don't lie.
Doctor Black Jack.
Doctor!
- Doctor! - Pinoko, it's fine now.
If you have decided, then I don't have any more business with you.
Leave this country immediately!
- I'll do as you say. - Doctor!
Doctor Black Jack, are you really going to stop the prince's surgery?
I'm not going to.
What? Then the prince will die!
I don't care.
Ha ha, they are running away.
Look, they gave in. Moravia is mine now.
Let's go! We will have a triumphal entry into the castle.
Ha ha ha, there's not even a shadow.
I'll kill the prince, first of all.
You, you are Black Jack! How come you are...
This guy's swear was proved by the delicate lie detector...
I kept my promise.
What?
I said I will stop the surgery of the prince, but not of the princess.
Wh, What?
This patient is not a prince but a princess!
It was a girl.
What a nonsense! Dang it...
Finish them!
Monster Three Neck and Big Bart, come out and finish Atom!
How is it?
Shoot...
Goa! Let it go now!
Locke!
Freeze!
You are the wanted criminal.
So you were trying to change the history calling yourself Goa?
Atom!
- Uran! I defeated him! - I copied you well, right?
There is a party for the prince's recovery tonight at the castle.
Is that so?
- Party! - What a relief.
Now you can do whatever you want.
Prince.
I don't want to live as a guy anymore.
Oh my!
- Not a prince... - But a princess.
In fact, I'm not the Sapphire Prince; I'm the Sapphire Princess.
As you know, only a man can inherit the throne.
So I pretended to be a prince until now.
But Doctor Black Jack told me that there should be no more lies.
So I decided to not lie to you.
If the surgery goes well, you promised to get me anything I want, right?
Yes, anything.
Then, I'll take the law that says that only a man can inherit the throne.
- Wow! - What a great guy.
I'll gladly get it to you.
- Hooray! - Hooray!
Doctor Black Jack, Atom. You were a great help.
- Thank you so much. - Get away! Move!
How is it, Atom? Isn't my prince costume awesome?
- I'm better looking. - Whatever.
Atom, why didn't you get gems?
Robots don't need it.
Doctor Black Jack didn't really get anything?
It's a coin that commemorates the birth of the prince, the Sapphire Princess.
It was on the ground.
- Why that? - There's only one of it.
Atom, for how much would it sell now?
Um... A 15th century commemorative coin...
That's amazing!
A million dollars!
I have to take my portion.
Movie Super Zero, selling nationally!
Uran is into Stanton, the lead role star.
Stanton is so hot, fighting gorilla in jungle.
But the dangerous scenes were done by the robot called Sam, who looks exactly like him.
But Uran kidnaps Sam, so the studio is in a mess!
Next on Astro Boy; Little Robot Sam's Great Adventure!
Little Robot Sam's Great Adventure!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together