Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Ah, it quieted down.
So scary. I can't sleep like this every night.
I'm going to move tomorrow!
Are you going to abandon your ancestor's land? I'm not going to!
That's right! As long as the Inmen Jiwa doesn't move, this town's safe!
Inmen Jiwa.
What is that?!
It's will-o'-the-wisp!
Inmen Jiwa
Everyone, please take a look at your left side.
What you can see on the mountain is called Inmen Jiwa.
It became like that by weathering.
That's a weird rock. It looks like someone.
It looks like Shibukaki.
A long time ago, there were many legends that said
that it's possessed or it was made by the devil...
No one believes in such superstition anymore.
However! There is one legend that
everyone in this town believes until today.
The legend says that if Inmen Jiwa, facing east,
turns away to where the lake is, the town of Sparitz will perish.
Ridiculous. A rock wouldn't move by itself. Right, Atom?
Huh? Is that a removal van?
That's strange.
It feels like the direction has changed a bit from 20 years ago.
Next is Sparitz.
Teacher, we are getting off at Sparitz, right?
Yes. Get ready.
We are finally here. Yay!
Mr.Shunsaku.
-Welcome. -It's been 10 years.
So you guys are Atom and Uran?
He's my old colleague, Goro Yamakawa.
Nice to meet you!
Welcome.
I see... There are that many earthquakes?
This town is over now.
Fields are getting dried up, cliffs are collapsing, and huts are crumbling as well.
So everyone is abandoning this town to move away?
There have been almost 100 earthquakes ever since I got here as a Japanese teacher.
It feels like the Inmen Jiwa has shifted a little.
Teacher, welcome.
Mr.Shunsaku. This is Dr.Archie, archaeologist.
He's staying here to study the ancient German ruins.
I'm Shunsaku Ban. Guten Morgen. This is Atom and Uran.
Nice to meet you!
Guten Morgen.
Would you like a cup of tea?
No, thank you. I have to go investigate.
He's weird.
Watch your mouth. Every scholar is bit eccentric.
Teacher, I'm going to go see the Inmen Jiwa. Is that all right?
-All right. -Me too!
No. I'm going to fly.
Take me.
I'll tell you about it after I see it.
You are mean.
It looks really heavy and hard.
It might be a meteor.
This rock did move, as expected.
It's because of those earthquakes Mr.Yamakawa talked about.
However,
there's no way we will be able to see the other side of this rock.
It's just my imagination.
The mountain-
This is heaven. It feels like I'm in one of hot springs in Japan.
Little bit of salt, sulfur and calcium.
Is this supposed to feel that much great?
Teacher, would you like to play the diving game?
I don't want to dive.
-Then let's get out. -You don't like hot springs?
It's difficult to clean myself if sulfur gets accumulated.
Robots are so inconvenient.
It's here!
Huh? I thought you didn't want to dive in.
Will-o'-the-wisp!
What? Oh!
Stop!
It's here! Here! Here!
Who are you?
What is that? It's like a bomb.
Shoot!
This time for sure!
I'm not going to let you go no matter what.
I lost it.
Earthquake!
Atom, get up. Uran, it's an earthquake.
-This is big. -Would the other teacher be okay?
-I'll go and check. Take care of Uran. -Yes, sir!
Neighbor! Dr.Archie!
It stopped.
Ouch!
Doctor! Dr.Archie.
Are you all right? Doctor...
He's not here. Where did he go in the middle of night?
Are you running away in the end?
There is a crack in the middle of my house.
I'm scared. It's so scary.
If the dam gets a crack or something, the whole town will be flooded.
-I'm not scared at all. -Whatever, you were sleeping.
It was fun, rocking like a ship.
Uran, you are so easygoing.
It's not the right time to fool around.
Everyone's having a hard time because of earthquakes.
You are doing it again. You are such a nagger.
-Where are you going? -Why would you care?
She's always like that.
-Ah, Doctor. -Hello.
Doctor, where were you last night?
I took a walk because I couldn't sleep.
Walk...?
That red dirt on that shirt is...
It looks the same as the Inmen Jiwa's red dirt.
Teacher, you are back.
Have you heard about it?
The government research team is getting here tomorrow.
A research team?
Yes. They are going to figure out the cause of frequent earthquakes or something.
Well, then. I'm going to get some sleep.
This is bellflower, this is cosmea.
That's... This... What is this?
That's Chinese pink!
-This is madder. This is... -Tuberose!
My name is Uran!
My brother is Atom!
Your name is?
I'm the will-o'-the-wisp boy.
-You know a lot. -I know everything about the mountain.
Where are you from?
From a faraway mountain.
What were you doing?
I was digging holes day and night.
I'm so tired. People can be annoying.
They've never treated you nicely, huh?
There's no such thing as a warm person in this world.
There is.
Let's go to the town. I'll introduce you to Mr.Beard.
Please keep it secret that you've met me.
How come?
If you do, I'll show you something great.
Then, I will.
All right, here.
Two wires are here!
From these two wires...
Fireworks!
Wow, that's amazing.
Spring, March. Weeping willows!
Great!
Look at that. The crack gets bigger as we get closer to the Inmen Jiwa mountain.
So the area near Inmen Jiwa is in trouble.
I see! That's why Inmen Jiwa is shifting. I see.
-Hey, I want to try making fireworks. -All right.
But you have to be careful.
So these have to touch each other, right?
What was that sound?
Teacher, I'll go and look.
Uran, wake up.
-I told you to be careful. -Hey!
What did you do to my sister?
Atom...
I won't forgive you if you bother her!
Stop!
Atom, it was my fault.
Don't do that to him!
Hey! Atom!
Atom!
Huh? What was it? There's no one.
As expected, there is a trace that Inmen Jiwa has shifted.
This dirt is...
Shoot.
Stop!
So last night's will-o'-the-wisp was that one.
All right!
I'm going to get you today for sure!
Shoot. I lost it.
I found it!
It's not this one.
Over there... Shoot.
This time for sure!
Gotcha!
I'm sorry.
Hold on!
I lost it again.
This area looks familiar.
It did disappear around here last time.
It's a castle.
I see. This is an old castle from a long time ago.
Earthquake again!
Teacher.
I'm tired.
Don't slack off!
I must be running out of energy.
We have to find that treasure chamber today no matter what.
There are suspicious visitors around and government workers are coming as well.
What in the world is in this mountain?
It's something great you cannot even imagine.
As I was studying the history of the Vikings,
I found out that their treasure is buried under this castle.
I don't know what it is, but there is a rock with carved letters in this hole as well.
What? A rock with carved letters?
Give me the lamp.
Here. They are ancient Scandinavian scripts.
All right, Will-o'-the-wisp. Smash this rock!
That rock is very hard. My drill won't work.
All right, turn around. I'll change your energy.
Now your energy is 200 times higher.
With that, you will be able to tear any rock down.
Wouldn't a huge earthquake occur if I do such thing?
I don't care. Do it.
Here I come, treasure!
I don't feel anything unusual.
-Atom! -Ah, it's Uran.
-Uran! Over here. -Atom.
I see. So that Will-o'-the-wisp disappeared here.
Hey, Uran.
Who is it? Whose robot is it?
I don't know.
You are hiding something, Uran.
-I promised to not tell anything. -He's a bad one.
He turns into a wil-o'-the-wisp every night and surprises townspeople.
He's not a bad one. He's just got little problems.
Uran!
Will-o'-the-wisp is my friend!
Atom, this rock's moving!
Huh? Rock?
Look. Here. You see?
That kind of device was...
It's like a magic. Atom, let's go in.
All right!
What was that explosion right now?
Help!
I'm going to be buried!
-The Inmen Jiwa is...! -It's facing the dam!
-It's a curse. -Something scary will happen!
Help!
Teacher!
Teacher, what happened?
While I was investigating the Inmen Jiwa, something exploded from the back.
This is a crime. Let's inform the people in town!
I finally found it. This is the treasure of the Vikings!
-Teacher, Inmen Jiwa is sliding down the mountain. -Stop!
Inmen Jiwa! Where are you going?
-Atom, stop it. -Okay!
Atom!
It's a heavy rock. Hurry...
Hurry...! Everyone, run...
-Go, Atom! -Teacher, I'm scared.
It's like that rock's alive.
It looks like it's heading to the dam with a purpose.
I'm losing my energy...
No more...
Atom!
Atom, run! You will be crushed!
Inmen Jiwa.
The town...
will sink underwater.
That's right!
Dr.Archie might be underground!
We have to save him!
Atom!
-Where are you going? -Atom's almost out of his energy...
-What is that sound? -Teacher, look at that.
There are strange letters again.
What? Letters?
"If anyone interrupts the King's sleep, he will be cursed.
The patron of this tomb, Inmen Jiwa, will take his life."
Oops!
Now you can't get out of here.
-You were trying to steal this treasure, right? -You, Will-o'-the-wisp...
Will-o'-the-wisp!
Make a hole on the ceiling with your drill.
Get me out of here right now!
-No! -What?
I don't like you anymore. You are always ordering me around.
What? You are my assistant.
You were just using my power.
Dr.Archie!
You are...
Doctor. You were here.
Help. Get me out of here.
Take my hand...
No, I can't...
I have no energy.
-Atom! Leave him! -Will-o'-the-wisp.
Were you there? Please help me.
No. I don't have much energy either.
We can survive if we work together.
No thanks. Bye!
Will-o'-the-wisp.
Please. Wait.
I'm losing it...
Atom!
Atom...
Atom, my precious Atom. He drowned to death.
I had to stop him. He was running out of his energy.
Atom!
I'll go and rescue him.
Wh, wh, wh, what?
I'm going to go rescue Atom and the doctor. That's what robots do!
You can't! Stop there!
What, Will-o'-the-wisp.
Leave it to me, Uran.
Will-o'-the-wisp!
Atom, I'm sorry to get you involved.
Doctor,
Teacher! Atom. I'll get you out.
Atom! Atom. My son.
I'm glad. I'm so glad.
You have to thank him.
-That's right! Where is he? -Over there.
Will-o'-the-wisp! Everyone wants to thank you.
It's all right.
Rather than that... Give this to your brother.
-What is this? -It's energy cassette.
-Huh? Thank you, Will-o'-the-wisp. -Well, then.
Huh? Where are you going?
No! Don't go!
We will meet again sometime for sure.
-Bye! -Will-o'-the-wisp!
Will-o'-the-wisp!
Hey.
It's here. That's the real rescue ship.
-You look satisfied. -We kept the treasure.
Now the treasure of the Vikings will be down there forever.
No one can take it.
Good bye, Inmen Jiwa.
A funny and peculiar robot found in the park.
It's not trying to part from Uran.
Uran's in trouble!
And I got attacked by the assassin Lamp, who goes only after robots.
And Uran falls in love with the handsome robot Zeus!
But the real aspect of Zeus is...
Next on Astro Boy, "Uran Loves Hitman"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together