Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
National Robot Museum Exhibition Hall
This is a robot called "Lightning," made with a newly
developed glass called "pH glass."
What is the robot?
-I don't see anything. -No.
You cannot touch it.
If I don't touch it, I wouldn't know where it is.
pH glass shines like a beautiful rainbow, when beamed with polarized light.
Wow, this is beautiful.
Is this a dream or a vision?
It's like an angel.
I think this will win the Grand Prix this year.
Yes.
A lightning man.
Lightning Man
You've waited for a long time.
I'm going to announce this year's Robot Arts Grand Prix.
The foreman of a jury, Doctor Ochanomizu, please come this way.
All right.
Ah! Ouch!
Doctor, are you all right?
I don't know to what I bumped into. It hurts.
Let me announce.
This year's Robot Arts Grand Prix goes to...
the Lightning Man.
Ah! Lightning isn't here.
Ah! My money is...
It's a ghost!
I think this will do.
Wow, how pretty.
"Banks and jewelry shops robbed; total of $10 million lost"
"Mystery of Ginza in the middle of the day"
Then Doctor, is Lightning a bad robot now, like this?
No, it isn't a bad robot.
But the scary thing is that it's acting
upon bad guys' orders, believing they are telling truths.
Lightning doesn't know how to distinguish between good and evil.
It's like a child.
Is that so?
Oh, Atom.
-How are you? Did you finish vacation homework? -Yes. Almost.
Are there some leads on Lightning?
-Breaking news. -Huh?
$80 million has disappeared from Shinzuku's bank safe.
Today, around 1 PM, from nine different bank safes in Shinzuku,
cash came out and have disappeared somewhere.
Since the case resembles yesterday's Ginza case,
the police has decided that it's done
by the Skunk group using Lightning Man.
Shoot, Skunk? What an annoying guy. Stupid!
Teacher! I'll be back!
Where are you going?
-I'm going to find Skunk's hideout. -What?
How are you going to find him in this big city? Let the police work on it.
But rather than doing nothing...
Atom!
Ah, this is Beard...
Ah! That laughing sound is from Skunk. We caught him last week, though.
You shouldn't underestimate me like other gangs.
I can get out anytime if I decide to.
It was bit sudden, but I started the work in Ginza as a greeting.
With Lightning Man.
Huh? With Lightning Man?
That's right. It's an opportunity.
He's a useful one.
Well, if it can't be seen, then it's almost like a wizard.
Be calm. Calm down.
What are you bragging about, Skunk?
You are not even responsible for today's Shinzuku case.
What did you say?
You've been nothing but a liar all along. It's also a lie that you stole Lightning, right?
There isn't an evidence that it's done by you.
You don't trust me?
Of course not. Who would trust you?
All right. Then let me show you the proof. The proof!
Come to Central Park at 6 PM. You alone.
Can you promise? All right? Come by yourself!
All right.
Yay! He's trapped!
-Boss, are you sure you want to do that? -Stupid!
I cannot let that old beard guy make fun of me.
Understand? Listen carefully. We are going to catch him and beat him up.
"Pay back within a year!" That is our motto.
He's here.
Stupid, it's the backward.
I see, so that's Lightning.
-You've come well with it. -Wait, don't touch it.
Ah, I found it, Skunk!
I'm not going to lose him!
Atom!
Shoot.
Stop! Stop it, Atom.
-No, I'm going to get Skunk! -You!
You broke the promise, Mr. Beard.
No. There's a reason for this...
No excuses are accepted now.
Lightning, take your clothes off and finish him!
Wait, Skunk!
Don't lose him!
Ah, hey!
I lost him...
Teacher! Are you all right?
Whatever. I almost got him. What did you just do?
You stupid!
I thought I did a good job, but I only made my teacher angry.
Ah, you are Lightning.
-I forgot about pants. -Pants?
Ah...
What are you here for?
I want to ask you something.
When I touched the legs today, it was hard. It's not like other people.
My legs? Ha ha! I'm a robot like you.
Robot? I am?
Huh? Did you not know? We the robots are people's friends.
Didn't Skunk tell you?
I only know my boss' orders.
But what your boss is doing is bad.
You must not know because you don't have much experience.
All right. Let me teach you!
Ah, the hat...
Lightning, if you pick that hat for him, he would be happy.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Ah! He has no legs.
It's a ghost!
I should have worn pants.
Good. Let's do this!
Here!
Let's have fun, huh?
What is it? Don't mess up!
Did I drink too much?
Are you all right?
Again!
You shouldn't wear clothes.
Give it to them.
-Take this. -Thank y...
It's a ghost!
Lightning. Isn't it lively?
What is this?
No! You shouldn't be playing around with that. It's called a Christmas tree.
It's pretty.
Yeah. We are having a Christmas party tomorrow night at my place.
You should come, too.
I'll ask my boss.
No, you shouldn't ask Skunk. Secretly come. All right?
Would there still be good things?
Of course. The best thing.
It's about telling where Skunk's hideout is.
No. Boss will scold me.
-Tell me, please? -But I'll be in trouble.
You will get complimented by everyone. Please, Lighting?
Ah... Lightning. Lightning!
Hey, where are you, Lightning?
Lightning!
What is it?
"No progress in Skunk case; the incompetence of the police"
Shoot!
What, is that Atom?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
-I met Lightning last night. -Wha, what? So?
We became friends. So I invited him to a Christmas party.
He might come...
-Stupid! -Pardon?
Why would you tell me that now?
It's an opportunity.
Lightning. It's Lightning, right?
Welcome.
Put this on. I wouldn't know where you are.
-Here, let's go to friends. -I have some work.
Work?
I'm leaving.
Wa, wait!
Merry Christmas!
I brought you gifts.
Here, I'll give this to you.
What is this?
Right now.
Teacher!
I don't want to sprinkle those things on my clean body!
-Ah, wait! -Hold on, Atom.
Teacher, if you do that, Lightning will run away.
I tried to stop...
If I can at least see his legs...
Now I can figure out his destination as well!
That pendant has a transmitter.
With this the beard guy is over.
This is his house.
Leave this there, Lightning.
You have to answer me!
Lightning, where did he go? Lightning! You!
It's a ghost!
Help me!
Wh, what is it. It's Lightning.
Where have you been?
-Huh? Spray? -Mr. Beard sprayed it.
He did? Shoot. Stupid Beard.
It's Skunk's hideout.
Boss, it doesn't work. It's not getting off.
Stupid! How useless!
Lightning won't be needed anymore. Now his legs can be seen.
Hey, take this timed bomb to Mr. Beard's house.
Tell him "Merry Christmas."
What a fun sound. I want to have this.
What?
-I don't want to give it to another person. -Stupid! Take it!
It will explode at 12 AM. Cheers!
-Cheers! -Cheers!
A, Atom!
Get rid of it!
Take it!
Stop!
Arrest him!
Stop there, Skunk!
You.
Here!
Where is Lightning, Skunk?
He became an envoy.
What does that mean?
I'm looking forward to 12 AM.
-12 AM? -No way!
Doctor Ochanomizu just called in
and said that Lightning showed up at Atom's place with a timed bomb.
Doctor! What about Lightning?
He ran away.
The explosion is set at 12 AM. We only have two hours!
Ah, we still haven't found it?
What? He went to Tsukuma mountains?
It will explode after 30 minutes.
The front is a national hospital with Japan's best equipments.
That's a problem.
Lightning!
Now 10 minutes.
It's Lightning's foot prints!
Hey! We found the foot prints!
It's heading to the worst direction possible.
Let's fly to the hospital.
Good. Let's get the electronic disassemble missile ready.
Five minutes remaining.
Doctor!
Don't destroy Lightning. He's a poor one.
I can't help it, if something happens.
One minute remaining.
Lightning! Lightning!
20 seconds remaining.
Lightning!
15 seconds remaining.
Ah, it's here!
Five seconds.
Lightning!
It's late now!
Shoot!
Lightning...
Don't cry, Atom.
I understand your feelings, but I couldn't help it.
I don't blame anyone.
But I wanted to talk to Lightning for one more time.
He was my friend...
♪♪ Few more nights,
♪♪ Then New Year's Day
Year 2031, New Year's Day
Doctor Ochanomizu gave me a new year's gift.
I was surprised by it!
Nice to meet you. My sister Uran!
But she's so mischievous that she threw the town into confusion.
Uran! She did it again.
Next on Astro Boy, "Tomboy Uran." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Tomboy Uran"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together