Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Pook.
You cannot do that to pencil.
A robot that takes things granted cannot be called to be complete.
I'm not a complete robot.
Pook.
I'm not finished yet. Look at this.
Pook. That's why you have to fix it at the repair department.
I don't want something like that.
Only my father can touch my body.
Pook, your father, Dr. Tozawa won't return to this island for a while.
-So... -That's why I keep waiting!
I'm going to prove that even an incomplete robot can do anything!
Pook! Wait, Pook!
Pook on Cruciform Island
It's true. It feels real to look from the above. Coral reef is forming a cross shape.
There is this rich vein of uranium under this island.
-Near 10,000 robots are working. -10,000 of them?
Works under the deep ocean is hard for others but robots.
In this place, they not only mine but refine uranium.
-There is a school here as well. -School, too?
It's usually a work training school for child robots and youth.
Even if they are young, they are all excellent engineers.
This is the main computer room.
Well, it's like a heart of this Cruciform island.
It's amazing.
Robots Dr. Tozawa made are all excellent.
He was a genius robot engineer...
That... Speaking of Doctor Tozawa...
Pook!
Running away again... Go back to classroom!
-Please, someone hold that kid! -Okay!
-Ah, what are you? -I'm Atom.
Not your name. Why did you run in?
But...
You are trying to catch me and drag me to the classroom, right?
-I was just... -I don't want to!
Is the manager here?
At Point 103, small submarine volcano has erupted!
Damage is increasing!
Rescue team, go immediately!
Rescue team has left, so it should be all right.
No!
Damage has increased.
Let me see.
I'm going to prove that I can also be a help.
Wait and see, Teacher!
Ah, it's Pook!
Pook! It's dangerous! When did you get there?
Here, Pook. You should run away.
Let me handle the rest.
You are amazing, Atom!
Injured ones should go directly to robot hospital!
Here, Doctor!
Huh? Pook's father escaped the prison? He was in prison?
Yeah...
So, how's Doctor Tozawa?
It seems like he jumped into the ocean with another prison mate.
We investigated the ocean thoroughly, but he's still missing.
And Pook?
No, we didn't tell him anything yet.
Pook must be sad if he hears this.
He remains as an incomplete robot.
We'd like to make him complete no matter how...
This way is the only way to enter Cruciform island.
Finally. We are here. I'm glad we broke out.
The ancestor of
Doctor Tozawa is an expert of spy art called Tozawa Hakunsai.
-What is spy art? -It's a spy technique.
Techniques old spies used to use.
Among them, there is a thing called transformation.
Doctor Tozawa tried to make Pook into such transforming robot.
Transforming robot?
A robot that can change into several forms.
As he worked on making working robots in this Cruciform island,
he made transforming robots in secret. That's Pook.
Pook was an achievement and a cute son
to Doctor Tozawa.
But because of that,
he used all the money funded for making working robots
How bad luck.
Then, he got imprisoned.
That's why Pook's incomplete, huh?
If you think about it, Pook is a poor one as well.
Everyone! Welcome!
It's Mr. Triangle.
This is our ship.
This is our famous scientist's...
grandchild of grandchild of grandchild.
We will acquire everything. We want uranium.
Cruciform island's uranium... We want it. We want everything.
Mr. Rectangle?
Yes, Boss.
How's it coming?
As you ordered, we broke Doctor Tozawa out and snuck into the island.
Good job!
Now we have to seize the uranium storage. All right?
-Yes, sir. -We are on our way!
Ready!
Pook!
Pook, it's me, dad.
-Dad's voice. -That's right. I'm back.
Dad, are you really my father?
Pook!
Dad, Dad!
Yes, yes. How have you been?
-Dad, you are real, right? -Of course.
Who is that?
Ah, thanks to this guy, I was able to get out of prison.
Here, Pook. I'll complete you as a transforming robot.
Really?
That's why I came back.
All I need is this robot.
I equipped it with important components long before.
You only need to change and assemble them,
but the only person that can do that
in the world is this Tozawa.
Now we just have to put an artificial skin on him.
You are just the way I left before.
-Hurry! If day comes, it will be a problem. -It's an important part...
I hear something.
Is it over?
Yes, it's over, Pook. You are now a great transforming robot.
It's a super power I've been dreaming about forever.
You can use that power on your own from now on.
Here, Pook.
Show Mr. Rectangle your power.
Wait. It's dangerous to stand out in such place.
No, you just have to see how this will be a help.
Yeah? If it doesn't seem like a help, you'll have to be held responsible.
Tozawa. In Pook's room.
-He's a dog now! -You shouldn't be surprised yet.
It's a lion!
Do something!
Help me!
Pook, stop it!
Go back.
Good boy.
He's not used to it, but it's a success.
Dad, I did transform, right? This hand really became a lion, right?
-Of course. It was a nice lion. -Dad, thank you!
How surprising.
But he's a monster.
He's not a monster!
All right. Then Doctor,
would you keep the promise? With that one's help?
What's wrong, Dad?
Ah, Pook. I have a favor to ask you.
I can do anything you ask me to do!
That guy asked for that favor.
Could you go to storage?
-Storage... Which one? -The uranium storage, of course.
That's right, kid.
Go turn on the switch of that uranium storage's gate.
Why?
-You just have to turn it on! -What are you doing, Dad?
-I'm trying to test your power. -Test?
Security in that place is very serious.
If you can sneak in and turn on the switch with no problem...
-You will score perfect on that test. Can you do that? -All right. I can do it!
Pook, don't go! Something's wrong!
-What is this? -I don't know.
I know the weak point of this kind of one.
Wow. I'm amazed. He has a great power.
Pook's dad...
Don't make Pook do bad things...
-Huh? What is it? -It's a dog.
Isn't it a robot dog?
What is robot dog doing here?
He must be of some kind of use.
Good boy. Go home.
Hey! Where are you going?
There's a storage there! Hey!
-That one's suspicious. -Hey! Stop!
It's a suspicious dog.
Stop it!
Who is it!
Rectangle owes you one.
What?
We broke the doctor out.
This one ordered to open the uranium storage gate.
Who are you?
We are Triangle. We are the man after Cruciform island's uranium.
Triangle? I've heard of that name. He's the boss of drug trafficking organization.
As you said.
We used you according to our plan, Doctor.
Then... Did you make me complete Pook on purpose?
Of course. We needed Pook!
Pook must have opened the storage by now. We will take all the uranium.
You... How dare you fool me!
I will make you regret...
-Hide that one! All right? -Yes, sir.
Dad! Dad! Where is dad?
Pook, your father's has been kidnapped!
Kidnapped?
Yes. A robot with a horn on his head kidnapped him.
It's Atom!
-I didn't know Atom was a bad one. -Right. We have to go save him!
Where did he go?
Kid, he went over to the storage.
-All right, I'll take care of him! -We will guide you.
Follow me.
We have to hurry and rescue dad!
Pook... The villains...
Pook... Please save my son.
They have all gone to the uranium storage.
Ah, Doctor!
Doctor Tozawa!
Here.
Get rid of them!
Pook!
Pook, stop it!
You are getting fooled!
Good, come on!
Atom! Give my dad back! You kidnapper!
No! They are the one who shot Doctor Tozawa!
Take it, Atom!
Poo, you fool!
Stop it!
Pook!
Where is Pook? Pook!
Doctor Tozawa said...
Dad!
-Pook, is it you? -Dad! Who did this to you?
The ones you took the storage.
Pook, fight for Cruciform island.
Dad!
Shoot!
Don't miss them! In the storage!
Pook! Let's go!
The ceiling is...
It's dangerous. Careful!
Atom!
Ah, it's Pook. Can you be like that too?
Atom, there's a problem.
The villains' submarine took the entire uranium storage!
They did?
-Get on my back. We will chase them! -All right!
We won't miss you.
We are coming!
Okay!
Take it, take it!
Take it!
Ah, not that one! The ship will explode!
-Pook! Hold on! -Atom, I'm over now.
I can't transform now. I'm broken. It's all over.
What are you talking about, Pook! You are still alive.
As long as you are alive, you are still a robot that can be of help!
Let's escape. Hold me.
-Atom. -Why?
My dad passed away, so I cannot be fixed.
Would you still be my friend?
Of course.
-Even though I'm an ordinary robot? -Of course.
Let's do our best and survive.
All right.
Ship Titan is a fancy space passenger ship.
Doctor Ochanomizu and I were invited to Deluxe Moon tour.
Ah! Meteor's coming!
A life-ship of mine got separated from Doctor Ochanomizu
and made an emergency landing on the back side of the Moon.
And there was a very old robot...
Ivan, you've been alone all along...?
Next on Astro Boy, "The Fool Ivan." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Fool Ivan"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together