Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
"Mountain Cabin SL"
Grandpa? Grandpa!
Grandpa...
-Ah, is it you, Sakura? -You've been reminiscing about the past again?
The Pegasus Super Express will be arriving soon.
The Pegasus?
Ah, there is a reserved guest coming for a picnic.
I totally forgot about it.
Be careful, Grandpa.
Dash in a Storm!
Everyone, take a look there. It's a dam construction site.
It's almost complete.
Since the upper dam is worn out, this one's getting constructed with emergency.
Hey! You are next.
Tamao, what are you going to bet?
This one. I got this on my birthday from my mom. There's my name on it.
All right, let's go!
Good, this time for sure!
The trace of the SL rail.
Chugging through there, puffing smokes...
Chug-chug- Let me see!
Kids these days...
Atom lost.
-Give us your most precious thing. -I don't have such thing.
There is one. Your energy capsule.
Huh? But that one is...!
It's only a game.
Give it to us.
All right, Atom, then show us the inside of your body.
What?
My!
-Wow, is it like this? -Let me see well.
Hold on, show me too.
-It hurts. It hurts! -Tamao, I'm sorry.
Thank goodness.
What are you guys doing?
We just looked inside Atom's chest.
Is this station unmanned?
That's right. Stations outside cities are mostly unmanned.
Teacher, what is that big construction?
That's the old upper dam.
Then it's included in our field trip, right?
Of course.
This is the cabin we are going to stay.
Wow, there's cow.
That's of milk cows, the Holsteins.
-Thank you for letting us stay. -No problem.
Ah! The SL!
Wow! It's real!
I've seen it in the transportation museum.
-What's SL? -It's an old steam locomotive.
Such an antique for this era.
What are you doing?
I won't let you talk bad about Degoichi!
Degoichi? What's the point of cleaning it? It doesn't even work.
-Are you out of your mind? -This one can run!
I don't think so. There's no way this junk is going to work.
Gosh! What are you... This thing!
Huh? That kid disappeared.
I'm scared.
-Thunders. -I'm scared.
Ah, it's raining.
I've heard mountain weather is unpredictable, but I didn't expect it to change so suddenly.
It's going to get worse.
-Look at that, Tamao's trembling. -Wow, it's true.
What a coward. It's only a storm.
Teacher, it's from the upper part of the station!
That's not good!
The last express is coming in at 7:30 in the afternoon.
-Atom, go and take a look. -All right!
It's not too late yet!
Atom!
Huh? It stopped.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Atom?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Everyone, cheer up.
Storm will pass by after we sing together.
Let's sing together. Sing.
Warm soup is ready.
Let's have some in the dining room.
Cheer up. It's not good for your body to not eat anything.
Anyhow, what a storm.
I've never seen such a storm since I was born, for 30 years.
30 years? Then you are only 30 years old?
-Scary! -Help!
Calm down. Calm down!
-Sakura, switch it to private powering. -Okay!
-Sir, what's this? -It's a signal for emergency evacuation.
What did you say?
Hello, we are from the cabin in lower region.
Sir, there's a problem.
Dam is about to collapse due to the drainage pump problem.
Evacuate to a safe place!
What? Can you not send us a rescue team?
All transportation have stopped. We can't move because of the storm.
Hello? Hello!
It's broken.
So you don't care about us?!
-Teacher! -Yeah?
I'll go take a look.
Wow, it's up at its limit.
What a crack...
We have to go back to the cabin.
Teacher! There's a problem! There's a crack on the dam!
What?
Huh? Atom, what's wrong with your legs?
It's broken for some unknown reason.
On top of another...
We have to evacuate below the constructing dam in downstream.
That new dam will keep us from that fast current even if the upper dam collapses!
Hmm... But how are we going to evacuate?
That's right!
We could get into the passenger car of Degoichi outside,
and Atom could move that to a safe place, right?
Atom!
It's not possible for Atom now.
If he upholds the passenger car, he wouldn't be able to fly.
His jet legs are broken now.
-My! -I was counting on Atom.
Sorry.
Grandpa, try operating Degoichi.
That's right! You said it can run, right?
Yes. I'm not lying.
Please? Grandpa. Grandpa!
I can't move this SL.
-Why not? -Explain it to us!
We will all drawn like this.
That is...
We are not even sure whether the rail is safe or not.
Besides, the railroad bridge is inside tunnel...
It's all right.
I could take care of that by flying in front of it.
No, it still wouldn't work. I can't do it.
Ah! The house in front...
No, no! I don't want to die! I don't want to die in a place like this!
Grandpa, please? Please save everyone.
Please operate Degoichi. Please?
There isn't a single day in which I haven't looked after Degoichi.
I've always believed that it will run some day.
Besides, it's your dream to make Degoichi run.
If you are not going to do it, then I will!
Hold on!
Everyone, get in Degoichi!
Grandpa.
Sakura, please take care of the passenger car. I'll be in the engine room.
All right.
Everyone, please get in the passenger car.
Hurry, hurry!
Come over here. We will get killed if we stay.
-Atom, let's move. -Okay!
Teacher.
In fact...
Take a look at this.
A robot!
I am an automated system of Degoichi.
To tell it simply, I am just a computer.
Since there was a coal mine near the upper dam,
Degoichi and I transported coal everyday,
but on a stormy day, at the usual curve,
brake suddenly stopped working.
That was my last run.
Then the owner of this house and the coal mine took us in.
He remodeled me like this that time. And...
I've been working in this house since then.
Then what about Sakura, the grandkid?
She's the inheritor of this house.
Her parents were killed in a plane accident
even before her first birthday,
so I've been looking after her since then.
My mission is to protect her forever.
I see.
I'm a retired one like this, but I'll try my best.
As much as possible!
Please insert me into Degoichi.
Sir!
-Hurry. We have to do this fast. -All right!
We are finally going.
Yes, he will take care of it from now on.
Sir, then let's go!
We are leaving!
Yay! We are leaving!
It's moving, moving!
Thank goodness!
-It's done! -It works!
Grandpa, it moved. It can run like I expected.
Atom, fly ahead and check the rails.
Okay!
Yes! Good, sir, please hang in there.
Everyone's life depends on you.
The railroad bridge will be in danger if we don't take that tree away.
Sir, please put forth your energy a little bit more.
We are going reviving Degoichi's strength and SL's soul.
Good job! Run! Run!
There's a problem there.
Grandpa, help me.
Naoto, countercurrent is right behind us?
-Shall we go check? -I don't want to see it. It's scary.
We are going to get caught up.
Sir, please! Speed up!
I see the new dam!
One more round! Cheer up!
All right, an uphill.
It will be safe to go up like this. Don't lose your speed!
Yes, like that!
Yes! We finally shook it off!
-We are safe! -Thank goodness.
-We are safe now. I'm not scared anymore. -Hooray!
We are safe thanks to your grandpa. Thank you very much.
Good job, sir.
Retired? No way. You can still do great jobs.
This is Tamao's pendant. Then...
Ah! So this is why.
This got in and must have interfered the circuit.
No. My energy...
Sir, you did a great job. Now the danger is gone.
Let's take a break. Put on the brake.
Wake up!
Huh? Now he can stop.
This is odd. The brake must be broken.
Naoto, is it pouring outside?
I think so. Would you like to take a look outside?
No. It's scary!
Grandpa?
Sir, try something.
That's right.
This brake lever...
It doesn't move. It's stuck.
Teacher! What's wrong?
Atom, the brake is broken. Please do something!
The brake? Oh my!
It won't work. Gosh, if only I had the energy...!
God...
The rail is over!
What should I do?
There's no path. No path!
That's right!
It's flying. Flying!
Ah, thank goodness.
Thank you. What about grandpa?
-Teacher, are you all right? -Yes, I'm fine.
Grandpa was determined to go through this.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Where's my grandpa?
In fact... Your grandfather was... What should I say...
He was a robot. The automated system.
You are lying! Lie!
There's no way my grandpa was a robot. Lie!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa! Grandpa! Grandpa...
Atom, it seems like we are going to have to
ask Dr. Ochanomizu to fix him back.
Yes. Doctor will fix it for sure.
The magical country of Egypt.
Robot Caesar was destroyed after leaving an odd cane.
What secret does this temple hold?
What are you doing?
Dog and scaraboid robots start attacking me.
It doesn't work. My energy...
You are Cleopatra?
Next on Astro Boy, "Cleopatra's Mystery." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "Cleopatra's Mystery"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together