Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Hey, take this cup.
Thank you.
Hey, what's wrong?
What do you think, Atom?
I think it's a robot.
In fact, there is a rumor that a suspicious guy is walking around this area.
Everyone's scared.
I succeeded getting this one filmed, but...
I failed to trace him.
How does this sound, Atom? Would you investigate this?
Yes!
Hurry, You Three Second-Rate Knights
According to the map, it should be around here...
There is something.
It's a cave.
It freaked me out.
All right, let's investigate it.
We can't use the searchlight since it stands out too much.
It's a perfect place for a suspicious one to hide.
Wouldn't we be able to hear something?
What, it's just a water sound.
What is it? I heard some kind of construction sound.
All right. It's all done.
-Who is it?! -This is Atom!
Atom? This is not a place for someone like you to come!
What?
Get out!
I came here after tracing the suspicious person
who has been appearing near towns.
All right, let me tell you then.
Those suspicious ones are robots here!
We got abandoned by humans and yet we missed our hometown
that we went out to hang out there.
Hang out...?
It's a tragedy of robots made by human beings.
I cannot forgive those who abandoned robots so willfully!
I'm going to get back at them!
What? What did you say?
Move. You'll get hurt.
Stop it!
You can't harm a person!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
All right!
Oops.
Atom, how is this?
Boss, Atom's a good robot. Stop it!
Shut up!
You just have to remain stuck to your department!
Would you like to continue?
Atom, an intelligent robot like you wouldn't understand our rage!
Stop it, Boss!
My.
Robot isn't a disposable machine.
Hey!
Woo! Pitato! Are you all right?
I'm all right. Pitato, let's get out.
Boss is broken.
What about you?
I'm Lili. It's us who you've been looking for.
I'm the fire fighter robot Woo.
I'm the welder robot Pitato.
We were abandoned a few days ago, and we missed where humans live.
That's why we visited there every night. Of course, the boss was angry about it.
Boss? Right...
Boss was very kind to us, but...
Get back at humans? We can't do that! We told him it's too reckless.
Hey, you said you were abandoned. Because of what?
We made a mistake.
But only once!
All of us just made one mistake.
As a nurse at a residence,
I was serving my ill mistress.
I'm tired of that robot now.
Madam, it's time for you to take medicine.
Ah, Miss Lili.
Would you pick some flowers there?
Would two or three be good for you?
Yes. That would be enough.
They are beautiful.
Madam, please cheer up.
You will get better soon.
You are fired!
I was a fire fighter of a city.
I even used to get several recognitions for what I did.
But one day...
Rather than sprinkling water from outside,
I tried to sprinkle water right in the burning place.
But...
Hose!
Huh? What happened? Water isn't coming out.
Oops!
And that's how I got kicked out.
I was working in a welding shop.
It's bit embarrassing for me to tell you, but I was a skillful welder.
But one day...
All right, all right.
We have Pitato, so we don't need it.
Sir, please take a look at this.
It's a brand new welder robot. Here, here.
You are one stubborn salesperson, huh?
Hey, Pitato. You are doing it well.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
Hey, Pitato! Please park my car outside there under the streetlamp.
Thank you.
All right, sir! Leave it to me.
Huh? Sir.
I don't need a new robot!
I don't need it! Not at all!
Here's our brochure.
Well, that's what happened.
However! We aren't outdated yet. We are still skillful.
We can work for a longer time!
But we got abandoned
and were transported
to junkyard.
It's a hell for us robots.
I'm scared.
Why would humans abandon us so easily?
For real. If they are careful about it, they could use us for a longer period of time.
But they just change it to a new robot.
No, I don't want to! No!
You will all get your energy removed and be crushed.
Come you all! Those who can still move, come!
If you don't want to be a scrap metal, follow me!
I see.
Your boss must have also been abandoned like you were.
What are you guys going to do from now on?
From now on?...What should we do?
What do you mean what we should do.
Even if we do get out, people will send us back to junkyard again
You guys can still work, right?
Of... Of course!
-Of course! -For sure!
There still must be places where robots are needed.
Let's check that place.
But would people be able to recognize our ability?
Well... There might be some people who can recognize our ability.
I'm coming with you!
Let's show people that you guys can work greatly!
Yeah!
We should do that for robots like us.
-I see. -Should we do that?
All right! We've decided!
What is it that all three of you want to show me?
Atom! Look, isn't this great?
What is that?
We all built it together.
-Its name is Hopping Plane. -Hopping Plane?
Guys! Get on!
-Let me fly it. -It's a fun thing to ride.
This is Atom.
Oh, Atom, how was it?
It's all right. It's all solved now.
Is that so? That's a relief.
Good job, Atom. Hurry and come back to report it.
That is... I have this thing and I can't go back yet.
Huh? What is it, Atom?
There are abandoned robots here. So I...
-What? -I'll tell you once I get back.
Hey, Atom.
Let's go!
Hop! Step! Jump!
Wow, it's a country of jungle.
-Look at that! -That's great!
This is how the country of construction should look like.
All right, let's go down!
This view looks a bit off.
Developing places would look like this, right?
Would we be able to do it?
It's all right. Cheer up.
What are you doing? We are not the bad ones!
All right, let's defeat this.
Stop it, Woo. If we leave it like this, someone will come.
I'm the sultan of this island. Who are you?
We are looking for some jobs.
We have tons of jobs here. Would you like to work here?
Wow, really?
-Huh? You guys are robots? -Yes!
-You are, you are, and you are, too! -That's right.
All of them here are robots except me.
That hurts!
Don't be jealous! You are a robot!
Ah, it's only for someone with some kind of ability.
Three of them here have great abilities.
Show me, then.
If I give shots, everything gets well.
Lili, do it well.
Wow, this is great. Great. Great!
I can weld anything.
How is it? It's like this.
Stupid! This is useless.
I'm an excellent fire fighter. I can put out anything.
Stupid! This is the smallest volcano in the world! It's our treasure!
Excuse me, Sultan, this was bit too much,
but can't you see how skillful they are?
Please hire all three of them together.
I see.
All right. I acknowledge your abilities.
I'll hire all three of you!
I object!
What? I'm the sultan.
If you don't like what I do, then get out of this country!
Turn your registration cards in.
I'll put in first.
Huh?
Fire fighter robot Woo. His registration has been cancelled.
No way!
Welder robot Pitato. This robot's registration has been cancelled as well.
What has happened?
Robots without registration cards are meant to be disassembled
as soon as they are discovered. Even the sultan cannot probably do anything about it.
Well... Don't be too tough on them.
No!
Run!
Don't lose them! Catch them!
Atom!
Everyone, cheer up. Even without registration cards...
That's right. Let's go to Cosmopolis. There should be some work there.
-Cosmopolis? -It's an independent space country.
An independent space country? That's great.
All right! Kids, let's go!
We are the Cosmopolis interception force.
You have invaded our territorial sky. If you don't get out, we'll shoot you!
Wait!
We are not anyone suspicious. We are here to look for jobs!
You are robots. Do you guys have registration cards?
We will ask you one last time. This is the last time.
Do you have registration cards?
Well...!
We don't even get a chance to beg!
Woo! Run! I'll take care of the back.
Let's meet at the K point of the desert!
In fact, I don't...
I don't want to do this!
What shall we do from now on?
It won't work now. We will get disassembled for not having registration cards.
Hey! Are you all safe?
What's wrong? Cheer up.
We are all finished now.
What do you mean? Even for robots like you...
Whatever! Go back!
There isn't any place where we are needed!
Even if there were, we don't have registration cards.
Kids...
Atom, there's a trouble. There has been an accident at the space factory 1022.
A meteor hit the factory and there was an explosion!
A rescue team was dispatched, but you should be faster.
-Hurry! -All right!
It's a goodbye, Atom.
You are coming with me!
Lili, Woo, Pitato, I need your help.
You will help me, right?
This is the fire accident site of the space factory.
The right wing of the factory is falling off from the main building with fire!
There are many people working in this factory.
Another minor explosion!
We can't wait any longer for the rescue team!
Wow, what an accident.
Huh? What is it? A rescue team?
No, we are not. We are just scrap metals.
A quite damaged vehicle is approaching!
Woo, please put that fire off.
Lili, help the injured ones.
Pitato, let's repair the factory.
Would we be able to do it?
We can do it! We will show them we can work!
Huh? They approached the factory.
They are getting off one by one. It seems like they are robots!
Is the rescue team here yet?
Not yet. It's all over now!
Everyone! Cheer up!
Atom, I'm leaving it to you.
Huh?
That looks like a hose! It's running up!
This one's rescuing the injured ones.
Let's check the situation.
Woo!
I'm fine. Go and help the injured ones...
Hang on there.
Lili!
I'm all right. It's nothing.
Another one is heading to the right wing of the factory!
Hey! Isn't that Woo?
How brave! He's so strong!
It's great! It's amazing!
He's putting the right wing back to the building!
He's welding it right away!
That is...? It's another meteor!
Watch out!
Stato!
Hang on there. It's almost over.
This is amazing. Who are these robots?
The rescue team is here!
You are late! Where have you been?
Excuse us.
Good job! We'll help you!
All right. They are reliable.
They are from earlier!
This one's pressing on as well.
The fire is off! Finally! It's gone!
It's off...
-It's all right now. -Thank you.
It's dangerous.
Lili! Lili!
"Robot Junkyard" Yay! Yay!
"Robot Recycling Factory"
Lili, Pitato, Woo. Thanks all to you.
This is great.
It's bit old, but it's still usable. Atom, I'll give this to you.
Really? Can I really take it?
I'll keep it precious forever.
The mysterious beam that destroys the planetary probe and the space station.
The League of Nations have decided that it's done by Atlas, and dispatched a strong defense force.
Even that Atlas fights a hard battle...
At that moment, a massive spaceship has appeared.
Who would this scary enemy be?
Next on Astro Boy, "Astro Boy vs. Atlas IX"
Please look forward to it!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together