Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Neptune
An unidentified flying object is approaching.
What?
Uranus
Neptune, when the planetary probe robot of Uranus exploded,
we reported about the approach of an unidentified flying object, but...
-Hurry and report it to the Earth! -Yes, sir!
This explosion is a fearful challenge for mankind that staked
its future on space development,
and in view of the results so far, Atlas is the criminal!
That's right! Let's organize the Earth defense force and defeat Atlas!
Let's defeat him! Defeat him!
Astro Boy vs. Atlas IX
The Mars base of the Earth defense force
Captain Kiri!
It's you, Atom! What's up?
Please let me persuade Atlas before we fight him.
Persuade him? About what?
To stop conquering the Earth.
Stupid! Atlas has already begun his work.
There has been a report that several space stations near Jupiter
was also destroyed, making many victims.
But...!
Do you understand, Atom?
It's our mission to defeat Atlas as the Earth defense force.
Don't forget that you are also a member of this force!
World's latest fighter that can even fly in space for a long time.
And the best pilots selected from each country!
And then there is you, Atom.
Besides, in this standard...
We will defeat Atlas for sure!
But before that...
Atom! My brother
was killed by Atlas at the space station near Saturn.
Your brother?
He was my only brother and an excellent scientist.
However...
This is the head office of the Earth defense force.
The PK-3 5th space station between Jupiter and an asteroid was blown up.
Intercept it immediately!
Did you all hear that? It's an order for a sally!
It's here!
Atlas!
Atom.
Atlas, why did you start such reckless thing?
What? What are you talking about?
You killed innocent people and robots at the end of space!
I don't know what you are talking about.
Huh? Then why are you here?
People were looking for me, so I came out for them.
What?
It's a good opportunity. Let me take you down!
Hold on! Listen to me!
Wait!
Atom! Don't fight!
Atlas is your brother, built from the same blueprint as yours!
What?
Atlas and I are brothers?
Livian! I told you not to tell him!
No matter how much you get angry, this is one thing I should say!
So what are you going to do, now that you know we are brothers?
Are you going to side with me? Side with your brother, Atlas?
Th, that is...
Don't worry, Atom.
I don't expect such thing from you.
Maybe I tried so hard to win you over
because of that so-called connection of brothers.
But I have already made decision!
I have to suppress my personal emotion in order to achieve my big dream.
Atom! There is no forgiveness even if we were to be brothers!
Stop it!
Atlas and I are brothers...
Atlas...
If you knew that we were brothers...
What are you going to do, Atom?
If you have found out that we are brothers...
Atom! Atom!
Atom, why are you in such a daze?
Atlas has run away to an asteroid! Let's go!
It's the Super Omegatrone cannon.
I developed it on my own.
It affects Atlas' omega factor and brings in a powerfully destructive power.
Powerfully destructive power?
I'm going to revenge my brother's enemy!
I'm not going to return unless I get rid of Atlas!
Atlas! Atlas!
Atom! Let me finish you off.
Atlas, run!
Captain Kiri's coming to get you with a tremendous weapon!
Do you think I'm going to run away
just because some strong one appears?
Hurry and run!
Shut up!
I got it.
Don't shoot!
Stop pretending you are brothers!
Right now!
Atlas.
Chase him! Don't lose track of him!
Ah, that's...
What is it?!
Several unidentified flying objects are approaching Saturn.
Distance: SA 102, Velocity: V0.8
Is this what Atom saw?
Yes! Captain Kiri also said that it's something we've never seen on the Earth.
-Hmm... Then this is an Invader. -Invader?
It's an alien from an unknown planet, targeting Earth.
So the explosions weren't from Atlas,
but from that Invader, huh?
Dr.Ochanomizu, about Atlas...
Yes, what about Atlas?
Atlas seems to be my brother, built from the same blueprint as mine.
What?
-Is that true? -Yes.
Was Atom's blueprint stolen by someone...?
Who would do such thing?
Atlas, what is this fate?
Minister! This is a video from the Mars base.
This must be reconnaissance unit.
We are currently passing near the Saturn orbit.
The radar has captured something like a command ship.
It's a flying object with tremendous mass. Its diameter is about 10 km.
10 km of diameter?!
If this is the main force, then we must have fought only a very little of it.
It's scary.
Over here!
-What must have happened? -Perhaps the Invader...
Connection lost from the Mars base.
Dr.Ochanomizu,
Yes, UN Secretary General.
A mysterious flying object finally stated approaching the Earth.
There are hundreds of reports from all around the world.
It's already here?
We are trying to hold an emergency conference. Please come!
All right.
Doctor, I'll go back to the force as well.
-Yes, be careful. -Yes, sir!
Invader.
Attention! We will encounter the enemy in 30 seconds!
It's here.
We got rid of him.
It worked!
It totally worked!
There's a problem, Captain Kiri!
-The Invader is... In the Earth... -What?
-It's the Invader! -It's the end of the world!
UN building area also started getting attacked!
All leaders of countries, please evacuate underground.
Shoot... It's an unprovoked assault. Stupid alien!
Watch out!
Ah... My energy is...
Atom, can you hear me?
Ah, Dr.Ochanomizu.
A kind person brought you to me.
Where am I?
This is the relief center next to the UN building.
We evacuated, but 70% of New York were attacked.
Similar thing has happened all around the world.
Thanks to the Earth defense force and you, we got rid of the advance troop, but...
Doctor, what is going to happen to this Earth?
Nothing has been decided in the UN.
We are just trying to unite and get over this situation.
Atom! Are you all right? I've been looking for you.
Are you all right, Captain Kiri?
Yes. But our troop has shrunken to 1/3.
Pardon?
The main Invader force has now entered the Jupiter orbit.
We will fight them tomorrow with our remaining force!
-Atom, please join us immediately. -Yes, sir!
But Atom, I think I have misunderstood Atlas...
It's only a matter of time that the main Invader force approaches the Earth.
We are like this already only with the advance troop.
Doctor, will mankind be finished for real?
I don't want that to happen! I have made many friends!
To imagine to not have them...
I don't want it!
Everyone must be thinking the same thing. That's human.
There is no difference between a human being and a robot in its heart.
Doctor! I'll try asking Atlas.
What?
Atom, Atlas.
If these two brothers work together, the mankind might be saved.
I'm going to Atlas!
Atlas!
I think I just heard Atom calling me.
What?
There's no way.
It's the Invader.
Atlas.
You want me to cooperate?
For those who tried to hurt me?
Atlas, it's not like that.
Captain Kiri, who lost his brother, has also misunderstood something!
Please do understand.
Go ahead and die.
Stupid humans... Just get destroyed.
They are not stupid. They are all good people.
There are my friends!
Friends? What friends?
Robots and humans can't be friends.
That is... There were people who made fun of me for being a robot.
But now all of them are my friends!
There is no difference between a human being and a robot in its heart.
Atom, do you really believe so?
Of course!
That's why Atom is fighting so desperately.
My friend...
My friends are your friends as well! You are my brother!
Humans are my friends? How could that be possible?
Don't you understand, Atlas?
Go back and tell them to screw themselves.
Atlas!
Atlas.
The Earth defense force is!
Having its final battle.
Atom!
If you were human, you would have shed tears.
Tears?
My friends are your friends as well! You are my brother!
Don't shoot!
Shoot... There are so many.
Atom! It's finally time to say goodbye!
Captain Kiri!
I'm coming!
Atlas!
I'll show the Invader what I've got.
That there is someone like me in the Earth as well!
Yes!
Atom! Don't turn your eyes to the small fry.
Our only target is the command ship of the enemy! Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Ah! That's...
That's the base of the enemy. All right!
Atom, you should stay here.
I'm going to show what I've really got from now on.
Atom, let's meet again if our fate allows.
Atlas!
I'm not sure your friends would be my friends as well.
But I'm sure that you are my brother.
I'm entrusting the Earth to you.
If I survive, I'll go after another planet.
Goodbye!
Livian.
I told you to leave; why would you...?
I'll always be with you, Atlas, whether in life or death.
Atlas!
It's a black hole.
Atlas...
Brother!
Scary black clouds that covers the sky of Tokyo.
The monster Mazev on a leopard appeared
and started sprinkling snow on our town.
It turns out that that snow is a scary creature that takes robots' energy away.
How could I get rid of this one?
All right! I have a good idea.
Everyone! Please help me.
Next on Astro Boy, "Snow Leopard"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together