Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Yes, sir. We will do our best to plan this project.
Who are you?
How dare a robot becomes successful earlier than a person?
Robots are supposed to work for people.
In that sense, you are doing great.
Zeus the Robot was born to destroy other robots.
Uran Loves Hitman
Driver, please hurry.
Again?
That's right. It's the robot president of the bank.
So how many times do I have to tell you guys?
-This is not a robot repair shop! -We know that.
Whatever!
First of all, the opponent is a professional hitman. Since he completely destroys the electronic brain,
It's impossible to repair!
But Dr.Ochanomizu, it wasn't completely destroyed this time.
What?
It looks like he just took a moderate approach.
If his memory isn't destroyed, then we might be able to figure out the criminal.
That's why I've brought this.
Let's connect the memory from the electronic brain to computer and visualize it.
This one is!
He's Acetylene Lamp.
Who is he?
He's the one who opposed greatly against the Declaration of Robot Rights.
He thinks robots are supposed to work under human beings.
He was arrested once for abusing a robot.
Let's continue.
It's a robot.
So Lamp used robot to kill robots?
That's why they've been done so neatly.
But how come an assassin robot missed its target this time?
Like the officers said earlier, he might have missed it on purpose.
Anyhow, this robot should be carried to the robot hospital.
All right.
A special newscast.
An important robot figure has been destroyed again.
The criminal seems to be Acetylene Lamp,
who is for robot slavery, and his robot Zeus.
How amazing.
I'd like to go out with someone great like him.
U... Uran.
What a peculiar kid. Atom might get attacked as well.
But he's good-looking.
I like Atom, but I like that handsome Zeus as well.
What is he doing?
-You are a funny robot. -Hey, walk some more.
It looks like fun. Let's go!
Can't you walk faster?
All right. Now move your butt.
Hurry! Move it!
-So fun! -Shake it.
Shake it! Shake it!
That's right. Shake your butt.
-More, more! -Good job!
Hey, I'm the robot assassin Lamp.
Then Uran will be Zeus the assassin robot.
I'm fine with that good-looking robot.
-Lamp the assassin! -Zeus!
We did it!
He's quite good at acting.
Hey, get up.
Move your butt again.
Hey.
He's not moving.
-I didn't do that. -Me neither.
I don't know, either.
-I don't know. -Me neither.
So mean!
-I don't know! -I do not know!
Everyone ran away? How irresponsible!
Uran, what strange thing did you pick up?
It's a robot.
Robot? It's a funny-looking robot.
It must be out of its energy. I couldn't just leave it.
Dr.Ochanomizu, you are being too careful.
There's no way something would attack me.
It's a missile!
Wow! There's a lot of people!
If a missile gets launched here, it will cause a huge trouble.
All right!
As expected, you followed me.
Shoot...!
Zeus! Help me.
Zeus, what are you doing?
Zeus! Help me!
Good! I'm going to hand him over to the police.
Atom's done for now with this.
He was just running out of his energy.
Well, it's a funny looking robot anyway.
Hey, what's your name?
My name is...
I can't hear the important part. What did you say?
Is...
Maybe it forgot its name?
Where are you from?
I'm from...
Gosh! I can't understand a thing!
Maybe something's wrong with him.
Nothing's wrong.
If nothing's wrong, then he should be able to answer.
Then...
Can you do simple math? One plus one is?
My gosh. Jump would be smarter than this!
He is impossible.
Until when is Atom going to stay at the Ministry of Science?
I hope he comes back soon enough.
You don't need to worry. He's my brother.
More than anything, I wonder what he would say if he finds out I picked this kind of robot up.
Wow! Fly! Fly!
Please.
Can I reach Dr.Ochanomizu at the Ministry of Science...
Super Man!
Do you understand? Go back to your house. Can you do that?
It did listen to you, unlike what I expected.
Uran, then what's behind you now?
My gosh!
Can't you understand what I'm saying?
I told you to go back to your house!
My house is here.
No! This is Uran's house.
I hate persistent ones!
Go back!
Uran, what are you doing?
It finally left.
I think he liked Uran very much.
Well, I don't want to be liked by something like that.
Jump, don't freak me out.
It's done now.
Are you awake now, Atom?
Dr.Ochanomizu!
Thank goodness.
Officers as well?
Atom, we have to borrow your power tomorrow.
The Robot UN ambassador is coming.
Then Lamp will...?
Yes. He will target him for sure.
If something happens to the ambassador, there will be a huge problem.
It's about keeping the police's pride. Please help us.
All right!
Is Atom still with Dr.Ochanomizu?
He will be back soon. Ah, I failed.
I won!
I'll wait for Atom out here!
Even though she is bit mischievous
Innocent smile on her face
Uran
Everyone's calling
Prettier than flowers
More refreshing than wind
Uran
When you are around
We always have fun
She likes her brother Atom
And she likes songs and dreams
Uran is like an angel
Everyone's calling
Hey!
Uran!
Since when were you friends with him?
I don't like it.
I guess robots get along well.
No!
Has Uran ever liked this kind of robots?
She always has.
No!
Be quiet!
I said no!
If you don't go back, your owner will be worried.
I'm telling you that I'm interested in someone good-looking like Zeus.
If you were little bit more good-looking, I would hang out with you,
but you are not my type.
If I were little bit more good-looking, you would hang out with me, right?
Uran!
Atom.
-What are you doing here? -Nothing.
-Then let's go back. -Okay!
The Robot UN ambassador is coming tomorrow.
Hey, Zeus! Let's plan for tomorrow.
You understand, Zeus? Don't be so tepid like you were with Atom.
Something's weird with you lately.
Completely destroy your target.
Do not let it get fixed. You understand?
...Yes.
I think it will be all right with all these guards, but...
Dr.Ochanomizu, would Lamp really show up?
Yes. The Robot UN ambassador is the best target for Lamp.
So mom and dad told me to wait at that immigration gate.
But because someone important is coming, no one can enter.
Doctor!
Uran, what are you doing here?
It seems like she's lost. Do you know her?
Yeah, well.
She's lost?
Please take care of her.
I have to go back to my location. Excuse me.
Uran, you are lying about being lost, right?
But I really wanted to see Zeus in person.
But Uran, this is not some game.
Dr.Ochanomizu, the plane is here.
I can't help it now. Uran, don't get away from me.
Okay!
What is this...
Doctor, the ambassador is finally here.
Is Atom waiting as arranged previously?
Atom's here as well?
Right now, Zeus!
It's Zeus! So good-looking!
Lamp, I'm not going to miss you this time!
Zeus, shoot Atom!
Go Zeus!
He's pretty even with Atom.
Amazing, Zeus.
Shoot...
Atom, don't move. If you do, she will be destroyed.
It's the tear gas.
Zeus! Hold this one hostage and run!
Atom!
Zeus!
You!
You are...
I'm the brain circuit of Zeus.
I didn't want to kill robots. That's why I ran.
Dang...That's why Zeus was acting so slow when he attacked Atom.
I was determined to never go back...
Because I told you that you are not good-looking?
I wanted to be friends with you.
I'll be your friends from now on!
Because you knew that I'm Zeus?
I've killed so many friends because he told me
that he would turn me into this once everything is over.
You! It's not over yet!
I'm not going to listen to you from now on!
Where are you going?
Bye, Uran!
Zeus! Come back!
Now Zeus will be happy as well.
He's finally free.
I'm fine with that less good-looking robot. I'm going to be his friend.
Odin, who was worshiped by the Vikings thousand years ago.
We left for Greenland to find its ruins.
But the guide, Captain Crowd, seems to be hiding something secret.
Javi boy.
Giants like snowmen.
Full of mystery and dangers!
And the Odin we finally discovered was...
Next on Astro Boy, "The Devil's Place in Odin"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together