Iron-Arm Atom
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a hundred-thousand horsepower engine
Iron-Arm Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-fold power
Iron-Arm Atom
Prof. Ochanomizu, the new Minister of Science and Technology
has arrived from the USA, today.
We will commence the new minister's press conference now
Hey, move aside! The light's blinding, hey!
Huh? How dare you call someone with just "hey"!
First of all, the government has promulgated
the Robotic Rights, Prof. Ochanomizu.
Would please explain briefly what the Robotic Rights are?
Fools!
You people, don't you even care?
Listen. Robots also possess 'personality'.
That is to say
Robots stand on equal ground with humans now.
Fool!
Yes? Prof. Ochanomizu?
Mmm... well, that's that.
Heh heh, piece of cake
Just like the Professor, it was an excellent speech.
No... it just blurted out.
It's embarrassing.
That's right. I haven't introduced yet, Atom.
My old friend, also called 'Mr. Mustachio'...
Mr. Mustachio?... Strange name.
I have a wonderful name, 'Ban Shunsaku'!
Now he's an elementary school teacher, but he was once...
A private detective.
Also a judo expert.
Also a flower master.
But, his true identity?
Ban Shunsaku the Mustachio!
That's it! Hahahaha
By the way, Professor, the reason why
I had to fly here today is none other than
Atom's school entrance, isn't it?
As expected. You're quick.
Since the Declaration of Robotic Rights guarantees
equal education of humans and robots.
I've seen an elementary school before.
It's where children study...
Indeed! They also play a lot of sports and games.
But, the most important of all
is to make friends with everyone.
Friends?
Saving our Classmate
We have 4 people, including me here.
We have 3, it's decided.
Osamu, how about you?
Five.
Hmm... 14 including me, huh...
It's 13.
Hmm. Does this mean I have to rely on the last resort?
Last resort?
Come, enjoy the election speeches. Hahahaha...
The teacher's here!
(Sit down!) (The teacher's here!)
Children, Let me introduce you a new friend.
He's Atom, and from today
we will all study together.
Nice to meet you!
(How?) (Why?)
That's right, Atom is a robot. But robots
are also allowed to enter the school. You all know, don't you?
Sir!
I don't want to study with a robot!
(Yeah yeah!) (Don't want!)
Why is that so?
Because... to say... Robots are... robots...
That can't be your reason.
Atom, your desk is over there
Yes.
Hey!
Next, as I said before
because our class captain has transferred,
we will hold a new election of a class captain.
What's a class captain?
Simply, he's the boss... nope, the leader of this class.
Then, I will leave everything to you children.
(You, who are you gonna choose?) (Well...)
Silence!
Then, we shall proceed with the class captain election.
We will now listen to the speeches
of Kenichi and Shibugaki, our candidates.
If I become a class captain, first,
I will purge all kinds of violence from this school.
Hey! Are you saying that I'm violent?!
I was not referring to you.
What did you say?!
Second, I will make a baseball and a football team
to strengthen our solidarity.
Agreed!
Hey, President!
Come come, now
I... no, if I become a class captain, first of all,
advance the lunch time to the 2nd period...
Wow~~ Agreed!
...which cannot be permitted whatsoever.
Then instead, if I become the captain
I shall invite you for free to the Far East Asia's best Mechanic Circuit
currently being constructed by my father!
Here you go!
(We've waited for so long!) (Good, good!)
Then we shall proceed with the voting.
Those in favour of Kenichi, press the green button
Those in favour of Shibugaki, press the red button
Turn it on~! Cool! Cool!
Go go! Hey, go! Hey, go~
(Go, Kenichi!) (Go go!)
(Go!) (Hey, go!)
Here here here! Ah, ugh...
J-Just a little more! Hey, just a little...
(Kenichi, be strong!)
D-Damn... a draw, huh... It's showdown vote now.
Strange... 15 to 15
There are 31 students in this class
Is there anyone who didn't press the buttons?
Atom, it's you! Press it, quickly!
You get a chance, too.
Y...Yeah...
Ah! Oh...
Then Kenichi is our new class captain!
(Hurray!) (Congrats~)
Hey you, so you chose Kenichi, huh?
why is it bad to choose Kenichi?
Nothing's decided!
It's your fault I'm not the class captain!
Only by a single vote...
Aah, I wish I was the class captain! Just once...
I wish everyone would call me "Captain"!
Your speech was interesting
But I thought Kenichi was much better
What the!
Stop it now!
Oh? What now, Kenichi, since you got a vote from the robot
You've decided to play up to him?!
How in the world did a robot
enter our school, the school of us noble humans!
Get out! Get the hell out!
(That's right!) (Go away!)
The teacher told us, too!
That we all should get along with each other!
Huh? What the hell, now you're all friendly with the robot!
You... You!
It's the teacher!
Ah, no... we're in trouble...
Where's the teacher?
It's such an obvious lie.
Right!
Atom, this is the specimen room.
This is a 'wolf', an animal of family Canidae
It grew extinct around 100 years ago
Try pressing that button
Wow! Cool!
It's a three-dimensional hologram
It's so real, isnt it?
Where are the bones of robots?
There's no such thing
Yes? Then after use...
Take care of it this way.
What do you mean by 'after use'?
You know, Midori, it's for fun!
Come over here!
Huh? But it's for boys only!
Let's go, Atom!
There!
No! You're not supposed to use your hands in football!
Ah! I don't know...
Atom, if we lose the ball
We're gonna get an earful from the teacher!
I'll go fetch it!
No hands used...
It's unbelievable!
It's still under construction
That why, try not to get found out, you guys
Heh heh heh, Wanna go for a ride?
Of course!
Then, tomorrow's runoff ballot... vote for me!
Runoff ballot?
Do we have another election?
Yeah. Without robots, this time.
Another election, heh heh...
By now, Mum must have taken care of everything.
I came to give you a word of advice, principal.
A-advice?
You should cancel the admission of the robot this instant
and rehold the class captain election.
That is something I've decided according to my convictions,
so I'm afraid I must refuse.
How could you!
Principal, this school's gym...
who sponsored its construction?
The construction of the school...
I am aware!
Ban, my friend, about that,
try to understand more...
I refuse such comprehension as well!
What?
Moreover!
Tomorrow, you have to choose me!
Wow! It getting palsy!
Robots are artificial.
Therefore they are beneath humans!
Those "beneath", are unworthy!
Their kind should just be expelled!
What in the world are you trying to say, you hysterical raccoon!
Raccoon!
Such hurting words to an innocent child,
only that, I can't forgive!
What do you mean by 'raccoon', you dumpy old mustache geezer!
Atom, you should go back
Yes.
Still... you had to make a fuss!
Fools like you,
understanding Atom's feeling, that is indeed
what I can't stand the most!
The likes of robots should just disappear!
Impudent robots...
The very fact you've dared to enter a school of humans is a mistake!
Get out! Your likes, should just disappear!
Get out! Go away!
"Rocket Coaster", the best one here
Have you got aerial whirls as well?
Of course! Right over there!
Huh? There's no rail!
Really!
We can't ride that
Don't worry now
The magnetic field acts instead of the rails
Everyone, get in!
Come on, get in
Make sure to fasten your belt
We're setting out!
So, how is it?
Wow, it's great!
It's fabulous...
It's so cool I can't stand it!
Wow!
It's a kick!
2nd round now!
I thought we were going to shoot out to the sky!
3rd round!
Busy as a bee. Just so full of letters...
Oh, Atom, welcome
How was it? First day of school?
Did you have fun? Anything happened?
Uh... are mothers... always that scary?
What? Not all mothers are scary...
but there are some exceptions.
Huh? What's going on?
That's!
Baldy, your insolence knows no place!
What do you mean by baldy! Identify yourself, monster!
We'll have you fired!
You think you have the right?!
Yes,... what? Shibugaki and friends are in trouble?!
What?!!
Mother!
What should we do... Just what...
Help me!
Ah! My baby!
Shibugaki's father?
What is exactly going on?
An instability of trance caused a massive energy
to burst in at once!
The problem is, the magnetic field
is getting stronger!
Th-Then... what will happen?
The volatile energy of the magnetic field will compress, and pile up
and exactly 19 minutes from now, this vortex of energy...
will penetrate through the field and explode...
Explode?
Do you understand, Atom?
Mum, so to say, a Mother,
is a person who gives birth and raises a child. A kind and noble person.
Sometimes she might get angry
But that's only because her child is so lovely, and also...
Oh, Mr. Mustachio Today Atom asked a great deal of...
What? Right away.
I will dispatch a robotic rescue party immediately.
Damn!
Oh! Professor Ochanomizu!
I've been waiting for you!
Planning to jump into the magnetic field?
3 minutes to explosion.. Ah...
What could we possibly do in this situation!
Right! Atom might be able to do something
Yes?
Atom, you're the only one who can save the children now
No, I believe that it's possible only because it's you.
Professor!
Impossible, even the rescue party couldn't!
And what could a small robot child possibly do?
Do you understand, Atom?
If you jump into the course, you could end up in the magnetic field
When you jump in, go around the coaster's direction
and block the coaster's speed
then move it to the opposite course.
Remember your training in the circus.
That is the trick.
Atom! Go save everyone!
Save them, our friends...
Friend...
Atom!
He jumped in!
Ah... 1 minutes...
30 seconds...
8... 7... 6...
Atom!
Ugh... Mum!
I'm sorry! I was so scared!
(So scary!) (I'm sorry!)
Maybe we should make Atom a father and mother
Atom~!
Atom!
Thank you!
Dad, sorry! Ouch! Please...
[Next Episode]
I'm "Atom". Professor Ochanomizu said
that he's going to make a father and mother for me!
I was so happy I just rushed to the Ministry of Science and Technology
What? They were abducted?
How could this happen...
Who's that? Who's calling me...
Ah! You... So you're 'Atlas'!
Next on [Astro Boy]...
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight eyes
Laser Blast hands
Seven-fold powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together