Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Don't miss that elephant.
Gotcha!
My! It's coming here!
Hey,this is a real elephant.
Where did this come from?
This is a real baby elephant. I'm going to make it my pet.
Stop it!
It's prohibited to capture real animals.
Don't you dare to stop me, stupid robot!
I'm sure it came from some hunting prohibited area nearby.
This is a safari park made only with robots, right?
It's his fault for coming here.
Why can't I hunt it?
Wh, what are you!
I'm Atom. Stop it!
You are a robot, right?
Hey!
Come here.
The Little Elephant Pura
This place is quite big for a robot safari park.
Ah, there's the border.
Hello! A real elephant has come here.
What are you talking about?
But look...
-Then go over to that side. -Yes, sir!
There is an invisible beam fence around this place.
Then where did this elephant come from?
It can never enter this place! It must be a robot.
No, this is a real...
Leave. I'm busy.
This is a real one for sure.
But it is true that it did come from somewhere.
Hey, where did you come from?
Hold on.
Atom, Atom.
He's late. Where did he go?
Doctor Ochanomizu. Welcome to our safari park.
Hey, Doctor Hura.
How is it? Isn't this a wonderful park?
I feel reluctant to use animals for hunting even if they were robots.
You are still too serious.
Real animals are decreasing in its number recently.
So I developed animal robots that's the same as real ones
so tourists can observe them and enjoy hunting.
That's why I opened this safari park in this vast field of Africa.
This is the improved version of flamingo.
If you insert money here...
-How is it? Do you want a glass? -I'm all right.
I got rid of three lions today.
Wow, I caught a leopard and two hippos.
Everything you need for safari,
from guns to clothes, you can borrow here.
There are different classes; Class A gets a jeep and two assistant robots.
Class B only gets a jeep, and Class C gets one assistant robot.
This is just beyond my imagination. Thank you for inviting, but I'm leaving now.
Wait, I called you because I wanted to ask you a favor.
Please come here.
Hey! Wait! Where are you going?
I see. He thinks I'm his mom.
Watch out!
One, two, three.
This was a robot as well.
Hey! Come out now. It's not scary anymore.
Look, bad snakes are...
Hold on!
I can't leave you alone since it's so dangerous around here.
We robots are also friends with animals, as well as with humans.
All right. Since it's hard to call you, I'm going to name you Pura.
Pura. How is it? Isn't it a good name?
Would you guide me to where you first entered this park?
It would be tough if another animals enters.
This is a place for repairing hunted robots.
Anyhow, Doctor Ochanomizu,
please take a look at that.
It's a very aggressive elephant called Zora.
Very aggressive?
All animal robots here are designed not to take people's lives.
However, this Zora is different. It kills people ruthlessly.
Why did you build such dangerous thing?
It's thrilling.
There wouldn't be any thrill if there weren't a crazy beast.
But this one is too dangerous. I need your help.
My help?
Please rebuild this Zora to listen to what workers here say at least.
Do you think I'm going to help you?
Please, Doctor Ochanomizu. Visitors are also expecting a lot from Zora.
It sure leaves me some profit as well.
This is not right. You are doing this for the sake of money...
That's right. I became a scientist to earn money.
A man like you is not suitable for the world of science.
Doctor Hura, a real elephant is shot dead near the spring.
What? Is that true?
There are real animals outside this park, right?
Then there must be some place where they enter through.
-That's impossible! -How come?
That's the surveillance panel.
It can detect even a little bird.
Then how did the elephant enter?
We will investigate it later.
Later isn't enough. Another similar accident will...
Anyhow, you should hurry and finish rebuilding Zora.
I can't take it anymore!
Doctor Hura, so you don't mind getting wild animals killed?
If I didn't invent animal robots,
more wild animals would have been killed by humans!
Help!
Wow, Zora moved.
My gosh. I can't do anything now.
It's beyond curbs.
Atom is the only one who can take care of this situation.
Pura, not ready yet? It's evening already.
Pura, do you understand?
I don't want Doctor Ochanomizu to worry, so I'm going to go tell him what happened and come back.
So please wait here for a moment.
I'll soon be back.
You are late, Atom.
Sorry? So Doctor Ochanomizu already went out with Doctor Hura to find me?
This is great.
Where would Doctor Ochanomizu be?
Ah, that's...
Where did that robot take the baby elephant?
I'm going to find it no matter what.
Ah, he hasn't given up on Pura yet.
Ah! There it is!
Good, catch it!
Yay! I got it.
Pura!
Dang...
It's that robot again.
All right. I'll let you go.
Pura, it's your bed.
Good night. You are safe here.
I have to go find Doctor Ochanomizu now.
Do you feel alone? I'm here next to you. Relax and sleep.
All right, good boy.
My, my. You are such a baby.
Doctor Ochanomizu.
I'll spend the night with Pura tonight. Please do understand.
Wow, it's pretty cold during the night.
What's wrong, Doctor Hura?
Doctor, it seems like we got into trouble again.
Wh, what?
Wh, what is it?
Doctor Hura, what in the world has happened here?
What are cannibals doing here?
Those are also the robots I built.
-Then stop them! -Well that is...
They will let you go if you pay $100.
This is too much. Making money even with this?
If you pay extra $500, they will make you their chief. How does that sound like?
Atom, where in the world are you?
Hey, Pura.
Where are you going? Don't go too far.
Pura!
Watch out!
You must be Zora, right?
What a suction power!
I could get rid of it if Pura weren't with me.
It's not that smart.
That's not your mom, Pura.
There it is!
Follow it immediately. Don't lose it!
Huh? What is that?
Waterfall...
Let's take a rest.
Ah, Pura. Where are you going?
What's wrong? Is something there?
All right. I'll go check it, so you wait here.
Ah, it's a cave.
There was a passage in this kind of place.
Pura and his mom must have entered through here.
Pura!
Don't do anything suspicious. If you do, the baby elephant won't survive.
Atom, right? What's behind that waterfall?
Are you not going to tell me?
There is a passage leading to where wild animals are...
-What? Real animals? -Is that for sure?
All right, guide us to there.
Hey, surely they are not going to cut our heads off for real, right?
They will just pretend to do it, unless they have some kind of breakdowns.
Breakdowns? My, that's horrible.
It's Zora.
It's looking this way.
Hey! I made you!
Help. My blood is draining to head.
You will fall if you keep wriggling.
Stop!
Hello, hello. Control Center!
Zora has escaped the surveillance and has invaded the wild animal protection area!
Atom, don't do anything suspicious.
If you do, I'm going to shoot you.
This is great.
-Look at that. -Oh, that's a legion of elephants.
I'm going to enjoy a real safari after not having one for a long time!
Huh? Are you guys really going to shoot real elephants?
There was a passage behind the waterfall. We can just say that we thought this place was also a part of the park.
Atom! Don't cut in.
This is the place for perfect aim.
Pura!
Zora. Good!
Zora! I'm going to fight you!
Here, Pura. Now it's time to say goodbye. Go ahead.
You can be happiest when you are with your kind.
I had no idea there was this kind of natural passage behind the waterfall.
I should have investigated it more thoroughly.
I just didn't know about this passage, but Pura's mom was...
She's beyond recovery now because of Zora.
No, it's all good now, Doctor Hura.
Ah, that's right! Let's build an ocean safari next time.
It will be a great item!
Cannibal whale this time? Don't invite me.
Atom! Where are you? Let's go back now.
Pura, you really are doing your best to live on.
I'm relieved now.
Goodbye, Pura.
The Bee Island is full of all kinds of flowers!
It's a beautiful island.
Uran! You will go missing if you run around like that.
Odd things keep happening on this island.
There is a huge underground city in that creepy cave there...
Swarm of honeybees ruling over people.
Queen Bee, you are here now. Let me deal with you!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Secret of Bee Island." Please look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "The Secret of Bee Island"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together