Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Therefore, the answer to this question is...
It's snow! It's snowing!
Hey! Be quiet!
Teacher! It's snowing!
What in the world are you talking about?
It's too early for snow to come. Be logical.
But look! It's snowing for real.
Atom, are you going to be like this, too?
I know there have been abnormal weathers,
but there's no way there would be snow in Tokyo in October.
What in the world is happening? The world is upside down now.
Mom! It's snow! It's snowing!
Oh my, in this weather...
That's strange.
I'm coming.
Uran's so happy.
Something's weird.
Uran? What's wrong?
That's odd. She should have her energy left.
My.
What happened?
My energy is...
What's wrong, honey?
Space Leopard
Snow! It's snow! Yay! Look at this!
Atom! Come here.
Okay!
Hey, Atom. Don't go out!
Huh? Why not?
I don't think the snow out there is normal.
Robots that get snowed on by this abnormally early snow
are losing their energy and collapsing all over the country.
According to the Ministry of Science,
This snow isn't an ice crystal but a compound of special substance.
Scientists are working to figure out the cause.
Do you understand, Atom? Until this weird snow case gets resolved,
you should stay home and take a break from school.
Don't come outside.
Huh? Is it broken? This stupid old car.
Huh? Energy meter is 0.
Teacher, look.
Even car energy got affected by this snow.
Atom, we can't be like this forever.
You should fly and go back first.
This is an emergency umbrella. It should be better than nothing.
Thank you!
-Be careful. -Okay!
I'm home.
Atom, you are all right.
What about mom and Uran?
They fell down in the yard.
They are changing their energy capsules.
Atom! You too?
It's done. It's all right now.
Atom, it's a call from Dr.Ochanomizu.
Atom! Big problem!
The snow started to take even the electricity away!
What?
Currently, this phone line is doing okay,
but soon the entire system in Tokyo could be down.
Please come to the ministry as soon as possible. Use the monorail!
Yes, sir!
-This is? -It's snow crystal.
It's moving.
It's the snow that's falling now.
It looks like snow outwardly, but each of them is an organism.
Snow is an organism...?
It's like amoeba.
The scary thing is that it absorbs the energy around it.
This stagnant black cloud 1,000 meters up above the Tokyo sky
is the source of this snow.
Besides, this cloud doesn't just sprinkle snow;
it retrieves snow that has absorbed energy.
Pardon?
And in an hour, it becomes twice its size.
At this rate, in less than a week,
entire Japan will be covered in this mysterious black cloud.
Doctor! Is there anything we can do?
I sent out a few investigating planes, but they all crashed.
Now I have no choice but to ask you.
I know it's dangerous, but could you, Atom?
Of course!
This rocket can reach that black cloud 1,000 meters up above
even if it gets its energy absorbed.
After that, Atom, you will only have your energy left with you.
Be careful, Atom.
Ah, that is...!
All right! It's that! I'm coming!
Leopard...
You were lucky to get here. But now it's over.
Lupe, destroy this one!
You are responsible for sprinkling this weird snow, huh?
All right!
I'm losing my energy.
Lupe, absorb as much as energy you'd like.
Shoot. This one absorbs energy.
It won't work.
All right. I'll breathe jet gas in!
Right now! I'll beat you before I run out of my energy!
Yay! I beat him! Hooray!
Stupid. This one doesn't have any forms.
Let me go.
I'm losing my energy.
How's the energy-absorbing organism I found?
Do you see how great this Lupe is?
It's even beyond Atom's capacity...?
Let's get Atom back!
Without energy, it's miserable even for the civilized world.
I don't know how this will turn out.
Announcement to all citizens of Japan.
From now on, I, Dr.Mazev, am your ruler.
If you disobey me, I will turn entire Japan into the Stone Age.
Artificial skin 3-degree damage. Repair complete.
FP joints 1-degree damage. Repair complete.
Electronic brain OK.
Nuclear motor OK.
Repair complete. Power on.
Good job, Atom.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of help, Doctor.
No, thanks to you,
I finally figured out the controller of this mysterious snow.
Who is that Doctor Mazev?
According to the data of the Ministry of Science, he used to be a nuclear scientist.
It seems like he was involved in studying nuclear fuel waste management.
It's just my opinion,
but he must have discovered that energy-absorbing microorganism while studying that.
Then that flying leopard might be related as well.
Researchers are going over that leopard's tail you held onto,
so some results will be out soon.
Until then, go back home and take some rest. Mr.Beard is waiting for you.
I never knew this kind of thing would prove to be useful in the 21st century.
Teacher, until when would this continue?
Well, I don't know about that. Only human children are happy about this.
Would robots be banned from going out forever?
It will be resolved soon. This kind of situation can be romantic sometimes,
but if this continues, it would be so uncomfortable.
Hey! Is the engine out of order again?
Hey! Move!
Even horses have forgotten to work.
Here. I'll give you some energy. Now move.
I'm home!
Welcome.
I'm so thankful Atom's back.
Is something wrong?
Well... Since Uran can't go out, she's feeling bored.
Hang out with her.
Uran! Uran!
It's odd. Where would she...
Uran!
Here. Here, Atom.
Uran, you can't go out!
I'm all right. I have this Christmas candle.
That won't do anything. This snow isn't normal.
Snow is snow.
Look. As long as I have this fire, they won't fall on me.
I'll show you something more interesting!
Look!
How is it? Isn't this awesome?
How can snow that can absorb all kinds of energy be affected by a mere candle?
What? Snow is afraid of fire?
Would that be possible, Doctor?
Is that so? I didn't notice since it was too simple,
but maybe it can absorb artificial energy
but not natural energy.
What do you mean?
For example, if I drink milk, I will get diarrhea.
I see! So this snow can eat artificial energy
but is allergic to natural energy?
Probably.
Finally the TV and phone lines got destroyed by the snow.
Atom, I'm sorry but please come to the ministry again.
Yes, sir!
Underground. What's wrong?
-Let me out! -I don't' want to stay here anymore!
When are you going to let me out?
Outside. I see outside.
You can't go out now. Be still!
I wasn't born to be locked up in this kind of place.
They are newly born robots.
They finally finished their training for human society
and were about to become independent, but then this snow happened.
When would we be able to let them out?
Poor them.
Atom, this is the identity of that scary enemy.
It's the magnified image of the leopard tail you held. Look at it carefully.
Something same as snow is continuing to get stuck and off.
It's called a colony.
Little organisms stick together
and form one big shape.
So that leopard is only a shape
made out of little organisms?
Corals and sponges are also
colonies made out of little bugs.
I see. That's why it all spread out and attacked me when I had thought I had finished it.
That's right, Atom.
We have to cut them at once while maintaining its integrated form.
At once.
What should we do?
I hereby notify the Minister of Science, Doctor Ochanomizu.
Hand over the Ministry of Science to me today!
That can't happen!
There's a pivotal system that controls Japan's energy under this building!
That's why I'm going to take it.
If you refuse to do so, entire Japan will turn into a country of death.
What in the world?!
Hold on! Mazev!
So he was after the dominance over energy.
There is the Energy Capsule Department in the Precision Machinery Division,
which is considered as the heart of all robots! Oh my!
If he takes it over, then we the robots will have to listen to him, right?
Huh? Yes...
Doctor, send me again.
But...
I have an idea.
If the enemy is a colony, then let's make a colony as well!
That's why we need your help!
I will do anything to be able to go out!
That's right! We were born to help people!
That's right! First of all, we can't let that
bad guy take our life, our energy away! We can't let that happen!
C-16 will be the shoulder joint of right arm!
All right. Atom will be the last.
Okay!
Now it's complete.
I trust you, Atom.
With this may, we wouldn't be affected so much even if we get our energy absorbed.
All right. Let's go!
Stupid, silly robot's here again.
Lupe, go take care of it!
You understand? All of it. You have to follow the orders of my electronic brain!
Yes, sir!
That's it. Spread out and attack!
Energy!
B part, zero energy!
This part is over as well.
Doctor! Our colony won't last like this!
Hurry!
No news from the weather satellite yet?
Doctor, there's a lightning cloud developing at 30Km WNW!
-Can you hear me, Atom? -Yes, sir!
All right! Robots that are still with energy, be on your full speed!
Little more! Cheer up!
How's natural energy lightning?
We finished it!
What is this, Lupe!
Help!
Dr.Ochanomizu! We did it.
Good job, Atom! Now robots are safe!
-Yay! Snow's gone! -Snow's gone!
Jump, let's go for a walk.
It seems like even that scary snow cannot defeat solar energy.
From old times, sun is known as the grace of Mother Nature.
Anyhow, Atom. So what about your classes?
Right! I forgot to go to school!
Who in the world forgets about going to school?
Now that snow is over, special vacation is over as well.
Do you understand? Studying is the most important thing for a child.
If you get even one tardy, they will start doubting our home discipline.
-It's been gone for a long time. -Pardon?
Bye!
Do you guys have mischievous sister like Uran?
She always causes troubles,
but she started doing strange things again, saying she's looking for a robot god.
The encyclopedia computer in amusement park caused an error after getting Uran's question.
Thanks to her, there's another turmoil!
But since she's a cute sister, we can't help it.
Next on Astro Boy, "Uran's God" Please look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Uran's God"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together