Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
-Ah, it's Atom! -Atom's here.
Atom, come down.
Huh? What's that?
-Isn't that Atom? -That's Atom.
Good.
All right. Here.
The Devil's Balloon
Atom! Why did you do such thing?
It's not me.
There was a tip-off that Atom made that balloon bomb by leading other robots.
I don't know anything about it.
-Don't you have some grudge against human? -Grudge? No...!
They said you also have problem with people's attitudes towards robots.
I really have nothing to do with it!
Tawashi! Do you believe such reports without any thoughts?
Police is on the side of citizens.
It's a sure thing that a police listens to the citizen's voice.
Atom would never do such things. Do you have any proof?
Proof?
All right! I'll get that proof. Be ready!
It upsets me to hear such things.
Atom, stop it.
I understand your feelings, but if you do such needless things, others will...
-Hold on. This... -What's wrong, Doctor Ochanomizu?
They might set you up in a trap.
What? Me? Why?
No, I suddenly just feel like it.
I'm going to go and ask!
Wait! Where are you going?
Atom!
Everyone! It's me, Atom. Please tell me about the balloon.
Atom?
Ah, it's Atom!
Everyone, please listen to me. I'm really...!
Go away! Now I can't play baseball.
I hurt my eyes because of you!
Wait! That wasn't me!
Leave! Go away!
Hey, are you all right?
Get your hands off!
You devil! What are you doing to my kid?
Please hold on. I...
-Oh my gosh! It's Atom! -It's the bomb! The Atom bomb!
Oh my! Help me!
-Help! -Ah!
-Atom is a bomb. -Mom told me robots are dangerous.
That's not true! Atom is our friend.
Isn't that right, Kenichi?
Yes. It's not right to blame someone for something so unsure...
But Atom got called by police.
That's why I told you not to trust robots.
Shibukaki! Have you forgotten that Atom saved you several times?
That might have been his shrewd way to deceive us.
Oh my! Listen to what he's saying!
Anyhow, now the problem is whether we approve his attendance or not.
Nay!
If Atom comes, let's all go to the theme park. Huh? Everyone.
Okay!
No way!
I don't care if Atom's here or not.
I'm against it!
My brother got hurt by the Atom balloon, and he can't come to school for two months.
I... I don't want to see Atom!
Human would cry in times like this.
Shoot! Shoot it down!
When I tell you to shoot, it means to aim and shoot!
I'm sorry. But what if I did aim and failed?
-You have to keep that failure in mind and aim. -Pardon?
Don't miss it! Never miss it!
What is it? It's coming here!
Stop it! Stop! Brake!
Jump out! Helicopter can't stop at once.
It's over now.
A cane for falling.
A parachute for falling...
Breaking news.
Atom balloon has appeared again in Shinjuku.
Riding the scary devil's balloon...
-Atom? Are you there? -Yes, Mom.
Atom.
-You didn't go to school? -No...
I'm home!
-Mom, Mom! -Here, Uran.
-Mom. -Uran, what happened to you?
How rude. Someone I don't know threw mud at me.
What? Uran got what?
Honey, look at Uran's clothes. It was a new one.
Uran didn't do it. Someone I don't know did it.
What did you do at park?
I was just playing at park.
-Is that it? -Yes.
He asked, "You are Atom's sister, right?" So I answered, "Yes. But why?"
Then he suddenly started throwing mud at me.
So I got mad and started throwing this much mud at...
I'm sorry. It's because of me.
Atom.
No, it's not because of you. It's because of the Atom balloon.
Uran, I'm going to catch the culprit no matter what, so don't fight from now on.
Ah, Atom.
Brother.
I'm not going to forgive that one. I'm going to get him for sure.
It's that one. All right!
Atom's finally here.
Yes!
Ah, the balloon is running away.
No matter how much it runs, I can't miss something big of that size.
That's odd. That balloon is getting smaller and smaller.
Ah, the balloon...
Has shrunk like this.
Raise your hands! You balloon bomb.
You saw Atom balloon entering this building for sure, right?
Hold on. I'm not a bomb. I'm real Atom.
A real one?
If you are real, you must have electronic brain inside your chest.
Show it to me.
My electronic brain?
I won't be able to trust you unless you show it.
I have no choice.
Ah, this is...
You are?
-I'm Dyhook Anko. -That senator candidate?
That's right! I shot it because I was confused when the bomb suddenly entered!
This is not a bomb. It's real Atom.
Really?
Anyhow, I want you to get such things away right away.
The reason why this society has become an anxious one in which
Atom balloon appears is the wrong law!
It's a dangerous thing for robots to join human society!
I'm tired.
Who is it?
As expected, my idea of Atom balloon was a success.
Skunk! How did you come in?
"Sudden appearance and disappearance" is a phrase of my existence.
Well, don't be too harsh on me, Doc.
Things got processed well like I said and we took care of Atom, right?
Now all the foolish ones hate robots.
Speaking of hatred, why do you hate robots so much?
Do you want to know, Skunk? It's grudge. Grudge.
Grudge?
Yes. It was when I was young, working in factory.
Companies started hiring robots
and I got kicked out of companies one by one.
I lost my job, so I didn't have any money.
I couldn't afford hospital bill for my daughter, so she died!
After that, I worked and worked
with that grudge against robots and got here!
Is that so? That's so sad. But sir,
now there's a rumor that you will get elected for sure.
But... You will be a senator and I'll still be a wanted criminal.
This won't work. Don't you think so?
That's why I told you I would pay 100 million!
So, speaking of 100 million, how about a monthly 100 million?
Wh, what? How ridiculous!
Let me show you something interesting.
This is...!
Do you want me to shoot this up next time? Of course, with a bomb.
That's right! Robots are humans' enemies!
There is Atom balloon over at Tokyo right now as well.
It might be your lovely child that could be sacrificed next time.
If I get elected, I will get all dangerous robots out of Tokyo
and find peace for this city again!
Thankfully damage to the IC of peripheral circuit is small,
but the microprocessor and some of nuclear motor is completely destroyed.
Motor could be completed in a few weeks using the stocked ones,
but without the processor, peripheral circuit cannot be completed either.
Uran, you cannot come in.
What? Uran?
Ah, it's all right. It doesn't matter. You must be worried about your brother.
Doctor Ochanomizu. Use my components for Atom!
What? U, Uran.
You won't be able to move if I do such thing.
It's all right. He has to get better.
He went to fight with the balloon for me.
Uran... How admirable you are.
Instead, you have to get me a new component, Doctor Ochanomizu.
All right. Then let's do that.
-Yes, sir! -Get ready immediately.
Yes, sir!
Breaking news.
It has just been assured that Dyhook Anko got elected.
Yay! Yay!
Oh, Atom!
-Doctor. -Are you awake?
I... What in the...
That's right. You went after the balloon...
Yeah, speaking of that balloon,
Atom, I'm sorry so suddenly, but come here.
Okay!
Looking at the flight orbits of the balloons that flew in until now,
I think they are coming from near this area.
It's the ocean.
Yes. Atom, would you go there?
Yes, Doctor!
According to the map, it's around here...
That is...
I found it. It's coming from there.
As expected, it's a factory.
-Atom, welcome. -That voice is Skunk's!
You remembered? I'm glad.
Then, let me introduce you to your friend.
Ah! This is rubber.
You will interrupt my work if you stay there.
That's the place you belong, Atom.
Who is it? Who put such thing?
Skunk, is it you?
Senator, congratulations.
What business do you have with me?
Well, it's nothing.
I'd like to get some thanks from you as well for getting elected.
Would you open the safe of your party's headquarter tonight?
-I gave you the money I promised earlier! -Well, that's that.
Ah, right. Did you get my congratulatory doll?
It would be interesting if you inflate and fly it.
Guys, on plan.
-Go immediately! -Yes, sir!
That's right! This is the base material for making balloons.
Good, then...
Freeze!
Help me!
Tell me what you were going to do! Where did others go?
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you. Tell you. In the vault of Dyhook's political party.
Party headquarter?
It will be fun if you go there, Atom.
Over there.
Hurry.
-Wait! -Atom.
Put that money back to where it was!
That won't happen.
We have a very big ally.
Three of them!
Good!
Beam!
Take it!
Ah! Gosh!
I did it! I got it!
Do you think I would lose to the fake one?
Run!
Huh? It became a squid!
Dyhook. You are under arrest for aiding robbery.
Wait! I think you've regretted enough, but
Dyhook, your hatred toward robots led to horrible result of
getting yourself cornered by letting villains like Skunk go active.
Start again, Dyhook!
Let's go.
Please forgive me, Atom.
Now you can go back to school. Atom, how nice.
Yes, Doctor!
Hey, bring it here!
It's a balloon!
It's Atom balloon!
What?
How is it? I can fly, too!
Uran! How dare you!
It's fun to see everyone's surprised look from above!
-Get down! -No!
What are you guys doing?
Brother, help me!
Cruciform island, surrounded by coral reef. There's a transforming robot called Pook.
But some villains are trying to use Pook for some bad cause.
Ah, Pook's father is...!
Pirates, we will fight you!
Let's fight together, Pook!
Next on Astro Boy, "Pook on Cruciform Island." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy. "Pook on Cruciform Island"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together