Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Every foreigner will be surprised when they see the change of 2031's Tokyo.
Because this strange city is messed up with
mechanism and emotion of the 20th Century.
This area was called "Musashino"...
This place was called "Musashino" before
There were valleys, mountains, and forests...
But that view only appears at Sasagaya
This place will change to Business Center soon
"You shouldn't choose where to walk in Musashino"
This quote is by Kunikida Dokuho, the poet
Meaning "Go wherever your feet want go,
roads will guide you somewhere you don't expect."
Wha...What?
What are you taking off?
It's called "Gen no Shoko"
It works for stomachache
Wow! "Gen no Shoko" still exists here
Leaves work for diseases?
Excuse me, may I ask something?
Where is the 13 Cho-me of 13 Ban-chi?
Get off that stone steps and go straight about 300m
Thanks!!
Everyone asks same question from this morning
Who is "Everyone"?
He is the 5th kid who asked
"Where is 'Sasagaya 13 Cho-me of 13 Ban-chi'?"
Huh? "13 Cho-me of 13 Ban-chi"?
Wow! Jeez, it's just birds!
Red Cat
"13 Cho-me of 13 Ban-chi" is this spooky western house
But Atom, you go first
Huh? Teacher, you should go first
Gosh, you robot shouldn't be scared
Gyaaaaaa!
Oh, that was you
Absolutely it says "Come here at 13 o'clock"
The sender is called "Red Cat"...
Yes, I came from Shizuoka
I came from Nigata
What "Red Cat" wanna do with
those who don't know each other?
My dad's company will build the building at Sasagaya.
Really? My dad will build the big building, too
Me, too. My dad will build the big chane mall.
I remember my dad, too
Hmm, every kid relates with developers of Sasagaya?
Well, let's search this house now.
You and you search 2nd floor. And you and you search the back room.
Atom and I will search the basement.
Where should I go?
Wait at the entrance. Tell me if someone comes.
Is there someone?
If there is someone, please reply us?
There is no one, right?
There is only one box.
Anyway, let's search this box.
Yes.
I will open, are you all right?
Someone is laughing at us
Oh, tha-that's just wind
Right? True, the window was just making sound.
I am not scared of you.
What? Eyes just moved!
Wa-Wait!!
Be careful, Atom.
We don't know what will come out.
Are you shaking, Teacher?
Wha-What? I'm just shaking of excitement...
Wow! It's coming out!
"Red Cat"!
Look, Teacher, the cat is running away!
No, I won't let you go!
In spite of, this was the famous professor, Nekomata.
He was my great classmate who claimed nature conservation.
He was missing 9 months ago and
this is his photo.
Th-This cat attacked us at the house!
Oh, maybe he was protecting the dead body.
This cat's name is "Chiri" and Professor took care as his child.
Where are these kids who disappeared?
The Police tried to find them but couldn't. This is a mystery.
You want to know?
Yo-You're the "Red Cat"?
If you want to save the kids, do as I say.
Go to the company tomorrow and stop Sasagaya's construction from happening.
This is my lord's will.
Lord? That's Professor Nekomata, right?
Yes, if you don't follow, a funeral can happen any time.
Wait!
This is kidnapping
Maybe someone controls Chiri
I saw speaker on his neck
So surely letters were from that person.
I came to talk about Sasagaya's construction work
Go to meet Chief Turui at Floor 121 of Room 4150
Oh, well, thanks.
Ouch!
Sorry, Sir
This is your hat
Thanks
Huh? Professor Nekomata died?
So please stop Sasagaya's construction work...
Yeah, Professor also visited everyday and said same things
This is wonderful, isn't it?
Earth took such a long time to create such beautiful nature.
Oh, well... Yes
You guys are trying to kill this beautiful nature now, huh?
You don't feel anything by making cold mechanisms in the middle of old Musashino?
Yoko and Taro, how are you doing guys?
Ryota, is your grandma's sickness getting better?
You named each animal?
Yes, they are like my grand children
I am surprised they understand your words.
So please stop works for my cute children
Yes, Sir, I will try my best
I can't believe it!
Are you not ashamed of what you said?
You said you will try your best but you betrayed the promise!
Yeah, but my power can't do anything
Minister chose to do this plan
Liar! I'll die to oppose you!
I'm sorry for him. But...
This Business Center is already having residents
It's too late to stop our works
Kidnapping kids doesn't matter to us, amissing
I'm excited. It's like a spy movie
Shut up! We need to know why he was stalking Teacher
I know it! Don't command me, robot!
This way goes to that spooky house
I know the shortcut, follow me
I got it!
"Red Cat"!?
Why are you doing, Chiri?
You guys saw me
Cat speaks?!
Chiri, Listen, we just wanna back these kids
Shut up! Since you knew who I am, I won't let you go without injures
Let's run away!!
He's a monster!!
Where is it? Is it the basement of hut fertilizer?
No, there's stairs. Maybe this is Chiri's secret house
Wait, I will raise the power of ears
Atom, do you hear anything?
Animals! I hear mixing of many animal voices
I hear from that door
I'm scared. Let's go back
Let's go back to home, please
What? What did you see? Show me, too
Why so many animals stay like this place?
Atom, I saw some people in jail
Really? They're missing kids! Shibugaki, I need your hand, I have to save them
Be quiet. Don't bother animals
Yes, I know it, but it's spooky... Ah!
Atom!
Let's run away immedietely!
That's enough
Hands up!
He's coming again!
You guys are my hostage. I'm not gonna let you escape
Hands up quickly
Atom, you, too. If you don't, I will fire the gun
If my hands rise
it will be like this
Wow! His head came off
He's Professor Nekomata who did suicide
Ghost?!
Now is the chance to go!
That means Professor Nekomata pretended that he was dead
Indeed, he's living by wearing cat's face
And tried to stop Sasagaya's construction work
Threaten us by kidnapping 5 kids in order to stop Sasagaya's work
We ask for arrest warrant by kidnapping and being cat monster
Is there that kind of crime?
Wait, Sir, I wanna meet Professor and wanna know why he did that
No! I wanna arrest because he took form of my hateful animal -cat!
He will run away if you make a fuss
Kids went back to home safely by Atom
Please, I will take care of him
Nekomata, it's me, Ochanomizu, please come up
I understand your feeling
You have hard time by watching being trampled your beloved Musashino
Nekomata, let's talk about that
Nekomata?
I'm here, Ochanomizu
Indeed, you are alive
The skeleton was the specimens of biology class. I welcome you
Why did you do that kind of excessive work?
I didn't do that, the sprit of great nature revenge people for me
You understand my feeling, right?
But it's true that you hurt sinless people. Stop doing that now.
Hurting "Sinless people"? Look at this!
Humans are already hurting these sinless animals and nature
This racing hose hurted his feet, and soon, people sold him to meat shop
The bird that sits next you got cut his muscle in order to not to escape
These sinless dogs were almost killed at stray dog camp
I'm protecting Sasagaya for these unable-speaking animals
Tell officials
If you don't stop in 2 days, scary incident will happen on November 19th
Wh-What are you planning?
If you don't stop now, you may regret of what you do
The government chose this 5 year plan, Chief can't stop
I told you for long time, but you don't listen. He will do what he said, so on November 19th, scary incident will happen
What? Swords fall from the sky?
I can't talk with you! Then, I will talk with minister now
Woks continue?
If you guys keep doing that
Let's move to new hideout and let's do it
Tonight's animals are so quiet
I'm not famliar with that robot
He copy human's move
Recent robots move like humans
Alas, Today is November 19th
Peace still exists but I feel gradual inauspiciousness
Hey you! Don't look away!
Ye-Yes, Sir!
Kids! I'm a teacher!!
Ca-Cat!!
My Pochi!!
Hey 110 (Police), Horses come to eat viggies. It's not good!
Help! Someone!!
What polices are doing? Where are riots?
No, Chief! It's not working
Can you hear, Atom?
Tokyo is filled with animal voices
I didn't expect Animal Demo
I will send these 1st graders to home, Teacher
Let's give poison food! Kill every animal! Or let's use sleeping gas
Before that, we have to know why animals took this action
This incident relates to Sasagaya's construction work that I told you before
You think this incident is by Profossor Nekomata?
Yes, he uses scientific trick to control animal's action
Are you all right, Atom?
Yes, I'm okay
Be carefull!
It works fine
Teacher!!
Shoot! Birds are also oppose to us
Watch out!!
Atom!!
So... That means there's a person who control animals by using hypnosis ultrasound equipment?
Yes, Sir. I'm sure about it
Move quickly and capture him
Only Atom can find the guy in Tokyo
Keep moving everyone! We can't let any animal!!
Teacher, Sibugaki went outside!
Wh-What!?
Look at this. Of course, birds are scared of fire
Atom, I'm coming here to help you!
Jeez!!
Shi-Shibugaki!!
Atom, Wait for my help!
Nam. Katsu. Bosatsu. Kishimojin-sama!
In the nick of time
Doctor Ochanomizu!
My life shrinks 1 week
Doctor, What are you putting in?
This machine can trace back hypnosis ultrasound equipment -How about that one?
This is high voltage current. In case if Atom got attacked by animals
Now, it is finished
Yes, he is fixed
Atom!
Don't touch. This Atom's body has 5000V
Go Atom! Find Nekomata quickly!!
Yes, Sir!
He is at south-southwest 80km away
He is in that building
A-Atom!!
Professor Nekomata, please stop panic of animals
I refuse. I need teach humans power of wild animals
Wa-Wait!! Stop doing that!
Chi-Chiri! My only friend!
Gosh! I'll kill you for Chiri
No! Don't touch my body!!
Animals are
going back to home
That's Atom. He calmed down animals
Sorry, Doctor
No, it's not your fault. It's me who put the high current voltage in your body
Give back... Give it back
Be strong, Nekomata. Sasagaya will keeep green as before
Really? -Yes, it is true
Yes, look at this. Minister mandated construction works.
That Chief received bribe from company to force works
Thanks. Now, I can sleep in peace next to Chiri. And go to heaven together
What are you saying, Nekomata?
Please bury me in that forest, so that I can protect nature
World only by humans will ruin
"You shouldn't choose where to walk in Musashino"
"Roads may guide you somewhere you don't expect"
You memorize it, Atom?
Because it is Teacher's favorite phrase
From this incident, we learned we shouldn't mistreat animals
Hurt and kill them... That's why we recieved such revenge
Teacher, Robot can do something for that?
Maybe you can protect these animals in this forest
I'm glad that you can live in peace
Valley, mountains, forests everywhere. If there are birds on your head, you are blessed
Musashino won't ruin although the civilization develops
The airplain that I was riding
fell on the ground by someone
Wait, who are you guys?
Drog gives me new energy caset
Then, big crystal appears in the middle of desert
Wow! What are you doing? Atlac?
Next Astro Boy -Atom vs. Atlac part 3. Crystal of dersert-
Enjoy!
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together