Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Oh the goddess of Isis.
The goddess of Egypt.
The time has come!
It's time to revive our queen!
Isis, the goddess of Egypt.
Please bring back the queen Cleopatra!
It's the holy bird Baah!
The holy bird that calls in the souls from the other world, Baah!
-There's a light on the coffin... -A light!
That is...
Cleopatra!
Cleopatra's Mystery
Those who believe in Isis, I'm brought back here.
Let us rebuild the empire of Egypt.
-Hurrah for the Queen! -Hurrah for Egypt!
-Doctor Baribari. -Yes?
Caesar ran away with the queen's pikestaff.
What?
Wait!
Hold on, everybody!
I can't trust that you are the queen!
Show me the proof that you are the queen!
Proof?
That's right! You don't have the pikestaff, which is the queen's token.
Where is the pikestaff?
That's right. The pikestaff isn't here.
Where is the pikestaff, the queen's token?
Show us!
Silence! Silence!
Are you guys saying that you cannot believe her
even though you are seeing her with your own eyes?
Show us... Show us the proof.
Queen!
The queen was offended.
We are going to postpone the ceremony. We will perform it after three days.
We will show you the proof, the pikestaff, then!
"It's very important, related to world peace. Please help me. From Caesar."
Welcome, Atom.
I'm Caesar, the one who sent the letter!
You are Caesar?
Atom, I know it's unexpected, but I ask you to keep this.
This is... What is this?
In fact...
Atom! Get down!
Atom, no matter what happens to me, don't come out.
What?
Caesar!
Don't come! Run away, Atom!
Stop!
No! Atom, run!
Atom, it's dangerous!
Stop!
What a swift one.
Caesar.
What did you want to request me?
What? You couldn't find the pikestaff back because of that kid robot?
And you came back just like that? How useless.
Call Cleopatra. Cleopatra!
Yes, sir!
Gosh, everyone's behaving so awfully.
Listen, Caesar!
You were built to protect the world's fairest beauty, Cleopatra.
We will rebuild the empire of Egypt and rule the world together.
Ruining world peace for your own greed?
Please stop that.
What did you say? I am the one who created you.
In other words, I'm your father! Are you going to defy your parent?
Even if you are my father,
I cannot follow this order!
I will stop it with all my life!
I'm going to make you into scrap metal!
Father, there's something.
Caesar!
The end of the traitor.
Where is the pikestaff?
Cleopatra, the pikestaff has been stolen.
Don't hesitate like that. Go find it right away.
It's an order!
Museum of Cairo
There it is!
It's something for the coronation of the queen.
I took something great in.
-What should I do...? -Give it back to me!
You are the one who stole it.
What? This is the pikestaff of Cleopatra who lived 2,000 years ago.
I'm that Cleopatra.
Come follow me.
Right before I woke up from the long sleep of 2,000 years,
someone stole the pikestaff, the token of the queen.
It's empty.
I'm here. I was brought back into life.
Lie! You are not a real Cleopatra.
I can feel it. You are a robot.
Give my pikestaff back!
What is a robot going to do with this pikestaff, the token of the queen?
You don't need to know.
I won't hold it if you don't give it back to me!
No. No.
The pikestaff is inside the coffin with the thief. Let's melt the coffin and find it back.
Shoot... The inside of that coffin is made out of super rubber.
All right!
I used this method with the devil balloon as well.
It's done!
I'm not going to lose you no matter how much you break cars!
Cleopatra.
Let me say it again. Give me the pikestaff you have!
No, I can't do that.
What you are trying to do is a very bad thing.
You should know that as a robot!
It's an order. An order from my creator, my father.
Even if he's your father, he's a bad one!
Shut up!
I'm going to get that pikestaff no matter what.
That is...
These are robot cobras.
That's right, Atom.
These cobras paralyze
circuits with strong magnetism once they coil somebody.
Pikestaff. It's the pikestaff. I found it back!
I'm going to stir up a revolution with this by stirring up foolish people!
The great revolution of Egypt. I'm going to conquer entire Africa soon.
Atom, I'm going to remodel you and appoint you as the commander of that robot army!
Cleopatra. You don't really trust that, do you?
I do. He's the one who created me...
How was Caesar?
Caesar opposed it even though he was a robot.
Clearly Caesar
was afraid of father, saying that he has a scary ambition.
However, however... I do not think that way.
Think carefully about what I say.
If you follow what your father says, millions of people will get killed.
Robots as well.
Cleopatra! Cleopatra!
Gosh, what is Cleopatra doing? She's late.
She's still with Atom.
What? Still?
Atom, Atom.
I'll give you some energy. Hurry and run!
Cleopatra.
Cleopatra!
What are you doing?
Come here. You are finally going to become the queen of Egypt tonight!
That won't happen.
What?
For destroyed Caesar as well.
Atom, you...
When did you get that energy?
Cleopatra gave me some just now!
Gosh!
Stop!
Anubis, Anubis! Stop Atom!
What is this guy?
This one's a robot.
Look. Tonight,
Cleopatra is going to become your queen!
-Hurrah for Cleopatra! -Hurrah!
Coming!
The goddess of Isis, the one who protects the empire of Egypt,
here, our queen Cleopatra stands,
brought back to life from 2,000 years ago!
-Hurrah! -Hurrah for Cleopatra!
Cleopatra, the queen of Egypt,
bring the entire Africa the glory of Egyptian
by rebuilding our great empire.
Let death follow those who defy.
What's wrong? Why wouldn't you take it?
...I can't do it.
What? You can't?
I will follow your orders.
But I won't lie. Robots can't lie.
What are you saying, coming all the way here? You are the revived Cleopatra!
-What happened? -What's wrong?
Robots can't lie to people. Please forgive me for this once.
What are you talking about!
I'm going to tell the truth to everyone.
What an ungrateful one!
I'm not the revived Cleopatra. I'm just a robot.
Do you think you are going to be safe after you reveal that?
Father, how come you didn't make me a robot that can lie?
Cleopatra!
-Hurrah! -Hurrah!
You, Cleopatra. Be ready.
Hold on!
Atom.
Doctor Baribari,
are you going to destroy Caesar
and Cleopatra for your own greed?
I'm going to make you into a living dead by taking your energy out!
It's dangerous!
Take it!
Ah! Cleopatra!
Ah! It's a mistake.
Cleopatra is...
Huh? Robot. This Cleopatra is a robot.
It's a robot! Robot!
Cleopatra is a robot!
-So it wasn't real? -The queen is fake.
It was fake.
Everyone! We've been fooled.
It's that one! That one is the one!
Don't be fooled! It's a fake Cleopatra!
Destroy the fake temple!
Gosh, what happened?
Isis, throw those who are messing up the temple out!
Stop it!
That's it. Giant, knock Atom down with your hand!
Dangerous!
He's going to get stepped!
Giant, forward!
Good job, Giant. Don't lose!
-Smash Atom! -Father,
you called me queen, right?
That's right.You are the queen.
Then I command you as the queen. Please die with me.
What?
I'm getting dragged to it.
Dang it...
That's right!
If I'm going to get dragged, then from this side...
I will jump!
Can this one fly?
Let me go! Let me-
I don't want to die yet. Let me go! I want to live!
Leave me!
I got out of his butt.
Cleopatra!
-Let me go! -Atom.
Cleopatra. Thank goodness, you are fixed.
Don't come near, Atom. I will have to fight you as well.
Hurry and run.
This temple is over now. I'm going to blow up this temple.
Blow up?
Good bye, Atom.
-Let me go! -Cleopatra!
Cleopatra!
Let me go!
You wanted the glory of the empire of Egypt, right?
Get an honorable death for the least.
Cleopatra!
It's a timed bomb.
I don't want to die. Please let me live.
Let me go! You ungrateful one! Help me!
Cleopatra, you...
You are trying to die
together to stop his plot, right?
Ah, it doesn't work anymore. The energy...
Cleopatra...
Good bye, Cleopatra.
Good bye, Egypt.
The subway of the 21st century runs 180km per hour.
Wow, it's like a jet coaster!
They scream for joy.
But the subway started running endlessly with passengers aboard.
Atlas! Is it you again? Why such a foul play?
It's the last station! We will crash like this!
Next on Astro Boy,
"Atom vs. Atlas VII." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy "Atom vs. Atlas VII"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together