Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Now the special show "The Robot Land" is over.
The land of dream for robots, the story land, Robot Land...
Oh, look at the time. Atom, go to bed.
Okay.
Mom, Dad, good night.
Good Night.
Dad, is the school ready tomorrow?
Not yet.
We just got into elementary school.
We have to study hard.
Hmm... I'm not very good at studying.
If you say such things, you won't be able to catch up with Atom.
Then... Where's the textbook?
Oh my!
Atom, you can't go outside this late at night.
It's a swan!
The Robot Land
Oh my, let's call the vet.
Wait, the vet's number is...
Oh! This swan is a robot!
What?
Ah...
It's awake now.
I'm Atom. Who are you?
Please, help me!
I'm not the bad one. I'm Princess Odette.
I escaped from "The Robot Land".
The Robot Land?
That...
The Robot Land is a scary place.
Ha Ha Ha... I found you, Princess Odette.
Let's go back to The Robot Land.
You... You!
I mean...
Here, Princess Odette. Come here!
What are you doing!
You little! What's your name?
I'm Atom!
Ha Ha... So you are Atom.
I'll teach you what would happen
if you fight against Satan.
Wait! Ah!
Help! Atom!
Ah! Princess Odette!
Now, did you get it?
Princess Odette!
Atom, did you have a dream or something?
Robots don't dream!
In The Robot Land...
I didn't hear anything about something scary happening at The Robot Land...
Hmm! There is Doctor Hyde in there.
What should we do, shall we go to The Robot Land
and check together?
Yes!
Look, Atom, that's the Robot Land.
I used to work with Dr. Hyde in the Department of Science
a long time ago. However...
He suddenly quit the job about 20 years ago.
I didn't expect him to work as a business man.
Ha Ha Ha... I'm looking forward to meet him.
Ochanomizu!
I don't want to see you again!
Because of that guy,
I was always in the 2nd place.
Even though I had a talent!
Maybe, Ochanomizu...
He's coming to find the secret of this island... No way...
I didn't expect that kind guy to suspect such fact.
Welcome to the Robot Land!
Now, this story land will
lead you to the land of dreams.
Oh, this is amazing!
It really feels like I'm in the story land.
Ochanomizu, I've waited for you!
Dr. Hyde, I missed you.
This is Atom.
Oh, you are that famous Atom.
It's an honor for me to see you.
Hello.
Let me guide you.
Wow, Dr. Hyde.
What a work!
It was the dream of my whole life.
My dream as a robot engineer.
Ha Ha
I thought of constructing legendary stories
with robots in this island.
I wanted to make the story land
that are getting forgotten by people.
Wow, wonderful!
However, you must have spent much money for this!
I invested my money I earned from my patented technology.
Mirror, Mirror, the most beautiful one in the world...
Get away!
Mirror, Mirror, answer me.
Who is the best robot engineer in the world?
That is, of course, you.
The best robot engineer in this world is you, Dr. Hyde.
Ha Ha ha... Is that so?
Ochanomizu, let me show you my robot factory.
The freshly built monsters.
How is it? Isn't this scary?
Ah! No! It's not done yet!
Make it more scary!
Make it more disgusting!
Look, here... It shouldn't be like this.
Now, it's good!
Oh my!
If you make it like this... Everyone will...
It's exactly like what Atom said, Dr. Hyde!
You shouldn't treat robots like this,
like your own toy.
My toy? Did I lock them up or something?
I don't do things like that.
Now, do you have a complaint about this island?
We are fine. We like this job.
See? Ochanomizu?
Do you really like this look?
Huh? Tell me the truth.
This is the minister of the Department of Science, Dr. Ochanomizu.
He will figure out the truth for you.
You are scared of someone!
Don't be afraid and tell the truth!
How rude! Ochanomizu!
Take this rude robot out!
Atom, there are many robots in the world.
The robots in this robot land
are all Dr. Hyde's property.
If there's no evidence that they have been treated harshly,
there's nothing we can do...
Oh, what a beautiful swan!
Ah! It's Princess Odette!
Princess Odette! I'm here to help you!
Doctor, if you ask this one, she will tell you the truth.
Is it true that
something scary is taking place in this robot land?
Princess Odette, tell the truth.
then everyone will get saved.
Ochanomizu!
Ah,
What are you doing?
Are you still trying to do something bad to my robots?
If you interfere, I'm going to call the police!
Ah... Atom...
That's right! When the clock turns to 12,
Princess Odette comes back to being human. Wait until then!
She will tell you the truth for sure.
What a fool!
Ochanomizu, hurry and go back
with that robot!
I don't want to be in a place like this anymore, either!
I'm going back, Atom!
Dr. Ochanomizu!
Wait!
Shoot...
I'm Prince Siegfried. What Atom is saying is...
Ah! You are!
The devil Satan!
Atom!
Atom, stop!
Dr. Hyde, stop that huge thing.
Stop! Satan!
Doctor, it's this one.
This one kidnapped Princess Odette last night.
Is what Atom is saying true, Hyde?
Huh? I don't know what you are talking about.
Then, what did you just do to
Prince Siegfried?
It's only a part of a play.
It's normal to be angry some times.
You are not acting like an adult. You are a minister!
Atom, let's go back! I feel unpleasant.
Atom.
Help, Atom.
Okay!
Princess Odette, it's me! It's me!
Ah! Princess Odette!
You shouldn't come!
Atom!
I've been waiting for you, Atom!
Ha ha ha... What's wrong, Atom?
Are you out of battery?
Check, Oome.
Yes!
Shibukaki.
Atom. Atom?
Is Atom absent? Is he sick?
Does a robot get sick, too?
He must be getting fixed.
Wait...
Everyone, study for a while.
What? Atom is fighting against
The Robot Land?
Besides, something bad is happening
by Dr. Hyde.
Today, there was a call in the morning.
It was your order to allow Atom
to be in that island. Ochanomizu?
What? Atom?
I know!
Because you didn't like The Robot Land,
you sent Atom to ruin it!
No way!
Come to The Robot Land and solve this problem right away.
This is why...
Okay. Let's go there first!
Thank you, let's go.
Teacher's gone.
Teacher's mean. He told everyone to study by himself.
And he's trying to go to the Robot Land by himself alone!
He went to help Atom!
So I'm going to help him, too!
Ah! How cunning, Shibukaki!
Kenichi, I'll catch him!
Wait!
Shibukaki!
What is it, Tamao.
Are you trying to catch me?
No, no... Take me, too.
Ah, I see. Let's go!
I can't let you get out.
Everyone, let's go!
Listen to me.
Atom didn't go there to make a scene.
Atom is a good boy in school.
He has no reason to do such thing.
He's not a good kid!
He makes that kind of robots jump!
My, my! I cannot bear it anymore!
Making a scene... Jumping... Atom is not a crazy dog!
If there is a student, there must be a teacher.
Wh.. What...
If you touch me, I'm going to call the police.
Dr. Hyde, the bearded guy planned this...
Dr. Ochanomizu, you are the minister of the Department of Science, right?
No, I'm the responsible one for Atom.
You know what happens if a robot trespasses other one's property
and breaks things, right?
That is...
According to the Robot Law #135 article 2,
That robot has to be destroyed and
the responsible one has to be questioned, too.
If I make a case against you, Atom is going to be a scrap iron
and you are going to be fired from your minister work.
The robot land!
This will make us get caught.
Leave it to me.
I brought the diving equipment!
Wow!
Dr. Hyde, what do you want me to do?
I'll do anything I can do.
Ha, then let me tell you. Destroy Atom with your own hands.
Destroy Atom... Destroy Atom?
Yeah, if you do so, I won't question your responsibility.
In other words, you don't have to give up your position as a minister.
Wh...What...
How mean!
What is it?
It's a secret path!
Good.
There's a way out!
This looks like a cargo ship.
Is it transporting materials for The Robot Land?
If that's the case, there's no reason to transport it underwater.
Let's look inside.
Ah! It's a missile!
He was making this in secret.
What is that?
The Robot Land is a fake one!
He's making robots to work on weapons...
And he's been selling those abroad with that submarine.
Let's go.
Get me out!
Shut up! Let me get you out.
However, after I make you into a scrap iron.
Someone is there.
Is that Atom?
No, I don't think so. Let me hear it.
Princess Odette is waiting. Get me out!
Huh?
Who is it?
Huh? Hey, wait!
Get me out!
Thank you. You are...
We are Atom's classmates.
Hurry and guide us to where Atom is.
What are you doing, Ochanomizu?
Destroy Atom!
Atom... I can't do it... How cruel...
It's just a robot.
Why can't you shoot it?
Hyde! Isn't this too much?
What is? If he destroys Atom,
everything will be forgotten!
I can't.
Dr.Hyde, I don't want to
protect myself doing this kind of things.
Poser! Then, I'll shoot him!
Give it to me!
Watch me.
Stop!
What are you?
We are here to help Atom!
Fools! Who comes to a place
like this after missing classes?
Teacher, we saw something amazing!
What?
This island is an illegal weapon factory!
It's full of missiles and laser guns.
What?
Dr. Hyde!
Ah... You saw it...
I see. I thought a lot of money
must have been invested to make this robot land.
Now you made robots to make weapons
and you've been selling those to bad guys!
You are a hypocrite!
As you said!
Then, you all have to die.
You can't do that!
I've been patient enough!
Look at this!
I'm... Satan!
Hey, Satan.
Destroy every single one of these.
No problem, Master.
Everyone, save Atom!
Robots... Satan, go!
Atom,
Thank you.
Get away.
Stop!
Huh?
Satan!
You are here!
I shall not lose.
Ha!
Ha ha ha... I'm going to make you into pieces!
This little!
Stupid... Leave it!
Ah... Satan... My Satan...
Ah... What is it.
What are you trying to do?
We are not slaves!
Now, we are not going to work under you!
The Robot Land is mine!
You are my slaves!
Freedom!
The Robot Land became a very good island to live in.
Everyone is lively again. Please, Atom...
Please come visit us with your family.
From Prince Siegfried and Princess Odette.
I'll visit for sure.
Next on Astro Boy
Department of Machinery
We are making a lot of robots.
Ah! A thunder! Franken, you cannot jump around!
You are not a complete robot yet.
Skank is trying to use you for the bad thing.
To Be Continued...
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together