Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Thank you for participating in the tour of Sunshine Islands today.
This ship will now reach this tour's highlighted spot,
the Bee Island that is known for its cannibal bee.
Atom, it's that place. I heard it's very beautiful with all its flowers!
But the cannibal bee might come.
That's a lie!
There's no way there's such thing as cannibal bee!
What is she?
Passengers who will land on the island, please put on the protection suit.
And please do not approach places other than the designated ones.
That's dad's island.
The Secret of Bee Island
You cannot take off your protection suit until you enter the observatory.
What a fuss. I feel like we are in space or something.
It's because humans can get stung by a bee unlike us.
Atom, where would that cannibal bee be?
-How beautiful... -Wow, the entire island is like a flower field.
Originally, this island was known for rare flowers.
An electronic biologist Doctor Mitsuda
was developing this island to be a honey farm,
but he suddenly went missing about two years ago.
Dad's alive for sure.
After that, some people who have landed on this island went missing,
so it started to gain its reputation as an island where cannibal bees live.
Where are you going, Uran?
I have always wanted to sleep in a bed made out of flowers.
Uran, let's now go back.
A little bit more.
Huh? She also doesn't seem to be satisfied just by watching.
Hey! It's dangerous to take off the protection suit!
-Something's strange. -Yes.
Hey! Wait! Kid!
Hey, why are you running away?
Why are you bothering me?
Bother? I was just...
I'm never going to leave this island until I find my dad!
Your dad?
So your dad lives in this island?
My dad is Doctor Mitsuda.
I see... So you came to this island to find that missing doctor.
He's going to cry.
I'm going to find my dad!
Atom, bees are...
They don't look like normal bees.
It feels like they are watching us.
Watch out!
Stop it!
How do you like this?
They are finally gone.
Atom! Look at that!
So many bees!
Run!
-Let's hide there. -Yeah.
Now we can relax.
-So where are we now? -Well...
Someone's there.
It's a robot.
Hello, welcome.
You are RP 3!
That voice is...
Have you forgotten? You used to be the research assistant robot of my dad.
This robot?
Dad must have brought him with him.
I'm an assistant of Doctor Mitsuda.
You have the same voice as Mitsuru, the son of the doctor.
But your size and weight are different.
It's been three years. I grew.
You grew?
Humans grow time after time.
It's like flowers!
You must not be a very smart robot.
So this is his lab.
But why did he go missing?
Doctor's out. I'm waiting. I don't know what happened.
But it's already been two years. You haven't gone out to look for him?
He told me to wait. So I wait.
What's wrong, Mitsuru?
My body feels hot.
It might be the venom from that bee earlier.
Disease! Sleep. Good boy.
So you could prove to be useful sometimes.
Mitsuru, get well soon.
It's time to supply my energy.
Has he waited for more than two years, supplying energy like that?
Probably.
Atom, what are you going to do?
Let's take Mitsuru to hospital once it gets dark.
I heard bees don't move at nights.
Dad, where are you, Dad?
-I'm hone. -How was it?
Yeah, it's all right now.
Bees are gone now. How's Mitsuru?
I just checked him. He's deeply asleep.
-All right, let's get ready to move him. -Okay.
-What is he doing? -He's fixing a dinner for the doctor.
Every night for two years?
Dad. Dad!
Hey, RP 3,
would you like to come with us?
I wait. Doctor told me to wait.
Atom, Mitsuru's gone.
What?
-How in the world... -Does he feel all right?
Mitsuru must have gotten out through here.
-Anyhow, let's find him! -Yes.
Mitsuru!
Wow, it's beautiful. I've never been to flower beds at night.
No! Look for him more seriously!
I thought your role was to wait.
I wait for Doctor. I wait for Mitsuru's father.
-Let's wait together. -Okay.
Mitsuru!
Atom!
Let's go.
-There's a village underneath.. -It's an underground city.
It looks similar to something. That's right! A bee hive!
I see. It's like a bee hive.
Where did Mitsuru go?
Someone's coming. Let's ask.
No.
Something's suspicious.
They must be controlled by that bee.
That's not a bee. There's no biological wing sound response from that.
I see. It's a bee-shaped robot.
They found us!
Go away!
They are the ones the surveillance camera at the entrance detected.
Those who enter our Bee City
will not be able to leave alive.
Guard robot, move!
What are you doing? You should help as well!
I'm a research assistant robot. It's not my job to fight.
This is not a right time to say that!
-Something great has come out. -Atom, over here!
Shoot... They are going to attack together.
Danger level 100%.
Leave them to me and you guys should run!
But...
Hurry!
Here, come on!
All right! I'll fight you guys!
Okay, only one left!
My energy...
-Atom! -Danger, danger.
Atom! Atom!
Are you the one? That robot called Atom?
Who are you?
Me? I'm the commander of this underground Bee City.
I'll soon be the commander of entire world.
What?
We are going to build the bee empire with this island as a base.
The bee empire? You think such thing's possible?
You think so?
You must have also seen what happens to people who have gotten exposed to bee venom.
It's the end for you once you get stung by our bee army.
Humans will be faithful servants of our Queen Mary.
Queen Mary?
Atom, you also should get rebuilt and become a soldier to serve Queen Mary.
Who would do that?
Well, this is the only moment you can be like that.
You will lie face down once you witness the great power of Queen Mary.
Shoot...
Danger. More danger.
Until when are you going to keep saying such things? We have to save Atom!
Are you going to run away?
Bees. It's my job to take care of bees.
Screw bees! Go find my brother!
-It's my job to take care of bees. -Gosh!
Someone's coming.
-There are bees in that chamber. -Huh?
Queen Bee Mary.
Is the plan coming together well?
Yes. Now the bee army will be ready to sally into the world.
Construct the bee empire as soon as possible.
No matter what.
Danger. Queen Bee danger.
Atom, we will rebuild you.
And you will be the honorable leader of our bee army for conquering this world.
I can't do that.
Do you want me to teach you for the last time?
Bee's venom is like this!
This is a special micro antenna.
It lets you accept Queen Mary's hypnosis radio wave.
Hypnosis radio wave?
Once you get stung by this, it's over. Humans will now follow Queen's orders.
As for robots, this has to be inserted to them through an operation.
I see.
So you will be Queen's slave now.
-Take him to the operating room! -Yes, sir!
Uran!
Atom.
Shoot... When did they...
Guard! Don't miss Atom!
Hurry. Someone's coming.
I have to give him the energy capsule first.
This will interfere with our running plan. Don't want to give.
How cheap.
It's all right, I'll take him. So give it to me!
All right! I won't be defeated now!
Leave them to me and you guys go save Mitsuru!
That won't work now!
Take this!
There he is.
Who are you?
Mitsuru, hurry!
I brought him.
Taking bee stinger out. My job.
You do look accustomed to this.
How dare they!
Dad.
It's me.
Doctor! I waited. Waited.
Dad, it's me!
I don't know you!
Watch out!
Dad, how come...
Maybe your dad was also...
As expected.
Dad.
Dad!
Mitsuru.
Thank goodness, Atom.
Doctor Mitsuda has also been a slave.
This is Queen Mary!
I'm the queen. Those who disobey me will die.
Everyone! Run!
Come! I'll fight you!
It won't work. No one can rebel against me.
Yeah, you are Atom. My slave.
Shoot, it's the hypnosis wave.
That's right. You will bow down to me.
Atom.
I can't be defeated by someone like this!
-Atom! -Ah, Uran!
Are you all right?
What are you doing to Atom?
Uran.
Stop it!
How useless.
The result will be the same no matter how many times you dare.
Queen Mary! Be ready!
You are getting above yourself.
It's now!
I'm not afraid of you as long as there's no hypnosis wave!
-Atom. -Take this!
It's all my fault.
That queen bee was built to increase the productivity
of honeybees through an electronic biology study.
It worked out,
so bees showed an amazing productivity, following that queen bee's orders
However, because of that strong hypnosis wave of queen bee,
human brainwave also got affected.
And the first victim was you, Doctor.
It was a fool of me to
go against the nature and control insects with lives
on my own.
It's all right. This is a normal honeybee.
Oh, so there was a honeybee that wasn't affected by this robot queen bee.
All right, I'm going to start over.
Atom, come visit again. I'll give you some tasty honey next time.
Okay! I promise I'll visit again.
Me too! Wait for me. RP 3, here.
I will wait. It's my job to wait.
-Goodbye! -Bye.
Bye!
The seas of Kuraken where the golden coral shines.
Pipi who works at the ocean ranch can freely talk with fish.
In that peaceful ocean ranch, a pirate called Kim Samgak invades.
You!
But a monster that surprised even Kim Samgak has appeared!
What is that monster?
Next on Astro Boy. The Monster of Kuraken. Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Monster of Kuraken"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together