Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
A spaceship called Memorial is traveling around the world right now,
and it will be arriving in Japan in two days.
When it is anchored, they are going to invite elementary students and let them see the inside.
Wow, great. I want to do that too.
No, you can't, Uran.
Only elementary students who won the writing contest are allowed to do that.
-You have to write an essay? -Yeah! It has to be about your dream.
Huh, dream.
I have never dreamt before.
I already finished researching about it.
Then you would surely win the first place.
I want to get aboard as soon as possible.
Spaceship in Imminent Danger
Therefore, I want to be a botanist
and make huge and small flowers at my choice.
If this works out, I will be able to make huge carrots
and huge radish,
and help people in starvation in the world.
The end.
Teacher, how was mine?
Atom? I'm sorry, but I think you misunderstood something.
Misunderstood?
That's right. You misunderstood.
Dream is a state of being hallucinated while asleep,
and it is different from one's personal behavior while awake.
You are a fool, Atom.
When we said "My Dream", did you think it was about a dream you get while asleep?
Huh? Isn't that right?
Nope.
Atom, do you understand?
It's a dream about your future as in
what you want to do when you grow up.
Dream about my future?
That's right, Atom.
You've never thought about that since you're a robot, right?
I'm a dreamful boy in that sense.
I'm going to go into that spaceship. Isn't that right, sir?
You fool!
You have so many misspellings that I can barely read it!
My,
So Midori Hayashi will go from our class.
Yes, sir!
-Kenichi Tezuka! -Yes!
These two will go aboard the spaceship.
-Good for them. -Yay!
Well, I don't know how to explain that dream.
Ah, look at that.
Why would Osamu work so hard like that?
That's because he has a dream of becoming a baseball player.
But teacher, I don't have to work that hard to...
Atom!
Here!
Shibukaki is lifting weights like that
because he wants to be a sumo wrestler in the future.
But teacher, I'm...
My, my.
Noboru wants to be a police officer.
Teacher, throw this with all your strenght.
This one?
How amazing.
As expected, it's difficult to teach a robot about "dream".
Teacher.
Yes?
If I become human, can I have dreams?
I'm not sure whether you can become one, but anyone can have dreams.
I see. I'm not having any dream since I can do everything.
I'll go and talk with Dr.Ochanomizu!
Hey, Atom!
What? You want me to disable your super powers?
I want to be human. Please.
What's wrong, Atom? Tell me what happened.
To this ship Memorial?
Yes. But since I have no dream, I couldn't write an essay.
That's why...
How sad.
Dr.Ochanomizu, please. Please make me human.
I can disable your powers for a little while, but...
That will do. I want to have a dream.
All right. All right, Atom.
That kind of experience could help you as well.
Are you sure?
It's done, Atom. Now get up.
Dr.Ochanomizu, now I'm like a human being, right?
Yes. Try lifting that as a test.
Okay!
Are you happy now, Atom?
Of course, you can't fly nor use your machine gun.
All right!
And Atom,
Even if you say you want to go back in the middle, I can't fix you back.
You'll have to stay like that for 24 hours. Do you understand?
Yes. So for 24 hours, I'm like a human being.
Trouble! Trouble!
-Teacher! Sir! -What's wrong, Shibukaki?
-Teacher, Atom must have gone crazy. -Atom?
-Over there. -What is he trying to do?
He's "trying" to become a skydiver.
I'm glad he's got a goal now, but he can fly anyway.
He doesn't have to practice or anything...
-Well, things have changed. -What?
Atom! Use your jet!
Atom!
Ah! Atom.
Stupid! You fool! What have you done...
Ah, sir.
Stupid! Why didn't you use your jet before you landed?
Teacher, I asked Dr.Ochanomizu
to disable my powers for 24 hours.
What?
I wanted to become like my friends.
But... If you do something wreckless like this, you will be broken.
Pardon?
If you wanted to become human, you should have considered that as well!
Yes...
Then, I'll be back. I'll get some postcards for you as a souvenir.
Bye!
How lucky are Kenichi and Midori!
I'm going to get the first place next year and get aboard the Ship Memorial.
You will go back to original Atom in three hours anyway.
Huh? Three hours?
That's right.
This is sad.
Hey, Atom. Don't you want to get aboard the spaceship?
Of course I do.
Okay! Then, it's done! Follow me!
Everyone, line up!
You all have to look around politely.
This elevator is 300 meters long.
It is connected to the lobby of this ship...
Wow, how amazing.
This lobby is the work of the world's best interior designer...
Huh?
We could play baseball here!
Look at that. It's so high.
Hey! Don't play around!
A spaceship that you can use to travle
must be much fancier than a cruise ship.
-Amazing. -Great.
Hey. Over here! Here!
Hello.
Are you here for a visit? They are over there.
-Yes! Excuse me. -Excuse me!
This is the controlling station. Only staff can enter.
You... You are!
Fly. Right now.
So this ship, Memorial, doesn't need to anchor
for about three months once it takes off.
That's why all kinds of recreation facilities are equipped here.
In this room, you can watch recent news, 3D movies, animes...
Teacher! I can't watch it because of your shadow!
Ah, I'm sorry.
That voice is Shibukaki's!
Shoot.
Atom, you too?!
Stop it! Are you going to let the kids get into this as well?
I have no choice. Now we are all on the same boat now.
I can't do that!
Shoot!
Move. Let the spaceship take off.
I can never do such thing!
Shoot...
I'm going to destroy this stupid machine.
Stupid!
What kind of reckless thing are you doing?
I'm sorry, sir.
Get off immediately! Once we are back at school, I'm going to...
What happened? Memorial just moved.
Teacher! Memorial is taking off!
What? There was no such plan.
-All right, Atom. -Huh?
Now we don't have to get off.
It is flying for sure.
Teacher! Maybe they are flying this as a special service for us?
Everyone!
Memorial has just been hijacked!
What? Hijacked?
What does 'hijacked' mean?
It means this spaceship has been abducted.
Be quiet! Quiet!
-Who did it? -He's in the cockpit.
The pilot must have been injured.
I'll go and check!
Atom! You! Hey!
It's flying.
I finally succeeded. Now I can ignite a fire on my way.
Shoot... How can he hijack our dream?
I won't forgive him!
Hijacked Memorial is heading to Megapolis right now!
The cockpit is here.
All right! I can easily take this door...
That's odd...
Atom!
Teacher, it's weird. I have no strength in my arms.
Of course. You disabled your powers.
That's right!
How can I turn them back on?
Th... That is...
I just have to wait for time to pass.
There are about 25 minutes remaining.
At a moment like this...
What is that? That's...
That's a rescue team.
You broke the meter but now I can relax.
Shoot... I was going to fly to the end of space and die there.
Shoot! Dang it! I'm always like this.
My plan always fails right before its success.
This is!
Ah, the net is going to break.
I guess there is some luck remaining.
Hey! You hijacker! Open the door!
Let the injured one out. I'll be your hostage instead!
What? Instead?
What's wrong? Hurry!
All right! Send the other one in. I'll let the pilot go.
Teacher! I'll go instead.
What are you talking about? You are just a kid. Leave this to me!
So who's the other one?
Come in!
-Teacher! -Atom!
-He's just a kid. -I'm the other one.
Sir.
Wake up.
Cheer up.
-Atom! -Please.
Emergency. Memorial ship which lost its control
has finally invaded Megapolis!
It's descending.
Kid, give up. The controller is broken.
Unless it bumps against something, it will never stop.
Mister. Why did you do such thing?
Why?
There's no point in saying that now, but kid,
You are an unfortunate one like me.
Unfortunate?
That's right. You got shoved into a criminal's room like this.
That's not right. I walked in here upon my will.
Well then, that's even more unfortunate. You must have so many dreams...
No, it doesn't matter.
I'm going to be a powerful robot again in 10 minutes anyway.
Robot? Are you a robot?
You are lucky to be human. You can dream.
No way. Because of that dream, I...
I kept making failures.
At firsst, I tried a transpacific, nonstop flight
with a solar-powered plane.
When I was about to land, the forecast went wrong
and I stopped in the middle of the Pacific Ocean.
I fell because I ran out of battery.
After that, I tried digging a gold mine.
At that time, a huge earthquake took place
and that big gold mine disappeared into underground soil.
I failed at every attempt to achieve my dream.
I see...
Nonetheless, I'm jealous of people who can dream, even if they could fail.
Huh?
You are lucky. You have tons of dreams.
No matter how many times you fail, you can always pursue your dreams.
The building is...!
We have to do something. But...
Atom!
Building! The big building is...!
One more minute. My power will come back after a minute!
No. I don't want to die!
I can't wait any longer!
No...
I'm back. My powers are back!
I won't get defeated.
God!
This is...!
The spaceship changed its direction.
It's Atom. Atom's powers are back.
The criminal got arrested and the kids were rescued.
We avoided a big accident. Atom saved us all.
Then Teacher, did Atom win the first place?
Pardon? Yes, of course! He won the first place.
Yay! First place! First!
However, I hope Atom doesn't have weird dreams anymore.
I like being a robot.
Even though I can't have dreams like human beings do,
it's more convenient to have my powers.
That's right, Atom. Your powers
also enable human beings to dream.
Enable them to dream?
I see! So I'm giving them dreams instead of having dreams myself?
That's right, Atom.
It's the Memorial ship.
Now it will really begin its around-the-world flight.
Goodbye!
In this town of Sparitz, Germany,
there is a strange rock that resembles a human face.
Everyone calls it "Inmen Jiwa".
Is it true that a town will perish if this rocks turns away to the West?
A mysterious robot has a secret!
Who is it? Who made an explosion underground?
Inmen Jiwa is falling. The dam's in danger!
What shall we do? The town is in danger!
Next on Astro Boy, "Inmen Jiwa"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together