Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
If there could be only one resting place in this world,
that would be mother's lap.
When Uran's not around,
I also crawl into mom's lap.
Doctor Ochanomizu, there's a package for you.
All right, I'm coming.
Doctor, here's your package.
I'm sorry, but could you bring it inside?
This package is huge.
Yes, it's quite big.
This is all mixed up.
It's a head!
Mutilation murder case! Officer!
Black Looks
What is it? What? What an agitation.
Doctor! There seems to be a mutilation murder case.
There are mutilated arms and legs. Look, over there.
It's a robot...
It's completely disassembled. I don't know what's what.
And the sender is?
That part got wet, so I can't recognize letters.
But it smells like crime.
Two robots are mixed up.
Let's assemble this. We might find something.
Since these are so small that it's hard to distinguish.
Will it be fixed?
It's done now.
Nakamura, can you turn the switch on?
Okay!
Is this it?
Nakamura!
Hurry, hurry! Turn the switch off!
All right. Is this the one?
I can't do it!
Ah... I failed.
Doctor, Are you all right?
It seems like that head wasn't the right one.
If it explodes again, it would be of great magnitude.
Nakamura, switch.
Ah, it's fixed!
Au.
Au.ro.ra.Looks!
Hey! Where are you going?
Aurora Looks.
Wait. Hold on. No! Hold him!
Stop! I'll shoot if you don't!
Aurora!
Atom, Atom, it's me. Please come immediately.
Aurora! Looks, Looks.
Aurora. Looks.
Ah, it's that robot.
Hold on!
Aurora Looks.
Stop! Stop there!
I have no choice.
Aurora Looks.
Aurora Looks
Looks. Aurora Looks.
Hmm, it's speaking out of its faint old memory.
Looks.
Nakamura. Maybe this robot is...
Ah, Black Looks!
Black Looks? What is that?
It's a gang group after robots.
The first place Black Looks appeared was...
the car factory in West Germany, in April five years ago.
Stop!
Who is it, a human?
I'm asking just in case; the executive of this factory is a robot, right?
That's right. Not only the executive, but all the workers here are robots.
I see. All robots. Then why not?
Go!
Please, I beg you. I have a wife and kids!
What, a robot is begging for its life like a human?
Move expensive ones!
Starting with this case, they attacked
London's World Robot Bank,
Texas' Robot Oil Company, and South Africa's Robot Development Base
and stole $80 million!
All crew members wear black masks
so no one know who they are.
I see. Like you said, this robot
might be a victim of that Black Looks.
Looks. Looks. Aurora.
Well, so "Looks" comes from "Black Looks". Then what is "Aurora"?
Aurora is an electric phenomenon in the stratosphere. Then...
I learned at school that there is a mountain called Aurora in the South Pole.
That's it!
I'm sure this robot was sent from there.
If we take this robot to the South Pole, we might get a clue on Black Looks,
but it would be complicated to bring our police into the other country without any evidence.
Robot is for a robot. How about I take it?
It's bit dangerous for Atom to investigate Black Looks by himself.
Doctor is... You are busy!
Oh, there's the perfect one.
He's aggressive and trustworthy!
I never imagined I would be able to travel in the South Pole with public money.
Atom, we are lucky.
Ah, it's hot. What happened?
-We are currently passing through the equator. -Equator?
Hold on. Isn't there an air conditioner?
I'm sorry. You must be human, sir?
Stupid, I am. How can you bear such heat?
Sir, all the other passengers are robots.
When are we going to arrive at the South Pole?
South Pole Penguin Land Airport
We will go to downtown.
There's an announcement for passengers.
There is a bus waiting at the front gate.
Please have a safe ride.
Hey, robots have to take that car.
It's a truck.
It doesn't matter, Atom. Get on this bus.
You should go there!
Hey, even robots do pay for it. What's so wrong about it?
What's wrong about it?
How come you are siding with this lump of metal?
Lump of what? Say it again!
Siding with robots in Penguin Land? How funny.
Teacher! Stop it!
-I'll just take that car. -Atom!
This robot's got more sense.
I'm taking that one as well.
Hey! Stop!
Interesting. Are you going to do it?
Stupid, I'm the Mr. Beard who trained at the institute.
Good for you.
Let's go to police station first.
It was a self-defense!
-Let me go! I'll walk on my own. -Teacher!
It was a self-defense. Don't worry.
Atom, go to Aurora Mountain first. I'll catch up.
Teacher...
That mountain is...
-What wrong, Kid? -What's the name of that mountain?
-It's Aurora Mountain. -As expected!
If you are going there, why don't you get in? I'm going to the same direction.
Really?
-You are a robot. -Ha ha, can you notice?
You are nice.
There isn't any hotel in Aurora Mountain. Would you like to come to my house?
Thank you.
Wow, so many whales...
We built a ranch to protect and increase the number of whales
that are becoming extinct every year.
Whale ranch. That's amazing.
Look, that's my house.
It's an ice castle?
Humans must not be able to survive in this temperature.
Yeah. We should be thankful that we are robots.
But it seems like the South Pole hates robots.
There weren't very many robots until a while ago.
That's why people are still treating robots like slaves.
Let me go! Call the captain!
Until when are you going to keep me here without questioning?
It's no use. Stop it. You will only exhaust yourself.
I hate being in this kind of place!
A day is nothing. I've been here for four years.
I heard that more than 50 times now. Is that the only thing you've got?
Do you want to hear about Black Looks?
Yes. I'll give you a dime.
You won't be able to get out of here until you die anyway.
Ask me anything. I'll tell you anything I know.
I have tons of questions.
Why do Black Looks attack only robots?
That's a good question.
He has a scary childhood memory.
He lost his mother to a robot.
To a robot? No way!
It must have killed her quite terribly.
That's why he hates robots.
Who are you?
I used to work for him.
Who in the world is Black Looks?
Well, I don't know that.
This is not the time to be like this.
I'm going to escape. Will you help me?
You shouldn't waste your time. How are you going to do it?
That's...
Like this.
Don't think of me so bad.
Help! Come here!
-What's wrong? -Be quiet!
-He fell. -What?
Hurry and open it!
Thief! Catch him!
Stupid.
If you go into that field, you won't be able to come back alive.
We don't even need to chase him. Let him die out there.
So it's like this. Has anyone seen him?
-Well... -I feel like I've seen him somewhere...
This doesn't work. Huh?
Jet is here.
Black mask! That's Black Looks.
-Black Looks? -He's going to kill us!
He's going to kill us all and steal all our money!
He's not someone whom we can fight back. Everyone, be ready.
No! Let's fight together!
No. We would never be able to win.
I have an idea!
Everyone, please wait for my signal in the top room of this house!
-What are you talking about? -We don't have time! Hurry!
All right. Let's hide first.
Kill them all!
-Yes, sir! -Get rid of them!
Where are you? Come out!
Hiding won't save you. Come out!
There's no one.
-Not here, either. -Same here.
All right, it's now!
Everyone, begin!
Ah, over there. On top of chandelier!
-They ran away! -Over there!
Move back!
Jet is...
Boss, let's steal a car and run away.
Stupid, I will come back.
Robot hospital? Please come right away.
All right, we will wait.
Everyone,
even though they are villains, they are human. No one can die.
I'm out of gas here?
I'd rather try my best than to freeze to death here.
What a land of snowstorm.
Someone's fallen down.
It must be human to fall down because of a snowstorm. Help him.
This one is...
Boss! This one's that kid robot's company!
What? How do you know?
I had a fight with him at the airport this morning. Good. Let's shoot him and go!
Hold on. I have a good idea. Burn.
What? Okay.
Now I can take revenge on that kid robot.
-Why is robot so kind? -I'm a nurse. It's a sure thing.
Thank you.
-Nurse robots are really good workers. -It's all thanks to you.
That is...
Maybe...
How can this be...
Do you know her?
I brought her from Japan.
I sent her to Japan.
What?
This robot used to be a nurse working for me.
She had a kind heart.
She raised human orphans. Kids loved her.
One day, there was a huge upheaval for the advancement of robots.
She participated there and went missing.
And a few days ago, as I was returning from house calls,
I found her terribly broken in scrap yard.
It's sad but here, robots are expendables.
There isn't a place to fix such terribly broken robots.
That's why I sent it to Doctor Ochanomizu in Japan.
After that, I found her head and other components.
Would you like to come to my office?
Yes!
Are you awake, Mr. Beard?
Black Looks!
Ah, this is...
Are you surprised? This is my treasure storage. It's worth billions of dollars!
What a thief.
That's right. I'm a thief.
But I don't steal from humans. I'm only after robots!
That's an excuse! A thief is a thief.
My mother was killed by a robot!
Robot is my enemy. These are nothing compared to my mother's life...
Will you help me after getting paid,
or will you get killed?
-All right. I'll take this much money. -Are you on my side now?
Wrong guy!
Getting caught in electric wire? Poor you, Mr. Beard.
It's done.
This is Rosaline, who used to be our nurse.
Now all the riddles will be solved.
Yes!
Atom, this is Black Looks.
Looks!
Mr. Beard? How dare you!
Whatever.
If you want him back, come to the valley of seal.
I'm sorry, but it's about time to decide.
I'll let you see some special execution event.
Atom will get here soon. As soon as he opens that door,
A 50,000-voltage electric current will flow to that pass and you will die!
Shoot...
Goodbye!
Mr. Beard, please hold on.
Mr. Beard!
Come out, Black Looks!
I'm here as I promised!
Welcome, Atom.
Mr. Beard is in that front room. Save him if you can!
That door won't open that easily.
Atom, don't be fooled by him! As soon as the door opens, I will get toasted!
Atom, no! Please don't come in!
Ah, it's over!
Something was suspicious, so I entered without opening the door.
Thank goodness.
Atom, catch Black Looks!
-Yes! -Don't miss him!
I've been waiting, Atom.
Let me finish this.
Atom!
Stop!
Atom, it's my defeat.
Then take that mask off!
You can take it off.
All right.
You are...
What's so shocking about it?
You are only about a middle school student...
Revenge is a scary thing.
Now, do whatever pleases you!
Teacher.
Looks, can you remember me?
Who are you?
You might not remember since you were too young, but I remember.
Rosaline!
Looks.
No way.
Looks, baby.
This is your mom.
Lie!
No, my mom's dead. You are fake.
Looks, have you forgotten my voice? I didn't forget you.
Since I got broken, you became alone...
Broken?
My mom was human. She died.
How can a human be born out of a robot?
You were an orphan.
That's why I hid my identity and raised you.
In this country, it's unforgivable for a robot to raise a human baby.
I participated in that protest for the advancement of robots
because I wanted to be acknowledged as your mom.
But I got destroyed by someone who was against that protest.
Looks, do you understand? Call her mom.
How come?
That's right. It's mom's lap you remember.
She's my mom.
Mom!
Looks...
If there could be only one resting place...
A huge scrap that fell from the night sky.
After assembling them...
Wow! It became a very powerful-looking robot!
What's your name?
Garon?
Garon who remodels everything
started spreading poisonous gas in a deserted island in the South.
No latest jet or missile won't work!
All right, Garon! I'm for it!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Devil Garon". Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "The Devil Garon"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together