Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Damdam's Neck
Yes, this is Ochanomizu.
What's up, so late at this hour?
What?
Hmm. All right.
All right, don't let anyone near it
until I get there.
Hello? Ah, Doctor Ochanomizu.
Huh? Atom?
That's difficult. Robots must sleep early as well.
It's a big case! I have no time to explain.
Please. Please call Atom.
-If you say so. Hold on. -I'm sorry.
Gosh, please hurry.
Oh, Atom. All right? Listen carefully to what I say.
Yes! Yes... Neck?
Yes, Damdam.
I can never understand what people say.
They told me that kids should sleep early, then they would call me at this late hour?
Yes, all right. I'm coming.
Ah, Atom.
Where are you going so late at night?
I'm sorry. There's a big trouble. I'll be back!
That's it. Good.
Ah! It's there.
Atom.
Was it okay?
How's it, Damdam? Is it all cured?
Yes...
Damdam, while you were being transported to Earth from Mars,
you lost your neck due to a rocket accident and explosion.
So you lost your memory and work ability,
but thanks to new electronic brain and vocal cords,
you can now live with no problem.
Thank you.
Ah, this is Atom.
He helped rescuing you when you were in accident.
I'm Atom! Nice to meet you.
I owe you. Thank you.
Doctor Maxon, who made you, will come pick you up.
Let's work on small things to get you used to it.
Okay.
Doctor, did I not have neck originally?
...No.
The explosion shattered everything.
Doctor Ochanomizu! I don't think my neck was shattered.
Wh, what?
I was fooled and got my neck stolen.
Damdam, calm down. Why would you think that your neck was stolen?
My body was made to cultivate the planet, so I worked hard in Mars base.
I wouldn't even get a scratch with a mere explosion.
Besides, while everything else's okay, would only my neck get exploded?
However, if you've got your neck stolen, you should know!
During the explosion, I fell down and passed out.
My neck must have been stolen by then.
You are just making guesses.
No!
Atom, when you rescued me, did you notice anything?
Th, that is...
For example, some suspicious ones were next to me?
Damdam, forget about previous neck.
Here, I made a new neck. Would you like to try it on?
It's a great neck, Damdam. Look.
No! I don't want this kind of neck!
Atom, you would hate to have some other neck than yours, right?
Besides, my neck's somewhere there.
I somehow have that feeling, Atom!
Damdam, you are tired. Go sleep.
Here, Atom. Let's go back.
I'd like to meet Doctor Ochanomizu!
No way. He called a student late at night
and he's making him miss classes, too? How dare!
-That guy is? -Mr. Beard, this way.
It must be painful, but please bear with me.
You can't do this, Doctor. Atom's still an elementary student.
Parents protested to school, so I...
Hey, I'm sorry, Mr. Beard. Something has occurred. In fact...
What? That's a problem.
No, I didn't say anything yet, Mr. Beard.
Nah, Doctor Ochanomizu wouldn't call Atom without any reason.
Something interesting must have occurred. I'd like to join as well.
But what kind of case is it?
Doctor Maxon has just arrived and is headed that way.
Doctor Maxon!
Hey, it's been a long time.
Ochanomizu. Give Damdam's neck back.
Doctor Maxon.
I know it, Ochanomizu.
I know you hid Damdam's neck.
Doctor Maxon, you are right. I hid Damdam's neck.
But please hear me, Doctor Maxon.
Damdam's neck is too dangerous in Earth.
I mean, even if it were for planet cultivation,
how could you install a neutron beam to a robot?
Damdam isn't a combat robot!
It's a Mars cultivation robot. It's for construction.
No! I'm not insisting my way. I have...
It feels like Damdam's neck will occur something scary.
Hah! You are just being jealous.
You were jealous of Damdam's success in Mars. That's why you are...
Maxon, I...
Ochanomizu! What you did is a theft.
Here! Give me Damdam's neck back. Give me!
If you say so.
It's not here!
Damdam's neck isn't here!
-What? -It's stolen...
Doctor, Wasn't Damdam's neck
contained in a duralumin box of this size?
That's right.
Shoot. It's that one.
Someone suspicious carried a cart in lobby. I have a hunch.
Mr. Beard!
-Atom, follow me! -Okay!
Shoot... Where did he go?
Ah, that's right.
Gosh. I don't hear any cart even after maximizing my ear power.
What a thief!
-Oh! Atom, how was it? -Not a hint, Teacher.
You are responsible for this!
There's a problem!
Doctor Ochanomizu, Damdam is!
What's wrong?
Yes... Damdam took off...
Saying he would get his neck back...
Ochanomizu! It's all your fault.
No matter what happens, you will have to take responsibility.
Gosh! What an annoying old man.
Doctor Ochanomizu, don't worry.
That Damedame or Damdam's neck,
I, Mr. Beard, will find it back for sure.
Stop!
Give me my neck.
I'm looking for my neck.
I'm going to borrow that one and try it!
Stop kidding! If I lose my neck, I'll get ruined!
I'll take it even if you don't want to!
Stop!
It doesn't fit. This is not it.
I'm sorry. Get some repair work.
This is not it, either.
Not this one.
Eight neck robberies have occurred in Tokyo last night.
According to the police's announcement,
the criminal is Damdam, a cultivating robot for Mars,
This is a trouble, Doctor.
This will be your responsibility, Doctor.
I... disbanded Damdam's neck. I...
Could we make this child robot responsible for this case?
Atom doesn't have any fault.
I asked him to get Damdam's neck.
You guys really did needless work!
I'm going to take your neck!
Damdam, let's go back to the Ministry of Science.
Who are you?
Atom!
I'm not going back to the ministry. I'm going to find my neck.
You won't be able to find your neck this way.
Shut up!
If you have to take me back, then use your power.
Ah, Damdam. I don't want to fight you.
If you are not going to listen...
Damdam, run.
You will get destructed if you fight the police here.
Good bye, Atom!
You again? Thanks to you, I lost Damdam.
A robot shouldn't interfere with this. Go back!
Stop it, Tawashi.
Atom's doing his best.
Hmm, good.
Ten recent laser guns stolen from Earth defenders!
How much is it?
-500 yen! -30,000 yen!
-10 million! -60 million!
All right, the winning bid is 60 million!
I learned this a while ago. I sneaked in well.
Ah! Skunk is here.
Then it must be true that something great will be traded here today.
Here, the best one of today.
It's the neck of neck hunter robot that's been making news lately!
That's it! We finally found it.
If this neck gets connected to Damdam, it becomes a million-horsepower robot!
This neck alone has a tremendous weapon, too!
This is interesting.
Maybe I could use that to get rid of Atom.
Now 30 million, 30 million! 30 million is the highest!
-50 million! -100 million.
-800 million! -Good, I'm taking that neck.
But cheaper.
What a trouble.
You must be Damdam.
As expected, you seem to have a strong body.
We are not here to get you. We are hear to make a deal.
We plan to give you your neck back.
What? My neck?
There's a condition to it.
Yes. All right. Atom, phone call.
Okay!
Yes! This is Atom.
Damdam! Where are you?
Yes, all right. I'll be on my way.
Ah, Atom.
Atom! Where are you going?
So early in the morning. What a kid!
Damdam!
What are you doing, Damdam?
Skunk said he would give my neck back if I knock you down!
Skunk won't give it back even if you knock me down!
You are getting fooled!
I'll be happy if I can get my neck back!
Damdam, you fool!
My neck!
Ah, dangerous!
Don't think of it badly.
Boss ordered to knock both of them down.
Damdam!
My neck... How dare you attack me.
I'm sorry, Damdam. I'm the one who disbanded your neck.
Doctor Ochanomizu told me that your neck is dangerous.
That's why...
Your neck isn't good for yourself, either...
But I wouldn't want to lose my neck, either.
I'll get it back.
Atom.
So promise me, Damdam.
Promise me you won't act violently even after you get your neck back.
I would have no problem if I can get my neck back.
Stay still until I come back.
He went this way.
Stupid! You think you got rid of Atom by just pushing him to a landslide?
-Is that not right? -Gosh!
Of course not! Atom has a million horsepower.
Do you want to be buried alive?
You stupid.
Mr. Beard, real name is Shunsaku Ban.
It's been a long time, Skunk.
What a game. Get rid of it!
Gosh! We can't defeat that.
Run!
Oh, Atom. Take this!
Shoot...
Gotcha!
Hey! Are you going to get the neck again?
No, I'm going to give it back to Damdam. I promised Damdam.
No! If you give Damdam his neck, something scary will happen!
I know.
But it's a promise, so I'm going to take it to Damdam and have a talk.
Atom...
I don't want to break a promise.
Oh, it's my neck.
Atom, you got it back. Thank you.
Let me put it back. Give it back to me.
Damdam, I have something to tell you.
Stop being so weird and give it back!
Could you not give this up?
What?
If you put this back, something bad will happen.
I can't have my own neck back in its place?
Damdam, please understand me. Please.
Let's ask the doctor to make a new one.
Shut up. I'm going to take it by force!
Ah! Damdam!
-No, Damdam. -It's my neck!
I shouldn't have shown you the neck.
I'm going to get my neck back no matter what.
Why can't you understand?!
Give me my neck back!
No! I can't!
Stop it!
Damdam, stop it.
Shut up!
No!
It's my neck.
Leave it.
Leave it!
Dangerous, Damdam!
Damdam...
Damdam, I'm sorry, sorry...
Neck hunting robot destroyed itself as well...
Damdam...
A neck with neutron beam...
Atom!
Why did humans make such robot? Why?!
Happy Christmas eve.
In this National Robot Museum, Robot Awards is taking place.
Wow, Lightning Man is a fabulous robot.
It will win the Grand Prix.
What? Skunk installed a timed bomb on Lighting?
No! We have to save Lightning!
Next on Astro Boy. "Lightning Man." Look forward to it!
Next on Astro Boy, "Lightning Man"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together