Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a hundred-thousand horsepower engine
Iron-Arm Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-fold power
Iron-Arm Atom
In order to create parents
that befit you...
I'd asked the specialist in the field,
Dr. Tatsuta, to design the faces.
I'm relieved they came out excellent as expected.
But I feel weird that I'm the one carrying those.
Look, we're off shore near Kinkazan.
Professor! Something's wrong!
This is Service no. 304, Control Tower, respond, Control Tower!
Wh-What a horrible magnetic storm!! The gauges all broke down!
N-No...
P-Professor!
We're saved...
Atom vs. Atlas II: The Resurrection of Atlas
Atom! Atom! Where are you?!
Atom!
This is similar to a 'Neotechtron'...
I was clasping it when I recovered my senses.
Let's examine it as soon as we return.
Anyway, it's all thanks to Atom
Thanks to you, there's no casualties... Everyone feels grateful.
No problem.
Professor!
Professor Ochanomizu!
How did the accident happen
We hurried here the moment we heard the news
What was exactly the cause of the accident?
It was a magnetic storm.
Magnetic storm?
It was different from a normal magnetic storm,
it was extremely violent, and focused only on that aeroplane.
Damn! We missed an extraordinary gemstone
just by a step... Come on, hurry up!
Understood!
Huh?
To actually see a father and a mother...
It feels a little bit strange.
Hahaha... we only need a cardiovascular test before completion.
We thought the sooner it is, the better
So we called you here
See, right here
Come, come closer and see
Well?
Mother's quite a beauty, isn't she?
Father's superb, too.
Until now, I acted as Atom's guardian
but when these are completed, they'll make a wonderful father and mother.
Live happily ever after with them.
Yes! Professor Ochanomizu
Hmm?
What is it, Atom?
N-No, it's okay... It's nothing.
Damn...persistent bastards!
Okay, okay!
Damn!
Resistance is futile! Disarm yourselves and surrender!
W-We should raise up our hands, Boss...
Heh, pestilent police!
Ah! What is it?
What in the world is that?!
Who are you?! We'll fire if you come any closer!
I-It's dangerous... We should escape!
Hurry up!
You can't be a proper villain like that, Atlas.
S...So you're actually the 'Atlas'?
This is an all-powerful transformation. It's only natural you were unaware.
Damn you...
Boss, can we really trust them?
I could bring you the same fate as them, if you want.
Ah... okay... Really, the 'Atlas'?
Heh, you know... heh heh heh...
H-Hold on, Atlas Where are planning to go?
Do you have anywhere to go at all? Huh?
Well, ask this guy over here.
I've decided! Come with me
I'll take care of you.
Come on, hurry!
Heh heh heh... It's getting interesting.
There's no mistake, this is a Neotechtron
Neotechtron?
It is said that it's a meteorite from outer space
It's beyond the reach of human science.
And yet, why did this Neotechtron
appear out of nowhere in the seas near Mount Kinka?
First, a try-out.
Try smashing that ATM over there.
What? Are you toying with me?
Heh heh... don't say that now. It's just a test, a test.
What a pity.
Hey, Atlas
W-Wait... It's all my fault!
I'll take you to a bigger place
Satisfied? You should feel better now, heh heh...
Hee hee hee hee... Good, Atlas.
Next, the jewellery store.
Hmph.
Both jewellery store and the bank
were completely obliterated, which explains
the ferocity of the modus operandi.
Who on the earth could possibly do this?
Ah, the police is here, let's see how the investigation fares so far
The problem is the estimated destructive power of the culprit.
Destructive power?
The only one who could do such a thing without using explosives
that's right, the culprit couldn't possibly be a human.
Inspector Tawashi!
I shall definitely
arrest the criminal who dared to do this!
What foolishness! If it isn't human, then it's a robot
Yes, a robot. And?
How can a robot have a motive of crime?!
Professor...
You'll find out in time. No need to worry.
Professor! Troubles!
Just moments ago, the jewellery facilities of the Ministry of Trade and Industry
were attacked by a renegade robot!
What? A robot?!
A never before seen robot was running amok
Inspector Nakamura's team also rushed immediately
Never before seen? Fools!
Pro-Professor!
Damn! It's the exactly same modus operandi!
It's definitely a robot's doing!
So you really saw a robot
attacking those facilities?
I... I was terrified! But I'm sure it was a robot!
That's right! Gigantic, like this~
It was a robot without a doubt, wasn't it?
Unbelievable, that a robot could do such a thing...
It's beyond my understanding...
It's not a lie! I saw it myself!
Spread the cash! Money, money! We're rich!! Heh heh heh
Heh heh, look, with this much money,
We could live it up for a while!
But, that fellow, isn't he a little eerie?
We should be on our guard, Boss.
Atlas, huh? What, his methods are a bit clumsy
but he's gotten much better than before!
Isn't that right, Atlas?
Huh? That oaf... where is he?
That oaf!
Where are you going, Atlas?!
You're all boring. I'm quitting.
Wh-what?
H-Hold a sec! Damn!
It's no use. Hey, a car!
I'm not letting you away, come back here!
Pesky fools...
F... Fool!
H-He's done for!
What, again
It feels like someone is calling
Ugh... again...
Who-Who is it!
What do you think you're doing?
Ah, thief!
There, go!
W-Wait!
What is it?
A-Atom, it's terrible, your parents are...
What? My father and mother were...?
What is this exactly...?
I'm sorry, Atom, it was so sudden.
Just the robot units!
I hope Atom's parents are safe...
Papa, Mama...
Who dared to do this?
It was a gigantic robot
It is too true... I saw with my own eyes.
All the recent incidents were definitely its doing.
I can't imagine there could be such a dangerous robot.
There's only one way, the Omega Factor!
Omega Factor?
It was created by a scientist named 'Walpurgis', a long time ago
If it is put into a robot, the robot can commit
heinous crimes without the slightest remorse! It's a fearsome factor!
Among us scientists, its use is
strictly forbidden...
However, a robot who can commit crimes to such extent...
there's no other explanation other than the Omega Factor.
Recently, I'm starting to feel a weird sensation near my chest...
and incidents would follow immediately.
Wh... What?!
I don't know why, but it's as if someone's beckoning to me
That's how I came here today as well
But, Atom, it could be a coincidence...
No, he was definitely calling out to me
I'll find him for sure
And save Papa and Mama from him!
W...Wait a minute, Atom!
If you're going, at least equip the Synchronometer!
Synchronometer?
It's a tracking radar device
Atom, open your abdomen parts
Yes
There, that should do it
Then go, Atom, and be careful!
Y-Yes!
It's faint, but it seems this is the way
Papa, Mama, I'll definitely...
Oh! Atom's flying over the sea now
This is near Mount Kinga
Mount Kinga?
It's calling out to me after all... in the sea...
Ah! That! Ugh, Aah...
Uwaa! Wh...What?!
A magnetic storm!
Splashdown!
Where's this?
Ah! Neotechtron has become...!
You... you're!
It's me, Atom.
You... you, but it's impossible!
I'm Atlas, the real thing.
Atlas! You... you're that... Atlas...
I've died once, but I've revived
to conquer these humans who made me wretched
Aren't you a robot?
You couldn't possibly think about such things!
Hu hu hu... Atom, won't you join me?
If you do so, you'll understand everything.
Return my Papa and Mama!
Your parents? Are you talking about those robot units?
Ah! Papa, Mama!
Why are you doing such a cruel thing?!
I'll become the emperor of this world. For that, I need to
take care of a lot of trivialities.
I need workers.
Atom, you should assist me here as well.
I am sure we can impress each other.
Never!
I'll go back with Papa and Mama!
Wahaha... Papa and Mama?
Stop making me laugh! Robots do not have parents!
Atom, open your eyes. You're being deceived by humans.
I am currently creating something here.
It is something unreachable by the limited wisdom of humans.
Planes will fall, drawn by this magnetic activity only
But my weapon of world dominance must be even more stronger!
And for that, this base is the absolute stepping stone for me!
I think what you're doing is wrong.
I don't agree!
I thought we could get along. What a shame.
Prepare yourself, Atom!
Ah, What are you doing!
Ugh, the energy is...
Energy-sucking sword, Zero Saber! Taste it!
Atlas, stop!
Very well, if you think so!
Atom, stop!
Atom, we'll finish this later.
Papa, Mama
Papa, Mama!
Ah, what's that?
Oh... maybe some kind of underwater explosion...
What?!
It's Atom!
W...What?! Let me see that
I... it's painful!
Oh~! They're safe! The parent units have also returned!
So the cause of the magnetic storm of that base...
This 'Atlas' robot should not be taken lightly...
Atom, you need to take caution
Yes, Professor Ochanomizu.
Here's...?
From today, it's your home, Atom.
My home?
Come, let's get inside
Ah~! Jump!
Jump... Ah!
Ahem, Oh? Hahaha... is that you, Atom?
Yeah... Yeah!
Welcome, Atom
Ye... Yeah!
Don't be so shy. It's your home. Though it's on sale now.
Come, come...
Wow...
Papa! Mama!
Atom...
[Next Episode]
Robot Land is a merry land of dreams!
The dream of every child on earth
But one day, a swan came running into our house!
The one who's been pursuing the Swan Princess Odette
is none other than the Demon King, Saturn!
Princess Odette is in danger... we should do something...
Ah! We've been deceived! It's a trap!
Next on [Astro Boy]...
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight eyes
Laser Blast hands
Seven-fold powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together