Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
Watch out!
Livian...
Ah, Livian!
What are you doing!
Atom vs. Atlas VI: The King in the Ice
Is Atlas that much of a scary robot?
Then why is Livian with such robot like this?
Livian is so beautiful. She's like a princess of a country.
Atlas has a reason to be obsessed.
Uran, what's up with such talking manner?
Huh? Atom, did Livian run away from Atlas?
I don't know well either.
But Atlas couldn't have lost Livian that easily.
- Oh, she's back. - Livian,
Livian, it's me. Atom.
A...tom?
This is jump. Look.
When you were locked in the Crystal,
You are the one who let Jump go.
Ju...mp?
What do you call this...Amne...?
Amnesia?
Yeah, that.
You forget everything because of a shock. I've seen it in movies.
Amnesia?
We should take her to Dr. Ochanomizu.
Okay.
Oh, no, that party was looking for us.
You can never move.
What kind of guys are they?
Hmm, there isn't any problem, but she does have a memory problem.
So because of that, she has a sort of... amnesia.
As expected.
Then, let me have a look at the memory part.
- Hmm. - How is it?
She's using a complete different system than the one we manufacture.
Atlas must be a real genius.
How's her response?
There is a problem, as expected.
Good! Let me give it a energy shock.
Atom,
Yes, it's Atom.
A...tom.
I thought it worked. I only need a clue to fix this.
Livian, what could have happened?
Wow... That's amazing.
That's beautiful.
Look at that.
Huh? That is?
- What's that? - That's a huge light.
- Iceberg is melting. - No way.
Noah,
It wants to say something.
Hmm, okay. Shall we give it one more energy shock?
Here, Livian,
Minister, one third of ice in North Pole suddenly melted down!
- Huh? - What did you say?
Doctor, one fifth of Alaskan territory is submerged in water.
There are many people injured and missing.
A huge flood in Siberia because of Tundra's meltdown?
And Japan has a problem in Sapporo?
What? Is the noodles ready? Don't be mistaken with the Sapporo noodles!
Doctor! There's a call from United Nations.
Minister, please come to Weather Bureau as quickly as possible.
Minister, please come to Technology Development Department.
Doctor! There's a call from the President of the U.S.
Okay. And?
What? Huh? Oh my.
Stop talking at the same time!
Anyway, Atom, go to North Pole and figure out what happened.
Yes, sir!
That's a huge wave.
Doctor is irresponsible, too. He returned her before she got perfectly well.
Poor Livian.
Well, he couldn't help it. The whole world is in trouble with this weather problem.
What would happen if the entire ice in the North Pole melts down?
Oceans would get much water. Ice is originally water, you know.
I already know that.
But honey, this is a serious problem.
Anyhow, the water level would get higher for more than 30 meters.
30 meters?
If it gets higher for 30 meters...
Cities near oceans would all get submerged.
- Tokyo as well? - Of course.
Wow, that's a problem.
Of course it is.
Then there wouldn't be much place for people to live in,
and the weather would get weird, so there would be many heavy rains and floods.
There wouldn't be much crops...
Wow, it is a big problem, now that I think about it.
Noah...
This is the center of the North Pole.
There isn't any strange part about it... Fine, let's go to Greenland next.
Second stage!
What? You didn't figure anything out?
Yes. I didn't find anything that could be a cause for this.
Well, it must be true since Atom did the job.
But then, why?
I don't know. I don't know! Now I have no idea at all.
There's a big problem!
The rest of the North Pole's ice began to melt down again!
Wh, what?
Ah, Doctor!
Alert the places immediately!
Hachinohe had less damage relatively.
The hlf of New York has already been submerged.
Now most of the ice in the North Pole has melted except for the big glacier in Greenland.
It is predicted to have more damages following waves, floods and abnormal climate.
Livian!
Are you all right, Livian?
Atlas went to the North Pole and... Ice...
Atlas did?
Yes, I escaped while Atlas was out.
Atlas' scary plan.
I'm going to let Atom know about Operation Noah.
I see.
What? Atlas melted the entire ice in the North Pole?
Atlas did?
Ah... This is getting troublesome.
Department of Technology Development
It's me, Ochanomizu. Please make the quantum-freeze bomb ready.
The quantum-freeze bomb?
Hmm, since there is an air pollution every year,
the atmosphere has become like a greenhouse.
So the temperature of the earth is rising little by little.
Between now and then, the ice in the North and South Pole might melt down.
I've been making something for that kind of situation.
With this one shot, we would be able to re-create the ice lost in the North Pole so far.
That's amazing.
Since it's very powerful and is in experimental stage, I don't want to use it if possible,
but now is not the right time. Shall we use it?
Yes!
If the big glacier in Greenland also melts down, the world would be in big trouble.
Please don't be late, Atom.
Ah, what is it! You guys!
Stop it.
Don't hurt these people. I'm going back to the Crystal.
Livian!
I assumed it would be discovered soon.
But I already achieved my purpose.
This is my destiny.
Livian!
Ah, it's Greenland.
This is the entrance Livian told us.
All set. Now the earth is Atlas'.
Operation Noah. Stage Three!
Atom!
How did you?
Livian told me!
Livian did?
Whatever. Livian is locked in the Crystal.
Besides, the Crystal is outside the atmosphere.
Livian got out of it, staking her own life.
And she told us all about this base.
Livian.
Atom, stop that silly talk. Livian is there like that.
Livian, Atom says that you escaped that place; is that true?
Yes, he's right.
Wh, what?
How dare you do that while I was away from the Crystal!
But why, why did you do such thing?
Atlas, don't you know how much scary what you are trying to do is?
Shut up!
Shut up. Shut up, Livian. Don't interfere with my work.
No, Atlas.
Atlas, don't be silly.
I, Atlas, am going to conquer the earth.
I'm going to be the king of this entire world!
Atom, I'm going to kill you today for sure!
You!
Atom, die!
Atlas.
Mom and dad are mad about what Uran did.
So she was dragged to piano classes by force.
Uran, behave.
Uran got excited about robot wrestling match, so she snuck out.
The audience was excited at Uran's power.
But there was a huge conspiracy there...
Next on Astro Boy. Uran and Uran. Please look forward!
Next on Astro Boy. "Uran and Uran"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light.
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together