Astro Boy
Over the sky, la-la-la
Beyond the stars
Let's go, Atom
Until the jet limit
A heart-warming la-la-la
The child of science
It's a million-horsepower engine
Mighty Atom
Listen carefully, la-la-la
Open your eyes wide
That's right, Atom
Don't be off your guard
A righteous la-la-la
The child of science
It's a seven-force power
Mighty Atom
This is Captain Tsukioka from the Satellite Patrol.
We have found a wrecked rocket.
The site is P-75. All assemble.
They are space gangs.
This is Tsukioka! Space gangs have escaped to W-38.
-Block them! -Roger!
Hold on! Stop pursuing them!
They are headed to the space airport.
Shoot... They hid there again.
Space Airport R-45
A space shuttle from Earth have arrived at the space airport R-45.
This is where rockets that travel to Moon or further gather.
Rockets from all around the world.
The space airport is a resting place for rockets.
So it's very crowded and busy.
Space airports looks like a downtown of a big city inside.
People and robots come and go.
There are hotels.
Movies as well.
And restaurants!
There are dishes that are not available at the end of space.
Rocket workers can finally have their Earth food here.
This is the downtown.
I'm right now on my way to meet the space airport director
to discuss recent space gang problems.
There are all kinds of stores.
This is a souvenir store.
Welcome. We have everything. We are the best for space souvenirs.
Meteor piece for kimchi jar.
How about Mars postcards?
Back issues of magazine from Earth. $1 for a bundle!
This is a frozen monster from Venus.
Welcome. Can I help you, sir?
I see. You need a new spacesuit, right?
This is a new seamless spacesuit.
Here!
It's $320 for both top and bottom!
No, sir. I wanted to ask you something.
Is that so? We also have some guide books.
Hotel guide books, traveling rocket guide books.
It's 20 cents a book.
No, about that space gang...
Space gang? Ah, well that is...
We don't sell them here. Ask somewhere else.
Don't be stupid! I don't want to be involved with them!
But we are good citizens.
We have to fight against violence with justice...
Shut up! If you are a good citizen,
it's better for you to just ignore!
-Okay? -Okay.
Director, it's your responsibility.
You've been managing this space airport for 30 years already.
Isn't it about time for you to retire?
If you keep making mistakes, people will lose confidence in you.
Rocket accidents happen everyday.
Thanks to that, the number of guests in my hotel has decreased a lot.
Do you think this will be over like this? You have to retire.
We have to get a new airport director.
No! I still have some work left.
I'm not going to step back!
I hope you take your word for it.
Anyhow, no more rocket accidents, please.
Such a greedy old one.
It's just a matter of time for him to step down.
Then, I'll be the new director.
This is the eleventh one now.
Now my dad's credibility will get lower and lower.
Excuse me...
-Mr.Tsukioka? -That's right. And you?
I'm Atom, a robot.
What is robot doing here?
I'm here to help get rid of space gangs upon Dr.Ochanomizu's order.
Thank you, but it's not something a robot can do.
Go back to Earth.
Hello, hello! What? Space gangs again?
The site is about 160,000Km to Bethelkius Star.
Mister! What happened?
Space gangs again.
Late...
What are you?
You shouldn't come to place like this. It's dangerous!
I'm sorry. But please let me take a look.
Robot's broken.
Gangs did it.
Captain! It's an evidence. It will be a clue
That won't help.
I can figure out, because I'm a robot as well.
This robot...
This robot saw the face of the criminal. For sure!
I'm home!
Dad.
That's weird. Where did he go?
Dad!
It's dad.
He's carrying something. It looks like a person.
It looks like a corpse.
He threw a corpse away in space?
Ah, Tsukio, you are home.
Dad, I've been hearing rumors. Is there a pressure for you to retire?
I will arrest gangs for sure, so please don't retire. All right?
I won't. I'm going to work more.
Look. You used to be that small 20 years ago.
You were born in this Satellite R-45 and grew up here.
R-45 and you are more precious than my own life.
Do you think I'd give that up? It's better for me to die than to leave this place.
I'm going to finish my life here on R-45.
I'm not going to be discouraged by some attacks or blames.
Why are you so downhearted?
Go to sleep. It's late.
Good night.
Welcome. We have everything. We are the best for space souvenirs.
A sample of wrecked rockets.
Fairy's costume piece.
This is the famous Venus cake.
You can't stop once you take a bite. How does it taste?
-Two more bites, you will fall in love. -You are so cunning.
More and more bites! Would you like to buy?
Empty box of Venus cake on sale.
Welcome. You are from...
There are many customers in your store, right?
Of course. Those who buy and sell.
Please take a look at this.
That won't do. I'm not going to buy that.
I'm not asking you to buy it.
This robot was destroyed inside a spaceship.
Robot's brain stop working as soon as it's destroyed,
so the last afterimage should be recorded in its electronic brain.
I see someone recorded in its electronic brain.
Sir, have you ever seen this face?
Right!
This is that man who came to sell that jewel yesterday.
Shut up!
Don't get involved!
You've seen him?
Where does he live? He came to sell jewels?
That is...
If you say something stupid, we will get in trouble!
A good citizen shouldn't be involved in such!
Man! I want to tell!
All right, if you want to talk about it so bad, then go talk inside there.
If you talk inside here, no one outside will be able to hear you.
-Go ahead. -I will!
Hmm... so he was trying to sell jewels.
He's staying in hotel? All right.
Get out, sir. I heard everything.
Huh? You heard everything?
Yes. I heard what you said inside there.
My ears can amplify up to 1,000 times.
Please be easy on me. Pretend you didn't hear anything!
The 120,000-ton cargo ship Arzanon was attacked again by space gangs.
Precious metals that were to be sent to Earth were all stolen.
Space gangs are beyond control lately.
Airport director Tsukioka is being held responsible for such incidents.
Are you still going to keep your position after all these mistakes?
I'm speaking on behalf of all people in the airport.
Please consider it carefully.
One more attack, and that old man will be retired.
Boss.
I want to show you something.
-Don't call me boss in a place like this! -I'm sorry,Bo...
So what do you want to show me?
Yes. Hey!
Don't surprise me! You picked it up again?
I picked it up floating in space.
It's an empty case of a robot again. It's very elaborate.
This face looks exactly like Captain Tsukioka, Boss.
So I don't understand. What's happening?
I've already picked up the same thing five times.
All of them have the same face. Besides, they are getting bigger.
What in the world is this?
Robot.
That's right. It's a robot.
Maybe...
Someone, hide in the airport director's room!
And figure his secret out! There should be something.
I'll do the job. I'm used to it.
No one would notice that I'm a gang.
It's that one.
I'm coming in.
Yes, sir.
It's odd. Nothing's happening since he entered.
All right. Let me amplify the sound.
Huh? This sound is...
That's right. It's the sound of deflating.
Boss, it was useful to sneak in.
The director takes that robot down and goes somewhere to throw it away.
Dad, that's... What is that?
Show me!
This is... a robot that looks exactly like me.
What is this? Dad!
Tsukio, I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Now I'd have to tell you everything. Please don't be shocked.
In fact, you are not human. You are a robot.
Tsukio, listen to me. I didn't have a child.
So I made a robot child and raised it, considering it as my child.
But do you know about the story of Dr.Tenma and Atom?
When Dr.Tenma made Atom,
Atom didn't grow even after time had passed.
So Dr.Tenma was disappointed.
I wanted to raise you like a human being.
So I changed your body every month.
Into a bigger one...
And I've been throwing old bodies away like this secretly.
Forgive me. I didn't tell you because...
I'm... I'm a robot?
No way. It's all over.
How can I be a captain of men when I'm just a robot?
This is interesting.
Who is it?
You!
My, not even a drop of blood!
I'm just a machine!
Mr.Tsukio! I caught the space gang boss!
He confessed everything!
The space gang boss is the president of the hotel.
Captain, let's go arrest him.
You are late, Atom.
I was a robot. A robot cannot arrest a man.
What if they find out that I'm a robot?
I've fooled everyone!
Mr.Tsukio, don't be too sad about such fact.
I've been through this as well. But I cheered up.
You should cheer up as well, Mr.Tsukio.
Let's go!
Come in.
Captain. What's up?
You are under arrest, Rossham.
Why am I under arrest?
Because you are behind the space gang!
You are falsely accusing. I won't forgive you for this!
I have an evidence. There is a witness as well.
Is that so?
I also heard an interesting story. I also have an evidence.
The fact that you are a robot.
Walls have ears. I heard everything.
You are a robot. Just a machine!
Go ahead and arrest me.
I will tell your secret.
If people find out about your secret, they will all abandon you.
Airport director will be fired as well, since he fooled everyone.
Go ahead! Arrest me.
Hey, kids! Get this arrogant robot's fingers burnt!
How dare a robot try to arrest a man?
Shut up, you villain!
Captain! Why wouldn't you arrest him?
Even a robot can fight against villains!
Captain! Get up and fight!
Shoot!
Stop!
I missed him, Atom.
Double door.
Mr.Tsukio, dispatch the patrol! I'll follow them as well!
Roger!
Patrol team is here.
Lose them!
You think I'll be done with such bullet?
Atom!
The boss of the space gang that have been intimidating us
was surprisingly the hotel president, Rossham.
We were able to resolve this case thanks to Captain Tsukioka.
Let's give him an applause for this.
Tsukio...
Dad, they all welcomed me even after they had found out that I'm a robot.
Good for you, Tsukio.
I'll do my best. This is my home.
What about Atom?
He's doing well, Mr.Tsukio. I'm going back to Earth.
Space airport looks crowded and busy today as well.
And both the airport director and captain will carry their duties out.
Memorial is the biggest spaceship in the world.
If you win the first place with the essay about your dream, you can get a chance to ride it.
But robots... cannot dream.
So I sealed my super power for 24 hours to be like humans.
And at that moment, the spaceship was hijacked.
What should I do? My seven powers...
Next on Astro Boy, "Spaceship in Imminent Danger"
My arms and legs
fly over the sky with a jet
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Inside my waist,
a machine gun's light
Astro Boy
Mighty Atom
Searchlight's eyes
Laser Blast's hands
Seven powers, Wa Wa Wa Wa
We fight for the peace
Come on, let's go together