Come on!  Hurry up!
That was pathetic.
You didn't even make the top eight, Hiroshi-kun.
Now, now, Dr. Harada.
This means we can cheer for
Chihaya-chan and her friends.
Oh, but if they've already lost,
we're wasting our time.
Hiroshi-kun!  Don't jinx them!
They lost?
The question is: what order
do we use for the finals.
I'm guessing one of Hokuo
Academy's two Class A players
is the guy with thin eyes.
The other Class A player is that little guy.
You know him, Nishida?
I ran into him when I was
practicing as a kid.
He's one year older than me.
But we don't know what order
they're going to use.
That's true, but if we guess correctly,
If I don't want to play against a Class A player...
that increases our chances of scoring three wins.
Um... Um... Um...
Please present this to the receptionist.
Match: Finals
Team: Mizusawa High School
Order| Name
Porky
Kana-chan
Taichi
Desktomu-kun
Chihaya
Forget it!  Let's use this!
Chihaya, don't just write
down a random order.
And you're not supposed to use nicknames.
This isn't a random order.
I realized something when we
were playing Tomihara West.
The player in the center needs to
be someone with an active voice
who can keep an eye on everyone else.
On our team, that would be Taichi.
The players on the ends should be
focused on their own matches
and scoring a quick win.
That's Porky and me.
Yeah...
Monitor the situation                                    Work hard
Chihaya | Desktomu | Taichi | Kana-chan | Porky
Work super hard
Then, we put Kana-chan and Desktomu-kun
between the three of us to give them a boost!
Instead of worrying about
our opponent's order,
we should go with an order
that brings out the best in us!
It doesn't matter who we play!
We're gonna win!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 11
The Sky
Is The
Road
Home
Here is Mizusawa High School's lineup.
Thank you.
Eyebrows!  Eyebrows!
Dr. Harada.
I heard you made it to the finals!
I'm so glad to hear that.
Chihaya-chan must be on a roll.
Doctor, I never knew that Chihaya
could succumb to pressure.
Huh?  Chihaya-chan?
I chose the wrong words when
I tried to stimulate her.
I didn't think she would fall apart...
So I need to accept that I
don't even understand Chihaya,
since I'm the president of this club.
I'll be going then.
This is why I can never stop watching...
I could spend my entire youth on karuta
without ever becoming better than Arata.
Remember all the time you
spent practicing your swing.
You've already become a different person.
You'll be fine.
You can do this!
Dr. Harada.
I see that kid hasn't changed.
Hmm?
Retrot answer!
Mashima   Nishida   Chihaya   Komano   Oe
This will be their order!
So they're switching it up?
You know, does this even matter?
They're not that strong.
Anyway, I'm playing #5.
Chihaya
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
I'll take on #3, Mashima!
Huh?  Why's that, Retro-kun?
We were in the same karuta
society back in grade school.
He's never beaten me.
He'll have a mental block when he faces me.
Guaranteed
R-Really...
Then I'll assign the rest randomly.
Let's just get these regionals
over with already.
This is the year we get our revenge
against Fujisaki from Shizuoka!
We'll win every match and
the national championship!
Naturally!
Yeah!
E-Everyone, if you look too
far ahead, you'll stumble.
Yeah, yeah.
Submit our order for us, Teach.
I'm sure you're already sick of the place,
but we'll be taking you to Omi Jingu again.
I will now read the
lineup for the finals.
Hokuo Academy, Amakasu-kun.
Oh, that's me.
Mizusawa High School, Nishida-kun.
Hokuo Academy, Ryugasaki-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Oe-san.
Hokuo Academy, Kinashi-kun.
Yes!
Huh?
Mizusawa High School, Mashima-kun.
Hokuo Academy, Takuma-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Komano-kun.
Hokuo Academy, Sudo-kun.
Mizusawa High School, Ayase-san.
Dead on...
Retrot cards are scary!
Good luck.
G-Good luck.
Oh!  Sorry!
Say, "Please forgive me."
Huh?
There he goes again.
Where's my apology?
I said I was sorry...
The only apology I'll accept
is a "Please forgive me."
Huh?
Please place your cards.
Memorization time will begin now.
Wh-What's wrong with this guy?
the red that is the Tatsuta River
Why did he put that there?
Stay calm.
He's trying to get in your head
by using your favorite card.
Why, if it isn't Mochida-kun.
Oh, Harada-san!
Oh, so you're the coach for Hokuo Academy.
I'm just a fan who's not very good.
All I can do is pray...
The boy on the end is placing
his cards in a peculiar manner.
Gosh, Sudo-kun is such a strange boy.
He always rubs people the wrong way.
But if it weren't for that,
he would certainly have the
potential to become a Master.
But he might lose to one of my pupils.
Please.
That girl's only a first-year.
No, I truly believe...
That she will be a Queen in the future.
Katsugi Books
Welcome.
Manager, can I use the computer?
Don't start looking at porn.
I'm just checking my e-mail.
My computer's been acting up.
Not that I spend much time on e-mail.
Logging In
49 New Messages
Subject: Thanks!
Subject: This is Chihaya
Subject: It's getting warmer
Subject: It's starting to rain
Subject: Rain was leaking into our clubroom
Subject: This is our clubroom.
Subject: I got in trouble with Dr. Harada
Subject: How do I cut down on faults?
Subject: This is Chihaya
Subject: Karuta players are...
Subject: About hakama
Subject: Guess what happened today
Subject: Notice for the
Tokyo regional tournament
What?!  Is it spam?!
49 New Messages
Subject: Thanks!
Subject: This is Chihaya
Subject: It's getting warmer
Subject: It's starting to rain
This is Chihaya.
Thank you for sending a birthday message.
I didn't think you actually remembered my birthday.
Notice for the Tokyo regional tournament
Yay!  We have five members now, so we can
enter the tournament!  Today, we received...
Mizusawa High School's first victory!
We won!!
Taichi and Porky both did well.
We made it out of the group stage!
We won group B 3-0!
We've made it to the finals!
I'm off to win. - Chihaya
Memorization time is over.
Let's begin then.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower blooms, but for winter
Hokuo!  Five wins for a sweep!
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Yeah!
Mi!
Zu!
Sa!
Wa!
Fight!
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
I don't remember Mizusawa having a cheer.
They must have just come up with it.
Don't let the Chihaya card distract me.
Stick to my usual style.
Go on the attack.
Note that though...
He was covering the "Nothing" card on
Chihaya's side before
he took her "Note" card...
His style is also offensive.
The S in Sudo stands for striker.
Excellent.
I held mine!
I took the card!
Got it!
What about Sudo?
I scored the first card, naturally.
Everyone lost that card?
We're just getting started!
Attack, Mizusawa!
Attack.
It doesn't matter if you're wrong sometimes.
Stay active!
Pressure your opponent's side of the field!
Why are you getting so excited, Mashima?
that you pine for me as the Inaba mountain pines,
I don't remember you being a hothead.
I shall return to you
Missing********
When the wind sends waves...
Here.
After I determined to...
I want to go on the attack,
but I'm having no luck.
She keeps reading cards on my side.
Here.
Offensive karuta is meant to
weaken your opponent's psyche,
but it also provides more opportunities
for sending cards to put
yourself in a better position.
Chihaya-chan is losing
control of the game.
Stay calm...
Check the cards.
The "Chihaya" card keeps getting in my way.
Feel the love...
She finally read a card
on the opponent's side!
That's what you get for not apologizing.
Got it!
I got it!  I took a card!
Yes!
Ayase!  I took a card from
the opponent's side!
You have to do the same!
I got the card, too!
I held onto mine!
I'm gonna take the next card!
In an individual match,
one card is one card, nothing more.
But now...
like a stream widening into a river
Every card I take is a card for our team!
Though I prayed to...
Got it!  Two in a row!
Chihaya!
Ayase!
Chihaya-chan!
Wait!  That wasn't two in a row!
But that speed...
She was moving after "Though",
even though "Though my" is still on the field.
Was she gambling?
Let's take the next one, everyone!
Yeah!
Mochida-kun.
How many readers are here today?
Oh, this is just a high school regional
tournament, so she's the only one.
Focus!
Yeah!
So this is her fifth match?
I never asked to be treated colder
than the winds of Mount Hatsuse
Chihaya-chan...
Your ears already recognize this reader's quirks.
While it brings me no joy...
Hey!  Now she really took two in a row!
Yes!
Chihaya took two in a row!
Right on!
Chihaya-chan is finding her rhythm!
I can feel everyone else relax.
Every card I take is worth
more than one card.
Let's go for three in a row!
Yeah!
Chihaya-chan may recognize
the reader's quirks,
but it's more than just that.
Sometimes, she gets in a zone.
But that leads...
The tail feathers of...
To mistakes.
Double fault.
Lucky!
Smirk
Su-Sudo-senpai?!
Excuse me.
He's trying to disrupt their onslaught.
Excellent timing.
I feel so much better when
I'm looking down on people.
Hokuo!  One card at a time!
Yeah!
long as the nights I spend alone
She certainly has quick reflexes.
But...
My only thought as the boat
takes me out to sea is that
Karuta is about more than speed.
What's this?
Did I just steal her heart?
Covering cards on the opponent's side...
That was one of Arata's best techniques.
Are Arata's hands this big now?
I'm moving a card.
Huh?
There?!
Damnit!
But this is fun.
the red that is the Tatsuta River
I'll stop thinking about it too much.
That's my special card.
My hand is drawn to it,
no matter where it is.
Like a magnet.
My fear is not of...
Since the dew atop the blades...
I feel that my love is...
Chihaya's pushing hard!
What's the score?
They're both at 13?
Ayase's catching up to Hokuo's ace!
Wow!
Porky.
What?!
Wow, that's really your nickname.
You're Nishida-kun from the
Suihoku karuta society, right?
I thought you quit karuta,
since you stopped going to tournaments.
burning brightly by night,
yet extinguished by day
You used to be so strong.
As this trip takes me...
Yes!
Amakasu Nayuta...
When we practiced together,
he was just a beginner.
He was older, but he couldn't
do anything against me.
You're a hard worker, Yusei.
You'll make Class A in no time!
Now he's Class A.
What have I been doing?
I haven't seen my master in ages.
Why did I...
The sound of birds crossing...
Oh.  A dead card?!
I'm sorry!  I'm sorry!
When I must hide...
I thought I had that one...
Wait, wait, wait!
I was faster on that one!
No, you weren't!
Look!  See how my pinky is lower?
Like this!  And this!
Your hand was higher than my pinky!
You don't know when to give up!
Because I took that card!
Now, now.
We'll give this card to the side it was on.
What?!  No way!
Listen to me!
I'm telling the truth!
Yeah, that's right...
I gave up.
I feel as though my body is
on fire with Ibuki mugwort
I hear the beating of cloth...
Whoa, he did a barrel roll!
What's with him?!
That was too strong!
Nice job, Nishida!
Porky!
Let's do this!
descends from Mount Yoshino
upon my long-forgotten home
I'm going to win...
by playing my offensive karuta!
Thank you very much.
Hokuo has two wins.
One more...
We just need one more win.
Sudo-senpai and Amakasu-senpai
are having more trouble
than I was expecting.
Which means it's my turn to save them!
But...
Why is this guy so tough?!
There are four "A" cards in total.
"A house" and "A mountain
village" have been read,
A night
A mountain stream
so I can go for both of the "A" cards
on my side at the same time.
For the "Said" cards, the two "Said
world" cards have been read,
but that leaves "Said bed" and "Said night",
so I can't move on "Said."
"Impassioned was" has been read,
so I can take both "Impassionate" and
"Impassioned vows" at the same time on "Im—".
There are eight "May" cards.
"May I live, May I see,
May the scarlet, May it",
and "May the time we" have been read,
so that only leaves "May my"
and "May the time spent."
I have to be careful if the dead
card "May my lonely" is read.
Listen carefully.
Don't let yourself be tricked.
I don't have Chihaya's instincts,
and I don't have Nishida's
ability to feel the match...
May my lonely nights...
What?!
Didn't she already read that card?!
The one thing I do have is my memory
of which cards have been read.
I can become the backbone of this team!
though you have never known that pain
I won't make a mistake!
I can win one card at a time!
Said bed was cold...
Thank you very much.
One win for Mizusawa!
Excuse me.
Six more cards.
I didn't expect this match to be so close.
I can't let her take one of my cards.
May the time spent in...
He was protecting his own card.
Attack!
Sorry!  Sorry!  Sorry!  Sorry!
My dream is to become a Master
Mr. Mochida...
You were the one who taught me
that karuta is fun
whether the match is going well or poorly.
Got it!
I got it!
Two wins for Mizusawa!
Great, Nishida!
I want to take Mr. Mochida-
Take everyone to the national tournament!
I want to win!
Impassionate gods...
Thank you very much.
Chihaya!
We did it!
You scared me!
"Impassioned vows" was still on the field!
Whoa!  She's already asleep!
Chihaya-chan!
This is great!
How was she still able to take that card?
When her eyes no longer burned
with the desire to win.
We did it, Chihaya!
Arata-kun, I thought you didn't
spend much time on e-mail.
Inbox
We're going to nationals!
Look, Arata.  These are my teammates.
Come watch us at Omi Jingu! -Chihaya
Look, Arata!
These are my teammates!
Come watch us at Omi Jingu!