The National High School Karuta
Championship Tokyo Regional winner
is Mizusawa High School!
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
33rd Champion Mizusawa High School
This is a trophy...
The first trophy we earned together.
We won.
Chihaya Furu
Verse 12
Sets
These
Forbidden
Fields
Aglow
Mizusawa High School, we look forward
to seeing how you do at
the National Tournament.
We did it!
We took first in our first tournament!
Was it really okay for us to win?!
What are you talking about, Kana-chan?!
We earned the right to represent Tokyo!
Yeah!
Wh-What?!
Retro-kun?
Scary...
What are you doing?!
That trophy is-
This has...
This has been
in the clubroom since I entered
Hokuo's middle school.
I saw it every day!
We'll take it back next year!
Let's go, Retro.
You better not disgrace
Tokyo with your playing.
Senpai, we're sorry!
Don't apologize.
But Senpai,
this was your last tournament!
Huh?
This trophy carries the
weight of Tokyo with it.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Chihaya.
Welcome home.
Um, Dad.
There was a karuta tournament today-
I'm home!
Oh.  Welcome home, Chitose.
Hey, welcome home...
Hey, Dad?!
Why isn't the TV on?!
Huh?  What's on?
I told you that I was going
to be on a quiz show!
What?!  It's today?!
Oh, dear.  I thought it was next week?
I set the machine to record it.
The model, Ayase Chitose-san!
Yamamoto Goro    |     Hiroyuki
Ayase Chitose
Oh, there you are!
Quiet, Chihaya!
Good evening.  I hope to have a great time.
You look so cute!
These four members will make up one team!
Hold on!
Hmm?
Retro-kun?
What's up?
Correct!
To the celebrity team!
What question are we on?
The second question!
The team that answers the
next question correctly
will receive five hundred million points!
Wait!
See you next week!
You have to buzz in on
a quiz show if you want
the camera to move to you.
Man, I'm not cut out to be an entertainer.
But you were the prettiest person on stage!
I agree!
I'll keep on trying until
I make a Taiga drama.
So bear with me.
Then I can pay off the
mortgage on this house.
What are you talking about, Chitose?!
You just have to stand there and shine!
That's right!
Your father's purpose in life
is to pay off that mortgage!
Exactly!
And to collect clippings of my daughters!
I'm already on the seventh
volume for Chitose!
Oh, right!  You have a
photo shoot in Saipan!
Chitose
Amazing!  We'll need to make copies!
I'm on my way to the
National Karuta Championship.
I'll be representing Tokyo.
Search Results
Messages      0
The Mizusawa High School Drama Club
is in the national competition
The Mizusawa Tennis Team is
in the national tournament
I heard from Mashima-kun that you won.
Congratulations.
So, only four schools participated?
There were twelve!
It was really tough!
Oh, sorry.
The tennis team was playing
at the same time.
So the national tournament is in
July at Omi Jingu in Shiga, right?
Yes!  It's like the Koshien for karuta!
Please come with us!
Oh...
I won't be able to make it.
The tennis team has a camp then,
since they made it to nationals!
Have you heard about the miraculous
comeback in the finals?
If not, I'll tell you the story.
No, thank you.
The team's gotten better since
I became the coach this year!
Oh, but you needed an adult.
Mr. Shibata.
Yes?
I talked to Mr. Shibata and he agreed
to accompany the karuta club.
Looking forward to it!
Oh...
Thank you very much.
Be careful.
Yes...
Komano-kun, you didn't do
too well on the last test.
Don't spend too much time on the club.
Yes, ma'am.
If you'll excuse us.
I didn't know there was a
national tournament for karuta.
It's probably like a festival
at some local shrine.
If you're interested, you can
take over as their advisor.
No, thank you!
I'm just interested in the Lake Biwa
Birdman Rally on the same day.
Huh?
I hope there's another brilliant
performance in the distance category!
The Empress should care about karuta
the way she cares about tennis!
She probably thinks that
we're just playing around.
At least we got a
teacher to accompany us.
Don't quit, Desktomu-kun!
I'm so sorry!
We practiced four days a week,
and even weekends the past few weeks!
But it's just for now!
This won't last forever!
What's this about?
I'm not going to quit.
But your grades went down
because of karuta...
Well, yeah.  But I still placed fifth.
Huh?  Fifth?
I was like fifth from the bottom.
I'm not so concerned about
my grades these days.
But you should be concerned, Ayase.
Fifth from the bottom?
Mizusawa Karuta Club Advances To the
National Tournament In Their Striking Hakama
Look!  It's a small article,
but we're in the newspaper!
"Mizusawa Karuta Club advances
to the national tournament
in their striking hakama!"
Champion Mizusawa | Champion Hokuo
Champion Hokuo | Champion Hokuo | Champion Hokuo
I've never been in the newspaper before!
Hey, everyone!
Would you be up for practicing
at the Shiranami Society?
Huh?
There's only one month
left before nationals!
If we want to improve in
this short amount of time,
we need to practice against strong players!
Um, we won't.
Huh?  Why?
We're representing Tokyo!
We need to do whatever it takes!
No, that's not it...
We'll be practicing at the Suihoku Society.
Huh?
My old coach is a really good teacher.
So long!
Impressive.
They understand what they
need to improve on.
We should get going!
Recycle for a
better Japan
Oh.  I'm glad to see you,
Chihaya-chan.  Eyebrows.
Fuchu City Katamachi Cultural Center
I have so much to teach you!
Eyebrows, you don't make many
faults, but you lack fire!
Your goal should be to intimidate
the reader into reading the card you want!
Also, your body needs to be off
the ground when you swing.
Cut your nails shorter!
Chihaya-chan, your play is unstable
because of your emotions.
Focus on the cards.
Your swing is too wide.
Also, you had issues when you were
sending cards in the finals!
Move straight to the card!
Why didn't you separate
those like cards sooner?
Follow a straight line!
Wait until you've heard a unique
syllable before moving.
Okay!
Let's start playing!
Eyebrows, you'll be playing Hiroshi-kun.
He wins the second most of all
the players here, so he's strong!
Heya!
H-Heya.
Chihaya-chan will be playing me.
Give me your best shot.
Dr. Harada!
I've never beaten him before.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower blooms,
but for winter
Here comes spring,
now the flower blooms
You better not disgrace
Tokyo with your play.
We'll take it back next year!
Hiroshi-san is strong.
He's in college and he
still plays all the time.
He'll be playing in the Master
tournament this year.
How did your match with Dr. Harada go?
Huh?
What's wrong, Chihaya?
Why?
Why can't I move straight to the
right card the way the Doctor does?
Why did I lose by fifteen cards?
Why do I send the wrong cards?
Why haven't I learned how to
wait for multi-syllable cards?
Why do I get "Note that" and
"None are" mixed up?
Chihaya!
Huh?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Don't lie to me.
You don't know how to hide your feelings.
Tell me the truth!
Taichi, I think...
I'm scared of nationals.
Huh?
What if we lose miserably?
What if the Hokuo people say
that they should have gone
instead of us?
What was that for, Taichi?!
Strategy for Nationals
Secret
This is data that's been compiled
by Hokuo over the years.
Retro-kun gave it to me yesterday.
Huh?
It includes the play styles
of the usual contenders,
and a guide for the Omi Jingu building.
They even put the name of
the inn Hokuo usually uses.
This helps a lot.
But look at you.
Why are you letting a team
we beat get you down!
That's just stupid!
There's no reason to feel ashamed!
We beat them fair and square!
You can still feel it inside, right?
We're taking Hokuo and the other
schools with us to Omi Jingu.
They're our closest allies.
We took your sister to Narita.
We'll be back around ten.  Microwave your dinner.  -Mom
Oh, right.  Sis is going to Saipan.
I qualified for the Karuta
National Championship.
I'll be going to Omi Jingu in Shiga.
So I need money for travel and lodging!
But I don't want to ask them for money...
There's still a mortgage to pay off...
Search Results
Messages      0
Arata, what should I do?
Huh?
Chitose
Chihaya
from the Daily Morning
So close!
Mizusawa Karuta Club Advances To the
National Tournament In Their Striking Hakama
from the Daily Morning
Chihaya's great!
And to collect clippings of my daughters!
We're home.
My First Win
-Komano Tsutomu
Hakama Domination
-Oe Kana
Total Victory
-Mashima Taichi
Victory and Omi Beef
-Nishida Yusei
Champion
-Ayase Chihaya
Everyone, let's start
yelling when we practice!
Huh?  You mean like Mizusawa fight?
Yeah!  That's it!
Mizusawa fight!
Huh?
Ooh!  That was good, Porky!
Nishida's fired up.
He's been practicing at his local
karuta society every weekend.
Plus, he's the only one who
has experience at Omi Jingu.
Huh?
Why do you look so upset, Kana-chan?
I can no longer tell which
chrysanthemums to pluck
As the first
Is there something wrong with that card?
Oh, that.
It's a beginner's card.
Since Kana-chan hasn't learned
all the unique syllables yet.
I've learned them!
I'm upset because it's inconsiderate
to draw over a card like this.
Kana-chan's positioning
has gotten a little...
What?!
What is this?!
I've never seen anything like it!
Representing Tokyo, huh?
Spring poems.
Summer poems.
Autumn poems.
Winter poems.
The ones that fall under any
season go in the center.
Why?
Haven't you been using the
placement Porky helped you with?
I wanted to try something on my own...
It's easier for me to
memorize them this way.
Maybe, but seasons don't mean
anything in competitive karuta.
Nishida.
The schools at nationals
are all incredibly strong!
Omi Jingu can be overwhelming.
We have to prepare or we'll lose.
So we need to start with the basics.
One-syllable cards go on
the row closest to you.
Keep like cards separate.
For example, "While autumn," "While some,"
"While I," and "While the" should be...
Porky.
Huh?
Recite the "While some" poem.
"While some" is followed by "I deflect".
I don't remember the entire poem.
Snap!
Outrageous!
Ka-Kana-chan!
While some dodge the famous waves of
Takashi shore to avoid getting wet,
I deflect your artful words
to keep my sleeves dry
This is a poem about how a woman was
able to successfully ward
off a playboy's advances!
Kana-chan, nobody said that the meaning
of the poem wasn't important.
But we have to become better
at competitive karuta.
We have to become stronger so we
can properly represent Tokyo,
for the sake of the other schools who
were at the regional tournament.
Good practice!
Honestly...
It's almost time to leave.
Waves creep closer to...
Desktomu-kun!
You need to swing with more power!
You're swinging too wide!
Nishida, you should have been
able to take that card!
Move faster!
You need to start attacking
cards on the opponent's side!
Ahem.
it is as though pearls have been
strung across the autumn plain
My own sleeves...
Who put this up here?!
You did.
Um...
Er...
Hmm...
Hey, Captain.
I understand that this is important
to you, but hurry it up.
It's getting dark.
I'll turn on the lights.
The crimson sunset
sets these forbidden fields aglow
Wave not, for the guards may find us
This is my favorite poem.
It's not from Hundred Poets?
It's from Ten Thousand Leaves.
The poem was written by Emperor
Tenji's wife, Princess Nukata.
It tells the story of when her
former husband, Prince Oama,
snuck into her husband's
lands and waved to her.
Princess Nukata was so happy to see him.
But she worried that someone
might see them together.
The human heart never changes...
Ah, sorry!
I was babbling again!
You know so much, Kana-chan.
I'm used to calling the
poems "The autumn paddy"
and "The sight of" now.
I really want to win at Omi Jingu,
but I don't want to lose sight of the
fact that these cards are poetry.
What are you doing?!
It's almost time to leave school!
The Empress!
Ms. Miyauchi!
Clean up and get changed.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Wh-What are you doing, Ms. Miyauchi?!
Just give it to me.
But this is important to us!
That's why I'm taking it
to the principal's office!
Huh?
I'll put it in the center of the trophy
case in front of the principal's office.
After all, this is a very important trophy.
Huh?
Don't just stand there!
Clean everything up!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
The World of Hundred Poets
Is this what you needed?
Thank you.
I'll need to borrow it for a while.
Go ahead.
Mr. Shibata.
Oh, yes?
I'll be going to Omi Jingu.
You'll have to watch the
Birdman Rally on TV.
What?!
Don't get any ideas.
These are all mine.
No.
All mine!
You can buy your own food!
Oh! Mt. Fuji!
Looks the same as it does in the pictures.
Mt. Fuji!
The crimson sunset
sets these forbidden fields aglow
Wave not, for the guards may find us
Kana-chan...
Ever since you taught me the meaning,
the "Impassionate gods" card
has been red for me.
A bright red marker
in a field of cards...
Arata!  What's Omi Jingu like?
They hold a bunch of big karuta
tournaments there, right?
You've been there a whole
bunch of times, right?
What's it like?
It's bright red.