When I must hide these burning feelings,
Did you see that?
He began moving towards
the two-syllable card
"When I" on the first syllable.
For most players, there are only
seven one-syllable cards: "Waves,
Gust, Long, All, Swift, Look, Rain."
But in our interview, the
Master had this to say.
There are 28 one-syllable cards for him.
28 one-syllable cards?!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 25
Moonlight,
Clear
and
Bright
In other words, there
are 21 additional cards
that Master Suo can recognize
on the first syllable?
For example, he can hear
the difference between the
"When" in "When I must hide"
and the "When" in "When the misty bridge",
by the following syllable.
In the world of karuta,
we describe this ability
as having excellent game sense.
It would be safe to
assume that Master Suo
has the best sense of
all current players.
But his sense is so lame.
I feel as though my body is
on fire with Ibuki mugwort
(While) some dodge the famous waves of
Takashi shore to avoid getting wet,
I love you, Kyoko-tan.
Of all the certified readers,
Kyoko-tan is the one who loves
the Japanese language the most.
The "Like" in "Like a boatsman".
The "Like" in "Like the sound".
They're the same word,
but Kyoko-tan sees different
images when she reads the cards.
Like the sound...
Even though I may be the only one
who can tell the difference.
He's on a completely different level.
What are we supposed to do against him?
He must be a psychic.
He moved as soon as she
opened her mouth...
Still, aren't they exaggerating about
having 28 one-syllable cards?
The human ear isn't capable
of differentiating
between those sounds.
Right, Chihaya-chan?
Since the dew atop the blades of grass
has been scattered by the winds,
Ooh.
Wow.
The Master's so good, Bro.
He's so good that it's boring.
There's no point in watching.
It's the opponent's
fault for being weak.
Bro was pretty weak when he lost.
B-But Bro put up more of a fight!
Really?
Yeah!
Hey, stop sucking up, Yuuta!
You should stop yapping, Kenta!
Hey, stop it!
Nobody wins in a fight between twins!
I didn't put up a fight.
It's our fault for leaving
him alone out there.
Alone...
The storm will soon carry
me to the afterlife,
Oh, no! Takemura, grade 6,
commits a fault by
touching "The storm blasts"
in his lower left row.
You can't gamble like that...
If you look at the Master's positioning,
he's sacrificing his
multiple-syllable cards.
They can be taken for sure.
I have to treat "As the years" and
"As the first" as two-syllable cards.
"Would the" and "Would this"
have to be split like one-syllable cards.
How should I...
No, the real one-syllable
cards are the key.
I can't afford to lose those.
"Long" and "Look" will come
down to the "L" sound.
The Master has an
overwhelming advantage
in the Master match.
The first opponent for a new challenger
is the pressure of sitting on that stage.
I know.
So I have to visualize...
I can do it.
I can do it...
I can do it, but...
Thank you very much.
It's over!
Master Suo was never behind
Thank you very much.
as he won his fourth
straight Master title.
Thank you very much.
His strengths are simple,
but consistent.
How long will his streak continue?
Grandpa, visualizing only goes so far.
I have to practice or my body
won't know how to move...
Against a strong opponent!
Suo-kun.
Congratulations on your fourth victory.
Please try to graduate
from college next year.
Yeah.
A little more confidence, please.
Congratulations, Shinobu-chan.
Thank you, Coach Ise.
Could you come practice
with the Kyoto Myojo society,
when you get a chance?
The other members would
be thrilled to have you.
Oh, that would be an honor.
Once I've gotten a little
stronger, I'll stop by.
I see...
Stronger?  Than she already is?
She's telling him that she won't go.
Kyoto women are all the same.
I suppose I may be biased, as a coach...
Please show me the way.
but those were the most beautiful
words I'll ever hear.
I don't know if it's
coincidence or fate,
Excuse me.  Can I take a picture?
but the current Master and Queen
Then can you and the Master
stand next to each other.
have no teacher figures.
What a waste...
A person who never had a teacher
can't become a teacher.
Oh, my, everyone?
Why does everyone look so sad?
Oh, dear.  It's already six.
I'm sure your parents
are getting worried.
Not good enough...
Not good enough.
Not good enough, not good enough.
Well, Chihaya-chan, see you later.
Catch you at practice.
Uh-huh, bye.
Desktomu-kun, watch where you're going.
Ayase!
20 cards!
You have 20!
20 what?
20 one-syllable cards!
How am I supposed to stay motivated?
What should I do?
Incoming Call
Taichi
Ta-Taichi!
Happy New Year!
It's a little late for that.
Well, it doesn't hurt.
Did you watch the Master match today?
Yeah, I did.
I've actually been doing some thinking.
Thinking?
Yeah, about the Master's
card positioning.
I asked some Nagumo society members,
who were there in person, to fill me in
on the games that weren't broadcast,
so I could line up the cards.
It helps me understand
the Master better.
Playing with cards by yourself
in Master Wataya's room?
You haven't grown up, huh?
Well, let's play.
Arata?  Arata?
I have to give it a shot!
Like I said!
I have notes from your practice games
and your games in official tournaments.
After reviewing them,
I determined that there are about 20 cards.
Of course, it depends on the
reader and your condition,
but "Since the", "Since I",
"Like the", "Like a",
"When I", "When the", "Impassionate",
"Would the", "Would this", "In the", "For the",
"Though I", and "Though my"
are all cards you take on
the first syllable, I think.
You must have noticed this?
I-I kind of did...
Only kind of...
Do I really recognize them
on the...
Trust my data!
Sorry!
You and Master Suo aren't the
only ones who can do this.
Most people with good game
sense will have a few cards
where they can anticipate
the next sound.
I wish I could do that.
What?!  I don't want this.
Uh, hey!
I-I'll find something better
to give you in return!
What?
Oh, it's Ayase-san!
Gotta admit that she's cute.
She's so fine.
No, I take it back.
She's muttering some kind of curse.
Yeah, not her.
Scary!  Let's go around.
Out of the question.
Chi-Chihaya-chan!
Since the, Since I,
Like the, Like a, When I, When the,
Impassionate, Would the, Would this,
In the, For the, Though I, Though my
Since the dew...
Since I could not...
Like a boatsman...
Like the sound...
When I must hide...
When the misty bridge...
You have 20!
Impassionate gods...
The number isn't important.
What matters is that...
Trust me!
Desktomu-kun figured it out for me.
He was able to tell me
what I was hearing.
I wish I could do that.
Though I prayed...
Though my hatred...
For the cold nights...
Would the mountain cherry blossoms...
Would this old palace courtyard...
I hope I'm able to return
the favor some day.
In the sleepy...
Since the dew...
Since I could not...
Like a boatsman...
Like the sound...
When I must hide...
When the misty bridge...
Impassionate gods...
Though I prayed...
Though my hatred...
For the cold nights...
Would the mountain cherry blossoms...
Would this old palace courtyard...
In the sleepy...
Since the dew...
I believe it was
Ki no Tsurayuki who said
Since I could not...
that the poetification of words
was as natural as birds
and animals crying out.
As long as the emotion is there,
a short phrase can sound like a poem.
Whoa!
You scared me, Kana-chan!
Yeah, it's all wasted once she moves.
Out of nowhere!  How long
have you been there?!
Ah!  You saw me acting weird!
So she realizes that it's weird.
What should I do?!
Chihaya-chan.
Huh?
I actually have a dream now.
I'm very interested in reading cards.
I-I want to become a certified reader.
I want to become a certified reader...
and read for your Queen match.
Ka-Kana-chan, are you serious?!
Dead serious?!
Y-Yes.
I don't know how difficult
it will be yet...
That's great!  Do your best, Kana-chan!
I will...
I mean, you have to be...
a Class A player to
become a certified reader!
Huh?
You have to be a Class A player
to become a certified reader!
...certified reader!
Okay, you have 15 minutes
of memorization time.
We'll start when the minute hand hits six.
Okay!
I didn't realize it was so difficult
to become a certified reader.
At least a Grade 4 (Class A) player
Five years of experience as an official Class A reader
(Multiple requirements for becoming an official Class A reader)
I'll have to devote my entire life.
And even that... that
might not be enough.
The president is working so hard
and he still can't make Class A.
It's impossible...  Impossible...
Impossible, impossible, impossible...
Two more minutes of memorization time.
Okay.
You never practice swinging
because you think it's embarrassing, right?
It helps me understand
the Master better.
My grandpa always used to tell me...
Tell you what?
You don't need game
sense to play karuta.
Huh?
You just have to take cards
faster than your opponent.
It's difficult to achieve a
similar level of game sense,
but there are plenty of other
ways to take cards faster.
Well, I have to train with my mentor.
Talk to you later.
Call me again.
Arata.
That's unusual...
Taichi is practicing his swing.
It's difficult to achieve a
similar level of game sense,
but there are plenty of other
ways to take cards faster.
If I win this game today,
I'll burn all the Daddy
Bears at your house.
What?!
Wh-Why?!  Why?!
Why would you burn them?!
There goes 10% of her concentration.
Why?!  Why would you do that?!
So this is why Sudo acts like a sadist...
I see now...
Arata...
In your world, there's no
such thing as a genius.
Call me again.
I really hope
I don't have to burn your Daddy Bears.
I-It's time.
The president is turning into a sadist.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
When reading cards,
the second verse should
take four seconds,
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
with three seconds of fade out.
Then you pause for one second,
before reading the first verse of
the next poem in five seconds.
One.
Note that though we may
be apart, if I am to hear
Ah, I was late.
It's difficult...
The players spend that second focused
on the next sound to come...
May the time we spend apart...
Ah, my voice jumped.
The hazy field of reeds...
Now I'm too loud.
but I cannot hide the love I
feel for one who is so dear
It's hard...
The reader must stay completely
focused for an entire hour,
and that's not an easy task.
But...
Since I could not hide my love,
while it may be difficult now,
the president will make Class A one day.
Nobody wants to give up their dream.
Club Advisor Meeting
Budget
Room Space
Scheduling
What?
You want to assign the Karuta
Club's room to the Concert Band?
That's nonsense!
However, the room is too
big for an arts club
that only has five members.
The Concert Band has forty members,
so they need the space.
The Karuta Club could simply
use an empty classroom.
I beg to differ.
Karuta requires a
soundproof environment.
The location can't have students
walking through the hallways
or athletes practicing nearby.
However, Ms. Miyauchi!
The Karuta Club advanced
to the national championship
in their first year.
The members also placed first and
second in sanctioned tournaments!
I'm sure there will be many
new members this year!
You will see excellent results!
Could you at least
let the Concert Band use the second floor?
I just said that karuta requires
a soundproof environment.
Right...
You certainly did.
Anything else?
The empress...
Ms. Miyauchi cares about
the Karuta Club very much.
Tissues?
Mr. Fukasaku, the classical
literature teacher.
The professor's the only person
the empress can't overwhelm.
How does this sound?
If there are five new members next year,
we'll leave everything as it is.
Karuta is a wonderful art.
I'm sure that it will be easy
to recruit five members.
Of course.
If we can't recruit five members,
we will return the room!
That's what I wanted to hear!
Five members...
Recruit five members to that
incredibly niche club?
Huh?
I just heard something.
From the door.
Notice:
If the Karuta Club does not recruit
five new members next year,
you will have to return the clubroom.
Good luck. ( ; △ ; )
I was able to increase the
club's budget to 30,000 yen.
Miyauchi
Huh?  Five people?
Isn't that impossible?
A-An emoticon?  And it's handwritten...
Thirty thousand yen budget!
That's what you care about, Kana-chan?
Hey, have you heard?
The younger sister of
the model Ayase Chitose
is a second-year here!
No way!  I'm a fan!
Okay, let's go check her out!
Oh, there she is!
1, 2, 3, 4!
Please come see Ayase Chihaya in class 2-9!!
Let's start a competitive karuta club!
Karuta?
Track pants?
And look at the belt.
Ayase-san!
You're an upperclassman now,
yet you're still embarrassing yourself!
Right, everyone was saying
how she's pretty,
That's right.  You ended up
failing your final exams!
After you were able to ever so slightly
improve your grades last year!
but it's wasted as soon as
she talks or does something.
Beauty in vain...
And Ayase-san.
Put another one up there!
Hey, let's play karuta!