So why my house?
Because you have a 60-inch TV!
Master Match  |   Queen Match
These are the Master and Queen matches!
Master and Queen matches!
We have to watch on a big screen!
There was the option of going
to Dr. Harada's house,
but the other three members
are in the Suihoku society,
so Coach Kitano would be upset.
Okay, I can understand that.
But now is a bad time...
Oh, Chihaya-chan.
You've come to visit?
It's been so long.
It turns out that the play
I was going to attend this afternoon was
actually scheduled for tonight.
But it worked out, since you're here.
No, um, I'll leave right away.
Why? Enjoy your stay.
I want to thank you for making
Taichi feel at home in the karuta club.
She hates me. She hates me.
She hates me.
She's looking at me. She's looking
at me. She's looking at me.
Want to go up to my room?
Huh?
There's a smaller TV in my room.
You can't concentrate on the match
if my mother's watching you.
I'll head on up then.
You shouldn't be running
to a guy's room like that.
I'm not gonna let you in.
Oh, this feels weird.
I'm a little nervous.
So very nervous.
Chihaya Furu
Nobody
Wishes
To See The
Beautiful
Cherry
Blossoms
Verse 24
Oh, you haven't rearranged anything.
Why would it change?
I haven't been in here
since grade school.
Your room always felt big,
but now it feels even bigger.
Really?
Even though you've gotten bigger?
There were a bunch of plastic
models and toys lying around.
What happened to that soccer poster?
Your room's so bare now.
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
Nothing, just...
You're in my room.
Huh?
Taichi!
You're supposed to leave the door open.
Your other friends are here.
O-Okay...
I can't believe Mashima
called this a "small" TV.
42 inch...
It's at least double the size
of the TV at my house...
The karuta club members
always look so plain.
Taichi, aren't you pushing
yourself too hard?
How long are you going
to keep playing karuta?
We bring you another
live broadcast from Omi Jingu,
in Shiga Prefecture.
The Ogura Hundred Poets
Competitive Karuta
Master Match and Queen Match.
It's finally here.
The Queen match is about to begin...
My dream...
The ultimate match in
the world of karuta...
Shinobu-chan will be playing
to defend her title!
56th Queen Match
Wakamiya Shinobu, Queen X Yamamoto Yumi, Grade 6
58th Master Match
Queen Match
We will now switch to the camera inside.
What?!
Sh-Shinobu-chan?!
Why?!  How?!
The Master match is a best of five.
Wait, the announcer
needs to say something!
The first person to three wins will be the Master.
The Queen match is a best of three.
The Queen's put on way too much weight!
The first person to two wins will be the Queen.
Her neck is gone.
Once memorization time is over,
we will begin the second game.
She was so thin last summer...
Why?  How could she...?
She's playing this match in a
patterned crepe silk piece?!
Kana-chan, that's your only concern?!
The golden lining on top...
The flower patterns are very Kyoto.
Even the threading is
achingly masterful.
She's playing competitive
karuta in a kimono that's
worth at least one million yen!
Oh!
The Snowmaru pouch and handkerchief
that were only available in Kansai!
What are those creepy things?
After collecting 25 winning
stickers from ice cream bars,
you get one submission!
Those are super rare items
that never come up!
She's so lucky!
She was eating ice cream
until she won those...
Wait.
Isn't the Queen in trouble?
Huh?
She's put on over ten kilograms.
If she's used to playing
karuta with a light body,
her strongest weapon,
her speed, will suffer!
Competitive Karuta Master Match
58th Master Match / 56th Queen Match
The first game took place this morning,
and Queen Wakamiya won by five cards.
Wait, the first game's already over?
Yumin lost the first game?
But she only lost by five cards.
She's putting up a fight!
Five cards...
We'll now provide a
summary of the first game.
Wakamiya                                                                               Yamamoto
First Game Digest
Both players started off very even.
Yamamoto, grade 6, did not allow
the Queen to play her game.
She certainly played admirably.
She's not as sharp as she was
in the high school tournament.
Is it because she's chubby now?
Shinobu-chan...
We'll now introduce our players.
This year's challenger is
Yamamoto Yumi, grade 6.
The former Queen has returned
Yamamoto Yumi, Grade 6
to Omi Jingu to reclaim her title.
During the day, she's a 24-year-old
in her second year as a working adult.
While working at a large Tokyo bank,
Wow!  They went to the
bank to interview her!
she's been making the best
of her limited practice time
to return to the Queen match!
Until I got here, I was scared
of Wakamiya Shinobu...
I could still remember how
strong she was last year...
But look at her now.
She's so chubby.
I'm not scared.
She's still human.
A child who came to the Queen match
without paying any attention to her health.
It's hot...
Her opponent is Wakamiya Shinobu,
the youngest Queen in history.
Wakamiya Shinobu, Queen
She currently attends a
high school in Kyoto.
Her high school does not
have a karuta club,
and she'd been practicing karuta
at Kyoto's Myojo society till sixth grade.
With additional practice at home,
she was able to achieve
overwhelming speed.
Practice swings?
She never did that during the
high school tournament...
This year too, the Queen is wearing
a very lovely kimono.
Yes, it's beautiful.
I believe that the kimono was
passed down from her grandmother,
who is a member of the prefectural board.
Oh, my.
So heavy...
And this isn't my style.
It's not like Grandma's
watching me on TV.
Well, well.  This is quite
serious, Shiho-san.
You divorced your husband
and returned home?
If you plan on leaving that girl here,
I want her learning something.
Her body is flexible,
but she has trouble following along.
Shinobu
Her sense is good, but it's
a little too dynamic.
Pass.  Who's got all the Hearts?
Your mother is very strict
about bringing up children.
Not me.
We haven't found anything
for her to do yet.
Though she seems to enjoy playing cards.
That won't work.
It needs to be something that
will help her in the future.
This is cute...
So many cute pictures!
Shinobu!  Enough already!
If you don't learn a useful skill,
it'll be awkward for us to live here!
Stop playing games that
won't help you in life!
If you like karuta, you can visit
the karuta society nearby.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Wakamiya
Yamamoto
As the first frost...
A four-syllable card!  Yumi-san got it!
The hazy early morning light
comes not from the moon
She defended the multi-syllable card!
You can tell that Yamamoto,
grade 6, is a veteran.
She's doing an excellent job of
protecting her multi-syllable cards.
The Queen is very good at
breaking down defenses,
but watch this.
Her hand is so low that the
Queen cannot slip a finger in.
Ooh! Slow motion replay
is really useful!
Watch carefully, Ayase!
Your defense is like Swiss
cheese compared to Yumin's!
Cheese...
Shinobu-chan...
Excuse me.
She's standing up already?
Good.  That's it, Yumin!
After extensive research
by the Suihoku society,
we've determined that Wakamiya Shinobu
has limited experience with long matches!
Do whatever you can to extend
the match and wear her down!
We'll call this
"Operation who gives a damn
about broadcast schedules!"
The first game was very close.
If you can win this game
and force a third one,
you have a chance, Yumin!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to take you.
Look for the sound of the cuckoo
Fast!
The Queen got that one!
No...
Huh?
It appeared that the
Queen had won the card,
but in slow motion, you can see
that she missed the card
by a few millimeters.
Yamamoto, grade 6,
was there to clean up.
She missed?
The additional weight is affecting her.
From what I've seen, the Queen
definitely has good sense,
but her main strength lies
in her body control.
Yumin's taking plenty of time
to decide on a card to send!
Her control is off now.
All according to the plan!
You can do it!  You can do it, Yumin!
But the Queen's swings
are sharp as a razor.
Please, Kana-chan.
Don't use that metaphor.
It's scary.
I'm sorry.
But you're right.
Heavy...
Oh, the kimono isn't heavy.
It's my body.
I ate too much ice cream.
Sorry...  Sorry...
At this rate, they'll all hate me.
Wakamiya is really weird.
She spends breaks staring at her cards.
Is she memorizing them?
She's already memorized them,
but she keeps staring at them.  Creepy.
Hey.
Where did you hide them?
All over the place.
You boys are despicable.
She's gonna cry.
Huh?
93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99...
I don't know why,
people would always ask if
I was pining for someone
but just as I love karuta,
the karuta also loves me.
Since I could not...
Fast!  Her fastest swing
today comes on one
of her sweet cards,
"Since I could not hide"!
Please watch the slow motion replay.
A beautiful stroke that only
connects with a single card.
This accuracy is the Queen's forte.
I always thought that
Shinobu-chan was aiming for
the corner of each card...
But that's not it.
Her swing isn't sharp as a razor.
Her fingers are connected to
the edge of every single card
by threads!
The second game began with
the challenger winning the first three cards.
Yamamoto, grade 6, appeared to
be running away with the game,
when the Queen showed off her speed
by taking six cards in a row.
The Queen has turned the tables
and taken over this game!
While I sigh...
Swift waters parted...
Impassioned vows exchanged...
Incredible...
This is like iaido!
No!
Huh?
This isn't violent!
She would never attack the cards.
Think of it as making 100 new friends.
Why are you crying?
She wants to practice...
She can't help herself.
She wants to practice this very second!
I guess I can help her...
No...
Next year, they'll be
your rivals in Class A!
You have to go watch them
play, not cheer them on!
For you, I would have given up my life
The Queen breaks through
her opponent's cover!
Impressive.
What's wrong, Yumin?!
Hang in there!
Don't give up!
The game has only just begun, Yumin!
Rain takes longer...
In order to restore...
Would this old palace...
The Queen has completely
taken over this game!
Will Yamamoto, grade 6,
be able to stage a comeback?
Don't be stupid!
Hearty
She's not going to roll
over and give up!
Do you have any idea how hard
Yumin practiced this year?!
Don't lose, Yumin!
The Queen is still human!
Oh, it appeared that the
Queen had taken the card,
but she missed again.
Oh, this is...
Ah, a card from the Master
match hit the Queen's back.
Yes, the Master match is being
played at the same time.
No way!
If Shinobu-chan was thrown off
by the card hitting her back,
that means the person who hit that
card was faster than Shinobu-chan.
There's someone faster?
I can feel his presence...
invading my concentration.
A disturbance...
A very strong presence.
That's it!  She's done it!
Wakamiya Shinobu is our Queen
for the second year in a row!
She won the second game
by thirteen cards.
A dominating performance
from this sixteen-year-old.
Does she still have room to grow?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much...
Waiting
Room
Twenty people came from
Tokyo to cheer me on...
They knew my chances were slim,
but they still believed
that I could win.
But it was obvious that
I stood no chance!
There was no way for me to defeat her!
She was so fast that I couldn't
even try to contest cards!
It didn't matter what I tried...
Coach...
I want to make it back here again.
Please show me the way.
Wakamiya-san, what is the
secret behind your strength?
I'm not that strong.
I still have much to learn.
This was your second match
against Yamamoto, grade 6.
Second match?
Oh, you're right.
She forgot that she
played Yumin last year!
She is a skilled player.
I've learned that I
still need to improve.
This won't work...
I'm not attached to the cards
the way Shinobu-chan and Kana-chan are...
Taichi, you have a set of cards, right?
Can I start lining them up?
Taichi?
I can hear her...
but I can't dedicate myself to Chihaya!
You blockhead!
You're done watching BS as soon
as the Queen match is over?!
That's absurd!
The real show's about
to begin for us men!
The Master match is next!
The Master match is our only
chance to watch the Master play!
Today is the only day we get
to watch Suo Hisashi play!
Takemura
Suo
The first game of the Master
match was won by five cards.
The second game was won
by thirteen cards.
Master Suo is up two games to zero.
Oh?
Doesn't that match the score differential
for the Queen match games?
Er, one moment please.
Yes, you're right.
He's such a nasty person.
If Master Suo wins the third game,
he will be Master for the
fourth year in a row.
We will now introduce the players.
The challenger is a member
of the Kotoku-in University
Karuta Society,
Takemura Keichi, grade 6.
He works as a bodywork
therapist in Shikoku,
while practicing karuta with
the university students.
I can't take it anymore...
I worked so hard.
Worked so hard to achieve my dream.
I finally made it here...
but now I'm ready to hate karuta.
His opponent is the three-time
defending Master, Suo Hisashi.
We interviewed him before the match,
and he still hasn't graduated
from college yet.
Oh, really?
Suo Hisashi, Master
Hasn't graduated?
The Master looks sharp,
but the narration ruined it.
Ayase.
We men need to watch
Master Suo carefully,
but I believe you also
need to pay attention.
Huh?
You're trying to copy
Wakamiya Shinobu's style,
but you're closer to Suo
Hisashi's style right now.
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
When I must hide these burning feelings,
Did you see that?
He began moving towards
the two-syllable card
"When I" on the first syllable.
For most players, there are only
seven one-syllable cards: "Waves,
Gust, Long, All, Swift, Look, Rain".
But in our interview, the
Master had this to say.
There are 28 one-syllable cards for him.