What's that?
Is this for some kind of
advertising campaign?
One, two, three, four!
Isn't she that really pretty
girl from Mizusawa High?
Is she going to play karuta in a hakama?
Five, six, seven, eight!
June. The middle of the rainy season.
The Tokyo regionals for the National
High School Karuta Championship!
Chihaya Furu
Verse 10
Exchange
Hellos
And
Goodbyes
Dressing Room
Please take turns
Players wear hakama for the
Master and Queen matches.
You should get used to it now!
No way!
I'm not trying to become a Master!
None of the other high
schools are wearing them!
What are you saying?!
Both of you look much better now
than when you were wearing
your school or gym uniforms.
You would fit in perfectly on a theater stage
or at a children's festival!
What?!
Traditional Clothing by Oe
Years
of
Serving
the
Community
Oe-san's business sense...
is really something.
Chihaya, why are you just standing there?
The opening ceremony's about to start.
Isn't this amazing, Taichi?
Everybody here plays karuta!
Everybody here is bonkers for karuta!
Wait, you're being rude.
Okay! I need to text Arata!
You've been texting Arata
a lot since your birthday.
Does he reply?
It's shocking how he never replies!
Huh?
I'm sending messages just in case.
But why did he text you instead of me?
I always put my number
on my notes and letters,
so he should know it.
I can understand.
Taichi, sorry about before.
Tell Chihaya happy birthday for me.
Wataya Arata
We both feel that Chihaya...
What?
Sorry, don't take pictures.
Sorry.
...belongs to both of us.
Taichi's been acting strange lately.
You always manage to stand out.
Huh?
I didn't expect to see you in
the team tournament, Chihaya.
Hokuo
Oh! It's Retro-kun!
Er, wait! You forgot about
me for a moment there!
I forgot, but then I remembered!
Long time no see!
What are you saying?!
Your high school is in this tournament?
That makes us rivals!
Rivals?
Don't you realize that you're
just a new karuta club?
Our Hokuo Academy is a karuta powerhouse
that's made the national
tournament five years in a row.
Two of the eight members
on the team are Class A.
Huh?
Our team is incredible!
Two members in Class A?
And I might add that I'm performing
very well for a first-year...
My team is just as amazing!
We'll blow you out of the water!
What are you saying?!
What do we do?
I knew this would be difficult.
Only one team will make it to Omi Jingu!
Oh, Chihaya-chan!
Kana-chan!
That won't do, Chihaya-chan!
Huh?
A woman must always move with grace,
whether you're wiping a
table or drying sheets.
Or in the fight of your life.
Twelve schools are participating.
There's a group stage,
followed by the tournament.
At least we weren't placed
in the same group as Hokuo.
We just need three people to win
their matches for a victory.
I was able to survive that brutal camp,
and I was up late last night practicing.
I know that I've improved!
My love of classical poetry is
greater than anyone else here!
I want to win!
Win and go to the national tournament...
With this team!
Naniwa Bay, now the flower
blooms, but for winter
Isn't that school a little too into this?
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
I heard one of them say,
"players wear hakama for the Master and Queen matches,
so you should get used to it now."
Wait, that's impossible.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
They wouldn't say that if they knew
how strong the current Queen is.
The sky is the road home
for the holy maidens,
Nice!
Keep it up!
Okay!
Oops. I need to be graceful.
may the wind bring clouds
to extend their stay
The hazy early morning mist over the Kawagiri River
but from the crystal white snow of Yoshino
Shoot! This is the wrong card!
I knew coming in that "The" cards were
the ones people usually mix up.
No matter where I stand on the shores of Tago,
Calm down.
The match has just started.
My own home is a retreat lying
southeast of the capital
I spent all that time practicing,
but I can't take any cards!
Group B Preliminaries
Eikou University High School
Mizusawa High School
Shuryukan
Hanasaki Academy
Yes! That's one win!
Gloom
I'm guessing that Komano was up
against Eikou's strongest player.
Bad luck on your part.
Oh? Really?
Luck of the draw,
more or less.
Anyway, Mashima.
I don't mind putting Ayase
in the middle for now,
but won't we need to rethink our order
when we face stronger schools?
Yeah.
Will Hokuo use a standard order?
Who are the two Class A Hokuo players?
We just need you, me, and Ayase to win.
So we should try to
match Kana-chan and Desktomu-kun
against the Class A players.
That would be...
That's right.
Where's Chihaya-chan?
She's over there sending a text.
Again?
She's been sending a lot of texts recently.
It must be him, you know?
Wataya Arata.
Who's that?
The person who taught Ayase karuta.
He's ridiculously good.
He's in Fukui right now,
so Ayase must have started a karuta club
so she could see him at nationals.
Swift!
Swift waters parted by the jagged rocks!
Well, she's obsessed with karuta,
so I'm pretty sure she just
wants to play strong opponents.
Let's get going.
It's time for our second match.
Is our next opponent, Shuryukan, strong?
They're pretty serious about karuta.
But you can take it easy, Kana-chan.
Oh, okay!
now the flower blooms
No more can we hear the
sounds of the waterfall
Got it!
Sorry about that.
I swung too hard.
My life means nothing after all
the agonizing I have endured,
Thank you very much.
Kana-chan won!
Nice job! It's your first victory!
Yes!
You can do it, Desktomu-kun!
I feel as though my body is
on fire with Ibuki mugwort
My fear is that you will forget
your promise to never forget me,
Thank you very much!
That was my first win!
That's great, Kana-chan! Congrats!
Thank you so much!
Shuryukan must have something against men.
Yeah.
I almost lost 'cause my
opponent had a scary face.
Group B Preliminaries
Eikou University High School
Mizusawa High School
Shuryukan
Hanasaki Academy
Today was the first time I've ever
felt like I was the one attacking.
It feels so good when you take
a card from the bottom right side
of the opponent's field!
I know what you mean!
We've made it out of the group stage.
We just have to win two more
matches to win the tournament.
I think we have a shot.
But if we lose once, it's over.
That's why I think we
should change the order
so the three of us can't lose!
Our next opponent,
Tomihara West High School,
has one really strong player!
Then we should match Desktomu-kun
against that player!
We don't know what order
they're going to use.
Chihaya-chan!
Um, excuse me.
Can I go home now?
Huh?
What are you saying, Desktomu-kun?!
Stupid, you can't leave now.
But you'll have enough wins without me,
and I can't beat anyone.
Y-You don't need to worry about that.
Don't get all cocky because
you lucked into a win!
Huh?
What's wrong with you?!
I'm only here because
you need five people
to make it to the national tournament!
Anyone could take my spot!
You don't need Oe-san or me!
That's not true, Desktomu-kun!
It is!
Your goal is to reach the
national tournament
because there's someone you want to meet!
Huh?
That's all you care about!
Anyway, I'm going home.
There's a test coming up,
and I didn't get any sleep last night.
Komano.
I'll let you skip the semi-finals,
but you'll be playing in the finals.
That's an order.
Taichi!
He can't take any cards with that mindset.
That's right!
Just forget about him.
It's not his fault!
We're still playing karuta individually.
We aren't a team yet...
Huh?
Anyway, we have to win
and make it to the finals.
The four of us need to score three wins.
So we can play with Komano again.
I will now read Mizusawa
High School's order.
Chihaya, you definitely can't lose.
Huh?
I'm only here because you
need five people to make
it to the national tournament!
Oh, no...
I never realized that
Desktomu-kun felt that way.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Tomihara West High! Victory!
Yeah!
The sight of the lonely
moon in the early morning
Got it!
Nice job, E-chan!
I was able to hold onto mine.
Way to go, Sano-senpai!
That's the spirit!
Keep it up, team!
Yes!
Huh? Everyone on their team won that card?
No... Taichi and Porky took theirs,
so we're actually even in score.
Make it two in a row!
Yeah!
Take the next one!
One at a time!
Focus... Focus...
Keep it up, team!
Yeah!
Focus!
Anyway, we have to win and
make it to the finals.
If we lose here...
So we can play with Komano again.
It will have all been for nothing.
You definitely can't lose.
Impassionate—
Yes!
Can't lose this card!
Got it!
Yes! We all-
Held onto the "Impassionate" card!
Nice job, Sano-senpai!
All right!
Ayase...
...lost the Chihaya card?!
Chihaya-chan!
the red that is the Tatsuta River
The sound is...
so far away.
Right! We're on a roll!
Yes!
Tomihara West is always so loud.
They're actually not that strong,
but the yelling makes
their movements crisper,
and it helps to intimidate their opponents.
There isn't a team that's stronger
when they keep your mouths shut.
1 retro, 2 retro, 3 retro, 4, 5...
Retro?
Retro, are you sitting out this round?
Sudo-senpai.
What are you doing?
These are like tarot cards,
but they're retrot cards.
I'm going to use these to
divine our opponent's order.
What's scary is that you're
right 80% of the time.
It looks like we'll be facing
Tomihara West in the finals,
so the order won't even matter.
If Mizusawa wins, I want to face
the girl with the long hair.
Chihaya?
She has good instincts,
but she's not that impressive otherwise.
She's no match for you.
I like to toy with pretty girls.
The S in Sudo stands for "sadist"!
How are the semi-finals going?
Mizusawa's getting dominated.
Tomihara West is probably in the finals.
What about the cute girl from Mizusawa?
She's not doing as well as
she was in the group stage.
Her opponent's got her number.
Something must have happened during lunch.
Did their team have an argument?
This is their first year as a team.
I guess they don't respect karuta.
Ayase won't lose!
She's just getting started!
What's with him?
Chihaya, one card at a time!
Pull yourself together!
Uh, yeah.
It's no good.
She's not her normal self.
If I'm going to order people around,
I need to pull myself together!
My fear is that you will forget
your promise to never forget me,
Right on!
Nice job, Sano-senpai!
Six cards up!
We can do this!
What do I do?
How do I usually take cards?
I can't remember!
May the scarlet kadsuras of Mount
Afusaka live up to their name
Excuse me.
Nishida, win your match first.
Huh?
That'll make it easier on the rest of us.
Oe-san's hanging in there!
I've never seen you play so well!
You can win!
Chihaya.
Huh?
You can win if you just breathe.
Breathe?
So this is what my opponent looks like.
She's been yelling the most.
Look at her sweat...
I have eight cards left.
She has two cards.
I'm losing pretty badly.
Third! Heads up!
and allow us this secret rendezvous
I can hear!
When I must hide these burning feelings,
Yes!
Yeah!
Nice!
All right!
Though I prayed to...
Four cards down.
She's on the attack since there
isn't much risk of a fault.
All of a sudden, she's incredibly good.
She must be a sadist.
Three cards down.
Gust of wind leaves fall leaves falling
Victory! Mizusawa's up one!
I also won! Mizusawa's up two!
Two cards down.
Since I could not hide my love,
Tomihara West has two wins!
She's still down a card.
She made up...
may the wind bring clouds to extend their stay
a six card deficit!
You can do it, Ayase!
Mizusawa High School, three wins.
Tomihara West High School, two wins.
Mizusawa High School wins the match.
Thank you very much!
She's asleep.
Again?
Oh! Kana-chan?!
Desktomu-kun!
I won't let you run away, Desktomu-kun!
Why did you loosen your obi?
I'll fix it for you, so stand up straight!
Have you noticed?
Huh?
Look at everyone's feet.
They all have calluses.
Because they've been kneeling
on tatami mats for many years.
It only makes sense that we can't beat them.
We'll have to keep practicing until
we also have calluses on our feet!
Kana-chan...
Huh?
Congratulations on your first victory!
Komano!
I would rather be on a team
with someone who puts in
effort on the tatami.
Sorry!
Sorry, everyone!
Give me another chance!
Stupid.
The five of us are a team.
The finals are next.
We need you to stand a chance.
Mizusawa fight!