Ah...
Okay, time's up.
Chemistry Exam
Pass your tests forward.
Exams are over.
Three days left until the Eastern qualifier!
Chihaya Furu
The English essay was a cinch this time!
Really?  It was a trick question.
What?!  A trick question?
Verse 21
While
Snow
Falls
Upon
My
Sleeves
It was written like you were
supposed to give the time,
but it was really asking for the speed.
What?!
Seriously?!
the thistle and brush are
blown by the autumn wind
Whoa, they're already at it.
You can't blame her.
Chihaya-chan never mentioned
karuta during exams.
Must have taken some
serious self-control...
My life means nothing after all
the agonizing I have endured,
I got it!  Yes!
Normally, when Ayase loses a card,
she starts shaking her head,
but she's just staring at the cards now.
Like water...
Flowing seamlessly...
How can I achieve that sensation?
Thank you very much.
That took forever!
Why did you start without us?!
Wake up, Ayase!
You're playing me next!
Yes, let's play!  Let's play!
Desktomu-kun, we're the other pair.
Oh, wait a moment.
It's my turn to do the reading?
Need a breather.
I love karuta.
Karuta brought Arata back to us.
Since nationals last summer, Chihaya...
always seemed so frantic
during practice.
Is it because she saw Arata?
Man, why can't I get over it?
I can still change.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Note that though we may be apart...
Like the sound of someone knocking...
the thistle and brush are
blown by the autumn wind
Look for the sound of the cuckoo
Thank you very much.
Mashima!
You don't have to push yourself so hard!
Humans aren't supposed to be perfect!
Oh, did I make any mistakes?
You were perfect!
Huh?  What's up?
Didn't you notice, Chihaya-chan?
Mashima-kun was reading all
of the cards from memory!
Huh?
He was randomly reading cards
without looking at anything!
All from his head!
What?!
Well, I read that this helps
improve your memorization.
He randomly read all one hundred
poems without doubling up?!
I've figured it out.
That's your strength and weakness.
You only see the words in your head.
Huh?
It's important to know what's been read,
but you have to feel
the cards on the field!
Use your eyes and treat them as images!
You never practice swinging because
you think it's embarrassing, right?
You need to learn the distance
between yourself and the cards!
You're playing karuta with
both your mind and your body!
Mind and body...
I want to move faster,
but my arm can't keep up.
I want to get better with you.
I wanted to play in the
Eastern qualifier together.
So what I'm saying is
you don't need to memorize everything.
Huh?  How am I supposed to win then?
You need to find your groove.
I only memorize the initial positions
for about half the cards.
Uh, I'd be too scared of making a mistake.
That's why...
Ayase-san!
Empress...
I talked to your teachers,
and you didn't fail any
of your exams this time!
She doesn't have to yell...
That's marvelous!
Good luck at the Queen qualifier!
I...
...love karuta!
Love it!
Here you go, Chihaya-chan!
We prepared a new hakama for
today's Eastern qualifier!
Forehead.
Forehead?
Sorry, but the heat works
against us in this tournament.
She won't be wearing a hakama.
Huh?
Most tournaments take place
in air-conditioned rooms,
but the windows here remain shut,
and there are no fans,
let alone air conditioning.
So it's ridiculously hot in there!
Wh-Why would they do that?
Because every sound matters.
Where's Nishida?
I saw him with some
Suihoku society members.
You and Komano ended up
joining the Suihoku society?
Yes, they've been helping us a lot.
Suihoku Karuta Society
Shiranami Karuta Society
They must have some history.
Chihaya's...
really focused.
That's a good sign.
Hopefully, she'll make
it past the first round.
Oh.
It's the person who lost
to the Queen by 20 cards.
S-Sudo-san!
Aren't you a third-year?
Don't you need to study for college exams?
I'm studying.
Since my first choice is a
national-level public school.
Though I managed to place second
for the high school scholarship.
High school scholarship?
You didn't know, stupid?
Famous Universities
If you come in first or second at
the high school tournament,
you'll get scholarships
to famous universities.
I should also mention that the Queen
gets scholarships to good schools.
Famous universities
Queen
Karuta Karuta
College
Scholarship
Daddy Bear
Dammit!
He's got Chihaya...
...thinking about...
...unrelated topics!
That guy's evil!
Super
Sadist
Well, it's not like you have a shot.
They say that Wakamiya Shinobu
might be a stronger player
than the current Master.
You can't see yourself beating her, right?
B-But I beat you.
Then let's make a bet!
Whoever loses first today
has to shave their head!
S-Sure!
Ah...
Ah.
Moron!
A girl shaving her head is
completely different from
a guy shaving his head,
and he's not going to take it back!
I-It was an accident...
You just accidentally threw
away every girl's glory!
The opening ceremony is about to begin.
She was all focused,
but now it's been ruined.
Accidentally...
Will all of the players please assemble?
Well, this is a beautiful day for karuta.
The Western qualifier is currently
being played at Omi Jingu.
If you become the best player in Japan,
you'll be the best in the world.
That makes you the Queen, Ayase-san.
In November, the East
and West qualifier winners
will play each other in this building.
It's about to begin.
It's about to begin!
Check the scorecard and sit
down at your assigned location.
I'm up against...
Sudo Akito
Nishida Yusei
Ack!
Burn.
A-Ayase.
I'll defend your hair.
U-Uh-huh.
Good luck.
You're also up against a tough opponent.
Ayase Chihaya
Tachikawa Ririka
A tough opponent?
What do you mean?
You have no clue, huh?
Look.
Ririka-chan, can you pose for the camera?
Tachikawa Ririka.
How are you feeling?
She's from Sendai,
Fine.
and she made Class A as a fourth
grader, just like the Queen.
No worries, huh?
You also placed at the tournament
in Chiba last summer.
They're saying that she's
the next Wakamiya Shinobu.
The child prodigy Ririka.
Ririka, your ribbon's loose.
The expectations for her are huge,
while most people don't
even know your name.
She's a speedy sixth grade star.
Um...
Huh?
Someone told me that you're really fast.
I hope we have a good match today.
Heartstrings
Y-You're too kind!
I hope I don't disappoint you.
Excuse me.  There are so
many matches being played
that we need spectators to remain outside.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Do your best, Ririka!
I'll be watching!
Uh-huh.
The child prodigy Ririka...
The expectations for her are huge,
while most people don't
even know your name.
I'm expecting a lot!
Huh?  Dr. Harada, shouldn't you be inside?
I get a bye in the first round.
We get to save our energy.
Oh?  You too, Hiroshi-san?
Yep.
Oh, Chihaya-chan's playing
Tachikawa Ririka?
H-How do you think she'll do?
She won't lose to a grade schooler, right?
Doctor, you told
Chihaya-chan to stop using
her speed to take cards, right?
Wasn't it a little early to tell her that?
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
Chihaya-chan's strength will
also be her game sense.
She was making big strides,
but now you've taken away her best weapon.
Especially when you consider that
she's up against Tachikawa Ririka.
Here comes spring, now the flower blooms
When I must hide these burning feelings,
Good, Ririka!
As friends and strangers...
I know that my heart...
She's so light!
Swift waters parted...
She's so light,
even when she moves with her entire body.
She's fast.
She's not scared of committing faults,
and her hearing is good.
Ririka...
Her ears are big like mine,
Show us your ears!
so kids used to tease her.
No!
Mom, do my hair!
The karuta coach said
that I have good hearing!
My ears are really sharp!
If karuta's what you need...
Ririka!
Is it possible?
She's faster than Chihaya?
Is something wrong?
Chihaya moved back.
I deflect your artful words
to keep my sleeves dry
After I determined to abandon
my love, my only regret
is that I have no way
to tell you in person
I did it!
I matched the reader's timing!
Huh?
is that I have no way to tell you in person
Focus on timing instead of speed...
It's a simple task for some people,
but not for me...
So the flower petals are scattered
like the snow by the passing storm,
I'm making progress!  Improving!
Though it may seem mundane.
She got the card, but she's slow.
yet it is I who withers and wilts
S-Sorry...
She's just like I was,
so I can understand how she feels.
The emotions experienced
after a long-awaited reunion
She's happy to be playing
against grown-ups,
and it's fun when people
say that she's fast.
banish any lingering memories of the past
While it may be beyond my ability,
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
I committed a fault on a dead card!
It looks like Ririka-chan
is dominating the match,
but she doesn't have much of a lead.
Her opponent is reacting well.
Which society is that girl from?
Ririka-chan was definitely
targeting this card.
and I have yet to visit Amanohashidate
or read my mother's letters
I'll send it and take it from her.
I have to pick up every card
that Ririka-chan doesn't target.
Stay calm.
Take each card at the perfect time.
Lucky me!
I get to play a girl who only has speed.
Chihaya-chan, stop taking
cards with your speed.
I finally understand.
Isn't Ririka-chan in trouble?
Her opponent doesn't seem that good.
So much for being a prodigy.
Chihaya-chan is setting a good pace.
If she's careful, she can pull this out!
If she takes her time, her
opponent will make mistakes!
Huh?
Aren't you supposed to be playing?
Good luck, Ayase!
You
You can
You can use
You can use your
You can use your speed
You can use your speed now.
"You can use your speed now"?
Huh?  Should I trust Doctor Harada?
I volunteer to shield the
people with my dark sleeves
Since the dew atop the blades of grass
has been scattered by the winds,
That fool!
Since I hasn't been read yet!
But she moved so fast!
Did you see that?
She was faster than the child prodigy!
Feel love deepen...
For you, I head out to the
fields to pick spring greens
The sight of the lonely moon...
makes me wonder how I ever
let you fade from my mind
A fault!
covered by the smoky mountain fog
reminds me of the lonely
dawns after we parted
Impassioned was your promise of salvation
Ririka!
You don't have to keep pushing yourself!
Alas, another autumn has passed in vain
Rain takes longer to
dry in the autumn time
If karuta's what you need...
I just want you to find
something you like.
Something that will
help you like yourself.
Thank you very much.
Her opponent's also holding back tears?
Why?
She made it past the first round.
That's a relief.
Hiroshi-kun.
I want to give Chihaya-chan
as many weapons as possible.
She needs more than her game sense.
She needs situational awareness,
timing, accuracy...
The most important thing
in karuta is talent,
but talent is never equal.
She needs more than one weapon to use,
so she doesn't find herself overwhelmed
by prodigies, like the Queen
and the current Master.
Hey, Chihaya-chan!
Gimme your hand.
This is my lucky mark!
Good luck!
Ririka-chan couldn't do it.
They said she was the
next Wakamiya Shinobu,
but she's not that talented.
Well, the Queen is special.
It's not fair to compare them.
Well, that's true.
Chocolate!
Mom!
I'm sure there was someone
who first encouraged Ririka-chan.
I believe that you have
the talent for Karuta.
It's a memory I've always treasured.
I won't let anyone ruin that.
Chihaya made it through the first round.
Sudo-kun!  I lost!  I'm so upset!
The first round was tough.
Class A is completely different.
I thought you were just
participating for the experience.
No!
Chihaya made it through the first round.
Good luck to you, Arata.
Since I'm in Class A, I want
to try to become Master!
Chihaya made it through the first round.
Good luck to you, Arata.
That's not what I want to say...
Chihaya-chan!
You don't need to stuff your mouth!
There's plenty of chocolate left!
This?  You want this, too?
Don't spill so much!
It's not ladylike!
What?  Murao-san lost?
Yeah, to a freshman from Seijo University.
Nobody expected him to lose that match.
Murao-kun
made it to the final match against
the Master two years ago.
He hasn't been practicing much, lately.
Yo.
You won your first match?
Congrats.
I'm glad you're back.
The Nagumo society has a lot of members,
but there aren't many with the
potential to become Master.
Everyone will be pinning
their hopes on you now.
However, you'll never make it
past the role of challenger.
The Master...
Suo Hisashi can't be defeated.
Murao-san, Murao-san!
Play me next!
Arata-kun, you've gotten really strong.
I need to become Master
before you catch up to me!
Chihaya made it through the first round.
My goal is to become the Eastern qualifier finalist,
so you better become the Western qualifier finalist.
The second round is about to begin!
Will the players please move
to their assigned seats?