Rikka.
Mama wants you to come say good-bye to Papa.
This will be your last chance to pay your respects. Please, one last good-bye.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Takanashi
It's cold.
Could you wash it for him?
Papa will feel even colder if you pour it on him like that.
Will he?
Takanashi
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Search Results
Received Messages
Good morning.
There's a letter for you.
Eternal Engage
I put it on your desk.
'Kay.
I know that!
What was I supposed to do?
Takanashi
Rikka!
Are you there, Rikka?
What the heck am I doing?!
Takanashi-san?
No, I haven't heard from her.
Oh, I bet you two got into a fight!
No, we didn't...
C'mon, don't lie.
You totally did!
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
Excuse me...
Who are you?
Oh, please, Senpai.
It's me, Dekomori.
Dekomori Sanae.
I'm gonna be sick!
You feel sick?
Did you eat some bad herb or something?
Who'd eat something like that?!
I feel sick because of you!
What's with your hair?!
I just thought that twin tails looked a bit childish,
Senpai.
Don't call me that!
Senpai, hang in there!
Quit it!
You talking like that is just plain wrong!
Please let go, Senpai.
A girl's hair is her life!
Don't grab it as if it were nothing!
This is just way too abrupt.
What's going on?
Well, I did some thinking since we last talked.
About Master—I mean, Takanashi-senpai, and the things you said to me.
Yuuta!
Senpai...
Kumin-senpai...
Whoa! Who's the babe?!
See?
Um... Tsuyuri-san, did something happen to your eye?
No, it's fine.
Do you have a cold?
I hope it's just a cold.
I'll be fine.
If I drink this...
What's that?
You really want to know?
N-No, um...
Kumin-senpai...
Oh, my. What is she wearing?
How embarrassing!
Like you can talk!
That hurt! Death!
"Death"?
Wait, don't tell me she's that middle schooler!
You just figured it out?
You've arrived...
Dark Flame Master.
Please don't call me that.
Do you want to see my eye?
No thanks.
Come on, don't be that way!
Well...
Why are you pretending to be Rikka, anyway?
This is no charade.
It has been passed down.
The Tyrant's Eye.
"Passed down"?
Yes.
On the night of the last new moon,
she bestowed unto me all the powers of darkness.
In other words, I am the successor of the Tyrant's Eye.
No! You don't need to fill her shoes!
There's nothing I can do about it.
The Tyrant's Eye must live on,
so long as the Dark Flame Master exists.
Did Rikka say that?
She's actually kinda cool!
So are you normal or not?
We really cleaned the place out.
Yeah. But it's not like we really did anything.
How did things go with the Drama Club?
I tried it out, of course.
But you know...
What?
The club president is one of those passionate types.
The types that go, "Let's make something that only we can make!"
Or, "Let's show everyone that the new generation has potential!"
Oh, I know what you mean.
Well, there's nothing wrong with being passionate,
but whenever I hear him, I always think something like, "Ugh, eighth-grade syndrome."
Is that really eighth-grade syndrome, though?
I guess I wouldn't really call it that.
It's more like, "I'm different from everyone else, and I'm special because I realized that."
It's like he's stuck on that train of thought.
I mean, the two of us thought we were done with eighth-grade syndrome
and that we'd be normal high schoolers, right?
Yeah.
But that was just us coming up with our own ideas of what a normal high schooler was
and getting stuck on that train.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing, really.
I just thought that maybe everyone always has a case of something.
That's deep.
Only because you're shallow.
Wait, stop. I'll make dinner.
You sure?
I don't want another broken plate!
What? When did I ever break a plate?
I know you're sad that Takanashi-san won't be around anymore, but...
It's not like she's dead.
And I'm not sad.
Didn't she tell you?
The movers came this evening and...
Rikka...
Rikka!
What the hell?!
Why?!
You said you were coming back!
That you'd only be gone a few days!
Hishiyama Station
Huh? Not at this hour.
You won't have a connecting train.
Okay, thank you.
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
New Message Received
New Messages        1
No subject
Takanashi Rikka
Rikka?
Mama, Grandpa, and Grandma were all really happy.
When I said I'd stay, they looked so relieved.
So I think it might be for the best.
You think so too, right?
I see.
When all is said and done, it's my fault.
I told her to take off her eyepatch
and to get over her eighth-grade syndrome.
Because I...
Okay.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
My Noble Friend, Yuuta
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This letter was received 7/31/2010 with
instructions to be delivered on this date.
Togashi Yuuta
This...
Dark Flame—
When you read this letter, you may no longer be the Dark Flame Master.
This is because in 2012, in accordance with the Mayan prophecy,
the waves of ruin shall engulf all and weaken the waves of your soul.
You will view life only philosophically,
give up, simply accept what you see before you,
and become a foolish, normal human.
I can sense that now.
Thus, I write you this letter.
Dark Flame Master,
do not be fooled!
You have power!
You are the King of Darkness,
He who was chosen by the Tyrant!
Hold no doubts. You are special.
When I was in eighth grade, I arranged for this to be sent to me in two years.
What the heck?
Just how stupid was I?
I got this coin from the arcade.
There's no power in it.
But...
Tails?
Guess I've got no choice.
I don't mind, but where are you going at this hour?
I'm going to get Rikka back.
Takanashi-san?
Wait, don't tell me you're...
That wasn't what I wanted to say.
What I wanted to say...
What I wanted to do...
That wasn't it.
I...
Halt!
Dark Flame Master,
I bear a message from the Second Tyrant's Eye.
Hey, did Papa really die?
Rikka...
It didn't feel real.
My heart couldn't accept the present.
I thought he was going to get better soon...
until the morning he died.
Rikka...
I...
I'm...
Then I met Yuuta.
What? She met me?
Yes. Rikka-chan—I mean, the Tyrant's Eye met you two years ago.
She was living with the Priestess.
Move?
Yeah.
You can move in with Grandpa and Grandma.
But what about our house?
I guess I should. It's for the best, right?
Rikka...
Hey, that hurts!
Stop it!
The air clings to my skin.
They must be close.
She watched you every day after that.
What?! There!
No, over there?!
Now, with this...
Who's there?!
Someone's watching me...
Rikka-chan thought that being able to live like that was wonderful.
That it was so much more honest—even cooler—than bottling up your feelings
and living how other people want you to.
Then what...
What...
What caused her eighth-grade syndrome?
Rikka-chan is a girl who was saved by eighth-grade syndrome.
A girl who saw your case and admired your strength.
A girl who was drawn to your power and tried to imitate it.
That's why she chose you.
It had to be you!
Rikka-chan was always...
always, always...
Always...
Rikka!
Yuuta?
I need to water them.
Yuuta?!
I am not Yuuta!
Yuuta!
Takanashi Rikka...
No, the Tyrant's Eye!
There is something I must show you.
Yuuta...
Be bound...
to me by contract!
Who's there?!
A thief?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Crap!
Grandma, the gun!
Bring me the gun!
Rikka! Come on!
But...
Do you want to stay in this boring reality?!
Or do you want to come with me and change that reality?!
Yuuta!
Grandma!
Rikka!
Yuuta!
Hey!
What are you doing up there?
It's a misunderstanding!
Eek! He's trying to molest me!
Eek!
Come on, act the part! You're the criminal!
Me?!
Guh-he-he! Lemme cop a feel!
Hey, freeze! Don't move!
Wait!
I have extenuating circumstances!
Why are they here?
Come on! Get going!
You're here too?!
Deko-chan's family lent us their car!
Here.
Get back here!
Damn, leg cramp!
Want to switch?
Be at ease.
Before the power of the Dark Flame Master,
this is nothing!
The lights...
Pretty, aren't they?
But those are just ship lights.
Normal, electric lights.
Get off.
Behold the power of darkness.
Reality, be rent.
Synapse, break.
Vanishment,
this
world!
Yuuta...
This is the Unseen Horizon.
Those lights are watching you.
Tell him.
What you wanted to say.
What you never had a chance to say.
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Papa!
Good-bye!
"Eighth-grade syndrome is embarrassing."
Anyone would tell you that.
"I don't want to remember my past."
"I'd erase it if I could."
But would the part of you that caused the whole affair really disappear?
The part of you that imagines you're being watched,
the part that pretends to be a made-up character...
Could that disappear?
Sometimes people say certain things,
On Patrol
imagine a world different from our own,
think of the distant future,
and write epics of love in their minds.
From the moment they're born to the moment they die,
people will repeat this, time and again,
without any hope of stopping.
Something sad and embarrassing, yet charming.
A disease called self-consciousness.
An unavoidable part of life called being true to yourself.
Indeed, everyone has eighth-grade syndrome all their lives.
It's freezing!
Do you want to see my eye?
But at any rate...
Eighth-grade syndrome is still embarrassing.
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
Until we meet again!
Rebel Against Reality