Looks like you're packing lightly.
I'm going to be living there.
It's cheaper to buy what I need once I move.
By the way, I appreciate the help.
Don't mention it.
I am the Dark Flame Master!
Wielder of the Dark Flame and—
Catch.
You can keep it.
How generous of you.
And I don't think I ever told you, but...
Thank you for everything.
I can leave without worrying thanks to you.
Thank you very much.
That's not...
Onee-chan...
Thanks.
Mama should be home soon...
No, I'll miss my plane.
Tell her "bye" for me.
Onee-chan...
Come on, Yumeha.
Bye-bye.
Let me see the kids sometimes.
No, Yumeha—
She learned that from me.
Don't worry. I'll let you see them.
Bye.
Good-bye.
I'll text you.
Three weeks have passed since Rikka stopped wearing her eyepatch.
She's trying to accept the
situation as best as she can.
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
We're having pepper steak again?
Stop complaining and just eat.
Pepper steak!
A One-Winged Fallen Angel
Kuzuha, help Yumeha get changed.
Come on, Yumeha.
Pepper steak!
Onii-chan, Takanashi-san's here.
Rikka!
Coming!
G-G-G-Good morning!
Good morning.
I'll go get Onii-chan now.
U-Um...
Yes?
P-Please get Yuuta-kun for me.
Okay.
When you make conversation, it has to flow.
If the person you're talking to knows what you want, you don't need to tell them.
But Nibutani said that you
should answer regardless.
Well, you should, but...
This is hard.
This is how you end up when you've suffered from eighth-grade syndrome for so long.
Now what?
She said to change how I talk too.
Really?
That is correct, Yuuta-kun.
Is there anything you require?
You're not a maid.
Might there be something you need?
You're not a rich girl either.
What do you want?
Please, anything but that.
What?
That's more like it.
She said that it's too blunt.
Well, maybe...
Wh-Wha'ccha want?
Don't get embarrassed when you're trying to make a joke.
You'll make me embarrassed too.
Halt.
Morning.
Don't you "Morning" me!
Today is the day that I banish the demon possessing Master's spirit!
Sanae-chan, I told you, I'm...
Don't you dare call me Sanae-chan!
Let's go!
Stop!
I thought I was a goner...
Be careful.
Sorry.
Not!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Banishment, this world!
Master!
I'm...
Open your eyes!
...done with that.
Master...
Look, you should try—
Shut up!
I will never give up!
I swear... I swear to destroy the demon controlling Master and save her!
Rikka?
What?
Are you...
Are you really okay with all of this?
No, forget I said anything.
It'd be irresponsible of me to keep talking.
She was scouted?
Yeah. The performance she did at the cultural festival was a huge hit.
Oh, the one she did with Dekomori?
They were looking for someone who could put on a lively performance.
Everyone had a wonderful time at the cultural festival, reaping the fruits of their labors.
What fruits?
I didn't get anything out of it.
You?! Nothing at all?!
You, who confessed to Takanashi-san at the festival, got nothing out of it?!
Why are you being so resentful?
You two have been coming to school together and acting all lovey-dovey!
Well, yeah...
Meanwhile, I keep dropping the ball!
Kumin-senpai was sleeping.
You didn't really get turned down—
You bet I didn't! I'll never give up!
Y-Yeah...
I'll never give up!
I heard you the first time.
Um...
Takanashi-san?
What is it?
Please be my friends.
What'd she say?
Is she...
We'd be happy to.
That was just like a confession scene! I was completely speechless!
Me too!
Damn it, it's my lunch break!
Library
Isn't this the librarian's job?
Yeah.
Library
Is that the last stack?
Those dumb teachers sure have it easy.
They just make the class reps do everything.
I heard you got scouted by the Drama Club.
Yeah, I was.
What are you going to do?
Nothing really.
Why do you want to know?
No reason.
Togashi-kun...
Do you regret it?
Regret what?
What happened with Takanashi-san.
Why would I?
No special reason.
Now that she's gotten over her eighth-grade syndrome,
Touka-san can rest easy, and she's getting along with her mom.
Nothing bad came out of it.
I guess you're right.
Yeah.
I see.
Did you see it, Takanashi-san?
Yeah.
It was so funny!
I like it.
Really? I didn't think you would.
Hey, let's go see them live sometime!
Yeah! Let's do that!
The wind blows.
Dekomori sways.
To the left, to the right.
Thinking of Master.
O, Master!
Hey.
What's up, middle-schooler?
You look down.
Do not speak to me, normal human.
Don't call me that.
And you're a normal human too.
No, I am not.
I am the Wielder of the Mjollnir Hammer!
Oh, I see. If you've got that much energy, you're fine.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm writing a love letter!
To Kumin-senpai
Isshiki Makoto
You still haven't given up?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Master! I've been waiting for you!
Deko—Sanae-chan.
I found something amazing!
You have to see it!
Look at all these sorcerer's stones!
Which do you want?
Which do you want?!
They're all filled with grade-A magic!
Dekomori...
Just one second!
This will make them even prettier!
Master!
Dekomori...
Yes?
I have something important to tell you.
Yes?!
Could it be a new plot from the Administration—
No.
This society...
No, this club...
is being disbanded today.
Master?
Everyone should do what they want.
That includes you.
What's gotten into you, Master?!
This society was necessary to find the
Unseen Horizon—to go to the other world!
Master!
You heard her.
So give me the Mabinogion and go back to middle school already.
Unhand me!
Shut up and come with me.
Don't you think you're trying a bit too hard?
Both you and Takanashi-san.
Unhand me!
Stop struggling!
It's okay.
Get out of my way...
We've got a lot of work to do.
We don't have much time.
I promised that I would put it all away before Mama came.
If I keep them out, she'll be worried.
I don't want to worry her.
I see.
What should we pack first?
Let's start with everything that's on the floor.
Got it.
You had one of these too?!
This...
You're taking that down too?
Why not?
I don't know what I can and can't keep.
Yeah, why not?
Let's take them down.
Thanks.
Are you sure?
That was practically your entire room.
I think she can have some peace of mind like this.
Yuuta!
Are you hungry?
You too?
Your mom's going to be late, right?
Wanna come to my place?
Can we eat out tonight?
Sure, I guess.
Is this really all you want?
Yeah. This is fine.
Yuuta, hold the bottom.
You really love doing that.
It's cool!
What's so cool about it?
Here.
Pretty, isn't it?
Yeah.
But those are cars.
They're just headlights.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean...
Yuuta.
What is it?
Mama...
wants me to visit to the cemetery with her.
To visit Papa's grave.
What do you think?
What do I think?
Tell me what you think.
I think Mama will be happy if I go.
Then why don't you go?
If you want to go, then...
Pinky.
Thanks.
I'll go home first.
Wait, Rikka...
Hi, Rikka-chan!
Kumin... senpai?
Dodomen?
He got himself hurt.
Hey, don't try to take it off.
Is something wrong?
Thanks.
She couldn't be...
It just left, so have a seat.
Here.
Thanks.
You've been thanking me a lot lately.
Hey, you're...
You're coming back, right?
After you visit the grave,
you're coming back here, right?
Yeah. I have to go to school.
Yeah.
You're right.
Wait right there!
I told you I'd never give up!
Dekomori?
I am your servant!
Even if it means being thrown into the deepest parts of the Abyss,
I will stay by your side!
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Banishment, this world!
Destiny Mjollnir Impulse!
Ultimate Technique!
Dekomori...
Don't touch me!
Rikka.
Why didn't you tell her?
Why didn't you tell her not to go?
Master wanted you to tell her!
To tell her, "I'll search for the
Unseen Horizon with you,
so don't go!"
Because she...
Master said that she could maintain the Tyrant's Eye this long
only because of the Dark Flame Master's presence!
You were an anchor for her heart!
That's why she called me when the Dark Flame Master said that the Unseen Horizon existed!
She called me when you were
joined by the contract of lovers!
She was crying!
Master was crying!
My master!
The strongest, crying!
She believed in you!
Why didn't you tell her that the Tyrant's Eye is the strongest?!
To be engulfed by the flames of darkness?!
She waited...
She waited and waited...
Master waited so long for you to say that!
Why didn't you? Why didn't you?!
What...
What good would it do?
What good would it do if I said that and made her happy?
That's—
There is no Unseen Horizon!
Her father is in a grave!
I can't do anything about that!
No matter how much she wishes...
Shut up.
No matter what kind of world she imagines...
Shut up!
No matter what kind of powers she believes she has...
If it doesn't exist, it doesn't exist!
Shut up!
Have your attacks ever worked on anyone?
They don't work on humans,
but they will work on demons.
Have you ever really summoned a weapon?
I...
You haven't.
No matter what how much you want, no matter how much you believe...
They don't exist!
I...
I know that!
N-No...
That's not...
what I wanted to say...
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
Next week, the last episode!