13:24 - Shinka
13:27 - Mori Summer
Quiz (Review Questions)
I don't get it.
I don't get it at all.
Nibutani
Magic?
Napping?
Why would Nibutani join a hobby group with no clear goals?
We're talking about the girl who was voted cutest in our class.
Nibutani
The one who all the guys are head over heels for.
I just don't get it.
Nibutani
Is she actually interested in magic?
Or is she interested in the napping part?
Or maybe...
No, there's no way.
Could she...
Huh?
You want to know why I joined?
Sorry, it's just been bugging me.
You seemed pretty excited about joining.
You really wanna know?
Y-Yeah.
Well, you see...
It's because a certain someone can't take a hint.
No, no, no!
Wait just a second!
I can't start jumping to conclusions!
I love you!
Eighty percent of guys do exactly that, only to experience the biggest shock of their lives!
I need to calm down and approach this logically.
What does she want now?
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
Stamp a seal of your blood
in this circle.
We shall hold a Black Mass.
In the end, I joined Rikka's hobby group.
I guess my quiz was too easy for you, Togashi.
No, it's not, but...
Needless to say, it wasn't because I missed my eighth-grade syndrome days
Get back to work, then! Stay focused!
or because I'm actually interested in the group.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't get her words out of my head.
I was thinking of joining your hobby group.
I just turned in the form to join.
My hobby group.
That's what she called it.
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
The Mabinogion... of Regrets
I hope Nibutani isn't here yet.
What the heck?
It looks like we've summoned the Dark Flame Master.
The Magic Circle of Saturnus is worthy of its reputation.
It continues to summon us various things.
Hey now...
Would you mind explaining this?
What did you do to the floor?!
What do you think? It's a magic circle.
Are you an idiot or something?
I know that much.
I'm asking why you made one on the floor.
I told you during class that we'd be holding a Black Mass.
That's right!
We've even prepared the sacrifice.
Heal-all tastes so good...
Now look here!
You can't bring the cat to school.
We formed this society for the purpose of finding the Unseen Horizon.
We require Chimaera.
Master, let's continue!
Let us summon something else in exchange for this sacrifice!
Yes, let's.
In the name of the Tyrant's Eye, I summon thee.
Thy name is Dark Annihilator.
Thy blood, thy flesh, thy bone, all without form.
Let's kick it up a notch.
You're putting way too much effort into this!
Master, that angle is perfect!
Let's do that again!
Master, you're so cool!
Wanna give it a try, Dekomori?
Yeah, you bet I do!
Darker than the deepening twilight.
Redder than the falling blood.
Laying equal ruin upon all,
Draugsleip!
What happened?
What do you think you're doing?!
That's my master!
You understand me so well!
Naturally.
You're amazing! I'm nothing compared to you!
Clean it up.
We're taking orders from a summoned being...
How humiliating!
The Dark Flame Master is a force to be reckoned with.
Less talking, more cleaning.
You too, Kumin-senpai. Wake up already!
But that stuff is really bitter.
What is she dreaming about?
Hello!
Nibutani?!
Sorry for not showing up till now.
I've been busy with cheerleading.
No need to worry.
Our search for the Unseen Horizon is making progress.
Unseen... what?
N-Nothing! Don't worry about it.
O-Okay.
Huh?
What's this?
I-It's nothing!
Wow! Is this a magic circle?
So you guys really are researching magic.
N-No! Not at all It's just a decoration!
This society was formed
to discover the Unseen Horizon.
It is for that purpose alone that I, the Tyrant's Eye,
the Mjollnir Hammer,
and the Dark Flame Master have assembled.
H-Hold on!
I thought I told you not to call me that!
What are you whispering about, Dark Flame Master?
Why don't you say something, Dark Flame Master?
You're doing that on purpose.
Doing what, Dark Flame Master?
Dark Flame Master!
Open up!
Open this door!
Will she be okay?
Don't worry about her.
She'll adjust to it soon enough.
This barrier...
Could it be connected to a parallel world?
See?
Wh-What?!
Oh, this is Tsuyuri Kumin-san.
She's a member and a second-year.
Her hobby is napping.
Remember that "Napping" you saw in the group's name?
Oh, right...
So, did you join to nap too?
Well, not really.
So why did you?
Well, um...
What about you, Nibutani?
Why did you join?
Oh c'mon, don't ask.
It's kind of hard to tell you, Togashi-kun.
That sounded really suggestive!
Could she actually have...
It isn't here!
What now?
The Rainbow Codex, the Mabinogion!
It's vanished!
I left it in this locker!
The Mabinogion?
Oh, you mean that binder you were carrying around?
Has it been taken to the depths of a parallel worl—
Calm down. It's in my room.
I took it home with me by mistake the last time I cleaned this room.
Give it back.
Give it back, now!
All right, all right! I'll bring it back.
Give it back!
What's wrong with you?
Oh, cheerleading practice should be starting soon.
I've gotta go.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Togashi-kun, do you have a minute?
This Sunday?
Yeah.
If you're busy, maybe we can do it another day?
No?
No—I mean, there's nothing to do at my place.
What's the occasion?
The occasion?
I just wanted to talk to you alone.
Well?
It's strange, no matter how much I think about it.
What should I do?
Let's go home together!
Let's go home together!!
Let's go home together!!!
Let's go home together!
Let's go home together!!
Let's go home together!!!
I haven't done anything to raise my stats or trigger any special events.
Well, I guess we could.
Then let's go.
Um...
So if an event like this is happening...
There's a place I want to go.
Okay.
No thanks.
Am I headed for a plain old bad ending?
But this is reality...
I hear you have a problem.
When did you get there?!
I've searched all night, but I've found no information regarding the Unseen Horizon.
'Tis a shame.
All I've found is this book.
The Human Realm has corrupted you.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with me looking at stuff like this?!
You shouldn't!
The Dark Flame Master shouldn't look at things like that.
J-Just drop it.
Are you doing anything this Sunday?
This Sunday?
Unfortunately, to prevent any leaks of information, I cannot—
I don't care! Just answer yes or no!
I don't have any plans.
I thought so.
That means...
Wow, what a great view!
You think so?
You look great, too...
What?
I've got no choice!
Hey, Rikka...
Let me show you something cool.
Something cool?
Yeah.
Back when I was in middle school,
I found a way to visit another world.
Look.
It's kind of far, but if you follow these directions,
you'll find a singularity that'll lead to the other world.
Well?
Are you interested?
A singularity?
At 4 pm, the second hands of this and the other world shall overlap.
Once that happens, if you follow the shadow of the 13th power pylon from the station...
We have four hours.
We must hurry.
This is so exciting!
I want to try eating curry in the other world!
I never imagined the Darkness Note could come in handy like this.
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Body
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Body
A
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
A
Nibutani Shinka
Hello
Body
I'm one station away!
Togashi-kun!
H-Hey!
My life starts now!
Your room's so nice and neat.
R-Really?
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yeah, two little sisters.
Oh, but they're both out with my mom for the day.
So it's just you here today?
Yeah, we'll be alone until night.
N-No! I didn't mean it like that!
Like what?
W-Well... uh... I...
I-I'll go make some tea.
Oh, uh... Thank you very much!
Crap!
What am I supposed to talk about?!
I can't be hasty again!
I got way too excited back in middle school, and...
With our past and future lives in mind,
I have filled this text with all the magic I could muster.
Love you forever.
Die! Die!
Please die!
I want my old self to die!
What was that?
It's coming from my room?
Did something happen—
Oh, Togashi-kun! What's up?
Um...
I-I'll go make some tea.
Oh, yeah!
Thank you very much!
What the hell just happened?
Come on! Where did you hide it?!
Wh-What is she doing?!
Where did you hide it?
Sealed Forever
What's this?
Is it in here?
Don't open that!
Where is it?
Where's what?
The Mabinogion that idiot had!
Why do you—
Just find it!
I think I put it in...
Oh, here it is.
Man, this thing is pretty heavy.
What?
Though I have lost my memories,
I am a true mage who has survived for the last 500 years.
This is the story of my life, a life of the faeries' blessing.
My name is...
Mori Summer.
Stop!
I don't... I don't want to hear anymore!
As you may already know, there exists a white world and a black world within our own.
The shame! The shame! The shame!
This reaction...
Wait a minute...
Ni
bu
tani
Shin
ka
Nibutani Shinka...
Shinka...
Shin
ka
"Mori" and "Summer"...
Mori Summer
Mori Summer!
I see!
What a strange book.
I wonder who wrote it!
Who...
would...
write this?!
Nibutani...
You...
We shall now open the space-time door.
Okay, Master!
This is a very dangerous operation.
I know that very well.
Then let's—
Schwarzsechs Prototype Mark II!
Wait!
Um...
Ridiculous, isn't it?
I'd gone to the trouble of deleting each and every post on my blog,
but I never stopped to think that someone would have a printed copy.
Well...
I still can't believe you wrote something like that.
I even chose a high school that no one from my middle school would go to.
I thought I'd be able to start anew after leaving behind my awful past.
Listen up! If you ever tell anyone, I'll curse you to death!
Her personality did a complete 180!
I-I understand. Your secret is safe with me.
Honestly, how many problems does that kid need to cause me?
Um...
So when you said you wanted to talk to me today...
Wanted to?
Of course I didn't.
I should've known.
S-So you joined the hobby group to...
...get rid of this binder, obviously.
Think I'd have any other reason to join that group?
Right...
But now I'm finally free from my past.
What sweltering heat!
It's over 200,005,000 degrees Celsius!
Bear with it, Dekomori.
Just until my incantation is complete.
You guys are back already?
Unfortunately, the clouds prevented us from locating the singularity.
And since I came all the way out here, I at least want to take the Mabinogion back with me.
Oh, y-yeah...
Return it to me at once!
Where is it?
Right here.
It's been burnt to ashes.
Too bad.
Now the records are lost for all eternity.
How could you...
do something like this?
Hey, you okay?
My precious...
Geh-heh.
"Geh-heh"?
Geh-heh-heh-heh-heh.
Dekomori?
There's nothing to worry about!
I made copies of it, just in case something like this happened.
Mori Summer is a great mage.
She and Master answered my queries about parallel worlds
that I submitted to the question box.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
I want to go to a parallel world
Asker:
Body
I want to go to a parallel world.
All my friends say that those are just in games
and won't talk to me about them.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Answerer: Tyrant's Eye
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Parallel worlds exist. However, the administration is
hiding their existence from us. There should be a way to
break through their interference somewhere in this  world.
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
Answerer: Mori Summer
I understand how you feel.
Ordinary citizens in this world cannot sense that which
does not belong in this world.
For someone like you, with strong spiritual power,
it may be possible to
She is truly a great mage!
Mori Summer
Her words were deemed too dangerous and removed by the authorities,
The page you have requested could not be found.
but I, Dekomori, shall continue to spread her—
I deleted it all myself.
I couldn't take it anymore.
And who are you supposed to be?
I'm Mori Summer.
Understand? I wrote all that stuff.
I'm the one who answered your question a year ago.
Now give the Mabinogion back to the one who wrote it.
Ha! Don't be stupid!
A normal, rotten human such as yourself could never pass as Mori Summer!
Who are you calling a normal, rotten human?!
Hey, Nibutani!
Huh?
What is your head made of?
That's what you get for calling yourself Mori Summer.
I'm the real deal!
Never speak that name again.
I'll spare your life so long as you comply.
Dekomori is serious.
Now then, Master, I shall take my leave.
I'm gonna make that stupid kid pay for that.
O faeries who inhabit Heaven and Earth.
By thy blessing, bestow upon me power!
May misfortune befall Dekomori Sanae!
Um, Nibutani?
I need to say it 100 times without being interrupted or it won't work!
Well, if you don't mind me asking...
Don't you think you're regressing back to your old self?
I wasn't thinking and started my
eighth-grade syndrome stuff again!
Yeah...
Back then, I...
The faeries are whispering to me again.
Die! Die!
I want my old self to die!
That's enough, Nibutani.
Die!
The ground hasn't done anything wrong.
But I know how you feel.
I mean, I had a case of it too.
I would get too absorbed into games and anime back then.
I even pretended I was some weird character who could control darkness and stuff.
Dark Flame Master!
Like that.
Oh, really?
What a loser.
More importantly, where does that girl live?
I don't know.
I think Rikka does.
You rang?
Wait, were you here the whole time?
Going to Dekomori's house would be pointless.
Her allegiance lies first with me, then with Mori Summer.
Also, she likely possesses infinite copies of the Mabinogion.
No way...
She will only listen to the true Mori Summer.
But that doesn't mean we don't have another way.
Huh? What is it?
Um, but...
Tell me!
My high school life is on the line here!
You have to...
What now?
Let's see how strong you really are.
It seems you're dead set on this.
We'll see how big your mouth is when I'm done with you!
You're good!
Looks like Togashi-kun was right.
In other words, you just need to make her believe
that you're really strong in her own delusions.
Reality, be rent!
Synapse, break!
Banishment, this world!
Let's see what you've got, kid.
You really are good.
Mjollnir Tornado!
Geraint Black!
Try all you want! You'll never convince me!
You are not Mori Summer!
I'm telling you, it's me!
Mori Summer said that love means everything!
That only those who are pure in heart can see faeries!
The last mage on Earth, living until the modern day!
Her sadness, her emptiness...
I will shoulder it all and live!
No!
Stop it!
It seems your rotten heart is being purified by the words of Mori Summer.
You fake!
I don't want to hear anymore!
Don't make me remember!
I guess someone who's been reformed can't handle someone who hasn't.
Just stop it!
Here you go. Enjoy!
Thank you.
So you're staying in our group?
Well, it's only until I accomplish what I set out to do.
Let me give you the symbol of the Napping Club, the magic pillow of friendship.
No thank you.
Here comes that stupid kid.
Oh, if it isn't the fake Mori Summer.
Don't call me that!
Seriously. You act so big even though you're so tiny.
What'd you call me?
I'm not tiny!
You look tiny to me.
I'm going to grow taller!
Oh? Did I hit a nerve?
I'll tell you how to get taller if you give me the Mabinogion.
Who'd give it to a rotten, fake Mori Summer like you?!
Don't call me that!
Shut up!
You'd better do something about this.
Roger.
Wait, don't—
Flour
What was that?
Come on!
What are you doing?!
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
What,
you say?!
What?!
See you next week!