23:31 - To Be Continued
I held a girl in my arms for the first time.
She felt really soft, and a little warm too.
So fragile that it felt like she
might break if I held too tight.
Inside me, it hurt.
Rikka...
Rikka?
Forget! Forget! Forget!
AV Lab
Video Projects Shown Here
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
All students must leave campus by 7 PM.
The Pandora's Box... of the Madonna
I repeat.
All students must leave campus by 7 PM.
Master!
Will the Magician's Night rise as the darkness falls?
Master?
Did time stop or something?
Doesn't look like it.
Master?
What is it, Master?
Wait a minute...
Master, do you...
Master, you mustn't!
I am your servant.
Such emotions are forbidden!
Though everyone knows that the more taboo something is, the more stimulating it is...
Master?
I was locked in embrace with Yuuta.
I love Yuuta.
Master?
How dare they create a fake Master?!
First a fake Mori Summer, and now a fake Master?
Your true master.
In other words, that means...
You've fallen to the Dark Flame Master...
...i-in love?
Master, there is somewhere I must go.
I shall take my leave.
Dekomori.
Don't stop me!
As your servant, I must deliver darkness upon those who steal your—
What should I do?
You said the Dark Flame
Master's presence was
the reason you could maintain the Tyrant's Eye this long.
I'm sure the Dark Flame Master senses those powerful feelings as well.
You think so?
I've served you for over two years now.
A servant knows everything about her master!
Dekomori...
There's no need to worry.
The Tyrant's Eye is the strongest.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
With Takanashi-san?
Yeah.
What should I do?
What do you mean?
Should I confess to her?
You like Takanashi-san, right?
I think so.
But it's not because she's sexy or cute or anything like that!
It's like... she's got a really bad
case of eighth-grade syndrome,
but she's not a normal case!
She has a hard time because
of that, so I feel sorry for her...
Um...
But it's not pity or anything like that...
Just stop talking!
You don't need a reason to love someone!
You stop talking.
Good luck.
Same to you.
Get off me! Gross!
What was that for?!
I offered an ear for you to talk to!
I never wanted to talk about it!
If I didn't tell you, you'd start
making stuff up about us!
You're pretty lucky though.
Takanashi-san made it to fourth place in the ranking, you know.
To think that...
To think what?
To think that you'll do it someday...
It?
Yuuta.
Unfortunately, I do not have experience making physical contact with another.
Unfortunately,
I don't either.
What the hell are you saying?! Are you stupid or something?!
Anyway, I think I'll try hitting it big tonight.
Kumin-senpai!
What is it?
W-Would you...
go with me to the bonfire?
Sure.
Really?!
Cut!
Why do I have to watch this dumb act?
It ain't an act!
And what're you doing here?
We need to practice our performance for tomorrow.
Where are Togashi-kun and Takanashi-san?
Do not speak of them.
I am presently very angry.
We shall fight.
We can do that some other day.
Do you know where those two—
They went home!
Together!
The Dark Flame Master said that he
had something important to tell her,
and they left!
Hey...
By my contract, I command thee.
What's that?
A sorcerer's stone.
It grants wishes.
Dekomori gave it to me.
Wishes?
I can't tell you my wish.
I never asked what it was.
You dropped it.
Wow, it's hot.
A sorcerer's stone emits heat in response to a strong wish.
In other words—
No!
Ow...
It's raining.
Yeah.
Do you have an umbrella—
Oh right, you do.
What did you want?
Oh, right.
No, I have something to tell you too.
Something top-secret.
I-I see...
Actually, I have something to tell you too...
but not here...
I can't just let it drag on like this.
Hey.
Schwarzsechs Prototype Mark II!
Do you have to say the full name every time?
Wait!
Good thing it didn't fall into the river.
Yeah.
What is it?
The lights.
The lights are moving.
nani mo iwanai senaka ni te noshite
If I were to reach out and put my hand on your back,
Rikka—
I love you, Yuuta.
nan tte ieba ii no kana
You'll just stay quiet, so what should I say?
suki ni naru no ni riyuu wa nai no ni
It doesn't take a reason to fall in love with someone,
yuuki no nasa ni iiwake bakari
But I need excuses because I'm too shy
I love you, Yuuta.
yuugure kumo nagameteitara
When I'm watching the clouds at sunset
kirakira tte oto ga suru mitai
It's almost like I can hear them glittering
W-Wait a second!
sou iu kimochi yume sura
I'm sure that feeling, and even my dreams,
I'm supposed to tell you first!
No.
kimi to nara wakachiaeru
Are things that only we could share
I get to go first by the
power of the Tyrant's Eye.
koi no kakera ima hitotsu ni
These bits of love are coming together now
But I'm the Dark Flame Master!
yasuppoi kotoba de kazattemo
Even if I dress them in all sorts of fancy words
The Tyrant's Eye is the strongest.
kimi ni todokanai kamoshirenai
They might not be able to reach your heart
No way! That didn't count!
I even thought up a cool line too. I'll say it now.
demo nani mo iwanai mama da to kimi wa
But if I don't say anything then you just might
Okay.
You, engulfed by the flames of darkness!
kiechau kamo shirenai
Disappear into the night
Be joined with the Dark Flame Master by the contract of lo—
ano hoshi mitai ni
Just like that star
ima koko de naiteru no
Right now I can see that you're crying
Never mind.
Anyway—
Keep going.
Yuuta.
doushitara warattekuremasu ka
What do I need to do to make you smile?
You, engulfed by the flames of darkness.
eien to tsunaide seiza ni shitai
I want to make it forever, like the constellations
Be joined with the Dark Flame Master by the contract of lovers.
kono yubi de
With these hands
Okay.
Don't you normally do this kind of thing face to face?
senaka awase ja nakute kocchi wo muite
Don't walk with your back to me, look this way
Too embarrassing?
Yeah.
Then how about holding hands?
soshite tonari wo arukitai yo
I want to walk beside you
Just the pinky.
Then just pinkies?
Yeah.
I'm home.
Onii-chan, you're really late.
Sorry, Kuzuha.
Does the plaintiff still love the defendant?
No.
I want to divorce the defendant as soon as humanly possible.
What are you doing?
We need to talk.
The taste has gotten worse.
You can have it.
Couldn't we talk in the apartment?
I don't want Rikka to hear this.
It's from the flagship restaurant in Italy.
They want me to train there.
I have no reason to refuse.
You really are amazing...
You doubted me?
No...
Doesn't matter.
But that's great!
I'm sure Rikka—
You understand, don't you?
She can't live in that apartment by herself.
That's why...
when I leave...
Mama will move in with her.
Rikka's mom?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
Do you think it'll go well?
Rikka doesn't have a grudge against her mom, right?
Then—
Mama...
Mama tried talking to Rikka countless times.
She apologized for not telling Rikka about Papa's condition.
But...
Wh-What's wrong, Touka-san?!
Please, do something about it.
I know she'll listen to you.
If you tell her to face reality, she will!
I think Rikka is already facing reality.
I think her eyepatch is like a shield to protect herself.
I think Rikka understands everything.
But she doesn't know what to do with her sadness.
That's why she does what she does.
By acting like that, she's holding on to something.
To what?
I don't know.
But she doesn't want it to disappear.
If she listens to what you and your mother have to say and accepts it, it'll all be over.
She doesn't want that.
What's wrong with it?
The "Horizon" and the "Tyrant's Eye" don't exist.
She'll never see Papa again no matter how hard she looks.
That's...
What good is there in letting her keep looking?
She'll never find what she wants to see.
But...
To let her keep looking...
is irresponsible.
Ginkgo Festival
Here you go!
Thank you for purchasing a cheese potato!
They have a big line.
Ugh. They look nice on the outside,
but on the inside, they're the
slimiest girls you'll ever meet.
That's why I lost my motivation.
Oh, so they're like cheese potatoes.
Crispy on the outside, slimy on the inside.
That wasn't funny, you know.
Now where are Togashi-kun and Takanashi-san?
They said they were going to change.
Hurry it up!
Just you wait, girls.
We're gonna steal all your
customers with our performance!
Hey, if it ain't Mori Summer!
Don't call me that—
Satou?! Suzuki?!
Yo! Long time no eighth.
How old are you now?
716?
Still catching lizards?
Like you can talk!
You wore purple lipstick and pretended you were terminal!
Oh? Satou used to be like that?
And Suzuki, you said you discovered elves.
That was...
Elves?
It's dangerous because you never know what kind of pasts are coming up next
when ex-sufferers start fighting.
Our fight...
Our fight isn't over yet.
I increased my Hammer's strength by four times for today.
They're heavy!
Man, you're really stupid...
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
What good is there in letting her keep looking?
To let her keep looking...
is irresponsible.
Yuuta, you look so cool!
Don't look at me like that!
Your attack.
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness and begone.
Yuuta, do it.
No.
You'll be doing it soon enough anyway.
Well, I guess.
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness and begone.
It had no impact.
Do I really need to make it have impact?
Yes.
Spread your legs, bend your knees,
and make your coat ripple in the wind.
Fine, fine.
Be engulfed by the flames of darkness and begone!
No pictures!
Next, us together.
Our mission is about to start.
We must be to our post.
Yeah.
Though I'm not really feeling it.
Rikka.
What?
Nothing.
Pinky.
Excuse me...
Yes?
Is there a girl named Takanashi Rikka here?
Is this...
She's not here right now.
I see.
Could you give this to her?
Um...
It's okay.
I'm going to go home now.
I'm sure...
she still isn't ready to see me again.
Is it irresponsible?
Yuuta.
What're you just sitting there for?
Let's get started already!
They've got a ton of customers right now!
Rikka.
Your eyepatch.
Take it off.
Now it's time for our annual talent show!
It's open to anyone who wants to jump in!
Now then, first contestant, the stage is yours!
Number one, Harada Shinya from class 2-3, will be doing impressions!
The vice-principal!
Wh-Wh-What?!
How did the performance go?
That kid and I managed somehow.
She hits hard, you know.
Sorry.
I never expected you to say something like that.
Her lunch...
You could feel that it was still warm.
It felt so heavy.
Like it was full of something.
Now for the second contestant!
Love?
Reality.
Number two, Isshiki Makoto from class 1-4!
I will be screaming!
Tsuyuri Kumin-senpai!
Please go out with me!
I'm sorry.
So where's Takanashi-san?
That's too bad!
But don't worry, I'm sure there's another girl out there for you!
I'll go look for her.
That was Isshiki Makoto-san with a lovely rejection!
Togashi-kun.
I think you did the right thing.
Next up is a jump-in contestant!
Could you tell us your name and class?
Takanashi Rikka from class 1-4.
Thanks.
I will be singing.
miagete goran yoru no hoshi wo
Take a look up above, see the stars out at night
What the heck is she doing?
chiisana hoshi no chiisana hikari ga
All those little stars, all those little lights
Papa...
It's Papa's favorite song.
sasayaka na shiawase wo utatteru
Singing about all the little things
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
That was Takanashi Rikka-san from class 1-4!
Rikka?
Thank you for the lovely song!
Was there a memory that made you want to sing this song?
To Be Continued
See you next week!