Man, it's hot.
Yeah.
Good morning!
You're totally overreacting.
How can she even wear something like that?
It's so last century.
You wouldn't understand.
Unlike you, Kumin-senpai is an honest person, uninfluenced by the changing times.
Whatever you say, you first-grader.
Don't call me that!
Isshiki-kun, you look like a first-grader!
I'm under attack from the sun and its gamma waves!
Dark Limited Unknown Shield!
Equipped! Ker-wink!
Eighth-grade syndrome?
More like first-grade syndrome.
What'd you just say, Fake Summer?!
Huh?! I-I didn't say anything!
Really?
I get the feeling you lumped me
together with Baldy over there.
Who are you calling bald?!
Shut up, first-grader!
Come with Rikka and me.
We need you.
You're going down, Fake Summer!
What?! If you're looking for a fight, I'll give you one!
Summer has arrived.
Summer vacation is here.
Don't drag me into it!
Good luck!
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Feeling sick already?
Recollections... of a Paradise Lost
What did I tell you? She's totally a first-grader.
Sh-Shut u—
All right, look outside.
Focus on greenery far away.
Shut up.
Now is the time to open the Mabinogion and purge myself of the beast!
My heart—
That'll just make it worse!
Nibutani, the bathroom's over there. Could you take her?
What?! Why me?!
I held it back...
What'll people think if a guy took her in there?
I will never... rely on a fake.
Okay, fine.
D-Don't touch me.
It's right over there. Hold it in.
Saved by an enemy in my time of need...
That's kind of cool.
Quit talking.
Isshiki, help me out here.
Isshiki?
A mole!
Everyone knows what you're looking at.
Now come on.
Okay.
We're almost there.
Hey.
Rikka.
What?
That's all you have to say?!
What, are you trainsick too?
I'm fine.
I've received training.
Then why are you so quiet?
I'm worried.
Did you just wake up?
Did something happen to Rikka-chan?
No...
The world is spinning...
Mjollnir Tornado...
I told you to shut up!
Seriously, why do I have to suffer too?
You're pretty good at this kind of stuff. No wonder you're a class rep.
Don't make it sound like I want to do it!
You got sick watching her throw up!
But more importantly, how's she doing?
Takanashi-san invited us, right?
She wanted us to go back home with her.
Well, you forced yourself into the trip.
Maybe she has something out here?
Like what?
You know what I mean.
Like a boyfriend from back in middle school
who ended up going to a different high school,
so now they're in a long-distance relationship.
Oh man, that'd be a bloodbath!
Bloodbath is a powerful barrier spell.
Shut up, you!
A relationship, huh?
Swear on the Tyrant's Eye?
Yeah, right.
Oh, look.
Who's that?
Touka-san.
Rikka's sister.
What's she doing?
What a big house!
Takanashi-san, is your family rich or something?
Thank you for coming all the way out here.
It was no problem at all.
We're always causing so much trouble for Takanashi-san.
Being invited here is an honor.
Are you sure we're not imposing on you?
Not at all.
Rikka, are you still playing pirate?
It's all the rage these days.
And I was hoping you'd eventually get a grip.
Dear...
Grandmother.
Give them the Dark Brown Liquid.
Rikka!
Hey, Rikka!
It's not much, but please accept it.
Oh my. Thank you so much.
You shouldn't have.
Please, make yourselves at home.
Thank you very much.
Hey, I just noticed this, but...
You're kind of like a grandma.
Shut up!
Wow! What a big puppy!
What the—
Is this the legendary beast?!
What the heck?!
Hey, stop! Don't!
Nice! Take her out!
Enter.
Doesn't look like you left much here.
What's that?
It can communicate with the
other side of the Unseen Horizon.
Where'd you find that?
You rarely see them these days.
I found it one year ago.
I thought to bring it to my current base,
but the priestess refused.
Yeah, she would.
What's wrong?
Why do you ask?
Well, let's see...
In terms you'd understand...
I sense a presence in this area.
What is it?
This is not my base of operations.
Rather, it is the Administration Bureau's headquarters—the enemy base.
Two years ago, I was brought here.
Two years ago?
At first glance, it appears to be a typical house.
However, a barrier to nullify the existence of the Unseen Horizon surrounds it.
The mental attacks and burdens were endless.
That's why I broke out.
I don't really understand, but
something must've happened.
I needed one thing to break through the barrier.
The power of the Tyrant's Eye.
You in there?
Yes.
I hope you're going this year.
I'll leave your stuff here.
Your friends want to go to the beach.
Don't make them worry about you.
Mori Summer-chan, that's a nice two-piece!
What's up with you?
Even your swimsuit's completely white.
Well, it's the only one I had.
How do I look?
Perfect!
Thank you...
Cut it out!
My eyes!
There's seawater in my eyes!
The Kraken lurks in these waters!
Now is the time to test the power of this mage's shroud in sea battle!
Behold!
That mage's shroud increases your
mobility by 3.88 times, even in water.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
You can move 3.88 times faster.
Come on. Go test it.
I'll get you back for this!
She is moving faster.
Let's go swimming too, Kumin-senpai!
She's asleep?!
You really haven't talked to her much, have you?
What?
Get her, Cerberus!
Wai—
Why do you listen to her?!
I'll get you back for this!
Yuuta.
Hey! Stop following me!
Stop it!
Hey!
Stay away from me!
Here
Come to  Point C3
There's no point in this...
Here
Someone, save me...
Yuuta.
Hurry.
On Patrol
What's this thing?
Rhönrad Zwei Hellbraun.
I wasn't asking for its name.
We are going to the apparition point for the Unseen Horizon.
Get on.
You're staying dressed like that?
We needed this camouflage to evade the priestess's eye—
I thought so.
Hey!
So that's how it is.
Togashi Yuuta.
Yes?
Come with me.
Where?
To see...
her father.
My entire body is in pain.
I've been struck by the holy light.
It's your own fault for playing
all day without any sunscreen.
But the seal is burned in perfectly.
Wow.
Totally lame.
Here. They gave us some snacks.
Sorry.
What's that?
Stupid
mori
Perfect, right?
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
It hurts!
Yeah...
Takanashi
Family
Today makes it three years.
Rikka was still young,
so Papa told us not to tell her.
As a result, Papa's death was really sudden for her.
She didn't have any warning.
And because of that, she still hasn't accepted his death.
She refuses to come here.
Hurry, Mama!
What about her mother?
She gave Rikka and me to Papa's parents and left.
You saw what a straight arrow Grandpa is.
He can't stand Rikka acting like that.
I ended up having to leave this place for work.
And two years later,
she hasn't changed at all.
I must find the Unseen Horizon.
One day, I shall.
I needed one thing to break through the barrier.
The power of the Tyrant's Eye.
Wow!
Did you make all of this, Touka-san?
It's my job, after all.
Oh, right! Takanashi-san's
lunches are always so huge!
Oh! Everyone in class was talking about it!
I can't believe you work at that restaurant.
I wish I were Rikka-chan!
Really?
Let's start eating already!
Thanks for the meal!
Is there cheese in this salad?!
Deko-chan, you can't eat cheese either?
Who could eat something that reeks of rotting rags?
It's made from milk.
Milk is rotten!
The root of all evil!
Eat it.
B-But milk...
Okay.
You're amazing, Deko-chan!
I can see why my master fears the priestess!
Her glare is truly powerful!
Oh, right. Where's Rikka-chan?
I'll go check on her.
Is she not feeling well?
No, um... Kinda.
You there?
What's the password?
The Tyrant's Eye is the strongest.
No.
It's not?!
It appears you've suffered a
mental attack from the priestess.
You are not Yuuta.
Is that what you think?
Ease your heart.
I was once the Dark Flame Master.
Are you sure?
Didn't you want to search for the Unseen Horizon?
You'll help?
Why would I lie now?
W-Well...
Mama, Onee-chan, Grandpa,
and Grandma, they all...
That's why you asked me, right?
Yuuta...
O-Onee—
The priestess is on guard now.
Evading her sight won't be easy.
So you don't want to go?
When are we going?
R-Right now!
Right now?
Yeah. Right now.
When you get on the tree, conceal yourself in its shadow by climbing down the right side.
I don't have my shoes.
I have mine. It's okay.
Hey...
What was that?
Dunno.
A washbasin?
Death.
She fell for it.
Ow...
Wow, Touka-san.
I never thought you'd help her.
What do you plan to do?
Who knows? I, for one, don't.
That line was pretty cool!
Whatever. Just keep quiet.
I knew it...
You're a threat.
Yuuta!
Rikka!
Come on!
Jump!
You okay?
I'm okay.
I've hidden Rhönrad Zwei Hellbraun over here.
Don't do it...
How far is it?
About ten kilometers.
It's that far?!
It's okay.
The Dark Flame Master is the strongest.
The strongest?
Yeah.
You were the strongest.
The Dark Flame Master was the strongest!
I told you not to call me that.
I'm gonna speed up.
But the true strongest is the Tyrant's Eye.
Yeah, yeah.
Togashi-kun and Rikka-chan never came to eat dinner with us.
Fake Summer
And Touka-san went somewhere too...
Well, every relationship needs an obstacle or two.
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Obstacles for what?
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Oh, come on, Deko-chan.
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
Fake Summer
Stupid
mori
But I think it's just a matter of time.
What is?
Stupid
mori
What's a matter of time?
Stupid
mori
I wonder!
Stupid
mori
Kumin-senpai!
You saw him?
Three years ago?
On the night Papa died...
I saw him.
Beyond the Horizon,
I saw Papa.
I could see him.
So he's still here.
He's watching us.
He's watching me from the other side of the Horizon.
I couldn't confirm it or deny it.
But...
Stop.
We're finally here?
Yeah.
My base.
We all lived here with Papa.
For Sale
This is reality.
Papa is gone.
You have to accept it.
For Sale
Reality, be rent.
Synapse, break.
Banishment,
this world!
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
Continued
next time!
See you next time!