Here I go.
Today, I shall defeat you!
Hang in there!
You can do it! I know you can!
It's warm, sticks to my throat, and tastes so raw...
How can people enjoy drinking this?
Hey, has anyone seen my pom-poms—
I-It's all gone!
That's great, Deko-chan!
I did it!
I drank it all!
You didn't drink any of it!
So you're here, Fake Mori Summer?
I have finally conquered milk.
By this time next year, I'll be looking down on you!
Gross!
Now's your chance to grovel at my feet!
It's coming out of your nose.
Faculty Room
Your math teacher gave me an earful
about how badly you're doing in his class.
He says it's because I let you start your hobby group.
I'm sorry.
The zero-axioms of the other world are engraved in my mind.
But getting 2 out of 100 on a your first midterm? That's a bit too low.
2?
Nana-chan, how could you?
Sorry, my tongue slipped.
That definitely wasn't a slip.
You're doing fine in everything else.
Why don't you try a little harder at math?
Leave it to me.
I'll show my true power tomorrow.
Really?
Have no doubts.
Then if you fail the final,
we'll disband your hobby group.
I'll tell the math teacher.
I'm so glad that you're finally motivated.
Thank you very much.
Yuuta.
What?
Wh-What should I do?!
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
Damn it, kid.
The Shackles... of Hard Study
I can't go to practice thanks to you.
I expected as much, Fake Mori Summer.
You smell of spoiled milk.
Oh, she does—
But I'm an upperclassman!
Then act like one!
Hey.
Master!
How long I've waited for you!
What happened in the faculty room?
We have an emergency on our hands.
Don't tell me it's a Blood Type Blue!
Don't make it more complicated!
Hey...
We don't need background music!
So, what happened?
Something smells like milk.
I don't care! What happened?!
Math?
Yeah.
If she fails the final, the group's getting disbanded.
Really? Sounds good to me.
Not like we're doing anything, anyway.
But it's not good!
We finally have our own Napping Club!
We have to devote our youthful days to it!
Is she asleep?
I think so.
You can devote your youthful days to it on your own.
Mori Summer is chubbier than she looks.
She's an idiot.
I don't want to hear that from you!
Well, that's how it is, so it should be more peaceful until finals—
What are you doing?
Deriving the solution.
O Truth, spirits of wisdom and knowledge,
gather here and obey my commands.
You still haven't cleaned that up?
Good timing, Dekomori.
So? What's the answer?
82 degrees.
More or less.
You're just guessing?!
And this part's wrong too.
You worked it out right, but you messed up this multiplication.
7 x 4?
A strong opponent.
4 x 7 isn't too difficult,
but switching the colors to 7 x 4 makes it strong.
Like, "What? They can use that spell?"
I know what you mean!
The 7 times tables are above last-boss level!
You need the Level Upper!
You're right. Like 7 x 8 = 56.
That one's like a king.
And once you pass that one, you reach the 9 times tables.
Casts 9 x 7! !
First, 9 x 7 = 63 is the first form.
Casts 9 x 8! !
Next, 9 x 8 = 72 is the second form.
And then, 9 x 9 = 81 is the final form!
What are you doing?
Anyway, if you stopped making careless mistakes—
Okay. Let's give these names.
7 x 3 is Evil Pierrot.
How about a gruntier-sounding name?
I said, stop!
Evil Pierrot
By the power of the Tyrant's Eye, I command you:
You shall dedicate your soul, your body, and your bone
to prevent me from receiving a failing grade on the math final.
Death.
Praying to gods already?
I'm not praying.
I'm commanding them by the power of the Tyrant's Eye.
Death!
Stop it! They'll punish you instead!
Aren't you in middle school, kid?
What are you doing here?
I am Master's servant.
Accompanying her in battle is my natural duty.
Why don't you study for your own finals instead?
I've already been accepted into your high school.
You? Already?
Keep your delusions to yourself, kid.
She's telling the truth.
I heard that Deko-chan is the top of her class.
No way...
This kid is the top of her class?
Something...
...is wrong with the world.
As far as math goes, I've already finished the middle school curriculum.
First-year high school problems should be no problem for me.
Really? Then what about this one?
Let me see...
I see.
Revised Edition
Math
The answer is x³ - 8.
She's right!
It's the basics of the basics.
Don't tell me you can't solve this, Mas—
You got into high school without being able to solve these?
That's my master!
You unleashed your latent powers!
Looks like she's down for the count.
In Smash terms, something like 300% damage?
Please help me avoid failing the final.
So you're praying now?!
Don't worry, Rikka-chan.
Kumin! Do you have a plan?
When you can't figure out an answer, you can use this!
I'll let you borrow my special pencil!
Question 1: What is the size of the marked angle?
4!
What's the answer?!
3!
Please help Rikka avoid failing her math final.
These two are hopeless.
There's no choice.
Faculty Room
Something you can do?
Yes. Our society is currently only considered a hobby group.
It is in the lowest stratum of the school hierarchy.
It is our intent to do service and contribute to the school. This is why it was founded.
Don't read it straight off.
So that's why you're asking if there's something you could do?
Right.
Something that would make the teachers think, "It's so wonderful to have a hobby group like this around."
She really doesn't want to study, does she?
Well, there is one thing, but...
Really?
It'll be really heavy work.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
We have Yuuta.
Hey!
Let's get this started!
Mjollnir Accel!
Let me explain:
By pumping mana into my lower body, Mjollnir Accel increases my athletic abilities by 3.88 times,
allowing me to move at inhuman speeds.
This acceleration...
Let's go!
Right to the speed of sound!
I'm gonna crash!
But it's a feint! I stop right before!
Come on.
Just get to work.
Why do I have to do this, anyway?
Nana-chan said all the members have to participate.
I don't remember joining this thing.
You turned in the form to join, right?
That was just to get closer to that kid.
I'm only part of the cheerleading team.
Sorry. My hand slipped.
But you know...
You keep saying that you don't like the upperclassmen on the cheerleading team and that you're tired of going.
Why'd you bring a pillow to the pool?!
Are you really?
Not really, but...
Well, I wasn't all that interested in the first place.
Clean! Hurry!
Then why'd you join it?
A class rep and cheerleader is like the polar opposite of an eighth-grade syndrome case.
Hurry hard!
I figured it'd be the best way to escape from my past.
Why do you want to escape from it so badly?
Eighth-grade syndrome looks like a lot of fun.
It's not fun!
Why not?
It's embarrassing!
It's like a diseased patch of life!
It's a tumor full of shame and suffering!
I agree with that on all counts!
You really think so?
To me, Rikka-chan and Deko-chan look like they don't mind it.
Don't sleep after saying that!
You'd better get to work too.
Schwarz Tackle!
Come on, come on, come on!
Adjust firing angle to Gel Dorva!
Gel Dorva!
I'll wash that rotten heart of yours clean, you hypocrite!
Begone! Begone and die!
Don't get ahead of yourself, kid!
This is...
GENESIS!
A battle between the old and the new?
You're not making any sense!
Just put down the hose!
I can't do that.
Leave it to me, Dekomori.
I'll lend you my power.
Master!
Evil Wein Shoot!
The power...
I feel the power!
I'm one with the hose!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Faculty Room
Three hours,
and you just played around in the pool instead of cleaning it?
No, we did try...
The P.E. teacher was really mad
because the pool wasn't any cleaner.
But we took on the cleaning mission.
Opinion of our society must have increased.
Well, it looks like it's the other way.
When your math teacher heard about it,
he said that just passing wasn't good enough.
You need to get at least the class average.
The class average...
Thank you very much.
Yuuta.
What?
Wh-What should I do?
Huh?
Where's Onii-chan?
He's with Rikka-chan.
What? Are you curious?
Wanna go spy?
Why? I'm not curious at all.
Why not?
It's a boy and girl in puberty.
Don't you think, "She's gonna take my Onii-chan away from me!" at all?
Not really.
Dad'll get really mad if you keep that up.
I called him in Jakarta a while ago, and he said,
"Go spy on 'em! Go spy on 'em!"
What's wrong with my parents?
I'll ask again.
You're serious about studying, right?
Of course.
Just warning you.
Our school does pretty well on the national exams,
so you'll need to grit your teeth if you want to get average.
I know that.
Okay, then I'll help you.
We'll start from an easy question.
What is the probability of rolling a 3 with two dice?
Can you do it?
With ease.
Man, your room's still a mess.
Why don't you clean it up a—
I don't get it.
I thought I'd get it if I knew what a
die-thrower thought, so I drew one.
But it's beyond my comprehension.
I don't know what he's thinking.
In other words, that's the limit of your abilities.
No.
I still haven't shown my true powers.
You just wanted to say that.
Guess there's no choice.
I'll ask a question from further back.
A-Are we going through everything from that far back?
You need to start from what you do know in math.
Who's there?!
No one's there.
No, there was!
Yuuta, look out!
I'm not falling for it.
By the way, Yuuta, the magic power in the number 8—
I'm not falling for that either.
You just sucked your teeth at me!
Sit!
You said you were serious about studying, right?
I am.
You said you were really going to study and asked me to help, right?
I did.
But...
I just can't do math!
I don't know what they're thinking!
What's the point of knowing the probability of rolling something in dice in the first place?!
Don't make a valid argument!
I don't get it!
She's completely out of character.
Then for now...
...a break!
Look...
I'll do it right after we take one!
I'll give you some tea too!
Fine.
Your sister still isn't home?
No.
What do you want to drink, Yuuta?
Yuuta?
Oh, anything.
Lizardtail tea, great morinda juice, or charga tea?
What kind of choices are those?
Stains are tougher if you don't soak them.
I'm using your detergent.
Why are you washing them?
Why?
Well, they're dirty,
and I don't really have much else to do.
What's with that stance?
Thanks.
What, too embarrased to just thank me?
Stop it!
What's that?!
From the Priestess.
Tooka-san?
Did something happen?
Detected an anomalous magic signature within the Magic Administration Bureau.
Don't lie.
She'll be home late.
It's normal.
She's always home late?
Almost every weekday.
Oh!
I don't have your electro-protocol code!
You mean my e-mail address?
You can call it that too.
Hurry! Infrared data communication!
You mean the infrared port?
You can call it that too.
Here you go.
Yuuta, your code is so cool!
Cool?
It's just a normal—
E-mail Address
Crap!
I left my middle school address on here!
Divine Exseed Freya Magna!
Quit it!
Don't say it out loud!
I'm changing it right now. Hold on.
No.
Mine is more normal.
Address Book
Takanashi Rikka
I'm changing mine.
Oh, I know, Yuuta!
You choose my code!
I know you'll come up with a good one!
No, I think yours is just fine.
Then I'll use your code.
No, you can't!
And are you sure about just changing it like that?
Why not?
I mean, don't you need to tell all your friends from middle school and your family if you change it?
No problem.
I only need to tell the Priestess and Dekomori.
Really?
In this universe, they are the only beings that acknowledge my presence.
But if you tell me, I'll tell you, Nibutani, and Kumin, too.
Come here.
But the lizardtail tea...
I'm teaching you everything before that final comes around.
So you'd better give it everything you've got.
Yuuta...
It took a lot to make the group.
If you can get above average on the final...
I'll think up a protocol code you might like.
You're back late.
Wh-Why are you here?!
When I got home, you two were completely focused on studying.
I thought I'd get in the way, so I came here.
Here. I signed it.
Looks like our relationship is over.
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
Yumeha and Tooka
are now divorced.
Yumeha
Tooka
I'm raising those kids by myself.
Don't forget to let me see them once a month.
What the heck are you doing?!
Yumeha, you too!
I just thought playing house normally wasn't very realistic.
You're being too realistic!
Got a problem with that?
Not at all...
Now then, guess I'll go home.
How's she doing?
She fell asleep on her desk, so I put her to bed.
I see.
Wish I were you.
For the next week...
If you can solve this one, I'll give you some gum you might like.
My mana charge is rising!
I kept the carrot in front of Rikka and taught her math.
And now it's time for finals.
Language
Arts
Math I
Social
Studies
Now then, we'll start the math final.
Don't look until the bell rings!
I can see it.
I can see it!
Ready...
Begin!
I can...
Reality, be rent.
Synapse, break.
Banishment, this world!
There!
I can see it!
I can see it too!
The light I've been searching for!
The answer!
The answer! I...
...can't see it.
And a few days later...
Crap.
I didn't study enough.
Guess that's that.
You guys didn't do too well.
The average was 50.
Better study harder.
What power!
Walk normally for a change.
Oh, right! I almost forgot!
Yuuta, my protocol code!
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm kidding! I thought one up for you!
I'm only doing it today, okay?
Wielder of the Tyrant's Eye!
In honor of your efforts and achievement,
I, the Dark Flame Master, have gathered the powers of darkness to create a fitting code for you!
May you carve it into your soul!
Protocol code...
Inscribe!
Carve it into your soul!
Togashi Yuuta
Received Message
"Black raison d'être."
It means "black reason for existence."
The code fits you, does it not?
It's so cool...
It's so cool, Yuuta!
Naturally.
How long am I going to keep this up?
Hey!
Wait a—
Thanks.
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
See you next week!
Hrngh