No—
Darn.
It's been too long since I've played this. I can't keep up.
I'm just getting in their way.
Hey, I can't see.
Yuuta!
Help me!
C'mon...
I have a request for you ASAP.
That's not how you use "ASAP."
I've made a uniform for our society.
A uniform?
You will be wearing this during our operations.
Dark
Flame
It's read as "Dark Flame."
I will wear this.
Evil
Eye
It's read as "Evil Eye."
Evil
Eye
We'll wear these starting tomorrow.
No thanks.
As I've said before, I'm done with all that.
Is this your character?
Y-Yeah.
Your name is Setsuna?
Who cares what my in-game name is?!
Hear that?
The priestess is back.
7 AM tomorrow at rendezvous point B.
Dark
Flame
So it's happening.
Let's look for sparkling daydream
shibaraku mitsume atte kara
That moment there, when we were looking eye-to-eye,
sorasu made ni nani wo kangaeteta no
Before you looked away, what was going through your head?
ki ni naru
I want to know
kuchibiru togaraseta atashi wo mite
You'll look this way
and see me pouting with a frown ❤
doushita no tte kiite kuru no
I'm just waiting for you
to ask me what's wrong
matte miru no
That's all I really want ❤
gomakashita ato no hitorigoto wa
The things I mumbled to myself
after I said that nothing was
hazukashii kara
were just too embarrassing ❤
kikanaide kureru
So don't ask what they were
ato ni hikenai hodo
A love so strong you can't escape it
hikareau koi
Drawing two together
mou hajimatteta
That's what's started for us now ❤
yume nara takusan mita
I've seen you in plenty of my dreams,
sameta mama demo mada aitai
But I still want to see you when I'm awake
kimi ga sou saseta
You made me feel this way
koi wa yokubari da ne
When you're in love, you want to have it all
tobihanesou na kokoro no
Let's go wherever our hearts want to go ❤
yuku mama ni yukou yo
They beat so fast that they could explode
risou mo mousou mo genjitsu mo
All of my dreams and ideals and realities
subete kimi wo jiku ni mawaru
All of them for a whole new world
atarashii sekai he
Where everything revolves around you
You know it's July, right?
The Atonement... of the Innocent
I understand since I'm the only one who's familiar with character you're supposed to be,
but couldn't you try talking to other people?
Apart from you, I already talk to Dekomori, Kumin, and Nibutani.
Okay... any others?
In our class, you only talk to me, Nibutani, and Isshiki.
We're the same.
We're not the same.
Besides, I don't like being around people.
This is pointless.
Maybe I'll just leave her—
In this universe, they are the only beings that acknowledge my presence.
Togashi-kun, your drawing's nice!
Takanashi-san looks so cute here!
Y-You think?
Let me see!
Oh wow!
Do you draw comics and stuff?
No, not really...
I did draw a lot of stuff back when I had eighth-grade syndrome...
I'm done.
It's cool.
Really? Let me see!
Is this Togashi-kun?
In battle.
In battle?
Cornered in desperation mode, releasing the Dark Flame with all his might!
Stop that!
Dark Flame?
Only to be spoken in whispers,
the Dark Flame is Yuuta's strongest offensive spell.
Because of it, Yuuta is—
What on Earth are they doing—
Ow...
Never let your guard down, Fake Mori Summer!
Don't call me that!
Are you all right, Nibutani-san?
Y-Yeah.
Do you know her?
N-No.
So you have underclassmen admirers too?
What is she doing?
Yuuta.
Wh-What?
Are you free after class?
What?!
You got a love letter?!
What should I do?
Wait, haven't you always wanted one?
What's the big deal?
Y-Yeah, but I never thought I'd actually get one!
Quit trying to be cute!
I'm telling you, it's gotta be the guitar!
Music is all I've got going for me, right?
I still can't play anything, though!
What should I do?!
Could you at least get off of me?
You're creeping everyone out.
Minor, right?
Chicks dig minor chords, right?
Who told you that?!
Calm down already!
I can't!
Let's try the logical approach.
First, is it really a love letter?
Of course it is!
Second, are you sure it's not a boy playing a trick on you?
Just look at this girly handwriting!
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
after school this Saturday
I'll be waiting for you
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
Dear Isshiki-kun,
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
under the ginkgo tree.
I'll be waiting for you
after school this Saturday
Dear Isshiki-kun,
"I'll be waiting for you after school this Saturday under the ginkgo tree."
See?
Third, are you sure it's not a boy and a girl teaming up on you?
Why are you so paranoid?
I've been through a lot.
Who do you think it's from?
It says it's from a classmate,
but her name isn't on it.
Do you have any suspicions?
Let me see...
Hirakata, Nabatame, Tsumuji...
Nope. No way.
But if I had to guess...
Go ahead.
Nibutani.
I mean, she smiles at me
whenever we look at each other.
As for her personality,
she's really serious and diligent.
So it makes sense that she'd be attracted to a wild musician like me.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
How can you be so sure?!
There's no way!
I can tell you that much!
How?!
W-Wait, don't tell me you and Nibutani are...
That ain't happening either.
True.
You and Nibutani just don't mix.
You're one to talk.
Anyway, I wanna know who gave me this letter.
It's not like I can go around school asking every girl.
You've gotta help me!
Can't you just wait?
Are you crazy?!
You think I could ad-lib a conversation with a girl I've never met before?!
I'll say something stupid and she'll run away!
Right?
Stop being so confident in your lack of confidence!
Oriental Magick Napping Society in Summer
It's enveloping me...
Purgatory
Dark Dream
I can feel the powers of darkness here!
Purgatory
Dark Dream
It feels great to sleep in!
There's no way these three would know.
Be sure to announce your entry
whenever you're here with these on.
Wielder of the Tyrant's Eye,
society member zero, Takanashi Rikka!
Servant of the Tyrant's Eye,
wielder of the Mjollnir Hammer,
society member zero, Dekomori Sanae!
Night Siesta of the Melody,
society member zero, Tsuyuri Kumin!
Perfect.
Death.
What's with the numbering?
Zero is the coolest number of them all.
There's no way I'm anything but zero.
I have no idea, but I guess it's cool!
And...
Now we will decide who the true zero is!
Bring it on!
W-We can do this!
I get it!
Stop encouraging her, Senpai.
But look, you're wearing it under your shirt.
N-No, I just didn't have anything else to wear...
Oh, Yuuta, you are wearing it.
Don't look!
You friggin' kid!
You're finally here!
Maybe this is the only way to get it into your head.
That's...
white water!
I made it nice and warm, so the taste and scent will overwhelm your senses.
Are you a demon?!
No, wait, I'm supposed to be dark here, so...
Are you an angel?!
Who cares?!
Now drink!
Drink it!
Stop! Stop it!
Hang in there, Deko-chan!
Drink! Drink! Drink!
Deko-chan!
Hey, Nibutani...
What?!
I'm busy! Shut up!
Uh... look behind you.
What?! Just shut up!
Keep bothering me, and I'll do the same—
H-Hey.
Oh my, Isshiki-kun.
What are you doing here?
N-Nothing much, I just wanted to talk with Yuuta.
O-Oh, I see.
You surprised me—
Nice try. You nearly had me.
But your white water has been drained away!
Now then, Fake Mori Summer!
I'll DS Drive you straight to the horizon of infinite energy!
Mori Summer?
Wh-Who's that?
She's a funny kid, right?
From the Mabinogion, the Rainbow Codex, 3:1.
When the whispers of the faeries and the dreams of the light and water reach our hearts,
the white world will open to us.
I know, for I have watched this world for 400 years.
What the world needs most...
is love!
Stop! I don't want to hear it!
What?!
You keep proving yourself a fake.
You've lost your mind after hearing the words of the true Mori Summer.
Mori Summer-chan, hang in—
Don't call me that!
N-Nibutani, you—
If you ever tell anyone in class about this...
I'll curse you to death.
The wind...
...is coming.
Wh-What do you think?
Is someone playing me for a fool?
No, I think a girl wrote this.
Really?!
Can you tell who wrote it?
Not just by looking at this.
How likely is love at first sight?!
Do you believe in it?
Nope.
Don't answer for me!
So basically, how well this goes is up to you.
Oh, and...
I hope you've forgotten what you saw today.
I-I have...
Oh, thank you!
Bye-bye!
So, what're you gonna do?
Well, guess I'll do what I can.
I'll do mental simulations of every girl in the class before Saturday rolls around.
That way, I'll be ready for anything!
Seriously?
Don't worry.
I've got all the intel I need on the girls thanks to the poll we had on the cutest girl.
If I start now, I'll make it in time.
Isshiki...
Anyway, I gotta get going.
I'm catching this train! See ya!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Yuuta.
Your hand.
My hand?
Don't move.
What was that about?!
I was reading the wind.
Th-The wind?
Look..
The wind is loud today.
That was just the sound of the train!
So if what's written in this notebook Inomata-san picked up is true,
then the boys in this class decided to rank us girls by looks.
Crap.
This is bad.
Did I leave it on the bench by the station yesterday?
I think so.
But they don't know whose notebook it is yet.
But...
I'd like to ask the boys to explain themselves.
Mera-kun.
Y-Yes?!
Mera-kun, were you involved in making this ranking?
No, um...
I wa—
"I wa—"?
I do—
"I do—"?
I don't recall!
How suspicious.
Crap.
Crap...
It's only a matter of time before they figure out I started it.
If that happens, my high school romance will end before it even started!
Think, damn it! Think!
Um... Why don't we ask Togashi-kun?
Huh?!
Yeah, he's a class rep and all.
Togashi-kun, what about you?
W-Well, I...
Did you know about this?
Um...
No...
I...
Well...
U-Um...
I did it.
I made that.
I made the ranking!
No way!
Seriously?
What a creep!
Isshiki?
Isshiki-kun, did you really?
Yes.
But don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't get a vote from the class or anything.
I made it all on my own!
I'm sorry!
I was just having a bit of fun!
None of the other boys were involved!
I did it all!
I'm the one!
I'm the only one at fault here!
Why are they clapping?
Yeah, why?
So you're saying that you're solely responsible for all of this.
Yes.
And I hurt the girls' feelings because of it.
Because it's my fault,
I'll shave my head in atonement!
Isshiki...
I have to do at least that much!
As a man!
But you'll be like a monk!
That's right.
You don't need to go that far.
No.
I must take responsibility as a man.
You're a real man...
Wh-What'd you think?
Didn't I look cool, sacrificing myself for the greater good?
Yeah, sure.
And stepping forward for my own sins and covering for others? I'm a real man.
But what're you going to do about your hair?
Oh, you mean shaving it?
No way.
I mean, I said it just to show that I had the willingness to do it.
But you said it was your responsibility...
Well, sure, but they wouldn't think I'd actually—
They do.
N-Nibutani, when'd you get here?!
Just warning you.
The girls don't believe you.
No one's going to believe a bunch of words.
You need to take responsibility for your actions.
I-I do?
Of course.
You said you would.
No way...
No way!
I'll ask one last time.
Are you sure about this?
No! I don't want it!
I finally grew out my hair after spending my years in middle school with a buzzcut!
Of course I don't wanna cut it!
So go apologize tomorrow and ask
for something other than cutting your hair!
But if I do that, I'd just be a coward!
If I don't take responsibility like Nibutani says, all the girls in class will think I'm a coward,
including whoever wrote me that love letter.
No, even worse.
If I don't do it, the guys will be under fire again!
But...
I'm the one who started the whole thing.
Taking responsibility for their actions...
...is what men do!
What's going on here?
Is this Japanese ritual suicide?
No!
It's close enough!
Just cut it off already!
You three!
You're in the way! Get out!
This is our society's base of operations.
It belongs to—
We'll be done soon enough!
Wait right there!
M-My servant!
Th-This door...
Is it sealed?!
Hey, Yuuta.
Thanks for everything.
I'm glad I talked to you before the entrance ceremony.
My dad lost his hair when he was 35.
If it's genetic, I've only got 20 years to play with my hair.
I spent the last three with a buzzcut,
and now I need to cut it off again.
Makes you laugh, doesn't it?
Isshiki...
I... I...
What're you crying for, Yuuta?
C'mon.
Let's get it over with!
With your own hands!
Isshiki!
Huh? What's everyone doing here?
We were sealed out.
It's been broken!
You done?
My servant!
Yeah, we're done.
But Isshiki's really shaken up right now.
Could you all please cheer him up a bit?
Sure.
Understood. I'll give him some mana.
I don't know what's going on, but sure.
Death!
Before that, let me ask for one thing.
Please...
Don't laugh.
Were you listening to me at all?!
What was that for?!
Isshiki.
Y-Yeah.
In honor of your courage,
let me give you some strength.
Come here.
Powers of darkness gathered here,
I command you to bless this mortal!
You two!
Look at him!
It's too funny!
Don't laugh! Don't you have a heart?!
And so, the cutest girl ranking incident drew to a close.
As for Isshiki, who still had the slightest hope that a girl would come to the ginkgo tree...
On that Saturday...
Isshiki-kun!
Isshiki found himself loved by all the guys in the class.
Hey!
So the girl who wrote the love letter never showed up?
Nibutani, are you sure you don't know who wrote it?
It wouldn't matter if you knew now, would it?
I guess.
But you shaved your head to cover for the rest of the boys.
There might be a girl or two
who'd be impressed by that.
Really?!
Don't be stupid.
Of course there aren't.
Don't screw with me!
Sorry. I just couldn't help myself!
Isshiki-kun, can I touch it?
S-Sure.
H-Hey...
Summer vacation is right around the corner.
What are you going to do, Yuuta?
Dad said he won't be able to
come back to Japan this year,
so he wants us to go see him in Jakarta.
I'll think about it.
Yuuta.
I have a favor to ask you.
Come with Rikka and me for summer vacation.
We need you.
Summer is coming.
To Be Continued
INSIDE IDENTITY
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
kanchigai ga haji da toka
"Making mistakes is a sin," they say
sunaosa ga itai toka
"Being honest hurts," or so they say
dare ga nan to iou to
Someone once said something, they say
tadashisa nante wakannai ze
But you can't say that it's all true, you know
futsuu ni nagareteiku nichijou ni
Everyone's always trying so hard to
muri shite najimaseta
Blend in with everything "normal"
shizunjimatta koseitachi wo
Doing away with their own personalities,
kande nonde haite warau
Chewing them up, spitting them out, and laughing
konna boku wo wakatte hoshii
"I want you to try to understand me,"
iitai kedo ienakutte
I want to tell you, but I can't say it
nande dare mo wakatte kunnai no to
"Why doesn't anyone even try to understand me?"
omou no wa zeitaku nano kana nano kanaa
Is it too much for me to ask? Is it, now? Is it, now?
The sun's getting full of emotion
Raising the temperature so much, who knows when I might snap?
I can't do anything, I need to scream
Trying everything I can to find my
Identity
I
den
ti
ty
INSIDE MY FEELING
INSIDE MY JUSTICE
jama shinai de
Don't try to stop me
ibasho wa doko
Where do I belong?
See you next week!
You could call me
Peter the Painter. Hehe...
What a joke. Hehe...
You could call me
Peter the Painter. Hehe...
What a joke. Hehe...
You could call me
Peter the Painter. Hehe...
What a joke. Hehe...
You could call me
Peter the Painter. Hehe...
What a joke. Hehe...
So cool...