He quit?!
He quit the kendo club?
Yes.
To be honest, I was struck speechless when he told me.
Did you ask why?
He wouldn't tell me.
He simply said he had other things to do.
Takkun...
Let's begin.
Black Lotus...
Why?
Did you hear me?
I said let's begin.
Wait! I-
You've been stopped by a
Burst Linker and challenged to a duel.
You must respond to such challenges with all your might.
That's the rule of this world.
If you won't make your move...
...then I will!
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
I'm currently exploring two possibilities.
You're either extremely crafty and bumped into me on purpose to expose my identity,
or you're just very clumsy.
It's definitely the latter case...
To begin with, it's strange how Silver Crow
would suddenly be in a near-death condition
when he's had a 70% win rate in the past two weeks.
You know about me?!
Don't speak out loud.
I'm sorry.
You're just about the only one in the
Accelerated World who's unaware of your own fame.
The one and only Aviating Avatar, and a genius...
I dunno...
...or so I had thought.
You sometimes let your emotions
take over and can be quite cunning,
but you're actually pretty slow-witted in real life.
Well, I suppose I am pretty slow-witted.
I really am.
I leveled up even though I only had 308 points.
If that's why you're in a near-death condition...
It all clicks. You really are clumsy.
I know, right?
I'm glad you believe me...
I guess?
This didn't turn out the way I had planned, but let me introduce myself again.
I'm Aqua Current.
I'll help you recover up to 50 points.
Just call me Karen.
O-Okay.
Thank you for helping me.
Well, let's register for and join a tag match.
Accelerate as soon as you've made your global connection.
O-Okay.
If we manage to reach our targeted number of points in the Chiyoda Area, then that's where we'll finish.
Otherwise, we'll move to Akihabara and continue.
Any questions?
Um...
Not really.
Should I apologize to her for touching her breasts?
I couldn't really feel anything, though, so maybe I didn't touch them...
I can hear you.
Burst Link.
You touched them all right.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You should learn to control your
own thoughts when you're cabling.
I can hear everything.
I'm sorry.
Who should we challenge?
W-Wait!
Were you about to select Level 3 and 4 opponents?
You're Level 2, and I'm Level 1,
so we should pick opponents
whose levels add up to 6 or higher.
If the total level difference is at least three,
you won't be stripped of all your points even if we lose.
I see the logic in that, but...
Is that why you stay at Level 1 and don't level up?
That's just one of the reasons.
I'll tell you about the other reason when the time comes.
Maybe, or maybe not.
What's that supposed to mean?
Perfect.
Sand Duct and Nickel Doll.
They're Level 3 and 4, but they'll fight us head-on since they have plenty of reserve points.
Oh...
If you stay calm and fight to the best
of your ability, you probably won't lose.
She took so many factors into
consideration in picking our opponents...
She really knows everything about me.
I'll do my best!
It's good to see you're motivated,
but fight like you always do.
You can't afford to lose this match,
but the most important thing isn't winning. It's...
...to enjoy the game.
That's what my parent told me.
She said I should enjoy all my matches.
I see.
Okay, let's get started.
The Corrosive Woods stage, huh?
Water...
Just like her name implies.
I see them.
Let's get down.
Okay!
Is this a poisonous swamp?
This is a troublesome stage.
Sorry we kept you waiting!
What's the matter?
You don't need to hold back.
I've regained enough points to survive a loss from you.
It's your chance to gain lots of points.
Or is that all you've got?
I heard about your situation from a Leonids messenger.
You aren't participating in the kendo tournament.
Why?
It's my way of settling things.
Settling things?
I committed a crime.
I can't stay here in this state.
As I thought.
You want to throw away
everything you've gained and earned,
and atone for your sins by losing everything.
After you've helped Haruyuki-kun become
a Burst Linker that can hold his own ground,
do you intend to uninstall Brain Burst on your own?
That's the only...
...the only way for me to...
What will that accomplish?
What will happen to Haruyuki-kun?
What about Kurashima-kun,
who's trying so hard to forgive you?
You're about to trample all over their feelings.
What am I supposed to do, then?
What am I supposed to do?!
You're finally taking this seriously.
You've got guts to charge in here at such low levels.
I'm sorry.
I'll handle Sand Duct.
You take Nickel Doll.
She can generate electric currents from her hands.
Don't get caught.
Stop giving my moves away!
Sand Blast!
I'm your opponent.
No!
Take that!
That wasn't nice!
Why would you throw me headfirst
into the muddy swamp, you DV bastard?!
What?!
Shouldn't you be worried?
This is a poisonous swamp.
You'll take a lot of damage.
I'm Level 4, so it's your HP that'll run out firs-
Poison doesn't work on Silver!
I see.
You're on the left end of the Metal Color Chart, after all.
That's right. You're Silver.
What?
You should do a little more research on your own color.
Silver is resistant to antigens...
...but it conducts electricity the best!
Look!
Silver conducts electricity four times better than nickel.
You won't last long!
Fly!
Is that the aviation ability?!
Dive Attack!
Did you win?
No, not yet.
That was a nice move.
It was elegant and powerful.
However, the battle is decided.
You're going to lose.
Splash Stinger!
What am I supposed to do?
What must I give to atone for my sins?!
I'll be blunt.
You aren't uninstalling to atone for your sins.
Brain Burst reminds you of the crimes you committed, and you simply want to escape the guilt of it all.
That's not...
The more you see Haruyuki-kun forgiving you...
The more Kurashima-kun keeps acting like nothing's changed,
the more guilty you feel.
You can't stand the fact that you've been forgiven.
You can't stand being imperfect.
You're wrong.
You're simply too narcissistic.
You're trying to escape from your sins by punishing yourself.
You're wrong!
How am I wrong?
You're wrong.
You're wrong, you're wrong, you're wrong!
Sand Blast!
You two have no teamwork, the
most important thing in tag matches.
Your attacks don't compliment each other.
No matter how strong you are individually,
it won't get you anywhere in a tag match.
You're right.
That's why...
The battle hasn't been decided yet.
So far, I've fought a lot of tag matches with my best friend.
That's why I know.
It's vital to trust your partner in tag matches.
And I trust Karen-san!
You think you're so cool, don't you?!
Sandy!
Let's blow them away with our ultra-gorgeous special move and end this match!
All right!
They're using their combo attack.
Don't let your guard down.
Okay.
What?!
We can't let them hit us both.
I'll watch and help you out if necessary.
What?!
Did we just agree that trust is vital in tag matches?!
Turbo...
...Molecular!
He's blowing wind with his right arm and sucking it back in with his left!
What could this mean?
I-Is this...
The turbines in his arms are blowing away
the molecules in the air, creating a vacuum.
The wind itself isn't very damaging.
It'll only pull you in close enough for melee combat.
Melee combat?
Indeed, if I can connect a kick when I get close...
All right!
Idiot!
Anode Cathode!
How come?!
I'm not touching her, and there's no water!
How do you like our ultra-gorgeous combo attack?
It can't compare to what the Purple Lady can do, but isn't it pretty effective?
Electric glow discharge.
When air pressure approaches near-vacuum levels, ionization occurs at the electrodes,
and a current flows through the air.
Your client will be burned to ashes if you just stand there.
Though, with your body, it's not like you can do anything.
Haruyuki-kun must've told you what he wants you to do.
Why won't you listen?
That's because...
Shouldn't listening to his wish
be the first thing you should do?
Haruyuki-kun told me that...
...you're his best friend!
Shouldn't you just give up?
Your HP is far too low for any kind of a comeback.
No!
I can't lose!
My best friend Taku and I will have a fresh start!
That's why I have to...!
It's over.
Nicky.
Impossible!
Water should conduct electricity!
My water contains no impurities.
Pure water, in other words.
Water with no impurities is almost a perfect insulator.
Damn you!
The important thing in tag matches...
...is teamwork.
Why do you think Legions exist in the Accelerated World?
It's because competing with and supporting our friends opens up many possibilities.
Since you've always fought alone, you still don't know of the joys and wonders of fighting as a team.
Venture into its infinite potential.
That's how you will atone for your sins.
You now have 54 points.
My work is done.
Thank you so much.
It was my pleasure.
Thanks to your hard work, I've learned about many hidden tricks that Burst Linkers use.
Um, do you always hang around here?
Why do you ask?
Well, I was hoping we could meet again sometime.
We won't meet again.
I chose this place because few Burst Linkers come here.
It makes it easier to obtain the deferred payment.
Deferred payment?
You never mentioned...
I will now strip you of all your points.
I can initiate consecutive cable duels before you unplug the cable.
We'll keep fighting until all your points are gone.
Is that the deferred payment?!
There's no point in being a bouncer otherwise.
Now, get ready.
Show me everything you've got.
Every last drop of it.
You give up already?
Didn't I tell you earlier?
I believed in you.
Ever since we first met, I knew you were a good person.
I fought a serious match against my best friend just a while ago.
I let my anger and sadness take over and fought him with hatred.
But I believed in him at the end.
I decided then.
I decided that I'd never change
my mind once I believe in someone.
That I'd always continue to believe.
Is that why you won't fight?
I don't want to betray someone I believe in.
I was just lying.
I decided to scare you a bit since you're too defenseless.
It wasn't very effective, though.
No, it was.
You really scared me!
A long time ago, I had friends too.
I also had a master I cared about.
But something happened, and we were all torn apart.
I see.
That's why you should cherish your friend.
You and I aren't supposed to meet just yet.
You have a long journey with your master ahead of you.
Elements shouldn't intervene in that.
That's why I'll be taking any memories of me that you have.
My memories?
Memory Leak.
Huh?
What was I doing?
Whose is this?
Chiyuri-chan came over earlier to drop off your stuff.
Chii-chan...
She left right after leaving them there.
Mom.
There's something you should know.
Morning!
G-Good morning.
Why are you still acting so worried?
What's done is done!
Or do you want to treat me to more ice cream?
Chiyu...
She's right, Haru.
Good morning.
Is that uniform...
Our school's?
What?!
Thank you.
Glasses in this day and age?
You don't need them with the
Neuro Linker's vision adjustment.
I want to see things with my own eyes from now on.
I want to see the real Chii-chan, Haru, and myself.
They look good on you.
Excuse me.
How...
How did you know so much about me?
I don't.
It's just that I've also committed irreversible crimes in the past, as you already know.
That's all there is to it.
I'll be in your care, my master.
Hey, Taku!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next Stage: Temptation.
The temptation from a girl
appearing out of the blue.
What does she want from Haruyuki?