I'll give you wings.
My Enhanced Armament, Gale Thruster.
I'm sure you'll be able to use those wings to reach greater heights than I could.
My foolishness caused me to lose such a bond in the past.
I don't want you to make the same mistake.
I want you to fight for things that need to be protected.
Things that need to be protected...
I will!
Thank you so much!
I'll fly again for sure using my own power.
When the time comes, I'll return these to you...
Your wings!
Okay.
Good luck, Crow-san.
Sorry, Chiyu, Taku...
But even if I don't get my wings back,
I'll still defeat Dusk Taker.
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
I was always wide awake
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nita wa no naka de
We are all in similar nets
Found You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I found the wind that day with trembling passion
And All Of My Past subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
And all of my past is a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou furuwasete itai kara
To send my pulse racing
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If I Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
Though, what should I do?
I don't know why his name
doesn't appear on the matching list...
A dive call?
From who?
D-Direct Link!
What's this?
A video stream?
Hey, it's been a while.
Or not.
It's been three days, Haruyuki-kun.
S-Senpai!
O-Oh, this is Henoko Beach.
A fighter plane you would've liked just flew past here.
Hey, Princess!
How much longer are you gonna keep that on?
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
Now who was it that made me spend
all morning with her picking out a swimsuit?
See you, Arita-kun. Enjoy!
W-Well, uh... you know...
This is Okinawa, after all.
I-Indeed! You're in Okinawa and all!
I-It looks wonderful on you!
Thank you.
Oh, this?
You can't normally see it very well, but it shows up a little when it's this sunny.
There's no need to feel bad about it.
To me, it's my one and only medal of honor.
It's the first wound and scar I've gotten from
protecting someone else, rather than simply fighting.
This scar keeps me going.
If I told Senpai about Noumi, she'd probably get angry
at first but then come back from Okinawa straight away.
That's why I shouldn't tell her.
I can't!
I...
I'll become really strong.
I'm still being protected by you right now,
but I'll definitely become strong enough to support you one day!
I said this before, but take your time.
It'd be boring if I didn't have the fun of protecting you.
Oh, right.
I received a weird message from Takumu-kun.
It's about the Noumi freshman guy
we suspect of being a Burst Linker.
He asked me if I could give him the
freshman's entrance exam scores by subject.
Huh?
Wh-What did you do?
I retrieved them from the student council's database and replied to him with the info.
Did something happen?
N-No, nothing happened.
I see.
Oh, I have to go.
We'll hang up here.
See you.
Porky's last, as usual!
Porky'd be faster if he rolled down the track instead!
Taku.
Burst Link?!
Why now?!
Taku!
Why would you duel with me now?
I-I'm watching a registered duel?
Dear me.
I was expecting you to be a more cautious person.
Mayuzumi-senpai.
I figured you'd be accelerating around now, Noumi.
Oh?
The freshmen are having their tests right now.
They're also testing social studies at Period 5,
which you got full marks for in your entrance exams.
You'd most likely use your power right before the exam ends,
so I simply narrowed things down by
accelerating repeatedly, and here we are.
Well? Are you here to tell me off for it?
No.
I've also used acceleration powers to cheat many times before.
But getting full marks is going too far.
It simply draws attention without conferring any real benefits.
I guess that's where our values differ.
I take whatever I can get.
Contesting for things is the basic rule of this world, Senpai.
That's why I love taking things.
But I hate having things taken from me even more.
I'll have you compensate, Mayuzumi-senpai...
...for the precious 1.8 seconds you're trying to take from me.
You'll pay with your Burst Points.
You're the one who'll be paying back.
You'll return the ability, the precious wings, that you took from my best friend!
Taku, how did you know?
I heard about your duel with Ash Roller last night.
Sorry I didn't realize anything, Haru.
It's my turn to fight now!
Taku...
Taku, beat him!
Do it to show him how strong you are!
I'll beat him.
I gotta get you your wings back as well, Haru!
Could you please stop that?
All this unconditional friendship, hypocrisy, and deceit makes me want to puke.
I've had enough.
I'll just take the points and leave.
I still have around five questions left on my test and all.
Careful, Taku!
His tentacles grow back if you cut them off!
Also, the cutter on his right hand is really sharp!
Taku...
Noumi, you lose.
Huh? Why would that happen?
You can't break the walls in this
Purgatory stage with your powers.
The exit is behind me.
A speed build like yours has no chance of winning.
So unless you want me to intrude every time you have a test, return those stolen wings to Silver Crow.
If you do, I'll no longer interfere, at the very least.
Indeed, it'd be a pain to get past you.
Retract all equipment.
It's not like I'm surrendering.
I'm just using my trump card since I have no other option.
Your trump card?
I don't like it when things get serious.
I didn't even want to use my special move, you know.
It's just too bad, I guess.
Take. Get. Grasp. Erase.
Steal. Steal. Steal. Steal.
What's that?
His special move... or is it?
Noumi's special move gauge isn't going down.
Then that must be...
The overwriting of phenomena.
The will of the mind can overwrite phenomena.
Steal. Steal. Steal. Steal.
Don't tell me...
Taku, don't worry about me!
Defeat him right now!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
So what were you saying just then, Mayuzumi-senpai?
Something about me being unable to break the walls in this stage?
I honestly didn't want to show you this, you know.
But you probably don't understand it even after seeing it.
The logic of this technique is known only to the six... I mean, seven kings and their closest associates...
...and to us .
It really is the Incarnate System!
You're a smart guy though.
After experiencing the difference in
our strengths, I'm sure you now know...
...that you'll be serving me as my dog
for the rest of your time at this school.
Neither of you have a choice!
How?
How does Noumi know about the Incarnate System?
There's no way you can even realize it exists on your own...
Five hundred seconds left, huh?
You did better than I'd thought, Mayuzumi-senpai.
You're better at this than you are at kendo.
Well, it's time for you to compensate me for the
1.3 seconds of real world time you took from me.
With your Burst Points, pain, and humiliation.
Wait, Noumi!
Huh?
Wait.
Taku must've used up tons of points in order to fight you!
Take the points from me instead!
Please, Noumi!
I'm begging you!
How terrible!
You're terrible in so many ways, Arita-senpai.
Even I think that's something you
should never do on the battlefield.
I don't mind.
I'll pay up next week's portion as well.
Please!
Fine, fine.
You remind me of the woodlice I used to torment in the garden when I was a kid.
But I guess that's why you were able to get that aviating ability.
What are you waiting for, Mayuzumi-senpai?
Don't tell me you can't even move a finger.
Press it.
Press it, Taku!
I haven't given up yet!
I can fight him if we switch to Battle Royal mode.
I want to fight him!
So please push the button, Taku!
Thanks, Taku.
Now I can finally...
...fight Noumi!
This technique...
Damned dog, when did you learn this trick?!
The image...
The image!
The speed...
The speed of light!
That's right.
You're fast.
Faster than everyone else.
Penetrate it!
Wow, I didn't expect an incarnation attack.
You must've been training real hard for the whole of last night.
Well? Are you out of energy already?
Of course not.
I didn't spend all of last night sleeping either!
These wings really are quite something.
How can you still be Level 4 despite
having such an overwhelming advantage?
Don't worry, though.
I'll show you just how much better I can use this power, Senpai.
Like so.
Equipment: Pyro Dealer.
The aviating ability and long-distance
flame power really do go well together.
My special move gauge gets recharged from the field-destruction bonus too.
I could go on forever.
Just to be clear, I'm invincible.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Huh?
There's one requirement you haven't fulfilled to truly call yourself invincible.
Oh? Like what?
It's...
...the fact that you're not the only one who can fly!
Sky Raker, I'll use them now.
Your wings!
Equip! Gale Thruster!
A heart that longs for the sky.
That's the Gale Thruster's source of power.
Now, go.
You should be able to fly again, Crow-san.
Wha-
I see.
So you were hiding that card up your sleeve.
You have to tell me, Senpai.
How did you get a hold of that?
Did you use points to buy it, or-
You wouldn't understand even if I told you.
What did you say?
The wishes of the one who manifested these sky-blue wings, and her thoughts as she entrusted them to me...
You could never understand them.
You think of the Accelerated World as just a means to an end!
You have no right to call yourself a Burst Linker!
A Burst Linker?
When did I ever call myself that?
What?
It's simply what the first generation started calling themselves.
We would never use it.
We?
Well, it's time to settle this.
Let's see which of us has the stronger
will of the mind, or should I say, desire!
The will of the mind isn't desire!
It's wishes!
I'm not done yet!
You're going to crash both of us into the ground?
If I activated my defenses,
it'll end with you destroying yourself.
I know.
Taku, now!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Haru.
Taku, I had faith.
I knew you were taking damage on purpose so you could charge up your special move gauge.
I had faith that you'd believe in me too.
Noumi.
My incarnation attack or the Gale Thruster wasn't the reason why you lost.
It's because we aren't alone.
It's also the reason why you'll never beat us again.
What was that?
Where'd that come from?
Huh?
Citron...
...Call!
Why?
Why would you?!
Why would you, Chiyu?!
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I couldn't grasp anything as I flapped my wings
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kogareru no mo zenbu
I also long for your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Invitation.
A sudden invitation to fight.
A battle begins under the sun
in the southern islands.