Listen, Chiyu...
Stay out of this, Haru.
Are you trying to say that I enjoy bullying him?
Isn't that what's going on?
Haru doesn't like to stand out or be in the center of attention.
I see.
Even if that were true, you don't
have the right to interfere with us.
But I do.
I've been friends with him the longest in this entire school.
Oh? Friends?
I'm closer to him than you, then.
I confessed to him and am currently waiting for his reply.
We're about to go on a date.
It's over! This is end of the world!
I'll have to transfer to another school tomorrow!
Have a good day, friend .
Wai- What?!
Are you out of your mind?!
Some things just can't be solved through acceleration!
I see you're already thinking about what it takes to be a Burst Linker.
That's great.
Nothing's great about any of this!
I provoked Kurashima-kun because something is bothering me...
Or rather, I wanted to confirm something.
Didn't you already know Chiyuri, though?
Oh, you're close enough to call her by her first name?
I-It's just that we've been friends forever!
I mean, she already has a boyfriend!
She drew my attention for a
completely different reason from you.
What do you mean by that?
It's not easy to explain.
It's directly related to the reason I chose you.
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Let me congratulate you again for your first victory.
I'm sure you'll become Level 2 in no time.
Th-Thank you.
I still can't imagine myself leveling up though.
You do have an unimaginably long journey ahead of you.
Out of 1,000 Burst Linkers, only a very few actually reach Level 4,
and you can assume Level 7 and 8
players to be leaders of large groups.
G-Groups?
They're like the teams you often see in online games.
We call them Legions, though.
The Accelerated World is currently divided into six major Legions.
They are ruled by six Level 9 Burst Linkers:
Blue, Red, Yellow, Green, Purple, and White.
They are the Six Kings of Pure Color.
I've never heard of a game where only six players have reached the max level.
I never said Level 9 is the max level.
What? Are there Level 10 players?
How many?
In the seven years since the release of
Brain Burst 2039 by an unknown developer,
nobody has ever reached Level 10 due to its harsh rules.
Do you have to win a ridiculous number of games?
Like 10,000 times?
You only need to win five times.
However, you must beat another Level 9 Linker, and a single loss will strip you of all your points.
Brain Burst will be forcefully uninstalled.
Do you know why Brain Burst still remains a
secret from rest of the world after seven years?
No.
It's because of its demanding requirements.
Demanding...
The most important requirement for Burst Linkers is to have worn a Neuro Linker for their entire lives.
Since the first generation Neuro Linker entered the market 15 years ago,
there are no adult Burst Linkers.
The oldest ones are 15 years old.
We are all kids, so we try to
keep the privileges to ourselves.
Furthermore, the program leave no traces once uninstalled.
Whatever you say about it will
simply be dismissed as nonsense.
During the summer two years ago, the young kings reached Level 9 nearly simultaneously
and learned of the cruel rule to reach
Level 10 through the system message.
You'd expect them to fight a bloody power struggle...
But they didn't.
The kings chose the status quo.
They called a truce and divided the
Accelerated World for each of them to rule.
It's a farce.
After all, they've hunted countless Linkers to reach Level 9.
So your goal is to challenge those Kings of Pure Color?
No. I've already tried.
There used to be seven Kings of Pure Color.
Despite being rivals, the seven boys and
girls were bound by a sense of comradery.
One night, two years ago, the Black King
betrayed everyone and tried to hunt them...
The Black King?
Yes, that's me.
The Black King, Black Lotus,
disrupted the peace and abandoned everything to suggest the seven of us should fight.
When they rejected the plan...
I beheaded the Red King, who was calling for peace in front of me.
He instantly lost the Brain Burst program.
Purple, his girlfriend, screamed in anguish.
Blue was enraged.
I fought in sheer madness.
However, I wasn't able to defeat anyone else.
Thirty minutes passed and I Linked Out.
I've been on the run for the two years after that.
I'm now known as the biggest
traitor of the Accelerated World,
the greatest public enemy,
and the epitome of cowardice.
Why did you do that?
Because reaching Level 10 is my greatest priority.
The system message also told us that the Burst Linker who reaches Level 10
will get to meet the developer and discover the true meaning behind the Brain Burst program
and its ultimate goal.
I absolutely must know.
Is accelerating to obtain money, grades, and fame the reason why we fight?
Are those the rewards we seek?
Are they all we can get?
There's got to be so much more to this.
Something beyond the limits of our human shells...
I think I understand, even if it's just a little.
That you, you too...
Well? Did my story disgust you?
Do you despise me now?
Um...
No matter the game, it's pointless to just wander
around the map forever right before you reach the ending.
Brain Burst exists so we can aim for higher levels, right?
You're already more of a Burst Linker than I am.
Th-This isn't supposed to be funny!
In any case, I'll continue to help you.
I want to reach Level 10 one day, too!
Thank you.
Thank you, Haruyuki-kun.
I made the right decision.
I'm truly glad to have chosen you.
N-No, I'm just...
Anyway, let's get back to the main topic...
Earlier, I told you I managed to survive the two years, but I didn't do so by winning battles.
I haven't made a single connection to the globalnet with my Neuro Linker.
R-Really?!
However, due to my social status, there is one network I must connect to every day.
Social status?
You mean like being a princess or something?
Fool.
You must mean the local network for Umesato Middle School.
Wait, so...
You guessed it.
I was challenged to a battle through
the school network two months ago.
By someone in Umesato Middle.
In the school?
I got accelerated?
A battle? Here?
Oh, no!
Brain Burst has a function that lets you switch your true Duel Avatar to a dummy one for spectating.
There are times when you'd want to
hide your identity and watch a game.
However, I carelessly used my school
network avatar when I was challenged.
So does that mean...
Yes.
She found out I am Black Lotus.
My real life identity was revealed, the greatest taboo for any Burst Linker.
No matter how much I despised my Lotus form, that was really careless of me.
I prepared myself for an attack in the real world.
So attacks in the real world really do happen.
Yes.
However, no one has confronted me in the real world yet.
On the other hand, she's challenged me more than ten times in the past two months via the school network.
Now that she knows my real identity, she probably wants all the points for herself.
Can't you defeat her if you revert to your true avatar?
She'll likely give up on challenging me and sell my real life information to the other kings.
What can you do, then?
It's clear that I only have one way out of this.
I have to discover her real identity as well.
I see!
If you both knew each other's
identities, you could call a truce...
Wait, isn't it pretty simple?
Oh?
You just need to request for a duel through the school network during assembly
or when all the students are in one place.
Students are always connected to the school network
while in school, and you can't turn down a duel request.
You can find the class and student ID of the player from the position where her Duel Avatar shows up.
That's impressive.
It took me a whole day to come up with that solution.
So you already tried...
Yes, and I was shocked.
Who was it?
Nobody.
My name was the only one in the matching list.
That's not all.
I couldn't find her name even
right after escaping with a draw.
It's hard to believe, but she can block a challenge.
Is that even possible?
If it is, she must be a super hacker good enough
to modify the supposedly unbreachable program,
or someone related to the developer.
So you basically want me to help you
discover the identity of that opponent.
Something like that.
Her Duel Avatar is Cyan Pile.
She's Level 4.
Her element is near-blue with high purity.
Level 4...
I believe she's quite cornered, too.
From what?
From the fear of losing her acceleration.
Her frenzied behavior is unique to
Burst Linkers desperate for points.
Is that all I need to know?
No. There's another important source of information.
The Guide Cursor.
It points towards the enemy
immediately after a game starts.
Which means...
Kouenji Overpass
I see.
The stage retains the layout of the real world, so...
By remembering where it points to, I'll know the
general direction in which the opponent's real body lies.
I continued to mark down the names of students in the direction of the cursor
and came up with a student most likely to be the culprit.
Haruyuki-kun, I want you to auto-observe my next
match and remember the direction pointing to Cyan Pile.
With two cursors...
We can narrow down the coordinate to one point.
If there is a student in that position...
...we can confirm Cyan Pile's true identity.
I prepared that file a week before I approached you.
Student ID
Name
Chiyu is a Burst Linker?
No way!
She's horrible at games.
She's not the type to persistently prey on one person either!
You saw her obvious hostility towards me.
That was only because you and I cabled, so...
Why would that make her angry?
Doesn't she already have a great boyfriend?
Well, yes... but...
Consider this.
Maybe it's because she was planning to make you her child ,
but I came out of nowhere and snatched you away.
That's why she lashed out at me in her anger.
What do you think?
I see.
I'll go find out on my own.
Oh?
You can't just go up to her and ask, though.
I-I know.
I can explore her memory and confirm whether
the program is installed by cabling with her, right?
Yes.
I'll cable with her, then.
Why did I say that?
Cabling, of all things!
Huh? Haru?
Taku!
The kendo team's heading to the nationals next, right?
All the best teams are participating, so I don't know how far I'll get.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
You might even win the national title!
Don't make it sound so easy.
Man! This is good!
Especially if you're the one paying for it!
Ah, I'm so nervous!
I'm so worried!
Will I win?
Fine! I'll pay.
Thanks.
Hey, Taku.
Um...
Do you think Chiyu would ever...
harm others for her own gain?
What do you think, Haru?
She would never!
You've already reached a conclusion, then.
Oh, right.
Sorry for asking such a weird question.
Don't worry about it.
We're friends, aren't we?
Yeah.
Well then, I'm going for another lap.
All right.
Good luck at the finals!
He's right. There's no way.
I already know that.
I called you so many times last night!
Huh?
You didn't check your email either.
S-Sorry...
Well? What do you want?
Um, Chiyu...
Please cable with me!
You want to cable because you can't apologize out loud?
At least bring a cable with you!
I have to warn you, I only have this one.
It's so short!
Do you always use that to cable with Taku?
A-Are you dumb?!
Taku has a meter-long cable!
Do whatever you want.
Um...
I'd prefer it if you sat on a chair or something...
Here goes...
S-Sorry.
Just a little further..
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
Um, about the day before...
I'm sorry about ruining the lunch you made me.
Where's the Brain Burst application file?
But I was shocked.
I was imagining how you and Taku were
talking about what Araya was doing to me...
You and Taku are the last people I want to be pitying me.
I want all three of us to stand on the same level.
Haru, you have it all wrong.
Takkun only knew about the sandwiches because I said I'd make you some too
when I brought some for him at the kendo preliminaries.
I wonder how many years it's been
since you talked to me about yourself.
I guess I wasn't being fair.
I knew you were suffering,
but I turned a blind eye because I was
afraid you'd end up hating me for asking.
But you aren't being fair either!
You said you'd never change and always be my friend!
I simply didn't want anything between us to change.
I just wanted the three of us to always be together.
But why would you go to her for help now?
I've been worrying about you all these years,
but she solved everything in a single day...
N-No!
She's the student council vice-president, so-
Then why does she drag you around like a pet?
Why do you follow her around like a baby?
No!
It... doesn't really bother me...
But it bothers me !
Ever since we started middle school, you've been cold to me and you never come over anymore...
What am I supposed to do?
You already have a boyfriend.
But you were the one who said the three of us could stay together that way forever!
Was that a lie?
It's not!
But we can't be elementary school kids forever!
It didn't use to bother me...
But I can't anymore.
Taku keeps getting more and more
handsome, and you're kind of cute too...
But I just feel like I want to disappear when I'm with you!
Why would you jump to that conclusion and hate yourself so much?
Of course I'd hate myself...
But I know...
I know so many good things about you.
Two years ago, if you were the one...
Sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
I just wanted you to know that
you'll always have two close friends.
That's why...
Wait, so that was only because you
wanted Taku and me to stay friends...?
I guess I'm doing the impossible.
Nothing stays the same, and you can't stop your feelings...
When I saw you and Princess Snow Black
together, I thought you didn't need me anymore.
That's why I...
Sorry, Chiyu.
It never even occurred to me that you were worried, too.
Yeah.
I worry about things, and so does Takkun.
He probably feels the same way...
I don't see anything suspicious.
I knew it. Chiyu can't be Cyan Pile.
What was that lag?
It's...
...a backdoor?!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
...tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "reality"
Next Stage: Declaration.
A moment of eternity in accelerated time.
It's a declaration with lives at stake.