Did I just get accelerated?
Is this 3D imagery?
What is... this?
It's so...
Looks like we got a wimp here.
I don't recognize his name either.
Is he a newbie?
He's metal-colored, though.
He can't be that weak.
They're not NPCs...
Are they human?
Are they Burst Linkers?
It's been so long since I got the Post-Apocalypse stage.
Lucky me!
And a fresh newbie opponent to boot.
Mega-lucky!
And you are...
Giga-unlucky!
I'm starting to understand...
Could this be...
I knew it...
I don't stand a chance!
You got hunted already?
This isn't funny!
I thought I was done for.
It's what you get for breaking
your promise with me, young man.
I know it's my fault for being careless and making a global connection, but...
At least I don't have to explain it to you now.
I'm sure you understand by now.
The Brain Burst program is...
...just a multiplayer fighting game.
It involves random-encounter battles in augmented reality.
That's right.
That's unbelievable...
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Thoughts a thousand times faster than usual, and the hacking of social cameras...
All that for a fighting game? That's ridiculous!
That's not quite correct.
We Burst Linkers aren't accelerating for entertainment.
We fight to continue accelerating.
What do you mean?
Try accelerating now.
O-Okay...
Burst Link.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing!
What are we doing, anyway?
There should be a new icon
on the left side of your vision.
That's the menu screen for the
multiplayer fighting game, Brain Burst.
Press the matchmaking button.
Because we're connected to just the school's
local network, we should be the only players online.
Yes, Miss Black Lotus.
Click on my name and challenge me to a fight.
What?!
We're not actually going to fight.
We'll just wait until the time runs out for a draw.
Go ahead.
Oh, it's the Twilight stage.
You've drawn a rare one.
So that's your Duel Avatar.
Silver Crow...
That's a great name.
The color is nice too.
I like the design as well.
I look like a weakling.
Can I remake my avatar?
Actually, who designed and named this one?
You did it yourself.
I'm sure you had a really long
and horrifying dream last night.
Yes.
I don't remember it very well,
but I did have a bad dream.
The Brain Burst program accessed your subconscious mind and recorded your ambitions and fears.
It then created your Duel Avatar based on that information.
So you're saying I wished for this scrawny and shiny body?
But...
The program doesn't read your ideals.
It reads what you are ashamed of.
Does that mean Brain Burst designed your avatar too?
No, I built this one myself.
I had to seal my true Duel Avatar.
You sealed it?
Unfortunately, my Duel Avatar is hideous.
It's an abomination.
Well, enough about me.
You were challenged to a duel this morning, and you lost.
Do you remember the results screen after the fight?
I think it had my name, the words "Level 1",
and something called "Burst Points"...
It decreased from 99 to 89.
Burst Points.
Yes.
That's exactly what drives us to
set foot into this ruthless battlefield.
Burst Points indicate the number of times we can accelerate.
Every time you accelerate, you use up a point.
H-How do you get more?
There's only one way.
You must fight and win.
Against an enemy of the same level, a victory
gives you ten points, while a loss takes away ten.
The ability to accelerate is a great power.
You can use it to win in real fights, score full marks in tests,
and give you an advantage in certain gambling and sports activities.
Having tasted that forbidden fruit, we have no choice but
to continue fighting forever so we can keep accelerating.
Hang on!
You lose points by accelerating, so does that mean
it's possible for weak fighters to lose all their points?
What happens then?
It's simple.
You lose Brain Burst.
The program uninstalls itself automatically, never to be installed again.
Players are identified by their brain waves, so switching Neuro Linkers won't work.
Those who have exhausted all of their points can never accelerate again.
I'll lose Brain Burst?
If that happens, I'll never talk to her again...
Haruyuki-kun.
You can still return to the normal world.
You won't ever see the idiot who bullied you again.
I guarantee it.
What will you do?
I-I...
...still have to return the favor!
Huh?
You've rescued me from living hell.
You must have some grand plan for me.
A grand plan worth the trouble of checking my squash scores and lecturing me like you are doing now.
I can see why you think that way.
I...
I'm not even worthy of talking to you.
I'm ugly, chubby, and cry all the time.
I'm completely useless. I'm such a disgrace.
However, you still talked to me and cabled with me.
I know my being kind of good at games was the only reason for all of that.
B-But I want something more!
That's why I...
I want to live up to your expectations!
I don't want your sympathy to go to waste!
That's why I'll fight...
...as a Burst Linker!
Don't call it sympathy.
I'm just a foolish and helpless middle schooler.
A human being who stands on the
same ground and breathes the same air.
You're the one who's distancing yourself.
Are these two virtual meters really beyond your reach?
It is.
You don't know how frightening it is for someone like me
to even be looked at by someone who has everything.
You've rescued me from living hell.
It's more happiness than I deserve in my entire life.
I won't ask for anything more.
I see.
I appreciate your determination.
It's true that I face a difficult problem and need your help to solve it.
I'll do anything that I can to help.
What do you want me to do?
Let's start by learning how fights are done.
I wonder if I really have what it takes.
I have faith in you.
Let's eat, Arita-kun.
Your food's getting cold.
Princess.
Isn't it about time you said something?
We're all dying to know.
What is this gentleman's relationship with you?
Simply put, I asked him out and he rejected me.
Are you out of your mind?!
I'm going to get bullied again!
I'm sure of it!
I was only telling the truth.
Not to mention you didn't seem to mind.
When did you take that optical screenshot?!
You should be proud of yourself.
I've rejected plenty of guys, but
you're the only guy who's rejected me.
More importantly...
Your Neuro Linker will make a global
connection once you step outside the school.
You must accelerate before someone challenges you,
and then find and challenge Ash Roller.
Got it.
This is your real debut battle, Silver Crow.
Good luck.
Let's start by learning how fights are done.
Click on your own name below your HP gauge.
Okay.
You can examine the moves available to your Duel Avatar.
All I have are the typical punch and kick moves...
and my only special move is a headbutt.
Don't worry.
Your moves may seem dull, but
I'm sure they have hidden potential.
But...
Your heart gave rise to that body.
Who will believe in it if you don't?
Here he comes.
Judging from what you've told me, he has two major weaknesses.
The first is the loud noise he makes while moving.
Your Guide Cursor will only indicate
the vague direction of your opponent,
but you'll know of his location and distance from the sound.
If we use that to our advantage...
Do I really have what it takes?
Snap out of it!
I'm not the chubby and helpless Arita Haruyuki right now.
I'm Silver Crow, a Burst Linker!
This is the game world, where I've spent all my free time and energy.
Kouenji Overpass
This is reality to me!
I-I did it?!
I can't just stand here!
Ash Roller's second weakness:
Practically all of his Duel Avatar's potential went to his bike.
Therefore, the combat ability of the
rider himself should be close to zero.
So after damaging him early in the match, you just need to wait until time's up.
Oh? The little guy's not bad at all.
He's so much better now.
I wonder who his parent is.
I'll add you to my watchlist if you win.
Good luck, kid.
Well, I don't think it'll be that easy.
Whoa!
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
Don't get ahead of yourself just yet, kiddo!
I'll make you dance to the sound of my V-Twins!
Here I come!
You've got to be kidding me!
The debris was enough to damage me?
This is going to be tough!
I actually became Level 2 this morning from beating you.
I couldn't decide what to do with the level up bonus, but I ended up going with the wall-driving ability.
I totally made the right choice!
And you are...
Tera-unlucky!
If your ambushing or escaping fails and you're forced to
fight him, your odds of winning will be drastically reduced.
This is because the name of a Burst Linker always includes a color, and you can tell an avatar's element from it.
Silver Crow has the color of metal.
It's a very rare and powerful color type.
You have resistance against
amputation, piercing, fire, and poison.
Your melee attack power is also decent.
However, you're weak against corrosion and impact attacks.
Impact attacks...
Ash Roller, with low color saturation, has attacks that have special characteristics.
While his wheels aren't obvious weapons,
their attack type is probably melee impact.
In other words, your armor is
practically useless against his tackles.
Which means you only have one choice.
Keep running until time runs out.
Easier said than done!
Damn it!
Even pain is simulated!
Are you out of options, Shiny Boy?
I'll make my move, then!
Is there... anything I can do?
I need an amazing comeback plan...
A way to turn things around!
I know!
The special move!
What a pity.
Looks like it's game over.
Damn it.
Damn it!
I'm supposed to be a hero in virtual games!
What's the point of a special move that doesn't even hit?
How can I win with such a weak character?!
I'm sick of this crap!
Your heart gave rise to that body.
Who will believe in it if you don't?
No one believes in me less than myself.
The appearance of this avatar
already reeks of incompetence.
I'm sorry I disappointed you.
Just forget about-
You fool!
Strength isn't solely defined by victory as a result.
It was too late for me when I realized that, however.
No.
I can't lose like this.
Even if I'm going to lose, I'll fight to the bitter end!
Otherwise...
I won't even be her pawn!
Think!
You've played so many virtual games!
He's got to have a some sort of
weakness since this world is so realistic.
What's the weakness of a bike with a
gasoline engine from the last century?
Think!
That's it!
Keep on dancing!
Please move just this once, Silver Crow!
Faster than him!
Even if I can't believe in myself...
...I can believe in her words!
Dumbass!
A scrawny midget like you can't
possibly stop my monster machine!
Ow! Ouch!
Your HP bar will keep going down if you don't let go!
Almost there!
Vroom!
This is it!
Wh-What?!
That's clever.
Harleys are usually AWD, but
internal-combustion engine bikes are RWD.
That bike is useless now.
Ash Roller is just like a fish out of water!
He's good!
Let's see... Silver Crow.
You've got a new fan.
You bastard! Put it down!
Let go!
Nope!
If you don't like it, just use the front wheel!
What did you say?!
You $@%# bastard!
You did it, Silver Crow!
I thought you were going to lose for a while there.
I-I did too.
Don't be so modest.
You outlasted him.
I was just lucky...
Now you've gotten all your points back.
Actually, it came with extra points.
He was Level 2 when I fought him.
I see.
So that's why he drove straight up the wall.
I couldn't believe my eyes!
It was an impressive win, Haruyuki-kun.
Let's go somewhere and celebrate this occasion...
Chiyu!
What are you trying to do with Haru?
I heard Haru was hurt yesterday
because you provoked somebody.
Yet here you are, trying to embarrass him again.
What are you up to?!
Oh?
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
...tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "reality"
Next Stage: Investigation.
A mysterious enemy preys on Snow Black.
Where will the investigation lead Haruyuki?