Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
Accepting Votes!
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Accepting Votes!
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
is most appropriate! Runs until 13:00 tomorrow.
asshole, Haruyuki Arita!  Don't forget to vote for what you feel
Your one vote can help decide a nickname for the voyeur
Final List
1st
Papayuki
15 votes
2nd
IHasCamera
11 votes
3rd
HaruPee
4 votes
4th
Splitfield Maniacson
1 vote
Final List
1st
Papayuki
15 votes
2nd
IHasCamera
11 votes
3rd
HaruPee
4 votes
4th
Splitfield Maniacson
1 vote
Final List
1st
Papayuki
15 votes
2nd
IHasCamera
11 votes
3rd
HaruPee
4 votes
4th
Splitfield Maniacson
1 vote
Final List
1st
Papayuki
15 votes
2nd
IHasCamera
11 votes
3rd
HaruPee
4 votes
4th
Splitfield Maniacson
1 vote
H-Hello.
It's been a long time.
What's with the call out of the blue?
W-Well, I want to talk to you about something.
Could we meet up now in the real world and talk?
Us two and Taku.
But it's raining!
I am in the mood for some cake, though.
With lots of strawberries on it!
Sure, I'll treat you to as many as you want, Yuniko-chan!
Just call me Niko, geez.
I know this really good patisserie,
so let's meet there, Haruyuki-oniichan!
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
I was always wide awake
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nita wa no naka de
We are all in similar nets
Found You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I found the wind that day with trembling passion
And All Of My Past subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
And all of my past is a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou furuwasete itai kara
To send my pulse racing
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If I Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
You managed to get the Red King to meet us?
Yeah, somehow.
Looks like the rumor spread everywhere in no time.
I didn't do it.
Of course you didn't!
That Sugeno shouldn't have called you in without any proof!
Noumi probably reported me.
Noumi did?
I guess I should tell you.
The whole thing was a trap Noumi set up.
I walked right into it.
I see.
So there was a virus in the photo I sent you.
Sorry, Haru.
I keep forgetting to check for that stuff.
It's not your fault.
No, I should've realized something was wrong, seeing how big the file was.
Yet...
Yet I barged into your place while you were having a hard time and tried to lecture you...
I even punched you...
Haru.
Wh-What are you...?
Haru, hit me.
I-It's fine, there's no need...
I can't forgive myself otherwise!
Wait, Taku!
Um...
You need to hit me, too.
Chiyu, I'm sorry.
When I got fooled by the visual masking and rushed into the girls' shower room, I ran into Chiyu inside.
Sorry.
I see.
So that's how Chii-chan got involved in this.
I'm really sorry for not telling you earlier.
You don't have to tell me exactly what you saw for the time being.
It's for Chii-chan's sake.
You really are a gentleman.
It's been so long, Haruyuki-oniichan!
You're as round as ever!
Long time too, Prof.
You're as gloomy as ever!
The Strawberry Labyrinth!
I got here early, so I went ahead and ordered it.
Will coffee do for you both?
Y-Yeah.
Two coffees, then.
None for you!
F-Fine, then.
Just kidding!
Come on, say "Ahh".
Just kidding again!
Anyway, Niko.
I'd like to get started.
Okay, I'll listen for ten strawberries.
I dunno if that's a fair trade...
Anyway, I'd like you to teach the Prof-
I mean, Takumu something.
How to use the Incarnate System.
What'd you say?
We're using the inside room for a bit.
W-Wait!
Are you retarded?!
Don't just talk about incarnation in public areas!
S-Sorry!
Well, you guys can start by telling me
where you heard about the Incarnate System.
Dusk Taker.
A duel avatar with a robbing ability.
What's more, he can use incarnation.
He's probably too much for you guys to handle right now.
It's exactly as you say, I'm afraid.
Well, I can sympathize, but to be frank, it's just another Legion's problem.
In fact, it'd be better for us if I just
ignore it and Nega Nebulous gets destroyed.
But if I say that, you'd reply with this.
"But didn't you come to us for help
when you had problems with your Legion?"
"You owe us", that kind of crap.
I figured this kind of thing would happen someday.
Still, an Incarnate System lecture comes with a super huge price.
So that's a yes, then?!
Geez.
If I knew, I would've ordered a Royal Palace and not a Strawberry Labyrinth.
Thank you!
Why the hell are you always grabbing my foot, you perv?!
Hook up to this.
What's that?
It's not a trap or anything!
This room blocks off radio waves, so we can only make a global connection through a cable.
I need to go back to my dorm by six, so I only have 30 minutes to spare.
That's 500 hours in the Accelerated World, or 20 days.
In that time, you'll learn incarnate techniques that you can use in battle.
No, one week inside is more than enough time.
Big words, Prof.
I'm gonna test just how strong your resolve is.
Ready?
Unlimited Burst!
Tch, the Ice and Snow stage?
Definitely not my favorite.
Hey, Crow.
Is your metallic armor cold-resistant?
Y-Yes, pretty much.
No fair!
Heh.
You little...!
It's no fair!
It's cold-resistant, but only in terms of damage values!
I feel just as cold as you do!
Okay, I'll start by explaining the
characteristics of incarnate techniques.
Thank you!
First, using them does not lower your special move gauge.
Second, only incarnate techniques can defend against incarnate attacks.
Third, they shine!
Th-They shine?
Crow, give it a try.
Show us the power you've managed to grasp.
O-Okay.
My hand is a blade.
A blade that can penetrate anything at the speed of light!
Oh, much better than I'd expected.
Pretty good for a complete beginner.
Beginner?
An incarnation strong enough to be
useful in battle should shine like this.
We call it the Over Ray.
That was the first of four basic types of
incarnate techniques: attack range augmentation.
And this is the second.
Movement ability augmentation.
Like that.
What about the third and the fourth?
Attack power augmentation and armor strength augmentation.
I can't use either of them, though.
You can't? But you're a king...
That's right.
It's because I know I'm not actually that strong.
I'm scared of the world.
The closer I get to it, the more it uses various ways to hurt me.
I want to distance myself from the world.
That desire and those mental scars
were what gave rise to Scarlet Rain.
Niko...
That's why I can't use incarnation to strengthen my avatar's offensive and defensive powers.
So basically, you can only learn incarnate techniques that match the nature of your duel avatar.
That's right.
The power of incarnation isn't supposed to be used for defeating your enemies.
It's for confronting your own weaknesses.
That's why you should only use incarnate techniques when they're being used against you.
We'll get started with the training, then.
Pile, is your avatar close-ranged or long-ranged?
Close-ranged, of course.
Blue means close-range, and look at how vividly blue his avatar is.
That's what I thought, but
consider his Enhanced Armament.
Y-You're right.
I had a feeling it'd come to this.
In order to learn incarnate techniques,
I'll have to face my mental scars up front.
I'll dive out here, then.
No, I want you to hear this.
It's something I should've told you a long time ago.
Cyan Pile is essentially a close-range avatar.
Yet it was created with a long-range starting weapon.
It's probably a representation of my fear.
Your fear?
Between third and fifth grade of elementary school,
I was severely bullied.
At the time, the older students in my kendo class decided to pick on me.
They said they were practicing their thrusts.
They did it over and over again...
I still have a scar from it here.
Taku, I had no idea...
This pile driver is the manifestation of
my fear and anger from being tormented.
At the time, I wanted to use this iron pile to skewer every last guy who bullied me.
So while my duel avatar is close-ranged, it was created with a piercing weapon instead of a blade, Red King.
I now understand your scars.
If you can overcome that fear of yours,
you should be able to master attack power augmentation incarnation as a true close-range avatar.
Yes.
Well, the prof and I will start the actual training now.
Uh, I guess I'll go investigate what Dusk Taker does to keep his name off the matching list.
Thanks, Haru.
Well then, I'll teach you one last secret about incarnation.
Did you give a name to that attack range augmentation incarnate technique you used earlier?
A-A name?
Incarnation techniques really depend on
how fast and how strongly you can form images.
Give it a name, and then use the name as a trigger.
Come on, name it now.
Um... Well then, "Sword".
"Laser Sword".
Lame.
What's the name of the skill you just used, then?
Like I'd tell you, dumbass!
Hang in there, Taku.
This way. Quick.
O-Oh, thank you.
We'll leave from the back.
Follow me, Silver Crow.
You know my avatar?!
You don't have to run, and it's too late to anyway.
Scarlet Rain told me to assist you in your investigation.
My name is Blood Leopard.
Call me Leopard, not Blood.
If you want to shorten it, Pard and not Leopa.
W-Wait a minute!
So basically, this isn't just a typical patisserie, but the Red Legion's-Prominence's-base.
And this maid is also a Burst Linker?
I did think she was a little cold for a maid.
I've waited ten seconds.
You can think while we're moving.
This is all my master told me.
There's a Burst Linker who doesn't appear on
matching lists despite being connected to the local network.
You want to find out how he does it.
There. 'Kay?
Yes, that's right.
Recently, I've heard rumors of a local network troublemaker.
What's known about him?
His details are unknown.
He's breaking in from another network.
Where is that network?
Akihabara.
Akihabara?
That's Yellow Legion territory.
Yes. We're heading there now.
A
Nerima Ward
Wow!
A
Nerima Ward
Huh?
Get on. Quick.
No way, I... uh...
Start.
You're driving dressed like that?
Changing would be a waste of time.
What about the cafe?
My shift ended at 5.
Ask the rest of your questions in one go.
I'm done.
'Kay.
Hold on.
Don't run away!
I've defused them.
Take them up front!
It's no use unless you conquer your fears!
O-Okay!
Shall we stop here?
No.
One more time, please.
There we go.
Here it comes!
Don't run away.
Haru recovered on his own.
He's gotten strong.
I can, too!
Uh, I think we really stand out.
Right.
Intruding into the Yellow Legion's base seems kinda dangerous.
No prob.
We'll fit right in.
Huh?
I see.
Sokmap
Akiba★Sokmap Shop 1
This way.
All right!
Damn it.
This is an arcade!
One from way back with all sorts of arcade games!
I don't have a 100 yen coin in real money!
Whatever.
Wait...
Um...
Where are we going?
A dive cafe.
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
Important Points
Other
About the Dive Booths.
Information on Cafe Usage
There's only one chair.
No two-seater booths were available.
You can sit if we squeeze up.
W-Well, uh...
No prob.
I don't mind snuggling up with a kid.
But I do, a lot!
And considering the first condition for Burst Linkers, we can't be more than three years apart!
After full-diving, enter the access gate with the "Akihabara BG" tag on it.
Huh?
Information
Counting down. One. Zero.
Wai-
Direct Link!
I prepared a disguise.
It suits you.
Where are we?
The Akihabara Battle Ground.
The Burst Linker holy land.
Holy land?
Is it the Yellow Legion's base or something?
No.
This is the only neutral place in the Akihabara area.
Follow me.
Good evening, Matchmaker.
Ooh, rare to see you here.
How many months has it been?
Eight.
Are you starting to miss the serious fights here?
Or are you here to earn some pocket money?
Sorry, but I didn't come here to fight or gamble.
G-Gamble? With real money?
It's just the pocket money of
junior high and high school students.
You'd earn more in an hour at a part-time job.
Anyway, I'd like to know the details
about the local network troublemaker.
Info on the Burst Linker who doesn't appear on the matching list.
Where'd you hear about that?
I'm asking the questions.
You don't need to pay me.
Just tell me what you know instead.
It's becoming a big problem for us, too.
A big problem?
Listen, young'un.
This is the holy land for fighters that not even the Yellow King, ruler of Akihabara, can touch.
But about a week ago, a rude chap showed up.
Without registering as a fighter, he began
challenging only suitable opponents to duels.
His name doesn't appear on the matching list
despite being connected to the local network.
If we let him go unchecked, the very existence of the Akihabara BG could be threatened.
What's the name of this Burst Linker who doesn't appear on the list?
Rust Jigsaw.
Princess Day ♡
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
Live Concert Info
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
Live Concert Info
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
Live Concert Info
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
Live Concert Info
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Princess Day ♡
Maid Cafe
New Feeling!!
Stylish Apple Action
Maid Cafe
Live Concert Info
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I couldn't grasp anything as I flapped my wings
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kogareru no mo zenbu
I also long for your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Determination.
Haruyuki finally discovers the truth.
With that determination, everything
begins moving towards its conclusion.