Burst Link!
Let it be in time!
Is that... Takumu?
Cyan Pile?!
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
I was surprised to see that
you've become a Burst Linker.
Taku...
But I really couldn't keep my cool yesterday.
How did it feel to cable with Chii-chan on the bed?
How did you like touching her body, fully knowing how I would feel?
So it was you who installed a virus in Chiyu's
Neuro Linker and spied on her memory and feeds?!
Weren't you poking around her memory too?
And you're not even her boyfriend!
Girls are hard to understand, though.
Chii-chan has always enjoyed taking care
of you far more than holding hands with me!
That's why I was really happy when she chose me.
I thought she had finally made a practical decision.
She's better off with the guy who's the top of
his year academically and the kendo champion.
Do you really mean that?
Chiyu's been worrying and suffering all this time!
You didn't earn your top grades and national title either!
It was the power of Brain Burst's acceleration!
Acceleration is my power!
A year ago, I became a Burst Linker after
the captain of the kendo club asked me to.
She was a close aide to the Blue King.
As her child , I was a promising bodyguard candidate.
They had high expectations for me.
But just because you're now a Burst Linker too,
you think you've become my equal?!
It's true that you have everything I don't.
But you're an idiot!
I'm an idiot?
Yeah.
That's why you can never beat me!
Have you ever beaten me in any game?
Haru.
Get ready to lose that last shred of pride you have!
He's fast!
But it's nowhere as fast as Ash's bike.
I can dodge him!
You're running away already, Haru?!
Please work!
Did Takumu call them here through a global connection?
I figured out his attack range.
There's nothing for me to fear!
I've got to do this!
I see.
So you think your hit and run tactics would work here.
Haru...
Or should I say, Silver Crow!
He shouldn't have a full grasp of my speed yet.
I have to win this before that happens!
This is it!
You really are good at games, Haru.
But those weak attacks won't work on me!
You idiot!
Chiyu never cared for you to get
top grades or the national kendo title!
Chiyu only wanted you to be yourself!
But you...!
You...!
Don't get carried away!
Splash Stinger!
You really did pound on me quite a bit.
However, all you did was pump up my special attack gauge.
Special attacks are what duels are all about.
I see your gauge is full too.
Feel free to use yours.
The headbutt won't be useful here.
But I have my fist and legs...
...and my speed!
Your leg came off!
How frail you are.
Are you really metal-colored?
Crap...
Oh, no!
I can't dodge or run anymore!
This is inevitable, Haru.
You are meant to kneel before me.
But you really did have a lot to say.
You act like you're the only one who understands Chii-chan!
I do.
More than you, at least!
Have you thought about me?
Chii-chan would look sad all of a sudden
when she's alone with me.
Did you think about how I felt when
I realized she was thinking about you, Haru?
That's how you are.
And that's exactly why Chii-chan and I can never escape the muddy hell that is you!
Just disappear already, Haru.
You'll free me and Chii-chan that way!
Let's end this, Haru.
Everything about it.
Spiral Gravity Driver!
He still has a bit of HP left.
Whatever, time will run out soon.
Did you see that, my spectators?
Especially everyone in the Blue Legion!
I can still fight.
I'm still useful!
It'd be a shame to abandon me just
because I overused my points a little!
Right?!
I'm still useful!
It'd be a shame to abandon me just
because I overused my points a little!
Right?!
Taku...
Takumu...
You...
This was a battle I couldn't lose...
...for Taku, Chiyu, and even myself...
For Princess Snow Black, too...
But even if I continue fighting...
Where am I?
Senpai...
I...
I couldn't protect you.
I couldn't meet your expectations.
I thought I could change.
Your words, kindness, and feelings
for me made me think I could change.
But I couldn't do it.
It's not the avatar's fault.
I probably the one who wrecked Silver Crow.
I've never looked up to the sky, always
facing down as I crawled on the ground.
I wanted to go to where you are...
To the distant sky where you gently flap your wings.
High and far away, free from the
muddy hell that is the real world...
I wanted...
...to fly with you...
Strength isn't solely defined by victory as a result.
She's right.
Strength isn't just about winning.
Even if my attempts are pathetic and comical,
and even if I'm covered in mud in my defeat...
If I can keep fighting and look up at
the sky even as I lie on the ground...
That alone...
...is the proof of true strength!
Isn't that right, Senpai?
Wings?
It's hot!
It's calling me.
Fly!
What's happening?
It's boundless.
This world is....
...boundless!
Look!
He's hovering!
It's not a jump...
He's flying?!
You're kidding me!
It's the aviation ability.
Look at those wings.
It finally happened.
Silver Crow is...
...the very first aviating avatar in the Accelerated World!
Wow!
Who is he?
Contact headquarters!
Don't you...
Don't you look down on me!
Taku.
He's using his special attack!
Fall back down!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Haru!
Taku!
Haruyuki-kun.
I'm sure that, one day, you'll be known far and
wide as the fastest Linker in the Accelerated World.
You'll discover the ultimate potential hidden within our brains and souls.
I can see it.
I can see it, Senpai!
I-I'm flying?
No, Haru.
Don't drop me.
If I fall now, I'll lose all my points.
No...
If I lose Brain Burst, I'll...
Please!
Please, Haru!
You tried to wipe out her dream, her only hope!
Even so...
Yes. You're right.
In the end, I still can't beat you.
Just like all the games we've played in the past.
I'm sorry.
You win, Haru!
Do you admit it, Taku?
Do you admit that you'll never beat me
in the Accelerated World, Taku?!
In the real world, I can't beat you in anything.
However, you can't beat me in this world.
We've become equals!
So, become my ally.
Come over to our side, Taku!
Fight under her command, just like me!
How can you trust me?
I've betrayed my own Legion, Brain Burst's rules, and even the two friends that I had...
We'll tell Chiyu everything.
About Brain Burst, about how we fought...
About the feelings we both kept to ourselves.
We probably need a fresh start from there.
Did I do the right thing, Senpai?
Senpai...
Senpai.
Senpai!
I'm so glad.
I believed in you.
I knew you'd survive.
Your voice was the only thing I heard in the darkness that surrounded me.
You must have protected me.
Look at all this damage.
Thank you, Haruyuki-kun.
No, it was all because you told me to believe in myself.
So I...
It's beautiful.
So this is your true form.
Until now, no Duel Avatar has
ever achieved true aviation ability.
My hunch was right.
You're the one who will change this world.
It seems the time has come for me to break out of
my tranquil cocoon and aim for the sky once more.
I should apologize to you as well, Cyan Pile.
I have dishonored what should've been an honorable duel together countless times.
I will now reveal my true form.
And if you wish...
I will fight with all my might.
Hey, is that...
Could that be...?
That Duel Avatar...
It's the Accelerated World's biggest traitor, Black Lotus, the Black King!
She's still alive?!
It's Black Lotus!
It's beautiful...
You said it was hideous, but I don't think so at all!
Really?
It doesn't even have hands you can hold.
Well then, Silver Crow.
Can you take me up for a flight?
Y-Yes.
I'm all yours.
Okay.
E-Excuse me.
This is amazing!
I could get addicted to this.
Listen, Burst Linkers of the Six Kings' Legions!
I am Black Lotus, the one who rebels against the thrones.
Me and my Legion, the Nega Nebulous,
have emerged from hiding to
put an end to this fallacious peace!
Take up your swords and raise your torches!
It is time to fight!
Err...
Congratulations...
...would be too early to say.
She hasn't been discharged from hospital yet.
What should I do?
Come on!
How long will you keep me waiting?
Come in already.
Okay!
Hey. Long time no see, Haruyuki-kun.
Y-Yes.
The backdoor has been rendered
unusable due to a BB server update.
Takumu's parent , the one who gave him the
backdoor program, lost all her points as punishment.
We still don't know who developed the program, though.
The Yellow Legion specializes in sneak attacks, so it's probably one of them.
We'll definitely track down the culprit and...
Oh, right.
Here.
I was holding on to it.
Here you go.
Did you look inside?
No! Yes! Uh...
Sorry, Princess Snow Black.
You know, Haruyuki-kun.
Could you call me by my first name
instead of my nickname?
O-Okay!
Um...
I-I don't know your... real name.
Didn't you look inside?
Um, I only briefly saw a bit of it.
That's so typical of you, Haruyuki-kun.
Allow me to introduce myself again, then.
It's not that different from my nickname.
My name is...
Next stage: Retribution.
Just like how a stream always
flows from high to low ground,
the fate of retribution awaits
Haruyuki and Takumu.