Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
It now trembles within my chest
Mou kuru ki ga shita
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne to
So happy for them
Alright...
Is there anyone who can explain what this "AD" means?
The time has finally come.
Anti-Angel Operations HQ
What?  Is something about to start?
Oh, yeah. Uh huh.
Tenshi's assault is going to begin.
Tenshi's assault?
An assault... but why?
It's because exams are coming up.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh... why?
You'll understand if you think about it.
Getting us to go to class is important.
But getting us to score well on our tests is important to Tenshi as well.
But this test period...
could also be a good opportunity to pull one over on Tenshi.
Looks like you have something in mind, Yurippe.
Let's hear it.
Completely get in the way of Tenshi's exams, and make her get failing grades.
That'll lower her scores to the lowest of the school.
And what will that accomplish?
Her fall from grace.
The Student Council sees her as almost majestic.
And if that majesty weakens?
At the very least, her image among the teachers and regular students will change.
And with that, changes will begin to surface.
Like what?
Who knows?  I can't predict that far ahead.
Then isn't this kinda meaningless?
However...
If by some small chance she's not an Angel created by God...
If her soul isn't made of steel...
If she has a human soul just like us...
Her fall from grace will deal her an effective emotional blow.
First, we'll decide which members to use for today's operation.
Preparations to take tests alongside Tenshi have already been completed.
Then wouldn't going in with everyone be okay?
No it wouldn't "be okay"!
I won't forgive any slip-ups!
If we get caught partway through, we'd all be moved to a different classroom...
We'd lose our ability to make Tenshi fail her exams.
I see.  I'm gonna pass, then.
Stuff like this can be handled by the pansies.
In that case, today's members will be...
Takamatsu-kun.
Hinata-kun.
Ooyama-kun.
Takeyama-kun.
Otonashi-kun.
Me again?
Please, call me Christ-
I just chose the members who look the most normal.
Now, then.
Operation... start!
The test seating will be assigned by lottery that morning.
Study Building B, Classroom
If we don't manage to get close to Tenshi, it'll be difficult to interfere.
Got it?
Pick the seat in front of her.
How are we supposed to do that?
Let's see...
20.  I missed!
11.  That's pretty far from Tenshi.
33.  Haha!  Not even close!
My turn.  25.  I'm pretty far, too.
Kyaa!  I'm number 1!
Hey wait... damn you!  Damn you!
Isn't anyone close to her?
Even next to her is okay.
One seat ahead.
YES!
So, what should I do?
When they're handing out the test sheets, grab two of them.
Then when they collect them after the test, switch one with Tenshi's.
Turn in that test paper blank...
Wait, turning it in blank will seem almost too unnatural.
Just put lots of stupid answers on it.
You make that sound easy...
Just write what you'd like to be in the future or something.
But it's a Physics test...
That's fine.  Just say you wanna become a pilot...
or maybe a dolphin trainer!
That's definitely stupid, alright...
So what do we do when they're being collected?
Hinata-kun!  Choose your timing well, and do something retarded!
Something everyone will notice!
I couldn't do that...
Why do you think I put you in here?
Wait.  That was what you were planning?
So, when the moment is right, Takeyama-kun will take Tenshi's test from the pile of answer sheets he'll receive from behind him...
and swap it with the fake.
At any rate, even if the unexpected happens, don't get confused.
Just follow each other's lead.  Understood?
Ah, but hold on a minute.
What should I write for her name?
"Tenshi".
Are you stupid?
Would "Student Council President" work?
It just might.
I mean, we're making her stupid enough to write stuff like dolphin trainer in her answers...
No way.  No one's stupid enough to not write their own name!
Actually, I'm surprised you guys don't even know her name!
We never had a chance to find out.
That's not cool at all!
Fine, you go and find out.
Go check the roster in the Teacher's Lounge.
Tch... fine.
Just a minute...
Where are you going?  Testing is about to start.
Oh, um... I'm just a little nervous.
Crap... what do I do?
Isn't it too cruel to hand in her test with the name "Student Council President"?
No no, this isn't the time for that.
With the question "What is the current in amperes that will flow when 3.0 volts is applied to a 20 ohm resistor?",
are we really gonna make her answer "Train Company President" amperes?!
Are you that worried?
Uh, no... it's not that...
Try to calm down.  You'll be fine.
Um...
Ah, uh... Otonashi.
Otonashi-kun.
I don't know your name, either...
Me?  Tachibana.
First name?
First?  Kanade.
Kanade... Tachibana.
It has a beautiful sound to it.
Like her name, like the sound of a note being played...
TL Note: "Kanaderu" means to play a musical instrument.
It was a good name, I thought.
Thank you.
I've calmed down thanks to you, Tachibana.
Okay, do your best.
Kanade Tachibana.
Oh yeah, that's what it was.
So you already knew?!
I just forgot.
Alright, we're starting.
Sit down.
How strange.
I have no memories, so how am I finishing my test so smoothly?
Don't answer the questions seriously.
There's a chance you might disappear.
Oops.
I'm not supposed to take it seriously.
Alright.  Pass them forwards starting at the back.
W-What is that ?!
There's a monstrous bamboo shoot coming up from the ground!
Stupid Hinata.
Geez.  I guess I've gotta use it.
I put a rocket engine under your chair just in case you messed up.
How did you like your taste of space flight?
All it was was me hitting the ceiling and then dropping to the floor within seconds!
And how the hell did you make a rocket engine?!
I followed up after your mistake.  Be grateful.
Operation successful, right, Takeyama-kun?
No errors at all.
Also, call me-
Well, you're next, Takamatsu-kun.
What about me?
Create a distraction.
I-Isn't that Hinata-san's role?
Do you know the story of the Boy Who Cried Wolf?
Lies told over and over become less believable-
Exactly that!
W-Wait, is that why you brought so many of us?
Who knows?
I-I refuse.
You'll do it!
Just give it up and fly, and get smashed into the ceiling.
I've got to think of something to distract everyone.
So, what should I do for the next set of answers?
You've got it easy, huh?
You just have to be sneaky, no need to fly...
What are you saying?
I'm taking on a mission with extreme risk here!
Then switch with me.
No way!
You're having it so much better!
Congrats for having good luck with the lottery!
This is a job that requires the finely-honed nerves that only I have.
All you need to do is act stupid and go flying.
What was that?  Are you calling me stupid?!
HEY!
STOP FIGHTING!
Sorry!
They were arguing about an answer.
It's settled now.
Turns out Hinata got zero points.
Everything's okay, now.
No problems!
Sorry about the ruckus.
It's all good now!
I see.
Idiot!
Who is?!
So... what should I do for the next set of answers?
What subject is it?
World History.
Then answer all the questions as if the Earth were under attack by aliens.
Okay, pass them forwards starting at the back.
I've gotta do it.
You there, what's wrong?
Sensei, the truth is...
I only look skinny when clothed!
How's this?
I understand.  Sit down.
Yes...
I can't believe you thought such a stupid plan would work.
I had confidence, but...
Could it be said to be surprising?
Does it not match my character?
I've been training in secret.
We get it.  Put your shirt back on.
The plan went well again, right, Takeyama-kun?
Without a hitch.
Isn't it about time you call me-
Next is Ooyama-kun.
I knew it was coming!
I can't come up with anything!
Ooyama-kun, your seat's behind hers to her left.  That's pretty close, isn't it?
That's true!  So... maybe I don't have to do any weird gags?
Sure.  Just confess to Tenshi.
Okay!  Wait, what?
Confess to Tenshi.
"I'm sorry for not picking a better time and place."
"I've always loved you.  Please go out with me."  Something like that.
If you do it just like that, you won't need to fly.
Tch.  He just has to confess?  That's almost unfair.
No way!  Put yourself in my shoes!
You got off with just damage to your body.
The damage to my mind is going to be extreme!
I mean, I've never confessed to a girl before!
And I already know I'll get turned down.
It'll be good practice for someone as naïve as you.
I'm not like you, Hinata!  I don't want practice!
I only fall in love for real!
What's that supposed to mean?
You saying that my love is fraught with insincerity?
HEY!
NO FIGHTING!
Sorry!
Yuri was feeling anxious.
It was because she had a dream about Hinata.
Don't think the me today will be the same as the me tomorrow.
You'd better watch out.
That's what he told her.
And just then, Yuri found out that it was true!
There's two Hinata-kuns?
U-Um... you took it that way?
You mean there might be 3 or more?
Um... sure...
My condolences.
Anyway, it's all calmed down, so no need to worry.
Everything's fine.
Thanks for your concern.
What do you mean there's 3 or more of me?
What do you mean I was anxious?
Hey now, I cleaned up after your mess.  What's with that response?
You guys brought it upon yourselves.
So, how should I answer the next set of questions?
What's the subject?
English.
Well then, answer everything with Katakana.
Okay, pass them forwards starting at the back.
Tachibana-san!
I'm sorry for not picking a better time and place!
I've always loved you!
Please go out with me!
Well then, pick a better time and place.
Hey you, sit down.
Yes, sir.
Ahhh, now he's done it.
He's gonna go fl-
Hey, wait a minute here!
What is it?  Don't come close!
Why did I get sent flying?!
Because Ooyama-kun had already suffered damage to his heart.
Why me though?  I don't get it!
More importantly, everyone...
Let's have lunch!
UTW Presents:
Study Building A, Roof
No mistakes yet, right, Takeyama-kun?
It's all perfect.  And it's Christ.
How many more times am I gonna have to get smashed through the ceiling?
All the way until the tests are over.
Let's change members tomorrow!
Matsushita-kun and TK seem too heavy.
You chose me because I'm light?!
And besides, if you keep sending me flying like that, they'll get sick of it!
"Oh, he's flying again"... they won't even look!
That's why we need to keep this up and come up with more gimmicks!
What's in store for us?  I'm scared!  We're friends, right?
And that's why you should help!
So you help, too!
I wonder if I'll need to confess again tomorrow...
Maybe I'll take my pants off too, next time.
The operation was almost perfect.
But... will anything change if we do this?
All we've done is make a big ruckus like we usually do.
And like usual, things calm down and return to normal.
I thought that's all that would happen.
And, the testing period ended...
Staff Building 1, Hallway Outside the Teacher's Lounge
Tachibana?
What's wrong?  Did something happen?
Nothing.
The Next
Day
It's begun.
What has?
The rumor about Tenshi scoring zeros across the board.
Seriously?
And all her answers were making fun of the teachers.
We went that far?
What did you guys do?
We went flying and spinning, and even went jumping out of windows.
What's with that?
But the teachers, they should realize it wasn't Tenshi, but someone's prank, right?
How many times do I have to tell you?  The teachers wouldn't realize that.
It's the same as it would go in reality.
The Student Council President turned in joke answers.
Therefore, Tenshi herself will be called into the office and scolded.
So, that's what happened back then...
I wonder if Tachibana explained it to them.
Who knows?
But it was all of the subjects.
Just how would she explain it to every last teacher?
Well, from the perspective of the teachers, it would seem like a lone rebellion.
A lone rebellion?
Gymnasium
Then, a few days later...
We heard about it at a school-wide assembly.
And so for those reasons...
Kanade Tachibana-san will be resigning as Student Council President.
And current Vice-President Naoi-kun will be standing in as President.
That's ridiculous!
She didn't resign, but was discharged.
Yurippe...
Now that she's been demoted to a common student like us,
I wonder if she'll be able to stop us now that she's lost her cause.
We'll carry out Operation Tornado tonight.
That's the last piece Iwasawa left behind.
What?!  Is it really okay for me to write the lyrics for it?
I suppose.
It all depends on how everyone will react...
to this new song, "Thousand Enemies", and the second incarnation of GirlDeMo.
Wakatta koto ga hitotsu aru yo
There's one thing I understood
Sonna furi shite tatakau koto ni hisshi
From you pretending like that, fighting desperately
Say...
Hm?
Who exactly are we fighting with?
Anyone who gets in our way.
Who's gonna get in our way?
If anyone's coming, it'd be Tenshi, right?
Oh wait, maybe it'll be that new acting President.
Isn't he just a normal student?
We can't shoot at him.
Oh, really?
Will Tenshi come?
Katachi aru sonna kokoro
A finely-formed heart
Dare datte kizukeba motteru
Once they notice it, everyone has one
Kimi mo motteru
You have one, too
She's here!
We'll get her before she uses her Guard Skills.
Here I go!
Wait!  Don't shoot!
Why?
Something's strange.
W-What's strange?
I don't know for sure...
She doesn't seem hostile...
Like she won't resist us...
It's like she's here for a different reason, this time.
What are you talking about?
Itsumademo motteta yo hagane no you na
I'll always keep mine like this, as hardened as steel
Donna mono mo toosanai kakko na iji wo
With this unshakable will that lets nothing through
Kitto ima mo tachitsukushita mamori no tochuu
I'm sure you are still standing stoutly in defense
Tenshi?!  What are they doing out there?
Teki ga ite atashi wo matteru
There are enemies waiting for me
What should we do?
Hang on a minute.
What's going on?  Something's strange.
What is she doing?
What?!
That's Szechuan Tofu, which is so legendarily spicy none of the students will touch it!
Why is she getting that?!
Is she planning to make us eat it as revenge?
Yurippe-san.  The show is almost at its apex.
Itsumademo issho dakara koibito no you ni
We'll always be together, just like lovers
Your instructions?
Yeah...
Sono toki wa matteita
I've been waiting for that time to come
Start it up!
Start it up, please.
Sono kimochi zenbu kiite yaru
I'll listen to all those feelings
Kimi ni mo kikasu
And I'll let you listen too
Tappuri kikasu
I'll let you listen to them all
Academy Dining Hall,  Food Court
Szechuan Tofu
What the hell?
That's the spicy Szechuan Tofu.  It's famous for nobody ever ordering it.
Even the tough guys have it with some white rice.
This is what I grabbed, so I don't have a choice, do I?
One bite and it's this spicy?!
But... it's good.  Hinata, try some!
Huh?  No way!
Fine, one bite...
It's spicy!  It hurts!
But... the taste that comes afterwards is...
I see, this has a pretty deep flavor to it!
See?!
I'll bet you've never had such delicious Szechuan Tofu, right?
This menu item is surprisingly good.
That's the ticket Tenshi bought.
T-This?
Yep.
All she wanted was to eat this, huh?
This must be her favorite...
I took that simple happiness away from her.
Tenshi is human.
I can't imagine an Angel who would want to eat her favorite food to drown her sorrows.
As the Student Council President, she was just trying to stop us from disrupting order.
Because we created weapons in the Guild, she devised new Guard Skills to counter us.
So, that's all it was.
What a joke.
To think we still have no thread to lead us to God...
Suppose for a minute...
Huh?
With Tenshi the way she is now... couldn't she become our ally?
HUHHH?!
What the hell are you talking about?!
Do you have any idea how many of us have fallen victim to her?!
Uh... well maybe not victim... we're all okay, but...
Do you have any idea how much pain she's put us through?!
That's right!
Sure, she was good today, but we don't know when she'll feel like going against us again!
She'll slit our throats while we're sleeping!
Not your best idea, Otonashi-kun.
Seems that way.
Where did I come up with such a ridiculous proposition?
Itsumo hitori de aruiteta
I've always walked alone
I guess it was because I just imagined her buying the ticket alone,
and then eating her Szechuan Tofu, all by herself.
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turned around, everyone was far away
The image of her having lost both the trust placed on her and her duty...
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
was so lonely...
that it was pitiful.
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
What the hell do you guys want?!
They're normal students.
That's as far as you go.
There's a number of charges I could file, but...
For the time being, for engaging in activities past curfew,
I'll be taking you all to detention.
Now that I'm the Student Council President, I won't be taking it easy on you.
Take them.
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetter/Editor: Nikon
Timer: ar
TLC/QC: Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c95] Take them.
[c3] What's with those guys?
[c45] Ayato Naoi-sama.
[c10] He's the acting Student Council President.
[c29] Doradora Oyaman!
[c222] Aren't you just screwing everything up!?
[c135] Tenshi's existence is necessary.
[c216] You're going against God?
[c117] Hand Sonic: Version 2.
[c296] Will you accept it?
[c57] What are you reconsidering!?
[246] It's those kids.
[c286] God!
[c262] Even your life!  It had to have been real!