What's the name of this Burst Linker who doesn't appear on the list?
Rust Jigsaw.
A different name...
Looks like this little 'un here knows something about this.
Y-Yes.
Actually, another Linker with the exact same ability
showed up on the local network I usually connect to.
What?!
That's not something I can ignore.
Maker, what is Jigsaw's level and type?
He's Level 6, like you.
He's rust-colored, just like his name.
His specialty is hunting close-range avatars
while maintaining a middle-to-long-range distance.
In other words, you'd have a hard time with him.
K. That might be a good thing.
As thanks for your info, I'll tag with this kid and act as bait.
What?
I have no doubts your name will be
good bait, but I dunno about this new guy.
Who exactly is he anyway?
He's probably more famous than me.
He's the silver crow from the revived Nega Nebulous.
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
I was always wide awake
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nita wa no naka de
We are all in similar nets
Found You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I found the wind that day with trembling passion
And All Of My Past subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
And all of my past is a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou furuwasete itai kara
To send my pulse racing
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If I Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
Hey, the leopard of Prominence is fighting!
Why is she teaming up with the crow of Nega?!
Will a solo fighter like Rust Jigsaw come if we're teaming up?
The rumor that you can no longer fly has spread far and wide.
If he's heard about it, it's likely that he'll come and attack.
I see.
If he can take me out straight away,
it'd be a normal one-on-one fight against you.
Something else also occurred to me.
Jigsaw would have to be somewhere in this building in the real world to connect to this local network.
Yes.
Then would it be possible to find his real-world self?
There might be a way.
What way?
I'll explain it later.
More importantly...
Don't use the Incarnate System unless our opponent does.
The Red King said the same thing, but why?
It's for your sake.
Huh?
Incarnation is a power born from the hole in your mind.
You're pulled a little closer to the
hole's darkness each time you use it.
D-Darkness?
Remember fighting the Calamity Armor?
That curse resulted from the first Disaster's will of the mind going berserk.
That's why the kings try to hide the existence of the Incarnate System.
Like Brain Burst itself, the
Incarnate System has two sides to it.
Just like how there's always despair behind hope.
Still, I want to believe in the will of the mind and the power of wishes.
And even Brain Burst, which has saved me.
I see.
It's just as Rain said.
Thanks to you, the Accelerated World will...
He's here.
K, he took the bait.
Jigsaw will try to take you out first
after splitting us up with ranged attacks.
So stay close to me.
R-Roger.
That must've been his long-distance attack, Wheel Saw.
I couldn't see it at all.
We'll have to tell by the sound.
After dodging the next one, close in in one go.
Don't hesitate!
Jump!
Rust Jigsaw.
You aren't going anywhere!
Stop.
What's this?
Good thing you're metal-colored.
S-Sorry.
Is that another of his moves?
Steel Saw.
A move that sets jigsaws in the air.
It blocks our advances while he uses
his long-distance circular saw attacks.
Indeed, he is a close-range avatar's worst enemy.
Wh-What should we do?
Transfer your special move gauge to me.
Huh?
Shape Change.
Get on. Quick.
Wheel Saw!
You handle it.
K!
It's fast, but bullets are faster!
GJ.
Damn it!
Good game.
Get up. We're leaving.
We might be able to identify him.
Huh?
Rust Jigsaw's real self.
I repeatedly dealt damage to Jigsaw's right shoulder.
With that much pain inflicted, the effects will linger on in the real world for a short while.
Look for someone with a seemingly hurt shoulder around the entrance.
O-Okay.
It's him.
Please come!
Crow.
I lost him.
So during the time I was training hard all alone, you had another date with an older woman.
Like I said, that's not what happened.
And at the holy land for duels, too.
If it weren't for this, I would've liked to go too.
Well, you were with Niko the whole time, fighting her.
Too bad she only showed me the alpha and the omega.
She disappeared after telling me to go hunt some Enemies.
Oh, I see.
So did the incarnate training go well?
"Nowhere near good enough to use in a
real battle", in the Red King's own words.
I think I got the gist of it, though.
I see.
That's good, Taku.
Yeah.
Regardless of the result, I think you did well too.
Good work.
Now we just need to wait on the Akihabara BG Matchmaker.
Let's hope that he'll figure out Jigsaw's identity from the real-world description you gave him.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
I guess this won't be so easy after all.
Wait a little longer, Chiyu.
I'll definitely free you from his beck and call.
Let's get started on our debut fight, Lime Bell.
Haru.
I hear Chii-chan teamed up with Noumi and fought in Shinjuku last night.
A 100% win rate?
Yeah.
One of my buddies in Shinjuku told me.
The moment Dusk Taker's gauge filled up and he started aviating, the other duel avatars couldn't do anything.
I see.
He's a long-ranged aviating avatar backed by a healer.
He has completely risen above the principle of
fighting only those of your level and potential.
Noumi...
Damn it!
However, the situation might be even worse than we think.
What do you mean?
Haru, I'm sure we both think this somewhere in our hearts.
No matter how strong Noumi is, as soon as our master,
Black Lotus, returns, she'll solve everything in one stroke.
But...
T-Taku, you're saying Senpai will lose to Noumi?
Obviously I don't want to think this way.
But we need to suppose the worst-case scenario and do all we can by Saturday.
Right, Haru?
Yeah.
Do all we can, huh?
But there's nothing we can do unless we discover how he hides his name from the matching list.
Inbox -
Matchmaker
Matchmaker                Nice to meet you.
Matchmaker                Akihabara BG
Matchmaker                 Rust Jigsaw's Battle History
Matchmaker                 Hope this helps
Refresh Inbox
Compose New Mail
Important Mail
Inbox
Tag
Important Mail
Sent Mail
Drafts
Refresh Inbox
Inbox - Pard-san
Pard-san
Refreshing
You have no new mail.
Looks like Pard-san's group and Matchmaker haven't found anything either.
What?
I've come to talk!
I see.
What did you want to talk about?
Are you skipping training?
Yeah.
Noumi told you to?
What if he did?
You shouldn't!
It's wrong to put Brain Burst ahead of reality!
Coming from you, Haru?
I'm not in a club!
And I've never forgotten to do my homework because of it!
But you spend all of your remaining time...
Hey, let's stop this.
Don't be so serious about it.
It's just a game.
I went up two levels just from
yesterday's fight! Amazing, right?
The gallery spectators said it might've
been the fastest in Brain Burst's history!
Chiyu...
I've already lost count of how many times I got invited to join a Legion.
Feels like I just burst into popularity-
Chiyu!
Stop it!
This isn't like you at all!
You're doing whatever Noumi tells you because of that video, right?
I dragged you into this! It's my fault!
I just played right into his hands and
gave him the means to threaten me...
If he takes you from me as well, I...
I don't know what to do!
You don't understand, Haru.
You don't understand a thing about me!
Even though my avatar obeys Noumi's commands in the Accelerated World,
in the real world, I'm right here...
I'm right where you can touch me if you want.
Yet you still don't understand?
He hasn't taken me away from you.
I'm doing this out of my own will.
I always have, and I always will!
Your own will?
I don't understand what Chiyu's thinking.
But...
Sorry. Put your clothes back on.
I believe in you.
So please believe in me too.
I won't lose to Noumi.
I'm going to get back everything he's taken from me.
Bye.
Yes, there's got to be something else I can do.
Think. Think!
Arita Haruyuki!
Every last bit of info...
Remember every last word and every last detail
since Noumi appeared, study them, and theorize!
It's my only remaining final weapon!
Noumi will never take this from me.
I'm sure there's a clue somewhere.
His secret, his weak point...
There's got to be!
Noumi's secret...
Oh yeah, there's Rust Jigsaw.
If we could just pin him down...
What was that gesture?
I thought he was just pushing someone out of the way, but it's strange.
What's more, it's a gesture I'm familiar with...
It's...
He was moving a virtual window away!
But he wasn't wearing a Neuro Linker.
Could it be another device?
But what apart from a Neuro Linker can...
Retro stuff's pretty useful!
Neuro Linker
Personal-use Communication Terminal「Neuro Linker」
History of the Neuro Linker
As for the devices that preceded the Neuro Linker...
Personal-use Communication Terminal「Neuro Linker」
History of the Neuro Linker
The first VR machine, the NerveGear of the 2020s.
NerveGear
But it's used exclusively for full dives, and the Neuro Linker was the first to integrate with augmented reality.
No, wait.
NerveGear
There was another device in between that made augmented reality possible.
VRengine_devlog
NerveGear
Brain Implant Chip
Neuro Linker
Brain Implant Chip.
I see now.
Noumi, I'm gonna settle things for real this time!
It's game over, Noumi Seiji!
Or should I say, Dusk Taker!
What? Does that mean you'll admit total defeat for real this time?
"I give up, so please stop bullying me", or something?
No, it means the game between us is over!
Senpai, you're pretty dimwitted, aren't you?
There's nothing you or Mayuzumi-senpai can do.
I'll defeat the Black King and rule over this school...
...no, the entire Suginami area.
You can just sit quietly and watch.
I won't let you do that.
You don't show up in matching lists because
you have a second VR machine inside your head!
The illegal Brain Implant Chip!
The Brain Implant Chip: a small bio-chip implanted
between the dura mater and the surface of the cerebrum.
It's an illegal device whose production was discontinued after only 3 years
due to the danger of brain hacking and its usage in entrance exam cheating.
You usually use the Brain Implant Chip to connect
to the school network and take lessons and tests.
You only go online with your
Neuro Linker right before a duel.
That's why you don't show up on matching lists.
A single scan will be enough to reveal the chip, and you'll be expelled.
The chip will be inactivated and disabled.
It's all over for you!
I thought you were a pig, but you're actually a rat.
You're always darting around in the shadows and sniffing around!
You should've crushed me first.
It's your mistake for not doing so.
Well, I'll admit that much.
So what do you want?
We have your voyeur video and my chip.
Are we going to expose each other
and ruin ourselves in the real world?
Have you forgotten, Noumi?
We're Burst Linkers.
There's a fitting way to decide this.
You're saying we should duel?
Good grief.
I can't stand being called a Burst Linker or that whole mentality of yours.
But if that's what you want,
Senpai, then I have no choice.
In that case, though, can I make a suggestion?
A suggestion?
You're probably thinking of something dumb like fighting until one of us loses all his points.
Why don't we settle it all in one go?
With a final duel, the way you like it.
In the Unlimited Field, there's an item that duelers can
charge all their points into, allowing the winner to take it all.
Let's decide this the smart way.
I see.
So that's how things played out.
Yeah.
And I've just sent you the list of conditions Noumi proposed during our negotiation afterwards.
List of Conditions for Final Duel with Noumi
Duel Conditions
The duel will take place in the Unlimited Neutral Field
The duel will be decided by both sides betting every last
Burst Point in a single match
Duel Guarantees
You may take Cyan Pile with you
Until right before the final duel begins, the time can be pushed
back as many times and for as long as you want
What do you think, Taku?
Kendo
Club
I still think accepting his proposal is dangerous.
There's always the danger of being ambushed in the Unlimited Field.
He's letting me come with you,
and this is Noumi we're talking about.
I don't think he's walking into this expecting to lose.
But he said we can change the duel location as many times as we want.
It'll make an ambush impossible to pull off.
Indeed.
They'd either need to have tons of Burst Points,
or the endurance to dive in and
stay there for hours or even months.
Would Noumi have any allies willing to go so far for him?
If he did, I'm sure Noumi would be more of a proper Burst Linker.
You're right.
This is a fight between us Burst Linkers and users of acceleration, like Noumi.
It's about the dignity that defines us.
Right?
All right. Let's fight this final duel!
Taku.
Let's end all of this before Senpai comes back!
It's the moment of truth!
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I couldn't grasp anything as I flapped my wings
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kogareru no mo zenbu
I also long for your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Consolidation.
A black flash cuts through the despair.
It's a sign of the strong bond
that consolidates them.