So you want to take my points already?
You want me to just lose to you and pay up today's portion?
You're a lot more imposing in your duel avatar, Senpai.
Though in the real world, you're still under my foot.
Dusk Taker.
I've never heard of that name before,
but his level is surprisingly high.
I see!
You've been luring other Burst Linkers
into traps and grasping their weaknesses,
then you threaten them and
force them to provide Burst Points!
That's how you've been leveling up
without fighting, am I right?!
It's exactly as you said, Senpai.
But before I take your points this time, I'll have you hand over one more thing.
Hand over?
That's right.
It's something very important to you.
Well, a stage has been laid out for us.
Shall we fight?
If you think you can beat me just as
easily in this world, go ahead and try!
Noumi Seiji!
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
My hopes are always dashed
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nikawa no naka de
We are all suspended in a gel
Find You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I'll find the wind that day with trembling passion
Ato mo mata subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
Everything to come is all a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou wo kuruwasete itai kara
To send my heart into overdrive
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If You Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
Well? How's this?!
You're obsessed with your dirty schemes in the real world
and won't use anything else to reach the top in Brain Burst!
You have no right to call yourself a Burst Linker!
One last attack and it's over!
I've fought against enemies like you before,
but none of them have been able to stop me!
I'll just drag you around and chip away at your HP...
Damn it!
Why now?!
You're a lot better than I had thought, Senpai.
Though there'd be no point in making you my dog otherwise.
You can regenerate?
Just like a lizard's tail...
It's more like an octopus or a sea anemone.
The previous owner said it was a starfish, though.
What? The previous owner?
I already said I'd have you hand over something important to you.
This is what I meant.
Demonic Commandeer!
Huh?
My HP gauge didn't go down...
Does Noumi's special move have a time lag?
Then...
I'll just fly up and smash you into the ground!
What are you doing, Senpai?
N-No way!
My wings won't come out!
Well, you see...
This is what happened.
I've taken your aviation ability, Arita-senpai!
Th-That can't be true.
It can't!
No no, it's true.
Look.
Until now, no duel avatar has
ever achieved true aviation ability.
You're the one who will change this world.
But she told me!
I'm the only one who can fly in this world.
Those wings belong only to me...
It's all I have...
It's my...
What are you mumbling about?
How creepy.
This is my only special move, Demonic Commandeer.
It lets me steal one of my opponent's
special moves, Enhanced Armaments, or abilities.
By the way, there's no time limit to my special move.
In other words, it's permanent, but there's a limit to how much I can keep at a time.
There's no time limit? It's permanent?!
Does that mean he'll have my wings forever?
No way...
Give them back.
Give them back!
Don't worry. I'll give them back.
You'll get them back the day you graduate from Umesato Junior High if you keep giving me points every week.
No way...
This can't be real.
With that said and done...
Right, this is a dream!
Once I wake up, I'm sure...
I'll be taking this week's portion.
Thank you very much, Arita-senpai.
Now we know who's superior in both
the real world and the Accelerated World.
Since you're the lowest of the low and I stand
far above you, it's only natural that you'd serve me.
That's how this world works.
You too, Kurashima-senpai.
Don't forget about your promise to be my pet.
Oh, right.
It should be obvious, but don't tell
Mayuzumi-senpai or your boss about this.
I need a little more time to prepare before I can face them.
Bye.
Haru.
Why?
Why did this happen?
Why did he have to say such horrible things?!
Sorry, Chiyu.
I dragged you into this...
Sorry you had to get so scared.
But...
There's...
There's nothing I can do.
He took my wings.
I-I can't fight anymore.
I'm nothing now!
No...
I don't want this!
It's all going to break!
Just when...
Just when the three of us were finally back to how we used to be...
Just when... Just when...!
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Talk
Monitor
Play
Volume
Menu
Taku.
Why aren't you telling me anything?
Chii-chan told me to ask you, but you say nothing happened.
Is it something you can't tell me?
I see.
I'll stop asking if you really can't tell me.
But let me know just this.
What is Chii-chan to you?
How can you leave her alone when she's crying in pain?
Isn't she our friend? Our best friend?!
I'm not leaving her alone!
And anyway, you're the one who sent me
that photo with the visual masking program!
Girls' Shower Room
Boys' Shower Room
If you had noticed the file was way too large, this wouldn't have happened!
What about you?
What do you think of Chiyu?
Why don't you do something about this first before giving me this crap?!
I want to.
I really do...
You like Chiyu, don't you?
You want to be her boyfriend again, don't you?!
Then-
That's right! I like her!
I like her more than anybody else!
I want to let her do what she wants because I like her!
Until Chii-chan gives me an answer, I could wait forever!
Wait? So you're waiting?
That's right.
And what will you do if her answer isn't you?
What will you do if she chooses someone else?!
Then I'd accept it!
If it'd make Chii-chan happy...
Even if the person she chooses is you...
I'd be fine with that!
Do you really mean that?
Yeah.
Then what?
Are you saying you'll let me have Chiyu?
Huh?
Or could it be that you like Princess Snow Black now?
What am I saying?
That's why you're bringing me and Chiyu together.
No! I don't mean this!
It's so you can get Senpai!
Is that what you want?!
Haru.
Didn't we promise not to keep anything from each other anymore?
Am I really that difficult to trust?!
N-No...
Haru...
Sorry for hitting you.
Oh, right.
This game got released already.
Maybe I'll buy it.
I'll put it into my Neuro Linker
and devote myself to playing it.
If it needs a lot of space, I could delete that program.
That ridiculously large Brain Burst program.
That's right, I should just delete it.
Noumi's plan would fail and he
wouldn't be able to threaten Chiyu.
It's perfectly fine.
Things would just go back to how they were.
Back to when I was the lowest of the low and bullied by Araya and his friends...
I'm just losing something that I temporarily got.
I just need to pretend like I never had it to begin with.
Don't worry. I'll give them back.
You'll get them back the day you graduate from Umesato Junior High if you keep giving me points every week.
Ugh, damn it!
I admit it.
I admit that you win, Noumi Seiji!
Shibuya Station
The next stop is Sasazuka 2nd Street. Sasazuka 2nd Street.
Anyway, I need to earn points by fighting and winning.
Sasazuka 2nd Street
Next Stop:
I'll soon be in Green Legion territory.
Sasazuka 2nd Street
Next Stop:
As for my opponent...
Sasazuka 2nd Street
Next Stop:
...it doesn't matter who!
The Post-Apocalypse stage.
Hey hey hey, let's get together~
Mega long time no see, you!
A-Ash-san...
Whaddup?
Missed me enough to come all the way to Bitter Valley, you?
Bitter Valley?
Dude, get the joke. Understand!
I'm talkin' about Shibuya, dumbass! Shibuya!
Uh...
What's that?
You're no fun, you!
I think bitter translates to "nigai" and not "shibui"...
Huh?
Seriously really?!
Seriously really.
"Bitter Valley" would be Nigaya, not Shibuya...
Huh? What's "shibui" in English, then?
U-Uh, "rough", I guess?
Mm.
Rough Valley.
Who gives a shit about that anyway?!
But you asked...
Enough! Shaddup!
Don't get all cocky just 'cause
you have more wins than me, you!
Check this out and tremble!
Huh? M-Missiles?
Yes, I do!
Homing missiles y'know, you flying bastard!
Well, get flying.
And get ready to cry!
Wait, why aren't your wings out?
We're starting, y'know!
Something happened, so I'll be
fighting you on the ground today.
Well, that's cool.
But you'll be cryin' if you take me lightly!
Let's dance!
I've fought Ash-san many times.
The trick to beating him is...
...this!
Hey hey hey! Did you see that, you?
That was my new technique.
V-Twin Fists, man!
Huh?
I thought I'd be able to win...
...but I really can't without my wings.
Yo, what was that, Crow?
It wasn't that damaging, right?
Why ain't you flying?
Because I can't.
Huh?
So it's fine.
Finish me off.
I just wanted to test how much I could fight without my wings.
I learned that I can't, so...
Please end this.
I don't really get what's happening,
but you're basically saying your wings
won't come out, so you can't fly and win,
and that's why you'll just lie there?
There's no point in getting back up on my feet.
You remember?
When we fought the second time, you lifted up the back of my bike.
Yes.
You really got me there.
You pretty much disabled my bike, my biggest weapon.
But did I just give up right there?
You didn't, but...
I won't get my wings back.
You still have your bike to
fight with, so you won't understand.
You suck!
You giga-suck!
No, you tera-suck, loser!
D'you have any idea how I felt
when I saw you fly for the first time?
And it wasn't just me. All the other Burst Linkers were the same!
Where you at right now?
Huh?
I'm askin' you where you dived from.
Koushuu Highway.
I'm on a bus.
'Kay, we'll end this duel as a draw right away.
Go straight home and get up there at 9!
Up there?
The Unlimited Neutral Field, dumbass!
Wh-Where exactly are we going?!
It's right there, man.
Look.
You mean the old Tokyo Tower?
Very yes!
Very yes?
What will we be doing there?
Well uh, y'know.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Someone?
To cut to the chase, it's my Parent.
Your Parent?
My Parent stepped back from all the dueling
a long time ago, so you probably don't know.
But way back then, the names of "Iron Arm"
and "ICBM" sent chills down everyone's spines.
I-ICBM?
My Parent had another nickname: "Icarus".
That doesn't sound very scary.
Until you came around, my Parent was the Burst Linker closest to the sky in the Accelerated World.
What are you doing, Ash-san?
Shut your mouth. I'm waiting for the wind to stop.
The wind?
Hell yeah, it's here!
All right, we're goin'!
Hold me tight!
Vertical Climb Setup!
You're joking!
You forgot about my wall-driving ability, you?
Oh right, you did drive up a building once.
Shit! Shit this wind!
Firmly hold me tight!
I don't get what you're saying!
Fly high!
Hell yeah! We got here safely!
I won't ride anything with less than four wheels ever again!
You're clueless, you.
Bikes are fun because they can fall over.
Falling over was the least of our worries just now!
Yo, get off the bike.
Oh, right.
This person is Ash-san's Parent?
It's been a long time, Ash.
I'm happy to know that you haven't forgotten about me.
L-Long time no see, master!
I would never, never ever forget about you!
Huh? It's not "mega long time no see"?
You must be Silver Crow.
Y-Yes!
N-Nice to meet you!
The honor is mine.
My name is Sky Raker.
I'm glad I could meet you, Crow-san.
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I was unable to grasp anything as I looked up
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kotaerareru no mo zenbu
I can live up to your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Imagination.
Guided by a sky-blue imagination,
Haruyuki aims for the sky once again.