I see.
Oh, I have to go.
We'll hang up here.
See you.
DISPLAY
Five more days, huh?
Princess.
No, I can't.
He wouldn't want me to be feeling down during my trip.
Princess?
All right.
I'll count to three and cheer up.
Hey...
One.
Princess, hello?
Two.
Three-
M-Megumi?!
What was that for?!
Well, I kept calling you but you didn't notice me.
We need to head back soon
for the sea kayak tour, Princess.
O-Oh, I see.
Sorry, I'll pass on the tour.
I'm not exactly... feeling very well.
I'll pass on it too, then.
Megumi?
Uh... yeah!
It's been a family rule for generations
to never get on a ship with no lifeboat.
Were your ancestors the passengers of
some shipwrecked luxury liner or something?
So good!
We are all protagonists of our own life stories.
This is true for me, Taku, and Chiyu.
Even my mom is the protagonist of her own life story.
Of course, Princess Snow Black is no different.
Well, her story is definitely
closer to a real drama than mine.
This took place in April 2047.
While Dusk Taker-Noumi Seiji-was toying around with Taku, Chiyu, and me in Tokyo,
this is what happened to Princess Snow Black during her school trip to Okinawa.
It's a story I don't know about.
It's been forever since I've seen that expression on your face!
Forever?
Yeah.
Since we first met, you've always
looked like you were lost or something.
That stopped when you met him last fall.
But now you're back to looking like you want to return.
Not to Tokyo, but to some other world.
Megumi?
You have another world that I can't see, right?
And that's probably where the real you is.
Am I right?
The real me?
Wanna find out?
Wh-What are you doing?
Come on, don't move, Princess.
But...
What exactly are you-
I'll show you another world you still don't know about!
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
I was always wide awake
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nita wa no naka de
We are all in similar nets
Found You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I found the wind that day with trembling passion
And All Of My Past subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
And all of my past is a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou furuwasete itai kara
To send my pulse racing
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If I Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
I'm really sorry, Princess.
I don't know why I did it.
Forgive me!
I know we're on a school trip,
but you're way too excited, Megumi.
But you always seem to be busy recently.
At least on this trip, I thought...
I thought I could have you all to myself, so I...
I forgive you, but never do that again.
Okay, I'll try really hard!
Geez, all that stuff about another world and the real me...
It's like you're hinting at something.
Oh? The stuff about another world is true.
It's something even I can relate to.
What?
There was this book I loved when I was really young.
In that book's world, there were always new encounters and adventures.
No matter how many times I reread the book, I'd never get tired of it.
But one day, that book disappeared.
Now I can't even remember
the title or contents of that book.
There was an incantation on the first page that you had to recite to continue.
I'm sure I'll never enter that world again unless I remember the incantation.
I see, so it was a fairy tale from your childhood.
Is that your other world?
Yep.
Maybe I joined the literature club because I wanted to reproduce that story myself.
Is that working out?
Not at all.
Shop:  Okinawan Donuts
Is something wrong, Princess?
No, well... you know.
Are you sure you don't need to buy any souvenirs?
Yeah.
Unfortunately for me, I don't have
a guy in Tokyo waiting for my return.
I-I see. Then...
I know! Let's try this.
We'll buy each other a souvenir during this trip
and exchange them when we're back at school.
Like a surprise present, right?
That's a pretty good idea coming from you!
Coming from me?
Yep!
But that's not something we can do if we're shopping together.
Why don't we split up for a bit...
...and meet back up at the hotel entrance 30 minutes later, at 4?
O-Okay.
Let's do that.
I'll find something that'll give you the biggest surprise you'll have this year!
A surprise, huh?
I'm looking forward to it.
A duel? In Okinawa?!
The Old Castle stage, huh?
But there's something different about it.
Is this difference unique to the Okinawan area?
It ain't the Old Castle stage!
It's the Okinawan Castle stage!
W-Wait, Ruka-chan!
Hmm.
You must be one of those school trip
students staying at that hotel.
And you two are Burst Linkers living in this area?
You betcha-
I mean, obviously!
My Okinawan ancestry goes way back!
M-Mine too, pretty much.
That's surprising.
Burst Linkers this far out, and more than one too...
Very interesting!
Cool, you're ready to go!
Let's fight, you and me!
C-Careful, Ruka-chan.
She's Level 9!
Heh, that's nothing!
She's just two levels higher than our master.
No way...
She created a hole in the battle field ground...
Th-That's enough, Ruka-chan!
Let's just go with her!
I'm not done yet!
An Okinawan warrior can't lose to a mainland samurai!
Tidal Wave!
Death by...
...Barraging!
I lost...
Mm, it was a nice fight.
Your feint and kick was especially good.
It'd be even better if you could connect them more smoothly.
Right.
I'll work on improving it, Big Sis!
W-Wait, Ruka-chan.
We still haven't addressed the main issue!
Oh right. I totally forgot!
Big Sis, I have a favor to ask
of someone as skilled as you.
Please hear us out!
Well, I can certainly hear what you have to say...
Cheers muchly!
Well then, Big Sis.
There's a cafe called Sabani down this shopping street.
Let's meet at a table there
a minute from now in the real world!
Hey, wait right there!
Meet in the real world?
I thought you were the ones who asked me to come here.
Soz!
Um... it's just that you're a real looker!
O-Oh, she means you're really pretty.
Um... I'm Asato Ruka of Class 2-2 from Kube Junior High.
I-I'm Itosu Mana of Class 1-3 from the same school.
Nice to meet you!
Wait, wait a minute!
D-Did you just tell me your real names?
Of course.
Geez...
When you said to meet in the real world, I was wary that you might've been plotting something...
What's the matter, Onee-sama?
Um...
Did your master not teach you
some rules regarding Brain Burst?
Ready, go!
One! Don't use acceleration to do anything bad!
Two! Don't talk about acceleration to just anyone!
That's all!
That's all?
Yes! That's all!
Looks like I'll need to have a word with your so-called master.
Really, Big Sis?!
Yay! We were wondering
how to ask you the entire time!
Wh-What?
We'd like you to meet our master!
So Ruka-kun's the Child of a Burst Linker who moved down here from Tokyo, and Mana-kun's the Child of Ruka-kun.
Yes.
There's only the three of us now,
but we want to expand our circle so Okinawa will one day
have a larger accelerated community than Tokyo.
That's right.
But something happened recently that might crush our dream.
Our master tried to face the problem at first
but seems to have completely given up now.
What happened?
We don't really understand either, to be honest.
Our master said a monster appeared...
That's why we'd like you to help our master.
Please!
I know you're desperate, but I can't say yes if I don't know what this monster is.
So in order to find out more about it, I guess I can see...
...your master.
Yay!
You were right, Mana!
What?
Let's go to my house right now!
Wait, wait!
Can we not do this in the real world?
Since your master's from Tokyo, we might've met before in the Accelerated World.
Oh, you're worried about that?
But I guess something crazy would happen if our master saw a real looker like you!
Oh no!
Ah, Princess!
Sorry I'm late.
Don't worry about it.
I barely made it myself!
I couldn't decide, and when I thought about how you were probably having difficulty choosing as well,
I got really happy and didn't notice the time...
Sorry, Megumi.
I wasn't able to pick out your present.
That's okay. The trip's only just begun.
You still have plenty of time to get me something.
But I promised to...
Really, I'm fine.
It's just that...
Huh?
Oh no, I didn't mean to...
Sorry, I don't know why I'm...
Megumi...
I-I'll go back to the room first.
Feel free to relax until free time's over.
Wait, Megumi!
Sorry, Megumi.
I was a fool.
It's not your fault.
I'm just really embarrassed that
I got way too excited over nothing.
Please, Princess.
Leave me alone for just 30 minutes.
I'll be back to my usual self afterwards.
Megumi, listen to me.
What you said at the beach today was correct.
There's another world that I have,
where time flows at a different rate.
I've spent a lot of time in that world
ever since I first set foot in it 7 years ago.
So much time that I don't know
which world is reality anymore.
Because of that, in time, I grew unsure of where I belonged to,
and even the purpose for my
existence became vague to me.
But you're the one who saved me when I was hopelessly lost.
Ever since you asked me to have lunch with you after the school entrance ceremony,
you've kept me well and tightly bound to the real world.
I've lost many of the bonds I'd made in the other world, though I'm trying my best to slowly rebuild them.
But my only real world bond is with you.
You're my only friend, Megumi.
Princess...
Megumi.
Thank you, Princess.
What you just said made me really happy.
But I'm sorry...
You don't need to apologize for anything.
I'm the one who forgot to buy you a souvenir.
That's not it.
I should've apologized to you
for something a long time ago.
Back then, I-
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Umesato Junior High:
School Trip Executive Committee
「  Regular Meeting  」
Huh? I...
P-Princess, I'm sorry!
I can't believe I forgot about the committee meeting!
I'll get ready real quick, so wait for me a bit.
I told you not to lose yourself in the Accelerated World and neglect the real world like I knew it all,
but I made Megumi so sad.
Looks like I have a long way to go, Haruyuki-kun.
I'm sure you're in a sticky situation right now.
But I won't act until you ask me to.
Do your best, Haruyuki-kun.
And over here, I'll do what a Burst Linker is supposed to.
Hey!
Big Sis!
Do we really need to do this?
The Sabani would've been good-
Don't be stupid.
If you dive up there without disconnection safety, what'll you do if you can't get to a portal?!
No problem at all!
It'll work out somehow!
If it comes to it, the waitresses will just unplug our Neuro Linkers!
Just listen to me! Got it?
I'll see your master as promised, but I can't guarantee what happens afterwards.
In the worst case scenario,
there might even be a fight.
Okay!
We'll dive in on the count of five.
Five, four, three...
Big Sis, wait.
Wh-What is it?
A trance.
Her Yuta blood comes forth.
Yuta? Is she an Okinawan shaman?
Mana was born with a gift.
I need another one, Onee-sama.
Another what?
This cord.
O-Oh...
Where do I plug it in?
Just leave it somewhere there.
Huh?
Just do as she says, Big Sis.
Well, let's go in this time.
Unlimited Burst!
The Weathered stage, huh?
So, where's your master?
This way!
A shop all the way out here?
Hiya, master!
Oh. Yo, hiya.
Geez, drinking so much in the middle of the day...
You're just like an Okinawan
old man with that habit of yours!
I'm not an old man!
I'm still a high school freshman.
Owner, gimme another glass of 300-year-old kusu liquor.
Geez, this isn't the time for drinking!
We've brought someone who can help us.
What? You seriously want a street duel?
It's no use, man!
No use, no use, no use...
I mean, one or two helpers ain't gonna
make a difference against that monster.
Hey, you.
I'm Level 7 and I couldn't do a thing.
Even a Level 8 wouldn't be able to defeat him, man.
You'd need to bring me a Level 9 king or something!
Hey, let me see your face!
Actually, even a king would have trouble!
You'd need a physical attack specialist like Vanquish, or maybe even World End herself.
I said hey!
What's the matter with you?!
I already said I ain't gonna budge unless I see the Black King...
I thought it'd be you.
It's been a while, Kurikin.
Wait... no way.
I need a time out.
Those legs, that appearance, and calling me Kurikin...
N-No way!
The real thing? In the flesh?!
The Black King, Black Lotus?!
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I couldn't grasp anything as I flapped my wings
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kogareru no mo zenbu
I also long for your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Revolution.
A pure prayer calls forth a revolution,
and a lost tale is resurrected.