Well, my mom and dad divorced suddenly, so I ended up moving to Okinawa.
I already expected it, but I couldn't
find a single Burst Linker anywhere.
I got pretty depressed about it.
I see.
You've done well to remain as a Burst Linker until now, Crikin.
Well, half of it was just letting things run their course.
This girl's my relative, and I ended up staying at her place.
I decided to gamble on something.
If I managed to copy and install the program into Ruka,
I'd give her all the Burst Points I had
at the time and get her up to Level 4.
Looks like you won your gamble.
Yeah.
The two of us slowly accumulated
enough points to try another gamble.
Miraculously, Mana's installation of the program was successful,
and here we are.
I see.
Looks like Enemy hunting is a real lifeline over here.
Outside!
What's that?
That's the giant monster, Big Sis.
It goes around eating everybody.
Please place your roomkey over the reader.
Room key No. 728 OK!
Door Unlocked.
Hateshinai sora wo yuku
I fly up to the boundless sky
Mienai tsubasa ga michibiku
My invisible wings will guide me
Haruka kanata bokura wo matsu
The faraway place awaits us
Mada minu mirai e to
We head towards an unseen future
UTW Presents
Accel World
Always samekitteta
I was always wide awake
Hayasugiru Day And Night
The days and nights pass too quickly
Toumei na yami ni kakomare
Enveloped in the transparent darkness
Daremo nita wa no naka de
We are all in similar nets
Found You ano hi no kaze yureugoita Passion
I found the wind that day with trembling passion
And All Of My Past subete kimi ni au tame no Process datta ne
And all of my past is a process to meet you
Slowly Open Up My Eyes Within The Blackness
Kanata kara kikoeru yokan ni
I want the premonition I heard from afar
Kodou furuwasete itai kara
To send my pulse racing
It's Unlimited, It's Unlimited
If I Can Believe Myself Again
Hikari no naka mezamete yuku
I wake gradually within the light
Shinjite kureta kimi to nara
If I'm with you, who had faith in me
Never Let It Go, Never Lose My Way
Koko de umarekawaru keshiki
The view here is born anew
Kizu sae ima hokori ni naru
Even past wounds are now my pride
Dakara kimi to Burst The Gravity
So together, we'll burst the gravity
Please, Lotus.
Take Ruka and Mana and use the
hotel's Leave Point to escape right now.
Do we really need to do that?
You see, Lotus, that's no ordinary Enemy.
That legendary Enemy has been tamed.
Are you saying it's someone's familiar?
Who would do something like that?
I don't know.
What?
We've checked the matching list many times,
but we could never find a name.
That's why its rider must be a monster too.
A small monster.
An opponent that doesn't appear on the matching list?
Here it comes!
The three of you should escape.
There are a few things I'd like to ask that monster.
Also, retreating without crossing blades just isn't my style.
You haven't changed at all, World End.
I guess I'll go with you.
It's great that the monster came to the
metal-rich town in the Weathered stage, after all.
Plus, no matter how big of a monster that is,
we've got a king on our side. Things'll work out~
It's coming.
What is this anyway?
The official name of this legendary Enemy is Nidhogg.
I call him Nick though.
You there, who are you?!
It's against our rules to needlessly reveal our names, but...
Nice to meet you, Black King.
And you local folks.
I'm Sulfur Pot.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
A backdoor program.
What could that be?
I knew it.
That program should've been disabled from an update.
You must be using a similar type of cheating technology.
What's more, you probably aren't in Okinawa right now.
You're diving remotely from Tokyo.
Am I right?
Wh-What?!
No way!
No! That's not fair!
I see, I see.
Even though you've been in hiding these
past few years, you're just as feisty as ever.
In that case, I'll have to get rid of you here, Black King.
It'd suck if our Frontier Farming experiment suffered a setback in your hands.
Frontier Farming, huh?!
He's probably using cheating tools to set up a hunting ground in this Henoko area for low-level Enemies.
The big Legions wouldn't notice what's going on here.
Sulfur Pot.
Don't think that the title of "Legend Slayer" belongs exclusively to the Blue King.
I'm going to cut open both your ride and your devious tricks!
What words.
Killing you the normal way wouldn't be enough.
Let's see if you can keep acting tough
when Nick bites off your limbs one by one!
Crikin, you should be able to use your powers to their fullest extent here.
Right?
You can count on me.
My apprentices!
Find as many metal objects as you can from the rubble and pile them all here at this intersection!
Huh? We wanna fight too-
Understood, master!
Collect scrap metal, right?
Leave it to us!
Do your best!
The outcome of this battle depends on how much metal you can find!
Here he comes.
Eat this, bastard!
Tapping Screw!
Huh?!
Crikin!
There's no way those half-ass flying screws would work against a heavily armored legend-type!
W-Well, it's been three years
since I've fought in a real battle.
Come on!
I'll have Nick trample you to death if you don't perk up!
Go ahead and try!
Overdrive!
Mode Green!
Your petty little tricks won't work on him!
Go, Nick!
Not yet...
Not yet.
Now!
Ugh!
Go, Nick!
Big Sis! Master!
This is most of the big stuff!
Crikin!
It's finally time for the real deal!
Huh? Someone's running away?
What a waste.
Nick's special move gauge just finished charging too.
What's that? A special move gauge?
You didn't know?
Tamed high-level Enemies have their own special move gauges.
It's fully charged right now too.
All right, Nick!
Scorching Inferno!
Lotus! Over here!
Metal, become dyed in my color!
Megamachine Awakening!
There's nothing you can do now, scum!
I'll reduce you and the Black King to ashes!
Huh?
He's so big!
Our master...
Our master's a giant!
I'm gonna vaporize that heap of junk!
Nick!
More! More power!
Wh-What?!
Go!
Retreat, Nick!
You're amazing, master!
Until the current Red King showed up,
he was the one with the strongest long-distance firepower in the Accelerated World's history.
How dare you...
How dare you damage Nick this badly!
One more time, Nick!
Charcoal Smoke!
This smell...
This is bad!
Run, Crikin!
This smoke is...
Scorching Inferno!
...gunpowder!
Where's Crikin?
I didn't expect to have to use that trick here.
We don't emerge from it unhurt either, you know.
But Nick did just as he was told.
Do you understand now?
The two of us are one, of one flesh, the greatest partners!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Looks like the dragon has something to tell you.
You're a king all right. You're even a sore loser of the highest order!
Just saying, but Nick's special move gauge hasn't been used up yet.
Don't worry, Onee-sama.
It's coming.
There's another world that I have,
where time flows at a different rate.
If I unplug this, Princess will return to me.
She'll come back to where I can reach her.
Don't!
That's a door.
A door inviting you to another world one last time.
Go.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
You are now cabling by wire to a Neuro Linker.
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
Unlimited Burst.
Princess, I'm here.
No way...
M-Megumi, is that you?!
Impossible...
How could this happen?
In the past, was Megumi also a Burst Linker?
Was she summoned back into this world through some kind of logic?
What? What the hell's with all of you?!
I'm gonna reduce you all to cinders!
Charcoal Storm!
Th-This is bad!
Don't worry.
I'll protect you, Princess.
Paradigm Revolution.
This is... no way...
A forced Transition...
Nick, light 'em up!
Blow them all away!
Scorching...
The Ocean stage...
Princess.
Magic time is over.
Well, Princess.
Live out your life story facing forward.
I won't look back anymore either.
I will.
Thank you, Megumi.
H-Help me!
I can't swim!
Sorry, but sink down just for a while, Crikin.
You fought bravely earlier.
Master, seeya later!
All right.
Dolphin and Merrow, we're on the brink of victory.
Let's finish this in one go before he escapes to some island.
Okay!
I'll go fight the dragon head on.
You two attack from the sides,
making sure you aren't targeted.
No worries, Big Sis.
This is the sea, after all!
You can count on us in the water!
Ready, go!
Shape Change!
Marine Mode!
You scum!
What are you doing?!
Onee-sama, please cut the dragon's reins!
All right. I got this!
Death By Piercing!
Nick, that's right! Over here!
Bite those annoying brats to pieces!
What?! No way!
Nick, I'm your master!
No way! Stop, stop!
Well done, Dolphin and Merrow.
You fought wonderfully.
Big Sis.
I'll become stronger, okay?
I'm going to practice and study to get stronger.
And one day, I'll...
Yes, get stronger.
I'll be waiting for the next time we meet in this world.
Me too!
I get the feeling we forgot something though.
Save me, please.
Whatever! It's fine!
I'm just a useless screw anyway!
Sorry, I completely forgot.
I'm sorry, master!
You're all heartless!
Well, it's about time you guys headed back.
Okay!
Oh, before you go, Lotus.
Take this.
I found it at the bottom of the sea.
Take it as a token of my appreciation.
Oh?
Enhanced Armament: Mystical Reins.
Ah.
I don't have any use for this though.
Don't say that.
I hear there are some pretty interesting Enemies,
like flying horses, in the northern part of Okinawa.
Please take it, Onee-sama.
I'm sure the time'll come when you'll need it.
Is that Yuta's message?
All right, I'll accept it with gratitude.
Well, I'll get going now.
Go easy on him.
Yeah.
Sulfur Pot.
Once you revive, you're going to tell me everything you know.
Big Sis!
Onee-sama!
Come to Okinawa again sometime!
Take care!
Ready, go!
Cheerio!
You managed to get such cute fans even during your trip.
Nice one, Princess.
They weren't my fans.
It's more of a cultural exchange thing...
Yeah, yeah.
I'll write that down in the student council log then.
Uh, that wouldn't be good...
After that fight, Megumi woke up in the dive cafe without remembering a thing.
About why she was there, about Brain Burst. Everything.
I won't press the matter though.
Just like how I have my own story, Megumi may have once had her own story with that world as her stage.
That's fine for now.
Receiving Mail
New mail has been received
I managed to find it in the dive cafe you directed me to.
It's a remodeled illegal linker that could
link you up even without being worn.
Unfortunately, the memory had self-destructed and there's nothing we can scavenge from it.
If Brain Burst was installed in it along with a backdoor, in theory it's possible to do what Sulfur Pot did.
They're total lowlifes if they seriously did that though.
You know, that organization he talked about.
An organization, huh?
Sulfur Pot didn't tell us anything about them in the end.
Will we have to fight them someday?
Well, we'll simply crush them
mercilessly when the time comes.
What is it, Princess?
You look like you're having fun.
R-Really?
Hey, Princess.
Hmm?
I think I'll write a story set in Okinawa when I get back to Tokyo.
A story about the sea, a dragon,
a mermaid, and a black swordsman.
I had a dream about it last night.
I'll obviously be the first to read it, right?
Okay, but you'd better be ready!
It'll probably be pretty long.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm also can't wait to open the gift you bought me.
I wonder what you got me.
According to my cosmic intuition...
You can't, Princess!
What'll we do if you guess correctly?!
I see it! It's...
Geez, stop it already!
If you don't, I'll grope you!
M-Megumi?!
Will this do?
Would you like it wrapped up?
It's a present, right?
Yes, please.
Yes, it's for a friend.
A very valuable friend.
Nobashita te to risou wa tooku
My ideals are well beyond my reach
Aoginagara nanimo tsukamenai mama
I couldn't grasp anything as I flapped my wings
Sagashimotomete ita kotae wo
I abandoned the answer I had been searching for
Okizari ni shite minai furi wo shite ita
And pretended I didn't see anything
Hitorikiri datta watashi wa mirai no
I used to be all alone
Imi wo machigaete ita hitei shitemo
I misunderstood what the future meant, even in my denial
Kimi no ude wa atatakai yo zenbu
Your arms are full of warmth
no ude wa
Hontou no ai hontou no yasashisa dakara
Because it's all true love and true kindness
Kimi no ishi ni kogareru no mo zenbu
I also long for your will
no ishi ni
Hontou no omoi hontou no tsuyosa dakara
Because it's all true affection and true strength
Kono kimochi wo tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
Next stage: Domination.
Noumi's domination grows stronger.
What decision does Haruyuki make
while deep in despair?