Count Cruhteo?
Yes. His eldest son inherited the title.
Klancain...
He is reputed to be extremely loyal to the emperor.
By now the knights are split clean into those on my side and those on the emperor's.
If we can convince him to join us,
perhaps the others will rethink their allegiance.
I agree.
It will depend on whether or not he is truly trustworthy.
Deucalion, launch!
All ahead, dead slow!
We will leave the Earth's atmosphere and ascend to the satellite belt.
Our destination is Parnassos Base!
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
The target of the attack is the enemy moon base.
Princess Asseylum is in their stronghold.
As there is a Landing Castle in close proximity to the moon base
which would likely shelter her in the event of an attack,
both fortifications will need
to be attacked simultaneously.
Consequently, our forces will be split for this operation.
Breton Platoon and the Deucalion
will attack the Landing Castle at 2200 UTC.
Once we have confirmation that the moon base
has sent out its garrison to defend the Landing Castle,
Trakehner Platoon will approach under cover
of the numerous asteroids in the area and strike.
This mission is designated Operation Lunar Gate.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I should have been more vigilant.
No.
It is I who must shoulder the blame.
None of this would have happened without my actions.
But, Your Highness...
Exactly.
If you weren't around, if you'd stayed unconscious,
then I would have had everything under control.
Nobody wept for you,
and he would not be as confused as he is now.
You care deeply for Slaine, don't you?
And you? What about you?
Who do you care for?
I am devoted to the world of Vers and its people.
That is what I was taught, and how I lived.
I pity you.
We will attack the Landing Castle together with Breton Platoon.
We will form one half of the operation,
the other being the attack on the moon base.
This is the mission we've been given by HQ.
A two-pronged operation, huh?
So we're basically only there to divide their forces.
Sounds to me like we're just bait.
However, I have no intention of quietly accepting that role.
I want everyone present to come back alive so that we can all celebrate on Earth.
Don't be reckless.
Dismissed.
All hands, to your stations.
Captain?
I had a feeling you'd want to talk to me.
I would like to speak with you too.
I apologize for the delay.
You've come a very long way to offer your condolences over the death of my father.
We are a great distance from Vers.
My condolences for your father and my congratulations for your succession are long overdue.
I fear I must apologize for failing to congratulate you on your own succession, Count Cruhteo.
Please, call me Klancain.
I am still unaccustomed to my father's title.
Very well.
Princess Asseylum was looking forward to seeing you again after so long, but...
I was given to understand
that she is not in good health.
It's nothing grave, but she should be given time to recuperate.
I am deeply indebted to your father.
Was he not hard on you?
He was a painfully austere man.
He taught me many valuable things.
I doubt that I would be standing here right now were it not for him.
I saw the Tharsis.
I am glad that it has been of use to you.
Also, I heard en route that you had proclaimed your intention to found a new kingdom here.
It was Princess Asseylum's wish.
Was it also His Imperial Majesty's?
As I understand, his health is failing.
He has the best doctors,
equipped with the best medical technology.
There is no need to worry about him.
I am glad to hear that.
If we should see Princess Asseylum's wishes come to fruition,
I am sure His Majesty would be overjoyed as well.
One would hope so.
If you were to assist us in our struggles, Lord Klancain,
it would bolster morale a great deal.
I am looking forward...
to seeing how your new kingdom will affect the future of Vers.
We noticed a number of asteroids behaving erratically.
It would appear objects of different density are in their shadow.
Camouflage, huh?
How is the Stygis Platoon?
Ready for launch.
See Count Klancain to a safe location.
Enemy force will be in range in seven minutes.
Start pulling back once we engage,
and draw the enemy out with you.
All personnel to combat stations.
Beginning launch sequence.
Flywheel connected.
Catapult arm rotating.
Opening hatch.
Clydesdale Platoon to launch point.
Roger.
Clydesdale Leader to all units.
Go to launch point.
Anchors engaged.
Catapult arm rotation within parameters.
Beginning acceleration.
Twenty seconds until launch rotation.
You're cleared for launch, Clydesdale Leader.
Roger, cleared for launch.
All units go.
Blast off!
Now, Mustang Platoon.
Prepare for launch.
Breton Platoon and the Deucalion
will commence their attack as planned.
Roger.
Let's go.
Attack!
Multiple enemy contacts coming in from Libra.
They're Cataphracts!
Intercept them.
It's begun.
Yeah.
The enemy's defenses are pretty tough.
It was obvious from the start that this'd be an uphill battle.
The reason we had to go ahead with this mission
was because HQ has an even bigger goal in mind.
The Captain was right to be suspicious.
That assault team is using our offensive as cover for an infiltration.
For sabotage?
No. There'd be no need to infiltrate secretly for that.
I would suspect their objective...
is to assassinate Princess Asseylum.
Bastard!
Fire.
Next.
They'll be closest to us in ninety seconds.
Roger. Move according to plan, then.
Inko.
I was supposed to do this alone.
It's going to get dangerous from here on.
So—
Seriously, this again? Gimme a break.
The captain assigned me to support you
out of recognition for my accomplishments.
I've been fighting right beside you
and the others all this time, after all.
Sorry, Inko.
Okay. Let's do this.
This is close enough.
I'll make my descent from here.
It's dangerous. You're still at high altitude.
Incoming!
Let me go! You're a sitting duck right now!
It's okay! The wind's strong!
I can dodge at this range!
Inko!
Just a little farther!
Yuki!
Leave this to me!
Thanks, Yuki.
You can drop me now, Inko.
Roger.
Be careful.
This is where we split up.
All teams, investigate your assigned routes.
Execute your missions as soon as you spot your target.
That's all.
Ambush!
I knew they would send an infiltration team.
I believe this is not the only block the enemy has infiltrated.
I will dispatch the palace guard.
And the princesses?
Evacuating to a more secure location as we speak.
Count Troyard.
I, Barouhcruz, have rushed to your side, swift as the wind.
You're here?
You have my thanks.
I will send Harklight to you.
What in the world is happening?
I'll keep them busy.
You guys find the target!
Importing base security footage and generating map.
I'm using you too much, huh?
I'll be all right.
Infiltration team located.
And beyond them... is where Seylum will be.
We can do this.
We might even kill 'em all...
Ultra high-tension monofilament wire spooled around a superconducting electromagnetic bobbin.
There is nothing this blade cannot cut through.
I'll leave the rat extermination to you, Sir Harklight.
Consider it done.
Target spotted!
Get behind me!
Girls!
Please run, Your Highness!
Sir Slaine, we've lost contact with the palace guards!
What?
And the princesses?
They're headed for the landing port,
but so is the enemy!
Dispatching immediate reinforc—
I'll go!
Why would you help me?
I need no reason to save a life.
The ego on you.
You have no idea how much it can hurt to be saved.
Princess Lemrina!
Keep going.
I'll stay here.
We have to escape!
Escape to where?
And from whom?
I'm certain we can find safety—
This place is my only refuge.
Go.
Where is this?
Do it again.
Search again, please.
Seylum...
has to be nearby.
I didn't expect to see you here, Kaizuka Inaho.
Slaine Troyard...
Calculate point of origin from bullet trajectory.
Thermography.
Steam pipes, huh?
Where's Seylum—Princess Asseylum?
Keep her out of this!
Out of it?
She and my goal go hand in hand.
That's all there is to it!
So you're just using her?
Using her?
What's it to you?
You were the enemy from the day we met!
If that was all, there would be no need for hate!
Over there!
After him!
Let's go.
Eddelrittuo!
Are you all right, Eddelrittuo?
What about you, Your Highness?
Your Highness!
Seylum?
Inaho!
Seylum...
I'm glad...
you're okay...
Inaho!
Your Highness!
Ina...
Princess Asseylum Vers Allusia, confirmed.
Inaho?
Thought processes offline.
Running backup program.
What's the matter, Inaho?
Temporarily assuming control of Kaizuka Inaho's thoughts, cognizance, and speech capabilities.
Who are you?
This boy, despite recognizing the individual identity of "Princess Asseylum,"
also misidentifies you as part of himself.
Part of himself?
For that reason, he put your safety on maximum priority and acted to preserve your life.
He came to save me?
In accordance with this maxim, I will provide you with the appropriate information.
Contact Amifumi Inko via the
communications line in the F3 gate airlock.
The people of the Deucalion are coming here?
Let us go, Your Highness.
I know where that airlock is.
But we can't leave Inaho—
There is no cause for concern.
In four hundred and twenty seconds, my comrades will arrive.
Which is exactly why we need to leave, Your Highness!
There's no telling if his
comrades will be on our side!
Please tell him: "Thank you,
from the bottom of my heart."
Command acknowledged.
And...
Tell him:
"I also think of you as part of myself."
We need to leave.
Hold on.
I have one more...
request.
It's this way!
Just one minute. I'll get the comms equipment on—
Princess Asseylum, is it?
Say your prayers.
Are you unharmed, Princess Asseylum?
You're...
Klancain?
We last met at my father's commendation ceremony.
I am honored that you remember me.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life