Where am I?
I see.
You lied to make her run away?
It was an accurate conjecture of my plan.
Sir Slaine.
What is it?
There is an altercation in the hangar.
Their assassination squad?
No.
It is Princess Asseylum.
I will provide cover.
Run!
Eliminate the Terrans!
We're under attack!
Perform emergency launch.
It wouldn't be safe, sir.
There's a battle raging outside.
It's no safer in here.
Get us away from the combat zone
at maximum speed.
Retreat!
Your Highness...
Inko...
Where is Princess Asseylum?
She hasn't contacted me yet.
Is she still inside?
No...
Mission successful.
Inko, come pick me up.
I'm truly sorry, Count Klancain.
I had no wish to involve you in this.
Do not worry.
This is part of my mission too.
Mission?
Yes.
I am here under His Imperial Majesty's orders.
My grandfather's?
Emperor Rayregalia was doubtful of the campaign staged by the previous Count Saazbaum.
He commanded me to investigate and see to your safety.
Then I must speak with my grandfather!
I can establish contact.
However...
Count Klancain, we have a transmission from the moon base.
Put it onscreen.
Count Klancain, where do you mean to take Princess Asseylum?
Ah, Count Troyard.
I am presently evacuating Her Highness to protect her from our enemies.
The moon base is heavily fortified.
There is no place safer.
I seem to recall a battle raging within it.
Have no fear.
All enemy forces have been eradicated.
Please return at once.
No!
I will not return!
I...
watched birds on Earth.
Your Highness...
The Earth was recovering,
and mankind was coexisting with nature.
You were the one who taught me that.
That mankind and nature...
That Earth and Vers...
could prosper together!
Yes.
It is as you say.
I said exactly that.
I've dispatched Stygis Platoon in pursuit.
Have them seize the ship.
I beg you, Slaine.
Please stop this war!
Make peace with Earth.
Yes.
Perhaps you are right.
Let us speak about that.
Slaine...
The sector you are entering is dangerous.
You should return immediately.
Count Klancain, please turn back at once.
I am afraid I cannot comply.
I shall observe Princess Asseylum's orders.
Maximum power to stealth devices!
Yes, sir.
The spacecraft Hadriacus
has vanished from our sensors.
Keep looking.
Yes, sir.
That should get him off our backs for the time being.
Thank you.
But what should I do now?
Earth's military is trying to kill me,
and the Orbital Knights obey Slaine.
Is there any way I could make contact with the Deucalion?
Your Highness...
There is still one who is on your side.
The knight who delivered the message from Kaizuka Inaho.
Count Mazuurek.
Now is the time to demonstrate
my loyalty to Princess Asseylum.
Landing Castle, lift off!
Clydesdale Leader to all units!
Target the enemies off starboard!
Don't let them get close to the Deucalion!
Enemies approaching from
three o'clock, sixty degrees up!
Focus AA fire to starboard.
Orders from HQ!
We're to withdraw!
Withdraw?
Looks like they got what they came for.
What they came for?
Whatever main operation we were used to divert attention from.
Prepare to withdraw.
All units are to return.
Mustang 00 and 11 are approaching.
They're coming back!
Inko and Inaho!
They're cleared to land.
Recover them at once.
They flee in the face of our superiority.
What are they playing at?
Count Troyard, Earth's forces are retreating.
Should we pursue?
No. Return to base.
Rearm and refuel for the next offensive.
Also, summon the Landing Castles.
Have them bolster the moon base's defenses.
As you wish.
Is that my sister's?
Princess Lemrina...
Did my sister...
I see.
I wonder if we will see her again.
I'm certain we will.
I pity you.
You...
and her both.
Inaho...
What is his condition?
It's nothing life-threatening.
But I'm concerned with the strain the
analytical engine is putting on his cranial nerves.
I told him not to let it expand too much.
What does that mean?
He's given up part of his brain to the machine.
Crazy kid.
I have to put a stop to this war.
I will speak to all the Orbital Knights.
I'm afraid that alone may not be enough.
Why not?
The Orbital Knights have long since desired to wage war with Earth and conquer it.
Count Troyard has issued them
carte blanche with a royal decree.
He has won them over to his side with promises of status and Aldnoah activation privileges
once he comes into his own kingdom.
Princess Asseylum, this all hinges on his upcoming marriage to you.
Calling for an end to hostilities will only invite their distrust at this point.
He still has your sister, who can pretend to be you.
Princess Asseylum.
I am overjoyed to see you unharmed.
Thank you for coming to my assistance.
You give me too much credit.
I am merely relieved to be able to repay my debt.
Debt?
Yes.
My debt to the Terran boy...
Kaizuka Inaho.
I've received report that you sent a team into the moon base.
Would you mind explaining why,
Captain Magbaredge?
It was a judgment call
based on the circumstances.
If we lose the princess now,
our only chance at peace is gone for good.
Why would Slaine instigate this war?
Your Highness...
The Slaine I knew was kind.
He loved nature and the Earth.
He would never start a meaningless war.
So why?
Your Highness...
Sir Slaine hasn't changed one bit!
What?
I cannot judge if he is right or wrong.
But you were always foremost in his thoughts.
He did everything for your sake,
caring not if it put his status or life in danger.
Always believing
that one day,
you would awaken...
Yes. I suppose that's true.
You are right on that count, Eddelrittuo.
Are you able to make contact with Vers?
Yes.
However, His Majesty...
We can no longer afford to hesitate.
Count Klancain, please lend me your assistance.
I will use the Hadriacus' audience chamber.
As you command, Princess Asseylum.
Notice to all units:
Operation will begin at 1500 hours UTC as planned.
Stand by at battle stations.
Lieutenant Marito, are you deploying?
Yeah.
I was hoping to have one last drink with you, Doc,
but I guess I missed my chance.
That's not like you.
Well, we're in a low-pressure environment.
Wouldn't want it to affect me too badly.
That's not what I meant.
There's no "last" about it.
Yeah. We'll have that drink when I get back.
Is this what you'd call a "final battle"?
I guess.
If we beat 'em here,
there won't be another one, right?
And if anyone dies in action,
that's as final a battle as they can get!
Stop it!
Could you not jinx us?
Yeah! We're all gonna make it back in one piece!
Sir Slaine.
Earth has begun to gather her forces.
What shall we do about them?
No change of plan.
Launch all forces and intercept them.
Also, send a request for assistance
from our supporting Orbital Knights.
Assistance?
We will launch an all-out offensive against the Earth.
They shall learn how it feels to no longer have anywhere to go home to.
Nao.
Yuki?
Are you okay, Nao?
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
You did good today. Now rest up.
He's going to launch an all-out attack.
The operation should be beginning soon.
Hey!
Stop! You need to stay in bed!
I'm sorry, Yuki.
There's something I have to do.
Nao!
Please.
Let me go.
I can tell from your face
that you'll go no matter what I say.
And I can tell from your voice
that you're ready to give up and let me.
Seriously.
When you come back, let's have dinner together.
That's a death flag, you know.
Hey, don't talk like that.
You're definitely coming back alive.
Yeah. And so are you.
Yo, Inaho.
Out of bed already?
Yeah.
Is this...
You guessed it!
It's the Sleipnir final battle loadout!
Little too much junk in the trunk if you ask me, though.
Getting close enough to use this
in a space battle would be crazy.
Well, this whole op's going to be crazy.
Seriously?
He's not taking this seriously at all!
Inko?
Why are boys always like this?
Inaho, you're in no condition to go into battle.
Let us handle this.
That I cannot do.
What?!
What the hell?
You think you're some hotshot ace?
That you're special?
I've never thought that.
Come on, Inaho!
Why are you acting like you can't see it?
If you deploy now, you might die out there for real!
You pulled through last time,
but miracles don't come twice!
I couldn't bear...
to go through that again.
I can't just lie in bed while everyone else fights.
He's right, Inko.
If you care for him, you'll let him go without a fight.
We've got enough to worry about ourselves.
If I had to say it, compared to Inaho,
our chances of survival are pretty low.
Get real! I'm an ace too!
Thanks, Inko.
Calm.
It's okay.
We're all going to make it back alive.
My left eye says so.
Master switch, on.
Fuel cells, heat up.
Voltage, check.
Pump activated.
Accumulator, pressure all good.
Force feedback checking program, start.
Ejection seat functional.
IFF confirmed.
Tactical datalink activated.
Systems, all green.
Mustang 00...
Ready.
Grandfather...
Grandfather.
It's me.
Asseylum.
Do you recognize me?
Ah... Asseylum...
You look well.
I am weary.
Is our conquest of Earth proceeding as planned?
I would ask you a favor in regards to that.
I ask that you make peace with Earth.
Please order the Orbital Knights to cease fighting.
I cannot.
Grandfather?
The Terrans can never be forgiven.
Press them with everything we have.
Conquer them, and make them ours.
Grandfather, why...
Why do you hate Earth so?
Where is Gillzeria?
What has become of my son?
Conquer the Earth at once!
Father passed away during Heaven's Fall.
Wretched Terrans. How dare they kill my son?
Not even my granddaughter, Asseylum, was spared.
I'm right here.
Vers.
That is what those of the ancient civilization called this planet—Mars.
Grandfather...
Rejoice.
For I have discovered...
a Martian superscience.
Its name is Aldnoah.
This is wonderful.
Mankind can now make even greater progress.
Aldnoah will make everyone happy.
It is the technology of our dreams.
Yes.
It is a great power.
It must not be misused.
Nurture it with care.
I will.
Is that you, Asseylum?
How you've grown.
And how fair you've become.
Become a fine princess.
Lead our people to happiness.
I will.
Klancain.
I will need all that your status and connections can achieve.
Of course.
I would be honored.
Your loyalty is appreciated, Count Cruhteo.
Goddamn Martians!
Glory to Vers!
What the hell is that?
Slice them to ribbons!
Annihilate them, my servants!
Open a comms channel
and contact all Orbital Knights!
Yes, sir!
The moon base has begun its all-out offensive on the United Forces of Earth!
Hear me, Knights that have traveled down to the satellite belt and to the planet's surface.
Launch an attack against the forces of Earth, wherever you are!
Prove to them our immense strength once and for all!
And show them that resistance—
Hear me, Orbital Knights of Vers.
Princess Asseylum!
I am Asseylum Vers Allusia,
first princess of the Vers Empire.
This great war began from a single confrontation.
What's going on?
A pirate broadcast?
It's being transmitted on all bands.
Many different people with different ideals have clashed, bringing forth great tragedy.
And that is truly regrettable.
I too have suffered from this war.
I feel both shame and regret for our use of a power not meant for human hands.
And so, here and now...
I claim my birthright to Rayregalia Vers Rayvers' title
and hereby name myself Empress of Vers.
I also announce my engagement to Count Cruhteo of the Orbital Knights' Thirty-Seven Clans.
We of the Vers imperial family hereby
extend the olive branch of peace to Earth!
kirameku kakera
Somewhere in a sky
furisosogu sora ni
of burning fragments falling heavy
mirai tsunagu doa kakushita
I lost the gateway to the future
hontou wa daremo mina
Every one of us
kizu tsuku to osoreteru
is afraid of being wounded
nanika wo mamoru tame kowasu tame ni
It is our wish to destroy or protect
bokura wa harmonious
that makes us harmonious
omoi wa yozora wo koete
My love passes the stars
utsushidasu sore wa
to shine pure light
hikari no michishirube
back on our path
kanashii ketsui wa
I hope the rain will soothe
ame ga naderu darou
the pain of my sad decisions
yurushiau tsuyosa oshiete hoshii
Tell me how to be strong enough to forgive
douka aisuru koto wasurenaide
Please don't forget how to love