Why are you doing this?
I want you to return to your Landing Castle
and find out where the real Princess Asseylum is.
Why me?
Because you are of the same mind as her.
There's one other thing I'd like you to find out:
Slaine Troyard's objective.
His objective?
Take this.
If you meet Princess Asseylum, show this to her.
She'll understand that you are on our side.
Your Highness!
kimi no te ga hirogeta nani mo nai sora yo
Your hands spread out the vast and empty sky
rikutsu no umi dake no kai wo asobeba
when you played with what the sea of reason would give
hodoite wa koboreta tagai no namida
Our tears welled up and fell
kouka shita kotoba uso kimagure
Words, lies, and whim down from orbit
soul art
Soul art
rhythm kanadete
We play a song now
aizu wo ringu ni tsunagu
and connect the signs to a ring
katachi dake no system to
A system of pure shape
katami dake no majinai mo
A magic spell without power
toubounin no hajirai on
The sound of shy fugitives
souzou drive carryon iji na tire
Carry on imagining, don't give up
gokai aru doa ni zero ga nemurikaketa
We're running out of false doors
tokei daita hito to tenshi
Men and angels embrace the passage of time
towa ni aku doorutachi
They are dolls who gave up on eternity,
mata onaji kaze ni mogaite
fighting against this recurring fever
What happened after that, Harklight?
We conquered the Lake Victoria area from the beachhead created by our Landing Castle.
Good work.
I'm sure the combined might of several
Orbital Knights awed more than just the UE.
I would expect this success will have impressed upon everyone the value of a leader.
They had never expected a difficult battle,
lulled into security by the power of Aldnoah.
Aldnoah...
Count Saazbaum once lamented our stratified society based around the privilege of Aldnoah.
He went as far as saying the emigration to Mars was a mistake in the first place.
That power, Aldnoah, allowed humanity to spread to every corner of Mars and start this very war.
Princess Asseylum, Princess Lemrina...
Both are victims of Aldnoah.
As are we.
But the days when that power ruled us are no more.
The land we have conquered shall be the first stone of an empire that spans Earth.
We will combine the power of Aldnoah
with the vast resources that Earth holds,
and build our own world.
How are the repairs?
It's looking pretty grim.
Most of the electrics are fried,
and it'll take time to replace them all.
Of all the times to be assigned a mission...
We're docked, so the Cataphract platoons
have to be sent to the front via landing craft.
Our two platoons will attack the enemy Landing Castle from the north
and support the main force
attacking from the southwest.
"Special forces" sounds fancy,
but we're little more than cannon fodder here.
Maybe HQ figures the chances for victory aren't so bad.
Does that victory include our survival?
I doubt it.
I suppose we need to improve our chances, then.
Hey, Kaizuka Junior.
Can that brain of yours do something about those damned Martians?
It's tricky.
Elektris uses electricity as a weapon.
Skandia can turn invisible.
They're both formidable in their own right.
And I don't have enough data about Ortygia's replication ability to say anything.
Sparky, Ninja, and Houdini.
I feel like I'm watching a Sonny Chiba movie.
What I can say about Ortygia is that he always splits from one into two—never into more.
The duplicate always appears within around thirty meters.
No matter how much it splits,
there's probably only one real, piloted unit.
The others are just copies.
So we have to seek out the real one
and eliminate him.
How are we going to do that?
I think the only way is to mark the first one
before the copies appear and keep track of it.
We can locate Skandia by raising a smokescreen and monitoring how she displaces it.
And what about Sparky?
Any ideas?
One hit from him'll fry your electronics, actuators... the whole shebang.
What about insulation?
That stuff blocks electricity, right?
What?
Are you retarded?
That's like, a grade school mistake.
Shut up!
What's wrong with it?
Air is already an excellent insulator.
We have nothing that could protect against
electricity powerful enough to go through it.
The real issue is that these bastards are working together.
Yeah. Even one of them would be tricky enough.
I think...
I have an idea.
Are you going to use your eye again?
Don't worry.
I have a mutation code running in the background.
It gets more and more optimized over time.
My computing power is even better than it used to be.
Calm, could you change my loadout for me?
Sure thing.
Just tell me what you need.
Give me what I used up there.
Princess Lemrina,
the invasion of Earth is proceeding according to plan.
I see.
I knew you could do it, Slaine.
On that note,
I was wondering if you could say a few words to the knights that have returned from battle.
My persona, you mean?
Yes.
If Princess Asseylum herself
were to honor their achievements,
it would surely inspire others to serve us.
"Us"?
Yes, Princess Lemrina.
Very well.
On an unrelated note, how is my sister's condition?
I'm told she is still in critical condition.
I see.
All we can do is put our trust in the medical staff
and allow them to do their work.
Yes.
Let us pray for her swift recovery.
Don't let it get to you.
Thank you for your kind words.
I must attend to my duties.
Liar.
Clydesdale Leader to all units.
Spread out!
Mustang Leader to Mustang 00.
Nao, what's our plan?
It's not finalized, but...
Here are the coordinates and timings.
Mustang 11, 22. Move out.
Roger.
The Ortygia Master is our primary target.
Attack together and destroy him.
Sorraia Platoon, advance!
Gotland Platoon, flank him west of here!
Sorraia Platoon, acknowledged.
Gotland Platoon, acknowledged.
The Master is the third from the right.
Commence attack!
Did you think that was the original?
I'm afraid not.
Leave this enemy force to me: Orga.
Nonius Platoon, Pleven Platoon,
focus your attacks on Skandia and destroy it!
Smoke grenades!
Over there!
Get her!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
The same trick again?
What an unimaginative lot.
Don't you agree, Count Sebring?
Let us have some fun with them, Countess Raffia.
The smoke screen vanished?
Colloids are adsorbed after ionization.
This is how you use high-voltage electricity.
A lightning attack from the invisibility cloak?
One should die an honorable death in battle, wouldn't you say?
Any true Cataphract pilot would agree.
Main force and assault units are in dire straits!
I guess this means that the lightning and invisibility units are working together.
Mustang 00, what's your status?
I have all the data I need.
Though the expanded invisibility field and smokescreen negation were unexpected.
Can you compensate?
I'll make do.
I see.
So they've been waging war for almost two years while I was unconscious.
Yes.
And Slaine started that?
What in the world is happening?
Where are you going, Your Highness?
I will meet with Slaine.
I need to know the truth.
Your Highness!
You...
Why?
Why...
Why are you always...
Who are...
I...
I am you!
I use my tactical data link to multidimensionally analyze the enemy's movements
and conjecture their attack habits.
I then deploy units in positions vulnerable to the enemy's preferred attack patterns
in order to bait them into attacking.
The question is: will my analysis finish in time?
Sending you the newest data.
Form up.
Roger.
Roger here too.
My guess is that the enemy is right-handed.
He moves counter-clockwise to make it easier
to attack enemies to the left.
It sucks being bait.
Where is he now?
Circling around behind you.
I'm guessing he's withholding his lightning attack
so as not to reveal his position.
Once he's taken your back,
he should stop for a second to take aim.
Yuki, now!
You sure he's there?
Got him!
This isn't possible!
This is Mustang Leader! Target found!
Mustang 00, launching.
Roger.
Dropping you, Mustang 00.
The Skandia's leg has been damaged!
It can no longer bear the Elektris' weight!
Disengaging!
Escape while I hold them off!
Target acquired.
#9, shoot.
Your bullets are useless!
But how about these?
What witchery?
Electricity flows via electrical potential difference.
Your lightning won't strike something
with the same electrical potential as you.
That's why you're safe from your own attacks.
Take this!
Too late. I have the same electrical potential as you now.
No...
Could this be the infamous orange Cataphract?
Count Sebring!
Sending reinforcements! Just hold out!
Inaho!
Smoke grenades!
There you are!
Fire!
It can't be...
Damn you!
How dare you kill my brethren!
You will pay!
You okay, Nao?
Yeah.
Thanks, Yuki.
Enemy at nine o'clock!
Here they come!
Get as many as you can!
You sent for me, Princess Lemrina?
Slaine...
What is the meaning of this?
Princess Asseylum—
my sister—
has already awoken.
I always knew this day would come.
Would you do me the courtesy of explaining yourself?
Princess Asseylum's memories have not fully returned.
I needed you to continue acting as her, as you have so gracefully done.
For the sake of the new world we are creating.
New world?
Yes.
A world free of worry,
with no conflict or sadness,
where everyone can live happily ever after.
And who will ensure the future of this world?
That would be Princess Asseylum Vers Allusia.
And you really think she wants that?
I am aware that she does not.
Which is exactly why I will create that world and offer it unto her.
Your Highness,
do you know why wars take place?
Well...
They are a means of negotiation between governments.
No.
Wars take place because there is someone to fight.
To eliminate war, we must either invade and gain control
or completely wipe out all opposition so that only one side remains.
The history of humanity is
one fraught with conflict.
The very instant that Mars split off from Earth, it was inevitable that war would occur.
Even if I had not done what I had,
I'm sure that someone, one day, would...
You've...
changed.
You're no longer...
the Slaine I knew, are you?
Princess Asseylum?
I told her everything.
In the name of Asseylum Vers Allusia, first princess of the Vers Empire:
I order you, Count Slaine Saazbaum Troyard, to declare an immediate cease-fire.
I thought we just needed to take out the master!
Which is the real one?
Clearly not the one we marked!
Is it hiding somewhere?
I assumed there would be one real unit
among them, but I may have been mistaken.
Mistaken? How?
In my analysis of the duplicates,
I found out something interesting.
The moment they're created, everything about the master, from position to energy status,
is perfectly preserved.
Which means what?
Perhaps he's creating copies via quantum teleportation.
Except that the original remains intact, thereby creating a doppelganger.
But what does it mean?!
They're...
all...
real.
Please hand over control of all Cataphract platoon targeting and triggers to me!
Relay request to central command.
On it!
Inputting coordinates and vectors for all Ortygias.
How many is he making?
You done yet, Kaizuka Junior?!
The targets are multiplying.
I need a second to update.
Well, they ain't gonna sit back and wait!
Our ammo won't last!
Tactical data link, synchronized.
Switching all allied Cataphract targeting to centralized control.
How much longer, Nao?
We only get one chance at this.
If they're all real...
All targets locked.
Fire!
Whoa.
If they're all real, then all we need to do is blow 'em up at the same time, huh?
Enemy Cataphracts annihilated!
You did it, Inaho!
Yeah. I'm just glad it worked.
Couldn't have done it without you all.
Slaine.
Please, put an end to this.
Princess Asseylum.
I am no longer subject to your authority.
You see...
I am a citizen of the Vers Empire no more.
Forgive me,
but I must take you both into custody.
Captain, message from HQ.
We've got about two minutes until the laser comms satellite falls below the horizon, cutting us off.
That's cutting it close.
On speaker, please.
This is Darzana Magbaredge, captain of the Deucalion.
Vice Admiral Eelis Hakkinen speaking.
Good work out there.
Status on repairs?
Nearly done.
That's good to hear.
You will need the equipment on your new mission.
A mission in the satellite belt?
No.
You'll be going even higher this time.
In any case, you'll be briefed later.
Transmission ended.
The laser's gain has dropped.
Comms satellite is almost out of sight.
I guess that doesn't leave us a chance to say no.
It sounds like this will be a large-scale battle.
That bastard.
He thinks he can send us wherever he wants just because we have an Aldnoah Drive.
It's equipment for space travel, then?
A catapult module.
Sir Slaine.
Yes?
The princesses have been escorted to their quarters with no issue.
I see.
Even if they cannot yet see what you are trying to accomplish, Sir Slaine,
surely one day—
It matters not.
If they wish to remain blind, so be it.
Sir Slaine, a ship is approaching the base.
It is requesting permission to dock.
A ship?
It is a visitor from the Vers homeworld.
So this is Earth?
The blue planet upon which my father sleeps.
Yes, Count Cruhteo.
Oh, stop.
It still bothers me to be addressed by my father's name.
Just call me Klancain.
As you wish, Count Klancain.
I wonder what he will be like...
The son of Dr. Troyard.
bokutachi wa samayoeru mirai
We are a future of dubious likelihood
kyuukutsu na sora ni
We look to the oppressive sky
hikari wo sagashiteiru
in search of light
furueru te wa muryoku de
Our trembling hands are powerless
sakebi wa mata tookute
Our screams reach no one
dakedo tobu koto wo
But we will never be afraid
osorete wa irarenai
of flying
eien ja nakutemo
We don't need eternity
kanpeki ja nakutemo
We don't need perfection
senaka-awase no sekai wo
We live in two related
massugu ikiteyuku
but wildly different worlds
nando kizu tsuitemo
No matter the wounds we receive
nando machigaetemo
and the mistakes we make,
unmei sae tobikoete yukou
we will overcome fate
kono sora no hate made
Until the skies above us end
hajimari wo shinjite
we will believe in the genesis of a better life