This great war began from a single confrontation.
Many different people with different ideals have clashed, bringing forth great tragedy.
And that is truly regrettable.
I too have suffered from this war.
I feel both shame and regret for our use of a power not meant for human hands.
And so, here and now...
I claim my birthright to Rayregalia Vers Rayvers's title
and hereby name myself Empress of Vers.
I also announce my engagement to Count Cruhteo of the Orbital Knights' Thirty-Seven Clans.
As the imperial family of the Vers Empire,
we hereby extend the olive branch of peace to Earth.
In the name of the Empress of Vers,
I order all Orbital Knights
whom this broadcast may reach
to cease hostilities at once.
What is this?
Was the princess not poised to found a new dynasty with Count Troyard?
What will we do about the all-out offensive against Earth?
Halt it.
Put the forces on standby.
Let us await further developments.
It is no wonder.
Count Troyard is still little more than Terran rabble.
Ascension to royalty was always beyond his reach.
What is this?
Sir Harklight, we withdraw to the moon!
Sir Slaine...
Why are they still fighting?
The princess ordered them to stand down!
The forces from the moon base still want to fight.
Stay focused!
The battle isn't over yet!
You hear that?
Yeah...
That Princess Asseylum just now—
I mean, Empress Asseylum—
sounded just like the one I remember.
Yeah.
So it's just as Second Lieutenant Kaizuka predicted.
Then that order for a ceasefire must be real as well.
The enemies we're engaging
aren't standing down, though.
Any word from HQ?
No new orders.
So we're to continue the operation.
Neither the moon base nor the Landing Castles show any intent to cease hostilities.
Where is Empress Asseylum?
The earlier transmission was broadcast from Count Mazuurek's Landing Castle.
Did she abandon the moon?
Or has a schism developed?
Count Troyard, how are we to proceed with Her Highness' orders?
Orders?
What orders?
Apologies, my lord.
I'm impressed.
This is an unexpected turn of events.
Princess Lemrina.
What truly matters is royal blood.
As long as you have Aldnoah activation rights,
your dream is still within reach.
I will stay with you.
This is the only place I can call home.
So please...
You are right.
I thank you for your kindness, Princess Lemrina.
Let's be off.
Yes, let's.
It's so beautiful.
Was that a heartless thing to say?
I've seen many things while flying through those lights.
Many things?
The future.
The future?
The good and the bad alike.
All I could see was the immediate future,
but I thought I understood everything.
Many things unfolded just as I foresaw,
but...
I lost sight of what was truly important.
Resupply.
Yes, sir!
Count Troyard!
What is the meaning of this?
Why would Princess Asseylum say such things?
Sir Slaine...
Patch me through to the command center.
I will address all units,
including the Stygis Platoon out in the field.
Yes, sir!
Listen up!
You have ten minutes to evacuate the moon base!
Surrender to the Earth forces
together with the Landing Castles!
We are abandoning the moon base!
Are you out of your mind?
Slaine!
Princess Lemrina...
Let me apologize for the many wrongs
I have rendered unto you.
Slaine...
I pray for your well-being.
Harklight, escort Her Highness to a shuttle.
As you wish.
Slaine! Stop!
Please come with me, Your Highness.
No! I won't leave!
Slaine! Slaine!
We're detecting numerous craft exiting the moon base!
Reinforcements?
No.
They're leaving the combat area.
The moon base...
is going down?
Did we beat them?
No...
They're self-destructing?
Sir Harklight?
Guard the shuttle.
Sir Harklight!
Harklight.
What are you doing? Turn back.
I thought I ordered you to surrender.
Harklight!
Stygis Squadron! Don't act on your own!
Reinforcements closing in.
Enemy at ten o'clock, ten degrees down!
Stand by to engage!
Stop! We no longer have any hope of winning!
Don't throw your lives away!
I made my peace with death long ago.
Please allow me this one selfish act.
Surrender, Harklight!
Forgive me, Sir Slaine.
But I cannot comply with that order.
Here they come!
All units, scatter!
Come on!
How could they do this?
Damn it all!
What's that?
Those moves...
You're right, Harklight.
We can't let it end like this.
There's still something I have to do.
I've come for you, Slaine Troyard.
Let's settle this once and for all, Kaizuka Inaho!
Reading my moves won't do you any good if you can't get away from them.
You're the one who isn't getting away!
Opening contact channel.
Decrypting protocols.
I doubt this will do any good, but I'll ask anyway.
Will you surrender, Slaine Troyard?
Did you come all this way just to
tell me poor jokes, Kaizuka Inaho?
No. I have a different objective.
I'm glad to hear that.
Don't disappoint me, now!
Damn! My monitors are damaged?
I know. We can't do any more high-load processing.
Cut all predictive imagers.
I no longer...
need a future!
Incoming at two o'clock, five degrees up!
All ahead, emergency speed!
Come about, 060!
Coming about, 060!
Load canister shot!
Fire once targets are locked!
Wow...
Nao's combat data is stored in the tactical data link.
All units, refer to that and—
Yuki!
I'm okay!
Barouhcruz of the Orbital Knights' Thirty-Seven Clans reporting.
May I intrude?
Count Barouhcruz...
Incoming at eight o'clock, twenty-five degrees down!
Intercept!
I've got this!
Three rounds remaining.
There is nothing to be gained by continuing to fight.
Agreed. But there is nothing to be lost, either.
Giving in to despair is a foolish choice.
You just don't get it!
This is precisely what I've wanted all along!
Slice them to ribbons!
Rayet!
Fool!
Radar returns approaching fast!
What?
It's the Tharsis... and a Terran Cataphract!
That's...
Rayet!
Three-direction crossfire!
MRSI, neutralize target, auto fire!
I've always...
I've always loathed...
that wretched color!
Sir Harklight!
The drones are on autopilot! Use the rocks!
We can limit the direction of their attack!
Are you all right?
Yes. I only lost an arm.
Sir Harklight!
Battle status?
Three Stygis Masters remain, myself included,
as well as some six Slaves.
The rest have been felled by Terran forces.
And I am perilously low on ammunition.
Count Barouhcruz.
The Octantis' right arm is out of commission.
It must have been damaged in that last attack.
These Terran warriors are not without skill.
Indeed.
I should expect as much from Sir Slaine's birthplace.
"Fight not an Olympus sandstorm," eh?
We seem to have misread the winds.
Let us join in battle once again!
I shall accompany you.
Enemy formation closing in at
nine o'clock, twenty degrees up!
All guns, take aim!
Cataphract platoons: all units fire at will!
I'll act as a drogue chute.
It will stabilize your descent.
You intend to die with me?
We'll burn up on re-entry.
Cataphract frames are high density.
They'll work well enough as ablative shielding.
Impossible. They'll never last.
You think so? I guess we'll see.
Look at that, Sis!
A shooting star!
Special report.
Aldnoah Reactor #1, constructed as a sign of goodwill between Earth and Vers,
is scheduled to be activated today.
We're told that Empress Asseylum herself
will participate in the activation ceremony.
Research into unrestricted activation privileges for all is still ongoing.
When that is achieved, it will signal
the birth of Aldnoah-based industries
that will help greatly with
the Earth's reconstruction.
And for the Vers Empire,
provider of Aldnoah technology,
it should prove an effective means
to earn foreign capital.
Dr. Troyard's theories have already been proven,
so we should see them put into practice
in the near future.
It's ironic that Slaine Troyard,
the son of that same Dr. Troyard, was the one who plotted the assassination of Empress Asseylum
and served as the trigger for Interplanetary War II.
Slaine Troyard's death allowed Earth and Vers
to settle upon a friendship treaty.
However, there are still Mars Knights who continue to occupy territory on Earth.
One goal of Empress Asseylum's visit
is peace negotiations with those knights.
Here's hoping that we'll see the prompt return
of that occupied territory.
May this light
form a bridge of peace between Earth and Vers.
Awaken!
How are you feeling?
You don't look too bad.
You really should eat your meals, though.
I've had complaints from the warden.
Your move.
Your eye...
Is that from when I shot you?
I replaced it with an analytical engine.
A biomechanical implant that was neuro-linked to my cranial nerves.
But I had it removed. I don't need it anymore.
Hasn't this gone long enough?
I deceived. I stole. I killed.
I sacrificed countless numbers of my own.
Please.
No. You're going to live.
Why?
Why did you save me?!
I have one more request.
It wasn't my decision.
It was Princess Asseylum's.
Please...
Please, save Slaine.
Save Slaine Troyard.
Save him from the cycle of misery.
I beg you.
Seylum asked me...
to save you.
Incredible.
The blue sky and ocean go on as far as the eye can see!
It's so beautiful.
I'm told that the blue sky is the result
of something called Rayleigh scattering.
You're quite well-informed.
When I visited Earth last time,
a Terran I had befriended
was kind enough to teach me.
It's a cherished memory of mine.
kimi ga miru yume wa
Your selfless dream
furui inku de kami ni kaita inori no you
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
Your fragile hands seek support,
ima wa mada doko ni mo nai
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
But even so, I want to guard
kirei na mono wa kirei na mama de
the path you walk
mamoritsuzuketai to omou yo
in all my beauty
sora to mizu ga hoshi wo somete
I can see our skies and seas in the stars
awaku niji wo egaite chitte
before they fall to make a rainbow
mabushii yoru kimi ga utau
Light tears through the night and you sing
koe wa doko made todoku no darou
How far will your voice travel?
akogare no sumau aoi hoshi no hikari
This is the light of the blue planet I admire,
tada bokura wa koi wo shite
the light that we love helplessly
tatta hitotsu no mirai no tame ni
We sacrifice all we have at our disposal
ima no subete kanadetemiru
for the only future we have left
kimi ga yume miru nara
When you dream,
soba ni tatte
I will stand next to you
onaji kanata he te wo nobasu yo
and reach for the same point on the horizon
kimi ga shinjita shizuka na sora ni
One day, I might be able
itsuka boku mo todoku darou
to see the sky you put so much faith into:
doko made mo mabushii
as far as the eye can see,
heavenly blue