Haru.
Wh-What?
Your breathing tickles.
Ch-Chiyu...
There's no need for us to cable like that!
No!
If the copy from Taku fails, I want to install it from you.
Are we ready?
Wait a sec.
Ow!
Anyway, why didn't you bring a cable?
Risk of wired cable communication!
Cable communication by wire may bypass 90% of the Neuro Linker firewall.
It's your fault for not having more than one long cable.
Chii-chan.
I want to make sure you're aware of this one last time.
The Brain Burst program I'm about to send you is more than just a game.
You might regret it someday.
He's right.
If you think it's just a simple way to obtain power and think lightly of it...
Like I said!
It's not the power that I want.
You two take the game really seriously, so I just want to show you that games are meant to be enjoyed.
Come on, hurry up!
All right.
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install
Cancel
Downloaded file - Security warning
Install executable file BB2039?
Install
Haru, I'm scared that Chii-chan
will become a different person...
If we...
I mean, if you protect her, she'll be fine.
Also, we don't know if it'll install successfully yet.
What's this?
Chii-chan?
"Welcome to the Accelerated World"?
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Porky, today we command you...
Why am I still seeing those dreams?
If only there weren't class changes...
Chiyuri Kurashima
Chiyu?
Haru, you're still awake?
I just woke up.
It's so windy outside.
It'll blow away the cherry blossoms.
Yeah.
Hey, I'll open the gate, so dive into my home server.
Huh? Now?
Yup. It's decided, then!
Chiyuri Kurashima
Geez, she's always like that.
Direct Link.
What the heck's this?
An anomalocaris.
It's from the Cambrian era.
I can't believe you're still using that avatar.
You should change it.
I've gotten used to it.
Anyway, what's with this cushion hel- I mean, heaven?
Isn't it great?
I got a memory expansion upgrade as a present for going up a year.
At this resolution, this place is 15 km wide.
Really?!
Let me play around with it too!
No way!
If you customize it, it'll stink of oil, steel, and smoke.
That's what's awesome!
We could get a Tiger tank and a BF109 fighter plane here!
I said no!
'Kay, stay still!
Wh-What are you doing?
You said I might have a scary dream tonight, so I couldn't fall asleep.
You can't avoid it.
Your duel avatar won't be created if you don't have the dream.
Huh? Wait...
Avatars are created based on painful past memories,
so if you've never experienced any trauma...
That's not nice!
I've had traumatic experiences.
Like, back in elementary school, somebody got sick on the bus during a trip and barfed all over my lap...
Sorry. I apologize.
Please say nothing more.
Good that you understand.
Just stay still. You're my pillow.
Your pillow?
There was this one time when you stayed over at my place.
I remember using you as a pillow and sleeping really well.
That was a really long time ago.
Hey, Haru.
I've worked really hard to become a Burst Linker, you know.
We'll be able to go back to the time when we all played together, right?
Umesato Junior High / Layout
I'm so nervous...
Please...
Hey, Haru.
T-Taku.
Haru! 'Sup?
Chiyu! So it's you...
Huh? Why are you crying?
It's nothing.
I'm glad the three of us are in the same class.
Ah, morning!
Isn't it such a coincidence?
All right, you guys. Time to get off the 'net!
Morning assembly's about to start!
The vast majority of you must be
feeling both hope and anxiety equally.
Especially the new students, as you come into a new school with new upperclassmen...
She speaks so confidently on the stage,
but in the other world, she's a destroyer and a
devil of an instructor that'd scare a US marine.
...holding the same anxiety and
standing in the same place as you are.
During this year...
She scared me!
Was she reading my thoughts?
...your time will feel long...
Your time will feel long but be over in an instant.
Please have a fulfilling year.
This concludes my welcome speech.
Next, the educational guidance teacher
will talk about the use of Neuro Linkers in...
What was Senpai's reaction about?
Don't tell me...
There's a Burst Linker among the new students?
Yeah.
She probably noticed something.
She was staring straight at the new students.
I was actually thinking the same thing.
It's typical for a Burst Linker to
go to the same school as their Parent.
But there's a small possibility, right?
At any rate, we should look into this.
It's about time the accounts have been distributed and students start logging in to the local network.
Burst L-
Wait!
Chiyu!
You guys are being sneaky again!
I totally know!
You're about to go into the Accelerated World, right?
Well...
Didn't I tell you?
I started this game so I could teach
you both that it's something to be enjoyed.
There's no point if we don't do it together.
Chiyu...
You're right.
Sorry.
Well, Taku, could you take a look at the corridor?
You'll be using one Burst Point anyway, so let's check out Chiyu's duel avatar while you're at it.
What should I do?
Just stay there.
I'll challenge you to a duel straight away.
Let's go.
Burst Link!
Ooh, is this me?
Wow, so that's your duel avatar, Chiyu.
The system gave you the name of Lime Bell.
Lime Bell?
Isn't the color a little flashy?
Stop complaining!
It's hard to get a color with such high saturation.
Wait, are you Haru?
Yes.
Oh? Avatars are the expressions of your traumatic experiences, huh?
I see.
You don't have to say it! I already know!
So, is that you, Taku?
You're just as I thought you'd be, unlike Haru.
Haru.
It doesn't look like there's a
Burst Linker among the new students.
Yeah, those listed are...
Silver Crow,
Black Lotus,
Cyan Pile,
and Lime Bell.
That's all.
Anyway, so like, Haru and I are
having a duel right now, aren't we?
Wait!
Do you even know the rules?
Taku already told me most of it.
You basically need to win lots of fights to get
lots of points to reach Level 10 and clear the game, right?
It sounds so simple when you put it like that.
Hey, do I have any special moves?
Geez...
Okay, you know how your HP gauge is around here on your screen?
You can open your skill list there.
Special moves, though...
Found it!
Hmm...
Citron Call!
Huh?
See? Just listen to what I have to say.
Your gauge needs to be fully
charged to use your special move.
When you damage or get damaged from your opponent...
O-Or if you destroy those objects over there...
Really?!
This feels good!
She's ruthless...
Huh? Her HP isn't going down.
You should take some damage when
you destroy objects in the Factory stage.
Her defence might be really high.
Take this!
U-Uh...
What?
N-Nah, I just figured your gauge should be about full, so it might work now.
Oh, you're right.
You should've told me earlier.
Time to try again!
Citron Call!
Huh?
What the heck?
Nothing happened!
That can't be right.
Maybe your move blinds people.
That's such a lame special move!
Haru, give me one of yours!
What?!
That's really not possible, though!
Her gauge went down a lot for just a blinding technique.
But it doesn't damage or weaken the opponent.
Which means...
Could it be...?!
Chii-chan.
What?
Hit Haru with that bell.
I was totally gonna do that anyway.
What?!
It didn't go down enough.
Hit him two more times.
What?! Taku!
That should be enough.
Chii-chan, try using your special move on Haru again.
Okay.
Citron...
...Call!
If I'm interpreting this correctly...
Huh? What's happening?
My HP is being recovered...
I knew it.
Lime Bell is...
...a healer!
A healer?
This is incredible!
Huh?
A healer?!
Yes.
Taku was surprised too.
He told me to keep it a secret as it might cause an uproar.
Takumu-kun's absolutely right.
If the rumor spreads, Burst Linkers from all over Tokyo will gather at Suginami and a scouting battle will begin.
Are healers really that amazing?
The Accelerated World was created seven years ago.
Only two Burst Linkers with
healing abilities have appeared since.
In fact, one of them was so sick of being
fought over that he left the Accelerated World.
So now there's only one healer other than Lime Bell...
What's more, that person is one of the Six Kings.
A king?!
What color?
Senpai?
Sorry.
Right now, I don't want to even tell you that person's name.
I don't want you to have even
the smallest interest in that person.
Senpai...
I trust you, of course.
I know you aren't interested in the other kings and won't be tempted by them.
Even so, I can't stop myself from worrying about it.
Haruyuki-kun.
You belong to me.
You always have, and you always will.
Forever and ever.
I won't let anyone else have you.
O-Of course...
We've veered off topic.
At any rate, healing abilities are powerful
because they are so rare in the Accelerated World.
I see.
So, where's Kurashima-kun?
She's probably being lectured by Taku
on how she can't be doing anything rash.
It looks like she and I will need to
have a heart-to-heart chat sometime.
Y-Yeah.
Senpai and Chiyu having a chat?
It's going to get messy.
Legions?
Yeah.
Haru and I belong to Nega Nebulous.
The leader is Princess Snow Black?
Yeah.
I'll join.
Really?
Yeah, if it means the three of us can be together like we used to.
Chii-chan.
We can go back to how it used to be, right?
I'll be going now.
Oh, right.
Let me know if you'd like me to get you anything from Okinawa.
Okinawa?
Are you going on a trip?
You didn't know?
The seniors are all going on a school trip this Sunday.
What? A school trip?!
I'll leave things in your care while I'm gone.
Though, only Kurashima-kun's case will be delayed for the ten days I'm away.
W-Wait a second here!
What about the territory battles?!
Defend it with your life.
I won't accept seeing the flag of
another Legion flying in Suginami.
B-But...
How about this?
If you successfully defend the place next week, as a reward, I'll grant you one wish. Any wish.
A reward?
Well, think about it.
A reward...
Are you sure this will do?
Yes! This is the best!
No!
That's not it!
You want me to cable with you?
Y-Yes.
Thank you very much.
My breathing!
She'll feel the breathing from my nose!
You belong to me.
I'm such a bad person!
I'll go home and calmly think about it.
O-Ow...
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm glad you aren't hurt.
Bye...
Senpai.
A new student?
Defend it with your life, huh?
That's just like our master.
Just like her? You seem pretty calm about this.
The two of us will have to fight
the territory battle by ourselves.
We have no other choice.
I expected this would happen eventually, ever since I joined Nega Nebulous.
So, what about Chiyu?
I mean, she has healing abilities, right?
Even if she doesn't fight, she can help us...
We can go back to how it used to be, right?
Taku? What's wrong?
Hey, Haru.
Nah, it's nothing.
Entrance:   Kendo Club Practice Matches
Go, Taku!
Sorry I'm late.
I got lost.
How's Taku doing?
He just allowed a point, so it's 1 to 1.
He's not as intimidating as he used to be, but he's doing his best.
I see.
It's because he stopped using his acceleration powers.
Taku!
If you can't even win the school tournament,
you won't stand a chance in outside matches!
A point! And a victory!
He did it!
That's our Taku.
That's the student who...
The final match. Noumi on red.
Okay!
Umesato Junior High
Noumi
Noumi...
Mayuzumi on white.
Okay!
Umesato Junior High
Mayuzumi
Begin!
What's with the new student?
Something is...
Go, Taku! Send him flying!
Come on, Haru. Cheer for him too!
R-Right...
Oh, come on! You're too quiet...
A point!
Taku...
What was that?
Begin!
That's weird.
My blade should've hit him, but not only did
he dodge it, he also managed to get the point.
No way!
But...
Burst...
Burst Link.
We did so much checking, though...
Why was he never listed?
I can't find him. Why?
I'm pretty sure he said "Burst".
Taku...
Chiyu...
Burst Out.
Head!
A point!
And a victory!
The winner is Noumi, the red side!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next stage: Arrestation.
Snow Black leaves on a trip.
Haruyuki is left behind and becomes
entangled in an arrestation.