Yellow Radio.
What's the Yellow King doing here?!
King? So that's...
...the leader of the Yellow Legion, a Level 9 Burst Linker?!
I see. So it was you!
You planned all of this out, Yellow Radio!
Oh, my.
Hello to you, Red King.
What a coincidence to meet you here!
Don't act all innocent!
It's obvious you were waiting for us!
That's right!
One second in real world time is 17 minutes here,
so there's no meeting someone here without planning.
That's a horrible accusation.
I was just out looking for someone from the Red Legion to take responsibility for breaking the Non-Aggression Pact
and stripping one of my adorable subordinates of all his points.
The Yellow King was the one
who hid away the Calamity Armor!
He then gave it to Cherry Rook to lure out Niko, or Scarlet Rain.
The Non-Aggression Pact states the following.
In the event a Legion member is forced to uninstall
the program due to an attack in violation of the pact,
his Legion can choose anyone from the
offending Legion to meet the same fate.
What a coincidence that the person would be
the leader of the Red Legion herself, Scarlet Rain!
This was all so he could hunt for the
head of a king, needed to reach Level 10!
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
I see.
I see now!
I'm glad you understand.
However, the Pact also states this.
You can choose anyone for revenge,
but the rule isn't applicable if the Legion Master of the offender punishes him by taking away all his points.
That's true.
But I've heard a certain rumor.
You tried to do that a few days ago but failed spectacularly.
You're free to try again, of course.
But when will the offender appear? When will you defeat him?
If you can't take care of him immediately,
I'm afraid we'll have to make do with you after all.
This is a trap, Niko.
Let's log out.
We'll find some other chance to-
We can't.
It's impossible to log out instantly in the Unlimited Neutral Field.
That's right, Haru.
To leave, you have to go to one of the Leave Points scattered throughout.
That's how the system works.
L-Let's go to a Leave Point, then.
The closest ones to here would be in Ikebukuro Station or Sunshine City.
We'd have to fight our way out to reach either one.
However, that bastard Radio made a miscalculation.
A miscalculation?
Yes.
That bastard assembled all these people just to hunt me down,
but there's one more king here now.
And so, Black Lotus,
you'll just quietly observe the fun carnival that's about to start, won't you?
You must be joking, Yellow Radio.
Why should I act according to your plans?
Oh my, how rebellious.
And I had just prepared a special present for you.
What's that?
The first Red King, Red Rider!
The first Red King?
So we've been fighting each other for such a pointless goal?
We hate, steal from, and kill each other.
It's not right!
We lead Legions and continue to fight
each other not because we're enemies,
but because we are rivals!
I like the way you fight, Lotus.
I'm sure we'd become friends if we met in the real world.
In fact, I'd like to become friends.
That's why I don't want to fight you in a Sudden Death duel.
Don't you feel the same?
Wait right there, Rider!
I can't ignore what you just said.
No, I didn't mean it like that...
Whoops.
You're right.
It's just as you said, Rider.
I like you too.
In a respectful sense, of course.
I knew you'd understand, Lotus.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
Let's do this instead.
Wait right there!
Don't get angry.
It's her way of shaking hands.
Death By Embracing.
No...
No!
Wonderful memories, aren't they?
S-Stop it.
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
S-Senpai?
H-Haruyuki-kun.
I...
S-Senpai!
Senpai! Senpai!
Zero Fill.
Lotus, I had no idea...
I figured she wouldn't have gotten over that betrayal yet!
Though, it's ridiculous how she's aiming
for Level 10 when her resolve's that weak.
Prepare to attack.
Come, Enhanced-
Don't, Red King!
If you activate your weaponry, you won't be able to move!
We should be retreating to the Leave Point at Sunshine City!
Haru, I'll act as cover,
so take care of our master!
Yeah, but what about you?
If they defeat the Red King,
they'll definitely come after our master next.
We can't let that happen.
Okay!
Commence attack!
Let's go!
Okay!
It really hurts! What the heck is this?
Haru, careful!
You feel double the pain in the Unlimited Neutral Field.
Geez!
Taku!
Run, Haru!
Got it!
Almost there!
We're almost at the crater's edge!
Once we're there, I'll take Senpai and Niko, and...!
That's not gonna work.
Silly Go Round!
What's going on?
The field's spinning...
No, it just looks that way.
Close your eyes and run!
Get down!
Taku!
It's fine, Haru.
This is nothing compared to the debt I owe you...
No! You don't owe me anything!
How many times must I tell you, Taku?!
Taku!
I take back what I said about you
being nothing but brains, Cyan Pile.
30 more seconds.
Radio's special move will be over in 30 seconds.
Roger.
I hear you're supposed to be pretty tough, but it
looks like they're nothing more than rumors, Cyan Pile.
Remember this before you die.
The one who defeated you is Sax...
I'm not interested in your stupid name!
Lightning Cyan Spike!
Taku!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Haru.
Splash Stinger!
Taku, you really are amazing.
I'm proud to have you as a friend.
Taku...
Senpai. Senpai.
Princess Snow Black.
Why won't you stand up?
It's no use, Silver Crow.
Right now, the signals generated by her soul that should
be transmitting to her avatar have been reduced to zeros.
A Burst Linker with no will to fight can't operate their Duel Avatar.
If you don't have the strength to face your wounds, you won't even be able to stand up.
That's the type of game Brain Burst is.
Wounds of the heart...
Take Lotus and go, Silver Crow.
I'm sorry.
I know Cyan Pile sacrificed himself to buy us time...
...but it's not in my personality to just run away from this.
M-Me too!
I can't run away either.
I won't leave my friends behind and run away!
Friends?
You really are a complete idiot.
Do whatever you want.
Yellow Radio!
The special move gauge you worked so hard to fill must be empty by now.
Now it's my turn to return the favor!
Don't forget.
If I defeat you, you'll be banished from here forever!
Come, Enhanced Armament!
Sorry, Silver Crow,
but take care of the close combat fighters that hang around my ass.
If I'm defeated, take Lotus and fly away.
Niko...
What are you so afraid of?!
That's just a stationary fort!
It's nothing but a lump of iron at close quarters!
There's no need to be scared.
Go!
You bastards are gonna find out just what it means to face the Red King!
A-Amazing...
Senpai.
You're in the way, scum!
Magnetron Wave!
It sucks up metal-colored Linkers nicely.
Y-You idiot!
My special move only last 13 seconds!
Metal-colored Linkers are weak against close combat specialists, so when you face them,
make sure you elude their attacks
and use their momentum against them.
Your reaction speed should be fast enough.
You're doing pretty good for a weakling, Silver Crow!
Why, thank you!
They're jamming me! Find them, Crow!
It's probably one of the yellow Linkers!
Roger!
Electric Therapy!
Stay down for just a little while, kid!
Until we're done stripping the Red King!
Shit!
What an awful and comical sight!
Not a shred of royal dignity!
You're just a red upstart and a black traitor, after all.
All right!
The Red King isn't such a big deal.
You guys, strip her down and drag her out!
S-Senpai...
Senpai!
Are you sure about this?
Is this the ending you wanted, Black King?!
What is accelerating and Brain Burst to you?!
Is your desire to become the first Linker to reach Level 10
really so weak that you'll abandon it
over the memory of one guy?!
How long are you going to sleep there for?!
Didn't you swear that you'd destroy and mow down any obstacles
and push on forward until you were the last one standing?!
Black Lotus!
Senpai...
Haruyuki-kun.
Yes!
You make it sound like Rider and I were lovers.
Huh?
A-Am I wrong?
Completely wrong!
Didn't I tell you?
You're my first.
Also, stop laying around and try
putting one hand into the ground.
Crap!
Of course, the earth!
You can handle the rest yourself.
I'm going to take care of our little friend.
Take this!
Sorry.
Grapple-type moves don't really work on me.
I harbor no grudges against any of you...
...but anyone who fights against me is going to lose a limb or two.
What's more, it'll be twice as painful in this field...
...but it's too late to run away now!
Wait, I'm in the middle of charging my battery!
Like I'd wait!
Good point!
Why?
Why must you show up now
and disrupt my plans, Black Lotus?!
Have you already forgotten about our friend that you betrayed and beheaded?!
I wonder where he is and what he's doing right now!
I wonder if he thinks about how he can never return to the Accelerated World and about the person who did that to him.
If it was me, I'd never forget about it.
I might have if it was a fair fight,
but not with a surprise attack like that!
Senpai!
You got one thing wrong, Yellow Radio.
Oh? What is it?
You think the taking of your head will weigh as heavily on me as taking Red Rider's.
I'll tell you just one more thing.
I disliked you from the moment we met!
Rain, I take it you've finished
recharging your remaining weapons.
Crow, protect her!
Here I go!
I need a little more time!
Crow, where's the source of that jamming signal?
Found it!
This time...
...will be different!
Niko!
Go!
Lotus!
It's so fast!
So this is a battle between two Level 9 Linkers!
Take a good look at it.
This is the first serious battle between two Level 9 Linkers since the beginning of the Accelerated World!
It's about time.
Huh?
It's about time their special move gauges are fully charged.
The real battle starts now!
Lotus' special move will probably be a direct attack type.
Radio's will probably be an illusion type.
The decider will be whether Lotus can land
the attack before Radio's special move activates.
Death By Piercing!
Futile Fortune Wh-
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next Stage: Absolution.
It's time to settle this.
Should a crime for love be absolved?