Haruyuki Arita
One more time...
Start!
Haruyuki Arita
I have to become faster and stronger.
For her sake...
For the sake of being her partner.
Territory, or the right for Legions to control areas,
is decided by territory battles every Saturday evening.
In a battle where both teams have
equal numbers, regardless of the level,
you must maintain an average win ratio of 50%.
We'll handle this. You go.
We're counting on you, Haru.
Use our winning strategy!
Leave it to me!
First, I'll crush the foothold of my enemies,
then I'll come down from the sky, and in one go...!
Damn it...
Like we'd keep falling for the same trick.
Once we're used to it, your aviating just makes you an easy target.
Haruyuki Arita
What was that scream?
Are you okay?
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Is that why you put that application together to do extreme training?
I was invincible when I first started flying,
but I've been stuck since becoming Level 4.
We've made no progress in expanding Nega Nebulous' territory either.
But you didn't need to resort to an illegal patch.
I'm not too sure if you should push the limits of your pain tolerance.
But without its aviating ability, Silver Crow is just a vulnerable melee fighter.
That's why I have to learn how to avoid anti-air fire!
Well, you can take your time with that.
Our master said so, didn't she?
This is so boring.
The three of us are finally walking home together, but all you talk about is that game.
Oh. I'm sorry, Chii-chan.
How about treating me to some more Enjiya ice cream?
I'll have all types of the jumbo parfait this time!
Well, that's...
And a tiramisu dorayaki.
Geez, whatever.
Still...
Still, I...
...want to become stronger!
Welcome back, Onii-chan.
Thanks.
A cherubim?
Or should I say, an angel?
I'm baking some cookies right now, so wait just a bit, Onii-chan!
She's too real to be a fantasy or a delusion.
This means someone must've set up some sort of visual deception trap on my Neuro Linker!
Because there's no way my little sister could be this cute!
Hey! What are you doing?
S-So they even programmed her to feel real?!
Damn it!
She's still here?
Of course.
Have you forgotten about me?
I'm Saito Tomoko from Nakano.
Saito-san from Nakano?
I'm a fifth grader at elementary school.
I believe we're second cousins.
I'm young and inexperienced, but please be kind to me.
This morning
Saya Arita
One of our relatives is leaving
her kid here for two or three days.
She has a last-minute business trip, and I'm going to Shanghai today, remember?
Please take care of her for me.
This morning
Saya Arita
Sorry for using your kitchen without asking.
I figured you'd be hungry when you got home, so...
Th-Thanks.
I'll have one.
How did you get a key?
Your mom issued me an instant key.
It's delicious!
Really?
I'm glad!
Don't move.
U-Um, uh...
Uh... what should we do now?
P-Play a game, maybe?
I don't really play games.
I don't like Neuro Linkers very much.
H-How about one of those old 2D movies, then?
Well, how about we talk instead?
I want to know about your junior high school life!
You're pretty cute, Onii-chan!
So this is what it's like to have a little sister?
The two of us will be alone for
three days until Mom gets home...
No, no!
It's too good to be true.
Do I really have a second cousin like her?
Saito-san from Nakano...
It's no good.
I can't find any photos of her.
How about here?
Onii-chan.
Can I get in too?
Uh... ah, huh?
You're taking too long, so I got tired of waiting.
Th-Then...
Sorry, I'll be done soon! Wait just a little longer!
It's okay. We're second cousins and all.
No, it's not okay at all!
D-Don't stare at me like that.
Tomoko-chan.
What, Onii-chan?
You're a new Burst Linker, aren't you?
You have tan marks on your neck.
There are also some photos on my grandpa's home server.
I don't know about saying this...
...but you're about ten times cuter.
You poked around that much?
You're too damn paranoid.
S-So you forged that mail from my mom and Saito-san.
Were you planning to use me to hack my Legion Master?
Huh? What are you talking about?
I understand why you'd feel that you can't defeat the Black King, Black Lotus, in a fair fight,
but this is pretty underhanded...
Yeah? You were saying?
Who are you talking about?
W-Well, I'm talking about you...
I'm sick of this bullshit.
I'll force you to listen to what I say!
I, Scarlet Rain, am gonna make you pay for insulting me! Just you wait!
Watch out!
I'm gonna kill you...
Scarlet?
Is she a Burst Linker from the Red Legion?
It's me.
Why the call at this hour, Haruyuki-kun?
Sorry for calling so late.
I have something to ask.
Oh? What is it?
Have you heard of a Burst Linker called Scarlet Rain?
Is something wrong?
Indeed, I only told you their aliases and not their real names.
You haven't been doing your research, though.
Scarlet Rain is the second Red King herself.
Yes?
Y-You're the Red King?!
Burst Link!
Uh, are you really the Red King?
No way...
No, I shouldn't run.
The red color specializes in long-ranged attacks.
Running away would be the stupidest thing to do!
Oh? You're not gonna run?
That's pretty courageous!
But you haven't forgotten, right?
About what?
I said I was gonna kill you...
...you perv!
That was unavoidable!
Plus, you were the one who
came in while I was taking a bath!
In games, there's usually a way to fight a giant, armed machine like this...
All right, I have its back!
If I aim for the joints where the armor is thinnest...!
It's burning!
Oh, right.
Silver Crow is metal-colored, so flames don't affect me!
I've got you now!
In your dreams, kid!
W-Wait...!
We're inside a building!
You're kidding me!
She destroyed herself.
No matter how fortified her avatar is, this-
Heat Blast Saturation!
No way!
Oh, you're flying.
I've always wanted to try out my anti-air fire.
J-Just saying, but it's always a single robot that takes down the giant battleship!
Not when a perv is piloting it, dumbass!
Hailstorm Domination!
I can see them... I think!
Silver Crow's "All or Nothing" kick!
Take this!
I guess I win, Onii-chan.
Looks like it.
Will you listen to my request, then?
Request?
Let me meet your Legion Master.
In the real world.
In the flesh, both of us.
Hey.
Morning, Haruyuki-kun.
Good morning, Senpai.
As always...
As always, you're here early.
Of course.
The junior-year classrooms are closer to here.
Y-You're right.
I'd also rather wait for you than have you wait for me.
The moment you appear in the entrance
makes for a precious and wonderful memory.
By the way, what exactly was yesterday's call about?
You mentioned the Red King.
Uh, um...
Well, about that...
That's what happened.
That was fast.
I really want to lecture you on how you
should've realized it when you first saw her...
But I guess it's difficult to think that the Red King herself would resort to something as reckless as a real-world hack.
I-I guess.
Why would she want to meet me, though?
What's her aim?
She said she'd explain after meeting you.
Movement.
Well, just take it as a valuable learning experience.
Y-Yes, it was valuable in many ways...
No matter how many Burst Points you have, a
direct battle with a king isn't something you can buy.
What was the second Red King like?
Well, she was insane!
She blasted off half the government office building in one hit and completely destroyed my apartment.
I hear Scarlet Rain spends all of her level-up bonuses on improving her long-distance firepower.
Did the Red King move at all during battle?
Yes.
But only about 50 centimeters.
Ooh, that's impressive.
The unmoving fort, Immobile Fortress.
She got her second name not because she can't move, but because she doesn't need to move.
I would've surrendered right away if I knew that.
I thought the Red King would be called "Red something".
Like I said on the phone, you need to do more research.
In the Accelerated World, the only one with red in their title is Red Rider...
Senpai?
I publicly beheaded the Red King, who was championing for peace.
Senpai, was the previous Red King someone important to you?
Sorry for being so insensitive.
Last night's call and the question just now...
I'm really sorry.
No, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I thought I had it all figured out a long time ago.
I decided that all Burst Linkers
other than myself were my enemies.
So to suddenly feel like this...
...is absolutely hilarious.
I-I...
I'll never fight against you.
I'll never be your enemy.
You are my Parent and I am your Child.
We're family before being competitors.
Am I right?
Senpai...
Senpai probably knows.
That in reality, even a Parent and Child might have to fight each other.
But even so, I'll still...
I'll still never fight her!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next Stage: Escalation.
The armor's history is spoken of.
The escalating situation engulfs
Haruyuki and his friends.