Well, let's go.
Huh?
What's this?
It's like a dream where I have both an older and a younger sister...
Hey.
What's with that smirk on your face?
You'd better not be fantasizing
this early in the morning, perv!
I'm not! I'm not!
Since you're in charge of the details of today's mission,
you won't have problems finding out where
and when Chrome Disaster will appear, right?
Yeah. I got this.
Okay.
We're going, then.
See you.
Okay, bye-
Wait, something's not quite right here!
It's going to be cloudy all day today.
I hope it doesn't rain.
Y-Yeah.
Woah, woah! I can't believe it.
I'm going to school with Senpai!
Haruyuki-kun.
Your tie's crooked.
Th-Thanks.
No!
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
sekai e
To a new world
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Umesato Junior High School
You sure like to live dangerously, Haru.
No, I don't! Not at all!
You really helped me out back then, though.
You smoothed things out so well.
So that's why Senpai had no choice but to stay at Haru's place.
What? That game again?
It's hard to believe, though.
I don't get what you mean by accelerating.
Didn't I show you the other day?
I know!
Install a copy of that Brain thingymabob in me!
Then I can become a Burst Linker too!
You think Chii-chan was serious?
Nah, it won't work.
Chiyu's pretty slow.
What do you think, my master?
About Chii-chan-
About Kurashima's chances of becoming a Burst Linker.
Well, does she even meet the first condition?
The one about having a Neuro Linker equipped since birth?
Yes.
Yeah, I think she meets the condition.
I see.
Actually, there aren't strict standards for the
second condition concerning cerebral reaction speed.
People who aren't good at VR games have been able to install it.
Really?
The circuit that moves your body is almost
the same as the one that moves your avatar.
You should give your real body a little more exercise.
Though, it's a big gamble to make someone a
Burst Linker when you aren't sure of their suitability.
A gamble?
Currently, the Brain Burst copy license,
or the right to make someone your Child,
can only be used once, regardless of its success.
O-Only once?
That's why a strong bond develops
between a Burst Linker Parent and Child.
Takumu-kun.
Yes.
If you become Kurashima's Parent and successfully install Brain Burst in her,
a strong relationship should form between you and her.
However, bear in mind that not
everything about it will be positive.
I'll keep that in mind.
Senpai used her one valuable chance on me...
That reminds me...
Looks like the break's over.
We'll talk about Chrome Disaster later.
Okay.
Who is Senpai's Parent?
Snow Black
Can we talk during
the next break?
Send
Can we talk during
the next break?
Send
Sorry for calling you here,
but I'm a little curious about something...
Or should I say, I want to ask you something...
You want to ask me who my Parent is, right?
Sorry, but I can't tell you yet.
I don't want you to come in contact with that
person, however slim the chances of that are.
As a Legion Master...
...and as a girl.
Ugly as this jealousy might be.
Senpai...
That person was once very close to me,
someone I had believed would shine brilliantly forever at the center of my world,
keeping all the darkness and the cold away.
Just like how you are to me.
However, it was...
...all an illusion.
You could even say that person is now my greatest enemy.
I want to fight that person right now, chop off their limbs,
and watch that person beg for mercy flat on the ground...
...before I ruthlessly cut that person's head off.
However, my wish will never be granted.
Do you know the critical difference between a Parent-Child relationship and a typical Burst Linker relationship?
Both Parent and Child know the real identities of each other?
Exactly.
Because they know each other in reality,
events in the Accelerated World can affect
and even magnify emotions in the real world.
Not just love and affection,
but also anger and hatred.
So while the Parent-Child relationship is the strongest bond in the Accelerated World,
it can also become the strongest curse.
Curse?
You can't fight even if you wanted to, because the real world implications can't be ignored.
If that's not a curse, then what is it?
And this is in spite of the fact that Burst Linkers exist to fight!
Even if things turn out that way, I'll never fight you!
If it happens, I'll uninstall Brain Burst before we fight!
Fool! If that happens-
I won't fight you!
I've sworn not to!
No matter what the future holds,
the one thing I won't regret is choosing you.
Senpai...
Both Takumu-kun and I will go to our homes to
drop off our stuff before heading to your place.
We'll start our mission after that.
I'm home.
Oh, welcome back.
Chrome Disaster hasn't moved yet.
What's wrong?
W-Well...
What?
D-Do you hate Princess Snow Black?
Huh? Why?
Well, she's the one who killed the previous Red King
and is the most wanted person in the Accelerated World.
Oh, that.
I don't actually hate her.
In fact, I'm grateful to her.
Huh?
It's thanks to her killing my predecessor and breaking up
my Legion that I was able to become the Red King.
And anyway, I've never even
talked to the previous Red King.
I-I see.
Plus...
N-Not a word about this to her, got it?! Not a word!
Wh-What?
I think she's amazing.
She's so motivated and all.
H-How come?
While I and the other kings pretend to fight each other under the tepid Territory Non-Aggression Pact,
she's the only one who's declared her aim to reach Level 10.
Though, I'm sure there are others who are secretly plotting the same thing.
A-Are you?
Huh?
Are you aiming for Level 10?
I don't know.
Some of the kings believe that Brain Burst will end the moment a Burst Linker reaches Level 10.
When that happens, Brain Burst would be
forcefully uninstalled from all Burst Linkers.
N-No way...
I think there's a chance that it's true.
Honestly, though, I don't even want to think about it.
That's how addicted I am to the Accelerated World.
But it's this kind of addiction that
has twisted the Accelerated World.
Chrome Disaster is a good example of that.
Cherry Rook reached for the Calamity Armor
because he wanted to reach a higher level in a world that has stagnated due to the Non-Aggression Pact.
And the one who made him do it, in a sense...
...was none other than me.
N-Niko...
Shut up! Don't look at me!
Go away!
Actually, just forget everything I said!
Right now!
I'll send you flying otherwise!
Wh-What the hell are you doing, you perv-
Niko, you didn't do anything wrong.
It's natural to want to stay in the game world and hope the game will never end.
However, I've learned one thing from playing all those online games.
There's nothing lonelier or sadder than the end of a game with no ending.
More and more players get bored and move on to other games...
And one day, even NPCs like your favorite blacksmith
or landlady disappear forever as they smile.
I've experienced that moment and cried many, many times.
That isn't how games should end.
It definitely isn't!
If Brain Burst really does have an ending, then we should be aiming for it!
Even if it means losing our acceleration powers,
it's easily the right thing to do, rather than seeing the world end so unreasonably!
The right thing, huh?
I didn't expect a Burst Linker to use those words.
You're pretty weird.
To be honest, I was wondering why a fat loser like you would have the unique aviating ability,
but I think I'm starting to understand.
But...
How long are you gonna keep
grabbing my foot for, you giant perv?!
There he is!
Cherry got on a train on the Seibu Ikebukuro line.
If he follows his usual pattern,
he'll be hunting in Ikebukuro today.
Ikebukuro, huh?
How shall we get there?
Do we travel in the real world, or...
Let's go from the inside.
With a team like this, no Enemy will be able to stop us.
Indeed.
Enemy?
Haruyuki-kun, do you remember the command I taught you when you became Level 4?
Y-Yes.
Well then, I'll take you to the
true battleground for us Burst Linkers.
You need to use 10 points to enter. No problems with that, right?
Y-Yes, if it's only 10 points.
What do you mean by the true battleground, though?
What the words mean.
It's where you can find the essence
of what we call the Accelerated World.
Let's go.
The mission to slay the fifth Chrome Disaster starts now.
Do you want to connect to the globalnet?
Unlimited Burst!
Where's this?
S-So this is the Unlimited Neutral Field.
That's right.
We used it before to hunt the Calamity Armor.
Have you noticed anything else, by the way?
What do you mean?
There's no time limit!
That's right.
That's what makes it an unlimited field.
Once you're here, you can stay forever.
Of course, you have to be Level 4 or above to enter.
We've accelerated, right?
Of course.
So if we were to stay here for
a whole day in real world time...
Uh...
Th-Three years?!
Why didn't you tell me earlier, Taku?!
There's so much I could've done!
It's better if you don't.
He's right.
If it's for a few days, you might just end up missing a few appointments.
But if you spend a month or half a year here, you'll be a different person when you return.
It's only natural.
While your body won't have aged, your soul will have.
The soul's age...
Anyway, we should get moving.
We have two minutes of real world time from when we accelerated to when Cherry's train will arrive at Ikebukuro.
That's plenty of time.
Indeed.
But how are we getting to Ikebukuro?
Are we going to run?
Obviously not.
Why do you think we brought you?
Huh?
You'll carry me, won't you? Onii-chan?
What?!
What are you talking about?
I'm the one he's going to hold.
I mean, just look at my limbs.
You see?
Rain, you can hang on to Silver Crow's legs.
You're kidding!
It's your fault that you're designed like that.
Go ride the train by yourself.
What did you say?
Well, how about this?
I'll-
Nobody asked you, four-eyes!
That's right, Prof!
Chii chan
You take it from here.
Taku!
Well, what will you do?
What are you going to do, Silver Crow?
Uh...
I'll start by charging up my special move gauge.
You doing okay, Haru?
Y-Yeah.
I can't fly very fast, though.
It's not too late.
Shouldn't Lotus take the train instead?
What did you say?
Why don't you go?
Um, please stop arguing.
I'm scared we might end up falling.
Wow...
It seems to go on forever.
So this is the actual Accelerated World.
It exists next to the real world.
A permanent world, not a temporary stage.
That's right.
It's also the true battlefield for Burst Linkers.
If you're going to become Level 9, you, too, will have to fight here and win someday.
The time hasn't come yet, though.
What's that sound?
Over there, Haruyuki-kun.
Look.
Wh-What's that?
An Enemy.
Inhabitants of this world, created and operated by the system.
Why would something like that...?
Well...
The hunt's about to begin.
That's... the hunt?
Yes.
Do you understand now?
Enemies are the only way to earn points other than the usual duels.
Though, even if you defeat a big monster
like that, you only get about 10 points at most.
Th-That's all?!
The hunt is a support component of the fighting game Brain Burst.
However, it's currently just about the only way to reach the highest levels.
Oh, because of the Joint Non-Aggression Pact...
But aren't there other methods, my master?
Yes.
Like what?
Basically, there are other things
to hunt here than just Enemies.
What's more, they're worth a lot more points.
I see.
Not the Enemy, but the other Burst Linkers!
Correct.
Because of the Joint Non-Aggression Pact, high level
Burst Linkers rarely venture out of their Legion's territories.
But when they come out here to hunt,
they can fight each other as much as they want.
That's exactly what Cherry Rook...
Or should I say, Chrome Disaster, is doing.
We're almost at Ikebukuro.
Ikebukuro is huge, though.
Do you know where he'll appear?
If he follows his usual pattern, he'll
show up somewhere around Sunshine City.
Pick any building to-
Haru!
Is that Chrome Disaster?!
It can't be!
It's too soon!
Plus, he doesn't have a move like that...
I'll land!
Here come the missiles!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes.
Somehow.
Who are these guys?
They don't look very friendly to me.
A-A clown?
Yellow Radio.
What's the Yellow King doing here?!
King? So that's...
...the leader of the Yellow Legion, a Level 9 Burst Linker?!
But the Yellow Legion's territory spans from Ueno to Akihabara.
Why are they in Ikebukuro?
I see. So it was you!
You planned all of this out, Yellow Radio!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next stage: Obligation.
A past of betrayal and
a wound that won't heal.
The chains of obligation
torment the Black King.