The Calamity Armor: Chrome Disaster.
But how?
We should've still had a day's worth of time in this world!
Don't tell me...
He accelerated on the train?!
Deceit Firecracker!
Get devoured!
Get devoured and become my meat!
This isn't even a fight anymore!
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
fumikonde mezameru
sekai e
UTW Presents
Accel World
utsumuki sugite chiisai
Curling up all the time has made me feel small
boku dake no keshiki ga kumitateta diorama no uso dato
I've realized my very own view is antagonistic
awasezurai shiten ni kizuite iru
And an assembled diorama of lies
kakedashite yuku mirai wa utsukushisa wo te ni
A future of beauty takes off forward
sorezore ga toberu basho wo toikaketeku
We'll all search for a place where we can fly
kono hitomi wa azayaka ni mau kimi shika shiranai
The splendor of your presence is all my eyes have ever seen
kasoku shite hajimete yukeru boku wa boku no saki e
Now I can accelerate beyond myself for the first time
motto takaku motto tsuyoku kimi ni todokitai
Higher and stronger so I can reach you
fumikonde mezameru
I'll take the first step and wake up
chasin' the world
Damned rabid dog!
Everyone, retreat!
I'm supposed to help disable him so
the Judgment Blow can be delivered?
I can't!
Oh, you managed to dodge my attack.
S-Senpai...
What's this?
What's wrong with me?
I was saying all those things to Senpai just a while ago...
Why can't I move?
"A Burst Linker with no will to fight can't operate their Duel Avatar".
It's exactly as the little girl said.
I don't want to admit it, but I still
regret my betrayal from two years ago.
Thus, I'm deeply afraid of my own will to fight and desire for victory.
However, Haruyuki-kun.
You're the opposite.
You're afraid of defeat because you believe it will negatively affect your value.
That's why you haven't been performing very well in the territory battles recently.
It's not a belief. It's the truth.
Because I...
Don't misjudge yourself!
I won't abandon you, no matter what happens.
Do you really think the bond between us...
...is that weak?!
Wow...
How can she...?
It's like she's enjoying it...
Run, Senpai!
This is my determination, Haruyuki-kun.
I showed you my ugly side just then.
As your mentor and Parent, I wouldn't be able to face you in the real world if I didn't do anything.
But there's no point if you lose-
And that's where you're mistaken!
A clever retreat? Throw that to the dogs!
Once you've dived into the battlefield, you can only
devote yourself to the fight, regardless of your opponent!
That's right.
Up until now, I was so focused that I
wasn't even aware people were watching...
But now I'm scared everyone will laugh at me if I lose.
I'm caring about what others think of me
even in the Accelerated World...
I'm...
...such a huge idiot!
Well, Haruyuki-kun.
Are you ready to lose in style?
Yes!
Senpai!
Princess Snow Black...
Why?
Why, Niko?!
Or should I say, Scarlet Rain!
You can't have forgotten!
If you defeat Black Lotus, she'll lose all her points!
What about it?
To a Burst Linker, every other Linker is an enemy.
You lose points when you're defeated,
and when it hits zero you're banished forever.
That's all there is to it.
But we're supposed to be...
...allies?
Your naiveté makes me want to puke!
I'll tell you one last thing.
You can't trust anyone in the Accelerated World.
Allies, your Legion, your friends,
and even the Parent-Child bond are all simply illusions!
Once I've taken care of him, I'll dispose of you guys as well.
If you don't want that, you should run away right now.
We'll be enemies the next time we meet.
Must things be this way?
This is so sad to look at.
Geez...
This is why I hate kids.
S-Sen-
She didn't shoot?!
She's just sulking.
What?
The little girl wants to trust, more than anyone,
the final bond between Burst Linkers.
Yes, I can tell.
They're Parent and Child.
The Red King is Disaster's...
I mean, Cherry Rook's Child.
Well, what are you doing?
I'm fine.
Go and help Niko.
Our ally.
Okay!
Stop that!
Y-You...
Why?
We're allies.
And I told you to stop being so naive-
You're the one who's naive.
You're a king! When will you finally get back on your feet?
Brain Burst is nothing more than a curse to him now.
You're the only one who can free him, Niko.
Yeah.
I know.
I know that.
Let's end this.
Aviation ability?!
No, it's a super long-distance jump.
He wants to go to the Sunshine City Leave Point and log out.
Niko.
You'll fire the Judgment Blow this time round, right?
Yes, I know. I'll fire.
For his sake.
In that case, I'll restrain him until you get to him.
You can't do it alone.
He may be hurt, but he's still very nimble.
He'll devour you if he catches you.
Then let him devour me!
So that edge at Sunshine City is the leave point...
If he's in the middle of a leap...
...he can't possibly dodge me!
In that case, I'll aim for the moment he lands.
What's that?
Wires!
I see. So that's how he's been...
What now? How do I stop him?
I know!
More!
I have to accelerate more!
All right!
I...
...want to become strong.
That's all.
I'm sure you understand, right?
Don't you want to be strong too?
You think that means you can be forgiven for everything you did?!
You wore that armor, attacked so many avatars, and even tried to devour Niko, your own Child!
Do you really think that makes it all okay?!
You're not the only one!
Who doesn't want the strength to face every hardship?!
You did it, Silver Crow.
I'll handle the rest.
Cherry and I don't know our parents.
Not in the Accelerated World.
Our real parents in the real world.
I go to an orphanage school.
Because of my personality, I couldn't fit in with the others in school.
I was always playing VR games alone.
But three years ago, a boy two years older than me suddenly talked to me.
His face was really red, and it was funny how he was trying so hard.
He asked me if I wanted to play a more enjoyable game.
Even after I became a Burst Linker, he was
really serious in teaching me all sorts of things.
He shielded and protected me.
However, my level soon caught up with his, surpassed his,
and I was Level 9 before I knew it.
After I was made the Legion Master, I worked really hard.
I didn't pay any attention to what he was
thinking about or what could be bothering him.
When we met in real life, in school, I didn't even notice he was acting strangely.
He wanted to remain as my Parent forever.
So he desired strength and succumbed to the temptation of the Calamity Armor.
If only I had said something to him...
Niko.
It's true that Brain Burst is more than just a game.
I'm always afraid that I'm not strong enough.
I'm also scared that she'll abandon me someday.
But...
I know her real face, name, and voice.
That bond won't disappear, no matter what happens.
So just become friends with him once again in the real world.
In the Accelerated World, you and I are in different Legions,
but in the real world, we were able to become friends.
Friends?!
In your dreams!
You're only just about good enough to be my subordinate.
Wh-What?
Who's subordinate are you talking about?
Senpai! Taku!
I see!
You've revived, now that the
one-hour knockout penalty is up!
Man, you pushed yourself too far.
You too.
Well then, Scarlet Rain.
Do you have anything to say to me?
My bad.
That's all?!
You just fell to the ground and passed out while we were fighting a difficult battle!
It's a Transition.
The Unlimited Neutral Field is of the Chaos element.
And so, it changes at specific intervals.
Anyway, I know it's quite a sight to behold, but there's something we need to do.
Indeed.
Everyone, open your status screen and check your item storage.
If you have the Calamity Armor, make sure you get rid of it.
It's not there.
It's gone for good this time.
Yeah.
Yes.
All right.
Then our mission's complete.
Now, let's go back and have a toast.
Let's open some champagne! Champagne!
Don't be stupid.
Kids drink juice.
I
want
to
devour
Is something wrong, Haru?
N-Nothing! Nothing's wrong!
Was that just my imagination?
I want to devour.
I want
to devour
Everyone's watching.
Senpai must be watching too.
When will he shoot?
If I get shot down again, I'll look really bad...
No!
Then it won't be any different from the last time.
Don't run!
My enemy isn't the rifle.
It's the Burst Linker operating the avatar holding the rifle!
I have to sense the signal to attack in his brain!
Hey, that was a really nice dodge.
U-Uh, um...
I was watching the guy and not his gun,
and I sensed a slight movement as he aimed.
Oh, is that so?
I see.
Huh?
That sniper probably has visual focusing perception.
In other words, the ability to sense it when enemies focus on his gun and automatically lock on to them.
Wait, so the reason I kept getting shot down is...
...you've been focusing on their guns.
N-No way...
Don't be so depressed.
I'm back.
Haruyuki, looks like I won't be able to come home today.
Oh, and I'm sorry, but one of my
colleague's kids is staying over at our place.
Well, good luck!
My prized collection again...
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
We informed the other five kings, including Radio, that Disaster has been taken care of.
I guess that's one thing settled.
I want to raise the question about the Yellows taking the armor, but I have no proof.
So... um...
What about Cherry Rook?
I hear he's moving away next month.
His distant relatives came out and
identified themselves not too long ago.
They're apparently from Fukuoka.
That's far away.
That's why he was panicking.
He thought Brain Burst would be
our only connection if he moved away.
But there aren't many Burst Linkers outside of Tokyo,
so he wouldn't be able to duel and raise his level.
His panic led him to be consumed by the armor...
But, you know...
Maybe it's because he doesn't have Brain Burst anymore.
Today, he was back to his original self, just like when he first talked to me.
That made me think.
Even if he's not a Burst Linker and he moves to Fukuoka,
the Accelerated World isn't the only VR world around, right?
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
So, if you know of any good online VR games, let me know!
Something he and I can play together for a long time.
I see, I see!
Feel free to take any of the games that I have.
They're all kind of the same genre, but...
Wh-What's this?
Well, uh... um...
It's to thank you.
C-Can I...
Can I really have these?
What? Give them back if you don't want them!
No, I'll have them!
Thank you!
I was just a little surprised...
They're good, Niko.
Really good.
Wh-What the hell are you crying for, you idiot?!
You're so embarrassing!
What's with you, you stupid idiot?
Don't eat and cry at the same time!
we are tossed by waves of pain and tears
I'm tossed into the fray
tossed by various fortune
wake up your brain!
flashed in the sky
It's a burst of sensation
akirame ga kureta anraku chintai no sekai
"Resignation" has given me comfort, a dull and boring world
itsukara datta darou fui ni kagayaki hajimeta
I no longer remember when it suddenly started to shine
kawarazu ni ite to negau koto
To wish you would never change
kawari yuku toki ni ikiru bokura
In an era of constant change
hontou no koe wo iienu yume wo
Let my true voice, my secret desires
kimi to tsunagatta sora e hibikasete
Ring out to the sky that connects us
motto tsuyoku
Stronger
kono ryoute de namida subete furiharaetara
If I can use my hands to wipe away all my tears
kondo koso wa tsubuyaku ima to
I will not let this moment of "determination"
kizu sae mo muda ni shinai
And pain go to waste
motto hayaku
Faster
kimi no moto e tatoe hane ga chigireyou tomo
I'll fly to your side, even if my wings are torn to shreds
yugamu sekai hashirinukete
I will race through this twisted world
kankaku no sono mukou e
Beyond my senses
shinjitsu to kasoku shiteku
Accelerating towards "truth"
Next stage: Violation.
A new intruder violates the peace.
A new season arrives
and a new battle begins.