How can he be this way?
Amidst such despair,
when others cling to each other, how can he
speak of survival, as though it's a given?
Why does this man's voice resonate
so strongly within me?
That thing will either disappear or
weaken when the sun hits it.
We just have to last until morning.
We're going to survive.
How can this man's voice
sound so reassuring to me?
Those Who Cling, Those Who Struggle
I hope it's not broken...
I have to get out of here.
Someone!
It hurts...
Is anyone out there?
Someone's out there?
Please...
I can't walk!
Please help...
That was a close call.
It was like a cattle stampede.
I'm sorry for being late.
Are you okay?
Luca!
I've been watching from below.
It looks like Elaine and the others are okay.
Luca!
Now, now...
This isn't the time to get sentimental.
Can you walk?
Yeah, but I can't run.
What should we do?
I-I can't do this!
Don't poke your head out, no matter what.
But what are you going to do, Luca?
I'll figure something out.
I don't want that!
I'm too scared to be alone.
I can't do it!
I need you to stay with me!
Ow...
Both of us won't fit in this barrel.
Besides, who'd seal it?
But...
Honestly, you're such a scaredy-cat!
Luca...
If nothing else, be a
proper scaredy-cat, okay?
Keep quiet, and don't make a sound.
You just might be the type
that survives the longest.
There.
Luca...
Luca!
Ever since that day,
I've felt like I'm wandering
through an endless night.
But I had forgotten...
That this world is a place
where the sun rises.
The time has finally come to
draw this secret sword.
Even just based on that,
I have a big advantage compared to back then.
Shit!
There are too many to burn...
More and more keep showing up!
Take this...
Explosive Fire Sword!
Oh?
Don't act dumb, you shitty bug!
I'll squash you!
Anyway, what's up with these guys?
It's the resentment of those who died
here due to torture or epidemic.
It's absorbing the emotions
of those engulfed,
continuing to expand.
It's full of their hatred
and desire for salvation!
If hate is all something like that takes,
the whole world would've sunk
into a cesspool by now!
Why is it just happening in Albion?
Well...
This is impossible.
It should not be possible.
It's just like before.
It's like I'm in a nightmare.
Is this actually happening in reality?
If you don't want to die, do something.
Lady Farnese...
He still stands and refuses to back down
in this overwhelming nightmare.
In all of this, he is the only certainty!
Shit!
It's coming in from behind, too!
Behind me, Lady Farnese!
O-Oh, God...
Don't pray!
If you pray, your hands are closed.
What's that you're holding?
Here they come!
No!
This is the end...
I'm going to get crushed.
I'm dead! I'm dead!
I'm dead! I'm going to die!
I can't stand it... Let me out.
Let me out of here!
Not now.
I might just die, anyway...
But it's warm.
I don't know if I'll die yet.
The more scared I am, the more alive I feel.
The more blood I cough up,
the more I know that it's warm in my veins!
I'm going to try...
I'm going to try, Luca.
Being scared means that I want to live!
That's...
Incredible.
Both the living and dead. All the souls
here are calling out for one thing.
Right now...
Everything in my world
is one unified thought.
Everything desires me,
the world I will create,
and calls out for it.
Everything will be
fulfilled by one voice.
Singing?
Guts, that...
Huh?
This.
It's resonating with the voices.
Hey...
Guts!
What is this agony coming from?
Oh, God...
Ah, the light overflows...
Griffith!
There will be a pillar of fire
where blind sheep gather on holy ground.
The hour of Heaven's fall...
It has come.
This is bad...
The tower and the monsters
vanished overnight.
Were we just having a bad dream?
I'm alive?
Oh, the puffy lady's alive!
I'm alive...
I'm really alive.
Oh, where's Luca?
Please!
Luca...
Find Luca!
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
Luca jammed me into the barrel.
I don't know what happened after that...
Luca!
Lady!
Damn it...
How will we find her in all this rubble?!
I don't want this...
No, Luca...
Huh?
O-O-Over here!
She said.
H-H-H-Hurry up... Get me out of here.
I-I-I-I'm going to catch a chill!
Luca!
I'm freezing!
You idiot...
There, there...
You're so warm.
It was worth living for.
They're Kushans!
Why are they all the way out here?
The guys from back then.
That is the krishna sena from earlier.
Could he be the one?
I don't know.
Yet just as the divine prophecy said,
there was a calamity in this
land, and he appeared.
The one we seek must be
among them, as well.
No way...
If we don't get outta here after
all that, I'm calling bullshit!
Capture them all!
They must be alive, not unharmed.
Specifically, don't go easy on the
man with the massive sword.
Don't lower your guard until
you've cut off his limbs.
Killing blow!
Personal issues aside,
I cannot think of a better man to have
at my side in such a circumstance.
Although, it may not amount to much...
Whatever.
Damn!
Don't move!
If you make a single move, these women...
Hey.
Taking women and children
as hostages? Barbarians.
Heretics,
how dare you enter our holy
land and do such a thing?!
Azan!
You're tough to kill...
Lady Farnese, I am glad to see you safe.
Thanks.
You, as well, Vice-commander.
We can talk later.
Hmm...
Things have taken a strange turn
in the short time I was away.
Here they come.
What the hell?
Hey, not again!
B-Bada?
Is this the continuation of last night?
Nothing can surprise me anymore.
Zodd...
Why is he here?
How monstrous...
This isn't the time to be impressed.
If we're to escape, it must be now!
Indeed.
Everyone, stay together!
We'll storm through this!
In that moment,
all held their breath.
And all were transfixed.
Griffith...
And all realized...
That what they had desired had come.
All of you, seize that man!
But, Lord Silat...
Stay calm.
This mission is critical for restoring
our Bakiraka Clan's honor!
Have you forgotten our clan's
centuries of torment in exile?
This is our one and only chance.
Capture him before their main forces arrive!
Go!
Good!
Their ranks here have thinned!
Lady Farnese!
Why are you two bumbling around?
Where are Elaine and the swordsman?
Don't tell me they're still back there.
Wait!
Haven't you had enough?
Shut up! Privates can stay back!
What'd you say, brat?
Even the main Kushan forces are here?
They haven't noticed us yet...
No way!
You're leaving those two behind?
What choice do we have?
If we don't, we'll die for sure this time!
Shit!
What the...
Who is he?
He isn't human.
Do we ever get a break?
What now?
He made it!
But against such a large army...
He'll be fine.
I'm sure he'll protect Elaine.
He'd better not die!
I'm gonna collect what he owes me!
Idiot! Keep it down!
Huh...
There were other survivors.
Everyone who fled into the tower died.
And those of little faith who fled
from the tower survived?
I bet none of them will ever
feel like praying again...
Not so fast.
Trying to survive is different
than trying to run from fear.
The survivors did what
they had to do to live,
without their surroundings interfering.
I don't know what God thinks or anything,
but I believe He left humans enough
free will to do what they need to.
Luca, what's that for?
Oh, this?
It's for a chick that died in the egg.
It died without ever leaving the egg.
Without meeting anyone or being known.
A lonely one like that
sleeps beneath the rubble.
I thought I should leave flowers for it.
Any sinner should have at least
one person to mourn them.
But if his wish came true,
what will happen to the world now?
Later, ladies!
I'm gonna bail! Bye!
As thanks, I'll be with you for free.
Whoa!
I'm in a hurry, though...
I'll take you up on it another time!
They were a busy bunch...
Thankfully, they're gone.
I wonder if Elaine's okay.
I'm sure she'll be fine with
that black swordsman.
He even fought Mozgus as an equal.
But...
The strength to protect someone
is different than the strength
to be with someone...
I need to take care of something.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Nina?
Joachim...
You're alive.
I've been wanting to apologize to you...
For before.
I was so scared of you.
I thought they'd kill me
if I didn't rat you out...
I know it's too late for me to say this,
but I really care for you...
I really thought I could go with you.
But I didn't have the courage,
so I ran away.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
W-Wait.
Wh-What did you say?
I'm going to follow the Black Swordsman.
I am leaving the Order.
Later.
In the end, I could not escape
the darkness of my childhood.
Eventually, the darkness took shape
and appeared before me.
As though the fate for one
who continues to fear
is to be led by the Black Swordsman
who stands alone in the darkness.
They left.
Thank goodness...
Hmm, Nina's late.
Hey, introduce me to a noble patron, too!
Me, too.
Someone with more money
than you, if possible.
Are you sure?
Yeah, if I go back now,
I won't be able to leave.
I'm sorry, Luca.
I'm making you worry until the very end.
I'm going with Joachim.
I love you and the others.
But if I stay with you,
I'll end up hating you again someday.
And I'll hate myself, too.
People who are strong will
end up hurting others,
and people who are weak
will end up hating others.
I think I'll go with this man, who has
the same weakness and sin.
If I'm with him, I think we can both
become a little stronger.
And a little kinder.
So slow!
She really is such a handful.
A rift appeared in the frontier that day.
Where the world's shape began to crumble.
2017 Spring
The Next Arc Arrives