Show yourself!
Huh?
What's happening?
Go back.
This is my garden.
The living should go back where they belong.
That appearance...
Hell's Angels
What is this?
An idol.
An idol made of the skin and bones of priests.
Wh-Who is that?
Who are you?
I am no one.
I have never been anyone,
and I was buried without ever
being known to anyone.
I never knew who I was,
nor was there anyone to teach me.
There was nowhere I belonged in this world.
No one needed me,
and no one knew me.
I came to scavenge garbage by night.
And by day, I hid silently in a pit.
After a very long time had passed,
my home became a grave for
the people who lived above.
I was buried...
Crushed by corpses
at the bottom of the pit.
No one knew of it.
But as my consciousness faded,
I met them.
I met the five angels.
Angels?
The angels taught me about the world.
And then, I knew.
The world was full of despair.
And I was to perish and disappear
at its nadir, as no one.
I screamed...
A scream between a dying cry and a birth cry.
The angels answered that call.
They said they would grant my wish.
Wish?
Indeed...
To hatch the perfect world.
You're an egg...
Yes, I am an egg.
The egg of the perfect world.
My wish is that world's wish.
I have been chosen as the one
who will hatch the new world.
This world is too flawed.
So much unjust death...
And the agony and terror of the living,
attempting to escape this fate.
Order, created to conceal the
chaos, yet full of hypocrisy...
The people, appeased by that twisted
order, bringing death to others...
The world is ugly.
What's your plan?
Are you planning revenge
on the townspeople?
It is not revenge.
It is salvation.
For those who are ugly, cowardly,
unscrupulous, fearful.
Clinging to what they hate.
We truly desire only one thing.
It is the first, and the last,
fragment this world lacks.
In other words, God!
H-He's fighting them.
Fighting those monsters
as an equal or more.
Of course!
He's the man I have high expectations for!
Train long and hard as my disciple,
and you will also be proficient.
What is...
What is this?
That man...
Whenever the Black Swordsman
appears, it breaks apart.
The world I know
shatters, with a deafening roar.
Luca, I'm scared!
That's right...
Now that the veil of faith has burned away,
only children, terrified of the
dark, are lit in the gloom...
Let go of me!
Let me go...
Do you have a death wish?
Y-You're the one who's gonna die!
What? What? What happened?
His manhood's been shattered!
All right, then...
Please hold back, master.
This is our job.
Father Mozgus, please fulfill
your own sacred task.
Ah, forgive me.
I have allowed myself to lose composure.
I leave our master's protection to you.
Let us go!
Casca!
Like hell you will!
Oh, fine...
Isidoro Punch!
Elven Lethal Head-Strike!
Huh?
God?
But i-it can't be.
It is true.
Everything is moving in a current
toward that point in time.
Your guiding that witch to this land
is but another sign.
As for that Black Swordsman...
He's... He's involved, too?
Vessels for the one they wish to bring
into the world through the advent.
Who is it?
Who do they so strongly desire?
That one will soon appear.
When the countless souls,
who have been trodden like dirt,
desire it with greater fervor.
In exchange for my insignificant self, who barely...
nay, never even existed in this world,
a new world will emerge.
Why?
Why did you bring me here?
Why are you telling me this?
It could have been anyone.
I just wanted to talk to someone...
before I disappeared...
It still had such power?
Death, are you...
No, who are you people?
That is of no concern to those
of the mortal realm.
It is best you not get too involved.
Of course, depending on what happens next,
the very principles of the world may change.
Hey, what the...
Ow!
Thanks, yet again...
No, it is too soon to thank me.
It's futile.
If you continue to resist,
you'll lose the lone eye you have left.
Casca!
Hey, wait!
Time out! Hey!
I now sentence you to the breaking wheel
for plotting to kill a priest.
H-Hey!
This is the end.
I can't dodge it.
I can't dodge it...
Fine.
A cannon?
He had a dangerous weapon like that
I'm so done...
in his false hand?
One...
Two.
Three.
Thank you, God.
For preparing such a miracle
for us here, at our end,
after having suffered merciless fates
due to our abhorrent forms.
And above all,
thank you for the miracle...
of our paths crossing
with Father Mozgus...
Shit... Not again.
Oh.
H-Hey, wait...
Crap! Commander, when did you arrive?
E-Earthquake?
Those are the monsters from the tower.
They are a whorl of the hatred festering here.
They responded to the aberration in the tower.
But I did not expect they would
take form, even without a gate,
just by having the branded assemble here.
Gate?
It is nearly time.
They noticed us!
It begins...
Reporting in!
We've captured dozens of heretics
attempting to escape from the dungeons!
They are terrified, rambling about monsters,
but nothing coherent.
Any word on Lady Farnese's whereabouts?
No, sir. We have been unable
to confirm her location.
Sir Azan, what is the meaning of this?
Should anything happen to Lady Farnese,
who will take responsibility?
Why is this happening?
I fled from the holy city's burdens
to spend the rest of my days peacefully
in this remote region...
What is going on?
Monsters!
We're in danger...
All men, retreat!
Get away from the tower!
This is seriously bad news!
My God.
Look!
Luca...
Wait, Pepe!
Even if you went, what could you possibly do?
But...
Shh! Quiet!
I hear something.
The wind?
No, it's coming from the refugee camp.
Are those... screams?
Dad!
Honey...
Mom, Dad's...
Mom?
Heretics!
Run!
Go to Albion!
Shit...
What the hell's going on?
All troops, get as far from
the tower as possible!
Any who can are to help the injured!
Oh, God!
Lady Farnese...
Vice-commander!
Have mercy!
Help!
Vice-commander!
God's breath!
That's...
Father Mozgus...
An angel! He's an angel!
Servants of God, you have naught to fear!
No matter what extraordinary powers
the heretics may bring to bear,
as long as your faith is pure, God will
manifest a miracle to defeat the Hawk's power.
See me as I now am!
This is God's power incarnate.
These wings will purify evil
and destroy demons!
I will now burn this witch at the
stake, for she is the origin
of all the evil now rife in this holy land.
I will put an end to these
loathsome abominations.
Casca!
Now!
While we keep these monstrosities
at bay, erect the pillar!
Vice-commander, what should we do?
There is no question!
Knights have but one duty.
All troops, charge!
Protect the people!
That bald rock-face...
He treats people like dirt.
Forget him. I wonder if Guts
and the rest are okay.
Four angels...
So that's what it means!
Unfortunately, no man possesses the means
to change this festival's outcome.
A shadow will be born.
It will simply be a shadow cast by a dying
sun that shines on a faraway land.
A shadow?
Come to think of it,
even being so close, my brand
isn't searing me with pain.
Do not have more than
one that you care for.
At a time like this... What am I doing?
Hurry up!
Burn her!
We'll be saved if we burn her!
Out of the way!
Next Episode Preview
Everything is following the same path as before...
Will it end the same way?
Mark this well, monkey child!!
I have to go.
Come, mighty strength!!
Come, superhuman strength!!
Next Episode
Shadows of Ideas