Hey, brat...
Put that down.
No way!
After four whole days, I finally got this food.
You should all work for what you need.
Don't latch on to a kid!
You're all grown-ups!
Man, talk about pathetic...
Ow!
Says a burglar.
Want me to make it so you never
become a pathetic grown-up?
Right here, right now, squirt.
You giant freak!
You look like your brain
stunted at three years old.
I'm not gonna say that out loud, though.
You just did, idiot.
Don't get so hung up over the details.
Here.
I don't want to die before
I've had a girl, anyway.
Nice.
There's even ale.
The villagers here must've run off in a hurry!
I bet there are valuables, too.
Many thanks to the Kushans!
Is it good?
Yeah, but there's not enough for you.
Oh, yeah?
I scrounged all that food together.
I hope you take the time to enjoy it.
Yeah, yeah. Just go already—
Hey, what's wrong?
Brat, what did you do?!
Oh, this sure is potent.
It was pretty expensive, after all...
My share's over here.
I'm not a fan of being underestimated.
Squirt...
I'm gonna crack your head right open—
Don't call me "squirt."
I have a name, Isidoro.
Don't worry, it's just bee venom.
It won't kill you.
Have a change of heart and live honestly.
You know, it's sad when a kid's lecturing you!
Later.
Hey, what's wrong?
Everyone's passed out.
Shit!
I didn't know there were more.
Calm down... Stay calm...
Think... Think!
What happened?!
Who's this brat?
I was so scared!
It was the Kushans!
What?
The army came and...
N-No, he—
What now?
We have to get out of here.
We don't have time to lose!
Fools...
Hang on, brat.
It doesn't make sense.
I didn't hear any hooves or anything.
And look... None of them have
injuries caused by swords.
Now that you mention it...
What's with you, brat?
Why are you unharmed,
if Kushans were here?
Huh? Because I'm just a kid...
The Kushans have no mercy, even for kids.
Where'd they go?
Um...
Shit! Shit!
Th-That way!
Hmm?
Tower of Conviction
It's the Kushans!
They're Kushan scouts!
We're surrounded!
Shit, we have to fight!
No way...
They all died in a flash!
That's...
What was that for?
What an unexpected test of my new blade.
He cut up those Kushan monsters
with one strike!
Hey, clear the way. I'm in a hurry.
What's with you guys?
No talking my way out of this?
Hey, squirt...
Hey, stay still, with your head down.
You're...
Hey, been a while!
Nice work, as usual, Godo.
Hey, you have food, huh?
And ale, too.
I can smell them, even though they're hidden.
They'll do as a sign of thanks.
No need to hold back.
A-Amazing!
Hey, let's go, Puck.
Okay.
Whoa!
W-Wait...
He's no ordinary guy!
You are certain we can let that
man go, Young Master?
It's of no consequence.
The Bakiraka Clan's duty is to scout ahead.
There is no need to take further casualties.
But if we, the Tapasa, combine our strength—
Do not underestimate him.
We may be able to subdue him, yes.
But we will not do so unscathed.
You know of this man, Young Master?
It was in the past...
A very long time ago.
Quickly.
Hurry.
Not another monk...
It was heretics.
There will be even more inquisitions now...
Hey, stop!
Alms...
Alms, I beg of you.
Fools!
These are tributes to the monastery.
You have already received your daily rations.
That soup of vegetable scraps isn't enough!
You guys eat your fill every day, right?
Please have mercy...
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Ah, food!
Alms!
Mercy!
S-Stop!
Catch them all!
Don't let a single one escape!
Crap...
It's the Holy Iron Chain Knights!
P-Please help—
Have mercy!
What is the meaning of this?
Is this what the faithful would do?
Some of us are sick...
We've been living on watery soup for days.
We have no firewood for winter!
We have already requested food, medicine,
and other supplies from the Holy See.
You are not the only ones who suffer!
Please...
My child no longer even
has the strength to nurse.
He's about to die.
He needs God's protection right away!
What?
Very well.
Because of your bravery, God will
show you His mercy.
But, Father Mozgus, that will disrupt order!
Of course I have considered that.
But I believe the fact that I am here
and that she has sinned
and has been brought before me
are all part of God's design.
It is said that love knows no fear.
We should respond to her act of
pure love, committed without
regard for her own well-being.
Thank you! Thank you!
For now, let us take these
people to the monastery.
These men should go there.
Do not worry.
You will see them again later.
Now, you will go this way.
Now, drink...
Good.
The child seems to be stable now.
If he stays nourished and gets some rest,
he'll recover soon.
I'm so glad!
I have sent a message to the Holy
See with a request for aid.
I shall also see if we can distribute
a portion of the food
from the earlier tributes among the refugees.
Oh, I don't know what to say...
Thank you!
I have merely executed God's will.
Now, come this way, please.
As one of the faithful, you have
a duty to perform.
Lady Farnese, I believe this is the first
time you've set foot in this room.
You must not look away!
This hellish scene is part of
the Holy See you serve.
It is not only benevolence that God
bestows upon this world.
He is also a stern judge.
You must not flee!
To save your child, you have sinned.
Your love and bravery should be praised.
However, sin is sin!
Because you are so brave,
I beg you to overcome this
ordeal from God Himself!
Surrender yourself to God's grace.
N-No!
Let me go...
I didn't kill any monk!
I'm not a heretic!
We have a witness to the crime!
What the hell? Shit!
Who was it?
Who framed me?
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you when I come back!
Take him.
Ah...
He's the thug who's been intimidating
everyone around here.
No one liked him...
I guess someone decided to get rid of him,
but I feel like spitting on both their faces.
Can you try to get more into this?
Oh, oops, sorry!
But are you sure about this?
Every day, you're here before
the sun's even set.
You don't want me here?
No, you're special...
Business aside, I'm glad to have you here.
But I'm worried that you'll get reprimanded
by that scary commander lady.
No need to worry about her.
All she talks about is duty and faith.
She works her men hard,
but she isn't skilled in fighting or leadership.
For the Holy Iron Chain Knights, having a
female commander is tradition.
She's only a figurehead.
It must be tough, I'm sure...
To be the only woman among men.
I don't even want to know what it takes to
work so hard on a shitty mission like that.
You hedonist...
Oh.
Bad Elaine!
I've told you that you can't come
in here. This is my job!
I've gone all soft...
Sorry, she's my little sister.
What's with all the bandages?
Disease that comes with our profession.
She was unlucky.
She's almost all gone upstairs.
That's too bad.
Well, for now, I'll go home.
I'll give you extra next time.
Here, the usual fee.
And here.
Wow, that's pretty...
It wasn't cheap.
It'd be out of reach for common folk.
I'm happy you got it for me, but I'm not
sure I deserve something like this.
Cast not pearls before... You know.
I think I'm getting too old for this.
Once this job's done,
I'll take you back home.
As the family heir, I can't marry you,
but all the nobles have mistresses, anyway.
I'll pamper you.
We'll bring your little sister, too.
I'll find her a good doctor.
Thanks, Jerome...
I'll wait, but I won't expect anything.
Jeez, I couldn't be a whore if I took
all the pillow talk seriously...
Hey, hey!
I heard that, Luca.
Girls...
Lucky Luca...
I wish someone would talk like that to me!
Oh, stop it.
It's only because it's good to know influential
people for when you need help.
Aw...
Come on!
Yeah.
So, by the way, Luca...
Don't eat it all at once.
We know!
Thanks, as always.
Oh, and this...
Wow!
You shouldn't have!
Listen, everyone gets an equal number of pearls.
But this was for you.
I'll keep some, too, of course.
We all agreed to this, remember?
No matter who earns how much,
we split our earnings.
Yeah, but...
This looks so expensive.
Hey, Pepe, Fouquet, Lucie.
Listen well.
We're working in the middle of
a witch hunt for heretics.
You get that, right?
Even though it's to survive, it's so dangerous.
Humans are wretched creatures...
They envy those who have more,
and they sneer at those who have less.
Even the smallest differences
can cause fear and hatred.
I'm sad to say it,
but that's especially true of us, who have little.
That's not true. We're...
That's why we'll prove that we're different.
When actions don't follow
words, there's no trust.
All right, then!
Just like usual, share half our earnings
among our neighbors.
Not again!
That's such a waste...
I told you.
It's so that we don't earn any grudges.
Just go and charm them!
Okay.
Huh? One's missing.
Oh, that's no good.
I'll have to tie it more tightly...
Bear with me, even if it's a bit tight.
If a looker like you went wandering
defenselessly around here,
you wouldn't stay safe for a single day.
You'd be the perfect victim
for all the desperate men.
Normally, I'd ask you to earn your own keep,
but since you aren't even capable
of making your own decisions...
And that brand on her chest...
There must be a story behind it.
Luca!
Oh, hello!
Please wait, good sir.
Nina, I'm going to work another job.
Please make sure everyone gets
food, and take care of Elaine.
Okay.
Also...
Here.
I talked to a customer, a doctor, about you.
And he gave me this.
He said to take two swallows
each morning and night.
Thanks, Luca...
I'll go get some water.
Heretics!
Throw!
Just throw now!
The bleeding just won't stop.
There's some pus in there, too.
My mouth's getting swollen.
This might be it for me...
The doctor said that
if the bad blood reaches
my brain, I'll go insane.
Will I become like you?
Do you have anything you're afraid of, Elaine?
That place is supposed to
be where God is present.
Why does it look so stark and terrifying?
Scared... I'm so scared.
I can't stand it, Luca...
I'm scared of dying and living,
of this world and of God.
I'm... I'm scared of everything!
Found you...
He ran a whole day and a half,
from yesterday afternoon?
If I hadn't hitched a ride on a refugee's
carriage, I would've lost him!
That sharp edge... So giant.
It must be a famous sword!
It won't budge!
But he was wielding it like a feather...
You aren't putting your back into it.
Put your back into it.
Here, like this! See?
I'm Puck.
When you ask people for their names,
you should always introduce yourself first.
I-Isidoro...
Though I didn't ask...
Well, then, Isidoro or whatever,
put your mind to it and give it a go.
You're not trying to stop me?
Heave-ho!
Hey, Guts...
I caught a thief.
It isn't a toy for kids.
It seems you've been following
me since yesterday.
What do you want?
You want to become his apprentice?
Then, you'll have to go through
me, his manager, first—
That's not it!
I don't wanna serve anyone.
O-Oh!
You must've come to take back
the food you gave me!
What a disgrace!
Too bad.
We already ate everything!
That's fine...
You have a sword.
You want to become a swordsman?
Have you ever drawn blood with a sword?
D-Don't underestimate me.
I've killed one or two...
Well, whatever...
You should stay away from me.
What I choose to do is my own business!
You have no right to tell me anything!
Well, you're right.
Hey, thief...
You should run.
My name is Isidoro!
Here they come.
What the hell?
Guts!
Well, this is different.
Shit!
Damn you!
Is this real?!
Damn you...
I'll rip you to pieces.
I don't recall anything that'd
make a wheel curse me!
Shit!
Go to hell!
Damn you all!
Full of hatred, eh?
On any other day, I'd feel
the same. But right now...
I don't have the time to deal with you.
I'm in a hurry.
I feel like I'm burning up inside...
Out of the way!
Next Episode Preview
Shadows, karma... Like I give a damn.
Joy?
You sure have some impressive faith.
You look to be in good health, Struggler.
All of this, for God alone!
Next Episode
A Nighttime Feast: Burning at the Stake