Give it back...
Give back...
My warm body...
Oh, no...
Let's go home, Elaine!
It's getting dark.
A Nighttime Feast: Burning at the Stake
Wow...
I knew it, he's...
Shit!
He took off without me again!
He won't leave me behind!
Hey, we've been on the move since yesterday.
If you don't rest, you'll be exhausted
when we reach our destination.
I wonder what happened to the boy.
His nasty looks and stubbornness kind
of reminded me of you, Guts.
Yeah, right.
No sudden stops!
Be more considerate of your host!
What is it this time?
Someone I've known for a long time.
You look to be in good health, Struggler.
An elf?
An interesting choice of companions.
Huh?
He's kind of...
Been a while, old man.
What are you doing out here?
I am a foe to otherworldly beings.
You will soon learn what lies ahead.
There's an Apostle nearby?
Or their root cause.
You don't mean...
They're...
The God Hand is here?
Did you not also see the shining
hawk in your dreams?
That was a revelation.
That someone, who signifies the hawk,
will appear in this mortal world.
The hawk...
The hawk?
The flocks of sheep are being guided
to a blood-stained holy land.
What they seek is a hawk of light.
When the place of power attains a critical
threshold, what normally lies in
the realm of gods is incarnated,
once every thousand years.
You and the girl will find yourselves
thrown into that maelstrom,
as though tracing a passage through time.
The Eclipse...
An event similar to the Eclipse is about to occur.
It's about to...
It's going to happen again?
Joy?
Unfortunately, no man possesses the means
to change this festival's outcome.
A shadow will be born.
It will simply be a shadow cast by a dying
sun that shines on a faraway land.
You're saying the outcome will
be the same as last time?
That we are both here, without meaning to be,
is proof beyond reproach.
We are already caught in the whorls of karma.
Shadows, karma... Like I give a damn.
In the past, I borrowed your powers, sure.
But this time, I will draw on my
own strength to save her!
And I'll...
Perhaps that brand will be of assistance to you.
What?
A word of advice.
Do not have more than
one that you care for.
Man, what is our holy commander thinking?
Why is she kissing up to Father Mozgus?
Yeah, she sure has some noble faith.
Hey, she can hear you!
Oh, my apologies...
Please be more careful!
Come on...
Don't waste food.
Why is a klutz like him the officer of arms?
Sorry.
Because he wags his tail and falls over
himself to please her, that's why.
Anyway, we have even more of them now.
More what?
Refugees.
A-Ah, where is Father Mozgus?
I will come with you.
I was just on my way to the chapel to call him.
Did we shock you?
Er, no...
All of us have been persecuted
because of our appearances.
Exiled from villages and towns,
we were reviled as monsters.
Some even lived in hiding, in the forests.
Please look.
I was born with a rare disease.
Without this mask,
I'd be burned all over my body.
I wouldn't even look human anymore...
God, I thank you for bringing us
here today in a fateful act.
Child of fate, find pride and
faith within yourself.
I do not like my work.
I cannot find it within myself
to enjoy hurting others.
But still, I am proud.
For this is a holy task given to me by God.
What is this sound?
It is the sound of
my master's worship.
Prostration.
Eh?
Every day, morning and evening,
Father Mozgus prostrates himself
before God a thousand times.
In the past decade, he hasn't
failed to do so even once.
He seems to be finished.
Well met, Lady Farnese.
Father Mozgus, you're bleeding...
Ah, excuse me.
This tower is a most sacred place.
A holy man, imprisoned here
by the conqueror Gaiseric,
continued to recount the king's sins
to God, even while being tortured.
Eventually, in response to his pleas,
an angel is said to have descended.
I cannot help but be more devout
in my worship here.
Thank you.
Because of these wounds, I can barely walk.
I can run no longer.
But I am fond of this agony.
My holy mission is to enforce God's stern law.
Regrettably, that means causing agony to many.
These wounds are admonitions to me,
as well as proof of my faith.
Are you having some kind of doubts?
I am simply unsure.
Will this mission allow us to save people?
The common people bear us only ill will.
And though it shames me to admit,
even some among my Holy Iron Chain
Knights oppose this mission.
Please dismiss this as a mere initiate's ramblings.
But I fear that continuing this way will
mean that terror spreads unchecked,
exhausting the people's hearts and minds.
You must not deplore difficult tasks.
You must not question God.
Though you may endure bloodshed,
in both mind and body,
you must continue to live for God's glory.
That is faith.
It is for God, and God alone, that we act.
For God.
And God alone...
For God alone!
Thank you for always doing this...
Don't strain yourself, ma'am.
Hey, Elaine!
Come on, you can't get yourself
all muddy like this.
N-Nina...
Joachim...
U-Um...
Don't you know what's happening to me?
Or are you saying you still want my
services, even though you know,
Customer?
I'm just worried about you...
Don't you get it?
I'm telling you that I can't lie with
you, even if you're nice to me!
Oh, but that's not what I meant—
Then try to screw me!
Oh, no. I...
If you think you're that brave,
come to the riverbank tonight,
when the midnight bell tolls.
What's going on, Nina?
Why all the racket so early in the morning?
It's nothing!
Do you love me?
Y-Yeah.
Then, are you willing to be
damned to Hell with me?
Y-Yeah.
If it's with you.
This isn't for work.
That girl. Could she be...
Come, let's go down.
I knew it. That girl...
This makes you hallucinate...
Now, let's run away together.
The goddess of flames!
Nina!
Come, Joachim.
Oh, Great Goat,
please convert this man.
Now, drink this, and become one of us.
Joachim!
Wa—
Kill him!
He'll expose us!
He can't have survived from this height.
Yeah, let's go home for now.
People might come because of the commotion.
Yeah, right... Liar...
Nina...
Luca, why are you here?
No, stay away...
Stay away.
Stay away from me!
Why...
Why are you looking at me like that?
I've always hated you!
Always acting like a know-it-all,
ordering us around!
I bet you feel good about yourself, don't you?!
You're a whore, just like me!
But how?
How can you look down on others like that?
I-If I scream, my people will come back.
You'll be torn apart!
Wh-What are you—
Stop!
Stop...
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry...
You worried me.
You stupid girl...
Luca, I...
Joachim...
Don't talk right now.
Who's this?
Hey, she's a whore with Nina.
Oh, right, the crazy one who's sick.
Interesting.
Elai—
That girl.
Hey, show us your rotting face!
Huh?
What?
What's going on?
She's a real beauty, once you
look under the bandages.
Yeah, struggle!
It's more fun when they fight!
What's with her?
Hey, you guys!
Luca...
Huh?
What?
Hey, what's wrong?
Starving!
Wh-What's going on here?
Meat!
Elaine!
Elaine, you...
A witch...
She's a witch.
Light the fire!
She's sure into this whole thing...
I heard the commander's family home
was right at a burning ground for heretics.
Since she was a young girl, she's willingly lit fires.
I heard she was allowed to search
for the Black Swordsman
because three years ago, she caught
heretics plotting to rebel against
the Holy See and burned them all at the stake.
So she's born and bred that way, huh?
I should stay away from her.
You, there!
No small talk!
Yes, sir!
Dad...
Brat, you're a heretic, too, aren't you?
The son of a heretic is also a heretic.
If not, throw this onto the pyre.
I... I...
That child is innocent.
We investigated him when
we questioned the father.
M-My apologies!
Oh?
I'm not trying to obligate you to me.
Hey!
Lord Jerome, I believe...
Oh, you aren't the officer of arms
for nothing. Good memory...
You're not so bad, huh?
Hmm?
That kid back there.
That was nice knightly behavior.
Oh, that.
You see, it's personal for me.
I was just like him.
My mother was also burned
at the stake as a heretic.
Three years ago, before my very eyes.
Three years ago?
Good work, miss!
Bless her.
God bless her.
I'm not wrong!
Shit!
That monster never gets tired...
I've finally caught up!
Casca...
Next Episode Preview
Giving up before the job's done? No, thanks.
We have come to welcome you, Lady Priestess.
I kind of have the advantage here, you know?
Go crush them!
You call this a holy land?
Next Episode
The Black Witch