We finally found you, Black Swordsman!
Hey, look.
Is that a sword?
No way...
How could anyone wield that?
This man is
the Hawk of Darkness.
We are the Holy See's Holy Iron Chain Knights.
We have made haste, by order of
the Miracle Certification Bureau,
to take you to the Holy See.
You will not be harmed if you lay
down your sword and surrender.
If not, we swear upon God
that you will be captured!
I don't recall doing anything that'd
make a priest arrest me.
How callous...
What is all that blood from?
While tracking you,
we saw the bodies of a monk,
his daughter, and countless others.
Guts...
The time for talk is over!
This is God's will!
Troops, capture the Black Swordsman!
This doesn't look good...
What are you gonna do?
The Holy Iron Chain Knights
Listen, I'll create an opening.
When I do, race through the forest.
But...
Don't get me wrong!
Do you really want to die like this,
in the middle of nowhere?
A good blade should rest in a scabbard.
You should return to the master of your sword!
What's his deal?
He can't use his sword at all.
Guts!
I can't get a good grip.
Great!
Have at him!
Idiot, don't kill him!
H-He's fast...
Stop, you'll kill him.
His false hand! Watch that hand!
Calm down! Don't get worked up!
Surround him! Don't let him move around!
We'll just hit each other...
No!
Idiots! We can't kill him!
The whole lot of you is pathetic...
How can a single fugitive
have you in such disarray?
You can't blame them.
The Holy Iron Chain Knights, also known
as the "Spoiled Brat Knights,"
are full of pampered heirs their
noble families wanted safe.
They're here for the prestige
and safety the order affords.
Most have never fought in a real battle.
Thank you for the lecture.
So, why are you here, Sir Serpico?
Oh, come now...
I'm sure you know.
I became an officer of arms because
I hate the sight of blood—
Good... Now! Secure him!
Oh, crap.
This is the Black Swordsman...
His malice is unmistakable.
He is the one written of in Revelations.
Lady Farnese...
As Serpico stated,
given our troops' combat inexperience,
we face mounting casualties
if we seek to overwhelm him with numbers.
I ask that you allow me, Azan,
to undertake this task!
Back, back!
Back, I say!
Vice-commander...
Sir Azan!
I am Azan, Second-in-Command of
the Holy Iron Chain Knights!
Wow, we'll never run out
of surprises around here.
Iron Staff Demon Azan?
I've heard of you.
I believe you're also called
the Knight of the Bridge.
Oh?
You know this guy, Guts?
The story goes that an injured old man
was standing on a narrow bridge.
The Knight of the Bridge was a curious guy,
who refused to let an army of
a hundred mounted men pass
because he was protecting that guy.
That was a long time ago.
People laughed and said he could've ended it
by carrying the old man to the other side.
A knight has a duty to uphold
his code of chivalry!
My circumstances led to being a cleric knight.
In any event, I have named myself.
If you are a knight,
courtesy demands you reciprocate!
I'm no knight...
I'm Guts.
Just "Guts," old man.
Very well, Guts...
Prepare yourself!
He's so old-fashioned.
Prepare to break at least one or two bones!
One or two bones, eh?
I can't keep dodging with this gimpy leg.
And the old man isn't just an idiot
who relies on brute strength.
You nimble trickster!
Summer Showers Thrust!
Vice-commander Azan!
I would commend you.
But given your lack of offense,
your execution lacks finesse.
Your swordsmanship
affirmed its battle-testing.
I'll admit it thrilled me,
hearkening to my own past.
I must apply myself to the order
with greater diligence,
to mend my foolish ways.
Shit...
I can barely feel my limbs anymore.
What should I do?
A frontal attack?
Commendable resolve!
What?
I was careless!
Lady Farnese!
I was the one who put him down?
Well done, Lady Farnese.
You really are our Lady Commander!
Hey, you! Get up!
Wait, is he dead?
He's unconscious. He seems to be asleep.
Oh, Tonio!
He was a good man...
Lady Farnese, please order a retreat.
Lady Farnese, was this the
first blood you've drawn?
As one who wields a sword,
you mustn't fear it.
But always remember
the weight of a life taken,
so long as you have men under your command.
What's this?
Very well!
All troops, retreat!
Hey, are you alive?
Yeah, somehow.
Well, you're a hard one to kill.
Here.
Good work.
On the battlefield, a common soldier's life
is worth less than a single silver coin.
In this day and age, most people are
abused by royalty and the nobility.
Well, not that even kings can
live as they please.
Everyone is merely swept along by the tide.
The tide known as fate.
And their lives spent,
they vanish into its depths.
They die before learning who they truly are.
Some, regardless of rank or station,
are born as key individuals,
who will shape this world.
They are the true privileged class.
I want to know who I am in this world.
What I am capable of,
and what I am meant to do.
How strange.
I've never spoken to anyone about this before.
At that moment,
the man appeared to me as something
beautiful, noble, and absolute.
We have brought the Black Swordsman.
Enter.
Yes, my lady.
Well done.
After you bind him to the post,
you are free to go.
But that would—
No need for concern.
With those gigantic shackles,
what harm could he possibly do?
We shall inform the vice-commander, then.
That won't be necessary.
But...
Further, instruct the guards to leave
this tent until I order otherwise.
But if something should happen...
We should inform the vice-commander.
What is your name and rank?
You dare say you cannot follow my order
unless the vice-commander tells you to?!
Tell me, who is the Supreme Commander
of the Holy Iron Chain Knights?
Yes, my lady! It is you, Commander Farnese!
I deeply regret speaking out of turn!
As long as you bear this in mind. Leave.
Yes, my lady!
Black Swordsman...
Or should I say... Guts, was it?
Before we deliver you to the Holy See,
it falls to me, as one of the grand
tribunal's junior members,
to ask you a few simple questions.
Why do you laugh, cur?!
Oh, I was just thinking that
I have the worst luck
with God and things of that ilk.
Blasphemy. I shan't allow you
to blaspheme a second time.
The Band of the Hawk.
A band of mercenaries, hired by Midland.
An elite military force that
won countless victories,
their military prowess
was said to be peerless.
But they plotted treason against the royal
family, becoming wanted fugitives.
However, the entire company
vanished into thin air overnight.
No one heard, even in rumors,
that the bounty was claimed.
Did someone obliterate them?
All we know is that there
are very few survivors.
Th-The leader of the Band
of the Hawk was Griffith.
After he went missing,
it's said a woman replaced
him as their leader.
It's also said that the captain of their raiders
wielded a massive sword and could
slay a hundred men with ease.
You seem to match his description.
And if I recall, his name was...
Also...
A questionable item,
one that would conceivably be
in a heretic's possession...
Nice, isn't it?
If this is a heathen idol,
you will be tried as a heretic.
If you do not wish to endure that,
you should confess everything now.
Is that not preferable to
being interrogated under torture,
then burned at the stake?
Answer me, cur!
Do you believe in God and the devil?
What's your point?
Are you trying to blaspheme yet again?
Have you ever met God?
God does not show us His miraculous
existence on this Earth so easily.
Through our faith, God is always with us.
In our souls and up in Heaven.
Wh-Why do you laugh?
What a picture-perfect response.
Did you learn that in a convent?
On a battlefield, a nobleman
said the exact same thing,
burning a city to the ground,
with its women and children.
I'm not talking about some shitty, useless god
who's just an empty decoration.
A confession would be a waste of time.
I have no intention of repenting,
and I don't think you'll learn
anything, even if I told you.
Just go say a prayer for me in
some moldy temple, will you?
You cur!
You just had to say that?
Cur,
how dare you blaspheme in front of me,
Commander of the Holy Iron Chain Knights?
I was prepared to show mercy,
in consideration of your
injuries, but no longer!
I shall make you talk,
even if it means flaying
the skin from your body!
I swear this by my faith!
You're trying way too hard, aren't you?
Be it God or your rank,
whatever weight you're trying to
throw around won't earn loyalty.
Not like that Knight of the Bridge commands.
If you ask me,
you're just like that idol you
worship, all empty inside.
You...
You!
How dare you?!
Lady Farnese!
Excuse me... Just what is going on?
Lady Farnese, what is the meaning of this?
Why all this commotion?
I am simply questioning him,
before we deliver him to the Holy See.
However, this is...
I am finished.
Return him to his cell.
You are dismissed, as well.
Lady Farnese...
Did you not hear me?
I said, you are dismissed!
As you wish.
Do not unshackle him.
Tend his wounds, and leave him in the cell.
Take him!
Yes, sir!
Don't be so rough on our commander, please.
She may not look it, but she
can be quite charming.
I can't afford to be wasting time here.
Shit.
I don't have time to be playing
nice with these lunatics.
Casca...
And...
It's nearly time.
Shit...
Unarmed and imprisoned,
not to mention not in the best shape.
What to do?
Hup!
I guess I had this guy.
I'm here to save you, Guts.
See, you can escape with this key.
Why are you here?
Elves have a strong sense of responsibility.
What're you gonna do?
I'm getting my stuff back.
It's everything I have, after all.
But your weapons are in that woman's tent.
That's perfect.
Depending how it goes, we'll take her hostage.
What?
I don't give a rat's ass if I end up
having to kill the lot of them.
There's someone I need to
find, no matter what.
I don't give a damn what happens
to those who try to stop me.
What's going on?
Oh, God... Please guide me.
You!
Oh, man...
Charming, huh?
You were hurt pretty bad.
You can't swing it around this soon.
You'll reopen the wound.
Guess I'm still at half strength.
Lady Farnese, we have an emergency.
The Black Swordsman has...
You—
That's brutal.
Guess I'll have to ask her along, after all.
A fire!
The Black Swordsman has escaped!
Stop it from spreading to the other tents!
Lady Farnese!
You...
How did you...
Step aside, old man.
You think you can escape with those injuries?
Yeah, I do.
The practice of burning people to death
isn't limited to clerics, is it?
Well?
I'll burn her ass.
Taking a woman hostage... You coward!
You leave us no choice.
Fall back, everyone.
Sorry.
What have you done?
Don't worry.
Hurry!
Gather the horses!
This is my biggest folly yet.
We cannot let him escape!
Who's that?
You're unbelievable.
Who do you think you have to
thank for being able to run this far?
The horse.
Then apologize to the horse.
Sorry, horse.
As long as you remember that.
Hey.
How the tables have turned, eh?
Quit struggling...
With your hands tied, if you fall
on these rocks, you'll die!
Don't worry.
We won't eat you or anything.
Oh, I'm Puck.
Let me go, cur!
How dare you treat the Commander of the Holy Iron Chain Knights this way—
Shut up.
Oh, hey!
Keep this up, and I'll just
knock you out again.
Sorry, you'll have to come along for now.
And there's something I want to ask you.
This is humiliating!
How could a heretic do this to me?
Let me down!
I'd rather fall and die than listen to you!
No!
Just calm down a bit, will you?
Jeez, isn't he capable of
love for his fellow man?
Nope.
Sorry, miss.
How dare you? Don't mock me!
What are you doing?
She isn't looking.
Huh?
She isn't trying to see me.
She can't...
She can't see elves.
Next Episode Preview
Does this have to do with what
was foretold in Revelations, as well?
Be nice to dogs.
I just remembered for
the first time in a while...
Humans who oppose us are just food.
I've had enough of miracles.
Next Episode
The Night of Miracles