It's time to work.
Shut up!
I won't stop at punches next time!
Hey, are you listening to me?
Over here, hey!
On that day, a dying sun rose above
the multitude of nations.
What's this?
As written in the Book of Revelations,
"When the sun has died five times,
a red lake will emerge to the west of a city
with a name both new and old."
"It will be the sign that the fifth angel
has descended upon this world.
The angel is the Hawk of Darkness.
He is the master of the sinful black sheep.
And the king of the blind white sheep.
He will usher in an age of darkness
to cover the world."
The Branded Swordsman
Hey, boy!
Bring more ale! Now!
Shit...
Why me?
What about our food?
Shut up!
Quit makin' me rush!
H-Hey, watch out!
Quit your twitching!
How're we s'posed to hit you?
I can't get free...
Come on, keep the knives coming! Next!
The fight's on, moron.
Untie me!
I'll bite right through your arteries!
I'll knock that wagging tongue
right back into your skull.
No, thanks! No, no, no!
Hey.
Huh?
Are you trying to make me clean up corpses?
What if we are?
I came with you guys because
I heard you were mercs.
But you're just acting like thugs and bandits!
I want to make a name with my sword!
Oh?
Anyway, I can't do this anymore!
Don't be so full of yourself, you sniveling brat!
After everything you just said,
you think you'll get out of this in one piece?
Screw you, asshole—
You'll be our next target.
Hey.
Yeah?
You're in the way.
Can you get going?
Huh?
Who do you think you're talkin' to—
You bastard!
Who do you think you are?
Wha?
Sorry for the ruckus.
Also, can you fill this with water?
And a bottle of rum.
S-Sure.
Hmm...
Oh!
There you are!
After you help someone, don't abandon them.
You should take full responsibility!
Oh, hey...
What's this heavy-looking lump?
Uh...
I'm Puck! Nice to meet you!
I was with a traveling troupe of entertainers,
but they were attacked by those bandits.
I've been stuffed in a birdcage
and dipped in a jug of ale.
I'm surprised I'm even still alive!
Um... Um...
I think those bandits have a lot of buddies nearby.
They have skilled men somewhere else.
If you don't leave soon,
you could be in bad trouble.
Ow!
What do you think you're doing, jerk?!
Don't gab at me...
I'll crush you.
Hmph!
That guy...
Crap...
I might've gotten lost.
Would you like to hop on?
It can't be easy,
dealing with this rain at night.
I'm fine. Just leave me alone.
There's no need to refuse.
My daughter wishes to help you, too.
I'm refusing for your own good.
You see, I'm possessed... By evil spirits.
That's unfortunate.
But there's no need for concern.
I have God on my side.
And a spirit of good fortune.
Now, hop on...
A man with a black prosthetic arm?
I'm not lying!
I swear he had a monster's strength!
Quit your yappin'.
We get it.
We called in thirty or so skilled
men to wait for him.
We'll finish him soon enough.
In any event, couldn't we have
found a better meeting spot?
Huh?
Guys, did you know this?
Know what?
These parts used to be home to evil cultists
that worshiped forest spirits.
Evil cultists?
It's said they held sacrificial rituals
where they staked your intestines
to a tree, and then made
you run around the trunk.
This is one of those trees.
You should learn to tell better jokes.
The place feels haunted enough as it is...
There are rumors that monsters
appear in these forests, too.
Monsters?
In this day and age, there are wars,
disasters, and piles of corpses,
no matter where you go.
It wouldn't be surprising if evil
spirits and the like appear.
What?
I got here first.
I don't want to hear any complaints!
Have some, if you'd like.
It's wine we made ourselves.
It will warm you up.
No, thanks.
But...
There are many dangers at night.
Jeez, don't waste people's goodwill...
Fine, give it to me—
Um, is that scar from battle?
I was bitten by an evil spirit.
Oh, no. Really?
Come, now... Please don't scare
my daughter too much.
What is your name?
Guts.
I am Adolf.
My daughter is Collette.
By the way, is that thing on your back a...
Well, never mind.
By the way, I was watching
you at the tavern earlier.
I don't approve of violence,
but saving the elven child was a noble act.
You don't seem to be a bad man.
Are you a mercenary?
Well, something like that.
I can't say I approve much
of a business that involves
killing people for money.
No, even to help another,
you shouldn't kill a human being so easily.
This is why I don't like monks.
Don't be that way.
My nephew left home, saying he'd
make his name with his sword.
Five years ago, he died on the battlefield,
just a nameless foot soldier.
If he had stayed alive,
he would have had a family,
and some happiness with it.
How foolish.
What's so bad about that?
No matter the cause, he died
doing what he wanted, right?
I'd call him a lucky man.
Though, once you're dead, that's it.
There's nothing beyond that.
Sorry, I'll be getting some rest now.
You'll catch a cold.
You won't be able to escape.
Griffith!
Hey, what's wrong?
Whoa, whoa!
What is that?
An incubus.
An evil spirit that makes people see
nightmares, to feed on terror.
An evil spirit?
Then what you said earlier...
What, you believe in God,
but not evil spirits?
Why is something like that here?
This attracts them.
A brand?
What's wrong?
Stay inside.
Incubi are born from bodies of the dead.
Long ago, this must've been a battlefield.
Evil spirits possess corpses and attack.
Given the incubus we had just now,
worse things may be out there.
Whoa, whoa!
Idiot, get back inside!
But...
Collette!
You should run!
You're free to go, if you want.
Why?
What's the point?
There are so many...
You'll get yourself killed!
That's nothing new.
It was far too large to be called a sword.
It was far too large, thick, heavy,
and much too crude.
By all accounts,
it was a hulking mass of iron.
Wow...
What's wrong, mister?
Guts!
Shut up!
I'm busy.
Guts!
Only twenty of us made it here.
Don't complain.
It's more than enough against one of him.
H-Hey, wait a minute...
Something's wrong.
Huh?
What the hell?
Hey, is that the guy who got you—
Guts!
You're too damp to be useful as firewood!
It isn't... your fault.
Huh?
Yeah, that's right. That's exactly right.
Only the weak get themselves killed
in someone else's battle.
If you can't even live your life as you want,
you should just die.
I'm a disaster
that those two didn't have the power
to protect themselves from.
That's all there is to it.
I wouldn't be able to take a
single step if I let myself
worry about stepping on ants.
It's no use.
You can't escape.
No matter where you may go...
...we'll be there.
We'll always be near you.
You can't escape.
We'll always be watching you.
You are mine.
You are ours.
Your blood, flesh, and bones...
Look, his ears.
His eyes.
His heart.
I want his heart.
As long as that brand exists...
Indeed, as long as you have that brand...
...you can't escape.
No matter where you may go...
...you are ours.
Your anger and grief...
Shut up.
Your pain...
And your terror...
All of it is ours.
Shut up!
So...
This is the world Guts inhabits.
We finally found you,
Black Swordsman!
Next Episode Preview
This is the Black Swordsman...
His malice is unmistakable.
I am Azan, Second-in-Command of
the Holy Iron Chain Knights!
Oh, Tonio! He was a good man...
Elves have a strong sense of responsibility.
Next Episode
The Holy Iron Chain Knights