Reunion in the Den of Evil
It's him...
Why is he here?
The Black Swordsman...
We're getting out of here, Isidoro.
Make sure those two get out.
Right! You can count on me!
I found an escape route in the back.
You're gonna owe me.
I charge high interest.
Save the talk for after we get out alive.
I'm so tired!
I bet I broke the sound barrier.
It appears they're fighting off heretics.
That does not mean they are our allies.
Have you all forgotten?
He's taken the lives of our comrades.
What should we do?
Should we also capture the Black
Swordsman, Lady Farnese?
That will not be necessary.
We are in the midst of battle!
Kill all who do not offer their surrender!
Lady Farnese, if I may...
We are to take the Black Swordsman alive—
Silence!
If we do not act, we shall only
suffer more casualties!
There is no doubt they are heretics.
Annihilate them, along with the Black Swordsman!
We have pledged our swords to God.
We cannot allow ourselves to fear!
All troops, attack!
So, fight fire with fire, huh?
Don't get distracted.
Let's go.
Show us the way, Isidoro!
No!
Do not let him get away!
Lady Farnese!
Oh, dear...
It's up there.
Won't let you have witch...
Consummate... Mine...
Stay back.
Without Godo's armor, my spine
would've been snapped in half.
Make him into goat stew!
Isidoro, take those two and go ahead.
But...
I'm leaving Casca to you.
Fine...
Don't die!
Wait...
Leave her!
You keep forcing Casca away from me.
You're like a half-Apostle.
I guess your being here means there's some
truth to the old skeleton's words.
Kill.
Trample you...
Skewer you!
But I can't leave her behind
in such a foul place.
This time, I'll take her with me for sure!
Looks like one or two arrows have no effect.
Guess I'll give this a try.
One...
Two.
Three.
These explosive bombs aren't bad.
Lady Farnese,
in this chaos, it is too dangerous
for our commander to endanger
her own person in battle!
Please retreat to the cave entrance!
But...
Escort the commander!
Yes, sir!
Come, Lady Farnese.
Azan!
Leave the rest to me!
Let me go!
Come with me, Officer of Arms!
Serpico, where are you?
I hope they didn't fall.
I have been waiting for you, Black Swordsman.
Huh?
Wait a...
That was uncalled for.
What was that sound?
Don't talk to me right now...
Hey!
There's no path!
Were the heretics planning to escape
by jumping off or something?
What now, monkey pants?
Hey, look.
I see!
With this, we're golden!
No way.
I can't do this.
It'll be fine.
I'll lower the rope.
Just like lowering boxes.
But...
If it doesn't work for you, jump.
Okay, I'll do it.
This lady's the problem...
I'm getting sucked in!
Damn.
On principle, I prevent people
from drawing their weapons.
Either way, you can't swing
that sword of yours here.
Bastard...
I made the right choice, getting ahead of you.
To think I'd chance upon such
perfect terrain to fight you.
I suppose this might be a sign of God's grace.
Above all...
Trying to overwhelm you with
sheer numbers is madness.
If you can cut down ten men with that sword,
it's enough to change the tide
of battle in an instant.
Allies infected by fear are even
worse foes than the enemy.
He's good.
I can't even get a chance to draw my blade!
You provoke our Lady Farnese a bit too much.
I have to get rid of you!
Don't look down.
Don't look down...
I'm falling!
I reached the bottom.
I'm okay.
Good.
All right, don't struggle...
The westward sun, shining in your eyes.
The cramped, unstable footing.
Your hulking body, encumbered by armor.
Your sword arm, made useless by the rocks.
They all serve to shackle you!
He's not just a glib talker.
He's highly skilled with his sword.
His attacks are so versatile,
I can't predict them.
He's a far more challenging foe
than that half-Apostle earlier!
Right now, I can't waste time here!
Are you worried about those girls?
My comrades are waiting for them up ahead.
I'm sure they have already
been taken into custody!
That's a total bluff...
I need you even more on edge.
I don't think I can win in a fair fight.
How foolhardy...
Fool? Not as much as you think.
If I were to pull back my blade,
your fingers would—
I have my reflexes. And my strong arms.
Also, I have really thick skin on my palms.
I didn't expect him to dodge like that.
On top of that, he moves like a pickpocket.
His quick wits let him use a
weapon he's only seen once.
He's more cunning than I thought.
Like a fox.
I shouldn't do things so out of character...
Really, it's unlike me to get so worked up.
With this many men,
how could you fail to capture
the Black Swordsman,
much less prevent him from entering the cave?!
I am deeply sorry.
We were taken by surprise.
I shan't tolerate excuses!
She's pretty unhinged...
And her flunky's nowhere to be seen, either.
What is it?
Nothing.
I just thought I saw something.
Just a little more.
Hang in there.
Is someone there?
Joachim...
What?
Did they find us?
Joachim, you're alive—
Heretics!
There are heretics behind those rocks!
What?
Joachim...
Hey, lady! Run!
If you stand there, they'll catch you!
What're you doing, Casca?
This is bad, Isidoro.
I'll go!
Commander,
our work to quell the heretics
is nearly complete.
What of the Black Swordsman?
He has not been seen among
the captured or the dead.
Walk!
That girl...
The one the Black Knight leapt to save.
Sorry.
Listen!
If we haven't returned by morning,
you have to leave Albion.
If you dawdle, the officials
will find you right away.
Luca...
You should change your mind.
I can't guarantee your survival,
and you'll hold me back.
My, so negative.
Yeah, this isn't a job for a lady, Luca!
That goes for you, too.
I'm doing this for my own reasons!
I'm gonna make up for my mistake!
I wasn't on top of my game earlier,
but that'll change this time.
You aren't the only one who's worried
about those girls, you know?
Besides, the monastery owes me one.
Depending on how it goes,
we might avoid bloodshed.
Do what you want.
Do you think it'll work?
I have no idea.
I think they should give up.
Once someone's inside that tower,
there's nothing to be done.
Luca's so stubborn...
She's way too responsible!
What do we do if they don't come back?
I don't know, silly!
Please return Luca and everyone
safely to us, oh...
Um...
A shadow will be born.
It will simply be a shadow cast by a dying
sun that shines on a faraway land.
We are already caught in the whorls of karma.
What should I do?
I lost them.
With so many people here, I can
barely sense their presences.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I thought I saw something there.
Maybe you saw a bat?
And I'm still visible,
even in this giant temple.
Anyway, why is it so hard to breathe here?
Is this a lair of demonic creatures?
Even that wouldn't explain all of it.
Many things are much more sinister.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
I need to find the girls soon!
Help...
Help, Luca...
Elaine, aren't you a witch?
Can't we use your witchcraft to escape?
Hey, listen!
If we don't escape soon, we'll be in big trouble!
Ugh, give me a break!
Whatever... I don't care anymore!
It's all your fault.
Since you came into my life,
nothing good has happened.
Only horrible things.
I took care of you, didn't I?
But look at me now.
Why is this
always happening to me?
Sorry.
That's a lie.
I'm sorry, Elaine.
Please forgive me.
One of you, out.
Don't care who.
Hurry up.
You, come.
Elaine...
You, never mind.
I choose you.
Your friend was getting taken away,
but you didn't try to help her at all.
You only thought of yourself.
I hate cowards like you!
But...
Wait!
I'm not like that...
Come out!
Elaine!
I... I...
Why?
Is it my fault?
Am I the one who's wrong?
But I couldn't say anything.
I was so scared.
I wanted to live, even if it meant
abandoning half-witted Elaine.
Even though I'm like this and may die soon.
No, that's why I want to live!
I'm horrible...
God is punishing me.
Our investigations revealed
there is an actual witch.
We've looked into all the other women.
One of you is the witch.
He's talking about Elaine!
If I tell him everything now,
maybe they won't hurt me.
If I tell him...
In the end, everyone looks out for themselves.
No way will I abandon anyone.
Not you or Elaine.
Luca...
Give me your strength...
I only need a tiny bit.
Just a small part of your courage!
No!
Just walk.
I can't...
I just can't!
Luca!
Wow!
It's ridiculously big up close!
More like a fortress than a holy temple!
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
What is it?
My brand's throbbing.
An Apostle?
No,
more monstrous than that.
There's something very wrong here.
Next Episode Preview
I have witnessed a miracle!
I have found that faith means death!!
Fool, you seek to rebel against God!!
Impertinent witch!!
I will have you atone with blood.
Next Episode
Blood Flow of the Dead