It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
I'm going to unleash all my magic!
Then all of you, this human,
and I will all be done for!
Disappear! Disappear! Die, humans!
What the hell is this ki?!
Asta, Magna, and Vanessa fought Luck,
who had reincarnated as an elf.
Humans... I will make you pay!
I don't know what the
heck you're talking about,
but if we humans really
are at fault, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
But for us... Luck is our precious friend!
So please... Don't take him from us!
Please!
Give him back to us!
And I'm pretty sure all those
people who are important to you
wouldn't want you to be like this!
Luck!
Their feelings for Luck
and Luck's feelings for the
Black Bulls connected, and then...
I...
I'm...
still one of the Black Bulls, right?
Of course you are, you dumbass.
Path of Revenge, Path of Atonement
Go!
Asta, Magna, Vanessa, and Luck
reunited with the other Black Bulls:
Gordon, Grey, Henry, and Charmy.
Aboard the Raging Black Bull,
they raced full speed ahead
for the royal capital.
I sense them.
There are three elves in the town up ahead.
The Greatest City in the Common Realm
Hecairo
Member of the Blue Rose Knights
Risakka Ondell
That was pathetic.
A shame, considering how
glorious this town is.
Vice Captain of the Purple Orcas
Xerx Lügner
But even that is a mere
shadow of what it once was.
Member of the Coral Peacocks
Protobe Collina
They're just about finished.
Mom! Dad!
I-It's no use... They're too powerful.
Lord Xerx...
Why is the Saint of Pure Ice attacking
the people he's supposed to protect?
Magic Knights doing something like this...
Is the Clover Kingdom finally finished?
Sol, I'm sorry... I couldn't
protect everyone.
But I won't give up until the very end!
I'm going to purify everything now.
Including you filthy humans.
Ice Magic...
What's the matter?
Something's charging this way.
What is that? An enemy?
The humans can resist all they want.
Whatever it may be, it shall not pass.
Stone Magic: Ground Wall!
Re...combi...nation... Magic...
Recombination Magic:
Raging Black Bull ~ Combat Style!
A giant...
...bull?
Rescue!
La!
Transformation Magic: Magic Conversion!
Ice to Water!
Stone to Sand!
Mom! Dad!
Thank you so much!
Th-Thank goodness!
Please hurry and get to safety!
That robe... Is she a Black Bull?
Don't get a big head, you humans.
I'll destroy that piece
of garbage in an instant!
Water Magic: Surging Waves!
Stone Magic: Rising Ground!
It won't connect.
Our attacks are being diverted.
What are you two doing?
Ice Magic: Ice Slicer!
Wh-What's going on?
As long as I have any magic left,
the Black Bulls will remain unharmed!
Munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy...
Okay. Here... we... go...
Flame Magic: Gargantuan Exploding Fireball!
Lightning Magic: Thunderbolt Destruction!
Poison Magic: Forbidden Fruit!
The destructive force of our
magic is being magnified...
...to take you down!
Not bad, hideout guy!
Great job!
Did you see just how
powerful my new friend is?
I... totally... know... everything...
Holy crap! That was so powerful! Damn!
there... is... to... know...
about... my... friends.
You guys are so awesome! The coolest!
I'm so happy. I finally get
to fight alongside everyone.
Let's go, everyone!
Let's go, Henry!
That's enough foolishness
from you humans!
You may be able to dodge this...
But this town will be blown away.
Take this! Combo Magic...
Asta Cannon!
Heck yeah!
The Black Bulls are invincible!
For as long as I could remember, I felt it.
There was someone sleeping inside me.
It felt as though they were terribly hurt,
terribly angry,
and terribly sad.
Because I felt that I needed
to protect this weak being...
Because I knew that this
wasn't just my body...
Because I felt as though I wasn't alone...
I was able to survive my
painful and lonely childhood.
Around the time I turned nine,
I started to have the same dream...
Of days filled with happiness.
They were your past memories.
And then an ending of disloyalty...
despair... and hatred.
I believed it was my duty to protect you.
And then, when I was thirteen...
I met Lord Julius.
William! Join the Magic Knights!
He was rather strange, but he was
the first person to acknowledge me.
Oh, but I guess you haven't
received your grimoire yet.
In that case, I'll keep dropping by until
you turn fifteen and get your grimoire.
He was a kind and great person.
I'm sure you'll become a
magnificent Magic Knight.
When I was sixteen, you awakened.
Where am I?
Didn't I die?
Around that time, I was working
as a newcomer in the Gray Deer,
which was led by Lord Julius.
Because you had received
a grimoire as well,
I confirmed the fact that we
were two souls sharing one body.
We were eventually able to share
our thoughts through our souls,
and we could even swap souls.
You had a mission that you
had to complete at all costs.
And that was going to make
me betray the other person
who was most important to me,
as well as my kingdom.
You, the person I had shared my life
and body with as if we were twins,
or the person who stood at the top of
the Magic Knights and showed
me how to live my life...
I was conflicted over who I should choose.
I took both sides as I hurt my comrades.
In the end, I couldn't completely choose a side
and let the two of them decide the outcome.
I'm the worst.
And you won.
I'm so sorry, Lord Julius.
Congratulations, Patry.
And since your wish came true,
this is where we say goodbye.
Goodbye, Patry.
If possible, I...
Did I fall asleep after
using too much of my power?
My incomplete reincarnation
is also now complete.
William has now fallen into
a deep, endless sleep.
Thank you, my one and only human friend.
William... Goodbye.
Now there is no longer any human I cannot kill.
Licht should be heading to the
royal capital along with Raia.
I must hurry, too.
Clover Castle... The center of
the humans' foolish bigotry...
It's where the royalty,
our most hated enemies, live,
and where we shall exact our revenge.
In the moment of reincarnation,
the fear for his life,
immense hatred, and anger
made Rades's magic, which could only
control the dead up until that point, grow.
This was the perfection of true wraith magic.
This evolved magic was just barely
able to return the souls
that were about to be sacrificed
for reincarnation to their bodies.
Licht!
How dare you trick me,
use me, and then kill me?!
You'll pay for this! You'll pay for
this if it's the last thing I do!
Right, guys?!
Valtos!
Sally!
You got lucky. You two just barely made it.
We're going to kill him together.
Heck yeah!
All three of them have been freed!
Spatial magic?
You guys...
What are you doing here?
Heya, Black Bulls.
I'm gonna use you guys to get my revenge.
Th-The Eye of the...
They attacked our base.
Are you the ones who destroyed my
vegetable garden back at the base?!
Those who waste food shall pay, la!
Shut up!
You guys piss me off, too, but right now,
I want to kill that bastard Licht.
Huh?
He tricked me, tricked us,
used us however he wanted,
and then sacrificed us for his own goals.
He's going to pay for this...
No matter what, if it's the last thing I do!
Licht is heading to the royal capital.
He's probably there by now.
If we power up Valtos's spatial magic
with Sally's Dark Magic Items,
we'll be able to transport
this moving base of yours.
We'd be in the royal capital in an instant.
You guys want to hurry to the
royal capital, too, don't you? Right?
Then we have the same goal.
Lend me your strength.
Not a bad deal, right?
I'll kill you, I'll kill you...
I'll kill you, Licht!
Judging from the mana, it feels like all
the elves are heading to the royal capital.
But isn't it too convenient that you
just suddenly showed up to ask for help?
I see you're going to coopera—
You're so annoying!
What?!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
We have the same goal?!
It's not the same at all!
Wha?
We're fighting to protect!
We're not helping anyone
for the sake of revenge!
More importantly...
You're the guy who attacked all those
innocent people at the royal capital before!
And now you want revenge?
You can't be serious!
"Revenge," my ass, you stupid jerk!
First, you need to atone for everything!
From now on, you're going
to help save the kingdom!
Huh?! You can't be serious, you bastard!
I'm totally serious!
With that, we're in a hurry to get to
the royal capital, so thanks for your help!
Huh?! Who died and made you the boss?!
This deal is null and void! Null and void!
You're not getting away!
You're gonna help us now!
Why are you so strong, damn it?!
That's so Asta.
Hell yeah, Asta! You get him!
But hey, if we're just heading to the
royal capital, do we really need that guy?
Oh, good point.
Huh?!
Luck's exactly right. I'll just
make a deal with these two.
You bastard!
Hey! What do you think about all this?
I...
I just want to see Master Licht
again and find out the truth.
I'll help you for that reason.
If Master Licht's words were nothing but lies,
then I am nothing more than a sinner.
Seeking atonement might be good for me.
Valtos, you jerk!
S-Sally! You want revenge, too, don't you?!
I don't have my glasses, so I can't see too well.
Who cares about your glasses right now?!
I was only with Master Licht because he
let me do all the experiments I wanted.
The Magic Knights always get in my way.
But I guess I'm happy that I'm
alive again and can do my research.
I saw a whole bunch of stuff when I was dying,
so I think I'm about to have
some kind of breakthrough!
You're only alive again because of me, Sally!
Yeah, I guess. Thanks, Rades.
You wanted to examine my body, right?!
If you help us out and this battle ends,
you can examine me all you want!
Huh?
Really, Asta?! Yay!
On one condition.
Nothing that hurts really bad!
Aw...
Don't "Aw..." me!
You can do all the experiments
and research you want,
as long as you don't harm or bother anyone!
Actually, if you did research
that'd help everyone out,
we'd all be happy to help!
That'd make you happy, too, right?
I don't really get it,
but if that'll let me do more research,
I guess I'll do that.
Yeah, you should!
You don't need any anesthesia
when I cut you apart, right?
Yes, I do!
You can't be serious, Sally!
I'm the one who brought you back to life!
Did you have enough time to reflect?
Eat up. You're nothing but skin and bones.
La? La?
Th-This is... My magic is recovering.
What?! That's amazing!
I'm starving! Gimme, please!
No one can fight on an empty stomach!
Eat up!
It's so yummy! I want to dissect
something even more now!
Make sure you use anesthesia, okay?!
Y-You jerks...
Well? Feel like saving the kingdom yet?
Go on... You know you're hungry.
La?
It's so good. My magic's recovering.
And I feel more energetic.
Nothing beats eating with friends!
I can't imagine why you wouldn't
want to eat something so yummy.
This is so good! So fricking good!
Yeah! I feel totally motivated now.
De...li...cious.
I'm so happy I'm alive.
Oh, wait, you were dead up until a while ago?
The only reason I'm able to eat
yummy things is because I'm alive!
Right?
Fine!
I'll go to the royal capital with you!
But I'm not gonna do whatever you want me to!
I'm gonna do whatever the hell I want!
You're supposed to ask us to take you with us!
Too bad! You're gonna
save the kingdom with us!
Shut up!
Go on, eat up! There's plenty
more where that came from, la!
Come on! Hurry up and eat so
you can get back on your feet!
Recover all your magic, and let's
head to the royal capital!
Yeah!
Damn it!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Rades,
Sally,
Valtos
Rades.
Sally.
Valtos.
We're fighting to protect!
We're not helping anyone
for the sake of revenge!
Take this!
Clover Twist!
Reverse Clover Hold!
Clover Backbreaker!
Clover Hold!
Tombstone Clover Driver!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
Maybe I won't have to use anesthesia now!
I think I'll give it a try!
Piss off!
Not yet!
Clover OLAP!
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
I can dissect you now without
using anesthesia, right?
Heck yes!
Don't "Heck yes!" me!
And what the hell are you even counting?!
Sixteen, seventeen, eighteen...
Black... Clover, Page... 107:
"The Battle for Clover Castle."
Page 107
The Battle for Clover Castle
My... name... is... Henry.