It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Vetto cast an ancient curse on Asta's arms.
The only hope of healing his arms was
the Queen of Witches,
who lives in the Witches' Forest.
But...
To be blunt, the queen is supreme.
She's so powerful that even the
Diamond Kingdom won't try to deal with her.
Not to mention that it's impossible
to reason with her.
We're going.
If there's a clue to healing
Asta's arms there...
Meanwhile, Vanessa was
also visiting her home,
the Witches' Forest,
in order to fix Asta's arms.
There it is!
Yeah!
When Asta and the others reached
the Queen of Witches, they saw...
Now get your foot off of her!
Miz Vanessa is one of us!
You fools.
What could imperfect creatures
such as yourselves possibly do?
They were much faster than I expected.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun...
Battlefield Decision
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
The Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Why are they heading here?
Y-You're not just saying
that to trick us, are you?
How imperfect.
If I chose to do so, I could end your
pathetic lives at this very moment.
Why would I need to lie?
She was at Nean!
She's from the Third Eye or whatever,
just like the hairy gorilla
that did this to my arms!
She's super bad news!
Then she's probably as powerful as Vetto.
She could be even more powerful!
You can't be serious!
Please tell me you're lying!
It matters not.
I will be more than happy to rid this
world of any imperfect creatures.
Warn the others.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
Fana the Hateful
The Queen of Witches, who pilfered one
of the magic stones, lives in that forest.
The humans that stole Vetto's
life are also there.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
Shidan
Indeed. They might have realized
the magic stone is there, as well.
They're unforgivable. I'll destroy everything
and take the magic stone.
I'm sure Master Licht will be pleased.
It seems they are with the queen
in the middle of the forest.
Let us burn them all and make examples
of them to the rest of the world.
Flame Spirit Magic: Salamander's Breath.
Flames!
We're being attacked!
The forest...
S-Such powerful flame magic...
The Flame Spirit, Salamander.
Its form is still not complete,
and yet it's this powerful...
It's much stronger than I predicted.
My readings were slightly off.
Any time fate veers off-course,
more deviations follow.
It can't be...
There are more of them!
Th-That's...
Near the border of the Diamond Kingdom.
Yeah.
As I suspected...
I thought this fate would
come to pass much later,
but the other force that wishes
to attack this forest...
The Diamond Kingdom.
You can't be serious. They're coming here?
One of the Diamond Kingdom's Eight Shining Generals
Ladros
Man... and just as I was relaxing
in a nice aromatherapy bath.
What's with the emergency summons?
We got word that the
One of the Diamond Kingdom's Eight Shining Generals
Mars
Eye of the Midnight Sun is going
to attack the Witches' Forest.
We have been ordered to take advantage
of the chaos that will cause
to capture the Queen of Witches.
We could do that easily
without being so sneaky.
Orders are orders.
That really pale guy...
It's the super strong guy
we fought in the dungeon!
Thank goodness... He's alive!
Should you be happy about that?!
S-Seriously?! What's going on?
This was already bad enough,
but it just keeps getting worse!
Why does this keep happening lately?!
Is that... Mars?
Then the one next to him must be Ladros.
Zell...
Anyway, we have to protect
the Witches' Forest!
I'll defeat both the Eye of the
Midnight Sun and the Diamonds!
And how are you going to
do that with those arms?
That's right!
The whole reason we even came
here was to fix your arms.
Right...
So much is going on that I totally forgot!
He's got a point.
Damn it all!
Captain?
Asta? Wait, what are you doing here?
Miz Vanessa!
Thank goodness! You're awake!
Vanessa!
Honestly, you were trying to
do way too much by yourself.
Noelle... Finral...
You're here, too?
Huh? And some other familiar faces...
Though one appears to have lost his shirt.
Well, you see...
That's just his hobby.
No, really, it isn't.
It's been a while, Vanessa.
We were also looking for
a way to cure Asta's arms
and ended up in the same place as you.
That's right!
Just you wait, Asta.
I'm going to talk to the queen
and have her fix your arms!
I decline your offer!
Huh?
It would be in exchange
for your freedom, right?
I refuse to let you do that!
Wha... How can you be so selfish?!
This is the only way, you moron!
You're the one being
selfish here, Miz Vanessa!
How could you sneak back home
without telling anyone, you drunk?!
Well, what was I supposed to do, you shrimp?!
U-Uh, calm down, you two...
I'll figure it out!
And how are you going to do that?!
Shut up!
Even Asta told me to shut up!
But I have seniority...
You don't have to go through all this.
I still have my last resort!
H-Hey, Asta!
H-His eyes look a little crazed, don't they?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Wh-What are you trying to do?
This!
That sword...
Ow!
Asta!
What are you doing, you moron?!
That curse has sunk deep into your arms!
No matter how crazy you try to get,
you can't always compete
with the fate you're dealt!
So you're telling me that
it's my fate to sacrifice
one of my friends for my arms to get better?!
Who the hell's gonna abide by that?!
I don't care if I have to crush fate itself!
I'm gonna fight with these arms!
Huh? It's your fate to stay here?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Good ol' fate.
I hate that crap.
Who the hell's gonna abide by that?
I'm gonna do what I want, even if it
means I have to crush fate itself.
He just said the same
thing Captain Yami did.
One more time!
You idiot!
That's enough!
Your friends aren't here to be sacrificed!
They're here to win against a fate
that you can't fight on your own!
I have no intention of sacrificing
myself for you, either!
After I use the queen to fix your arms,
I'm going to use that anti-magic of yours
to get the hell out of here!
Crap...
Oh, then you should've just said so.
Uh, I'm pretty sure you shouldn't
have said that out loud...
Hey, Queenie.
If you can actually dispel Asta's curse,
could you go ahead and do it already?
Looks like your forest's in a lot of trouble.
He wants to save the people
out there as soon as possible.
He's an idiot, but he's strong.
I'm sure he'll be useful to you if you heal him!
And if he goes,
we'll follow.
The enemy is immense.
Couldn't you use all the manpower
you can get right now?
If you're truly a queen, you should be
doing whatever's best for your forest!
It's true. We currently lack the strength
to deal with the impending attackers.
Very well. I shall heal that brat's arms.
I'll even make them sturdier than before.
Sturdier? Really? Are they gonna be
huge like Captain Yami's, then?
I highly doubt that.
Sturdiness isn't necessarily
equal to how big they are.
Aw, come on!
What am I supposed to do about it?
You've got some guts, Noelle!
Yeah! I've never seen anyone
talk down to the queen before!
I'm royalty myself.
My legs are still shaking...
Be merry while you still can.
But in the end, both Vanessa
and that boy's anti-magic
sword's powers shall be mine.
Blood Recovery Magic:
Curse-Breaking Blood-Filled Cocoon.
My arms feel so light! This is awesome!
She performed such a powerful
spell in a mere instant?
This is the power of the queen?
This is great! They're completely better!
Look! Look, look, look, look!
Asta!
Look, look, look, look!
Now, when my back itches, I don't
have to scratch it against a pole!
And I can pick my nose!
But what I'm happiest about is that
I'll be able to work out again!
Asta...
He's still an idiot.
Well, I don't know if they're
actually sturdier or not,
but I can feel strength welling up inside me!
All right! Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Or...
"Let's go," my ass!
Do you know how worried we were?!
You crazy moron!
You could barely move a second ago!
Take that! And that! And that! And that!
Here! Take your stupid robe!
Thank you so much, guys! And I'm sorry!
No effect!
They're so hard!
What the heck? Did she use
a strengthening spell?!
No! They're just pure muscle! Hurgh!
Congrats, Asta.
Yeah! Thank you all for what you did, too!
I've fulfilled my end of the bargain.
Now let us see this so-called power of yours.
Yeah! Leave this to us!
Thanks for fixing my arms!
Hmph.
Asta, leave the Diamond forces to us.
Mars and Ladros... I have some
unfinished business with them.
All right, Old Man Zell. Don't die.
Yeah.
And put some clothes on.
Right...
You, too!
Burn! Burn!
Have they given up after a
single attack by Lady Fana?
They're weaker than I thought.
L-Look!
They must be the enemies
you warned us about!
How dare you do this?!
Let's go, Akimo!
Yeah! Let's protect the forest!
Wh-What's that monster?
Stay calm.
The queen's golem!
Wh-Who are those guys?
The great Third Eye is magnificent!
Lady Fana is not only immensely
powerful, but also beautiful.
I'd love to have a shot at her
if I ever get the chance.
But I guess I'll just have to settle
for these lowly witches today.
Attack!
Yes, sir!
Make sure you capture the lookers alive.
These witches possess powerful magic.
They'll make excellent slaves.
N-No!
Are you okay?!
Huh?
Eek! I was saved by a man!
Your muscles are gross!
Hmph.
What the heck was that for?!
The witches firmly believe
that women are superior.
Sorry she acted like that
after you saved her.
I'll put out all the flames.
Thanks, Noelle.
I'll rescue all the witchies!
I'm counting on you, Finral!
You've got some nerve,
doing this to the forest.
This place isn't the best,
but it was still my home.
I'll protect it, no matter what.
Let's go, Asta!
You got it!
Oh, hey. There it is.
I can't wait!
Diamond Kingdom
Mohawq
We are prepared to attack at any time.
Well, aren't you psyched?
But... Tsk, tsk, tsk... Hold your horses.
Where's the fun in dealing with the peons?
We're going to enjoy whoever's
left from both sides later on.
Yes, sir!
They're here.
Those numbers... Even with all the witches,
we're still vastly outnumbered.
But what's important is how
you fight. Right, Master?
Yeah.
Let's all split up.
B-But I swore that I'd protect you.
Thanks, Zell. But this
isn't the time for that.
You were considered a genius strategist,
so you should already know...
This is the only way we can win.
All right.
So many excellent slave
ladies to choose from!
Let us go!
That bastard! What does he
think he's doing to my cuties?!
The number of guards he has around him...
He must be the commander.
Miz Vanessa!
Use your threads to blast me up to them!
What? But I won't be able to
pull you back at that distance!
You'd be fighting in the air
with nothing to hold you up!
I'll be fine!
Well, if you're sure... I'll trust you!
Who the heck is that?
Fool! He's headed right toward us!
Take this!
No, you take this!
That's... the anti-magic brat
who defeated Lord Vetto!
Kill him!
There!
He's using the enemies as stepping stones.
I can't believe that boy!
Then again, I guess I can.
You guys cause trouble every single time!
Wh-What's with this brat?
Now no one...
will be able to stop Asta!
Quit it already!
Now's your chance to run!
Stop bossing me around, you stupid man!
I'm not thanking you!
Let's go!
Seriously?!
There you are.
How dare you kill Vetto?
I'll kill you!
Crap! I'm gonna die!
As if...
I'd be scared!
Made it just in time.
Thanks!
You keep getting in our way
over and over again.
I'll kill you once and for all.
Bring it on! I'll just keep throwing
your attacks right back at you!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Not Yet!
Cup o' Magic Noodles
Nothing beats eating a Cup o' Magic Noodles
while everyone else is fighting.
But... Tsk, tsk, tsk.
It's too early to eat them yet!
Magic in 3 Minutes
They won't be ready until three
minutes after you pour the magic in.
Ladros, is it time yet?
Cup o' Magic Noodles
Not yet!
But I like my noodles a little firm.
No! Not yet!
But—
Not yet!
I can do what I want—
Hey—
Not yet! Not yet! Not yet! Not yet!
And they're done!
Let's eat!
Thanks for the meal.
So fast!
I'm so glad your arms are better now, Asta!
But the Queen of Witches is amazing.
Scary, but get a good look
at her, and she's pretty.
I guess older ladies can be charming, too.
Black Clover, Page 59: "Flames of Hatred."
Page 59
Flames of Hatred
My magic is liking all of the ladies!