It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Life of a Certain Man
In the second stage of the
Royal Knights Selection Exam,
the battle between E Team and
G Team was growing intense.
Leopold from E Team approached
G Team's crystal,
and Langris from G Team was also
getting closer to E Team's crystal.
It's over, Brother!
Langris!
I'll stop you!
What a nice cold dessert.
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Snow Magic: Unclimbed Ice Wall!
Yes! We did i—
G Team wins!
G Team's crystal was also destroyed,
but E Team's crystal was destroyed first.
Thank goodness. Langris must've
gotten to it first.
Oh, dear. What happened?
Damn it! We lost! I wasn't
concentrating enough!
Does this mean I'm still nowhere
near my brother's level?
This ominous magic...
It's coming from where Finral is.
What in the world is happening?
How do you like that?
There's nothing you can beat me at!
What?
Miz Charmy!
Cotton Creation Magic: Fluffy Sheep Cushion!
Disappear.
Hey!
Just try and do something else.
Forget the match. We'll kill you.
There's something wrong with you!
The match was already over!
Maybe you've been on a roll lately,
but you're still Black Bulls flunkies.
What do you think you'll do against
the Vice Captain of the Golden Dawn?
Who the hell cares about status when we're
trying to protect our precious friend?!
Precious friend?
That's enough.
Those who go easy on their companions
in a fight can't be trusted.
But those who try to kill their
companions have problems
that run much deeper than trust.
He's in bad shape. Leave him to me.
Dr. Owen!
Water Recovery Magic:
Qualle Operation.
Will he be okay?
I'll do everything I can.
Companion? That useless fool brings
shame upon the Magic Knights.
You little...
Let's kill him after all.
Finral's nicer than anybody!
That's what makes him a true Magic Knight!
No matter how tough you are,
you're no Magic Knight!
I'm not a Magic Knight? What?
I guess making it this far
has gone to your head.
You sure talk big for a Black Bulls newbie.
Wizard King, before the next
teams conduct their match,
would you let me battle them?
Actually... Let's just start.
Why, you—
Asta!
Let the semi-finals begin!
You little—
Asta!
Vice Captain Langris has always
been a bit belligerent,
but it's not normal for him to act like this!
Yes. Something definitely isn't right.
Sir, aren't you going to stop them?
In actual combat,
no one says "stop" or "start."
So keep going.
You were with him then...
I disliked you from the first time we met.
You belong to the worst
possible Magic Knight squad,
Asta of the Black Bulls!
That's my line, you jerk...
Vice Captain Langris Vaude
of the Golden Dawn!
Time Binding Magic: Chrono Stasis.
You two can hear me, yes?
Although I'd like for you two to fight as if
this were real combat, it is still a match.
Sit tight for a long second,
until preparations for the
match are completed.
Don't worry. I'll have everything
ready before your enthusiasm cools.
Prepare for the semi-finals.
Get the crystals ready.
Y-Yes, sir!
Also, bring the other members
of B Team and G Team here.
Roger-dodger-roger! Um...
B Team has Xerx Lügner
and Mimosa Vermillion.
G Team has Fragil Tormenta
and Sekke Bronzazza.
Now, then...
I need to make sure to thank you
for interrupting my golden time.
Y-You don't need to thank me-ha.
Now, there's no need to be shy.
Pardon me.
Dark Magic...
Dimension Slash!
What in the world?!
His heartbeat is getting weaker.
Finral!
I'll never forgive you if you die!
Yeah! If you're going to die,
I need to kill you first!
Wake up! Don't make me set you on fire!
It'll be okay. I know that
he's really strong deep down!
Today won't be the last entry in
my observation journal for you!
That's a long way off!
If you die, you won't be able
to eat delicious noms, la!
You can make it through, la!
To think that's what was going on...
Must've been rough.
My eternal rival, Asta! Don't lose!
Have fun!
I thought we won.
Asta...
What's going on?
Huh? What's Asta doing here?
The semi-final round
between B Team and G Team.
We've already set up your crystals
at your starting positions.
What? We're starting the semi-finals already?
Let me just remind you that this is a match.
Whichever team can destroy
the other team's crystal first wins.
It's not about killing your opponent.
I wish you luck.
Mimosa, Xerx, I'm sorry about this.
I didn't mean for this to happen,
but I want to beat him!
Please, help me!
Of course!
There's something wrong with Langris.
Xerx?
Magic Knights clashing over personal stuff
and doing whatever the hell they want...
Are you all stupid?!
Hey!
But fine, whatever.
For now, he's much worse than you.
Let's do this, you little shit!
Langris...
What's going on?
Kindly explain, bah-ha.
Shut your mouths.
Bah-ha! Ha-bah, ha-bah...
You shouldn't talk to us
like that. Don't worry-ha.
Next time, I'll use my magic to—
There's no need.
Bah-ha?
All of you are absolutely worthless.
I'll show you all that I'm special!
Unconscious betrayal?
Yes. Based on the circumstances
up to this point,
it seems someone
among the Magic Knights
is unwittingly cooperating with
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
I can't help but feel like
there's someone like that.
So they're being controlled
by some kind of spell?
No... It's not a spell.
I wonder...
Maybe it is a spell.
He always leaves work undone to go
on his little trips to observe magic,
but his intuition is sharp.
There must be something going
on with the Magic Knights.
My other goal with this
Royal Knights Selection Exam
is to bring this unconscious
traitor to light.
Huh?
When they expend their
mana on the battlefield
or when they're confronted by powerful mana,
people tend to show their true colors.
But won't that be dangerous?
No.
We're doing this.
Does this mean that Langris
is the unconscious traitor,
Wizard King?
Let's go after the enemy's crystal
while protecting our own,
like we did in the first stage!
Mimosa, could you pull the crystal?
Right!
I need you to back me up, Xerx!
There has been a change of plans.
Sekke   Langris   Fragil
G Team
Xerx   Asta   Mimosa
B Team
We will now begin round
one of the semi-finals.
B Team: Xerx, Mimosa, Asta versus
G Team: Langris, Fragil, and Sekke.
Begin!
They handled that quickly.
His anti-magic sword can cut the
crystal in two with a single slash.
Which means...
I just have to break you and your crystal
before you can get to ours!
These don't suddenly change like
Magna's attack, so I can cut these.
But there are so many of them!
Recovery Magic: Princess-Healing Flower Robe!
Thanks, Mimosa!
It's only a matter of time before your
recovery spells aren't fast enough!
Before that happens, take back what you said!
Come on! Asta's doing his best out there!
You need to keep fighting
so you don't get laughed at!
That cowardly loser isn't a Magic Knight!
I won! That makes me the true Magic Knight!
You didn't even hesitate
to abandon the people!
Oh, well. They'll just have to be noble
sacrifices for the sake of our country.
Give me a break!
Finral has always used
his magic to help others!
So what, you naïve little brat?!
That's all he can do!
He was never strong enough
to defeat his enemies!
Asta!
I can't...
The one who wins in the end is the
one who's right about everything!
Is that so? In that case,
I'm right about everything!
What?
Because I'm going to win
for Finral's sake, too!
Oh, please.
Asta!
Don't give up, no matter what!
This is no longer a match.
What's going to happen in
this battle, Wizard King?
My recovery magic can't keep up!
Asta! Any more of this and your body
will break down before the crystal does!
We—
Not yet!
The side effects of my black form...
The intense pain in my muscles and bones...
My cool-down period is over.
Right now, I'm only able to go
into that state twice a day.
I was planning to save it for
when I fight Yuno in the finals,
but I can't afford to think like that now!
Still, in order to go into that state,
I need to concentrate and
make my ki circulate.
In these circumstances,
that's going to be impossible.
So...
It's all you, Xerx!
You dumbass!
Like I'd take orders from you.
Xerx!
I'm only doing this because
I don't like that guy.
Yet this dumbass is actually
putting all his trust in me.
Damn it.
Zora! Zora!
Zara Ideale
I'm home, Zora.
Welcome home, Dad.
Did you behave—Whoa! You did
all the housework perfectly again!
Thanks for everything you do, Zora.
My father was a very cheerful person.
You stink!
My father loved practical jokes.
You fell for it, Zora.
And he always laughed like a child.
Boom! The envoy of justice,
the Super Magic Knight Zora!
What is this?
It's a doll I made.
You made this?
Super Magic Knight Zora has a mouth
on him, but he's as good as his word.
He's a warrior who protects
the country behind the scenes!
Well? Isn't he cool?
I'm twelve years old, you know...
I'm not saying you have to match this.
I just think you should learn to
communicate with others more, Zora.
Right...
All right, then.
I'm gonna go protect the peace again.
Zara was the first peasant
to become a Magic Knight.
From the age of fifteen,
he failed the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam over and over.
But despite getting older and
becoming a father, he never gave up
and worked harder than anyone.
All of Zara's hard work
shone in Zora's eyes.
And he was prouder than anyone when
his father became a Magic Knight.
I ended up alongside this amazing
guy on the battlefield today.
He could use time magic.
He's the kind of guy who's gonna succeed.
I get to protect the country with a
bunch of amazing people like that.
Man, being a Magic Knight is awesome!
We all believe in each other and get
through life-or-death situations!
I'm going to continue protecting everything
I can with all the power that I have.
That's what makes a Magic Knight!
How are you going to protect
anything if you're dead, Dad?
Those are... Magic Knights
from the Purple Orcas.
They're Dad's companions.
They must've come to pay their respects.
Too bad, Zara Ideale.
A peasant trying to pass himself off
as a Magic Knight on the battlefield?
That's why you got nailed in
the back by one of your own.
I mean, the insolence of a mere peasant
thinking he could get along
with nobles like us...
Buzzing around saving civilians
on the brink of death...
You were an eyesore, you piece of trash.
No one wants a filthy Magic Knight like you.
Y-You people...
You call this a VIP room?
We're Magic Knights here!
Bring us your best alcohol!
B-But...
What? You don't want to pour me a drink?
Th-That's not...
I guess I'll have to punish you
for that attitude of yours.
Sir... Please forgive me!
Good job. This is making the
alcohol taste a little better.
Well, hello there, Magic Knights.
I'm about to get in your way.
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Just try and arrest me for
obstructing public duties!
You people...
They said my granddaughter
who lives in the town of Poe
was taken away by you and hasn't been back.
Please... Please give me
back my granddaughter.
Lord Xerx is exhausted after a long
expedition! Stay back, you old hag!
Please... Please, Sir Magic Knight!
You people...
Would you like to beautifully lose what
little life you have left with my magic?
Don't you dare defy the Vice Captain of the
Purple Orcas! He's the Saint of Pure Ice!
Who are you?
You people...
are not the Magic Knights
that my father dreamed of!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Golden Time
Golden Time.
Golden time.
That's my very precious
and irreplaceable time.
If someone is stupid enough to disturb it...
This is what happens.
You should all be careful. Bah-ha...
Lalala-di-la!
Next week,
we're going to make sure you stuff
yourself full of extra yummy goodness!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 82:
"Petit Clover! The Nightmarish Charmy SP."
Page 82
Petit Clover! The Nightmarish Charmy SP!
My never-ending appetite is my magic, la!