Gin.
I've woken you.
I apologize for my carelessness.
The dream the Miss drew for us...
Leaving this place to raise a flag of justice there;
calling in members of the group
and taking on the city of villains.
It was thrilling.
But we have seen how skilled these Russian soldiers are.
I will cut a path through them
and challenge Balalaika one on one.
She is certainly worthy of this white scabbard.
I've come this far with you, Gin.
So I'll be with you from now on as well.
Even to Roanapur?
Yes.
Good work.
Thanks to you, our job here will end without incident.
My job ends here.
Someone from Moscow will take over from here.
It's a shame I won't get to see the aftermath.
It really is a shame.
Hey Ishiguro.
Those three that came here.
Oh? What is it?
Not "oh!"
The two Caucasians and one Japanese
that came in here, did you look into them?
I'm having someone check the ICPO data,
but I haven't got anything-
What about having an international specialist come in?
Yeah. Someone named Kouno is supposed to be coming.
That white woman is definitely involved in the war
between the Washimine Group and the Kousa Council.
And maybe even the Adachi bowling center
shooting incident.
Got it? Don't take your eyes off of them.
What is it?
What?
You're the one who looked like you had something to say.
Was it my imagination?
Miss Balalaika...
Rock, are you going to keep talking about that?
I've already saved your life.
Is there something else you want?
If I were to simply wish.
If I were to simply listen.
One thing.
Let me say one thing.
If this is about to end,
before that happens,
I'd like you to completely crush the Washimine Group
until the survival of the group becomes impossible.
Without leaving a single withered tree.
Only that can free her.
I see.
I see. I see.
Indeed.
That is the only method
to push the princess back into a normal life.
You're a villain, Rock.
That was the correct decision.
You'll become a good villain.
Please forgive my delay.
I'm certain you must be tired from these long discussions.
Please don't worry about it.
This accomplishes one of our goals as well.
Let's wipe the slate clean and...
Boss,
We must prepare plans on who will succeed us,
in the future.
Hm?
If certain contingencies should occur in our absence,
it will be difficult for us to respond properly.
I wish to know your state of readiness over firearms.
Is that okay?
I can't say it too loud,
but compared to other groups, we have many more guns.
We've even purchased machine guns
from the guys in Hawaii.
Would you oblige me?
Morozumi.
I'd like to see the bullets as well.
I see. That's quite a competent bodyguard you have.
Do you have a secondary firearm?
Boss...
There's no profit in having a shoot-out now.
It'll be a pain later. Give it to her.
What is this?
Absolutely atrocious!
Keep up with me, okay Rock?
This is a atrocious gun.
Take a look, sergeant... Atrocious, isn't it?
Atrocious isn't it?
I doubt if even low life punks in the gutter
would use guns like this.
Absolutely atrocious.
What a hideous gun.
Have you ever stopped to consider,
what it would feel like to be shot with a gun like this?
That's it.
I can't work with scum
who shamelessly sport shoddy guns like this.
Mr. Yasuda! Gun shots!
Do it!
Enter the mansion!
Open up!
Open this door!
Or we'll force our way in!
Oh? This gun isn't so bad.
Sergeant, how are we on time?
It is not an issue, Kapitan.
But how do we explain this to the head?
He told me to make war and burn it all to ashes.
I simply followed orders obediently.
Rock.
This is your gun.
Do you want it as a souvenir?
I don't like guns.
And I don't carry things I'm not accustomed to.
But,
I will not forget that I pulled this trigger.
I'm returning this to you.
Sergeant, throw that gun away here as well.
We're returning to base.
No one move!
This is Yasuda of the fourth precinct!
I am Ishikawa of the 1st precinct.
I'm in charge of this case.
I'd like to hear about the gun shots earlier.
Please come with us.
How are we on time?
Just enough.
Rock, give this message to the Washimine girl.
Hotel Moscow will cease all attacks as of this moment.
The Washimine Group you seek to destroy
has already dispersed underground.
That girl thinks more flexibly than you imagine.
According to the information Bulgazivi gathered,
their group members believe
that their princess will invite them
to Roanapur to raise their flag.
Roanapur of all places.
My ride is coming.
Open a path, civilian policemen!
Hey! I'm not done...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The ambassador is waiting at the Mamiana.
Miss Vlatinera.
Hey wait!
Don't, Mr. Yasuda. It's a foreign plate.
Rock!
Hey!
You!
Wait!
Get him!
Don't panic!
We're the ones you have business with.
Don't be so easily distracted by small fry.
Farewell Mr. Civilian Cop.
If you ever need me, come by the CIS embassy any time.
It's V. N. Vasilinov.
Excuse me.
Damn it! I didn't make it in time!
Who are you?
I'm Kouno with International Investigations.
Why didn't you arrest them, if you witnessed gun shots?
It occurred inside, we only had assumption.
Who was that? Did you figure it out?
She's a big one.
They have their base of operations in Moscow,
they even have a strong foothold in Chechnya and New York,
The powerful Mafia organization called Hotel Moscow.
She's known as Balalaika.
She's a high ranking officer in Hotel Moscow!
What?
Damn it!
Emergency!
The scene of the incident to Center!
Send a message to all PCs in the area!
Did you get a photograph of her face?
Did you get a description of her appearance?
Nothing.
Then I'll at least find out her contacts within Japan!
Revy!
We need to tell her that the war's over!
Don't be stupid!
In just over thirty minutes
this place is going to be quarantined!
You're not getting to see her!
We don't have time.
Contact them from the ship.
We're close to departure time!
But!
Mr. Okajima.
Yukio.
Please escort us to the Maria Zeleska.
Miss.
Damn it!
I can't believe it!
He's been kidnapped by a high school girl!
You drive too?
I am a delinquent, after all.
Yukio, what was that act about taking Roanapur?
I'm standing in the twilight, just like you said.
But there are some things I can see because of that.
Doesn't it sound fun?
Hotel Moscow announced an end to fighting.
It's over!
What kind of promise is Balalaika's word?
Yukio.
How can anyone trust that rabid dog that
breaks all promises, betrays you, and spits on faith.
Hey! Hey!
This is a hold up!
Don't you understand?
If I could honestly believe that I could recreate the
group in Roanapur, that would have been wonderful.
But it was just a passing wish.
As long as Gin and I are here,
the Washimine and our emblem exist.
It has not been grounded yet.
So that's what you keep coming back to.
To begin with, I was born into the night.
I grew up with the night.
I've enjoyed pretending and playing on the side.
In the end, this is the path of reality.
I have no value as a hostage against Hotel Moscow.
Then as a shield.
At the very least, I'd like you to witness how this ends.
Only a massacre is waiting for you!
But there is a flower that may bloom there.
Have you forgotten?
We are Yakuza.
Damn it!
Gentlemen, the operation is complete.
Let us return to Roanapur.
Miss.
I'm not letting you get away!
We can't be the ones to break first in this battle.
Knock it off!
Rock!
I told you! She's already the walking dead.
Revy!
I heard that the Kousa Council
was destroyed due to internal discord.
However, the one who betrayed and slaughtered
Bando Tsugio, our group's leader, still lives.
The head of our enemy Hotel Moscow, Balalaika.
Living with honor, seeing justice through,
to reward honor is our pride.
There is no duty that you must be bound by!
That's just a front!
Please open the way.
Gin...
Mr. Gin is no longer with you.
I shouldn't have brought the Miss.
We're all the same.
No matter how far we go, we're not normal.
This is a place only those like us should be.
Don't you think so?
Lady?
There was a way in which you could have
avoided ending up like Miss Balalaika.
I thought you would choose that.
That's where I was mistaken.
You're not here to save face as Yakuza.
You struggled against being absorbed into the night.
That's why.
Standing here in the twilight, there are things I can see.
You should have Gin throw away his sword
and run away with him.
Become wanderers together,
seeking a far-off land.
That's a joke as well.
It's not a joke!
Where is the real you!
There are times I wonder,
"What if I were able to live like that?"
But the die is already cast.
I've always quietly wished
that life in Takamachi would go on forever.
With the trees and stores up.
That it'd be fun with you...
Too late.
It is too damn late.
The only place we end up is in a coffin of mud.
You tried to live.
I've blundered.
Revy!
I'm all right.
It was looking a little black,
but you made her say that.
That was your real bullet.
If it weren't for that, I'd be the one on the ground.
Don't talk!
This is going to hurt.
You'll have to withstand it.
Raise your leg up Revy!
I'm going to rewrap it!
Why?
Why has it come to this?
You were warped,
by lying to yourself that you wanted this.
You were too smart to fool yourself.
Eleven...
Eleven people have been killed on my orders
since that night I threw the dice.
Our city is full of people like that.
Now that I've woken up, it's much too far.
That land...
I apologize for having troubled you.
I will bring everything to an end.
Don't look at her, Rock!
You'll be damaged!
Is that you, Rock?
I feel like I haven't seen you in a million years.
How was that fake Chinese passport I got you?
Was it useful?
Dutch...
I've heard.
People are like dice, we throw ourselves into life.
Do you know the Frenchman who said that?
Jean-Paul Sartre.
An existentialist philosopher.
But I prefer, "Quickly put a hole in a guy
who tries to put five eggs into three baskets."
Those words.
Yeah, that's right.
There's work as soon as you get back.
They want a us to deliver a pile of guns
by the day after tomorrow.
All right. Later.
It's time for our flight, partner.
From Miss Balalaika for you.
In this city, Roanapur,
by the power of guns and liquor,
there's a wonderful place where you can
blow anything away through barbaric power.
It's not such a bad place.
That's what I'm beginning to think.
Yeah. It's not bad.
I want to see it all through from the twilight.
All right. Let's go then.
Into our city.
And? How was Japan?
Yeah, Balalaika was there and we were there.
It's the same everywhere.
What are you talking about?
I'm asking about Rock!
You two were away together for so long.
You did do it this time, right?
I don't want to tell.
When it comes to you.
Die.
We villains don't die that easily.
Bang.