What in the world is that creature?!
R-Run!
Where are we supposed to run?!
Oh, God...
It's the end of the world.
It appeared as though the world
would be destroyed by the demon.
But a single mage...
Lumiere...
Please kill me!
I finally understand...
why I was born with so much...
magical power.
I will not let you...
become a murderer!
A Reunion Across Time and Space
That's...
The prince!
Prince Lumiere!
They used a magic item that I created
to steal the elves' magic...
It was supposed to be used so
that we can all share magic.
Prince... Lady Tetia... What should I...
Is there still something I can do?
What were you even trying to do?
How annoying.
Wouldn't you have been better off
just giving me that body of yours?
Of course, if I had taken over your body,
that light magic would've
been absolutely useless.
But at this rate...
Everything will soon be gone!
The magic stones are amplifying his magic.
Even if I stop him, the kingdom will be...
Can I even stop him?
My prince!
Our magic item! The one we
made for equality and peace!
Of course!
I'll use the magic item we created...
and absorb his magic!
Did that work?
As I suspected... It's impossible
for it to absorb all of the magic!
He stopped...
The negative mana seems to be subsiding.
Lumi...ere...
Lumiere...
Soon, I'll marry Tetia and become your brother.
I'm sure there will be humans
who look down upon that.
You're probably right.
But with you...
I'll be able to create a
peaceful and equal world.
I truly believe that.
I believe that, too.
I'm sure...
...it was fate that brought us together.
Now's your chance.
Hurry...
Licht...
You are the future we believed in.
You are hope.
I... will stop you!
He defeated that monster!
The prince saved our kingdom!
He's our savior!
You stopped me from obtaining his body,
but that was still quite
an entertaining show.
I guess I'll just have to take
his grimoire for the time being.
Stop!
I won't let you have Licht's grimoire!
The magic stones...
You witnessed the end of that elf, didn't you?
If a human like yourself who isn't
loved by mana tried to use those,
you wouldn't be able to keep
your form even if you tried to
perform a puny little spell.
Like I care. I'm going to use the
magic stones to increase my magic.
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
This is...
Confinement magic, eh?
This girl isn't even concerned about
the effects of using forbidden magic.
Her seal is a bit vexing,
but I'll be able to use reincarnation
with the magic stones.
In that case...
"Come."
What?
Even more despair and tragedy for
the soul who possesses the four-leaf.
I guess I'll just have to
sow those seeds for him.
Forbidden Magic: Noad Nepesh.
I'll be sure to work slower and
much more carefully next time.
In an era where you two don't exist.
Secré!
Are you all right?
My prince!
So you managed to seal the devil.
But the seal that I put on
the devil will eventually...
Prince!
No...
This is how it should be.
I was able to keep my promise to Licht.
So...
My prince, I'm going to use
the magic stones to seal you.
It probably won't be complete, but it
should be enough to keep you alive.
If the devil's seal is broken,
the peaceful future we sought
will be taken away from us.
Secré, don't. If you use
any more forbidden magic,
you'll lose your humanity.
I cannot let you die here, Your Highness.
As Licht said, you are our hope for the future.
Several Years Later
The prince began his long
slumber in the form of a statue,
and for some reason, I turned into a bird.
I've been spared? But in this form...
I'll need the help of the future mages.
Five hundred years ago, I was
excluded from the natural realm.
I started preparing for the day that
the devil's seal would be broken
as I watched over Licht's
five-leaf grimoire.
And the one who ended up with that grimoire...
was a boy who was born without magic.
There was a sign that things were in motion,
but once the wheel started turning,
it proceeded quickly.
And finally, that day has come.
Today, we put an end to this long fight!
There you are, you creepy bastard!
Well, well... To think you were
able to undo his dark elf form.
I have no interest in toys
I'm done playing with, though.
I'm surprised this anti-magic
was able to undo this spell that
craves the life of whoever it touches.
It's far more annoying than
I could've ever imagined.
It's been five hundred years
since we last met, devil!
Unbelievable! To think I'd also
be reuniting with you two.
Wait, Yuno, is that...
Yeah...
The legendary first Wizard King?
Are you the real deal?!
But wait, you can move?!
Wait, what the heck is going on?!
Calm down, Asta.
Now's really not the time for that.
Wh-What?!
Who are they?
An elf revived by forbidden magic
and Magic Knights from
this era who helped with
gathering the magic stones
and protecting the kingdom.
That lady's ki seems kinda familiar.
Prince, we need to help Licht first.
Probably due to the forbidden spell,
he was reincarnated with his soul intact.
His soul is indeed here,
but he's not fully awakened.
Licht... Will you be able to wake him up?
Leave it to me.
Once, my magic could only
open and close things.
But after spending time with the prince,
it started to evolve as we
pursued further opportunities.
The prince was a genius at figuring
out the best potential for my magic.
My sealing magic in its current
state can release any seal!
Licht...
I can finally say
the words I wasn't able to say back then.
Thank you, Lumiere.
Well, it's a good thing you
made it in time in this era.
You had a rather unfortunate
farewell five hundred years ago.
This time, I'll get rid of both of you at once.
Licht...
Patry, I saw everything from
within my soul's deep slumber.
Licht, I...
Five hundred years ago, we lost
to this devil's scheme.
While I was drowning in despair,
the one who kept me from hurting
even more innocent people
and causing even more despair
was Lumiere.
Regardless of how it was done,
it appears that someone came to stop you, too.
Patry, even though you believed the
blade you wielded was for justice,
for those who were struck by your blade,
it was an unforgivable crime.
Still, even if you cannot be forgiven,
let me just say this...
I know you did your best.
Licht...
What we can do right now
is fight against the next tragedy
that's about to occur without letting
our mistakes break our spirits.
Let us finally put an end
to our five hundred years.
Yes, indeed.
I'll swallow up your trivial little feelings,
and that'll be the end of it.
Light Magic: Mana Zone...
Lamp of Avior-Gloria.
Sword Magic: Origin Flash-Rampage.
They managed to blow apart my magic,
which devours this world's magic.
The one who used the most forbidden spell,
and the one who absorbed all his magic...
In other words, they've been
affected by that world.
They're fast!
H-Holy crap...
If our attacks continue at
this speed and power...
He won't be able to counter
with his word soul magic.
They did it!
Douve Nuutra Edde!
My prince!
Lumiere!
That spear... It breaks down spells.
I commend you for being able
to attack me this much.
But no matter how powerful you may be,
you will not be able to kill me now
that I have my body and grimoire!
Not happening!
Anti-magic?
As I thought...
Maybe with anti-magic...
This spear can break down
anything it touches, but he...
But alone, he's nothing to fear.
"Get back."
"Storm of Blades."
Thanks, everyone!
His magic is overwhelmingly vast...
But it doesn't feel oppressive at all.
It's like a well-honed blade.
So this is the awakened elf leader.
But what is this warm and nostalgic
feeling that seems to be embracing me?
My prince! Your arm!
I will close the wound and seal the damage.
Sealing Magic: Closed Sorrow.
Thanks, Secré.
That's so freakin' cool!
As I'd expect from a friend
of the first Wizard King!
But, uh... Somehow, I don't feel like
this is the first time we're meeting.
Hrm...
Like, your ki, your atmosphere,
and your eyes really remind
me of someone I know...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! What's
the big idea?! Ow, ow, ow!
Focus on the fight.
That ability of yours is rather convenient.
It did manage to seal me, after all.
For magic of this world, which is
like a weed and not even powerful
like four-leaf magic, that is.
Though now that I have my body,
it's just stunted and worthless magic.
Be quiet.
My prince managed to find
possibilities even in magic like mine.
He showed me that there was
something even I could do!
I have a four-leaf grimoire and light magic,
so people say that my magic is amazing,
but I just think we're all different,
and we're all pretty amazing.
But my magic can only open and close things.
It's practically useless.
What did I tell you?
I'm sure there are plenty of
uses for your sealing magic
that you haven't discovered yet.
There are opportunities for everyone,
and things that only they can do.
Something only I can do?
Just like the magic items
we're making right now...
If everyone tried to use
their powers for everyone,
I think this would be a wonderful kingdom.
You exist only to steal from others!
The ones you looked down on,
stomped on, and made a mockery of
are going to defeat you today!
Then you should probably hurry it up.
No matter how much you blow away this magic,
it will keep flowing until you defeat me.
Since the exit is on this top floor,
all of your friends in the lower levels
will be swallowed up and die
if you keep wasting time.
You bastard!
But even Licht and Lumiere's
magic wasn't able to defeat him.
Anything but a full-fledged attack
on our part will be useless.
But of course.
We will rid this place of this accursed magic
with a mighty blow made with
the help of our friends.
Licht!
I'll be borrowing your strength.
Tch. This seemed like
a good idea at the time.
Hey, you're far too close to me, human.
Can't you make this space wider?
Are you being serious right now?
I just saved your ass,
and that's how you thank me?
You're totally still the Prickly Queen,
despite being someone else inside.
Damn it. At this rate, it's just going to
chip away at my magic until it's all gone.
The only bright side to all this
is the fact that you can use
recovery magic. Damn it...
You have some nerve. And when I
was kind enough to heal you...
Wait, uh... Why the hell are you shining?
You're blinding me!
This is...
That's what you get for
wasting my precious food!
Behold the power of appetite!
Licht...
And now, you will face the
true wrath of the elves.
Ultimate Sword Magic: Demon-Dweller
Sword-Conquering Eon!
Holy crap!
His magic is on a completely
different level.
We did it.
You're so amazing, Licht!
That's... the devil's heart?
"Heal."
I told you! You cannot kill me.
Not with magic from this world.
He can still regenerate,
despite how powerful that spell was?
How are we supposed to...
That's the true power of that sword.
Is there still some power I haven't
unlocked in my own sword?
There might still be a possibility!
I couldn't erase that spear,
but I was able to block it!
In that case, it's just that my anti-magic
was weak, but it was still effective!
If I can fight like them...
There's a power I can use
because I've got no magic!
I have no magic.
But that's exactly why there's
a power only I can use!
Not yet! I'm not done yet!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 119: "The Final Attack."
Page 119
The Final Attack
Yuno! Let's shut that guy up together!