It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Asta and the other Black Bulls headed
to the beach town of Raquey
in order to go to the Underwater Temple
that lay deep beneath the water there.
Asta and the other Black
Bulls received an order
to retrieve the magic stone in the temple
so they can stop the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
who want to separate from the
Clover Kingdom and create their own country.
But...
Why are you all playing around?!
And you're not?
C-Captain Yami...
All right, gather round, you idiots.
Apparently the Underwater Temple
really is at the bottom of the ocean.
But the mana kicks up the
ocean currents so much that,
ordinarily, even a first-class
mage can't get near it.
But on the night of the full moon,
the mana becomes weaker.
We might be able to get in then.
Like the name suggests, the Underwater
Temple is on the ocean floor.
We can't just walk to it.
So Noelle...
Take us there with your water magic.
Give us a ride there.
B-But I'd need incredible magic
control in order to do that.
I can't!
You do it.
The next full moon is a week away.
Learn to control it by then.
Surpass your limits.
The Water Girl Grows Up
Where are you going?
Oh, I just thought I'd let in some fresh air.
I see. So...
What's your foot doing there?
Hey, now, how did that get there?
This foot is so rude.
You were planning to forget your work
and go out to play, weren't you?
What? Now, why would I go out to play?
I just wanted to go observe some magic—
You don't have time for that!
Please do your work for once!
Hurry up and shut that window!
Right...
Honestly... We haven't even resolved the
incident with the Eye of the Midnight Sun yet.
Don't be so angry, Marx.
You're gonna die young.
And whose fault is that?!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun, eh?
I hope Yami and the others are doing well.
I just hope they aren't fooling around.
I wish I could've gone to
the Underwater Temple.
I feel sick from drinking too much...
I'll be the sun that'll make you shine.
You bastard! How dare you eat my pudding?!
It was yummy!
I wrote my name on it!
Other people's food always tastes better!
You bastard!
Goodnight, my angel.
Munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy...
Seconds, please!
Knock it off, you assholes!
We're not here to play!
I can't concentrate like this!
I'll kill you all!
Sorry!
What a beautiful voice.
I wonder if she's from Raquey.
It's so beautiful and ethereal...
Are these bubbles magic?
Whoa, is she a water spirit?
Eek! You heard that?
How embarrassing!
Eek!
Oh. She's not like what I'd imagined.
Well, now that you've heard me,
there's no way around it. Let's be friends!
La-dee-dah!
Friends?
I'm Kahono. What are your names?
I'm Noelle. The meathead is Stupidsta.
Who are you calling
"Stupidsta the meathead"?!
Ah, so Noelle and Stupidsta the meathead.
What a strange name.
Wait, don't believe her!
How naïve are you?!
Huh?
That's totally a nickname,
and she's making fun of me!
It's Asta! My name's Asta!
I see. Nice to meet you, Asta!
So what were you doing out here, Kahono?
I was singing.
Well, yeah, I could see that.
I was doing vocal training.
I love singing at this spot.
Training?
Yup! I have a dream!
I want to be a singing,
dancing, magic-using...
idol!
What's an idol?
What?!
You don't know?!
Nope.
They're all the rage in the Common Realm
and Noble Realm right now!
Oh...
Well, you see... So, you see... Well...
Idols are popular people who
can sing, dance, and use magic!
Huh...
I'm going to become a famous
idol and get super rich!
So you're after money?
What's so great about money, anyway?
If you do have it, it's just in the way.
It's not in the way! Money's important!
You've never had to worry about not
having money, so you wouldn't understand.
But money's really important!
You can't eat tatoes without any money!
If you don't have any tatoes,
why don't you just eat steak?
Damned royalty!
Yeah! Money's really important.
I totally understand what Stupidsta's saying!
Seriously, who are you calling "Stupidsta"?!
Was it Kasta?
I told you, it's Asta!
Oh, right. As—Oh?
What?
Stupidsta, your body's weakened.
It's Asta, damn it!
Huh?
What?
Your muscles are pretty fatigued.
Are they?
Do you ache when you move?
Wait, how can you tell?
That's my power.
Power?
Don't worry. You'll feel better in a sec.
Song Recovery Magic: Healing Lullaby.
This is...
She pinpointed each individual spot.
What precise magic use.
H-How do you feel?
Well, I feel...
This is awesome! I don't
hurt anywhere anymore!
My body feels so light!
My muscles aren't fatigued anymore!
Thank you, Kahono! You're amazing!
I've never seen song recovery magic before.
Great!
Okay, that'll be 100 yuls per session.
You're charging me?!
Just kidding!
Good...
Or not!
You're really charging me?!
Money's important, right?
Here...
One hundred.
Thank you kindly.
Just let me know when you
want me to sing for you again.
My hundred yuls...
That's just spare change.
How is that spare change?!
I can buy at least ten tatoes with that!
See? It is change.
Damned royalty!
You're both really funny.
How old are you?
Fifteen...
Same here.
Really? I'm fifteen, too!
We're the same!
Really?
Hey, let's be friends!
Sure, count me in. You're pretty funny.
A girl my age... who's a friend?
This is my first one.
W-Well, if you insist,
I guess I don't mind.
I'm willing to be your friend.
Yay!
Oh, sorry. I'm so happy, I couldn't help myself.
Really?
I see. So you're both Magic Knights.
That's amazing!
I-It's no big deal.
It's to be expected for me. I'm royalty.
I'm a peasant, though.
So, what brings you to Raquey?
Taking a vacation?
We're on an important mission.
We're actually trying to get
to the Underwater Tem—
Stupidsta!
The Underwater Temple?
Sorry, but this mission's a secret.
Well, whatever.
So, what were you two up to at this hour?
Could it be... Eek!
Wh-What are you talking about? Of course not!
The moonlight is so romantic, isn't it?
The sound of the splashing waves
also heightens the mood and... Eek!
I told you, that's not it!
I was training, too! Magic training!
Magic training?
Y-Yeah. I can't give you the details,
but I need to learn how to control my magic
within the week before the next full moon.
Otherwise, this important mission—
I see.
So you want to control your magic...
Hey, Noelle. Show me your magic real quick.
Huh?
You can do it, Noelle!
Wow! That's amazing!
I see. Good work, Noelle.
Now that we're friends,
I have some advice for you.
Huh?
I think you're trying to hold in
your mana too much when
you try to control your magic.
Huh?
Listen closely.
Can you hear it?
I listen to the sound of
the waves to calm myself
so I can use my magic exactly how I want to.
Exactly how you want to?
It might just be me, but I think that true
concentration comes from a calm heart.
From a calm heart?
I get it!
I also feel like my best swings happen when
I'm not thinking about anything at all!
Would you shut up?
You don't even use magic, and you're
never thinking about anything, anyway.
What's the kindest memory you have
that brings you the most peace?
My kindest... memory?
Yeah. Maybe your family?
My family...
To think that the last thing the
one they called the Steel Princess
gave this world would be
someone as useless as you.
I'll never accept a failure
like you as family.
Solid...
Are you seriously Mother's child?
The House of Silva doesn't
need someone like you.
Nebra...
Um, Nozel...
Why did Mother have to die to
give birth to someone like you?
You killed our mother.
Thanks for the advice, Kahono.
I'll try practicing a bit more.
Let me know if you get tired.
It'll only be a hundred... No, it'll only
be a thousand yuls, since you're a royal.
A kind memory...
Sister, how are you doing?
You're shining under my sun!
Are you stupid?
Not yet!
Keep it up!
You're truly a goddess.
My little sister, Marie...
What the heck is that?
Are they having some kind of contest?
Not yet!
Thanks, Kahono.
You can just pay me later.
Of course.
Not yet...
I can't drink any more...
Not yet!
Noelle!
Everyone left me...
Won't someone come get me?
The full moon is tomorrow...
Tonight's my last chance.
Don't worry! You've almost got it, Noelle!
There's no time... I still
can't control it at all.
At this rate, the mission will be...
I just got a great idea!
Asta?!
Noelle! Stop thinking,
and set all of your magic free!
Huh?
I just remembered!
That thing from the first time you lost control
would probably go underwater the best.
Remember what Kahono said earlier?
That you were holding your magic back?
If that's the case, maybe it'll work
if you just let everything loose.
A-Are you crazy?
If it doesn't work—
I told you! If that happens,
I'll use my sword to save you!
So don't worry and just go!
Fine! Don't blame me if something happens!
I'm releasing...
all my magic!
Amazing!
I knew it! This isn't going to work at all!
How am I supposed to relax in this situation?
Noelle!
I guess I really can't do it.
I mean...
I don't have any... kind memories at all...
Noelle!
You can do it!
You're always talking big,
so what the hell is that?
And you call yourself a Black Bull?!
All that awesome magic is going to waste.
Hurry and learn how to control it
so you can fight me!
It'll be fine! Even if you mess up,
you won't die or anything!
Just take it easy!
You must be hungry!
Hurry up and finish so you can eat this!
Even if you fall, I'll catch you gently!
If you fall, I'm kicking you back
up there, so make this work.
Grey Disguised as Magna
Just get it done, damn it!
Noelle! You can do this!
I had some...
Some kind memories within me.
So you're Nozel's little sister.
Your big bro mentioned that you're some
loser who can't even control her magic.
And that you wouldn't be able to pass
the Entrance Exam even if you tried.
I've never seen a royal fail before.
If you'll excuse me...
Well, if you feel like fighting,
why don't you come join my team?
Huh?
The absolute worst Magic
Knights squad, the Black Bulls.
We're all nothing but losers.
Meaning we're perfect for you.
I was with my family for years, but I didn't
have a single pleasant memory of them.
It's only been a few months since
I joined the Black Bulls, but...
I have so many memories!
So many kind memories.
And...
They all acknowledged me
and gave me a mission.
I want to help them!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Cradle!
I... I did it!
All right!
The Sea Dragon's Cradle...
I did it! I really did it!
Don't get distracted!
I'll protect the food!
This feels great after
being in the sun all day!
Hey, it's my turn!
I'll be right there!
Hup!
Asta! That was my job!
S-Stupidsta...
You did it, Noelle!
Huh?
Could you not touch me so casually?!
What?!
Who the hell are you?
Thank goodness everything ended well.
Now, let's drink up.
Kahono! I did it—
Huh? Kahono?
All right! Time to celebrate!
Yeah! Let's celebrate!
Here we go!
You did it, Noelle.
You surpassed your limits.
Well, guess we should get going
to the Underwater Temple.
You've got some great friends!
They're the ones who should be
cheering for you in the end!
Good for you!
Well, I'll be waiting for you, Noelle!
Inside the temple! Okay?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Song Recovery Magic!
Song recovery magic?! That's amazing!
Sing for me!
Sure! It'll just be ten billion yuls!
Here you go!
Okay, I'll sing!
L-o-v-e! Kahono!
Kahono Idol Show
What in the world are you doing?
Yay! I made some new friends!
I'm sure you'll be invincible once
you can control your magic, Noelle.
Let's meet again soon!
Black Clover, Page 42:
"The Underwater Temple."
Page 42
The Underwater Temple
My magic is song magic!