The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
After cleaning up the mess at
the royal capital for the time being,
Asta and the other Black Bulls
returned to their hideout.
We're almost home, you dumbasses!
Yeah!
After all that's happened, it feels
like we haven't been back in forever.
Right?! Once we get back, I'm gonna
work out in peace, at least for today!
In peace, eh?
We're... almost... there.
Return
Heck yeah! We're here!
Hey, Henry! Hurry up and turn
this thing back into our hideout!
Hmm...
Henry?
What's the matter?
Are you constipated?
I... forgot... what... the...
hideout... looked... like.
What?!
Well, that's classic.
What the hell, man?!
You lived in the place the longest!
How could you forget?!
When you go in, there's the huge common room,
and beyond that is...
Tell him, Asta!
Huh? W-Wait! I have no idea!
It was my exhibit of Marie merchandise.
It was a giant pantry filled with
ingredients from around the kingdom!
Nah, it was a sauna.
Did any of those actually exist?!
Then again, I sorta think they did exist...
Well...
The rooms did keep moving around in
the hideout, so it's hard to remember.
That's... because... you... guys...
kept... breaking... everything.
Thanks for fixing the rooms, but don't
change the floor plan without telling us!
How many times did I take the lost Yami
to the bathroom with my spatial magic?
I-I wish you would've told us!
I'm... sorry... about... that.
I know!
Why don't we tell Henry all of our requests
and make the hideout even more
comfy than it was before?
Great idea, Asta!
Agreed!
Making it even easier to enjoy
a drink than before is the best.
We're making it comfier in general.
This is my chance to get closer to everyone!
Sure, knock yourselves out.
All right!
We're counting on you, Henry!
Leave... it... to... me.
Here and here.
Just go ahead and jot down
your requests on those forms.
Here. You guys get one, too, Nero and Zora.
Jeez... You sure like meddling, you little shit.
He seems to be having a hard time...
Well, everyone basically
wrote whatever they wanted.
My request is that we transfer the hideout
right next to the church where Marie is.
Big Brother! Now we can
see each other every day!
Marie! We'll be neighbors soon!
I want to be in the same room as everyone
else for 24 hours a day and 365 days a year.
I-I'm so embarrassed... I just want you to
make it so no one ever sees me again.
I'd like a lot of curtains to shut so
I can make the place completely dark.
I'm shooting for ten meals a day!
You do that anyway.
Make sure you tack on an
all-you-can-drink option, too!
I'm surrounded by idiots.
I wrote that I want the
room next to yours, Magna.
Because I can tell what you're doing
behind those walls with my magic detection.
I can mess with you all I want!
I'm gonna kill you!
Like you even could.
The hell did you say?! Come back here, damn it!
A-A room next door?!
I guess if Nero ends up in a different room,
she can't wake me up anymore.
I was just pecking at you because
your snoring was so loud.
C-Come to think of it,
Asta and Nero weren't even neighbors.
They were in the same room!
B-But that was when Nero was a bird!
She just perched on the windowsill!
Not that this has anything to do with me!
Hmm...
Looks like Henry's gonna take a while yet.
O-Of course he is.
Here, if you're bored.
What's this for?
Are we gonna kill some time looking for bugs?
Did you dumbasses forget
about my adorable little pets
that ran off when our hideout got destroyed?
Go catch them before they
cause trouble anywhere.
That's right!
Oh, but that'll be a cinch. They got
used to me after I took care of them.
Don't you underestimate those monsters.
This forest is their backyard.
After a couple of days,
they probably went feral again.
You'll be dead an instant
if you let your guard down.
Wait, wait, wait! If that's the case,
aren't you underestimating the situation,
telling me to catch them with just thi—
Shut your mouth and get going.
Yes, sir!
There are three magical beasts.
If the rest of you are bored,
split up and go find them, too.
Okay!
You got it!
Fighting magical beasts sounds like so much fun!
I'll kill you if you lay so much as a
finger on any of my adorable pets.
Hey, stop that! I'm busy talking
with Marie's picture here!
Let's find them together, friends.
I-It's a pleasure to work with you both.
Listen to me, damn it!
Noelle, Nero! Let's group up,
since we're all newbies.
I guess I don't have a choice.
Hang on, where'd Zora go?
What a pain. Like I have time for that.
Now, then... I'll punish Masked Boy
With Droopy Eyebrows later for bailing.
I've got a big job to take care of myself.
I'm counting on you dumbasses.
Hey, magical beasts!
Get out here!
Woof! Woof, woof, woof! Meow!
Th-That's actually sort of cute.
Meow?
L-Like we'll ever find them that way!
Besides, he said the magical
beasts went feral again,
so they'll get us if we let our guard down.
But I'm sure they'll remember me,
since I took care of them!
They'll warm up to me!
I mean, Nero, you were basically
like my pet when you were a bird,
so you agree, right?
Don't be rude.
I was only watching over your grimoire.
You were actually my pet.
Ow, ow, ow!
They say the more you bicker,
the better you get along...
N-Not that I care about that at all!
I only came with him because I had to!
I sense ki!
I-It's not like I was worried about you two—
There you are!
Anti-birds?!
What are you guys doing here?!
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You must've annoyed them by being so loud.
Ow, ow, ow!
I'll try looking for the
magical beasts from the sky.
H-H-Hey, wait a sec!
Maybe I was overthinking this.
I'm actually not sure they get along at all.
Wait, we're alone together?!
What a creepy-ass forest.
You scared, Magna?
Wh-What'd you say?! Shut yer trap
and hurry your ass over here!
Hey, I told you to hurry—
Knowing that dumbass,
he probably hid somewhere just so he
could go "Boo!" and jump out at me.
You're not gonna scare me!
And I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
There you are! You think an ambush
like that would actually work?!
Boo!
My "scare and shock" plan
was a huge success!
I'm gonna kill you!
You think you actually can, Magna?
Come at me with all you've got.
No one's gonna stop us here,
so we can let loose all we want!
You sure about that? I think we're
on pretty different levels now—
I'll just have to show you.
I became incredibly strong after
fighting you when you were an elf!
Ooh, then me, too!
The mana's calling me...
It's been a while since we've faced each other.
I might have so much fun that I go overboard!
Bring it on!
Wh-What in the world was that sound?!
I think Magna and Luck are
revisiting their fiery friendship!
Who the hell cares?!
Hey! How long are you two
gonna hide behind me?!
I-I'm so embarrassed! Please don't look at me!
Then you should've stayed home!
B-B-B-B-B-But I need a wall to hide behind!
Who the hell are you calling a wall?!
We don't know when the
magical beasts will attack,
and this forest is really creepy and scary.
Your face is scarier than
anything else here, Gordon!
Huh?
Also, it's really embarrassing,
so please don't look!
There they are.
I need to hurry up
and catch them so I can get
back to Marie as soon as possible!
Let's do this, you two!
Whoa!
Th-The hell are you two doing?!
W-W-Well, they just appeared out of nowhere!
Hey! You! Let go of me already!
My fear's intensified even more!
Hey! Hey, I said!
M-My heart's not ready yet...
I-I was a fool to count on either of you!
Let go of me! How the hell
am I supposed to catch them?!
So yummy, la!
It's fate that makes me want to eat
buns while looking for magical beasts.
And it's fate that I want to drink.
Finral, go buy me another
one with your spatial magic.
Um... We should probably get back
to looking for the magical beasts...
Oh, quit being such a square and
drink with me, you goody-two-shoes.
Have a bun. They're piping hot,
straight out of the oven, and nummy!
Look, I'd honestly love to, but...
If Yami found out, I'd be killed!
But I'm sure the others
are already catching them.
I guess we can relax for a
little bit longer—Huh?
Hey, where'd Finral go?
He must've gone to buy more booze.
La!
Hey, Charmy. Get me a snack—
Did I drink too much?
You got big all of a sudden, Charmy.
And you're all hairy. And look at those nails.
You need to take better care of them.
The pretty boy from the Golden Dawn
won't give you the time of day at this rate.
Wow, that was fun. You're not bad, Magna.
Same to you.
I guess I'll let you off the hook for today.
Luck, you're not leaving me behind.
If you get ten times stronger,
I'll get ten times stronger, too.
So both of us can still get stronger.
Don't you think so?
My bad.
I couldn't really hear you because
this magical beast caught me.
Damn, you're hopeless.
I'll save you in a sec...
I don't have any stamina or mana left...
I know, right?
Hey, stop that! It's me!
I was taking care of you guys before Asta!
I don't even taste good!
Man, I can't find them anywhere.
A-And Nero hasn't come back, either.
I feel all antsy when it's just the two of us.
Those are Magna's...
Don't tell me a magical beast got him...
Magna! Luck!
Wake up!
This isn't good. The other Black Bulls
were also defeated by the magical beasts.
What?!
Asta... Forget about us...
The captain's in... trouble...
Occupied.
Tch. I'm in here, damn it!
Is that you, kid? Who said
you could come back already?
You might be in a hurry,
but I'm facing my final boss, and if I lose
focus, it's gonna go back into hiding!
I said occupied, damn it!
I guess you three aren't here
to take a piss together, huh?
I'm sure Captain Yami will be fine, but...
Magna and Luck were almost eaten,
so if all three happened to attack
at once, it might be bad news!
Captain Yami! Please be safe!
Hey, come on. Stop licking me.
Your drool reeks.
Wait, Captain Yami! What the heck's going on?!
I thought the magical beasts were after you!
Yeah, I guess they sorta were.
Looks... like... they...
wanted... some... attention.
They wanted attention?
Come to think of it,
when I first ran into these guys,
they just wanted to be coddled, too.
I can't remember exactly when,
but I was heading back to the hideout.
I ran into them after their
parents were killed.
Guess some nobles were having
some fun hunting magical beasts.
Better give it up. Your folks aren't
ever going to wake up again.
I got separated from my parents, too.
Chin up. We have to keep living.
Hey, now. Don't get the wrong idea.
I never said I was going to take care of—
Guess you're not giving me much of a choice.
That's such a touching story!
I'm so happy I heard it!
The baby magical beasts are way too cute!
Yeah...
It didn't even take six months for
them to grow as big as their folks.
Feeding them costs a fortune. I've tried
to abandon them so many times.
I wish I hadn't heard that!
Yeah...
So I had you dumbasses catch them
before they attacked a nearby village,
though if they wanted to go back into the wild,
I was gonna let them loose in
some mountains somewhere.
La!
Are you all right, Mister Yami?!
Magna!
You're all safe!
Yeah! Though we reek after those
magical beasts licked us all over.
I thought we were gonna get eaten,
but they just wanted some attention.
Apparently, everyone got exhausted
from that and collapsed.
All of you sure are troublesome.
I-If that's how they were with us,
we were worried about how hard they were
going to beg Captain Yami for attention.
But I guess that's Mister Yami for you!
Well, he is their owner.
He's used to taking care of them.
There, there, there, there...
I need to make dolls of all of you, too.
If you lick Marie, I'll kill you.
They're cute, but their drool stinks.
If you want any more attention,
go take a bath and brush your teeth.
I see... You guys must love
Captain Yami and the Black Bulls, too.
There, there. You can ask me,
your caretaker, for attention, too.
Guess they still think of you as food, kid.
Wait, wait, wait! That can't be true!
You must be hungry. Here you go!
I've got some food for you!
Yeah, he's definitely food.
That was a nice nap.
Zora! Where the heck did you go?
Don't worry about the details, you little shit.
The hideout isn't done yet?
The sun's going down.
Don't... worry.
I... just... put... everything... together.
Recombination Magic: Black Bulls' Hideout
~ Hard Rock Bison Style!
Black Bulls' Hideout
Hard Rock Bison Style
This... was... Magna's... request.
How vulgar.
The hell are you talking about?!
How could it get any cooler than that?!
I can't wait to see the inside!
Now this is what I'm talking about!
I can drink all I want!
I keep eating and eating, and food
still keeps coming around, la!
Why the heck is there a hole here?
I-I'm embarrassed, so I wanted a place to hide.
I couldn't become neighbors
with Marie, but Angel Marie,
tell Big Brother what the
weather will be like tomorrow!
Tomorrow will be mostly sunny,
but partly cloudy.
The high for tomorrow will be
24 degrees Celsius, with a low of 13 degrees.
This talking Marie doll is the best!
Good work!
I guess a cutie-pie maid was too
much to ask for after all.
I'll... clean... for... you.
What?!
Sorry... about... that.
I-I appreciate the thought.
So, Henry... How are
everyone's rooms split up?
About... that...
Here's... Gordon's... request.
Let's all share a room as friends.
What?!
I'm not neighbors with Asta,
but in the same room as him!
As friends? This is way beyond friendly!
This can't be happening!
This reminds me of when I used to sleep
with Yuno and Nash back at the church.
Man, every night is gonna be so much fun!
You can count me out.
Same here.
Y-Yeah. I'm royalty.
I'm so embarrassed!
Well, it pisses me off that
I'm in the same room as Luck,
but it'll be cool talking with Mister Yami
into the wee hours of the morning.
Yeah, that's not happening every night.
What?!
The... captain... gets... a... different... room.
The hell's this?!
That... was... the...
magical... beasts'... request.
All right, fine, then.
Like hell, you asshole!
Yeah, so...
Our hideout isn't some fun little theme park.
As before, this filthy mansion is our hideout.
After all's said and done,
this is the most relaxing.
I feel like we're finally home.
I-I'm not disappointed in the least.
When I first came here after
joining the Black Bulls...
They all accepted me immediately,
even though I didn't have any magic.
Ever since then, every day's been action-packed,
and we had plenty of close calls,
but I was able to get through
them thanks to everyone's help.
I'm so happy that I got to join the
Black Bulls and get to know all of you!
Wh-Where'd that come from?
You're making me blush.
The same goes for us.
It's because you never gave up,
Asta, that we were able to grow.
You're always reckless, but I'll admit
that you're as stubborn as ever.
We need to hurry up and prove Asta's innocence.
Yeah.
For now, we're gonna have to continue
our research on the devils.
Right!
We're back at our hideout,
so I'm gonna work even harder!
Huh? Where are you going, Captain Yami?
Next time on Black Clover, Page 126:
"The Blue Rose's Confession."
Page 126
The Blue Rose's Confession
So what exactly is Captain
Charlotte going to confess?