Roanapur...
Various gangs from around the
world fight for territory in this city.
It's a strange balancing game.
This is a terrible tragedy.
The outside of the building is unrecognizable.
Right now we know that there are 32
fatalities from among the embassy workers.
And when the wounded are added, there are 150 victims.
Currently the Zaire military is continuing its rescue efforts.
Right after the bombing, a terrorist organization calling themselves
the Protectors of the Islamic Front have taken credit for the attack.
It sure is a dirty room.
Revy, are you awake?
We have a job. Dutch says it's an emergency.
Revy!
That you, Rock?
Yeah. It's a big last minute request.
He told me to "wake her the hell up", so I rushed down.
God dammit.
The job... from who?
Mr. Chan.
From the Triad.
I've been waiting for a while now.
Don't you even offer a cup of coffee?
You call this service, Dutch?
I didn't know we were a café.
You know why we have a torpedo
boat, don't you, Mr. Chan?
That's cold, Dutch.
We were burned out of our place and came straight here.
Isn't it human nature to at least offer a cup of tea?
That sure was a tragedy, Chan-san.
They say half of your offices are gone.
We got hit hard.
Was it the Russians?
Of course not.
We're always very friendly with Miss Balalaika...
Hey Two-Hands.
Did I miss a lot?
Not at all. We're about to start.
This is the cause of everything.
But that just shows it was worth it.
I took this from a stupid Bulgarian who
tried to make a quick buck in my territory.
I don't recall giving permission to anyone but Yolanda
from the Church of Violence to sell weapons.
But these guys misunderstood.
They were selling guns like they
were hot shrimps from a stall.
He misunderstood my warnings as a crazy joke.
He finally understood and made a deal
when it was time to crush his balls like nuts.
What an idiot.
But it turns out he had an interesting job.
He worked on intelligence for Bulgaria, Dutch.
This city is a comfortable place for folks like that, too.
Normally a guy like that is very useful, but...
playing with fire this time cost him.
What he offered us for the sake
of his balls was this, Dutch.
Papers.
The hiking charts for a certain amusing little group.
The job they did right before us
has been on TV all damn morning.
The US Embassy!
That's a dangerous one.
Balls-boy's real job was with them.
The world's full of folks who want Uncle Sam to disappear.
I told one of those groups that they dropped something.
But before they heard what it'd cost them, they told me to
"get the hell out of here before your ass becomes roast."
And this is how I answered.
"All right, then I'll go elsewhere."
Thanks to that, my offices flew all the way to Jordan.
And, as predicted, my ass nearly
became a roast before I got here.
They're really no fun at all.
So, Dutch, this is the deal.
I want you to deliver this.
Five teams will leave Roanapur at the
same time, with different destinations.
There are five cases but only one bingo.
A feint.
As insurance, of course.
Your goal is the Filipino base on Basilan Island.
The time limit is two days.
Then my CIA contacts will leave Basilan.
Two days is too soon, Chan.
It's always too soon.
This morning's embassy bombing
was the beginning of a chain.
In two days the next schedule starts.
When they're done hiking there's
going to be a new president.
Uncle Sam came to me because their
embassy blew up like the Apollo.
A getaway driver we hired will
deliver it to the base when you land.
I'm counting on you, Dutch.
Did you bring our pay here?
And we're calculating expenses separately.
I know...
R
RP
RPG!
My, my. They sure are quick. They're already here.
Boss! Are you safe?!
Your information's off, Chan-san.
This job's cancelled.
Are you going to quit?
Then you're going to have to pay the repair bill for this.
I'll at least escort you to the boat.
But...
I haven't been on the field in a while.
Where's your emergency exit?
I'll lead the way, Chan.
Thanks.
Hand gre...
Don't panic, Two-Hands.
In this situation,
if you hesitate, you lose.
Chan's cleared the way. Let's go.
OK, let's go.
You're getting lax, boss.
Don't bark, Two-Hands.
You've got the nerves, but...
you don't see the big picture yet.
Not compared to you. I'll just stick with you.
That's good.
I'm sending a car. Get to the harbor with that.
Boy...
I'd like to do a job that doesn't
involve risking my life sometime.
Don't bitch, Dutch. We're about to do the hard part.
Hurry!
I'll leave it to you, Chan-san!
Such a pain in the ass.
When you get there don't forget the password.
The password is...
OK. I understand.
Our comrades have found the
delivery boys on the main road.
We can take care of them near Bankantan.
I wonder.
This job should have been over with
after the bombing of the Triad office.
I'm in no mood to judge the failures of our comrades.
You mocked the "simple gangsters."
Chan was a much smarter gangster than you thought.
"See the enemy you should respect,
not the enemy you despise."
The words of Mao Tse-tung. You should study it, Ibraha.
The lesson of a man who does not believe in God.
It's garbage.
But he was right.
Besides, I don't believe in God either.
You are my comrade, Takenaka.
More importantly.
Perhaps we should speed up the plan in America.
Impossible. The FBI has been watching.
If we move now, the plan will be wasted.
Out of the five routes they've taken,
the first one to discount is over land.
Flying is too risky.
That only leaves a sea route. Do you have proof?
It's intuition.
I will ask a comrade commander
in the Philippines for assistance.
The sea route... I guess I'll have to take care of it.
This is the final step in changing the world.
OK.
The sea is wide, and so big...
Did you hear the password?
"The Triad is super cool!"
Boss Chan can handle himself and has
great style, but when it comes to jokes...
Well, nobody's perfect.
You found it?
A torpedo boat?
Chan's got some interesting friends.
You've determined their path too?
That's perfect.
That's just as we predicted.
Now I don't have to change my flight route.
I'm about to switch planes.
Just don't do anything until I arrive.
We need to confirm a few things.
Later.
Are you from Japan too?
Thanks.
How did you know?
The way you held your hand when you asked me.
We're on a family trip to Seb Island.
It's a bit far from Manilla if you're with your family.
Well...
Hmm, wait a sec.
Have we met somewhere before?
I feel like this isn't the first time we've met.
I'm sure you do.
Ken-san is a Japanese comedian
Ken-san.
People always say I look like him.
Well, goodbye.
Sorry for being awkward.
Bye.
You sure are aloof.
If you've seen me somewhere,
it's at the police station.
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Takenaka Masahiro
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
Evading the police
Use of explosives
Murder
We've got them, Dutch.
The noisy little fly.
OK.
Rock, bring me the Remington, and the Hydra API for ammo.
We've taken out the enemy's
eyes, but that might not be all.
Rock, we'll be bait and charge towards Basilan.
I want you and Revy to get off at Zamboanga
and use the Zodiac to get to Basilan.
Got it.
Ibraha! I can't hear you!
Hurry and get down here!
Takenaka! Where are you?
Basilan?
Hey! Our diversion team is there!
Don't panic.
I'm at their camp.
The lighthouse's base is always the darkest.
We're waiting here for the first blow
among the local guerillas, but...
it's the same for them too.
The only place an American imperialist agent can come
and go is the anti-guerilla special operations camp.
It's right over the hill.
I can see Chan's next move. This is going to be fun.
This isn't a game, Takenaka!
This is the precursor to the plan!
Brother, this is an exchange of pawns.
Did you think there's something else in this world?
We're going to be the ones that take the next piece.
He sure is hard-headed.
What are you going to do if you don't have fun?
So, once we deliver the papers we'll meet you at the base.
Yea, I'll come get you when I lose the guys that are bitten on.
Guys who fight for a cause are so damn persistent.
Oh yeah.
I have a message from Mr. Chan.
When Rock comes back from the bathroom tell him, too.
Sorry for the wait.
The target is moving further north from Zamboanga coast.
So they passed Basilan.
Basilan is already behind us.
We believe they will be heading north from Negros.
We will continue pursuit.
Good job.
That's not happening. They're coming here.
To Basilan, there's no mistaking it.
This is such a dinky-ass place.
What time is it?
Nearly six.
We took more time than expected to find a place to land.
The village should be right ahead.
It sure is quiet here.
It's a human-less ghost village.
There's been martial law here for the last two years.
The police and the guerillas are shooting
lead at each other day and night.
The people here must have run away to a real city.
Did I keep you waiting?
You're from Lagoon, right? I heard that there were four of you.
And why should I answer that?
Hey now.
Just me and him and a briefcase. That's it.
I don't see your partner. Where's your guard?
He's running around looking for a bathroom.
He doesn't know the difference between beer and Volvic.
So let's cut to the chase.
The Triad is...
What about them?
This isn't a time for jokes.
If you fuck around I'll shoot you in the face.
Now, now, don't get hot.
It was just a little joke to break the ice.
The Triad is...
super cool, right?
His sense of humor is a little screwy.
You think so too?
I didn't think it was that bad for Mr. Chan.
Exactly, asshole.
I have a message from the boss for you.
"I am Taishanfujun."
You don't know the meaning?
It's the god of death and punishment
here to bring down judgement.
I don't know where you got the password,
but Boss Chan isn't an idiot or a fool.
He prepared a new password for shitheads like you.
You hopped into this parade with your ass hanging out.
What? Laugh.
This is where you laugh.
Laugh.
I guess I got a little carried away.
Getting handled like this by a little girl, pathetic.
Get back!
That idiot!
Rock, you idiot! You fucked up!
Gunfire's started.
Ah, I don't wanna.
Legarch!
It's a pain.
You relax too much before work.
I said not to.
I don't want to move until the gunfire dies down.
If she dies, no pay.
It's a pain.
No, work important.
Damn, there's no end to them.
That idiot shithead Rock!
Sister, lower your head.
Are you the getaway driver?!
Do I look like an attorney?
Later bitch.
Don't go after them.
The military's left their camp, fall back!
I heard that there were four of you from Mr. Chan.
Where's the other three?
Plans changed so it became two. Then one got captured.
Pathetic.
We're going straight to the base.
I want to finish this job and go home!
Where's their base?
North of village. Six miles. In the jungle yes, it is.
Don't go to the base. We'll take care of them first.
Wipe your own damn ass.
Or tell that to the cavalry, Mary Read.
Job is take you to base.
Get pay. No to all else.
My partner has the papers.
Get it? "Understand you yes?"
"Yes it is" lady.
Don't stain the seats, Shenhua.
If you're gonna do it, do it outside.
English not good because I am real Taiwanese.
Or is it not big deal if head separated from neck?
You don't get it.
Why do you think the boss hired you?
The papers.
If they aren't all together then it's us three idiots in this
car that's gonna have to do the twist in front of the boss.
Hey, you're here.
We've formed an alliance. This
camp is under our command.
Perfect.
Now... welcome to our demilitarized zone.
We saw what was inside the briefcase. It was empty.
I don't know.
And even if I did, I couldn't answer. You know that.
A straightforward answer.
At a time like this, you should at least crack a joke. Anyway.
We have time. We'll ask you slowly.
So.
Let's do this in Japanese, bro.
If you're going to get involved in this kind of
stuff, you need to be a little more careful.
You're Japanese, right?
Since when have you been doing this kind of job?
I guess I can't get to you.
You're going to keep quiet?
It won't hurt for similar people like us to be friendly to each other.
This is a problem.
Has the launderer's delivery boy arrived?
You're late, Langley!