It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demon.
But a single mage saved them all.
His name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He would eventually be called the first
Wizard King, and he became a legend.
The Final Attack
What was that shaking just now?
Did something happen up above?
What in the world are these
creepy crawly things, anyway?
If not for Gueldre's transparency magic,
we would've been done for immediately.
Not to mention, there are
ridiculously powerful
mages lurking everywhere around here.
I knew I shouldn't have come here.
There's always some danger
in anything you do.
But we need to get out of here
before I run out of mana.
Where's the exit?
Licht's ultimate spell...
Those things just couldn't
bear it any longer.
How crazy strong is that spell, anyway?
It pretty much saved our asses, though.
But we ended up way further down.
Thanks for fixing my arm, Prickly Queen.
Now we're even.
I can probably manage another Dimension Slash.
I can feel the evil mana and
ki even this far away...
So you're telling me that
insane attack wasn't enough?
I wanna hurry up and get back there,
but jumping in without
a plan isn't a great idea.
I'm not sure why, but my darkness
magic works against that devil.
If I can get the chance to
land a final blow on him...
I think the only other one who stands a chance
is our lively little kid.
The sword that boy is using... That's Licht's.
After Licht's grimoire became
a five-leaf grimoire that
could be used by devils,
it apparently acquired anti-magic
from a different devil.
Crap... There's too much power!
You clearly don't have control.
He just shattered a spear
from the other world.
Its effects can trap light magic and
warp space, and it even ignored that!
I don't know what devil this power belongs to,
but you need to learn your
place in the pecking order!
Word Soul Magic...
"Voizuiinemidoren..."
"Futogerueofu..."
"Snoittnedeidoog."
Thank you for—
First Wizard King!
Light Magic: Light Swords of Conviction!
Wind Magic: Tornado Fang!
Damn it!
As I thought, our magic has no
effect against the devil's magic.
Even though we also have four-leaf
magic, he's on another level.
The only thing I can do right now...
I should be able to do it...
This time, not to hurt others...
but to protect!
Demon Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction!
Yes!
You may be rotten now, but you're
still an elf chosen by the four-leaf.
Not bad at all,
though it's all for naught, of course.
I should be able to do... what everyone
else is doing with their magic!
So should I make it take
shape... and hold it there?
Are you all right, Your Highness?
Ow, ow, ow...
Anti-magic sure is something!
I don't think I'll be able
to use magic for a while.
So you're not all right, then.
There's little chance it'll work...
But I'll use my sealing magic to bind it,
and then I'll try to control it.
No.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Why are you taking forever
over there, Asta?
If you can't even use your
power to its full extent,
then you've still got a long way to go...
before you can become the Wizard King!
Yu...no?
He used the wind to condense the dregs of
our magic, which had returned to the air,
and managed to create a sword from it
that should work on the devil's spells.
And that's since our battle started.
His growth is incredibly fast!
Wind Spirit Creation Magic:
Spirit of Zephyr.
Hey, I was just about to get it, okay?!
See? You can do it if you try.
Yeah. Because...
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
Anti-Magic Demon-Slayer Sword:
Black Divider!
Unbelievable!
How are they able to evolve so fast?
A wind attribute and sword magic?
I see. So he's...
But who's the boy using the five-leaf grimoire?
A foolish little boy who was born without
any magic and doesn't know his place.
He worked harder than anyone in this
kingdom and never knew when to give up.
He truly is a foolish boy.
Did you see that, Yuno, you jerk?!
I managed to give it shape, but I doubt
I'm gonna last long at all!
Make sure you last until we cut him down, Asta!
I'll finish this in an instant!
I'll admit, you're rather lively.
But do you think you'll be able
to reach me at that speed?
He became even faster...
because of the wind magic.
The anti-magic pursued the wind, and the
wind magic raced through the void.
What a magnificent combination!
They... did it?
You trash...
How dare you?
Really, how dare you?
You filthy maggot with no magic...
I'm done with this.
Despair and resistance are
merely my playthings.
It's over. I'll kill you all.
This can't be...
You're nothing more than a ripple in a pond.
My powers...
I pierced his heart... but it just
appeared somewhere else?
"Voizuiinemidoren."
"Futogerueofu."
"Snoittnedeidoog."
I'll make sure to exterminate
every single last one of you.
That devil's actually getting serious.
At this rate, he's going
to swallow up everything!
Come on, you can't be serious!
We can't even get close to this thing now.
This is proving difficult even for
those of us who can stand against him.
At this rate, everyone down below...
Patry...
Sorry, but I'll need you to
hold the perimeter for a bit.
We cannot let the people of the present die.
They are the mages who carry the future
of the Clover Kingdom, after all.
You're nothing more than a lump
of meat! Foolish and useless!
Goodbye.
I'll kill all of you.
I'll slaughter all of you.
Humanity is finished.
Bring down the curtain.
Who said you get to end this, you dark,
creepy freak covered in mouths?!
You still good to go, Yuno?
That's my line, Asta!
Let's shut that guy up!
You're no better than vomit.
You just swarm grossly in front of me.
And yet you
had the nerve to bite me.
Die.
You'll have to pay with your deaths.
No other way.
You're just maggots hiding under a rock.
I'll twist off your arms and legs.
I'll rot your mana and lives, then kill you.
Die!
Because the anti-magic is so effective on him...
That's why he avoided that attack to his heart
and why that damage has gotten him so furious.
If we can get Asta's sword to
actually pierce his heart...
Damn it! There's no end to this!
Crap! My body's nearing its limit...
The anti-magic boy,
and the wind-magic boy he's fighting
alongside, who he trusts so much...
We must leave this in their hands.
We'll go save their friends.
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
It's almost time...
Soon I'll be able to sever
her healing magic, too!
Wait a sec!
We really shouldn't be fighting here right now!
Nozel! Mimosa!
This place is about to be
flooded with inhuman magic!
Evacuate immediately, all of you!
Mana Zone: Calidos Brachium Barrage!
Lady Mereoleona, too?
To think magic like this even existed...
The world certainly is vast!
La! What's all this yucky-looking stuff?!
It's getting even more intense!
Not good!
It's going to swallow me up!
The Demon-Dweller Sword bestows
and stores up magic for those who have
bonds with each other, and connects them.
Since my magic has a chance against the devil,
we'll send it through the
sword to everyone else.
Combo Spell: Demon-Dweller Sword
~ Protecting Light!
What is this?
This is Licht and your prince's magic.
Prince?
My connection with Licht shows
me what's going on up above.
Looks like the prince got
to have a touching reunion.
He's making me jealous.
As long as my magic lasts, I won't
let a single one of them die!
Demon Light Creation Magic:
Light Whip of Judgment!
The bond between them...
I won't doubt it this time!
As long as we have this light,
we can concentrate on attacking!
Hey, what's with that light? No fair, Yuno!
You just need to concentrate on finishing
the devil, you one-and-done moron.
I know that, you multi-talented,
handsome jerk!
It's so much fun when you die pathetically.
Your sword still hasn't reached me.
It's utterly useless.
Already...
Right here...
Just like this...
Finally...
It's over.
You're finished.
Again, keep your distance, human.
Hey, you still owe me from earlier. Let me in.
By the way, you said you can see
what's going on above, right?
I was just thinking that having nothing
but mana detection and ki
to rely on is really unsafe.
Tell me what that creepy thing
is doing, Prickly Queen.
You can't possibly be... From here?
I don't like how you asked,
but I'll at least add momentum to your strike.
Don't you dare miss!
Yeah.
We'll do an all-out attack...
and finish this!
At first, I only got close to
you so that I could use you.
You coincidentally managed to obtain
the five-leaf grimoire that kept magic away.
A boy with no magic...
But the longer I stayed with you,
and the more I saw you fight,
the more I wanted to believe in you.
I wanted to bet on you!
Please...
Win this, Asta!
This light... I can feel my power welling forth.
Is Asta at his limit?
Asta, I'm gonna leave you
behind if you can't keep up!
Where do you think you're going, Yuno?!
You're just a human.
Yet you're using spirit power
and elven powers...
To fight my magic...
But you cannot pierce my heart with that wind.
That anti-magic brat
is merely letting himself
be pulled along, following that
wind magic. He's hopeless.
And he isn't even following properly.
They're nothing to worry about... hmm?
Where'd the anti-magic brat go?
He hid in the shadows of the severed magic!
He's in my blind spot, coming from
a different direction!
They're pulling each other in and speeding up!
"Sto—"
"Stop."
"Weaken!"
"Go back!"
"Hold back!"
"Stop!"
I reached my... limit?
Asta!
Too bad!
His... His concentration is astounding!
But it's still not possible.
Not from this distance!
You sure about this?
Making a foreigner like me a
Magic Knights Squad captain?
Don't worry. I'm sure you'll do fine.
I mean, I'm gonna do whatever I want.
I'm sure the higher-ups aren't gonna like this.
Just because my magic's a bit rare...
I know.
Because I've watched you all this time.
Yami...
I know you can do this.
Mana Zone...
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash ~ Equinox!
Equinox
Dark magic can interfere with the other world!
This ki...
It's... Captain Yami!
You maggots!
Sealing Recovery Magic...
Heavenly Prison: Faint Omen.
I've sealed his physical damage.
Now it's just a question of whether he
can draw out his anti-magic power.
Asta!
Die!
Perish!
Disappear!
You go ahead and do that!
You pieces of trash!
Asta...
You're going to be...
You're going to be the Wizard King, right?
Yeah!
Right here, right now...
I'll surpass my limits!
Asta... Did we do it?
This is exactly why you're my rival!
The Shadow Palace is starting to crumble?
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 120: "Dawn."
Page 120
Dawn
The battle ends, and a new morning comes!