The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently
aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
The Blue Rose's Confession
Doing this! Doing that!
There, there, good boys. Here's your food.
What are you doing?
And after I played with you guys...
Do you have to be so loud
this early in the morning, kid?
You're not even letting me
push one out in peace.
Hey, how long are you gonna
keep messing around? Let's go!
Where are we going?
Huh? Where the hell do you think?
To find out more about the devils.
We're going to start with the curse, weg.
We'll get some clues from that.
Right!
You come, too.
All right.
Royal Capital: Magic Knights Squad Hospital
I'm very sorry, Sol.
An elf stole my body...
and I couldn't protect all of you.
I'm a failure as a captain.
That's not true!
It wasn't your fault, Sis!
I was completely useless, too.
The Black Bulls' captain... As much
as I hate to admit it, he saved us.
Yami did?
I see...
Also, don't call me "Sis." Call me "Captain."
Sure thing, Sis.
More importantly, that guy...
I guess he's not so bad for a guy.
For a guy, at least.
I mean, he's still no match
for you, though, Sis.
Don't tell me all that wasn't a dream...
They're things that happened
when I was possessed?
Well done, human.
Y-Yami in my memories is so... close! And...
But I had fun fighting
by your side, Yami Sukehiro.
Well, look at you. Being all nice
and honest in the end, Charla.
I'm pretty sure I'm not as awkward
as the owner of this body.
I can't remember exactly, but I think
it was something like that.
Wait... Does that mean Yami
knows how I feel about him?
No, that can't be...
Sis...
Hey, Sis!
What is it, Sol?
Yo.
The Captain of the Black Bulls is here.
Yami?!
Yami!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you...
What do you mean? I came
to see how you were doing.
Here you go, Prickly Queen.
I-I-I do not currently have the
mental or emotional capacity
to be in the same room as Yami right now...
Sol... Chase him away
like you usually do, Sol!
Yeah... I mean, I guess he did save you,
so it wouldn't hurt to let
him stay for a little while.
Sol!
You all better?
Sis?
It's not like I can stay in bed forever.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What does my
face look like right now?!
Calm down, Charlotte...
You can do this, Charlotte.
Don't push yourself too hard.
You've always been the
stubborn, awkward type.
Awkward
Awkward...
You always cause so much trouble.
Trouble
Trouble...
But I'm a bit relieved now.
By the way, there's something
I wanted to ask you, Prickly Queen.
S-Something he wants to ask me?!
Wh-What... D-D-D-Don't tell me...
You said something earlier, remember?
You know...
Wha-Wha-Wha-Wha...
When you were under that spell...
S-Spell?
I want you to give me the details.
So that thing of yours...
I'm pretty sure it was...
A forbidden curse...
The heck?
Th-The Captain of the Blue Rose Knights?!
Was he able to ask about the curse? About weg?
Come on. Why so scared?
Let's just go. It'll be fine.
P-Please stop.
Oh, come on. The country's a
mess right now, so we gotta—
Not happening!
Thank you very much!
That was a close one!
Thank you!
Oh?
Burglar!
Thank you, miss—W-Wait!
There's a river over there!
I was just hoping you could tell
me about the forbidden magic...
Sis! Come back!
Now I've done it.
Why am I like this?
I wasn't able to be honest
with Yami yet again.
I'm sure he just thinks I'm a freak now...
I became strong to persevere over
the House of Roselei's curse.
Apparently, she raised her rank again.
That newbie from the
Blue Rose Knights is so powerful!
Not to mention beautiful!
Lady Charlotte, please marry me.
No, marry me!
But I couldn't trust men, who were all talk.
If you cannot defeat me,
you could never accept my curse.
And then, my curse went out of control.
The curse!
The curse upon the House
of Roselei has activated!
It's no use. We can't stop it! Ru—
It won't... stop...
At this rate, the town...
Curses! How pathetic... I'm so pathetic!
I'm so sorry... Mother and Father...
What the hell's the big idea, you jerk?
You flung the pasta soup
I was eating everywhere.
Yami Sukehiro? To think I'd let him see
me in such a disgraceful situation!
What a failure I am.
On missions, you're as cool as a cucumber
and always raring to go. So what gives?
I like tough girls.
But it probably wouldn't hurt to ask
someone for help once in a while.
Our Magic Knights Squads are full
of strong people you can rely on.
Yami saved me when all that was happening.
But still, there was a part of me
that didn't want to admit that,
and I continued fighting as the captain
of an all-women Magic Knights Squad.
I...
I'm...
Blue Rose Knights' Headquarters
What's up, Sis?
Captain...
What did you want to tell us?
As all of you know,
we, the Blue Rose Knights,
are female knights who pride ourselves
in achieving acts of valor on
our own, without the help of men.
Therefore...
I'm prepared to resign as
your captain after I say this.
I-I...
I like Yami!
No matter how hard I tried to
rid myself of these feelings...
No matter how much I tried to
forget him, it was no use!
I... I'm just...
I'm just hopelessly in love with that man!
Sis...
As I figured...
This is unforgivable.
I'm... a failure as a captain.
Oh my gosh!
We'll support you, Captain!
Huh?
They're totally Beauty and the Beast!
What a grand romance!
You're both captains, so you're
perfect for each other!
I actually have a boyfriend, too!
We've been secretly dating this whole time.
What?!
Me, too! It's been so hard to keep it secret.
Me, too!
Actually, me, too!
You should totally ask him out on a date!
A d-date?!
You've got this, Captain! I mean,
you could win any guy over!
Wha—
But before that, you have to
let him know you're interested!
I-Interested?!
You should tell him you love him!
I know! There's a perfect restaurant!
The night view there will
definitely set the mood!
You'll be fine! No man could ever hate you.
I'm sure he likes you, too!
Captain, you have a cool complexion...
And you're a summer!
So pink and pastel colors
would look best on you!
Wow, your skin is so beautiful!
Do you have a skin care routine? Oh, and...
You've got great romance luck!
I think a rose color would...
Tell him how you feel!
Tell him how I feel?!
H-Hey...
Tell him how you feel! Tell him how you feel!
Tell him how you feel!
I'm... going to tell Yami... how I feel...
Sis! W-Wait! Calm down!
I don't know what's going on, but it
looks like you're having a blast.
Sorry for butting in!
Wow, so this is the
Blue Rose Knights' headquarters!
It's really pretty!
The hell are you doing?
Of all the times for him to show up!
Go on, Captain! This is
your big, big, big chance!
Wh-What?
Go ask him out on a date!
What?!
You can do it!
H-Hey!
Y-Yami... Um, uh... you see...
Captain! I can't hear you at all!
How cute are you?!
Why'd you turn into a statue and
start muttering? Are you Gordon now?
I know how you feel.
Ba-dump!
I've known all along.
Ba-dump, ba-dump...
Your ki is unique and indescribable...
You...
really don't like being around me, do you?
Like, you can't stand me.
Huh?
But did you really have to scream your
lungs out and run away like that?
You're going to scar my delicate little heart.
We've known each other for years.
It wouldn't hurt just to hear me out, would it?
He's such an insanely oblivious, uncouth man!
She's doomed.
She won't even be able to
tell him how she feels!
Th-That's not...
I-I-I-It's no use! I can't get
the right words to come out!
A-At this rate, he's going
to get the wrong idea...
That's not true, Captain Yami!
I don't think she hates you.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Who the hell asked for your opinion,
Mr. Suspended Sentence?
Th-The way the Blue Rose captain
is acting... it reminds me of Noelle.
What?
So she doesn't hate you.
She just really trusts you, I think.
The more she trusts you, the harder
it is for her to tell you how she feels!
I just recently realized this myself.
So you just said yourself
that Noelle trusts you,
and you're not embarrassed?
Not one bit!
We're comrades who've come through
so many life-or-death situations together!
Seriously, Noelle just has a hard
time expressing how she really feels.
So, Captain Blue Rose, if you have
a hard time saying something,
just keep carrying on like you usually do!
You're comrades who've been through
life-or-death situations, after all!
Who the hell gave you permission to
touch Sis like that, you shrimp?!
Looks like we've both been blessed
with wonderful Magic Knights.
No, he's caused me
nothing but trouble, really.
Asta, was it?
I was informed of what happened.
I'm sorry for all of the trouble
we caused while we were possessed.
Nah, it wasn't your fault at all!
Y-Yami... Um... You wanted to talk
to me about something, right?
H-How about we have dinner?
Sure.
I have no idea what's going on, but finally...
Sis... If she ends up with that guy,
what am I supposed to do?
So... What did you want to talk about?
Well, you see...
Ba-dump, ba-dump...
I wanted to know...
...more about your rose curse.
What's wrong?
Thank goodness! Thank goodness
they didn't get together!
But I also sorta feel bad for Sis,
since her feelings didn't get across to him.
O-Oh... So that's what you wanted to talk about.
Was there something else?
Curse you for getting my hopes up!
You know. The Black Bulls have to
investigate the devils on
the Wizard King's orders.
That psycho scales judge guy is
just itching to execute the kid.
So I've gotta gather some clues,
being the kid's captain and all.
It all began
with a spell cast by a curse mage
who had a grudge against my family.
But that spell was unlike any other in
this kingdom and impossible to break.
Forbidden magic interferes with the
shape of your life and of the world.
The curse that activated when I was eighteen
changed the shape of my soul and
the quality of my magic itself.
It is extremely likely that this was
a forbidden curse that used
power from another world.
I knew it.
But I don't know much else about it.
I see.
I guess I wasn't much help.
But if you need to know
about forbidden curses...
There's someone in your own squad
who has been affected far more than I have.
In my squad?
So many close friends... I'm so happy.
So happy...
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Practice
P-Practice?
P-Practicing telling him how I feel about him?
This is so embarrassing. But if it's
to help let him know how I feel...
Ya...
Yami...
Your eyes are like jewels.
They're so clear and pure...
I love you!
I love you too, Prickly Queen.
I-Is that so? I see...
Whatcha doin', Sis?
S-Sis!
Curse you, Yami. I was hoping
you'd at least take the hint...
But I guess that's one of his charms.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 127: "Clues."
Page 127
Clues
One day, my thorns will prick
him right in the heart! Squee!