It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
A new dungeon was discovered on
the border of the Clover Kingdom.
Asta, Noelle, and Luck of the Black
Bulls were assigned to investigate it.
W-Wow!
Here it is, Asta.
This.
Where?
Hup.
The dungeon was filled with traps.
This is so much fun!
Isn't this exciting?
We're going to die if we stay with this guy.
Now, then...
I think I'm about to reach my limit.
I knew it.
There are others here.
The strongest looking one is...
Something important just came up.
So I'm leaving the dungeon
exploration to you guys!
Don't worry.
No matter what kind of traps might spring up,
I'll slice through them with my sword.
We're alone right now.
Something wrong?
It's nothing! Nothing at all!
Let's hurry.
A trap! Oh, no!
Noelle!
Asta and Noelle were in danger. And then...
Crap!
Such precise and powerful magic...
Who could it be?
Now...
I've repaid my debt,
Asta.
Yuno...
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
The Diamond Mage
Captain Vangeance!
What is it?
Sir, about the exploration
of the new dungeon...
Why did you send that new peasant
recruit on such an important mission?
Do you trust me?
Of course.
I, Alecdora Sandler, am ready to die for you.
In that case, I'd like you to trust
him, too. Because I trust him.
He's also a member of the Golden Dawn.
I'm sure he'll become an even
more powerful force for us.
Yes, sir.
Yes... We need him to get stronger.
So he's Yuno? And that's...
Yuno,
why did you bother saving them?
Our only mission is to explore this dungeon...
In other words, to quickly reach the
treasure chamber buried deep below.
We don't have any time
to waste on these fools.
Hey, Yuno. What's the deal
with this rude four-eyed dude?
He's my senior.
Four—
You're the rude one!
I'm a four... er, I'm a nobleman!
How dare you address me so casually?!
He's flustered all of a sudden.
Member of the Golden Dawn
Mimosa Vermillion
Good day, Noelle.
I don't think I've seen you since
the royal banquet last year.
You know her?
Yes... Somewhat.
I'm Noelle's cousin.
Huh...
So, you're here, too.
It just had to be her...
I've heard the Black Bulls are a very
barbaric squad. Have you been faring well?
And are you doing okay, Mimosa?
Huh?
I'm not sure someone as dense as you
can make it in the Golden Dawn.
Yes! Everyone is so kind.
Because of that, I've been able to
use my magic without hesitation.
If I remember correctly, you weren't
able to control your magic at all.
Have things improved since then?
She's as obliviously rude as ever.
She still pisses me off.
I-I've been working on it.
Oh, the three of us recently received
a star from the Wizard King himself
for another mission.
Hmph.
We just got a star, too!
You liars.
Newbies from the Black Bulls wouldn't
be awarded stars so easily.
We did get one!
We're at minus thirty now!
It's laughable that you've been
charged with this mission, too.
The Wizard King appointed
us to this mission himself!
Such a blatant lie.
I'm not lying!
Hmph.
He really is flustered.
Come to think of it, I heard
there'd be three of you, too.
Where's the other one?
Don't tell me they left you two and ran.
Or did they fall prey to one of the traps?
He didn't run away, nor did he
fall prey to any of the traps.
Then where is he?
Just a little more!
There's no way we can tell them he
ditched us and went off somewhere.
Nope.
Regardless, it's clear your lot consists
of filth that leaves new recruits behind.
The Black Bulls... How unsightly.
You're an embarrassment to the Magic Knights.
You've got some nerve, you jerk!
We're going to conquer this
dungeon first for the Black Bulls!
Just you wait, Gol... No, Goober?
No, uh... you guys with the
weird masked captain!
Goober? It's Golden!
And "weird mask"? You scum!
You dare mock our esteemed
Captain Vangeance?!
You're the ones with a weird captain!
What kind of freak runs around with all
those muscles bulging out of a tank top?!
What'd you say?!
He's manly and totally awesome!
How dare you talk to a noble like that?!
Not to mention your senior!
Well, excuse me! My bad!
You bastard!
Yeah, he's really flustered.
Very well, you fools!
We'll just have to show you the difference
between the top of the Magic Knights
and the bottom!
Mimosa!
Sure.
Plant Creation Magic: Magic Flower Guidepost.
Let's see... Ah, got it.
I've learned the basic layout of the dungeon.
Very well. Yuno!
Right.
He can carry all three of them so easily.
I hope you suffer.
Impressive as always, Yuno!
All right! Let's go, Noelle!
Hey!
Let's see which of us gets to
the treasure chamber first!
And what are we supposed to do?
Neither of us can use tracking spells!
We'll just have to check
every path very carefully!
I'm gonna do this!
Are you stupid? Oh, right, you are.
At this rate, we'll get lost before
we even find the treasure chamber!
Nero?
Take the next right.
Okay.
What was that fool's name? Asta? The nerve.
There's no way he can beat us.
What's with him, anyway? I couldn't
sense any magic from him.
You're right.
What was the captain
of the Black Bulls thinking,
taking someone like him—
Klaus.
It's best that you don't underestimate him.
They'll do well enough to get
out of this dungeon alive.
I'm just trying to conquer this dungeon as
fast as possible, for our country's sake.
I have a report for the Wizard King.
The two Magic Knight Squads,
the Golden Dawn and the Black Bulls,
have begun their investigations
of the dungeon.
We have also confirmed that a military mage
squad from the Diamond Kingdom is there.
Our neighbor, the Diamond Kingdom...
They've been trying to expand
their borders lately.
Clover
Kingdom
Dungeon
Diamond
Kingdom
They're an aggressive kingdom.
There'll be trouble if we let
them steal the ancient magic
that might be in the dungeon.
Who's in charge of this
invasion from Diamond?
Yes, sir. The one leading the
enemy squad is Lotus of the Abyss.
Lotus?!
Ah... I've met him on the battlefield before.
He was pretty strong!
The magic he used was really interesting.
Sir, should you sound so amused right now?
Shouldn't you be more concerned?
Don't worry, it's fine. I hear Yami's
sent an interesting one on this mission.
But...
Lotus is strong, but our
kids are strong, too.
Huh?
You're so weak.
But I'm sure you're different.
Well, this isn't good.
Nothing good comes of
raising hurdles too high.
Enthusiastic young power...
Terrifying, really.
Lotus of the Abyss
You took my subordinates out in an instant.
You're pretty strong.
Well, they are just subordinates.
But if you're their boss and you're
strong, there's no problem.
So you fight wrapped in
your own lightning magic.
Not only is that practical,
but you seem pretty powerful.
And you're fast.
You're making the most
of your youthful strength.
You've got this old man shaking in his boots.
What kind of magic do you fight with?
You seem rather enthusiastic.
You Clover people are also after this
dungeon's treasure chamber, aren't you?
Come on, let's fight!
Good grief.
Actually, I'm pretty sure
we don't have to fight.
Let's just compete nonviolently!
Yeah, great idea. Bye!
Nope!
You sure are fast.
He dodged me?
Smoke?
Goodness, that was scary.
I can see why the citizens of
the Clover Kingdom would be mad.
I mean, we've been trying
to invade here and there.
I apologize for all the trouble the
Diamond Kingdom's been causing you.
But you see, our kingdom's running out
of resources, so we have it rough, too.
If we want to survive,
we don't really have a choice.
Living can be so hard.
You see, I have three daughters...
Oh, is that so?!
Whatever! I don't care as long
as I get to fight strong people.
Looks like I've caught the
eye of some real trouble.
This old man might just cry.
What is this place?
The gravity's all messed up!
Are you sure we're going the right way?
Hey, Nero!
Don't fall asleep!
Hey, treasure!
Yeah, that's definitely not treasure.
Come on, Stupidsta! That has to be a trap!
All right! I got it!
Hey, stop that!
I wonder what's inside!
I told you to stop! What are you
going to do if it's a trap?
Open!
Wh-Why did you have to
show me that, Shrimpsta?!
It's not my faul—
You're so full of life.
Stop dodging, and let's fight!
Please? Come on!
Oh, now I remember. The Black Bulls.
I've fought with your captain before.
He was pretty hot-headed, too.
What? You know the captain?
How could I forget?
He gave me this lovely scar.
I pissed my pants and ran.
Goodness, that was scary.
He had a very unusual fighting style.
He was the only younger opponent
I've had that I couldn't defeat.
That makes you even more worth figh—
Wh-Whoa, there...
Oh?
What's the matter?
It's... nothing!
So slow!
Little by little, fall right into the abyss.
What is this? Magic? But I don't
remember getting hit by his magic...
You see, this whole room
is enveloped in my magic.
Very thin smoke that you can't really see.
It's called Weakening Smoke Magic: Garden
of Plundering Smoke, if you were wondering.
My body's not listening to me.
A spell that lowers physical
abilities? When did he...
I had a feeling you'd block it
if it were a visible attack.
I lowered my magical
ability as much as I could
so I could use this without you noticing...
While you were fighting my subordinates.
They didn't go out in vain.
They sacrificed themselves
so I could use this spell.
It's very important, isn't it?
Teamwork.
We're almost there. Once we
get through this tunnel...
How amazing!
That's all there is to dungeons?
That wasn't very difficult.
I wonder how you get in.
It appears the Black Bulls aren't here yet.
Of course not. There's no way they'd beat us.
Indeed.
Mimosa!
It ripped through her
magic-shielding cloak...
She's an expert at sensing mana,
but she didn't notice?
You're alive, aren't you?
That wasn't a trap spell...
What is this magic?
Who are you?!
Who stands in my way?
Move.
Friends you can trust are
worth their weight in gold.
Sorry, but stay there a while and get weaker.
Win...
Keep winning, Luck!
Wait.
It's been a while
since things actually got interesting.
More... More!
Let's fight some more!
I'd rather not pluck a bud
that's still so young...
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
A Lotus Flower
That Doesn't Bloom
Is Just a Lotus
A Lotus Flower That Doesn't
Bloom Is Just a Lotus.
You see, I have three daughters...
"When I get older,
I'm going to marry you, Daddy!"
And all three of them fight over me.
But once they hit puberty...
"Get away from me!"
"Don't mix my laundry with yours!"
I'm sure they'll say things like that.
And my wife was so nice when
we first met, but now...
This is really annoying, so I think I'm
ready to fall into the abyss now.
We're not done yet. It's finally getting fun.
More! Let's play more!
Let's kill each other! Please, Mister?
Black Clover, Page 16: "Friends."
Page 16
Friends
Not giving up is my magic.