It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
So you two finally showed up,
but why the hell are you all
shiny and attacking our comrades?
Marx! Old Man Owen!
Yami was attacked by Marx and Owen,
who had been reincarnated as elves.
Memory Magic: Torment Canceller!
Dark Cloaked Lightless Blunt Slash!
He managed to incapacitate
them both, but...
Red roses?
Charlotte Roselei, who had also
been reincarnated as an elf,
appeared before Yami.
I don't know who you are, but you
seem quite skilled for a human.
Overwhelming Disadvantage
Okay...
That should take care of that.
The Black Bulls' captain seemed
pretty protective of it.
I wonder what's inside.
Dark Magic...
Briar Magic...
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
Crimson Vine Spear!
Sis!
Our attacks just now...
My magical power definitely
overpowered his.
And yet his spell managed
to cut through mine,
softening the blow,
which protected the town.
Though it only damaged my arm
guard, he managed to reach me.
Regardless of whose magic was stronger,
he turned the tide of the battle.
So there are humans who have managed
to master skills such as that one?
If that were not the case, those two
wouldn't have been defeated, either.
It appears as though we've
underestimated the humans.
I used more magic than I intended.
I should retreat for now.
I'll wait for Licht and the others to arrive
and take every precaution
necessary before proceeding.
Sis!
What happened to the Black Bulls' captain?
D-Don't tell me that Sis defeated
the Black Bulls' captain...
Come back here, you jackass!
You didn't finish me off yet, you bitch!
Watch what you're doing!
I thought I was gonna die!
Where the hell'd she go?!
He's alive. I mean, I'm glad he's alive, but...
I'm gonna slap you back to your senses,
Spiny Prickly Queen,
a.k.a. Prickly Queen for short!
Hey, rowdy girl!
Rowdy girl?
What are you doing back here?
Where's the thing I gave you?
I hid it somewhere safe.
You'd better have!
I'm trusting you, you jerk!
A-And you'd better take care of my sis!
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
Right now, I can't save Sis.
I'm trusting you!
Yeah, you do that.
So what are you going to do?
I'm trying to figure that out right now.
Actually...
Rowdy girl! You go save the citizens!
I'm sure there are other Magic Knights around,
so save all the people you can!
Yes, sir!
And as for me...
What has happened?
What is this overwhelming magical
power I feel coming from outside?
And the commotion was great enough to
break open this magically sealed prison.
Former Captain of the Purple Orcas
Gueldre Poizot
Whatever this may be,
it's the chance of a lifetime!
I'm going to use this chance to escape.
Well, well, look who it is.
If it isn't the former captain of
the Purple Orcas, the great Gueldre.
Well, well... I never thought
I'd see your face again,
Revchi of Chain Magic.
Revchi Salik
I do beg your pardon, but I'm in quite a hurry.
We'll have to catch up some other time.
That may be convenient for you,
but it's definitely not for me.
Because two years ago, you did this
number to my face during a mission,
blamed the mission going wrong on me,
then kicked me out of the Purple Orcas!
You brought that upon yourself.
Everyone in the squad hated you.
Not a single person took your side.
I believe that goes for you, too.
Isn't that why the great former
captain of the Purple Orcas
was trapped down here?
This has nothing to do with a pathetic loser who avoided dangerous missions
out of fear for his life,
who never aimed for the top,
and who kept getting outdone by his juniors.
Pretty pathetic for Mister Transparency Magic,
who's immune to all attacks.
Your chain magic was able to
seal any mage's magical power,
so my heart bleeds for you.
That's right! I'm invincible!
If it hadn't been for that ridiculous
brat and his anti-magic...
Hm?
You, too?
The same thing happened to you?
I don't even need my chains
to touch him. I can tell.
His magical power is off the charts!
Humans located.
There are guys like him wreaking havoc outside?
So the commotion outside is
the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Looks like I might've
aided some real monsters.
All humans are to be killed on sight.
Wait! I'm not your enemy!
Depending on the circumstances,
I don't mind helping you out!
Let me speak with your leader.
We will never be tricked
by you humans ever again.
It doesn't matter who you are.
All humans shall be slain.
It appears we have no choice
here, Mister Revchi.
This sucks, but you're right, Gueldre.
Transparency Magic: Invincible Seeker
plus Invisible Traveling Companion.
They disappeared?
Impossible... Even their
magic disappeared?
In that case, I'll just have
to destroy this whole area!
Chain Creation Magic:
Magic-Binding Iron Chain Formation!
My magic has been sealed?
But my magical powers were
far superior to theirs.
What in the world is their magic?
You can pose no problem once we've caught you.
Is this my ticket out of obscurity?
Yes... My legend won't end here.
Come, let us retake our greatness,
Mister Revchi.
Indeed, Gueldre.
Luck? Ben?
Such menacing magic...
It's the same as Vetto and the others.
Why is that magic coming from you two?
Noelle's right. What's mixed in
with their magic seems to be...
the same as the one from
the House of Vaude.
A tremendously menacing magic...
It appears we've made it back.
Let me do this.
You sure have a lot of energy,
for one who just awakened.
It's because I just awakened. I have more
energy than I know what to do with.
This is in the way.
W-Wait, Luck. What are you talking about?
I'm sure they won't amount
to much as opponents,
since they're human.
Whoopsie. It's been so long, I missed.
Let's try that again.
Cherry Blossom Magic:
Magic Cherry Blossom Storm of Petals.
I'm not sure what happened,
but it appears those two
aren't who they used to be.
Beautifully prepare for combat, Noelle!
B-But Luck is one of the Black Bulls...
He's my friend...
Noelle!
Aw, I can't see.
I won't be able to aim like this.
Then I'll have to...
get up close and personal.
His magic is swelling...
He's coming! Defend!
Luck... Why? Why?!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
Were they brainwashed? No, the very
nature of their magic has changed!
Luck's magical power is on a completely
different level than usual!
That feel of your magic a
second ago... Are you royals?
What if I were to tell you that my
beautiful self is indeed royalty?
That just gives me even
more reason to kill you.
Come on, you can't be serious.
This guy was already a monster,
and now he's even worse.
Maybe it's because I'm a liar myself,
but I've always been able to
tell when someone is lying.
Anti-magic shrimp...
What you said earlier...
A free kingdom
where everyone can acknowledge
each other and smile...
That's the kind of kingdom I want to create
when I become the Wizard King.
You were actually serious about that.
I hate to admit it,
but it moved my heart a bit.
The same thing happened back then...
We can come to understand each other.
He wasn't lying, either.
That's why I believed him.
But because I believed him, that happened.
That's why I'll never trust them again.
I'm going to kill you so I can
get over any hesitation.
Copy Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction!
Copy Dark Magic: Lightless Slash!
He's casting spells with different
attributes at the same time?!
Mana Zone: Calidos Brachium Barrage!
Do you see now, you fool?
No matter how much you want to understand,
that's not an option for them!
They're trying to kill us based
on feelings they can't negotiate.
In that case, I'm going to win
and create a path to
understanding each other!
That path has long been closed.
Then I'll just open it up again!
Very well, you fool.
You should probably hurry up, though.
Otherwise, I'm going to defeat him.
Yes, ma'am!
Calidos Brachium!
That spell of hers is a trap
and hold move that I won't
be able to break free from if she hits me.
Which means...
I'm not letting you hit me again!
A combination of spatial
and light magic...
He's using light magic to speed up even faster.
When you can use it with something else,
Li'l Val's magic is awesome.
Though I'm pretty sure he's dead by now.
Copy Spatial Magic: Myriad Black!
Copy Light Magic: Sky-Rending Flash!
Seriously, how the hell are
we supposed to deal with him?
Oh?
Rill...?
Oh, hey, it's Raia. Heya, how've you been?
Hey, Lira. I see you're as crazy as ever.
And I see that your face
is as droll as ever, Raia.
Shut it.
Raia, Raia, Raia!
Stop it! You're so annoying!
I'm so happy to see you!
Come on!
Hey! What are you doing, Rill?!
My magic has a stylish name now!
It's called picture magic.
Oh?
He's a blockhead who's determined to kill us!
What's his problem? He's so loud.
We're in the middle of fighting him right
now! When'd you get all buddy-buddy?!
Who are you?
Huh? Wha... Rill?
Rill? My name is Lira.
Huh?! What are you talking about?
The Captain of the Aqua Deer...
That huge mana of his is even bigger,
and now he feels like that copy bastard.
The way that space-gouging guy,
the Golden Dawn's vice captain, felt...
Was that a sign that this was coming?
An enemy spell... Was it that light?
From the feel of their magic,
this isn't a form of brainwashing.
He apparently doesn't
recognize the brat, either.
Does that mean someone
different is inside?
I'm a fellow Magic Knight
and your friend, Asta!
I'm not gonna let you say that you
forgot someone this loud, you jerk!
Jeez, you're so persistent and loud.
I don't have any human friends.
I'll just have to shut you up with my
Picture Magic: Four-Headed Lindworm.
He's basically being controlled
by the enemy's magic.
Go smack him with your anti-magic!
G-Got it!
Sorry, but your magic won't
be able to reach us anymore!
Oh, I don't know about that.
It's not like I was just watching two
monsters duke it out this whole time.
Ash Trap Spell: Total Activation!
Ah, so you secretly planted some trap magic.
But paralysis on this level
does next to nothing to us.
Whoa, I can't see!
But our mana detection is on point,
so we're perfectly fine!
Too bad, because what's heading your way
is a monster with no magic.
He's circulating anti-magic
throughout his body?
Wake up, Rill!
I only grazed him!
But I did hit him. That should break the spe—
Jeez, that hurt. What'd you do that for?
He's still not normal?
Tch. Guess anti-magic didn't work, either.
This isn't a simple little spell.
It's a reincarnation spell that brings the
souls of elves to dwell in human bodies.
A reincarnation spell?
The spell that summons the souls is complete.
These bodies belong to us now.
Reincarnation? Elves?
You can't be serious! Change Rill back to nor—
Them, too?
This is some kind of joke, right?
All these bastards' magical
power is off the charts now.
How are we supposed to win against them?
Hey, we're retreating.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
We can't just leave everyone!
Not yet! We can't leave yet!
You dumbass.
There's no way to save them right now,
so we're retreating to figure that out!
You stupid little shit.
I guess you're right,
you cool masked jerk!
Besides, we both know that you can't
kill them. They're your comrades.
Neither can you.
Anyway, do you really think
you can get away from us?
Okay, kiddos.
You can head home first,
you fools.
Captain Mereo—
What?
You're going to stay behind and try to
stall all of us so those two can escape?
Well, aren't you nice to
your friends, Miss Royalty?
You seem to have the wrong idea.
Those kiddos would've just been in my way.
Stall you? Don't make me laugh.
I intend to kill all of you!
Crimson Lion Kings, let the
flames within you rage!
No matter how dire the situation
may be, never give up!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 98: "The Sleeping Lion."
Page 98
The Sleeping Lion
How long do you plan on sleeping,
my foolish brother?!