It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demon.
But a single mage saved them all.
His name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He would eventually be called the first
Wizard King, and he became a legend.
Asta, I'm gonna leave you
behind if you can't keep up!
Where do you think you're going, Yuno?!
You're just a human.
Yet you're using spirit power
and elven powers...
To fight my magic...
Mana Zone...
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash ~ Equinox!
Equinox
Dark magic can interfere with the other world!
Right here, right now...
I'll surpass my limits!
Dawn
Impossible...
This can't be...Impossible!
Inconceivable... I...
Hey there, chief.
Who...
Who are you?
Like you need to know that.
It doesn't matter how
strong or amazing you are.
You've lost, and you're about to disappear.
See ya, loser.
We... won...
Thank you.
The devil's magic... disappeared?
Did they actually defeat him?
Looks like someone else finished
him off before I could, but...
Well done, human.
The name's Yami Sukehiro,
Prickly Queen 2.0.
The name's Charla, you heathen.
This is...
The devil's magic hasn't completely disappeared,
and continues to devour this area.
The Shadow Palace is starting to crumble!
We have to hurry up and get out of here!
But everyone's still...
Not good... My body's about to reach its limit.
The light is dimming...
My body feels all creepy-crawly!
My connection to Licht is telling me...
The only way out is on the top floor!
Hurry!
We've got no way up there.
Well, this sucks. At this rate...
That ki...
Lumiere?
The light is... disappearing...
La?!
The light is...
Guys!
Asta!
Noelle! I'm glad you're all okay!
Why are you clinging to me, Stupidsta?!
Get off of me!
What?!
Both I and the one I believed in
were nothing but pitiful sinners.
I'm going to atone for my sins.
And this is the first step.
You guys!
Don't you get the wrong idea.
I've never been wrong.
And you haven't done anything here, either!
Shut the hell up! I do what I want!
There's still something that I have to do.
Man, thank goodness there was a
boneless ham that just happened to pass by.
Even if you go invisible with your magic,
your ki makes you totally obvious.
Don't even think you can
get away, you ham bastard.
Captain Yami! And the Captain
of the Blue Rose Knights!
And...
The former Captain of the Purple Orcas?!
How dare you treat me like
this when I've been weakened?
And you're... that bastard that stole
my grimoire, like, who knows when?!
The name's Revchi.
What the heck are you two doing here?!
What are you doing here
when you have no magic?!
Wow... So many humans with so
many different kinds of magic!
Looks like the Clover
Kingdom is in good hands.
Anyway, we gotta get the heck outta here!
La! Yuno! I'm never letting
you go ever again!
Uh, get your mitts off of
him right now, Domehead!
Huh? I guess you returned
to normal, Miz Charmy.
You turned into this tall,
slim, older-looking lady.
Not to mention, you were super awesome!
La? What are you talking about?
I'm always the sexy older girl.
What?
Huh? Was that a dream?
Or rather, what's Charmy doing here anyway?
I'll appear anywhere there's
delicious noms and Yuno!
Hey, woman! Let me slash you later!
What the heck is wrong with
this guy? He's creepy!
You two... It's a bit early for idle chatter.
It's not like everything is over.
We have to stop all the elves
destroying the kingdom.
They're still being taken
over by their hatred,
and fighting without souls.
How in the world are we going
to deal with that many of them?
Let's just knock them all out.
Yeah, she's more dangerous
than all of us put together.
Damn it!
I'm not gonna be able to get
to everyone with just one sword.
Not to mention, I can't use my
powers that much right now.
With Licht here, there's a way.
With the world tree magic
that belongs to William,
who's currently asleep inside of me,
we can gather the magic and life force
from people all over the kingdom.
But for that, we'll need his grimoire.
Take this.
That's William's... Thank you, Valtos.
It doesn't matter who you are.
You're still the one who saved me that day.
Wait, are you saying...
Yes. Asta, use your Demon-Destroyer Sword
to undo my reincarnation.
You sure about this?
This has always been my second life.
I may have some regrets, but no fear.
If I'm just going to disappear after this,
I almost think that's not enough for atonement.
Patry...
I'm gonna head out first.
I'm sorry, Licht. You'll have
to take care of the rest.
I will.
In the end, I got to fight alongside
Licht and everyone else.
That made me really happy.
Captain Vangeance...
Patry...
The lonely soul that has been
with me ever since I was little.
It appears that your rage and
suffering have come to an end.
But it's not over yet.
This time, it's my turn.
This curse that was carved
upon my face without reason...
Because of this curse, I'd been
discriminated against and hated, and so...
The warped feelings he felt towards
the kingdom and the suffering he felt
were undoubtedly real to me.
This battle came about because
I was weak and could not believe in
Master Julius or the future
I should've protected.
That being the case,
I need to be the one who
brings this battle to an end.
I need to connect to everyone's
souls and tell them the truth.
We're going to lure the connected
souls to the world tree
and tie them all together.
Combo Spell: Demon-Dweller
Sword Spirit Light Tree.
Anti-magic boy, use the
Demon-Destroyer Sword on this tree.
The sword's power is reaching
all of the elves.
That's... The magic of the
Captain of the Golden Dawn.
How beautiful...
Did they save the kingdom?
Figured as much.
Looks like the three of us
won't be able to go with you.
Our souls are bound to these bodies
after our second reincarnation,
so our souls don't belong to
our original bodies anymore.
I see. That makes things a little lonely.
I wanted to talk to you about this long
journey filled with pain and hatred.
But there might be a good reason for this.
Please continue to live in
this world for our sakes, too.
Licht...
See you later.
Guess we're passing each other by again.
Like I have a choice if this
is your request, Licht.
It'll be a pain, but I'll just have to
live this life to the fullest, I guess.
I regret not seeing my younger brother again,
but I had fun fighting
by your side, Yami Sukehiro.
Well, look at you. Being all nice
and honest in the end, Charla.
I'm pretty sure I'm not as awkward
as the owner of this body.
I'm gonna go on ahead, Lumiere.
I've kept Tetia waiting all this time.
Yeah.
I'm glad we got to see a glimpse of the
ideal future that we'd hoped for.
Yeah.
The one that's in my body...
Is he your...
Thanks to you, it felt like I
got to fight alongside my son.
Thank you, the current owner
of the four-leaf grimoire.
May luck be with you.
This grimoire is yours.
That grimoire belongs to you now.
Please let it accompany you on your journey.
Thank you...
Mages of the present Clover Kingdom.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on a damn second.
Wraith Magic: Soul Abductor.
I can only use this spell on someone
who's been with me a long time.
Ironically, you qualify.
The body that contained Licht's
soul has magic in it again?
But this magic is...
Patry?!
Is this... reincarnation?
No... reanimation?
That body was a copy of yours
that Sally made, anyway.
I'm sure you'll feel right at home in it.
Hey, what the heck are you doing?!
Shut up, shut up! I... I...
I don't really get it either, damn it!
Anyway, Licht... No, Patry, was it?
I'm not gonna let you just disappear
and live happily ever after!
I'm never gonna forgive you!
You get to keep thinking about all
those humans you trampled... including me!
Uh... I'm pretty sure that's gonna
come back to bite you in the butt.
Shut up!
Rades... Should I thank you?
You've given me the opportunity to atone.
Shut up! I'm gonna come for your head!
I won't let you die easily.
Go on and spend your life trembling in fear!
Let's go, Valtos!
For crying out loud...
So in the end, you didn't even
get to go back with Licht.
You're such a pain in the ass.
Talk about just deserts.
Raia...
To think the day would come where
I could actually touch you.
William...
My closest friend, who shares my sin.
There was so much that I wanted
to tell you, and yet...
More importantly, there's someone
I need to apologize to right now,
even though he may not forgive me.
I know that this is a
selfish request. I'm sorry, Yami.
But please take me to Master Julius.
Right.
The Wizard King...
The long battle is finally over.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Everything's been
hurting this whole... Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Are you all right, Asta?
That's what you get for being
reckless all the time. Deal with it.
I cannot thank all of you enough.
The devil's spell that had been cast
in my time has finally been lifted.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! When I realized,
I was just—ow, ow, ow, ow!
By the power of another devil, oddly enough.
It's been a while since
the seal has been broken,
and you're just now feeling the pain?
That's actually pretty impressive.
Asta, who are these people?
Is that person made of stone?
He looks just like the statue
of the first Wizard King.
Oh, but his eye is...
Who is he? That's the actual first Wizard King.
What?!
You were awakened by magic, right?
I'll be an amazing Wizard King
just like you someday!
And you're Nero, right?
Huh? What are you talking about,
Asta? How hard did you hit your he—
I am.
What?!
You're...
I always thought you were an amazing bird,
but you can turn into a human now, too?!
That's freakin' awesome!
I didn't turn into a human.
I was a human to begin with.
What?! You should've told me earlier!
I couldn't even talk until
the Shadow Palace appeared.
More importantly, how dare you suggest
that you could be like the prince?
Hey! Stop doing this really familiar thing!
The spiteful, adorable Nero is...
Actually, she's pretty cute, too.
To me, "Wizard King" is just a phrase.
But thanks to you and your
childhood friend, I now know
that our ideals have been carried
down to this era as well.
Now... I wonder which one of you
will become the Wizard King.
It's me, sir!
You and the prince are nothing alike, Asta.
What?!
I guess it's time.
I don't have the magic to keep
this body together anymore.
My recovery magic can't help here...
My prince...
Secré... Though I guess you might be Nero now.
Will you watch their futures and
ideals play out for me, as well?
Prince Lumiere! I've always...
If you're going, I'll go with you!
I gave everything I had 500 years ago,
and my life was supposed to end back then.
But thanks to you, I was
able to protect the future.
That's more than enough.
I don't want you to close
off your own potential.
I'm looking forward to futures beyond this one.
Both of the Magic Knights, and the
Clover Kingdom you'll defend.
I was able to meet my own descendants, too.
I couldn't be more satisfied!
I... The fact that I got to
serve you for all this time...
made me very happy!
And I was happy, too.
Five hundred years...
Thank you so much for waiting
for me for five hundred years,
Secré.
What the hell's going on?!
Julius's body is gone?
But I know his body was in here.
This magic is...
Wha—
What? Don't tell me you're...
Julius?!
The long night is finally over.
Look at that beautiful dawn.
It's the new dawn of the Clover Kingdom.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 121: "Three Problems."
Page 121
Three Problems
Damn, this old dude's crazy.