It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Royal Knights arrived at the
Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
They headed for its center,
where they believed the leader
Licht was, with no opposition.
But...
We seriously have nothing to do!
Who gave you permission to
make another one of you?
Uh, it's not like I wanted another me!
You're the fake!
No, that's you!
Knock it off.
She just set them both on fire.
What are you doing?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
I don't remember bringing along someone
weak enough to be killed by that.
The true identity of the fake Asta
was the last member of the Third Eye,
Raia the Disloyal.
The all-incinerating spell
of total destruction...
Flame Magic:
Calidos Brachium!
Thus began an intense fight between
flame magic and copy magic.
Eventually, Mereoleona's magic and
attack power began to overtake Raia.
Meanwhile, Yuno and his team
continued to the center.
Sorry, but people at your
level can't stop me anymore.
That sound...
We heard it earlier, too.
A heartbeat?
The feel of this mana... I've felt it before.
Also during that time...
Back at the Black Bulls' hideout,
which had been attacked by
the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
W-We somehow managed to chase them off,
but something awful still happened!
I hope they never come back.
U-Um... Could you turn the
hideout back to normal now?
I can't... I have no magic.
So he says, Gauche.
Where is it? Where is it, damn it?!
Where's all my Marie merchandise?!
Probably smashed to bits...
Squishy, squish...
Stop saying such awful things so slowly!
Get down here and help me, damn it!
But I...
Just shut up and get down here,
you slow-ass, long-haired jerk!
U-Um, Gauche...
I wouldn't do that.
Come down here!
But I...
Don't "But I..." me!
Get down here or I'll kill you!
Okay, then...
Tch. Took you long eno—
H-Henry absorbs your magic
if he gets too close!
We tried to stop you.
I found it!
Thank goodness! It's safe!
Nothing inside got smashed,
and nothing's dirt—
M-Marie's... cheek...
I'll kill you! I'm going to murder
all of you, Eye of the Midnight Sun!
But they're gone now...
Shut up! I'll kill you, too, while I'm at it!
Sorry about that...
Give me back my magic, damn it!
I can't...
I said give it back!
Anyway... Why did the
Eye of the Midnight Sun attack?
They said they "obtained" something.
They were probably just bluffing.
Nothing here is more important
than my Marie merchandise.
Were they after my dolls?
I don't think so...
Well, if there's anything
else that's important...
What is it?
Is it me?
Tch. It's nothing!
More importantly, why isn't Captain
Yami back yet at a time like this?
Indeed...
He told us not to let the hideout be taken over
Golden Dawn Headquarters
by bandits while he was gone, too...
What is he, a prophet?
The Wizard King vs.
The Leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
Hey, isn't he from the Black Bulls?
Why is he here?
Apparently, he's waiting
for Captain Vangeance.
He's been here for quite a while now.
Should we say something to him?
But he seems sorta angry.
You go talk to him!
No, you!
What the hell are you looking at, huh?
Sir Yami...
W-Would you like more tea?
Sure... But just how much tea
are you gonna make me drink?!
There's so much tea sloshing
around in my stomach,
I've been running to the bathroom constantly!
You wanna literally detox the shit out of me?!
I don't feel refreshed at all, damn it!
I-I'm terribly sorry!
Hey, how long is that golden
weird mask guy captain of yours
going to make me wait after he
said he wanted to apologize?
H-He should be here any second.
P-Please, have some more tea.
Sure.
Didn't I just say there's enough tea
sloshing around in my stomach?!
I-I'm terribly sorry!
Damn it... My ride's in the shop right now,
so it was a pain in the
ass to get here, too.
You know, your vice captain was
the one who put my ride in the shop
after the Royal Knights Selection Exam.
Finral's still in the hospital
and hasn't woken up.
I also hear that the questioning of your
vice captain isn't getting far, either.
Shouldn't your golden weird mask
captain come to me to apologize?
Are you Golden Dawn jerks messing with me?
Such pressure...
W-We sincerely apologize for
what Vice Captain Langris did.
But I ask that you have faith
in Captain Vangeance.
He is a wonderful person.
He would never knowingly insult you.
Who the hell are you?
I'm no one suspicious.
Everything about you is suspicious!
Yami, was it?
I'm counting on you to watch my back.
This guy moves like he can read my mind.
Our ki goes together.
How many years has it been since then?
We both became captains.
I'm someone who believes his gut instincts.
Vangeance...
Could you take off that mask?
You suspect that I may be the leader of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun, don't you?
I feel something similar in you...
So just let me see your face, all right?
I was born with it.
They called me a cursed child.
I'm glad I was able to tell you and
show you things as they really are.
Thank you, Yami.
It didn't feel like he was lying.
Sir Yami, please just wait a little longer.
He would never...
Tch.
I know that, you dumbasses.
Lord Julius, are you here? Lord Julius?
Honestly, the moment I
take my eyes off of him...
He needs to realize that
he's the Wizard King.
Work just keeps piling up.
I can't even get through to
him with communication magic.
Right about now...
The Royal Knights are having
the last battle with the Eye of
the Midnight Sun at their hideout.
I wish I could join in, but I've watched
over them this whole time, so I know...
Their strength and
their desire to protect the citizens
of this kingdom are real.
It'll be all right...
I know they can do this.
Not to mention, Marx will get mad at me.
I must do what I'm meant to do.
It's not often you to ask to
discuss something with me.
What's on your mind, William?
Thank you for making time
for me, Lord Julius.
You never cared about how I looked,
and were the first person to ever
acknowledge my strength.
The path to my future
opened once I met you.
I grew up as a cursed child in a
small village in the Forsaken Realm,
and though I was welcomed into
a noble family as its heir,
I was treated terribly.
But...
Little boy, what kind of magic is that?
You were different.
You truly acknowledged my power and
invited me into the Magic Knights.
It really is nothing to worry about,
but if you are so worried about it...
In that case...
When you gave me this mask...
When you invited into the Magic Knights...
I decided that I would dedicate
my grimoire to your service.
It's been eleven years since then,
and my feelings have not
changed in the least.
I have always respected you, Lord Julius.
Jeez, what brought all this on?
You're making me blush.
That is why I climbed up the ranks to
become a Magic Knights Squad captain,
chose highly capable squad members
that my mana pointed out to me,
and created the Golden Dawn.
I believed that making the ultimate
Magic Knights Squad would be
the best way to repay you.
And that was also...
for the sake of the other person
who is deeply important to me.
My friend who has always been with me,
even before I met you, Lord Julius.
From here on out, you two will wish
to walk completely different paths.
Both of you are very dear to me.
I cannot choose between you.
And so...
You two will have to choose for me.
His scar...
Thank you, William...
My one and only human friend.
Good day to you,
Wizard King Julius Novachrono.
I am the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun, Licht.
I had really hoped that wasn't the case.
William... I always knew that
you were hiding something.
That there was a side of you that
you didn't want to be known.
I'm sure Yami realized this, too.
It could be that Fuegoleon was also
caught off-guard when he
saw who you really were.
The day that the royal capital was
attacked by the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
The uneasy feeling I felt when
I faced their leader, Licht...
That somewhat familiar mana...
And right around the time I injured his arm,
I started seeing you only rarely.
I couldn't help but harbor my doubts,
though I couldn't bring myself
to believe that it was true.
But...
Who would've thought that there
were two souls in one body?
So it was you, but at the
same time, it wasn't you.
How did you get rid of that scar?
It doesn't seem to be the work of magic.
That scar is a curse cast upon
the clan of this body's mother.
No curse cast upon humans
has anything to do with me.
I despise humans.
But William... He was the
only one that was different.
We were able to share the
same body, after all.
Despite being human, he accepted
my feeling and understood them.
This uncontrollable rage,
sadness, and hatred.
We're just like this bird.
Because it can fly,
like we can use special magic,
they envy and want to hurt us.
But I believe that one day, we and the humans
will be able to understand each other.
But I was wrong.
I was surprised that your brother
felt the same way I do.
I also feel the same way.
I hope that elves and humans can
live together peacefully someday.
Because if that doesn't happen...
Tetia...
I'm sure we'll all understand
each other someday.
Yes!
If I had never met those humans,
we would've never...
There is only one way to be rid of
these overflowing emotions.
We shall collect all of the magic
stones and fulfill our hearts' desire!
So their motive is to get
revenge against the humans.
And having all of the magic stones
will make that possible?
William understood, too.
That's why he let me see you.
You have the remaining two, don't you?
Yes, because that's the safest option.
I shall obtain those magic stones,
and we shall fulfill our hearts' desire.
William... You are a kind person.
The fact that there was
another in your body
and you treasured him
so well this whole time
is also part of your kindness.
And it is my job, as someone who's
also important to you, to stop him.
You support me, which means I'll win.
No... His heart is with me.
Wizard King, I'm afraid
you're going to die.
As the Wizard King, the most
powerful mage in this land,
you will take responsibility for all the sins
the humans in the Clover Kingdom
have committed.
Light Creation Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
Mana Zone: Chrono Stasis Grigora.
Light magic is the fastest
among all magical attributes.
But that doesn't mean it's unstoppable.
I see.
But I wonder how long that can last.
This man's magic is a type
that controls the flow of time.
He can slow time down to
almost a complete halt,
bind it, speed it up tremendously,
or even destroy it...
A single attack can be lethal.
But I sense a sort of destiny
in that, ironic though it is,
I was born with light magic.
The only thing that can oppose time...
is light.
Light Creation Magic:
Light Whip of Judgment!
He uses a combination of Mana Zone
and time acceleration.
By accelerating time for
the mana around him,
he can read the flow of
the mana in the future,
which lets him sense the very near future
and anticipate attacks.
But don't think...
that you can actually outdo me.
Too slow.
Even if you can see what's ahead,
there are limits to how quickly you can evade.
Has it been a while since you
were last wounded, Wizard King?
It has. I've taken the
futures of many people,
but it's been a while since
I've seen my own blood.
Your time-controlling magic
isn't so invincible anymore.
The true nature of my magic is
to steal time from my target.
That time gets stockpiled,
and I can use it at any time,
though it takes a lot out of me.
He reversed time and healed his wound?
As someone who was born with
magic that steals futures,
my goal as the Wizard King is to create
a future without discrimination.
Until that future happens, I cannot die.
A future without discrimination,
but with humans? That's an impossible dream!
At that speed, it's taking everything
you have to evade this attack.
You cannot fight back,
or even get close to me.
I have you now!
Wha—
He's anticipating even faster!
I can already see your future.
You cannot defeat me.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Anticipation
Anticipation.
I've already read all of your moves.
So you can anticipate what'll
happen in the near future...
In that case, guess what
I'm about to do next.
Very well. Mana Zone:
Chrono Stasis Grigora.
You're about to break into a nimble dance.
And then...
There!
A dove will fly out of your hat...
Hup!
You'll spin a ball on an umbrella,
quickly remove a tablecloth without
spilling what's in the glasses...
And then you'll mimic the sounds
that various animals make.
Well? You can't do that, now, can you?
Who knew that you were so talented?
I had really hoped that wasn't the case.
You cannot defeat me.
I am the Wizard King.
It is my duty to protect this
kingdom and all of its people.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 93: "Julius Novachrono."
Page 93
Julius Novachrono
You shall be defeated by my time magic.