It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Light Creation Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
Copy Light Magic:
Mana Zone: Spirit's Hushed Dance.
Again!
I don't know if it's a magic stone
or not, but that belongs to me.
Give it back!
Nice job, Ronne!
Now... we'll finally make things right.
Yeah.
I can tell when someone's lying.
Why was what you just said a lie, Ronne?
Raia?
Who the hell are you?
Don't tell me this reincarnation is...
Mastermind
Because he betrayed us, we elves
were destroyed by the humans.
But because I can see through lies, I knew...
that he didn't actually betray us.
But I didn't tell everyone that.
Because I didn't want them to lose any
of their hatred for the humans.
I wanted to see him one more time,
no matter how many lies I had to tell.
That was my disloyalty.
And I guess I get a huge hole
in my chest for that.
But what the hell is this thing that
just made this hole in my chest?
They're the biggest liar of all.
How long were they acting like Ronne?
How long had they blended in with us?
Raia!
Raia! Raia!
What's the meaning of this, Ronne?!
The three leaves of the clover
represent faith, hope, and love.
Within a fourth leaf dwells good luck.
And...
Within a fifth leaf...
resides a demon.
This reminds me...
of the day I took advantage
of the bond between
the two mages chosen
by the four-leaf grimoires,
and created a grimoire of despair.
I can finally obtain what
should've been mine.
This magic doesn't belong to an elf!
This Shadow Palace, which lies
between this world and the next...
And the spell of the magic
stones that can draw out
what I desire from the land of the dead...
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Ronne!
What is this cold, pitch-black magic?
Don't tell me he's...
A demon!
What in the world is that creature?
Thought it's still incomplete, I haven't
been in my own body in centuries.
What a wonderful feeling.
Elf that was chosen by a
four-leaf grimoire, I commend you.
I praise you from the bottom of my heart
for everything you've done up to this point,
as well as the results you have shown me.
And now, I shall have you taste the
depths of despair, like he did back then.
What... are you talking about?
What's... going on?
That day, the one who tricked the
humans into destroying the elves
was me!
The humans were easy to manipulate,
as they wanted power.
We can come to understand each other.
And then you lot managed to let me fool
you in the most amusing way, too.
The revenge went according to plan.
All of you are fools!
How dare you?!
"Return."
Hey! That body belongs to Captain Vangeance.
I won't let you die like that.
I'd prefer to deal with you later, if possible.
You can't be serious.
You just showed up out of nowhere.
Though I'm very aware that
you're nothing more than trash.
If all I have to do is destroy
you to end all of this,
so be it!
Mana Zone: Spirit Storm!
Vacuum Wall.
What?!
Everything is meaningless
before my word soul magic.
Word soul magic?
His magic is insane!
Now that I'm stronger, I can tell.
I can't beat this guy.
Tch.
At least, not alone!
Yuno!
Took you long enough, Asta.
What in the world
is going on here?
And what is that strange creature?
What the heck is that creepy black thing?!
But... I get the feeling that I sorta know.
I see that some uninvited guests have arrived.
Well, I'll leave them alone
for now. More importantly...
"Come here."
Word soul magic...
Whatever he says becomes a reality.
Is that how he recreated
Ronne's switching magic, too?
Don't toy with me!
Light Creation Magic: Light Whip of—
"Vanish."
"Iron Spears."
Patry...
Asta! That creepy black
thing is behind all of this!
Yeah, I figured!
"Storm of Blades."
There are physical weapons mixed in?
I can't erase them with my anti-magic!
Damn it... It's taking all
I have just to evade them!
"Vacuum Wall."
"Be crushed."
"Smashed."
"Broken to pieces."
"Riddled with holes."
Asta! Yuno!
I will not allow anyone to get in my way.
Are you awake?
Thanks to you, the time that had stopped
for me will finally begin moving again.
I commend you, hero.
Five centuries ago, they got in my way,
and though I was close, my incarnation failed.
What... are you talking about?
You were the next one I set my sights on.
A new sacrifice that was loved by mana,
still young, and swayed oh so easily.
Tragedy and a sense of mission...
That was enough for you to
dabble in forbidden magic,
which allowed the elves' souls to
be reincarnated in human bodies.
What are you talking about?
The one... The one who reincarnated us is Licht!
Even if it meant dabbling in forbidden
magic, he gave us our last hope!
Wrong.
Because I was the one
who reincarnated you elves.
Wha...
Your leader doesn't want
the humans exterminated.
Restoring the elves and that revenge
you longed for... All false goals.
You merely walked down the
path I prepared for you,
neatly leading the other fools after you.
You truly did a splendid job.
In the end, it led you to a
future that Licht didn't want,
It's a lie... It's a lie... It's a lie...
It's a lie... It's a lie...
and my incarnation, which finally
allowed my soul to return to my body.
I'm... like Licht.
I was chosen by the four-leaf clover...
Indeed. You were chosen...
as my brilliant, foolish pawn.
Excellent work.
What the hell is that black thing?
Are you telling me Licht was
being used by that black thing,
just like he used us?
Patry... Everything we'd done...
This is just too amusing!
Elves and humans... Your dreams and
ambitions make the best playthings!
Don't give me that crap!
You just show up outta nowhere
and make a mess of everything.
You're super strong and scary,
but who the hell do you think you are?!
Whatever you are, you piss me off!
You're just a piece of shit...
...and my dream won't lose
to the likes of you!
Asta! Yuno!
The magic that's welling up from him
is changing the objects around him into wind.
Is Licht's child... waking up inside him?
Oh? His overflowing anti-magic is
erasing all of the magic around him.
Is his magic resonating with my own?
"Storm of Blades!"
Asta!
Yeah!
Yuno's taking care of the physical blades,
and Asta's taking care of the magical blades...
They're using both of their
powers to block all of them!
You and I...
...can do this!
If you're going to get in our
way, then you can break!
"Heal."
Damn it! What's going on?
He can do that?!
How impressive that you
were able to wound me.
Having the power of a spirit
and being loved by mana...
And the power of a meddlesome
comrade who dwells within
the five-leaf grimoire that
I should have possessed.
I don't know where you came from,
but you may have that grimoire.
When the owner of a four-leaf grimoire
is engulfed in deep despair,
a five-leaf grimoire is born.
At last, I possess both my body
and my pitch-black grimoire.
I can rule over the current world as
a demon with my true form and power!
Five hundred years ago, I succeeded
in creating a grimoire of despair,
but I was met with resistance in the very end.
So this time, by using
forbidden reincarnation magic,
I mingled wicked thoughts with their souls,
making it easier to steal their egos.
I wanted my stepping stones to do their job
and allow themselves to be stepped on.
Empty hearts are so simple.
For the sake of this moment,
I have deceived, killed, and plundered.
And oh, was it delightful!
You're unforgivable...
I'm not going to let you get away with that!
Unfortunately, I'm not the
one you have to deal with.
Rampage as you please.
Let your hatred and despair guide you.
Pat...ry...
The final state of an elf who's
overflowing with malice...
A dark elf!
Demon Light Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
Black light!
And it's so fast. Even with my
Mana Zone, I couldn't evade all of it!
Asta! You alive?
Of course I am, Yuno, you jerk!
What insane numbers and force! The weight
of that attack was off the charts!
If the anti-magic flooding out of me
hadn't softened it, I'd be dead right now!
Damn it! He's gotten way stronger!
Both the destined one who carries
the hybrid child of elves and humans
and the defective, magicless one
who's somehow able to handle
the five-leaf grimoire will
meet their ends here.
I'm not sure who you are, demon,
but if you don't steal that body soon,
you'll just die along with it.
What the heck's going on?
I don't feel any ki from him at all!
This is just a heartless, burned-out shell now.
It's merely casting scorched shadows
of the spells in its grimoire.
At least have some fun with it.
So the exit is up above, is it?
Now, if you'll excuse me... Farewell!
Hold it, you bastard!
Tch.
Yuno!
Mana Zone...
Spirit Storm!
Please move...
You probably can't forgive
me because I'm human,
and I can't forgive you, either.
But I know...
We should've been able to
understand each other!
I'm begging you! Move!
Hate...
Crap...
This spell is...
No matter what happened in the past...
No matter what hardships
and pain we go through...
I know we can come to
understand each other!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 116:
"The Ultimate Natural Enemy."
Page 116
The Ultimate Natural Enemy
I'm never going to give up!