It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Wizard King Saw, Continued
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know, yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go, though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide, I never give up
To faraway future, I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had, so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
So these are Hage's famous tatoes.
I'm not sure if they'll be to your liking,
Lord Salim, but help yourself.
They're so dry and flaky. I've never had
anything that made me so thirsty before.
But... it's delicious.
Oh, thank goodness!
It would seem that you're
a splendid cook, Miss Lily.
I'm not all that good, really...
Please, eat as much as you'd like.
You too, Klaus, Mimosa.
Right...
Why must a noble such as myself
eat this unknown thing?
Oh, this makes me so thirsty.
Yes, isn't it wonderful?
Both Yuno and Asta sent us money
from their first pay as Magic Knights.
And then... We were able to
buy so many tatoes that we can
feed the children as much as
they want to eat every day.
Actually, couldn't you feed us
something besides tatoes, too?
Don't be picky! Look how big
Yuno got from eating tatoes!
Yuno, it's wonderful that you're sending
money home when you're just a newcomer.
It's nothing.
Yuno, thank you for everything.
You've helped us out a lot.
And not just with the tatoes.
We were able to plug up
that hole in the floor.
We even dug up a well in the yard.
Thanks, Yuno!
Thanks!
Asta's been sending money, too?
Yes. To think he'd be able to do that...
How much is Asta sending?
Huh? Um...
Whisper, whisper, whisper...
I win!
Starting next month,
I'll send all of my pay.
Huh?! Really, you don't have to.
We'll be fine for a while
with the amount you sent us.
I appreciate the thought.
I'll send it!
R-Really? Thanks...
Lord Salim, we should be on our way.
Oh, it won't hurt to stay a bit longer.
In the future, it'll be important for nobles
to have more knowledge of the world.
Miss Lily, may I have some more water?
Of course.
Oh, it's empty. I'll go get some more.
I'll do it.
It's fine. You relax, Yuno.
Oh, one moment.
It's chilly at night.
Thank you very much.
I guess you're a gentleman.
Oh, it's nothing. My body
just acted on its own.
It's just proper etiquette for a noble.
Yuno...
What happened?
Where's Sister?
That brooch...
It's the same one the men who were
after Lord Salim were wearing.
H-How awful!
Of course! It must be because
I put my robe on her.
Miss Lily was taken instead of me!
Yes, that must be it.
Is Sister going to be okay? Is she, Yuno?
Yuno...
Don't worry. I'll go save her.
Yuno! I'll go, too!
Me, too!
No.
I need all of you to stay here.
I'll be fine on my own.
Wait.
Our mission is to escort Lord Salim.
We don't know when the enemy
will come after him again.
We must leave at once.
B-But...
But Sister...
Hey, Four-eyes!
Who are you calling "Four-eyes"?
Um, Four... Er, Klaus, um...
You stay out of this, Mimosa.
Yuno, I'm sure you're
worried about the sister,
but let's leave her to the authorities
who have jurisdiction here.
We're leaving immediately.
Let us go, Lord Salim.
Yuno, Mimosa.
Yes, sir.
Yuno.
I'm not leaving.
Huh?
We must fulfill our mission.
Disobeying an order is a crime.
Even so, I'm going to go save her.
Yuno!
How dare he...
You're confusing recklessness
with courage, Yuno.
You know my name?
Take this!
Meha!
Towering Tornado.
What?!
One down,
four to go.
I'm not going to kill you or anything,
but I've got to at least
rough you up a little bit.
I see. So you were after me all along.
You're brighter than you look.
Can't breathe, eh? Then drown!
How is this magic supposed to drown me?
He's...
This is how
you're supposed to drown.
That's two.
Looks like you completely
fell for the footsteps I laid.
Take that, and that, and that, and that!
Not bad. In that case...
There! Think you can stop that?!
Take that!
What?!
Why is size the only thing
that matters to you people?
Damn it! In that case...
Too late.
That's three. Two more to go.
Sister...
Hold it right there.
Good boy.
It'd be a shame
if the sister's pretty face got burned.
Yuno.
It looks like you have a talent for magic.
If you see someone in need,
make sure you help them.
Promise me.
You too, Asta.
Huh? Did you say something?
Now then, Yuno. Why don't
you hand over your grimoire?
You won't be able to do anything without it.
What do you plan to do with my grimoire?
Maybe I'll sell it. Maybe I'll burn it.
I honestly don't care.
Without your grimoire,
you'll be useless as a Magic Knight.
Is that your plan?
What if I refuse?
Are you going to?
That's a good boy. Hand it over.
Then I'll let you take
your precious sister home.
I refuse.
What?! Don't you get it? The sister—
I won't let you harm her.
Are you going to attack me?
No matter how you attack—
I'm not the one who's going to attack.
Huh? Then who—
Steel Creation Magic: Fierce Spiral Lance!
Mimosa.
Yes, sir.
She's all right.
I hope you defeated all of them.
There should be one more.
Did he flee?
What would you have done if I hadn't come?
Why did you come?
Do you think I'm some kind of fool?
He does!
Listen well, Yuno. Our duty as Magic
Knights is to protect the people.
I thought it was strange.
These men were after you, not Salim.
Do you think a noble would want
to come to a village like this?
Do you think they'd happily eat those tatoes?
Sorry to say it, but I definitely wouldn't.
There's no way they'd accidentally take
Sister Lily instead of Salim, either.
Besides...
It was strange for Salim, whom you defeated,
to specifically ask you to escort him.
And that's when we used my Plant
Creation Magic: Flower of Truth.
It's all your fault I wasn't able
to join the Magic Knights, Yuno!
Who cares about your stupid four-leaf
grimoire, damn it?! I'll steal it from you!
I'll get my daddy to hurt you!
I'll get my revenge!
He coughed up everything.
I'm still surprised you managed to find me.
That was also thanks to Mimosa's abilities.
Flower Creation Magic:
Magic Flower Guidepost.
Let's see...
Oh, there he is.
That's why we were able to back you up.
Thank you.
You helped me out a lot, Klaus, Mimosa.
No problem.
Shut up!
Honestly, revenge? How pathetic!
It's only natural that you lost to Yuno.
Our honorable captain of the Golden Dawn,
William Vangeance, chose him!
That means he's truly that talented!
Klaus...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I still haven't acknowledged you.
Oh, dear.
Right...
But I'll overlook your insolence this time,
since this was all Salim's doing.
So what shall we do?
Take him to the royal capital?
No, let's just leave them.
Are you sure?
As long as they don't go
near Hage Village again.
You heard him. You're free to go.
Don't ever try anything like this again.
Do you understand?
You're just a peasant.
Getting you to let your guard
down was all part of my plan!
Huh?
God of Lighting Rising Salim!
Water Creation Magic: Holy Strike of Love!
Stop this! Show some remorse
for what you've done!
All of you, too!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I almost want to scout the
sister for the Magic Knights.
Yuno, we're going to take them
to the royal capital after all.
By the way, where did the other one go?
No idea.
Man, that was fun.
If they were actually in trouble, I was
going save them, but I didn't need to at all.
William's newbie is pretty impressive, too.
How long do you intend to fool around?
You're too loud!
You need to return at once!
Your work is piling up!
All right, all right.
It's not healthy to be so
irritated all the time.
Whose fault do you think that is, huh?!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Thank goodness!
Goodness!
Awesome as usual, Yuno.
Well, he is a Magic Knight.
Klaus, Mimosa, thank you both very much.
Don't mention it.
Salim was behind all of this. How unsightly.
Please, please, help yourselves.
Let me repay you with more tato dishes.
They've gotten a bit cold,
but please eat as much as you'd like!
It's not bad.
You're not very honest, are you, Klaus?
It's good.
A star?
The Wizard King was pleased with
your work, and we received a star.
Thank you very much! It's an honor!
I never thought I'd get
one on my first mission.
But I don't feel as if we did
enough to earn a star.
After you brought Salim in,
he ended up confessing
to various evil deeds Lord Hapshass had done.
Bribes, fraudulent accounts,
and shady deals.
You made quite the catch.
It's all thanks to you three.
Sir, did you happen to take on this mission
because you knew this would happen?
We mustn't allow any evil deeds
to be done in the Clover Kingdom.
Yes, sir.
Klaus, Yuno, and Mimosa, I look forward
to all of your future great deeds.
Yes, sir.
Yuno and Mimosa...
It appears that the newbies this year are...
well, at least slightly competent.
I'm counting on you all.
Especially you, Yuno.
So, a star...
Everything ended well this time, but don't
ever act on your own again, Yuno.
Yes, sir.
Why was there a pause? Yuno, look at me!
Look me in the eyes and say that
you won't act on your own again.
Yes, sir.
Yuno! Hey, Yuno!
What?! The Golden Dawn received a star?!
We are hoomans.
And I thought we were finally only
100 away. Now we're 101 away again.
Damn it! I thought we'd
finally caught up to them!
So close.
How is that close? We're at minus 30.
We are hoomans.
Shut up!
I'm not going to lose!
They're only ahead by 101!
I'll catch up in no time!
Just you wait, Golden Dawn!
Yuno!
Sir, there's trouble. An anomaly—
An anomaly has occurred, right?
Well... Let's have them work on this mission.
Them?
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh, go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
My Steed
"My Steed."
Well, isn't it beautiful? Its eyes,
its beak... Perfection.
Sure.
Doesn't it just scream "Golden Dawn"?
Whoa, that's so cool! What is that?!
It's as cool as Magna's Crazy Cyclone
and Bah-ha's Shooting Star!
Isn't it? I have no idea
who you are, but thank you.
Not a chance.
What? Explore a dungeon?
Along with Stupidsta and Luck?
Leave it to me. Exploring
a dungeon will be easy!
Black Clover, Page 14: "Dungeon."
Page 14
Dungeon
Not giving up is my magic.