The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
A New Resolve
Noelle, control your broom!
I am!
We're gonna fall!
What are you grabbing, Stupidsta?!
I'm royalty!
In front of you! Look in front of you!
In front?
Dang it, stop shaking my broom!
I can't regain control.
You never had control to begin with!
That's why I said I'd run! And yet...
"You're going back to Hage Village?
F-Fine, I guess I can take you!
I've got complete control
of my broom now!"
My ass!
There's no way you could
run all the way there!
How many days would that take?!
Also, quit complaining when I'm
kind enough to give you a ride.
You consider this giving me a ride?!
I'm going on ahead.
Hey! No fair, Nero! Take me with you!
Nope.
Nero!
S-See? I told you that I was
able to control my magic now.
This is n-no biggie at all.
I knew I should've had Finral take me.
Hey, look, Asta! Over there!
I see the demon head.
Y-Yeah...
You'd better be grateful! I'm royalty!
Whoa!
Yuno!
Hey!
Hngh!
Yuno!
Hey, it's Meathead.
Yeah, the biggest meathead I know.
Yuno! Are you going home to the village, too?!
Yeah. Captain Vangeance gave me permission.
I'm in the same boat!
All right, it's competition time!
What competition?
To see who can get to the church first, duh!
Of course, it's going to be me!
Seriously, a race?
You're not children. What an idiot.
Right, Yuno?
You can't be serious.
Nom.
Thank goodness the damage
was minimal over here.
It's a blessing in disguise, I'd say.
What's that?
That's...
All right! I win!
Took you long enough.
Looks like I win, Asta.
You just got here, too, dang it!
I win.
Jeez, even Yuno's acting like a kid.
But...
That's what's so cute about you. Poke!
Look at you, being all bashful!
That just makes you even cuter!
Asta?! Yuno?!
Hey, Father.
I'm home.
Asta! Yuno! You've gotten so big!
Look at the two of you!
You just saw us recently.
Oh, right. I just couldn't help myself.
Are you okay now, Father?
Orsi Orfai
Yup! I'm all better!
More importantly, Asta...
I saw you in the paper.
Right. About that...
That article is mistaken.
Yuno...
Asta isn't a devil's servant.
He's actually trying to defeat them.
Please believe that.
Of course I do.
No one in Hage Village believes that article.
Asta, Yuno...
You two saved this village.
We're all proud of you.
I see. Thank goodness.
By the way, about that newspaper article...
I made sure to get it framed!
Please don't!
Could you sign it later?
No!
Where's everyone else?
They...
Did something happen?
Father!
They've... They've all left!
They've all left!
A school?
Yes. The magic school that everyone
in Hage Village always wanted.
We were finally able to build
a school in this village.
Thinking back... on everything
Hage Village has been through...
since we were basically abandoned
by the royal capital...
After you two joined the Magic Knights,
everyone felt more motivated,
and we were finally able to make it a reality.
Sister Lily is teaching the
children as an instructor.
Way to go, Sister!
I teach some lessons now and then, too.
Hey, welcome back!
Asta! Yuno! Thanks for saving the village!
Sure!
And that's the magic school.
The whole village got together and remodeled
the tato storage we weren't using anymore.
Remember when we'd play hide-and-seek
in there all the time, Yuno?
Did we?
Sure we did! You hid in there until it got dark,
then you started crying because you
got scared when I couldn't find you.
You can't be serious.
I'm totally serious!
Now you're ignoring me?!
My prince...
197... 198... 199...
200... 201... 202...
Asta! Yuno!
Welcome home!
Home!
Hey! It's good to be back!
It's really them?
Asta! Yuno!
Whoa...
Yay! It's really them!
Wow!
Asta, I think maybe you grew a bit... or not.
Hey!
And Yuno is as cool as ever.
He's not just cool. He can be cute, too.
The dolly talked!
She's the Wind Spirit!
Spiwit!
I'm Bell.
I'd prefer it if you didn't
treat me like a dol—
I'm gonna play with the spirit dolly.
Me, too! Me, too!
Spirit dolly!
Uh, hello?! Hey, Yuno! Save me! Yuno!
Asta... Yuno...
Lily Aquaria
I'm so glad you're both safe.
Sister...
Please marry me!
Wow, that takes me back.
We used to hear that every day
when Asta still lived here.
I think I finally got the hang of it.
Please marry me!
M-Marry?!
Wait, you can't just propose
to me out of nowhe—
I missed this feeling.
Sorry, it was a reflex.
Don't come charging at me like that, Stupidsta!
Uh, okay...
N-Not to mention, m-m-m-m-marriage?
That's so sudden...
You must be a fellow Magic Knight
from the Black Bulls, young lady.
Yes.
Thank you for always taking care
of Asta. You must be Noelle.
Asta always mentions you in his letters.
Huh? Letters?
J-Jeez... What could you possibly
be saying about me in those letters?
Could it be...
My heart is set on someone.
Yes... Noelle.
How dare you?!
Wait, why?!
What in the world are they doing?
Oh? Are you also a member
of the Black Bulls, miss?
That's Nero!
She's our new squad member!
My, my...
Please continue to look after Asta.
Likewise.
I know! Asta, Yuno...
I know you just got here, but I have
a favor to ask you. Is that all right?
Yes.
I'll do anything for you, Sister!
So you see...
I'd like you two to act as
teachers for the little ones.
Us?
Teachers?
Yes. Everyone in this kingdom
looks up to the Magic Knights,
so I think being instructed by some
Magic Knights would be a nice memory.
They've truly grown up so much.
Instructor Asta!
Instructor Yuno!
Structor!
Instructor...
All right, leave it to me! I'll teach
you all the important things!
Listen up! Magic equals muscles!
What are you even talking about?
You guys haven't got much mana yet!
So how are you gonna make up for it?
That's right! With muscles!
That's why you all need to train!
All right, let's do this! Go run!
What in the world are they doing?
Instructor Yuno!
Will you be the girls' instructor, then, Yuno?
Instructor...
You don't need to think too
hard about the "instructor" part.
Just playing with them is fine.
Playing with them?
I'm sure the little ones will learn
something just by observing you.
I see.
Instructor Yuno, let's play house!
Play... house?
Why do I have to be the baby?
I'm royalty...
You're so cute, Noelle!
R-Really?
If I'm doing this,
then I need to give it my all.
I'm a baby...
I'll do it!
Wah! Wah! Wah! Wah!
You're so good!
Mommy, please calm your baby.
O-Okay...
Th-There, there...
That's not right, Yuno! You need to be nicer!
Nicer?
Sister!
You need to take this seriously.
The little ones will definitely
learn something by watching you.
All right.
Come here, little one. There, there.
There's no need to cry.
Oh, you must be hungry.
Here, have some milk.
Suckle, suckle, suckle...
Is that good? Excellent. Now, now...
Parum, you've got ketchup on your cheek.
Whatever am I going to do with you?
You're such a little troublemaker.
Yuno...
I wonder who you took after.
It must be your father.
Well done, Yuno.
But what are the children
supposed to learn from this?
This is the "new leaves" class.
They're all working hard for the
day they get their grimoire.
The grimoire awarding ceremony...
It hasn't even been that long since
we had ours, but it feels so long ago.
Yeah...
All right, that's it.
They're...
Yeah.
And stop.
Wonderful! You're doing wonderfully!
Your magic is improving so
much through your studies.
Keep it up.
Yay!
It's Asta and Yuno!
It's been so long!
I'm honored to see you again!
Asta!
Yuno!
We feel really bad for what we did back then.
We decided to turn over a new leaf
after we saw how amazing you two were,
and became assistant instructors here.
They actually became good guys!
Did you hit your heads?
Oh, Headmaster.
Headmaster?
Oh! It's the old guy who gave us our
grimoires at the grimoire tower!
Asta, Yuno, welcome back.
I heard of all the wonderful
things you've been doing.
I'm very proud of you.
Because of your feats, the children have more
motivation when it comes to learning magic.
That's why we built this school.
It's thanks to us?
Now, then...
The Grimoire Tower is home to many
a grimoire, each waiting for its master.
They are all unique.
That includes size and thickness.
But the ones who will increase the number
and the power of the spells
within them are you children.
With a little bit of hard work,
you can become whatever you'd like.
Yes, just like Yuno and Asta here.
Aw, shucks.
I have a dream.
I dream that some of you children will
someday become like Yuno and Asta.
No, seriously!
Okay!
I see.
So you'll be going back in the morning.
All right, then. We're going to throw
the biggest tato party tonight!
Look forward to it, Asta and Yuno.
Yeah!
Miss Noelle, Miss Nero,
I hope you'll both join us.
Thank you...
I'm pretty sure it's going to
make my mouth a desert again.
Hey, is that Nash?
Hey, Nash!
Oh, it's just you, Asta.
Don't give me that.
By the way, why weren't you at school?
Playing hooky?
I had something I needed to do.
Like what?
That's none of your business.
Hey, wait a second!
Nash! You shouldn't be playing hooky!
You know, Nash isn't actually skipping school.
Yes. We're all trying to
act like we don't know...
But you know how much he
looks up to Asta, right?
So he said he wanted to be like Asta
and join the Magic Knights someday.
I see.
298... 299... 300!
And now for this moguro leaf juice,
which is supposed to be
good for increasing magical powers!
So gross...
One more drink!
All right! I can feel my mana overflowing!
That even if you're poor... or an orphan...
I'll prove that you can become more
amazing than anyone else in this world!
Just like Asta!
My prince, please continue
to watch over them.
I'm sure this kingdom's future... will be bright.
Here, give this to Asta and Yuno to eat.
I brought so many tatoes!
Yes, yes...
Do you need any help?
Leave peeling that tato to me!
Thanks.
Honestly...
Where could Asta have gone?
But really... What did he write about
me in the letters he sent here?
You crying?
Of course I'm not!
I'm just really happy.
Not only was I an orphan,
but unlike you, I had no magic.
I was always made fun of when we lived here.
But...
Asta, Yuno, welcome back.
"I heard of all the wonderful
things you've been doing.
I'm very proud of you."
So, yeah...
Of course.
Because we've accomplished that much.
We've proven that you can
become whatever you want
through hard work with our actions.
But it's not over yet.
We've only just begun.
Yeah. In order to face the
threat of the Spade Kingdom...
And the devils...
We have to become even stronger.
In order to protect everyone...
...let's continue moving forward.
Let's get stronger, Yuno.
Of course, I'm going to become
far stronger than you.
Guess we're about even for now.
You can't be serious.
I'm going to become the Wizard King.
No matter what hardships await us,
I will overcome them.
I will become stronger.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 132: "The Lion Awakens."
Page 132
The Lion Awakens
There are others trying to
become stronger, too.