It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Yami's tales of his younger years taught Asta
that you'll always find a path
as long as you don't give up,
and Asta's competitive spirit was
ignited in his rivalry with Yuno.
All right! I'm gonna catch
up to Yuno and surpass him!
And then...
The hell?
I dunno who the hell you are,
but stop that racket!
Don't you know that this is the
home of the Black Bulls,
the Magic Knights Squad that Mister Yami—
Th-The heck?!
Y-You're Lady Sisgoleon!
Formation of the Royal Knights
Mereoleona Vermillion
What? Are you serious?
What the hell is the Captain of
the Crimson Lion Kings doing here?
Yeah!
Yeah! What are you doing here,
Captain Sisgoleon?!
It's Mereoleona!
What the hell is all that racket?
I can't even take a dump in pea—
It's an emergency! A wild beast
has invaded the premises!
Everyone, leave the base immediately!
Any of you that don't make
it out, just play dead!
Don't look her in the eye! She'll eat you!
Just shut up and accept this, you fool.
Um... Is this some hellish drink
that'll set my throat ablaze
and make me spit fire after a single sip?
It's to thank you for visiting Fuegoleon.
Do you wanna die for real?
You don't need to thank me.
At any rate, this drink can't be for humans
if someone as violent as you likes it.
I don't want it.
Okay, I'm going to kill you.
You're not supposed to kill
the person you're thanking.
I'll kill you with gratitude.
Your eyes are way too serious...
I dislike jokes.
You don't want it, Captain?
Then can I have it?
Oh, I see. You just came to see Captain Yami.
I totally thought you were gonna
take me someplace awful aga—
While I'm at it, I might
as well take you lot, too.
What do you mean by that?!
Where are you taking us?
Hell? Is it hell?!
No! Wh-Why are you taking me, too?!
Are there strong people where we're going?
Are you leaving already? But I made tea...
H-Hey! Your squad members
are being kidnapped!
Do something!
Well, if that means you're leaving, have at it.
What?!
We're sacrifices! What the heck
did we do to deserve this?!
Looks like you guys shoulda
been better people!
Especially you, Luck! Serves you damn right!
They all passed the
Royal Knights Selection Exam.
What?!
W-We passed?!
We made it into the Royal Knights?!
I couldn't win the tournament,
but Yuno didn't leave me behind, either!
We can both still strive to become the
Wizard King and fight on the same stage!
Heck yeah!
I did it!
I passed! I passed!
That means I get to stay with Asta—
N-Not that I actually care about that!
I-I mean, I'm happy that Asta passed,
but that's just because he's in
the same squad as me! Yeah!
That's all it is!
Noelle, it'll be great working
together as fellow Royal Knights!
H-Hmph.
Don't go barging in on your own again
and cause trouble for everyone else.
Yeah! I've been training even harder,
so you don't have to worry about that!
Did you even hear what I said?!
I said don't go barging into places!
By the way, I believe there's
one other Black Bull who passed.
Huh? One more?
R-Really? Maybe I'm the
one you're looking for.
Hey, right here!
I don't see him, though.
Hello?! I'm right here!
Right here! Magna Swing!
It's not you.
It doesn't matter.
A summons has been sent to them.
Guess I didn't make it after all.
Magna...
Too bad for you, Magna.
I'm gonna become even stronger
in the Royal Knights,
so I might get too strong for you.
H-Hey, what are you—
You've got some nerve, you little shit!
I'll keep getting back up no
matter how many times I fall!
You'd better not crap your pants when you
come back and I'm way stronger than you!
All right, training time!
Vanessa, spar with me!
What? But I'm about to enjoy this.
I wanna get stronger! I have to!
Oh, fine. I guess I'll just have my
fun later, you virgin delinquent.
Who are you calling a delinquent?!
You'd better be ready, Luck!
So... come back safely.
Yeah!
The same goes for you two.
But of course.
We'll be cheering you on.
I'm loving the looks on their faces.
Go kick some ass.
Venue for the Royal Knights' Swearing-In Ceremony
The Tower of Hope
From the Silver Eagles, Nils Ragus.
Yes, ma'am!
The Vice Captain of the Coral Peacocks,
Kirsch Vermillion.
Vice Captain of the Coral Peacocks, 1st Class Senior Magic Knight
Kirsch Vermillion
My name always sounds so beautiful.
From the Blue Rose Knights, Puli Angel.
Member of the Blue Rose Knights, 4th Class Senior Magic Knight
Puli Angel
I'm here! Did you all miss me?
From the Green Praying Mantises, En Ringard.
Member of the Green Praying Mantises, 4th Class Senior Magic Knight
En Ringard
Hell yeah! Let's do this!
Yeah...
Captain of the Aqua Deer
Rill Boismortier
From the Aqua Deer, Captain Rill
Boismortier and Fragil Tormenta.
Member of the Aqua Deer Squad, 3rd Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Fragil Tormenta
Hi. I'm Rill, the Magic Knights Squad captain
who couldn't even win the tournament.
Captain, please get a hold of yourself!
From the Golden Dawn, Hamon Caseus,
Klaus Lunettes, Mimosa Vermillion, and Yuno!
Yes, ma'am!
Member of the Golden Dawn, 2nd Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Hamon Caseus
More candidates were chosen
from our squad than any other.
Member of the Golden Dawn, 3rd Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Klaus Lunettes
This is what we call Golden Dawn
quality and Golden Dawn pride.
Member of the Golden Dawn, 5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Yuno
Of course Yuno was chosen!
He was the MVP of the Selection Exam!
Bell
Hey, are you listening?
From the Black Bulls,
Luck Voltia, Noelle Silva, and Asta.
Yes, ma'am!
How you like that, Yuno?!
I didn't get left behind!
I'll keep getting back up,
no matter how many times I fall!
And you'll fall again.
You do nothing but fall.
Yeah, whenever I get a chance..
Wait! What the hell, man?!
I'm just stating the truth.
Yeah, and the part where I keep
getting back up is true, too!
Guess he accepted the falling part.
Member of the Golden Dawn, 5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Mimosa Vermillion
I'm so happy that I get to
work with you again, Asta.
Likewise!
I'm late in introducing myself,
but I'm Mereoleona Vermillion,
and I've been appointed
the Captain of the Royal Knights!
What?! Lady Sisgoleon's the
Captain of the Royal Knights?!
Wait, why's no one else surprised?
I figured that'd be the case.
She just did roll call, and she's
the one who came to get us.
Got a problem with me?
Absolutely not!
1st Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Nils Ragus
4th Class Senior Magic Knight
Ben Benfunk
1st Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Ruben Shagger
Not only is she leading our
Crimson Lion Kings Squad,
Lady Mereoleona's also royalty!
Who could be more fit?
Yes.
I would've preferred
that our captain of the Golden Dawn,
Captain Vangeance, be chosen,
but he's busy leading the troops guarding
the royal capital, so this'll have to do.
If any of you have any objections,
don't hold back! State them now!
I also won't hold back in crushing you!
You can't be serious.
Listen up! You sixteen survived
the brutal Selection Exam
and were chosen to become Royal Knights.
If there are no objections,
from this day until we annihilate
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
your lives will be in my hands!
Yes, ma'am!
Hm? One, two, three...
One of you is missing.
Is he disrespecting me by being late?
My bad! Guess I'm late.
So you are disrespecting me.
I wanted to see how strong you were,
since my life's going to be in your hands.
Pleasure to work with you.
You're—
Wait!
Wh-Why the heck are you wearing that robe?!
Hey! Why the heck are you
wearing a Black Bulls robe?!
You dumbass. It's because I'm a member
of the Black Bulls, obviously.
What?!
You're one of the Black Bulls?!
Hey! Explain yourself!
It's a bittersweet memory from years ago.
I was kicking the asses of some
Magic Knights due to reasons.
Magic Knights?! You can't do that!
Ow!
Shut up. I said I had reasons, you little shit.
Anyway, while I was doing that,
I ran into this terrible monster,
and he ended up kicking my ass instead.
Y-You bastard...
This is...
You're pretty fun, so you can have that.
You can toss it if you don't want it, though.
Quit messing with me, you crazy Magic Knight!
Like I'd ever wear—
You shouldn't just hand these out like candy!
See? You do understand.
Anyway, you can just put it
on whenever you feel like it.
So, yeah, that's what happened.
Yami scouted me, and I got into the
Magic Knights through the back door.
What the heck, Xerx?! That's not fair!
Also got in through
the back door
Do you have any idea what
I went through to get in?!
Also, I'm not Xerx.
The name's Zora Ideale,
you shitty little junior shrimp.
What?! What the heck is a Zora?
Is that your real name?!
I just told you it was, you stupid shrimp.
Why the heck did you lie?!
You know what they say.
If you want to fool your enemies,
you need to fool your friends first.
What enemies?! And wait,
are you my senior, then?!
Damn straight. Show me some respect.
Heck no! And you need to
apologize for a lot of things!
What was your name again? Zura?
It's Zora.
I don't know what the heck is going on!
You're so noisy, you shitty little shrimp.
Ah, what the hell?
I'll start working toward it now. Not a
super mage, but a true Magic Knight.
Here you go. Have another rainbow stink bug.
It's a raging stench!
Actually, it smells kinda okay
once you get used to it...
It absolutely does not!
You're right! It reeks like no other!
Hey, you should fight me, too!
How long are you gonna keep yapping,
you impudent little fools?!
We're sorry!
Huh? Where'd everyone else go?
They went to change into their
Royal Knights robes ages ago, you fools!
R-Royal Knights robes, you say?!
What in the world is that
super-cool-sounding thing?!
They were created for our fight against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
with high resistance to magic attacks!
Hurry up and go change!
Hey, look!
Well? Well?
Isn't he just the handsomest?
I think I fell in love all over again!
Who knew a day would come when
we'd be wearing the same robes?
But we're not on the same level.
I'm the one who'll become the Wizard King.
Nope, it's me!
You can't be serious.
All right, it looks like
you've all finished changing.
So beautiful. Why do I look
so good in everything?
Brother, you're so narcissistic
that it's making me ill.
This is so exhilarating.
It fits so nicely, even on us heftier folks.
Whoo! I'm so pumped!
I-I guess it's not bad.
Um...
Why's mine so short?!
What's with that robe?!
Asta, why are you joking around?
I'm not! This is how it
looked when I put it on!
Guess the half-baked twit
also gets just half a robe.
We ran out of fabric because we
got a few additional members.
Additional members?
They didn't take the exam, but they
are essential to making this plan work.
Mage Attendant to the Wizard King
Cob Portaport
1st Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Shiren Tium
Shiren Tium and Cob Portaport.
Shiren's stone creation magic can
create models of the enemy's base
and measure the magic
levels of the mages there.
Cob has very convenient spatial magic.
He has been added because Finral Roulacase
is still recovering from his injuries.
And one more...
Captain of the Silver Eagles
Nozel Silva
Nozel Silva! He will be joining us, too.
Nozel...
The Captain of the Silver Eagles?
We couldn't ask for better!
Unbelievable! I get to
fight alongside my captain!
I figured you'd decline.
What brought this on?
I don't want to hear anything from you.
I'm only here because the king ordered it.
You lot, along with these three,
are the Royal Knights!
What?! Hey, Nozel!
Why did you just show up
like it's no big deal?!
You didn't even take the exam!
That's not fair!
What I want to know is, why did you bother
taking the exam when you're a captain?
What?! I could've joined
without even taking the exam?!
King of the Clover Kingdom
Augustus Kira Clover XIII
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
is a fearsome enemy!
The aid of a Magic Knights Squad captain,
particularly a royal one, will be essential!
Nothing beats royalty!
It's all about us royals!
Hey, it's the king.
Hello, Your Majesty,
King Augustus Kira Clover XIII.
She's so fierce.
I can't remember the last time
anyone used my full name.
Listen well, men! Don't do
anything to bring shame upon—
I think you all know this, but we have
no use for anything other than victory!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is
a terrorist organization that
threatens the Clover Kingdom!
If we don't take care of them ourselves,
there will never be peace in our land!
You all worked together when
they attacked the royal capital
and were successful in eliminating them,
but there were still severe consequences.
My foolish younger brother Fuegoleon
fell at the enemy's hands,
and he has still not awakened.
What we learned from the agents
we captured is that their leader
is a mage with a four leaf
clover grimoire, Licht.
We learned that they have an upper
echelon called the Third Eye...
And that, for reasons unknown,
they are collecting magic
stones in order to be
reborn in their true forms
and obtain great power.
There are only three magic stones left.
We were able to obtain two of
them before they got to them.
We were also able to defeat Vetto,
the Third Eye's user of beast magic,
as well as Fana, who commanded Salamander.
The remaining member of the Third Eye
is a user of copy magic, Raia.
There's no doubt that Raia and Licht will
be our strongest opponents in this battle!
We are going to be attacking
their stronghold,
so our enemy will do everything
they can to stop us.
Some of us may fall,
but we will be victorious!
We are going to give our all in this battle!
Any fools who fail to do so will be
taken out by me before we even
get to the enemy's stronghold!
Are you ready?!
Yes!
Your Majesty, King Augustus Kira Clover XIII!
Wh-Why are you yelling at me?!
Please continue what you were saying earlier.
You're ordering me to continue the conversation
when you already said everything?!
There's absolutely nothing else left to say!
Well, do good work out there. That is all.
Really?!
That's it?
Oh, yeah. Where is the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout, anyway?
A good question, even though
he's an infuriating little peasant.
Well—
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout
is located in...
Strong Magic Region "Gravito Stones"
Floating Dungeon
a floating dungeon within the strong
magic region known as Gravito Stones!
Guess I'm pretty late.
Heya.
I see you look as moronic as ever.
Don't be like that.
Let's have a drink sometime, Miss.
I decline.
He is pretty weak.
Oh, there they are.
Hey there, Raia.
Jeez, you're late!
Are you too lazy to even wake up nowadays?
You're the worst.
Oh, shut up.
Jeez, Patry. Hogging the
spot next to Licht again?
After tomorrow's ceremony,
he's going to belong to someone else,
so you should probably cut the cord soon.
Shut up. I can do what I want.
What, you little brat?!
It's fine. Even if I marry Licht,
he still belongs to everyone.
The human princess sure is nice.
That kindness is going to
cause you trouble someday.
Anyway, that space is gonna
be gone sooner or later.
Stop picking on him. Patry knows that.
So, Licht, how does it feel, knowing you're
going to be a father in a few months?
I can feel the mana blessing us.
I'm very happy our child will come into
this world welcomed by everyone.
This child is our future.
It'll bridge the gap between elves and humans.
Congratulations, Licht and Tetia!
Congratulations!
Talk about a fleeting dream...
I guess the awakening must be near.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
All Kinds of Robes
Part 1
All Kinds of Robes, Part 1.
R-Royal police robes, you say?!
What in the world is that
super-cool-sounding thing?!
They're robes made to
excel in investigations!
Hurry up and go change!
Halt
They aren't even robes!
Wait, why is mine so different?!
All Kinds of Robes
Part 2
Part 2.
R-Royal school robes, you say?!
What in the world is that
super-cool-sounding thing?!
They're robes made to excel in academic life!
Hurry up and go change!
Again, why is mine so different?!
All Kinds of Robes
Part 3
Part 3.
R-Royal doctor robes, you say?!
What in the world is that
super-cool-sounding thing?!
They're robes made to excel
in emergency medicine!
Hurry up and go change!
Seriously! Why is mine the
only one that's different?!
You can't be serious.
It's finally time to fight
the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
We, the Royal Knights, are going to protect
the Clover Kingdom and its people!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 88:
"Storming the Eye of the Midnight Sun's Hideout!!!"
Page 88
Storming the Eye of the Midnight Sun's Hideout!!!
Lady Sisgoleon's strong! Super strong!