It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
While Asta and the other Royal Knights
were attacking the hideout of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
back at the royal capital, the leader
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun, Licht,
had revealed himself before Julius
and was fighting him for
possession of the magic stones.
What is behind this man's strength?
He's just an ordinary human. So why...
Julius used a grimoire that had no cover
and his time magic, overpowering Licht.
As the Wizard King,
I will protect this kingdom
and its people.
But Licht then released his sealing magic and
was about to attack every
citizen of the Clover Kingdom.
The size of that light spell
is ridiculous... damn it!
Now... Accept your judgment, humans!
Light Magic: Arrows of Judgment!
Time Reversal Magic: Chrono Anastasis.
Julius used all of the time and magic
he had left in order to save the people.
But that was exactly what Licht wanted.
I'm sure you saw my attack.
But you couldn't cancel that time spell
in order to evade.
Because...
you are the Wizard King.
What the hell's going on here...
Vangeance?!
New Future
Good day to you, Yami Sukehiro.
I am Licht.
Licht...
William is asleep inside me.
No... I guess he was watching the Wizard King
draw his last breath through this eye.
Huh? What the hell are you talking about?
I hope you're prepared.
This can't be... This can't be happening...
Lord Julius... No...
What the hell are you doing, Marx?!
We need to get him healed! Hurry up and
get Owen over here, you dumbass!
Right away!
Don't worry, Julius! We'll get you—
It's no use.
This man will die soon.
You protected this country to the very end.
You have my respect for that,
Wizard King Julius Novachrono.
But...
Master Licht!
Dark Magic...
Dark Cloaked...
We will never, ever understand each other!
Dimension Slash!
I let him get away.
Julius! Hang in there!
Yami...
That spell you just used was amazing...
You actually cut through dimensions...
Now's not the time for that.
You've truly become an amazing Magic Knight...
I keep telling you, I'm 28 now.
I'm not a kid anymore.
This is promising... The next
generation has grown up well,
and the generation after
is starting to bloom...
My wishes will live on with
the next Magic Knights...
Mana Zone: Calidos Brachium Barrage!
What's wrong, last of the Third Eye?
Is that all you've got?
He doesn't stand a chance.
I don't have any time to use
super speed or healing.
Where's your next move? Are you done?
She's defeating the Third Eye,
which gave us so much trouble, this easily?
Captain Mereoleona is so freakin' cool!
If this is all you've got,
I'm just going to keep punching you
until there's nothing left.
Well, shit.
Burn to ashes!
I'll acknowledge your strength, royal lady.
And that's exactly why...
Before I burn to ashes,
I'll self-destruct and take you with me!
Land one more hit on me, and it's kaboom!
The anti-magic kid... He must've
sensed the self-destruct spell
and managed to get over here
even faster than that lady's attack.
How freakin' fast can he
read his opponent and move?!
I saw two others that tried
to self-destruct, too!
I'm starting to catch on, you Third Eye jerk!
Don't waste your life like that!
What the heck is the deal with you people?!
Going on about having something stolen
from you and getting revenge against humans!
I still don't get it! But you're
humans just like us, aren't you?!
First, you guys need to
clearly explain your deal!
Then you can listen to what I've got to say!
I won't allow you to die before that!
For crying out loud... You sure are
a fiery little brat, aren't you?
You've got some nerve, cutting into my fight.
Would you like to burn to ashes, too?
What?!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
threw our country into chaos,
and left us with many casualties.
They have no intention of coming
to an understanding with us!
Out of the way.
We have to squash them here and now...
Even if it means killing them!
Huh? Why's that?
We can understand each other.
I mean, we're basically the same as them.
They're mad because something
precious to them was hurt.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
We're fighting because we
can't forgive each other.
So how can we get rid of that rage and hatred?
I'm an idiot,
so I couldn't figure it out,
no matter how hard I thought about it,
but I'm sure we can!
We have to get rid of that rage and hatred!
What I strived to achieve...
The future I tried to create...
I believe that it's not too far away...
The royals and nobles...
Commoners and peasants...
Even if they're not human...
A kingdom without discrimination or hatred...
A new future I'd create with all of you...
A free kingdom
where everyone can acknowledge
each other and smile...
That's the kind of kingdom I want to create
when I become the Wizard King.
What a fool,
blurting out something so overambitious
without any hesitation...
He's actually serious about that.
There used to be a guy who
said the same thing.
This child is our future.
It'll bridge the gap between elves and humans.
Congratulations, Licht and Tetia!
Congratulations!
If all humans were like
you two, then maybe...
But...
There's no stopping this now.
Welcome back!
Took you long enough! You got the
last magic stones, didn't you?
Watch your mouth.
Everything went according to plan.
No, even better! Master Licht
has slain the Wizard King!
Whoa, are you serious?!
Way to go, Master Licht!
It's finally time.
Now, no one can stop us.
Julius... just hold on a little longer.
Owen can fix up a wound like this in no time!
The leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
had the power to kill all
the people in our kingdom
even without the help of the magic stones.
He has another goal.
Something terrifying might
happen to this kingdom...
I'm sorry I let him steal the magic stones.
I am unworthy of being Wizard King...
The hell are you talking about?!
You saved this damn kingdom!
Lord Julius... Let us make it in time.
I'm sure Marx will be angry
that I let this happen...
It's a pity that I can't be there
when Fuegoleon wakes up...
Yami... There's so much I still
wanted to talk to you about...
You can't be serious! Who the
hell said you could leave?
I'm not letting that happen! I still...
I hear he's not from this kingdom.
Apparently he's a castaway from some foreign
country who lives on the coast by himself.
I wish he'd just leave the country.
Wow! That's dark magic, isn't it?!
That's amazing! I've never seen that before!
Hey, hey, hey! Let me
get a better look at it!
No. Who the heck are you, old man?
Old...? Oh, but I'm not suspicious at all!
I'm just a Magic Knights Captain who
was wandering around in disguise.
What's a Magic Knight?
Huh? You don't know?!
Hmm...
Well, why not come see for yourself?
I'm sure you've got potential.
This is how you write your
name in our kingdom.
Seriously? I can't learn to write
wormy-looking letters like that.
Oh, don't be like that! Let's practice!
I don't wanna.
Huh? Um, if you learn to write it,
I'll treat you to dinner.
I'll do it.
Huh?
You've only just joined, but your
performance never fails to amaze me.
Just make sure you don't go too crazy.
We've been getting some complaints...
Hey, the enemy's here. There's a swarm of them.
Let's go, Yami.
Just don't go too crazy.
Yeah, he's definitely not listening.
And starting today, you are the Captain of
the Magic Knights Squad, the Black Bulls.
Congratulations, Yami.
Yami...
I leave the rest to you...
You got it.
I'm so happy that I got to see so
many different kinds of magic...
I'm so happy that I got to meet so
many different kinds of people...
Julius...
We'll protect...
this kingdom!
I hope everyone is okay in there.
It's been a few hours since I activated
this spatial jamming spell.
It's becoming difficult to
stay in this position.
But there's no time for complaining!
Everyone is risking their lives
fighting the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
For the future of the Clover Kingdom.
Please do your best in there.
Look over there!
That's...
A tremendous amount of mana!
That's the center of the hideout.
Everyone, please be careful!
I don't feel like I'd lose to anyone right now!
Yeah, yeah! Go, go, Yuno!
What is this?
Is that... a person?
This mana...
I-It's so overwhelming...
Once I set this final magic stone,
the tree of life monument will become
the guide that will awaken our true power.
Yes...
This day has finally come, Master Licht.
Now we, who have been chosen by the mana,
will have a tremendous amount
of magic awaken in us, right?
I'll show those Magic Knight bastards
my true power the next time I see them!
If we magnify our magic powers even
more with my dark magic items,
we might be invincible!
Then we can sweep up Asta, and I can
run all the experiments I want on him!
Silence. The magic
we're about to acquire
is to be used only for the creation
of a new kingdom by Master Licht.
If we hadn't met Master Licht...
Our very existence would've been disavowed
and scorned, and we would've
continued living alone.
But Master Licht welcomed us
into the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
All I want is to serve Master
Licht and be of some use to him.
Damn! You're so annoying,
you goody two-shoes.
But it sounds like we'll be able to raise hell
even more now, so I guess I'll follow you.
I'll help you out even
more with my experiments!
Everyone, you've done amazing work so far.
I thank you.
I'm very proud of all of you.
The time to make our long-cherished
dream come true is finally here.
Let us be reborn in our true forms
and create our own country.
Yes...
What I've said up to this point
has been the words of the Eye of
the Midnight Sun's leader, Licht.
Huh?
And from here on out,
I'll say what I really think.
All of you are greedy and selfish.
You have no qualms about harming others,
although you're terribly
sensitive to your own pain.
You envy, hate, and discriminate
against other humans for
the most trivial reasons.
You justify your own weaknesses
by thoroughly idolizing something.
Everything... Every last thing is for
the sake of your own filthy selves!
You humans truly are selfish, hopeless,
foolish, and ugly creatures.
Master Licht?
What the hell are you talking about?
This is goodbye for all of you.
You will serve as the foundation
of the resurrection.
Huh? What's that light?
What is that? It's coming from the boonies.
What's...
Looks like it's begun.
Begun?
His magic power suddenly skyrocketed...
Hey, this isn't good.
We're going to regain our true
forms... and our true power.
Wh-What's going on?
This terrifying magic power...
It doesn't belong to a human being!
E-Everyone... We should all leave for—
Yuno?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Studying
Studying.
What does this say, Yami?
I dunno.
What about this?
Then...
I'm telling you, I can't learn all this.
Don't underestimate how terrible
I am at remembering things!
Yami, you shouldn't set limits for yourself.
You may think it's impossible right now,
but as long as you believe,
you can surpass your limits.
One day, I'm going to make this kingdom
a place where your magic, status,
and where you were born don't matter.
A place where we can all smile together.
It might sound like a dream,
but I believe that it's possible.
Surpass my limits...
How do you write that?
Feeling motivated now?
Then here's your last question!
What's this letter?
Left.
This isn't a vision test.
We walked for many months and years
consumed by sadness and loneliness.
But now, that comes to an end.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 95: "Reincarnation."
Page 95
Reincarnation
We shall destroy the humans!