This is a businessman's town. I snuck in somehow by graduating from a state college.
I get my ass kicked by my superiors.
But you yearn to be like that just to get by in this place.
The city of winter, where I live.
But all that seems far away.
All that's in front of me is the azure of the South China Sea,
The clamoring wind,
And...
All right Mr. Japanese, I'm going to ask you again.
The one package you got from Asahi Industries in Tokyo.
The one you're in charge of until you hand it over to the chief in Borneo. This is it, right?
Yeah.
But what I want to ask is...
That's it.
That's everything we were going to ask you.
Dutch, this is a pain in the ass.
Shoot him in his knees.
He'll start singing like a bird.
There's no need.
That one disk is more than enough for the payment.
Payment, huh?
Dutch.
Hey Dutch.
Are you through yet?
There's someone heading straight for us from Supick.
It's probably a scout from the Filipino Navy.
Don't panic Benny-Boy, everything's taken care of.
Start the engines.
OK, gentlemen!
We're going to disperse and then you'll be free.
But the deal's off if anyone decides to come after us.
What you see there is a torpedo launcher.
If you don't want to be blown out of the water, then stay still for the next half hour.
Then you will be free.
We're saved.
What are you getting relaxed over?
You're coming with us.
Dipshit.
You're joking.
You're joking, right?
Shut up and walk.
You're joking, right?!
Japan is getting further away.
Black Lagoon to Balalaika.
Can you hear me?
Just fine.
How is the target?
Of course I have it.
Smart jobs are lovely, Dutch.
The trade-off goes as planned.
Yes, just as promised.
Connect me to Tokyo.
How about an explanation,
Investigational Department Chief Kageyama?
About the case we have been informed about.
Let me explain the situation to you further.
Today at 4pm the Burgenbiria Trade Company contacted us...
...regarding the negotiations for the disk stolen from the Meramarsia.
Who are they?
The Russian Mafia.
The front for the group that aims to take top position after displacing the Chinese Mafia from Southeast Asia.
What are they after specifically? Money?
Most likely the route to Southeast Asia where the barter is going to take place.
They wish to take part in some of our more unsavory trade routes.
Blackmail.
It's shameful, having something to be blackmailed about.
But they do not seem to know what's really on the disk.
If they find out it will be the worst scandal since the founding of Asahi Industries.
Indeed.
A report from Jakarta has just arrived.
According to a local Chinese merchant, the Russian Mafia has yet to receive the disk.
The disk is still in the hands of the pirates that attacked the Meramarsia.
This is our chance.
We can't trust the word of the Mafia.
We must take the disk before it reaches them.
Before it reaches them? How?
I understand. The board will leave this matter in your hands.
Choosing what actions to take will also be your responsibility.
Revy, what do you plan on doing with the hostage? Well?
You don't get it.
You don't get it, Dutch.
Think about it!
This job is twenty grand! Only twenty grand!
What's so wrong about collecting a bonus with a ransom?
You're being simple-minded.
You want to be killed, Benny?!
Not really.
Who's going to negotiate with Japan? You?
Do you have their phone number?
How about a bank account to accept the ransom?
Fine then!
We'll just kill his ass and throw him in the ocean!
Stop!
Idiot! Don't damage the ship!
Shut up!
Dutch. Dutch, I get it.
Get what?
I get it, so let me go.
OK, Revy.
Let's play it cool.
Tch.
I'm alive. I don't know why, but I'm alive.
All right, all right. Let's go topside for a smoke.
What's going to happen to me?
We'll contact your company somehow and set up a trade.
A ransom, huh? This'll go on my permanent record.
But we have our own priorities.
Getting the disk to the client comes first.
So there's a client.
We're just delivery boys.
We brush up against the law from time to time, so we can eat.
But that's business.
I guess this is what they call the Stockholm Syndrome.
At this moment, I feel like this big guy next to me is the only one I can trust in this whole world.
What's your name?
Okajima.
Okajima Rokuro
What's the name of that employee?
It's Okajima, Director. Okajima Rokuro.
It is entirely the fault of my managerial skills.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was only informed recently, sir.
And because there were no other employees we could trust with vital information,
there was some time lost in communication.
That's enough.
Do you have an opinion, Kageyama-kun?
Our company is in a crisis.
We cannot accept any more delays.
The E.O. Company, with whom we've made a secret contract, have already sent their mercenaries.
Well, it was your responsibility.
Still, I feel bad for this employee. What's his name?
It's Okajima, Director. Okajima Rokuro.
Let's go, Rock.
Rock?
I think he means you.
So let's go.
Go where?
Somewhere to get a drink.
Don't you want to come?
But I thought I was a hostage?
Let's go.
Wait! I'm coming too!
But where on Earth is this?
I don't understand.
Why is there a pistol on every table?
Is this a Western movie bar, at the end of the World?
Not a bad analogy.
This place was started by the losers of the Vietnam War.
They started taking in deserters too and before we knew it, it went to hell.
Hookers, junkies, mercs, killers...
Irredeemable criminals.
Do you dislike it?
Japanese pubs...
I love those unguarded smiles.
Places like this...
Shut up or I'll throw you out onto the beach. Damn it.
I'm not suited for fighting.
You have that kind of face.
Benny, I'm going to make a call.
He's a weird guy.
After being around him for two years all I know is that he's tough, intelligent and weird.
Give up on trying to understand him.
Thanks.
You seem different.
Where were you before?
A college in Florida.
Playing with fire pissed off the Mafia and the FBI.
Then...
I saved his ass before he was used as a weight in a suitcase.
Stop this worthless storytelling.
You're not old enough to be reminiscing about the past.
One for you, one for me.
We came all the way here for a drink,
let's talk about something a littler cooler, Mr. Japanese.
This is?
Beer's as good as piss.
No matter how much you drink, you don't get drunk.
If you're a man you'll drink rum.
But if... you're a wuss who can't even take a challenge from a woman...
I won't force you.
But I'll make you wear a skirt, put on ribbons and take you to a dance party.
I hate chugging down drinks.
But...
We're forced to drink at company socials. Don't mock a Japanese businessman!
You...
Hey, bartender.
Bring all the Bacardi you've got!
Geez, I thought you didn't like fighting.
I see.
That's not good. Go on.
I didn't trust Asahi Industries' response.
So I left out bait, and a Chinese rat bit. I'm talking to it now.
Who's on the move?
Wait a moment.
Say you're owner's name loudly.
Shinginan's Wan Taikei!
Wan Taikei sent an assassin to get you!
He sent an assassin to Roanapur!
Hear that?
Yeah. Not good.
Tell me the number and affiliation of those soldiers. Hurry, we're busy.
Guys from Extra Order, a mercenary contracting agency! I don't know how many there are!
The E.O. Company scouts experienced war junkies.
Just our luck.
For god's sake.
Let's start.
OK, boys.
It's party time.
Give any runners extra assholes.
Make sure there are only corpses when we're done.
Revy, if they are your friends then you deal with them.
I don't know them.
You've bulletproofed the bar.
It can handle up to a .50 caliber.
Revy!
I'm alive.
Benny!
Miraculously, I'm alive.
How about Rock?
Dead!
People are dead!
I finally graduated a state college and got into a good company!
This isn't fair!
Don't cry, dipshit.
You've got to enjoy life.
Or you'll end up wasting it.
Revy! Show them why you're named Two-Hands!
Check it out.
I thought I heard a voice.
I hate survivors.
He says good things.
Got 'em, Dutch!
Don't come back here!
You're a nuisance.
How many times have you destroyed my shop?!
You owe me for all of this!
Or I'll weld your asshole shut and make you a new one on your head!
Got it.
Dutch!
She's...
...smiling.
Sorry.
I think, at this rate, trading you is out of the question.
What's going to happen to me?
Well, we didn't make any plans to begin with.
What if we just part ways here?
That's not fair!
I'm going to die! Take me with you!
Fine then.
Just don't pull our leg.
Revy, we're leaving!
Got it!
Get in!
Here you go, you war junkies!
Dutch, Bao was so pissed he looked like a steaming pot.
Unless we pay him back he's going to weld our assholes.
Scary. Makes me want to cry.
What the hell is this?
Is this a movie?
Don't be stupid.
This is a lot more entertaining than Hollywood.
Captain, 16 dead, 8 wounded.
I'm sorry sir. We thought they were punks and underestimated them.
Shutorm, they're not punks.
They're somebodies we can go after.
All we had to shoot at were old men and brats in Liberia.
Too slow and no fight left in them.
But these guys are full of fight.
I've been waiting for this.
If we stay at this speed we'll be at the Balawan Port by daybreak.
We'll meet Balalaika there.
So... Rock,
Benny is getting in touch with your company.
You can pull it off if you try, eh?
If negotiations don't go well, we're going to have to leave you around Malaya. Sorry.
There are bandits all around, but you shouldn't die immediately. OK?
What? You bring me this far and you're going to let me die?!
What is this?! After dragging me all over the place,
at least take me somewhere safe!
Don't get so excited.
First you cry then you want to use us like a taxi?
All right then.
I can show you what color your brain is.
Wait.
We're connected.
We're using an Assault Dial so it's secure.
Rock, it's your boss, Kageyama-san.
Department Chief! It's Okajima, I'm very sorry.
About the disk...
Don't worry about that anymore.
That disk no longer exists.
I don't think I understand.
Because of the situation, I'll tell you the truth.
Don't tell anyone else.
It's hard to explain, but we were hired to help develop nuclear capabilities for a certain country.
The disk contained the plans.
It is troublesome...
Nukes in this day and age.
And war...
Eventually I will be at the top and do something about this,
but this can't be made public.
Okajima-kun, for the sake of the 50,000 employees of Asahi Industries, disappear into the South China Sea.
You'll be promoted to chief and we won't treat you badly.
And the president and everyone under him will be at your funeral.
The professional ruffians should almost be there.
What's my equipment status?
Fully equipped, Captain.
Rockets and machine guns, the more you shoot the more the invoice will be.
The Japanese are very generous.
Let's go!
You were ditched pretty easily.
I sympathize, though.
And the ransom bonus is all gone.
But is that enough to make you sick?
Leave me alone.
Revy?
Are you on the deck?
Yeah.
There's something coming straight at us over the ocean, but it's not a boat, it's too fast.
At 3 hours 5 minutes. Can you see anything?
A low-altitude assault gunship!
God damn it!
An assault helicopter?!
You see them?
I don't need to see them, I can smell them.
Damn them. Using that to kill me.
Rock! Hold this!
A gun?! Don't make me hold this!
It won't be more than a comfort, though.
He's coming. He's on our ass.
Not good, not good. This isn't good.
He's shooting!
I know, it's not good, Dutch.
Hit it!
Shoot it down!
Shut up!
You try it, dipshit Rock!
You're hiding under a torpedo launcher.
Don't get blown up.
Rock you bastard!
I'm done with you guys.
I'm getting off here.
You impotent son of a bitch!
You're gonna run away?!
Why do I need to suffer like this?
Alright, we're just gonna watch from up high.
But Captain, we can turn them into mincemeat now.
You don't get it.
From their heads to their tails, they're in my trap.
Don't you want to laugh at them while they cry, howl and piss themselves?
Damn it!
You do and say whatever you want to me!
Everyone, even the Department Chief...
Why do I need to suffer?!
I'm already dead.
You told me that.