It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
As a plan to get a strategic upper
hand against the Clover Kingdom,
the Diamond Kingdom attacked
the border town of Kiten.
But the Golden Dawn arrived
there before anyone else
and faced off with the Diamond army,
quelling the situation.
Wind Magic: Swift White Bow.
I thought I saw a familiar little speck.
What are you doing here, Asta?
The fact that you're so beat up means...
You got stronger again, didn't you?
Huh?
I'm not losing to you, Asta.
Look who's talking! You got
crazy strong, too, you jerk!
I'm not gonna lose either, Yuno!
Behind the Mask
Your arm... Is it okay?
Yeah, I'm fine!
See? No problem at all!
I see. It looks like you're
as reckless as ever.
Y-Yuno's actually smiling?
I think you got a little taller
since I last saw you, Yuno.
What the heck? He always acts
apathetic when he's with me!
Oh, yeah. I might've grown
four or five centimeters.
How do you keep getting taller so easily?!
Damn it! I'm not gonna lose!
I'm gonna get 20 centimeters taller
by tomorrow and look down on you!
Not a chance.
What are you doing, Yuno?!
Yuno, who the heck is this twerp?!
You're acting all apathetic again!
What the heck is that fussy,
mysterious little critter?
Is that the Sylph I've heard so much about?
I've never seen Yuno make that face!
Is this the power of the Sylph?!
Tell me! Who is this mummified shrimp?!
Hey, you're small, too!
He's a guy I used to live with.
Y-Y-Y-You...
Y-You lived with him?
We would eat together, study together...
...sleep in the same bed together,
and even bathe together.
Slept in the same bed... and even bathed...?
Sneaky, sneaky, sneaky, sneaky...
U-Um...
It's been a while!
Um, thank you so much for
saving my meal last time.
Are you all better now?
Oh, you're the girl from back then...
From the Black Bulls.
Please enjoy this after-battle snack!
Thanks.
I'll even thrown in some extra dragees.
Now who's this insolent child?
She's clearly head over heels for Yuno.
I'm Charmy. May I call you "Yuno"?
Sure.
La!
This is good.
La, la!
But my Sylph senses are telling me that
she doesn't actually pose a threat.
I'm sorry for pushing you
down so suddenly back then.
La...
Oh, don't worry about that! It's just
something that did indeed happen!
P-Push... P-Pushed down?!
La?!
Why, you... You must've used some
sneaky spell to seduce Yuno!
You snot-nosed little brat!
La? What's this creature?
Are you yummy?
Miz Charmy! She's a spirit!
Don't eat her!
What's with you people?!
Yuno belongs to me, dang it!
"Snot-nosed little brat"?
I can't let that slide.
I'm nineteen!
I'm older than Yuno and
rather sophisticated, too!
My sexiness doesn't need
any magical enhancement!
Sexy?! You're built like a grade-schooler,
besides your giant forehead!
La?! Oh, you did not just go there!
You're also built like a grade-schooler
and have a giant forehead!
What did you say?! I'll show you
what happens when you cross a Sylph!
You insolent little brat!
I'll fry you up and eat you!
La!
Come back here, you little insect!
Calm down, Miz Charmy!
Bell, that's enough.
Hup.
Hey, looks like you're having fun.
Let me join in.
Finral.
Who's that?
This is my senior from
the Black Bulls, Finral.
You guys haven't met before?
Nope.
It's fine. Not like I'd catch the
eye of an elite from the Golden—
What's this?
Well, well... If it isn't my big brother.
It's been so long! I never
dreamed I'd run into you here.
Langris...
Who's that?
What's the black sheep of our family,
who can barely even fight,
even doing on the battlefield?
Finral, who's that rude little twerp?!
He's my little brother.
Huh?
That's the Vice Captain of the
Golden Dawn, Langris Vaude.
Golden Dawn Vice Captain
Langris Vaude
What? Vice captain?!
Are you still acting as the
Black Bulls' pack mule, Finral?
It looks like I'll have to be the next head
of the Vaude family,
since you're such a loser.
Get over yourself!
Finral's awesome!
At the Underwater Temple,
it was only because I had Finral's help
that we were able to defeat the enemy!
Wow! You mean you were actually
useful for once in your life?
More importantly, how can you talk to
your big brother like that, you punk?!
How dare you address the Vice Captain
of the Golden Dawn like that?
Wh-What did you say?!
It's okay, Asta. He's only telling the truth.
But...
It's fine.
We've already cleaned up
most of the enemies...
Or rather, our captain dealt
with most of them himself.
The Bulls aren't needed here anymore.
And anyway...
When did the Black Bulls
become a daycare center?
Looking after two children must be rough.
Aren't you embarrassed at having
to babysit those two rugrats?
Who're you calling a rugrat?!
I'll show you the charms of a mature woman!
I'm not a little kid, damn it!
Langris, you can insult me
to your heart's content.
Hmph.
But... don't you dare insult the
members of my Black Bulls!
Wow. Who knew you could look so scary?
You little brat...
On the honor of the Eight Shining Generals,
I'm taking your head back home with me!
Oh, dear... You're still alive?
Not only that, but at this rate,
my spatial magic is going
to hit those civilians.
You can't lay a finger on me, Magic Knights!
Save us!
I don't have time to hesitate.
Oh, well. They'll just have to be noble
sacrifices for the sake of our country.
Hold it!
How can you even think about
abandoning our citizens?!
We're Magic Knights!
And if this goes on, we'll just
end up with even more victims!
Shut up! I'm not gonna abandon anyone!
Finral! Miz Charmy!
Right!
Roger!
Just you watch, Yuno!
Let's see what you've got.
What can you possibly do
in the condition you're in?
Talk about a lively retreat...
Cotton Creation Magic: Fluffy Sheep Cushion!
Who the hell are you?!
Stay out of this, brat!
Spatial magic?
Wh-What?! My magic disappeared!
What did you do, you brat?!
Looks like I owe you one, Yuno.
Your fighting style's
as insane as ever, Asta.
Yuno's smiling again! Hmph!
Langris...
You're right. I can't beat you.
But...
The Black Bulls will beat the Golden Dawn!
Yeah!
Man, your world tree magic
is as impressive as ever.
Exactly what are you trying to say?
I'm someone who believes his gut instincts.
Vangeance...
Could you take off that mask?
This isn't a face that most
people would want to see.
What? Are you, like, super ugly
under there or something?
Don't worry. I promise I won't laugh.
I know what this is, Yami.
You suspect that I may be the leader of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun, don't you?
Frankly, yeah.
His light magic and your world
tree magic are obviously different,
but something's really bugging me.
Their builds, their voices, and more
than anything, their ki feels the same.
But...
I think it's been about ten
years since I first met you.
Indeed.
We met on the battlefield, and after that,
we fought together from time to time.
Then we became captains at the same time.
Nozel's braid shook like
crazy when that happened.
It's not like we're best buds or anything,
but we go back pretty far, don't we?
I feel something similar in you...
So just let me see your face, all right?
Very well.
That's one hell of a scar.
Did you get it on the battlefield?
No, I was born with it.
They called me a cursed child.
A cursed child?
Even magic couldn't fix this scar.
It creeped out the people around me,
and they came to fear me.
I was the illegitimate
child of a certain noble.
I lived in the Forsaken Realm
until I was eight.
But following the loss of that noble's heir,
I was taken in as an aristocrat.
Fortunately, I had great magical power,
and my world tree magic was viewed with awe.
But even there, they loathed my face.
In addition, my foster mother
brutally abused me.
It was a hellish childhood.
You sure had it rough, didn't you?
But in the midst of all that,
I met Master Julius.
He didn't care about my appearance.
All he saw was my power.
Little boy, what kind of magic is that?
I-It's world tree magic, sir.
World tree magic?! How sublime and majestic!
That's terrific!
Most of all... It's as though your
kindness is trying to protect everything.
What wonderful magic!
You should definitely join the Magic Knights!
Do you not want to?
N-No! I would love to...
I never even thought about
joining the Magic Knights.
But my face...
It's nothing to worry about.
Huh?
It really is nothing to worry about,
but if you are so worried about it...
In that case...
I'll give you this mask!
Master Julius, this is so... tacky.
What?! But it's my best work!
I was happy.
I wanted to pledge my
grimoire to his service.
This story sounds pretty familiar.
The lines of his face also look like Licht's.
But I can't sense the slightest
trace of magic from his scar.
He doesn't seem to be doing anything tricky
with magic or showing me an illusion.
And more than anything...
His ki tells me he's not lying.
I guess this was just some odd coincidence.
Sorry about that.
No... I'm glad I was able to tell you
and show you things as they really are.
Thank you, Yami.
I see.
Captain Vangeance! Captain Vangeance!
The Diamonds have begun to retreat.
Understood. There's no need to
pursue those who are fleeing.
Could you concentrate on helping the injured?
Understood, sir.
Shall we go, too? There are
plenty of captives.
It's going to be a pain
transporting them all.
Yeah.
Oh, if we're transporting captives,
I brought some useful guys along.
Let's work 'em to the bone.
Within reason, of course.
I wonder if a cute girl is talking about me.
Looks like the fighting has calmed down,
so why don't we meet up with Yami?
Good idea.
La?! Already?
Well, see ya, Yuno.
Yeah, see you, Asta. Don't eat
stuff you find lying on the ground.
Like I'd do that! I mean, I used to, but...
Um, c-could I maybe ask for your address?
Stay away from Yuno, you thieving raccoon!
La! Scales!
Your scales are getting in my eyes!
La! No way!
I'm gonna fry you up!
Come back here!
Get away from me!
You little insect!
La?
La! I'm definitely going
to fry you up next time!
I know it's too late to take it back now,
but the worst squad just picked
a fight with the best squad!
Does your stomach hurt, Finral?
I wanna hurry up and practice with my sword!
I wanted to talk with Yuno more!
I'm going to eat my sorrows away!
You guys are way too laid-back! I mean,
I'm the one who picked the fight, but...
Now, now. Here, eat this. Nomity noms.
Hey, it's good.
Honestly, what a vulgar bunch.
You should be more careful about
who you associate with, Yuno.
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with them?
Why?
I've never thought that, not even once.
I'm proud of Asta, and he's my rival.
Rival? That guy?
Rival in what? Are you guys
competing for something?
Yeah...
By the way, Asta, was it okay to
just leave so abruptly like that?
That handsome guy is your
old friend, isn't he?
It's fine!
We'll meet on some other battlefield, anyway.
Because...
...we're both working to
become the Wizard King!
The Wizard King?!
You really aren't embarrassed
to say that at all, are you?!
Maybe you peasants don't
even feel embarrassment.
I'd expect no less from the great peasant
who was chosen by the four-leaf grimoire!
What's your problem?! I won't
allow you to make fun of Yuno—
There's no rule that says commoners
can't become the Wizard King.
Huh?
So first, I'll become the
Captain of the Golden Dawn.
I see. Meaning you're completely
ignoring my existence as vice captain.
Yuno, things are taken care of over here.
All the wounded are taken care of, too.
What in the world happened?
The Diamond forces have retreated,
and we've taken a number of captives.
Kiten was successfully defended.
Excellent work.
Please see to the repair
of the damaged buildings
and set up shelters immediately.
Yes, sir.
Now, then... I don't think that was
a serious attempt by the Diamonds
to invade our kingdom.
So what were they after?
I see... The Sylph, eh?
Offensive spatial magic...
Oh, and world tree magic
that uses others' magic.
I guess the rusty old generals of the
previous era had their useful moments,
but from here on out, this era belongs
to us Mage Warriors, the new generals!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Together!
T-Together!
Is that the Sylph I've heard so much about?
I've never seen Yuno make that face!
Is this the power of the Sylph?!
He's a guy I used to live with.
What?!
You can't be serious.
You guys slept together?!
Asta, hey. You can't be serious...
You guys ate together?!
Go!
You can't be serious...
You guys bathed together?!
What's wrong with her?
No idea.
Thank goodness.
I didn't know what I was
going to do if Vangeance
was actually Licht from
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Black Clover, Page 54: "Never Again."
Page 54
Never Again
I know. I'll get him a hyottoko
mask from my homeland.