It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
When he was younger,
Yami was on a journey to train,
when the head of a little village asked him
to protect it some magical bandits.
He ended up battling the bandits,
and during that battle...
Yami, was it?
I'm counting on you to watch my back.
Yami encountered Vangeance,
who was nearby on another mission.
First, I'm going to become a
Magic Knights Squad captain...
Looks like the challenge is on.
Let's see who can do it first.
And all kinds of stuff happened after that.
A few years later,
Julius became the Wizard King,
and both the golden weird mask guy and I
The Wizard King's Attendant
Marx Francois
were appointed Vice Captains
of the Gray Deer.
Vice Captain of the Gray Deer
William Vangeance
Yami Sukehiro
Then, one day...
28th Wizard King
Julius Novachrono
Hey! Thanks for coming.
Welcome!
You don't have to be so formal with us.
I agree.
I heard you did amazing work exploring
that dungeon the other day.
It was nothing.
I heard you saved all the
knights who were caught
by the trap spell with your magic.
I wish I could've seen that magic!
Oh, I'll give you the stars for
that next time. Don't worry.
I'm honored. Thank you very much.
I heard you were absolutely fierce in
the defensive battle at Kuka Village.
I heard you split the giant soldier that the
enemy created using rock magic in two.
Yeah, that was nothing...
Actually, it was everything!
You're going to give me some stars, too, right?
Of course! I'm sure your
captain is very proud.
Sir, it's about time.
Oh, right. Sorry to have you
stop by when you're so busy.
There's a job that I'd like
you two to take on.
Bandits?
Yeah, they're causing trouble all over.
Would you two catch them for me?
Of course, sir.
The Magic Knights live to serve and
protect the people of the Clover Kingdom.
We will happily accept this mission.
But...
Why are you just asking the two of us?
Well, it's possible that
someone from the Magic Knights
is aiding the bandits.
Well, can't say I'm surprised.
I don't think they're ordinary bandits.
They're very organized and even
have some ancient magic items.
Pretty powerful ones, at that.
It may be that someone is providing them
with magic items that we found in dungeons.
I see. So that's why you want us.
If all the Magic Knights were assigned
to this, evidence may be destroyed,
and the guilty party may disappear.
That's why we've been assigned
to this secret mission.
Exactly.
Say, Julius. What are you going to
do if one of us is that traitor?
We might just let the bandits escape.
Well, that would be a problem.
But I think I know you
two pretty well by now.
I've known you both since before
you even joined the Magic Knights.
That's why I trust you.
But if you two end up betraying me,
I guess there's not much I can do.
You always were a cunning old dude.
Well, I'll be counting on both of you.
Yes, sir.
Heart Kingdom
Spade Kingdom
Forsaken Realm
Common Realm
Noble Realm
Rayaka
Nean
Kikka
Raquey
Kiten
Diamond Kingdom
Heart
Kingdom
Spade Kingdom
Forsaken Realm
Common Realm
Noble Realm
Rayaka
Nean
Kikka
Raquey
Kiten
Diamond
Kingdom
I've marked the towns and villages that
have been attacked by the bandits.
I see... So they're showing up
in unexpected places.
Must be so people won't figure
out where they'll show up next.
Nean
Common Realm
Kikka
I've sent messages to the Magic Knights
in these areas to be on their guard,
but that information
might've also been leaked.
The bandits keep appearing in places
that aren't heavily guarded.
Heart Kingdom
We're gonna have to figure out
where they'll pop up next,
but that'll be tough to do.
No, it's actually quite simple.
Huh?
Forsaken Realm
Common Realm
Noble Realm
Rayaka
Nean
Kikka
Raquey
First, we can rule out any place
that's already been attacked.
Spade Kingdom
Diamond
Kingdom
The next likely targets will probably be
somewhere a treasure's been found lately,
or somewhere near a harvest.
A bountiful one, specifically.
Even then, that's more than
ten or twenty places.
We can probably rule out places that
are near the sites of attacks, too.
They'll probably assume that such places
will be on alert and harder to attack.
Even then...
You think the two of us can't
cover so many locations, right?
I know. That's why...
Nean
Common Realm
Kikka
Here, and here...
And this village.
Could you send out Magic Knights
to these locations to be on
high alert for these bandits?
Why, though? If someone's leaking,
there'd be no point—
I see!
You want to take advantage of the fact
that someone is leaking information.
Yes. They'll probably avoid places that
are being guarded by the Magic Knights.
They'll prioritize places that
aren't being guarded by the Knights.
I-I knew that, duh...
I was just testing you.
Which means the places they're
probably going to go after
will be the town of Aymaia or Zocodany Village.
Heart
Kingdom
Yami and Vangeance
How are things looking over there, Yami?
Nothing suspicious so far.
Zocodany Village
It appears that an ancient magic item
was found in a cave near
Zocodany Village recently.
That item is being regarded
as the village's treasure and is on
display at the village elder's home.
Only a handful of Magic Knights
would know about that at this point.
It's too early for the bandits
to show up for that treasure.
So if they show up in
search of that treasure,
it'll be clear that there's
a traitor within our ranks.
Yeah. How are thing looking in Aymaia?
Nothing suspicious here, either.
They just finished harvesting, and they're
preparing for their harvest festival.
The Town of Aymaia
Apparently, their harvest
was very good this year.
I'm sure the bandits would
love to get their hands on it.
Just to remind you...
No matter where the bandits show up,
don't handle them alone.
We'll wait until we contact the other
and they arrive to fight.
Got it?
Yeah, yeah.
You better not go back on that just so
you can get all the stars for yourself.
I won't.
I'll contact you again if I see anything.
Jeez...
They actually showed up.
Hey, they're here, masked weirdo.
You hear me? Hey!
What the hell is going on?
This thing was working fine earlier.
This ki...
Are they blocking the flow of mana?
Looks like they're somehow
able to block comms.
Guess they aren't ordinary bandits after all.
Must be a traitor from the Magic Knights...
I'm gonna have to hunt them down.
Looks like there are thirty...
no, more than that.
There are probably at least fifty.
No matter where the bandits show up,
don't handle them alone.
We'll wait until we contact the other...
Well, I can't get a hold of you,
so what the hell am I supposed to do?
I'm just gonna have to go on my own!
I'll cut them down before
they get to the village.
Dark Cloaked...
Black Blade!
An enemy attack! Scatter!
Who the hell are you?!
A Magic Knight?
You've got some nerve, facing us alone!
You're gonna regret that!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
That should take care
of about half of them...
Are you the boss?
I think I've seen you before.
You don't look like a Magic Knight, though.
You're the guy from that one time.
What one time?
A few years ago, you got in the way of
us plundering that crummy little village.
Guess I get to repay you for
that sooner than I thought.
A few years ago?
Hey! You're the dude from that one time!
I see now...
Putting the guy's horrible
fashion sense aside,
his magic powers aren't too impressive,
but that staff is bad news.
Was that a treasure someone
found in a dungeon?
Don't think I'm the same as before!
Hey, who gave you that staff?
If you want to know,
you'll have to defeat me first!
Take this!
Damn you guys for wasting my time.
Now, then...
Let's have you spill who
the hell gave you this staff.
Five... four... three...
W-Wait! I'll tell you!
Th-The truth is...
Stay in your home!
Not another step, Magic Knight!
If you move, this old bat is gonna get it!
I'm gonna pay you back a millionfold!
How? You think your buddies
stand a chance against me?
No, they probably don't.
But...
Wha—
This magic—
It's a type of earth magic spell,
Witch Hunter Claws,
you see.
Likewise,
that's a binding spell
called Sheep Horn Snag.
I've seen you guys before.
You're Goht from the Crimson Lion Kings
and Mohl from the Silver Eagles.
Silver Eagles Squad Member
Mohl
Crimson Lion Kings Squad Member
Goht
Guess we actually had two
traitors instead of one.
So you were the ones giving these bandits
magic items and information,
and having them attack the villages.
There's no use in struggling.
No man can break through that.
You guys are a disgrace to the Magic Knights!
You're the foreigner named Yami Sukehiro
that the Wizard King picked up, aren't you?
I thought the Wizard King was up to
something. So this is what it was.
Which means that the
Wizard King's order to protect
the villages in the area was a diversion
to pinpoint where we'd attack next.
I guess we completely fell for it.
Lord Goht and Lord Mohl,
you're amazing for figuring out their plan!
You go hurry up and find their treasure.
Y-Y-Yes, sir.
Uh, it was at the village elder's house,
right? Hey, take me there.
O-Okay...
You men, follow me!
Yes, sir!
The Magic Knights exist to serve and
protect the people of the Clover Kingdom!
Yet you bastards...
We'll tell the Wizard King
that we found you after you'd
been defeated by the bandits.
Don't think I'll go down that easily!
I'll pay you back a millionfold!
Oh, my. Only a weakling would
say something like that.
Goodbye now.
How long do you think he can hold out?
Just give it up already.
Like I'd give up that easily!
Not yet... I'm not done yet!
I think you're just about at your limit.
Who the hell cares about limits?
I'll just surpass them! Right here, right now!
Dracaena Formation.
Are you all right?
Took you long enough!
I'll have you know that I hurried over.
When I wasn't able to get a hold of you,
I figured the bandits had
appeared in Zocodany.
Looks like I owe you one.
And I'm gonna pay it back quick, masked weirdo.
They're the ones behind all this.
Goht and Mohl... I see.
William Vangeance...
I guess you were following the
Wizard King's orders, too.
We'll just have to defeat you
along with Yami Sukehiro.
You bastard!
Attack of the Horn!
Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
I told you I'd pay you back
a billionfold, didn't I?
Please go easy on me.
Not bad.
Let's negotiate. Why not join us?
Join you?
Yes, it'll be quite fun.
That sounds tempting... But I'll pass.
I swore my loyalty to the
Wizard King, after all.
I see. That's unfortunate.
Looks like I already paid you back.
It truly is unfortunate
that there were traitors
among the Magic Knights.
Now, all that's left is...
Yeah.
I don't know who the hell
that is, but take him down!
I wasn't planning on interfering,
but I think I'm allowed
to have a little fun.
The hell?
Well done.
You were able to capture the traitors
as well as all of the bandits.
I mean... the bandits' boss was
out cold at the top of the tree.
I guess weirder things have happened.
Again, excellent work.
By the way...
Yami, Vangeance...
Considering everything you've done so far,
I'm appointing both of you
as captains of new squads.
You're making us...
...captains of new squads?
Will you accept my offer?
I guess the competition to see who can
become squad captain first ended in a draw.
Yes, but our true competition
still lies ahead.
Yeah.
I won't lose.
Neither will I.
I believe in both of you. Yami,
what kind of squad will you create?
What kind of squad? Let's see...
A squad where status, bloodlines,
and social standing don't matter.
I'll round up some outsiders and hooligans,
and create a place where they can belong.
Just like you did for me.
Sure. That sounds great!
I'll call them... Let's see...
I'll gather up a bunch of guys who all
have their own color, mix them all up,
and once their colors all mix together...
Black. The Black Hooligans?
Nah, let's go with bulls.
Okay, I'll call them the Black Bulls!
The Black Bulls...
That sounds perfect for you.
And you?
I will create the Golden Dawn.
The Golden...?
Yes. Creating the ultimate squad is
my way of repaying you, Lord Julius.
As the name suggests,
I will make a squad that will bring
a golden dawn to this world.
Even though the night is dark,
I will prove that the light will always shine,
and a golden dawn will come one day.
How cheesy can you be?
That sounds wonderful, too.
I look forward to it.
Starting today, you are the Captain of the
Golden Dawn. Congratulations, William.
Thank you, sir.
And starting today, you are the Captain of
the Magic Knights Squad, the Black Bulls.
Congratulations, Yami.
Looking forward to working with you, Goldie.
So there you have it.
Right...
What'd you think?
Um... I guess you went through a lot.
So, what were you trying to say?
Even if you stumble,
even if you think you might lose,
you'll be fine as long as you don't give up!
Don't ever give up in any situation!
Surpass your limits!
Then a path will always open up for you!
Quit being so depressed just because
you lost to your rival once!
Even if you lose 99 times, you just
have to win the next time!
I-I see... You should've just
said that in the first pla—
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Captain! You're going to crush my skull!
But Captain Yami's right!
There's no point in being depressed!
All right! I'm gonna catch
up to Yuno and surpass him!
Come to think of it,
shouldn't we be getting the results from
the Royal Knights Selection Exam soon?
O-Oh, yeah... I-I can't wait!
Come on, messenger owls!
The hell? That's no messenger owl.
I dunno who the hell you are,
but stop that racket!
Don't you know that this is the
home of the Black Bulls,
the Magic Knights Squad that Mister Yami—
Th-The heck?!
Y-You're Lady Sisgoleon!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Golden Weird Mask Guy!
Say, Golden Weird Mask Guy.
I'd rather you didn't call me that.
Then...
Baldie Weird Mask Guy.
I'd rather you didn't call me that, either.
Baldie Long Drawers Mask Guy!
Please stop.
Baldie Long Drawers Belly Warmer Mask Guy!
This doesn't even make sense anymore.
Baldie Long Drawers Belly Warmer
Tiny Mustache Mask Guy!
How long is this going to go on?
Baldie Long Drawers Belly
Warmer Tiny Mustache...
who wears his shirt and
socks backwards... Mask Guy?
No, really. How long?
How about Birthday Suit Mask Guy?
It's finally time to find out the results
of the Royal Knights Selection Exam!
I know for damn sure that I was chosen!
Who are you calling worried?!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 87:
"Formation of the Royal Knights."
Page 87
Formation of the Royal Knights
I'm fired up!