It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Licht and the other elves
headed to the Shadow Palace,
which lies between this
world and the next,
in order to complete the
elves' reincarnation.
Once the process is complete,
the souls of the humans being inhabited
by elves will be sent to the next world.
I'm sure you dumbasses can handle this!
Surpass your damn limits!
Yes, sir!
And so Yami and Jack followed
Licht and the elves,
while Asta and some of the Black
Bulls ended up fighting Gauche
and his sister Marie,
who had reincarnated as elves.
Meanwhile, Vanessa and the other
Black Bulls were taken to Glamour World
and struggled in a face-off with
the Captain of the Coral Peacocks,
Dorothy, who had reincarnated
as an elf, and her dream magic.
Everything that exists in Glamour World
will eventually get drowsy.
But Dorothy's dream magic has the
ability to make anything materialize,
and Sally uses that to their advantage.
What this world needs... is an
exit, exit, exit! Make one, please?
Hell yeah!
Meanwhile, Asta and the others struggled
against Marie's magic, which made anyone
who looked into her eyes unable to move.
But the Black Bulls worked
together to continue the fight!
I'm gonna stop you two, no matter what,
and turn you back into the
normal Gauche and Marie!
I'm going to save my friend!
Since I know that form's secret,
dealing with it won't be a problem.
It homes in on powerful magic, doesn't it?
M-My sword is reacting to the magic!
So just keep flying around...
Asta!
Humans Who Can Be Trusted
Hell yeah! Let's just take a
door and get the hell outta here!
Yeah!
Okay, get on this, la!
It's so fluffy and interesting!
Luck, pull the rest of us.
Roger!
Go!
You're not leaving.
That destiny avoidance thing is amazing,
no matter how many times I see it!
And it's bad for my heart,
no matter how many times it happens!
Go, go!
Just a little further!
Okay, we're here!
If I can't make them disappear,
I just have to seal them up.
Huh?
N... No...
Aw, and we were so close!
You're taking this way
too lightly, stupid Luck!
Damn it, we were almost out!
Exit! Exit, exit!
Give us another exit, damn it!
If she's concentrating that hard to close them,
we're screwed, exploding protozoan.
Look at this delicious meal...
That's your own damn cotton magic!
Charmy, wake up! If you fall asleep,
you'll never wake up again!
Oh, no... If we don't get out,
this might actually be the end for us.
Anything goes in the dream world...
Oh, I know! If anything goes,
let's just have her take care of this herself.
Huh? Herself?
The hell are you talking about, you mor—
Just shut up for a while, Magna, 'kay?
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Hey, I wanna ask you something.
If we did this, then that...
Oho! That sounds fun!
True, that's definitely worth a try!
La!
Hey! Talk louder, damn it!
You're making me even more tired!
If I said it any louder, she'd hear me.
So is there a good way to make this plan work?
Of course!
I don't know what you could
possibly be discussing,
but no matter what you try,
you can't escape this place.
You will all fall into
your eternal slumber here.
Okay! Now it's your turn, stupid Magna!
I don't know what the hell is going on, but...
Flame Magic: Time Bomb Explosive Scattershot!
Trying to hide from me in
this world? How futile.
Is this...
What we created isn't real, of course.
It's not like the stuff you make.
It's a doll made out of Charmy's
cotton and Vanessa's thread!
Then we used the exploding
protozoan's flames
to create a heat mirage and blur it.
It's just a fake version of you.
But for a brief moment...
...it must've crossed your mind.
The possibility that it
might be the real thing!
Because right now, just like when
I was reincarnated as an elf,
there are two souls connected
inside the same body!
So that mirage is probably making you
think of her, even if you don't want to...
Oh, no...
The real Dorothy Unsworth!
Hell yeah! The Captain of the
Coral Peacocks has arrived!
We couldn't ask for a better helper!
But I think she's asleep!
Come to think of it, I heard
that captain's always asleep.
Wait, don't tell me she's already
fallen into that eternal slumber...
She woke up!
Don't freak us out like that!
Also, hurry up! I can
barely keep my eyes open!
Are you the ones who summoned me here?
That was...
Fantastic, Black Bulls and Glasses Girl!
Captain of the Coral Peacocks
Dorothy Unsworth
Just leave the rest to me!
Your big sister is a captain, after all!
Holy crap, she's chipper!
So, how old are you, Big Sister?
You totally look younger than us.
Should you be asking that right now?
I mean, I'm curious, but...
I'm 27! I'm right at my peak!
She's older than me?! Oh, no!
My role as the "little cutie
who's actually older"!
Go to sleep within the depths
of my soul once more.
We've each finally found someone
we can share our dreams with...
So let's have a little fun!
Like I would ever play with a human!
Take that!
Whoa!
Holy crap!
I guess anything goes since
we're in the dream world!
I wanna research this so bad!
Drool... That shark looks so nummy.
Amazing... She's a match for her
elf counterpart in this battle.
This is our chance to recover some mana.
Charmy, get cooking!
Roger!
We'll make it out for sure this time!
Wait for us, guys!
I can't get to Gauche!
Not to mention...
And while you're at it...
Keep your eyes shut.
Oh, no! I'm—
See ya, brat.
Thanks, guys!
We gave some of our mana to Henry!
He's sucking away our mana
at an incredible speed!
Get... inside... quickly!
Comin' through!
What do I do? Right now, I can
only go black about 2.5 times!
I used it once before coming to the capital,
so next time, it'll come undone pretty fast!
Transformation Magic!
Magic Conversion: Mirrored Mini Black Bull!
Go!
Like it'd actually be that easy.
You didn't actually mirror the
parts that are expelling magic.
At this distance, I could...
This is where we say goodbye.
Henry?!
Going to die in a blaze of glory?
And try to take me with you?
No...
I'm the only one who's going to die.
I only lived this long...
so I could save my friends.
What?
He's absorbing my mana...
Outside the hideout, my magic
absorption rate skyrockets.
This isn't magic, either,
so her eye magic can't stop it.
But this is all useless.
My mana's not so weak that this
is enough to undermine it.
You can disappear all on your own.
That's just fine. My job ends here.
I'm just happy I got to fight
alongside everyone in the end.
I'm sure they'll be able
to stop you after this.
The rest is...
...up... to... you.
Not yet, Henry!
Live!
You must be Henry, the one with the
weird illness that sucks up magic.
Heya! I'm the new squad member, Asta!
Captain Yami told me about this place
after I accidentally wandered in!
Don't you worry! I don't have any magic!
You're always getting magic from them,
so you're embarrassed to go see them?
I don't think you need to worry about that!
I mean, I'm not one to talk,
but they're all pretty crazy.
Once I have better control
over my magic absorption...
One... day... I'll... go...
see... them... all... myself.
You will? Then we'll be waiting for you!
I'm sure it'll be even more fun
once you meet them in person!
It's like a dream.
Until I met all of them, I was all alone.
I didn't care about when I'd die.
And yet...
I don't want to die.
I want to continue living with my friends.
Let's continue living together!
Poison Magic: Forbidden Fruit!
Transformation... released!
I don't want to lose a
single one of my friends!
That goes for you, too...
Gauche!
The binding spell...
It's gone.
I need you to return those
bodies to Gauche and Marie.
They're our precious friends.
You damned humans...
I can't use any magic!
Our magic has been sealed!
They put up a barrier! We can't go—
No, wait. Our magic is being taken away...
This is... It goes against all natural law!
It couldn't be...
It's the power of a human magic item?!
That's...
Excellent...
I'm overflowing with power.
Now the elves' magic will be ours!
The princess is of no use to us now.
She's carrying their child.
She's no longer fit to be a royal!
How dare anyone other than us humans
possess strong magical powers?
Even the idea of coexisting with
such creatures is dreadful.
We must make them pay for
leading one of our own astray!
The human royals shall become
the gods of this land!
I'll never forget those
humans' faces, even in death!
Tense with fear, but ecstatic!
Unreasonable anger...
They kill us because of their greed,
and their rotten brains warp
the truth to fit their needs!
Their filthy, disgusting laughter...
How could you do something like that?!
I just can't understand!
I will never forgive you!
It makes me sick!
My malice is out of control...
I won't be satisfied until
I rip them all to shreds!
You filthy, disgusting humans!
But that...
isn't them.
They're just like us.
They're fighting for their precious friends.
I'm sorry, everyone...
At this rate, my malice will take over,
and I won't be myself anymore.
Do as you will.
I'm sorry, Eclat.
No... I'll always stay with
my gentle big brother.
Then I'm sorry about this,
but I'm taking my friends back.
This is even erasing the forbidden magic.
Licht, why did you...
Well, whatever. I know you worked
really hard, so I'm sorry, Patry and Raia.
I'm going to bow out here.
This also goes for the forbidden
spell that brought us back, but...
A convenient power that can make it
so that something never happened...
Do you think such a thing exists?
Actions come with consequences.
You can't escape that.
Make sure you never forget that, human.
Yeah.
I'll never forget you two.
You're exactly right. There isn't
a single human you can trust.
No matter how close you try
to get, they're still strangers.
Everyone looks out for themselves first.
They want to have it easier
than the rest of the world.
And to make that happen, they'd betray
anyone without even a second thought.
I'm the same way.
I don't care what happens as
long as Marie and I are happy.
That was... enough.
Gauche...
Gauche!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
So close...
Are you okay?
Marie!
I... I'm so glad I didn't... hurt anyone.
Yeah! And I'm glad you guys are okay, too!
How stupid are you people?!
If you're safe, that's all that matters!
You were about to die for someone else!
And now, our precious hideout
is reduced to rubble!
I'm only ever thinking about Marie and myself!
As long as we're safe,
I don't care about anything else!
I only joined the Black Bulls
for our own sake!
I never planned on being
buddy-buddy with all of you!
And deep down inside, I don't trust
a single one of you bastards!
Big Brother!
You should've just left me alone!
He really doesn't get it, does he?
I thought he was smarter than that.
W-We obviously know he only cares about
himself and his little sister by now!
You're... the... moron.
That's not what you're
supposed to say right now!
Come on! Look at us!
Big Brother!
Ugh, damn it!
Thanks... you jerks.
It's our pleasure, you sister-loving jerk!
Get off me, you numbskulls!
Oh, come on! Give in to the love, you jerk!
You're suddenly calling me "jerk" a lot!
I'm so embarrassed!
Then get off of me already!
But we're the Go-Gau Duo!
Don't give us a name!
That's...
Things are getting exciting!
Shut up!
Uh... things are getting really crazy!
We'd be dead by now if it
weren't for this kitty-cat!
Look!
It can't withstand the dreams of two people?
Glamour World...
is collapsing!
Ah, that was so much fun!
I feel so much better now!
Take care of my body, 'kay?
See you later!
I'm glad I got to meet you.
Not all humans are consumed
by betrayal and greed.
Don't you think so after seeing those kids?
Our enemy's got an
insane amount of magic...
So we can go all out, right?!
Hell yeah, we can!
Her power and magic were top class,
but the compatibility was just awful.
She didn't finish us off in one blow,
so we had time to come up with a plan.
We're all working together, la!
True...
Combo Spell: Flame Lightning
Exploding Cannon!
Welcome back, everyone!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Oh, Gauche! You're back to normal!
Thank goodness!
Now we're all best friends again.
For now, just eat this, 'kay?
Don't go stuffing food in my mouth, domehead!
Damn it, that's good!
It's a magical nummy
that recovers your mana!
Eat up, sweet child.
This food is so yummy!
The psycho woman?! What the
hell is she doing here?!
Stay away from Marie!
Aw, I can't research her?
I'll murder you!
Never mind that! Since we both got
taken over, let's fight each other next time!
No!
And now, the Captain of the
Coral Peacocks is back, too!
And right back to sleep.
Tch! Guess all the tension's gone.
Y-Yeah...
Whoops, I slipped!
Now it's raining Noelle and Zora!
What the hell's the big idea?!
I-It's not like I was jealous
that you all looked like
you were having so much fun or anything.
Yeah, whatever! You're stepping
on me, so get the hell off, Lady Noe!
I'm royalty. I have every
right to step on you.
I have seniority, damn it!
Miz Charmy! Please go feed Henry!
Are you the one who's hungry for nummies?!
I'm... starving.
All right! Finral's sorta missing right now,
but the rest of the Black Bulls are all here!
Once we're all recovered,
we're gonna go after Captain Yami!
Yeah!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Leave It to Me!
Thank you all for your hard work!
gLaMoUr
wOrLd
This is my dream world, Glamour World!
To thank you, I'll grant you any wish!
Then I want meat! Please bless
us with some nummy meat!
Sure thing! Meat coming right up!
La?!
I wanna go all-out with someone!
Sure thing!
With these on, you can hit anyone as
much as you want, and they'll be fine!
Huh?
I think we're going to be fighting all night,
so I'd like to take care of my skin.
I want some serious muscles
like Captain Yami!
I got you both!
You just keep doing whatever!
This is a nightmare! A nightmare!
All right! Let's go to the Shadow Palace!
We need to end this! And then,
we're gonna all come back here!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 113:
"Storming the Shadow Palace."
Page 113
Storming the Shadow Palace
Not giving up is my magic!