The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently
aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
To the Heart Kingdom!
Captain Yami! The Heart Kingdom!
All that's coming through is your
enthusiasm. Use your damn words.
Gordon's dad looked into it for us!
There's a stupidly huge
curse in the Heart Kingdom!
Oh?
I think we can find out something
about the devil's curse
if we go to the Heart Kingdom!
Where's Gordon? And what
does he think about this?
He was gonna learn some curse magic,
so he decided to stay at home for a while.
I see. Also, why did those two come back
looking like their minds are blown?
Something about the food not
agreeing with them or something?
I thought it was great!
I think I got the gist of what's going on.
Hup.
Then do I get to go to the Heart Kingdom?
Sure.
I'll go make the arrangements,
so just sit tight.
Not happening.
Huh?
There's no way into the Heart Kingdom.
What?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
I was going to go to the Heart Kingdom, too,
since the devil's curse is there!
The Heart Kingdom has
a bunch of its own unique trap
spells set up along its border.
We set any of those off and
we're instant fugitives.
Heart
Kingdom
Clover Kingdom
Then it'd become an international incident.
No way! Oh, but if we nullify the
trap spells with my anti-magic,
we could probably get in!
No, you fool. The moment we mess
with them, they'll find us out.
Well, that's not good.
Sounds like Rouge isn't going
to be able to help either, then.
It'd be pretty much impossible
to get in without them knowing.
Come to think of it, I think Mimosa mentioned
going to the Heart Kingdom before.
Really?!
Yes. She mentioned that
there were some nobles going there
like they were exchange students.
All right, Finral. Take these
jerks to the Golden Dawn.
Sure!
Huh? Finral, you usually complain
when you get used as an errand boy.
Well, there's someone in the
Golden Dawn that I want to see.
The Golden Dawn's Headquarters
And that's when Finral did his best to stop you.
Curse you, Brother.
Langris! I heard you're awake! Thank goodness!
Brother!
Finral!
I'm so glad you're all right, Miss Finnes.
Must be satisfying.
Huh?
I tried to kill my own brother,
but was defeated.
Then, when my parents tried
desperately to apologize for me,
I tried to kill the king.
I'm sure Father must be
quite disappointed in me.
What are you talking about?!
It all happened because you
were possessed by an elf!
Don't worry! We can clear this up—
On top of everything, I was saved by my
brother, who I've mocked this whole time.
I heard about the trial.
You and that peasant are so insolent!
You have no talent, yet you
take on so many burdens!
This isn't over yet!
Yeah, that's the spirit!
You being like that makes
declaring war on you worth it.
What?
Starting now, I'm going to work hard
to make Father acknowledge me.
I'll be a man worthy of being the
head of the House of Vaude!
And...
I'll be the one who makes Miss Finnes happy!
I'm sorry to drag you into this, Miss Finnes.
But...
I'll become a man worthy of you,
and then I'll come for you.
Please try not to take too long.
Brother, a moment.
Wait! Should you be moving, Langris?!
Please wait here, Miss Finnes.
Huh?
Don't worry. I'm not going to try to gouge
a bunch of holes in my brother again.
That's pretty scary, Langris.
What's wrong, Langris?
As you are now, you won't be
able to make Miss Finnes happy.
Huh?
Because...
Vice Captain Langris...
So you've awakened as well, Vice Captain.
Yay! Look at you cuties!
How about we grab some tea?
See? I knew it.
You're cursed!
What?!
You're a hopeless playboy who hits
on any woman in your path!
Playboy
P-Playboy?
All that running away and trying
to act cool made you a bigger
failure than you already were!
Failure
Failure?
And once you pick up bad habits,
they won't be easy to break!
Bad Habits
How could someone like you with so
many faults make Miss Finnes happy?!
Y-You're absolutely right.
What in the world are these two doing?
The vice captain has seemed like a
different person ever since he awakened.
Make sure you work hard to
rid yourself of that curse.
If you don't, I might just end
up marrying Miss Finnes first.
So was breaking my curse a part
of this investigation, too?
"No."
Hmph. I won't let you be happy
that easily, Brother.
I see... So that's why you've come to see me.
Anything to help Asta.
Yes, I've been to the Heart Kingdom.
I went there on an exchange with
my brother when I was thirteen.
Though I hated the fact
that it had to be with him.
We were only allowed access to a limited area,
but their magic techniques
are different from the Clover
Kingdom's, so I learned a lot.
It's a lovely kingdom with
abundant water and lush greenery,
and its rich natural environment
generated so much mana.
If what lies at its center
is indeed a devil or a curse,
that's truly terrifying.
Though it's hard to believe.
A curse... That might be a clue about
the devil that Mother encountered.
We weren't allowed to meet her, but the
queen who rules over the Heart Kingdom
is apparently as powerful as
one of our Magic Knights Squads.
She's known as the all-knowing mage who sees
everything that happens in her kingdom.
What?! That's awesome!
A queen... Is she like the Witch Queen?
Then we might be in trouble.
But I guess we're not going
over there to pick a fight.
I'm not letting my guard down, though.
I believe they're recruiting applicants
to go there right about now.
I'll apply for permission
to enter their kingdom.
Thanks, Mimosa!
Holy crap! This is the first time
I've ever been on a ship this huge!
My, what a cute little ship.
You idiot. We're not going to play.
I didn't know you had a boat, Yami.
Why didn't you ever mention it before?
Well, I went to go see the mushroom head
who works for Julius and threatened...
er, discussed the matter with him,
and he was happy to lend it to us.
Huh?
You guys better not damage it.
Right!
Asta...
Take care of Mimosa.
You're overreacting, Klaus.
We're not going over there to fight.
But if something happens while
you're in a different kingdom,
we won't be able to come to your aid.
If only I could go with you...
There's a limit of four...
So first, there's Asta.
The royal lady from the Golden Dawn
who arranged all of this...
And then Noelle, who doesn't seem like
she'll let go of her spot this time.
And lastly, Finral.
Oh, yeah. Why am I the fourth one?
Having wheels with you comes in handy.
Right?
Yup, yup.
Can't really argue with that.
Definitely.
He is rather convenient.
Indeed. Spatial magic is convenient.
I know that, but...
No, really. You don't need to understand!
Asta! Go kick some ass in the Heart Kingdom!
What are you talking about?
Right!
Take care of things there and come home soon.
I still have to fight you, Asta.
Right!
If you get homesick and have trouble
sleeping, just have a sip of this.
Right!
Wait, you can't.
That should be enough to send them off.
I hope you guys didn't forget that
you have a job to do yourselves.
Of course we didn't forget, Mister Yami.
Off we go!
Yeah.
All right. Make sure you all
stay on your toes out there.
Yes, sir!
Two thousand and thirty-one...
Two thousand and thirty-two...
Two thousand and thirty-three...
Two thousand and thirty-four...
Two thousand and thirty-five...
Two thousand and thirty-six...
Keep it steady...
Two thousand and thirty-seven...
Two thousand and thirty-eight...
Keep it steady...
Out of all the possibilities,
why did I have to be stuck on a boat
with two super-adorable royal cuties
and a cool beauty who turns into a bird?!
I don't think I'm gonna be
able to sleep at night!
Tough it out... Tough it out, Finral!
Miss Finnes is the only one for me!
Um...
Why don't we have some lunch?
Thanks, Mimosa!
I hope you like them, Asta.
So you made these, Mimosa?
I'm digging right in!
It's so good!
This one's good, too!
Thank you very much.
Asta... Don't eat all of it, okay?
This frustrates me for some reason.
I-I need water!
Here's some water.
That's too much!
I hope you're grateful.
For what?!
I almost fell into the ocean just now, y'know!
I'm not sure why, but this frustrates me.
Didn't I tell you that I can't swim?!
I don't recall.
What?!
What in the world am I being
forced to watch right now?
How was I supposed to know? I'm royalty.
What?! That doesn't even make sense!
We're finally here!
We're actually entering
the Heart Kingdom legally!
We're not coming here to play, you know.
I'm sorry I was only able to
gain entry for the four of us.
What are you talking about, Mimosa?
I have nothing but thanks for you!
If all else fails, we could
use Finral's spatial magic—
That would be unlawful entry.
It got foggy all of a sudden.
The only ones who are
allowed through this fog
are those permitted by the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
I couldn't sleep one bit knowing two
beautiful girls were sleeping near me.
More importantly, what does the Queen
of the Heart Kingdom look like?!
Damn it! Is she hot, too?!
The Heart Kingdom... I wonder what it's like.
Heart Kingdom
That's the Heart Kingdom?
Their water sources, the city, and the
forest are all mixed together?
That's awesome!
It looks like they have arrived as planned.
The devil power from the Clover Kingdom...
We must get our hands on it.
Hmph. I guess this place is sort of pretty.
I wonder where we should tie the boat up.
Please continue sailing forward.
You're...
Welcome to the Heart Kingdom.
Spirit Guardian
Gaja
I am the Spirit Guardian Gaja,
and I will act as your guide.
Is he someone important?
Seems to be.
It's been quite some time, Lady Mimosa.
We met on your previous visit.
Good day to you, Gaja.
I'm honored that you remember me.
You were quite popular with those who
had made your acquaintance, Lady Mimosa.
This is Asta, Noelle, and Finral.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Here is some crimson orange
juice that tastes even sweeter
after some magic is run through it.
Please enjoy.
Thank you very much.
What in the world is this? It's delicious.
Mine's not sweet at all! Run some
magic through mine, too!
O-Oh, fine...
You said to keep sailing, but it
looks like a dead end up ahead.
Fear not.
The queen will transport us.
The queen? So this is just one mage's magic?!
The mist barrier and the water stairs
are a product of the queen's Mana Zone,
which covers the whole kingdom.
That's awesome! And so is this juice!
He can't be serious. It covers the
whole kingdom? Is that even possible?
Look! Pretty butterflies!
It truly is a lovely kingdom.
It's hard to believe there's a devil here.
It's been 1,200 years since
our kingdom was founded.
In every generation,
the queen has made a pact
with the Water Spirit as a priestess,
and has used its magic to protect the kingdom.
Using the power of the water and trees,
this has encouraged the development
of a magic civilization with deep mana
that does not allow unwanted guests to enter.
That's amazing... A single queen manages
to keep peace in a kingdom this big?
Yes. That has been the case up until now.
Though we do not know what the future holds.
Asta!
What are you... What is the
meaning of this, Gaja?!
There's something we need
to maintain this peace.
First, we need to go after Asta!
Leave that to me!
Let's go, Mimosa!
Believe in our transporter!
Of course!
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
Ah... That's only third stage or so.
Your magic is rather intriguing.
Finral!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
Huh?
He's floating without using any magic?
I don't know what you're trying to do here...
But do you really think you'll
get away with harming a friend
of royalty from the Clover Kingdom?
That's our Noelle!
She's super cool, pretty, and cute!
No, wait! Miss Finnes is the only one for me!
Rare and powerful magic...
Definitely first stage.
That's rather impressive water magic.
I will not hold back either, then.
What is that?
I'm sorry for inviting you
here in such a rough manner.
Huh?
We were waiting for your devil,
for the sake of our kingdom.
I just got blown away to some weird place!
This is the Heart Kingdom's queen?
Then that's...
Damn it!
His attribute is lightning?
Then what were those rune things?
Is that a unique Heart Kingdom
magic technique?
Lightning Magic: Tenjiolia.
It's fast...
But I can evade it with my Valkyrie Armor!
As expected from a first stage. But...
I told my spell to pursue
you until it strikes you.
Gaja, please return Asta to us.
Otherwise, we'll be forced to fight with you.
An attack spell...
It appears Lady Mimosa
has also grown to third stage.
And it looks like that spatial mage
is able to create a path wherever he can see.
Let me give you a glimpse of the
difference between our levels.
He cast his technique into the sky?
This magic is...
Humans are no match for
the vast mana of nature!
I'm somehow getting by for now,
but I don't know how much mana they have!
Damn it! Why the heck am
I even fighting, anyway?!
So you negate magic...
That is your devil's power.
What the...
It's quite abominable, but it
also seems rather useful.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
devil-possessed boy from the Clover Kingdom.
Water Spirit
Undine
I'm Undine. I'm one of the four
Great Spirits, and I'm contracted
to the Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
You're quite amazing,
but you're no match for me.
Not to mention, you don't have
a lick of magic yourself.
Without any magic, you're less than ninth stage.
Ninth stage?! What's that?!
Oh, right. You don't use magic
stages in your kingdom, do you?
The lowest is the ninth stage, and then
you have the eighth, the seventh...
That's how we measure and rank
both magical talent and skill.
I can't move... or breathe!
And the highest...
is stage zero.
True Lighting Magic: Irial Astrauza!
I can't sense their mana
anywhere that I can see.
They must've fled using spatial magic.
A wise choice.
But no matter where they go...
He accurately manipulated space
in a place he couldn't see?
Plant Creation Magic: Magic Flower Guidepost!
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel Gate!
Sorry, but we can't just back down
after you did all that showing off!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Sorry, but you can't measure our
true powers by talent alone.
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
This magic...
I'll keep my anti-magic in reserve
so she can't pull me in!
Judging from the ki,
there's definitely a person over there!
That means there must be air there, too!
Pardon me! I'm coming in!
Asta and the others are attacked
as they arrive at the Heart Kingdom.
Could it be that the Heart Kingdom
has been taken over by a devil?
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 129: "The Devil Megicula."
Page 129
The Devil Megicula
And the queen, Loropechika, appears.