It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Asta and the others who infiltrated
the Eye of the Midnight Sun's base
continued to dominate the battle.
Mereoleona tried to finish Raia off, but...
We can understand each other.
I mean, we're basically the same as them.
They're mad because something
precious to them was hurt.
A free kingdom
where everyone can acknowledge
each other and smile...
That's the kind of kingdom I want to create
when I become the Wizard King.
What a fool,
blurting out something so overambitious
without any hesitation...
He's actually serious about that.
There used to be a guy who
said the same thing.
If all humans were like you two, then maybe...
But...
There's no stopping this now.
And around the same time, Licht...
no, Patry's true motive was revealed.
Patry was once betrayed by the humans
and witnessed the massacre
of many of his elven friends.
In order to bring back his friends,
he had been acting as Licht this entire time.
The humans betrayed someone precious
to me. They betrayed all of us!
This time...
This time, we'll destroy the humans!
Humans, you shall serve as the
foundation of the resurrection.
What the...
This is...
The Black Bulls Captain
vs
the Crimson Wild Rose
I don't think I have the
profile just right yet.
This is insane!
We should have no problems
defeating these insects!
Hey, so where's your boss?
U-Uh...
Come on, tell me. I'm dying to paint right now.
Master Licht is...
Huh, what? What, what, what?!
I didn't even do anything yet!
Wh-What in the world...
What's going on?
Wow, I wonder what's happening!
A Village Out in the Boonies: Hage
The demon's skull...
D-Don't worry. It'll be okay, kids.
There's nothing to worry about.
Even if something dangerous
were to happen,
the Clover Kingdom has the Magic Knights.
Asta... Yuno...
Town in the Common Realm: Nean
It's nighttime, but it looks
like the sun's about to rise.
Earlier, there were swords of
light coming from the sky.
What in the world is
going on in this kingdom?
What... is... that?
Th-This seems different from
the swords of light earlier.
That light is like the light of our friendship.
But I guess this isn't the
time to talk about that.
Is this another attack by
the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
It disappeared... but our
friendship will never fade.
U-Um, Gauche?!
What?
Um... Your body...
What about it?
It's... shining... really... bright.
M-Marie?
Things keep happening one after
another. What's going on?
What the...
What is this light?
Luck?
H-Huh? Huh, wait, what?!
What the heck is going on with you now?!
You just started shining outta nowhere!
Once you're done with that,
you better explain what's going on!
Hey, are you listening?!
Too bad...
What is?
The era of the humans has come to an end.
Wh-What's the matter...
E-Everyone?
Yuno... Hamon... Klaus...
Do not talk to us.
You are not one of us.
Begone...
Begone, humans!
Now, the time for revenge has come!
That light just now... wasn't an attack.
So what the hell was it?
I feel strong magic throughout the kingdom.
This ki... Don't tell me...
Wh-What was that light?
Are you all right? What happened?
We must contact all the
Magic Knights in the area.
Wait, what are you doing?!
So you two finally showed up,
but why the hell are you all
shiny and attacking our comrades?
Marx! Old Man Owen!
Sorry, but we aren't the
men you knew anymore.
Long ago, we were destroyed by
the humans of this kingdom.
We are elves.
Elves?
This time, we'll be destroying you.
Just as you did to us, we will
destroy every last one of you.
Well, this sounds like it's
going to be a pain in the ass.
The guy did say that once they
collected all the magic stones,
they'd be reborn into their true
forms and obtain enormous power.
So the ones who were reborn aren't the
guys in the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Don't worry. You'll be put out
of your misery soon enough.
Marx's magic...
If any of these hit me, I'll lose
my memory of what just happened.
And now the jerk's speed
and range have skyrocketed.
And Old Man Owen's healing
magic also skyrocketed,
except now the healing's so powerful,
it'll bust a hole in my ass.
I'll be finished if either one of
them manages to hit me. Shit!
I don't know who that corpse is,
but is it precious to you?
It doesn't matter who they are.
All humans are sinners and deserve to die.
You bastard!
If it's that precious to you,
how about I rip it to shreds
right in front of you?
Don't you dare make those two
say shit like that ever again.
You're just going to be easier
to hit if you leap right at us!
Memory Magic: Torment Canceller!
Dark Magic: Black Hole.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked...
Lightless Blade Storm!
What?
This human's movements...
Dark Cloaked Lightless Blunt Slash!
You two can take a little nap.
See, I swore to a man you both
respected that I'd protect this country.
For crying out loud...
These two don't even use battle magic,
and they were this much trouble?
Red roses?
My comrades...
It appears you let your guard down,
considering you just woke up.
Rest a while within my magic.
Well, that's damn nice of you.
It's not like you, though, Spiny Prickly Queen.
I don't know who you are, but you
seem quite skilled for a human.
What's going on?
There are powerful spells
going off everywhere!
Is it another attack on the royal capital?
Get the hell outta here, you dumbasses!
If you guys don't survive,
I'll murder you!
I can't do much about the
destruction to the town.
As long as the citizens survive,
the kingdom won't die.
But if more of these things
keep sprouting up everywhere,
we might just get wiped out.
The scent from the roses is
cloaking the Prickly Queen's magic.
This isn't like her at all.
But you see...
I was always really badass
at playing hide-and-seek!
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
You have impressive instincts for a human.
That wasn't instinct.
I distinctly felt your ki!
Ki?!
Three cheers for ki!
The way she moves and her ki
are definitely Charlotte's,
but her magic combat tactics are different.
In addition to her normal
midrange attacks,
she's using roses that scramble
magic with their scent
and a variety of close-range attacks.
On top of that, she's not
leaving any openings now.
Knocking her out with the blunt edge of
my sword will be nearly impossible.
I heard her roses turned blue when
she got hit with that curse as a kid.
The curse!
The curse upon the House
of Roselei has activated!
Damn it!
What the hell's the big idea, you jerk?
You flung the pasta soup
I was eating everywhere.
On missions, you're as cool as a cucumber
and always raring to go. So what gives?
I like tough girls.
But it probably wouldn't hurt to ask
someone for help once in a while.
Our Magic Knights Squads are full
of strong people you can rely on.
I don't really get it, but apparently
the curse was broken back then.
Yet, because of the curse,
her roses remained blue.
But an elf's in there right now.
Did turning into something that's not
human kill off the lingering effects, too?
So this is what Charlotte Roselei's
briar magic was supposed to be!
You used the power of the curse
to make yourself stronger
through sheer grit...
And now some other woman's
using your magic perfectly.
That's pretty lame, Prickly Queen!
S-Sis!
You're...
Sis!
B-Back there...
When you attacked us...
That was...
That was some kind of mistake, right?
Sis!
Stop acting so familiar with me, human.
I only have a younger brother.
I have no younger sisters.
Sis...
She's basically being controlled by
some kind of spell. Don't worry about it.
You're the Black Bulls' captain...
I'll deal with her.
Huh?
But you showed up at a good time.
Hey, what is this?
Take this and get to someplace safe.
I-I don't take any requests from men!
Damn it, now's not the time for that!
But...
There's a hero in there.
Be extra careful with it.
Hey!
I can't leave my sis with any guy!
Hey, you dumbass! Come back here!
How can I leave my sis and run off?
I'll bring Sis back to her senses!
Earth Magic: Divided—
Sis's magic is really dense here.
It's preventing me from using my magic well.
The Black Bulls' captain was
doing all that in here?!
I can't even fight properly?
No!
I'm only alive now...
because Sis saved me!
I'll wake Sis up, even if it kills me!
Quit screwing around!
Our mission right now is
to protect and to survive!
I understand how you feel.
Then—
But you need to survive for
her sake, too, you dumbass!
I won't let anyone near
my Sis! Especially men!
Please take care of Sis.
Save the Blue Rose Knights' captain!
Leave it to me! Now get outta here.
You cannot run now.
Who said I was gonna run?
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
Your subordinate is crying, you know.
Why the hell are you letting
them control you like this?
You're not that weak,
Charlotte!
You have my respect. You are strong.
That magic sure is insane.
My Black Hole can't absorb all that.
If she fires that off cleanly,
it'll blow away half this town, and we'll
be dealing with a bunch of dead people.
Tch! You've always had my respect.
So... I'll use everything I've
got to take you back alive!
Dark Magic...
Briar Magic...
Crimson Vine Spear!
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
Luck? Ben?
Golden magic... How beautiful.
Such menacing magic...
It's the same as Vetto and the others.
Why is that magic coming from you two?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Noelle, the Beautiful Little
Royal Girl of the "Na" Column
Royal Girl of the "Na" Column.
Languish (naeru).
Languish
(Naeru)
Gloomy gloom... I have no energy.
Stew (nieru).
Stew
(Nieru)
Hot, hot, hot! You're stewing me!
Sew
(Nueru)
Sew (nueru).
Yay, I sewed this really well. Ow!
Nails (neiru).
Nails
(Neiru)
I-Isn't this one a bit of a stretch?
Noelle (Noeru)!
Look at my grand appearance!
But what else did you expect?
I'm royalty!
What the?! The Eye of the Midnight Sun
guy started shining outta nowhere,
and now he's super strong!
Wait... Rill?!
Why the heck are you attacking us?
Next time on Black Clover, Page 97:
"Overwhelming Disadvantage."
Page 97
Overwhelming Disadvantage
What are we going to do,
Captain Mereoleona?!