It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Burning with rage toward humans, the Magic
Knights who reincarnated as elves attacked.
Asta and the others headed toward
the royal capital to stop them
and encountered Rades, Valtos, and Sally,
who had been sacrificed in order to
reincarnate the elves, and almost died.
You guys piss me off, too, but right now,
I want to kill that bastard Licht.
The three former Eye of
the Midnight Sun members
joined them, and they
all hurried to the capital.
Meanwhile, at the royal capital...
To save her brother Nozel
and protect the capital,
Noelle awakened a new spell.
You're mine!
Langris!
As for Finral...
I'm your older brother!
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
This is... my last chance!
Your big brother's pretty confident
when it comes to agility and accuracy.
I'm going to stop you, no matter what!
Come here...
Langris!
He finally stopped his younger brother
Langris's destructive rampage,
which began when Langris
reincarnated as an elf.
But now, Patry, who had
returned to the hideout,
was about to set a
terrifying plan in motion.
Now all we have to do is fit the final
magic stone into the pedestal in the castle,
and activate the spell that
uses the entire kingdom.
We'll wipe out all of the humans,
and we'll take back this world,
making it a peaceful world for elves alone.
Now, then...
As soon as those two wake up,
we'll have all the actors in place.
The Raging Bull
Joins the Showdown!!
Morning. How do you feel
after that long nap...
Fana? Vetto?
Do you remember your previous incarnations?
Yeah. We were the Third Eye, weren't we?
Vetto the Despair
Fana the Hateful
Fana the Hateful, Vetto the Despair,
and Raia the Disloyal, was it? How hilarious.
Vetto and Fana were previously part
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun's
elite three, known as the Third Eye,
where they fought against Asta and the others.
Vetto lost his life, and Fana's soul
left the body it had inhabited,
allowing that body to start a new life.
Raia incubated the general traits of
the human bodies they had inhabited
and prepared new bodies
for their souls to inhabit.
Welcome back.
Since we're short on time,
I could only incubate your bodies long
enough for you to be about fifteen.
Now you're smaller than me, Vetto.
Well, I've died twice now.
I can't exactly be picky.
Yeah.
Creating duplicate bodies
with the exact same mana...
I've really gotta hand it to Sally
and her research on this one.
Too bad she's probably dead by now.
My mind is much clearer this time.
We used the evil eye
to force your previous incarnation,
so your malice was probably stronger.
Evil eye?
True, I did feel half-asleep last time...
like I was having a nightmare.
Salamander!
No response.
I guess Salamander's gone.
So someone else who was qualified
showed up while Fana's soul was away?
Well, you're strong enough right now,
even without Salamander.
Guess you're right. If nothing else,
there's no way I'd lose to those stupid humans.
All right, I'm gonna take
you to the Grimoire Tower,
so hurry up and let one pick you.
Actually, before that, we need some clothes.
Especially Fana.
They do seem a bit bigger than they
were the last time you were fifteen.
Soon this false royal capital created
by the humans will be no more.
It appears they've finally gathered up above.
Come to think of it,
they must've received the revelation
in preparation for this moment.
Those who guide the elves...
The Apostles of Sephira!
The Apostles of Sephira
Licht!
He may seem like that right now,
but I'm certain Licht is actually in there.
Once the reincarnation is fully complete,
he'll be back to the same old Licht.
Right...
Wait, where's that one boy?
Well, the weird thing is...
He was reincarnated, but somehow,
his personality was still the human's.
Wait, what?
Don't worry. He'll be with us
once everything is complete.
Let's go wait over there.
Right.
Man, look at this view.
The party's in full swing.
All right. Let's get started.
By infusing Gravito Stones with magic,
we will open the door to the underworld
that was sealed under Clover Castle!
The hell is that?
What's going on?
Nozel, the castle...
What in the world is that?
It's a magic space that acts as the
border between this world and the next.
The elves of antiquity entrusted it
to the humans in an ancient pact.
It's called the Shadow Palace.
Only the Apostles of Sephira,
ten elves who are able
to receive divine revelations, can open it.
See?
When we put the final magic stone
in its pedestal inside the palace,
the elves' reincarnation
will be complete!
In exchange, the souls of the
humans who owned these bodies
will be sent to the underworld!
And because I am so beautiful...
I shall not allow that to happen!
David's dice magic acquires effects
that give him an advantage
depending on his roll.
Better rolls mean more advantage.
But getting this much power from a two...
This is absurd!
I mean, it probably won't do you
much good, but give it your all.
What in the world was that about?
So basically, there's a magical
space spreading over there.
I don't know what the hell's over there,
but this looks pretty bad.
Well, why don't we head on over?
We will not let you get in the
way of the Apostles of Sephira!
Guess they're not just
gonna let us go over there.
Bring it on!
I'll slash you all up!
Uh, fighting those numbers without Finral's
spatial magic is gonna be a bit rough.
Damn it!
It's just one thing after another...
Give us a break already, damn it!
What should we do?
That's...
Everyone!
Are you okay?!
So basically, there's a magical
space spreading over there.
I don't know what the hell's over there,
but this looks pretty bad.
Well, why don't we head on over?
We will not let you get in the
way of the Apostles of Sephira!
Guess they're not just
gonna let us go over there.
Bring it on!
I'll slash you all up!
Uh, fighting those numbers without Finral's
spatial magic is gonna be a bit rough.
Damn it!
It's just one thing after another...
Give us a break already, damn it!
What should we do?
That's...
Don't worry, everyone! We're no one suspicious!
We're the Black Bulls,
here with some other guys who
ended up joining us for reasons!
What... is... that... black... castle... back... there?
Looks like Gauche is chilling
on top of the enemy base.
We're coming to save you, Gauche!
P-P-Please wait!
Where the hell is Licht?!
A stupidly huge... bull?
So you've finally shown yourself, Henry.
What kind of entrance was that?
Welcome, you dumbasses!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mister Yami!
Hey, Finral's passed out behind the captain.
What?! Are you okay, Finral?!
Wait! You already woke up once?!
Really?! Then you should've woken up faster!
La! Eat my cooking and feel all better!
All of you, eat!
You guys are way too late!
You should thank me for keeping things
smoothed over until you got here!
Oh, gosh, I felt so helpless without them!
What the heck, Noelle?! What even
is that outfit?! You look so cool!
You were the ones in trouble!
You're the one who should
be thankful to us, Lady Noe!
Hey, now... What the hell is that mess?
It's not exactly clear to me either,
but they've always been a mess.
They're our teammates, the other Black Bulls!
Curse you, humans! It doesn't
matter how many of you show up!
You're no match for us elves!
Here they come!
Luck's High Mana Detection
High
High Mana
High Mana De
High Mana Detect
High Mana Detection
It gauges the magic attack's affinity
and uses balls of our magic...
...to intercept it!
That's so cool!
Where the hell is Licht?!
Curse you! Take this!
Rouge!
Vanessa's Fate Manipulation and Absolute Evasion
Our attacks are missing them?!
Take... this.
La! All of you who used magic,
eat up and recover your mana!
I can't use magic, but I'm
sure the heck gonna eat!
Where the hell is Licht?!
Y'all are crazy!
So, beanpole, what do you think of my team?
I wanna slash 'em.
Well, don't, dumbass!
The Black Bulls...
Even here, you intend to get in my way?
That one is troublesome.
Magic that interferes with natural laws...
A witch, eh?
That's the cornerstone of their defense.
I'll go.
Reve!
Ah, guess you're finally awake.
You somehow sleep even more than Raia.
This will be your first spell in several
centuries, counting your past life.
Are you gonna be okay?
There's no problem.
Members of the Black Bulls!
Mimosa! Mimosa's big brother
and Mushroom Guy, too!
Asta! We have to hurry,
or everyone's who's been taken over by
elves will be taken over completely!
What?!
This beautiful magic...
Oh, come on. Don't tell me this ki is...
Isn't that...
Captain of the Coral Peacocks
Dorothy Unsworth
The Captain of the Coral Peacocks,
Dorothy Unsworth?!
Dream Magic: Glamour World.
Wha...
What the heck just happened?!
I can sense the magic of the vanished pieces,
but they don't exist anywhere.
Miz Vanessa... and Magna and Luck...
and Miz Charmy and Sally... are all gone?!
How beautiful!
The moment Captain Dorothy's
magic activates, it's over.
Its targets are taken to the World of Dreams,
and there's not a thing they can do about it.
The World of Dreams?
Now the cornerstone of their defense is gone.
Guess we should wrap things up, then.
Combo Spell: Storm of Light Swords
of Imperial Conviction.
There you are, Licht!
Gauche!
G-G-G-G-Gordon!
Okay!
Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud!
What's the big idea, Gordon?!
Conversion Magic: Poison to Cotton!
We're saved! Thanks, Miz Grey!
Were you trying to kill us, Gordon?!
Uh, that was teamwork, Asta.
Leave the rest to us.
You go on ahead with your precious Licht.
Please don't say it like that.
I'm counting on you, Droit.
Sure. Get going.
Tch.
Valtos, open up a path!
Hey, those jerks!
Everyone...
Get... away... from... me.
Henry!
It's because he left the Raging Black Bull.
And without Miz Charmy here,
the others can't recover their mana!
Everyone!
No... My body...
That was one hell of a spell,
and it doesn't look like
your body can keep up yet.
Though I don't have much magic
left right now, either.
Asta...
Are you all right,
Shriveled Little Mushroom?
Things aren't looking too good over there,
but I can't just let Licht go like this.
I'm sure you dumbasses can handle this!
Surpass your damn limits!
Yes, sir!
All right. We'll leave this to you.
Let's go, beanpole!
Who died and made you boss, meathead?!
Big Brother, some of them left.
Then we need to quickly
kill the ones that are here
so we can hurry after them.
Now... it's time for hide and seek.
Find all of them, Eclat.
Okay.
Willpower's not gonna help you now, humans.
I found them.
Look at me.
Mirror Magic...
Eye Magic...
Combo Spell: Reflect Iris.
Wha...
Th-This...
I-I can't...
...move!
And...
...my magic's...
Eclat's magic allows her to immobilize
anyone who looks into her eyes.
It binds them physically,
but also blocks their magic.
Marie doesn't even have her grimoire yet!
I guess she's awesome, too!
Now you can just die, completely helpless.
Not yet...
Not... yet!
I'm not going to give up...
I'm going to turn Gauche
and Marie back to normal.
I'm going to...
stop you, no matter what!
My body can move again?
He nullified the magical effects?
Asta...
Can all three of you move now?
Yeah!
That's Licht's...
Demon-Destroyer Sword?
Why does he have it?
That weapon's too good for you!
Die and give it back!
I'll use transformation magic...
Take that!
...to make more mirrors!
Poison Magic: Forbidden Fruit!
Even though it's more powerful...
I know Gauche's magic really well!
Actually, he kind of pisses me off.
Always attacking me unfairly
with those weird beams...
He hasn't actually changed much
after getting his body taken over!
Yeah... And when he comes back,
he'll insult us even more.
And he'll keep showing us
the photo of his little sister,
and making figures of his little sister,
and always having nose bleeds...
He's... very... creepy.
We'll get him back to normal,
even if it hurts us,
so we can complain directly to his face!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Revival
Revival.
Part 1
Part 1.
You guys are smaller now,
since we didn't have time.
Yeah, I definitely jumped the gun.
Part 2
Part 2.
I had a little too much time on my hands,
so I incubated them too long.
Vetto and Fana are way older now.
Yeah, I definitely took too long.
My best friend, Gauche Adlai.
Your little sister is basically my little sister.
Yes. Marie is my actual little sister!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 111: "The Eyes in the Mirror."
Page 111
The Eyes in the Mirror
Ah, little sister, I cry for you.