It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Hey, come on! Are you
finished already, you jerk?
Asta!
What...
are you?
I'm someone who was born without any magic!
But even so, I'm going to
become the Wizard King!
And I'm alive...
to prove that!
Mars!
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I'm...
I'm just going to destroy everything!
Destroy everything?
The Wizard King protects everyone!
We were born to protect
everyone in this country.
Like hell I'm going to lose
to someone like you!
You're in my way...
Begone, pebble!
I may be just a pebble,
but I'm...
a pebble that shatters diamonds!
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
Memories of You
That should do it.
Is this actually going
to keep him restrained?
Of course it is!
My magic is not so weak that it'd
be broken by someone who's injured.
Look! We've taken his grimoire, too.
Don't get so pissy.
Want some medicinal herbs?
I don't want your leftovers!
What about you, Yuno?
Not a chance.
I'm glad that you're all safe.
Should you be moving around now?
It's fine. I feel much better.
It's all because you protected me, Noelle.
I-I didn't protect you.
You're just so helpless that
I couldn't leave you alone.
Right. Thank you very much.
M-More importantly, Asta,
do something about your clothes!
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why are you the one turning red?
I'm not turning red!
Actually...
My robe's ripped to shreds...
Magna's gonna kill me.
Vanessa will fix it for you when we get back.
Well, that's good, I guess.
To think that we'd be saved
by the Black Bulls...
We were the first ones to arrive,
therefore we win this competition,
but I will allow you three to enter
the treasure chamber, also.
Why do you always sound
so arrogant, four-eyes?
Well, thank you very much, you jerk!
You're very welcome!
Watch how you speak to me!
Well, excuse me, Lord Four-Eyes!
Who are you calling "Lord Four-Eyes"?!
Hmph! I don't have time to argue with you!
Well, excuse me, Lord Four-Eyes!
Shut your mouth!
They sure like wasting each other's time.
Keep it up and I'll break
those glasses of yours!
That's just cruelty!
I wouldn't say that, Lord Four-Eyes!
That's enough!
Let us head to the treasure chamber!
Yeah!
It'll be the Clover Kingdom's Magic Knights
who get to the treasure chamber!
You're so annoying!
You're the one who's annoying!
How do you get in?
There must be some code to
open this door somewhere.
You can do it! Think harder, four-eyes!
Shut up! Stop calling me that!
My name is Klaus!
It appears this door is made with magic,
so just cut through it.
Like, swoosh.
All right!
There's no way you can open it.
Yes!
That's awesome!
It's a mountain of treasure!
Hey! Be careful!
Heya, Asta.
Luck popped out!
It's beautiful.
I wonder what you use this for.
I haven't the slightest idea.
All of you! Stop touching
things without permission!
They might be magical items
worthy of being national treasures!
A little bit won't hurt, crabbypants.
Who are you calling "crabbypants"?!
Then we'll just go back to "four-eyes."
Stop calling me that!
Then "glasses man."
You bastard!
See? You are a crabbypants!
You think that makes you clever or something?!
What are these symbols?
I've never seen them before.
The symbols...
What was that just now?
No idea.
Don't go around touching things.
Put that back.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Stop!
You're gonna tear it out, Nero!
Hey!
What about it?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
But this is a rather rare,
strange grimoire.
It's as though it's stitched together.
Well...
We have a four-leaf clover,
and a grimoire so filthy
you can't even read it.
I have three oddities on my hands.
Isn't there anything interesting here?
This power...
Everyone, run!
I-Impossible!
My restraining magic...
And in so little time...
How could he have revived?!
Th-That's...
Flame recovery magic? That's impossible!
Everyone should have only
one magical attribute!
Mages have mana from the four classical
elements: fire, wind, water, and earth.
Fire
Wind
Water
Earth
Fire is strong against wind,
and weak against water.
There are compatibilities
between each element.
Mages can only use magic
from their own mana or
from a single attribute derived from it.
He's breaking all of those laws to have
two different kinds of magic!
Not to mention, he was clearly
a user of offensive magic,
but now he's using recovery magic!
That's inconceivable!
Are these the results of the
Diamond Kingdom's experiments?!
I'm sure you'll become a great warrior, Mars.
I'm sorry, Mars.
I have no other choice.
Please die.
I'll put that fire out!
Noelle!
You bastard!
How dare you do that to my friend?!
I know your abilities now.
If that blade is able to cut
through various magics,
then what about magic that's
faster than your blade?
So fast!
How dare you do that to my friend?!
Mars!
The strong will survive,
and the weak will die.
Noelle!
The strong will survive...
Hey, you idiot! Get a hold of yourself!
The Dream-Healing Flower
Cradle won't be fast enough!
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing Flower Robe!
Noelle...
This is the strongest
spell I can use right now.
Please don't die,
Noelle!
Ow...
What are you doing, Mimosa?
Honestly, you're so slow.
Here.
Thanks, Noelle.
That's amazing, Mimosa!
Who knew you'd be able to use
recovery magic that's this powerful?
With your royal magic, you may become
a healer who can heal any injury.
This is exciting.
On the other hand...
There's the House of Silva's second daughter,
who can't even control her powers.
I hear she's training every day.
Who knew someone like that
would be born into royalty?
I guess we Vermillions are the true royalty.
I might've just given up
if I were in her shoes...
Royals mock hard work.
It's something only those who
aren't born into power do,
not something that royalty does.
But...
I admire you for the hard work you do.
The strong will survive,
and the weak will die.
If only I could use my grimoire...
My sword...
Noelle... Mimosa...
With my big, heavy sword, I won't
be able to beat his magic's speed.
He changed the way he fights,
and the magic he uses while doing it.
What am I supposed to...
Nero?
Please die.
The strong will survive...
and the weak...
Mimosa!
What is that sword?
This sword will work.
Your opponent...
is me!
How's that?
Disappear!
Even if I can cut through his attack magic,
as long as he has that recovery magic,
I won't be able to finish him off!
What should I do?
What are you doing, Stupidsta?
Noelle!
Noelle...
You're the first peasant...
that I, a royal, ever acknowledged.
Hurry up and
defeat that guy, Asta!
Yeah, leave it to me.
I'll throw enough at him from the both of us!
Move. I'm going to make that girl,
that weakling, disappear!
Like hell I'll let that happen!
I don't have any magic,
but I've got...
my friends!
This is nothing!
Wh-What just happened? He's not
supposed to have any magic!
A water magic attack?
He borrowed Noelle's powers?
What in the world is that sword?
I don't really get it, but I did it!
I messed up...
Asta...
Asta!
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Resilient
Resilient.
Flame Recovery Magic: Phoenix Robe.
Isn't it hot in there?
It is.
Isn't it heavy?
And...
My face itches, but I can't scratch it!
The strong will survive,
and the weak will die.
Pebbles on the side of the road,
disperse in the wind.
Black Clover, Page 19:
"Destruction and Salvation."
Page 19
Destruction and Salvation
My magic destroys all.