It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Crimson Lion Kings placed fifth?
The new Captain of the
Crimson Lion Kings, Mereoleona Vermillion,
is the older sister of Fuegoleon,
who was injured
fighting the Eye of the Midnight Sun
and has yet to awaken.
Thus,
she decided to hold a training camp at
a hot spring in a strong magic region,
and she ended up dragging Asta
and some of the others there.
Asta and the others head toward the
summit where the hot spring is, but...
I'm not going back!
I...
What we're striving for isn't something
that can be obtained just by luck!
I'll get to the top!
Our dream is waiting for us
at the top, beyond merit!
Saint Elmo's Fire
Strong
Magic
Region
Yultim
Volcano
Trail
I acted all tough and
said I'd get to the top,
but I can't even move an inch in this heat!
What should I do? If my muscles
or guts can't get me through this,
there's nothing I can do right now.
I can't do this my normal way.
Normal? Then what if I try
something that's not normal?
That power!
But how do I use it?
Last time, I sorta went unconscious and
ended up like that when I came to.
I don't know!
Your head looks like it's
about to explode, too.
That's what you get for thinking too hard.
Right...
I can't think too hard about this.
It's not like thinking helped
at all last time, either.
I need to concentrate. Empty my mind...
Transform!
Actually, you can go home after all.
Please forget you saw that!
You got it all wrong! I can do this!
I can do it if I try!
Then I suggest that you keep struggling.
Yes, ma'am!
That's the only thing I can do!
I'll struggle, struggle,
and struggle some more!
Come to think of it, back then,
it wasn't just the fact that
I wasn't thinking about anything.
I was about to die.
Is that why I unconsciously...
Then, I guess...
I'll try jumping into the lava.
I ran head-first into Salamander's explosions!
This isn't going to be scary at all!
No, wait! That's just being reckless!
Did you forget what he told you back then?
Stay calm at all times!
I need to think...
I-It's no use! I can't think of a damn thing!
Because I'm stupid!
I'm so jealous of that
Mana Skin barrier thingie.
If only I had some magic... Damn it!
I haven't been this jealous
of everyone in a long time.
Hang on, Asta. You've gotta stop
being so envious of others.
You've done a lot yourself.
There's no way a fool who doesn't
know himself can manage it.
I don't know myself? Could it be that...
I still don't fully comprehend
the power that I have?
First, I have this anti-magic sword
that only I can hold, because I
don't have any magical powers.
It can cut through any magic.
But I can't do anything
about this environment.
Second, I trained my body and increased my
stamina so that I could use this sword.
I could climb any other mountain,
but not this one.
Third, I can now use the ki detection
that Captain Yami taught me about.
It's now part of my routine.
Using that, I'll know when the rocks or lava
from the eruptions are heading my way, but...
Ki?
Ki
People looking at you,
the sound of their breathing,
their smell, the motions of their muscles,
the vague sense that they're there...
Ki is the blanket term for all of the
different types of life energy
the human body emits.
When I do it, I combine it with
magic and muscle, and fight that way.
Could it be that if I use
ki detection on myself,
I'll find out more about that power?
I was right. I sense my own ki within my body,
as well as something black flowing
into my body from the sword.
If I could only strengthen this flow.
Like, circulate it throughout my body more...
Circulate... like a river? No, like a ring?
What stance would make
that easier to visualize?
This is it!
All right, good! Flow even
more throughout my body!
More... Even more!
More fiercely!
The sword's anti-magic flowed
into Asta's body amplified itself,
and then brought about
a change in Asta's body.
There it is!
I can feel the power overflowing!
All right, I'm gonna make it to the top!
I can't stop!
Y-You can't be serious!
That attack didn't work?
Magical Lifeform
Borula
Don't falter! If we can't
defeat something like this,
we're unworthy to be called Magic Knights!
Yeah, so take care of it already, Leopold.
You got it! Wait... Noelle!
Your attribute is water, which gives
you an edge over that thing!
What are you doing?!
Shut up! It's taking all my concentration
to keep my Mana Skin up!
Asta?
But that form...
One Horn Bull Thrust!
That's my rival for you! So you've
acquired a new special technique, eh?
That black aura...
I shall dub you Black Asta!
Wait, where are you going?!
Hell if I know!
Oh, crap! Oh, crap! I don't know how to stop!
I seem to be heading
toward the summit, but...
That's...
Yuno!
Asta...
I'm headed head-first into the lava!
You're not going to help him?
There's no need.
The anti-magic overflowing from his
body isn't heading toward the lava.
It's headed toward her fierce magic.
She's pulling me to her?
P-Please run!
Run?
You fool!
Among lions, the females
are the ones who hunt!
Flame Magic:
Calidos Brachium!
Impressive.
Looks like that violent lioness
is as psychotic as ever.
How'd she do that midair?
Yo, kid! You alive?
H-Holy crap!
She's definitely Captain
Fuegoleon's big sister!
It looks like you've finally
learned a little about yourself.
But you still have a ways to go.
Yes, ma'am!
I couldn't control it very well,
but I was able to use that power!
I'm gonna get even stronger and
pass that Royal Knights exam!
So you're finally all here, you fools!
The Yultim Volcano becomes
completely dormant at night.
You're supposed to get
here before that, damn it!
At this rate, we're never
going to win back first place!
Those who couldn't make
it up here before nightfall
will try again another day!
Yes, ma'am!
I made it here before the sun set,
but I shall climb it one more time...
no, a hundred more times, and become
even stronger than you, Sister!
That's not enough! Climb it 10,000 times!
Yes, ma'am!
Good! Now I give you all permission
to soak in the hot spring!
Hot springs, huh?
I remember soaking in one back
at Hage Village after my training.
B-But where is the hot spring?
Holy crap! Hot water came outta nowhere!
And now it's a huge bath!
So this is the Yultim Volcano hot spring!
You can't be serious.
The analeptic effect of this hot
spring is the best in our kingdom!
But no one ever bothers to use it,
so we always get it to ourselves.
It's the best hole in the
wall you could ask for!
Well, I mean, any normal bastard would
die before they ever got up here.
All right, you fools! Take off your clothes!
What?!
B-But Sister, we couldn't possibly...
All the ladies are here, too!
What's gonna happen?!
Are we all getting in together?!
I don't know if her name
is Meringue or Orange Juice,
but what the heck's her problem?!
I'm not going to allow Yuno to take
off his clothes in front of any girls!
T-Together with Yami in a hot spring?
I like women who like hot springs.
It doesn't hurt to have someone
wash your back sometimes.
Wh-Why am I having
such ludicrous delusions?!
Okay, don't lose it.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
How am I supposed to stay calm?!
I will never allow any man to
see Sis's pure, naked body!
Earth Magic: Mud Wall Partition!
Anyone who dares to climb
this wall shall die!
Whoa! She created a women's bath
and a men's bath in an instant!
All right, you fools! Hurry up and get in!
Yeah!
The view's as nice as ever.
The temperature's just right.
Sis... You're so b-beautiful.
If this isn't heaven,
then I don't know what is.
Nothing beats having a drink
while soaking in here.
How about it, Charlotte?
Have a drink with me.
No, thank you. I'll pass.
What? Is my liquor too good for you?
No, it's nothing like that.
I hold you in the highest regard,
Lady Mereoleona.
Then drink with me.
I was already a drunken mess in
front of Yami at the Star Festival.
If that happens when I'm naked, I'll just die!
Then I'll have some.
Despite how I look,
I'm way older than all of you!
Oh? The Wind Spirit?
This wall won't suddenly break, will it?
Why are you zoning out?
H-Hey! I can wash my hair myself!
Oh, don't be shy! You said
your name was Noelle?
You've got some guts! I like gutsy women!
Wanna join our squad?
Um... I'm already a Black Bull...
What's so great about that squad?
It's overrun by men.
What? Well, the girls are working hard, too.
I mean, there are some loud
and reckless guys, but...
But they're not all bad...
Most of the Blue Rose Knights are women!
All the guys in our squad are errand boys.
I was hoping we could get that Yuno guy to
join so we could work him to the bone, too.
I never thought he'd get that strong.
All the guys are errand boys...
That doesn't sound so bad.
The men's bath is right over there.
R-Right about now, Yami's over there...
Nude...
Right over there!
Why are you floating like that?
You didn't even drink anything.
And that's how you are after one sip?
S-Sis, are you okay?!
You're so beautiful,
even when you're passed out!
C-Call me "Captain."
You got it, Sis!
Fan me, too...
What happened to them?
This is a decent bath.
The stars are so beautiful.
Lady Acier also loved the
view of the stars from here.
My mother came here?
She's the one who showed me
this spot in the first place.
What was my mother like?
Um... No one will tell me about her.
She was a strong woman.
She would give me lessons quite often.
I was undefeated on the battlefield,
yet I was never able to defeat her once.
It didn't even matter that my magical
attribute had the advantage.
The Steel Warrior Princess who would
dance around the battlefield, Acier Silva...
Her strength and beauty
captivated everyone.
And you look a lot like her.
You're her spitting image.
But your magical abilities
aren't like hers at all.
Your sloppy magic control makes it hard
to believe that you're her daughter.
Her daughter
Her magic was refined beyond belief,
Refined
and it had dignity.
Your magic is so crude and unsightly,
it's hard to believe you're royalty.
Crude
And that's why you must surpass her.
You may look like your mother,
but surpass her with a
strength that's all your own.
Yes, ma'am!
Of course. Even that idiot who doesn't
have any magical powers is doing his best.
Even if I lack talent, I'm not
going to run or make excuses.
I'm getting fired up,
and my body's feeling warm, too.
Wait, it's actually getting hotter?!
How dare you try to show off?!
I'm sure you can't handle this heat!
I'll melt the cool right off of you!
I'm totally fine.
What did you say?!
Leo, he's not trying to act cool or anything!
He just hates losing!
I also hate losing!
Let's see who can stay in here the longest!
Hey! Why are you cooling down
the water with your wind?!
That's not fair!
It's not cheating. Magic is
part of my strength, too.
Besides, you're heating it
with magic in the first place.
What the hell are you dumbasses doing?
There are better ways to enjoy a hot spring.
Captain Yami!
What are the other ways to enjoy a hot spring?
Do you mean working out?
Or maybe working out?
It's working out, isn't it?!
Shut the hell up.
Is your head full of muscles, too?
You're the only moron who'd enjoy that.
No!
It's not working out?
And here's another one with
a head full of muscles.
Captain... Then what's this
other way to enjoy it?
What else?
We're gonna go peep at the women's bath!
D-Did he say peep?
Are we allowed to do that?
Won't they kill us if they find out?
I can't believe what a bunch of whiners you are.
If you're a true man,
this is a risk you've gotta take.
Even if it costs your life.
I-Is that what it means...
...to be a man?
Yes. All guys are like that.
I'm sure you want to take
a look, too, Mister Cool.
No, I don't.
You stupid little punk.
Don't you try and act cool with me,
you breezy little pretty boy.
Uh... again, this isn't just part of
my character, so please stop...
Well, someone doesn't give a shit about
your character, you dumbass.
And that's me.
Please stop, Captain Yami!
Yuno really isn't interested!
He's only ever bathed with
guys since he was a kid!
Come to think of it,
my brother loved baths, too.
Leopold, I still have many
things I must teach you.
Of course, Big Brother!
W-Wait! Was the thing he said he
had to teach me back then...
Leopold, what I'm going to
teach you right now is...
To peep into women's baths!
Of course, Big Brother!
There's no way that happened!
No... My brother would never look.
Actually, he'd probably be
furious and try to stop us.
What are you mumbling about, bomb head?
Why are you trying to be like that
Hot-Blooded King of Hardnoses?
You're going to surpass him, aren't you?
That's right!
I'm going to surpass my brother!
What the hell are you
guys standing around for?
This is a battle, in a sense.
Why are you so scared of being killed?
We came here to whip you
wimps back into shape!
He's right!
You must never run from a battle!
We are the best! The Crimson Lion Kings!
All right! We're gonna peep!
Let's show them how manly we are!
Yeah!
Wh-What is that?
Don't tell me those guys...
Oh? Listen to those fearless voices.
Now they sound more like
the Crimson Lion Kings.
But they're going to try to peep!
You're never going to see
Sis's pure, naked body!
Earth Magic: Mud Wall Cliff!
Don't back down!
We are the Crimson Lion Kings! We can
climb over any wall, no matter how high!
Yeah!
You can't be serious.
Okay, get going, kid!
You've learned a new technique.
Now go become a real man!
No! My heart belongs to Sister,
so I absolutely refuse to look!
Uh... Sure.
Hot Spring Training Camp Arc
Fin!!
Hot Spring Training Camp Arc... Fin.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Exhaustion Recovery
Exhaustion Recovery.
Sister Lily always heals the people
of Hage Village with her sweet smile.
And it's said that it's the Hage
Hot Spring that heals her soul.
But there are times when she's so
busy with her duties at the church
that even a hot spring is not
enough to help her recover.
When that happens, she eats
tatoes pickled in black vinegar.
Father introduced me to these, and they
worked instantly the day after I ate them!
Order now, and we'll throw in some
garlic extract-infused moguro leaf juice.
Order now!
Express delivery!
Order now for free shipping!
Don't wait! Order now!
She's on an infomercial!
Sister is as beautiful as ever!
Hello, everyone. It's been a while.
Asta and Yuno are working so hard!
Everyone at the church is proud of you two.
Black Clover, Page 73:
"The Royal Knights Selection Test."
Page 73
The Royal Knights Selection Test
Make sure you're taking care of yourselves.