It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Langris and the other
members of the Golden Dawn
who had been reincarnated as
elves infiltrated the castle.
Yami and Finral rushed to the castle
and were forced into a rough battle.
It doesn't matter how many of you
humans try and attack us! You cannot wi—
Of course the ones who
are most worth slicing up
would show up at the castle, huh?
Jack joined the battle, and they
were able to turn the tables.
They regrouped with Nozel and the
others and rushed into the castle.
Kivn had already infiltrated the Silvas' home,
where she attacked Nebra and Solid.
Damn it!
Nozel!
Noelle!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Compass Magic: Another Atlas!
Noelle and Nozel joined the fight,
but they were also attacked
by Kivn's compass magic.
Nozel!
Calm down.
You can no longer fight.
Worry about your own—
Battlefield Dancer
Mother! Mother!
At least realize you're being
attacked and evade, you slowpoke!
You piece of trash!
How dare you eat before me?!
If you're mad, just try to get me back.
I'm sure it's hard to look in the
mirror with a face like yours.
You should be grateful for my kindness.
What's with that flimsy little grimoire?
Are you really royalty?
It's just pathetic that you can't
even control your powers.
It disgusts me that you're my little sister.
I will not have someone as shameful
as you in the Silver Eagles.
Pathetic, isn't it?
What, really?
Noelle is practicing her water magic
against a dead tree by herself at night.
Not only that, she keeps missing.
A few even come back to hit her,
so she just gets soaked.
I couldn't even do that as
a joke. She's so talented.
Maybe she's even some kind of genius.
I hate to think of her as my sister, though.
Noelle, I've decided which Magic Knights
squad you'll be joining.
You'll be joining the Black Bulls.
The matter has already been settled.
What?
The Black Bulls? You mean
the worst of the worst?
That's perfect!
Don't they just do lame missions out
in the boonies? Like hunting boars?
That's perfect for you, Noelle.
It's okay... It's okay...
It's okay.
I did all that training.
I can do this... I can do this!
I can still fight!
Let's show her the true power
of the royal House of Silva!
Right!
Unfortunately,
your attacks will never reach
me in this sealed space.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
You're just wasting your magic.
You're only going to exhaust yourself.
And after all I went through to
try to let you die peacefully.
What... What should I do?
Even using Mana Skin, I can't use
Sea Dragon's Lair in this magical space.
Even when I direct my magic with
all my strength, this is all I can do.
All I can manage are simple
movements at close range.
The only possible strategy is...
You're trying very hard, but I
wonder how long you'll last.
Nozel...
Think. If Asta or the other
Black Bulls were here,
they would think of something crazy...
Damn it! If we don't break her spell,
we can't get out of here!
There's no way out!
No way out?
I can't currently use creation
magic within this space,
but I can intentionally cast
that rampaging spell!
Nozel, please help me out!
This is...
What in the world is going on?
Curse you...
You flooded this enclosed
magical space with water.
Another Atlas traps everything inside.
I'm going to drown. I have no
choice but to undo the spell.
How dare you, human...
In a mere instant?!
Such speed and precision...
That was amazing... I expected
that from Nozel, but Noelle...
W-We did it, Nozel.
Th-Thank you very much for going
along with my reckless plan.
It was quite a crazy method of fighting,
unbefitting of royalty.
But we were able to win because of it.
So this is the method of fighting
that you've learned...
Because you look just like our mother,
I feared I'd lose her again.
Huh?
I didn't think you would become strong.
I couldn't lose you. I had to protect you.
That's why I tried to keep
you off the battlefield.
But you became strong.
And that means I was mistaken.
So, er...
I-I apologize, Noelle.
Nozel...
...apologized?
N-Nozel...
The fight is not yet over.
We must treat Nebra at once.
No...
Nozel...
Nozel! Nozel!
Too bad for you.
This mad world will not end.
It's now even bigger and more powerful.
It cannot be stopped.
Damn it! What are we supposed to do?!
There's nothing you can do.
Give up, grieve, and regret
your actions, royals.
I won't give up.
There has to be...
There has to be some way!
Think, Noelle!
You can do this!
After all, you were finally able
to get Nozel to acknowledge you!
At this rate, Nozel and Nebra will...
I can wait until you slowly weaken,
but I think you'd prefer to die quickly,
you foolish and sinful humans!
I don't have a single good memory of them...
But they're still my siblings!
Long distance attacks won't hit.
I can't do any complicated
magic manipulation.
But if it's nearer and denser...
This is a spell that I can cast only
because of this situation
and who I am right now!
The biggest factor in getting spells
to manifest is natural talent.
But dedicated training and unwavering
effort can also pay off.
In some rare cases,
intense wishes or determination
can grant power in a crisis, as well.
Many royal mages acquire spells
intuitively using their innate,
powerful magic and natural resourcefulness.
And because of this ability,
they rarely ever research, train,
or have their lives put in
danger on the battlefield.
But while Noelle had an enormous
amount of magic as well as talent,
as a member of the Black Bulls,
she trained, worked hard,
and fought for her life.
Everything she had gone through,
and her strong desire to protect her siblings,
gave her the power to get through this crisis!
Water Creation Magic: Valkyrie Armor!
Noelle!
What is this magic?
A tremendous amount of magic
is being concentrated.
Royal girl...
It's like she's swimming
through this space.
Is she riding mana from the magical attacks,
and the disturbance in this magical space,
as if they were some sort of high waves?
Is her armor a spell that lets her
control all the mana around her?
But... will you be able to evade all of these?
I still have the absolute advantage.
If I find even the slightest
tear in your defense,
this world will rip off your armor!
It's hard to believe I was
struggling just a moment ago.
I feel like I've been freed from my cage.
I never knew magic was so freeing.
I wonder if this is how Mother felt, too.
Mother... The Dancing
Princess of the Battlefield...
You managed to cut through
all of that attack?
You're mine!
Willful Compass!
The mana currents you dance
through so elegantly...
I'm going to change their destination,
as well as your own...
To hell!
Fall, royal!
She overruled my mana compulsion?!
Sorry, but I'm not dancing elegantly.
This armor... Everything that
touches this mana...
is under my control!
I'm desperately struggling and fighting,
forcing my way forward!
Now be destroyed!
Both you and this mad world!
Did I win?
Hurry, take Nozel and Nebra...
This isn't good. I don't have
enough magic to fight this many.
How dare you do that to Kivn?
It appears that we have
underestimated you humans.
That will not happen again.
Begone!
Solid!
Now that's what I call a
perfect surprise attack.
Not bad. It's even more
insane when it's doubled.
What was that spell?
I've never seen anything like it.
Don't let your guard down! Curse you, human!
Considering the huge amounts of magic
you were throwing at each other,
I figured a crowd would show up eventually.
Zora!
Go on, get to work,
you royal attendant jerk.
House of Silva Attendant
Paplo Espuma
What are you thinking, bringing me
somewhere so dangerous?!
I saved your ass, so now
you're gonna listen to me.
No...
More importantly, if you don't hurry up,
you won't have any masters anymore.
Huh? Lady Nebra and Lord Nozel!
O-Oh, no!
Bubble Recovery Magic: Bubble Refresher!
Lord Solid, please bring me Lord Nozel!
Lord Solid?!
What? You lost your will to fight?
Give me a break, you royal Magic Knight.
The other two got their asses kicked, too.
All you do is flaunt your arrogance,
and this is all you've got? Pathetic.
You can't even protect your own family,
you royal Magic Knights Squad captain?
Nozel...
You're finally receiving
your grimoire next year.
I can't wait to see what kind
of magic you're going to learn.
I'll learn spells of unparalleled power
and become a powerful Magic Knights
Squad captain, just like you, Mother.
Well... Nebra and Solid both have
water magic, just like your father.
It's just a hunch, but I think
this little one will be the same.
You're the only one who
inherited my steel attribute.
Make sure you protect your
siblings with that magic, okay?
That's right... I...
You guys are supposed to be stronger
than the rest of us commoners, aren't you?
Let's see just how brave you can be!
Hey, that's enough out of y—
It's all right.
Nozel?
He's exactly right.
Groveling at something like this
brings shame upon the royal House of Silva,
as well as the title of
Captain of the Silver Eagles.
I'll reinforce my physical
functions with magic.
Nozel... I never knew mercury
magic could do that.
It's such sophisticated magic!
Let us go, Noelle.
Yes, sir!
All of you bastards have so
much magic, it makes me sick.
I'm gonna need you to dial it
down to commoner level.
Ash Magic: Revelation of the Cowardly.
Here they come!
Take my magic with you, Noelle!
You won't escape!
You're too slow!
Hold still, damn it!
You won't get away!
Trap magic?
I've rigged plenty for ya.
The Revelation of the Cowardly reveals
where I've placed my trap spells.
If they show even a moment of vulnerability,
I'm sure those royals can take care of them!
You can't move so easily with your
body in that condition, can you?!
Nozel!
He's ignoring the force of those spells?
What was that spell?
Considering your reactions,
I guess you guys don't know about
complicated magic like counter-traps.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Your control is faltering!
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver!
This is nothing!
These spells were derived and
developed over countless years.
Complicated human spells...
Looks like you elves don't know about them.
Langris! No matter what you think of me,
I'll always be your older brother,
and you're my younger brother!
Come back, Langris!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 109: "Spatial Mage Brothers."
Page 109
Spatial Mage Brothers
I can actually do it if I try!