It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Holy crap! There's a castle
floating in the sky!
That's the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
The Royal Knights, a team of
individuals specially selected
to defeat the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
finally began their operation!
So that's where Licht is...
We will now split up into
five groups and proceed.
Group 1 will attack from the upper left.
Yes, ma'am!
Group 2 will attack from the lower left.
'Kay!
Yes, ma'am.
Group 3 will attack from the upper right.
Group 4 will attack from the lower right.
Yes, ma'am!
And we're going to attack front and center.
All that matters is if you're weak or strong.
You're here because you're strong,
are you not?
The fools that Yami selected...
Don't let me down.
Yes, ma'am!
Sure thing. Guess I'll
be careful, Lady Captain.
I'm sure you don't need detailed plans.
Take down any enemies you encounter
as you proceed toward the center.
You may do that
however you prefer!
The Royal Knights infiltrated
the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout,
which was a floating dungeon
located in the strong magic
region known as Gravito Stones,
and were headed toward its center.
Their ultimate goal is to
defeat the leader, Licht.
H-Holy crap!
Wait, do we even need to be here?!
Meanwhile, back at the Black
Bulls' hideout...
Well, I'm heading out for a bit.
Where are you going, Captain?
Apparently, Golden Weird Mask Guy
wants to apologize for Langris's behavior.
So I'm heading to the
Golden Dawn's headquarters.
Actually, why the hell do I have to go?
If he wants to apologize,
he should come over here.
Then can I go see Marie, too?
Of course not, you dumbass.
What if we get an emergency mission?
Tch.
I'm going to go visit Finral.
How long is that boy going to stay asleep?
I hope he wakes up soon.
I'm gonna go train!
I'm gonna get even stronger!
You can do it! Don't even worry about
not being picked for the Royal Knights,
you virgin delinquent.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Who are you calling a virgin?!
And I'm not worried!
I'm going to go find some delicious noms, la!
You should all look forward to it, la!
H-Have a safe trip!
Come back soon.
It gets lonely when the whole gang isn't here.
Well, see ya. Make sure you don't let any
bandits take over the place or anything.
Man... what a pain.
Make sure you ask that quack
doctor how Finral's doing.
Of course. Sure thing!
Stronger... I'm gonna get stronger!
Just wait, la... All of you delicious noms
that have grown just to be eaten...
Me and my sheep cooks are coming for you, la!
The Black Bulls' Hideout
Fidget, fidget... Fidget, fidget...
What the hell?
It's not like we're going to do anything,
but both Grey and Gordon are sitting near me.
Fidget, fidget...
It's probably because all
the rowdy guys are gone,
but this is somehow really distracting.
Fidget, fidget, blush, blush...
It's nice spending time together,
just the three of us.
We have so much to talk about,
and my heart is happy.
I'm so excited.
Hey!
Want to exchange secrets?
Though I already know all your secrets...
Heheh.
If we get a summons for a mission, I'll go,
so you two can rest in your own rooms.
N-No! B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-But
th-th-th-th-th-th-that's...
Oh, come on.
If we get a mission,
of course I'm going with you.
What the hell are they even saying?!
Just go get some rest already.
I'm telling you that I'll go so I can get some
more money to get presents for Marie.
You don't need to hold back.
It's so embarrassing, not using
my transformation magic
and talking in my normal form.
I wanted to form deeper bonds with
everyone at the Underwater Temple, too.
But the others consider me a part of the team!
So I should try to stay
myself in front of them!
I didn't get to create deeper bonds with
everyone at the Star Festival, either.
Gauche even complimented me on how I look!
So I'm going to deepen my bonds
with the two of you today.
As deep as I possibly can get them.
I'm going to my room
so I can concentrate on making
this doll of my goddess.
Let me know if we get a mission.
It's so embarrassing for you
two to see me like this,
but it's even more embarrassing
to be left alone together
and have him stare at me! I just can't!
Then I'll go to your room, too.
I don't care if it's messy.
We went to the library together, after all!
What the hell is wrong with these two?!
I need to be more confident
and speak to him myself!
G-G-G-G-G-Gauche, wh-wh-wh-wh-what...
What's that you're making?
Oh, this?
The other day, when I became a nerd,
I realized how awesome figures are.
So I'm making a 1/8th scale Marie!
M-Marie?
When I'm finished, I'll let you worship her.
I-I see?
I already knew
that Gauche had an interest in dolls.
The day that I can show you
my collection has come at last.
Peeksies...
My handmade Black Bulls dolls.
They look just like everyone, don't they?
V-V-V-Voodoo dolls?!
So cute.
I'm so scared!
Seriously, you're terrifying.
Huh?!
I probably shouldn't be the one to say this,
but if you want to get
along with everyone else,
you need to make an effort to be friendlier.
Starting with your face.
M-My face?!
Try smiling.
Smiling?
Go on.
Ba-dump, ba-dump...
That's terrifying!
D'oh...
D'oh... D'oh...
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Don't touch her.
I-I won't!
Where's the bathroom today?
Today, it's on the second
floor on the far right.
I guess I should've asked this sooner,
but why do parts of this hideout
keep changing randomly?
Who knows?
It's been like this ever since I joined.
Talk about a pain.
I'm sure it's some kind of magic,
but what the hell is the point?
P-P-P-P-P-P-Please come
back as soon as possible!
I heard Charmy and Vanessa
talk about it before, but...
I-I saw it, la! It was kind of floaty!
It wasn't one of my sheep cooks! It was
something even more mysterious, la!
I swear I wasn't seeing things!
It was really there! It was a ghost.
I'm telling the truth.
What if it wasn't magic,
but was actually a ghost?
Please don't make weird jokes like tha—
What the hell are these things?!
P-Please don't look at me!
This is no time to be embarrassed!
Hurry up and transform, damn it!
So many of you came here
to be friends with me...
The hell they did!
I don't know what these guys are,
but this is obviously an enemy attack!
Hurry up and get ready to fi—
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
So this is Asta's hideout.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
Sally
Rades
Sadly, Asta's not here today, though.
I was hoping to dissect him while
he's still alive. What a shame.
Sally, Asta's not your toy.
He's my toy. And after I came all
this way to play with him, too...
Eye of the Midnight Sun
Valtos
Sally, Rades... Don't forget our objective.
But I'm sure I can get some other decent toys
while I'm at the Black Bulls' hideout.
I wanna conduct experiments! Dissections!
Modifications! Operations!
Wow!
I don't know who the hell is dumb
enough to attack our hideout...
But now you're gonna pay!
There you are, you useless Magic Knights.
You bastards...
You know them, Gauche?
Do I know them?
They're from that dirtbag terrorist
group, the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The Eye of...
So what the hell do you want?
Did you come to get your asses kicked again?
Since you're pulling the strings on those
zombies, I'm assuming you're Rades.
You assumed correctly.
We happen to be looking for something.
You're looking for something?
What could you possibly want
from our broken-down hideout?
I'm sure you guys wouldn't know about it,
but you've got something really good.
If you're looking for friendship, it's right here.
They're not!
And as long as we're here looking for that,
we figured we'd also destroy your hideout.
Oh? Then you can die!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
Whee!
That's right... My magic
doesn't work on that woman.
Tch.
Come on, relax.
Gauche, was it? I have no
interest in you, anyway.
We've been told to not kill you, so...
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Who knows? I'm not really sure,
but Master Licht insisted.
The leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Actually, before...
I couldn't...
risk hurting you...
What are you talking about?
What? You know him?
Sorry I beat the crap out of him.
Of course I don't know this bastard.
You'll understand eventually...
I guess he did say that...
So, let's play.
Are you ready, Black Bulls losers?
Now's not the time to think about that.
For now, I've gotta do something
about these bastards.
The captain and the others probably
won't be back for a while,
so the three of us will take care of them!
There ya go.
Dark Magic Item:
Special Properties Plus Alpha Reinforcement!
All right! Let's go!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun... The really
bad people who hurt my friends...
Stay away from our hideout.
Poison Curse Magic: Aufwachen Dachs.
Since we're dealing with the dead,
I don't have to hold back with my magic.
Damn, man.
Oho... That's some impressive poison.
But if we're playing with poison...
I'll just neutralize it with my gel!
G-Gauche!
I learned a new spell!
T-Transformation Magic: Magic Conversion!
She turned my gel magic...
...into crystal magic?
N-Now, Gauche!
Right! Now I can actually crack it!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain!
Oho!
Ooh, you can change the properties of
magic itself. That's pretty interesting!
I think I'm a little interested in you now!
P-P-P-Please don't look at me!
That's the way. This'll make
crushing you guys even more fun.
Valtos!
Right.
You're up, Number Zero...
Mikael Caesar.
What the hell is that creepy thing?
Do it.
It used two different
magic attributes at once?
And why the hell is it so powerful?
Making this guy was a pain in the ass, you know.
He was only completed because I helped
you with some dark magic items.
You'd better be grateful.
That thing's made from two different corpses.
Both of those corpses used to be
Magic Knights Squad captains!
You'll never be able to
defeat my perfect corpses
with your stupid little tricks!
Hurry up and destroy this stupid
Magic Knights Squad hideout!
Let's go.
Stop it...
Since I was born into a family that dealt with
curses, I wasn't allowed to make friends.
So I ended up unable to speak to people,
and had this hideous poison magic.
I was shunned by everyone around me.
Stop it...
Because I was unable to be self-confident
and couldn't reveal my true self,
people didn't trust me and
were creeped out by me.
I was all alone.
But even then...
You're hilarious! Come join my squad!
A bull! That's friggin' awesome!
I-I'm awesome?
I'm happy that you're all having fun.
You'll be even happier after
eating a lot of delicious noms, la!
Maybe he'll be able to speak louder someday.
It's delicious.
This cooking made with love is filling
not only my stomach, but my heart, too.
Happy birthday, la!
Come on, let's drink!
Th-Thank you very much!
He's fast asleep.
This one's Asta and this one's Grey?
Wait, maybe the other way around?
Either way, your muscles are creepy.
This place...
...accepted me for who I am!
What the hell are we supposed
to do with this freak?!
Don't give up, Gauche.
We're going to protect our hideout!
For crying out loud... I guess
you can speak loud and clear!
Damn it...
Now I have things I want to protect
besides Marie!
And once the captain gets back,
who knows what he'll do to us if
we couldn't protect the hideout?
Wow, they can still stand.
But I think it's about time
I dissected you guys.
Having a lot of spirit isn't gonna help you.
It doesn't change the fact
that you guys can't win.
Now, I'm gonna finish you off!
Make sure you don't kill them, though.
I'm gonna dissect them
while they're still alive.
Don't hold your breath on that one.
Go, Mikael Caesar!
Emergency! Emergency!
What the?
It's floating?
What's going on?
Emergency! Emergency!
What's... going... on... here?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Gordon and
Grey's Comedy Routine
Gordon and Grey's Comedy Routine.
G-G-G-Gordon and Grey's Comedy Routine!
Bulls
Hello, we're Gordon and Grey.
Please don't look at me!
Don't listen to my voice, either!
Cover your ears!
But then we can't do our comedy routine.
W-Well, I can't tell what
you're saying anyway,
so how can we even do a comedy routine?
Well, you got me there. Hahaha.
Th-That's all from us!
Bulls
You two need to apologize
to every comedian out there!
What? What the hell is going on?
I don't know who you are,
but speak faster, damn it!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 90: "Crazy Magic Battle."
Page 90
Crazy Magic Battle
My little sister, the goddess Marie...
I'm gonna hurry up and end this
battle so I can come see you!