It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The terrifying truth revealed
by the resurrected devil:
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
had devoted their lives to getting
revenge against the humans,
but that was all part of this
devil's 500-year-old plan.
Rampage as you please.
The final state of an elf who's
overflowing with malice...
The devil turned the
haggard Patry into a dark elf
and had him attack Asta and Yuno.
Hate...
Crap...
This spell is...
This magic is...
The Ultimate Natural Enemy
This spell is...
the one that gave
Captain Yami all that trouble.
And now, it's even more powered up!
Gauche managed to help us back then, but...
But...
Patry...
So much magic is being concentrated.
This is bad!
Hate... Hate...
Demon Light Magic: Ray of Divine Punishment!
Die.
But with how Yuno and I are now...
We somehow made it through.
Asta!
Thanks, Yuno!
That was close.
He should've used up most of
his mana with that spell.
Hate...
I hate you!
You've got to be kidding me!
You can't be serious.
That sinister magic just keeps welling up...
Even if I can't change into my black form...
I can't lose here!
Asta! Yuno!
Die.
It seems your appearance has changed a bit,
but we meet at last.
Nozel!
Captain Nozel...
I...
am nowhere near as lenient as him!
Hate... Hate...
You cannot defeat me.
Magical attributes play a big role
in how a magic battle can play out.
That is why Magic Knights act in teams,
so that they can cover each other's
weaknesses when they go on missions.
And that is exactly why Nozel
Silva's all-purpose magic
is a team unto itself.
His ever-changing mercury magic
can face any enemy, and has
always yielded results.
Hate...
My magic's affinity with your light
magic is better than anyone else's.
Using vast, sophisticated magic to
create a huge amount of mercury,
he instantaneously hardens it, smooths
its surface, and reflects the light.
Though I don't plan on losing to the one
I have the worst affinity with, either.
And I have been sharpening my
skills for this moment, too.
Captain Nozel...
He always seemed cold, but he
is the Captain of the Silver Eagles.
He's super amazing!
But what's going on with the other guy?
He unleashed all that power and
can still move that fast?
I see you like to scurry away
like the vermin you are, but...
The preparations are complete.
Since this spell requires
maximum control and power,
I couldn't use it in the last battle
because my magic was being disturbed.
Mercury Creation Magic:
Silver Star of Execution.
Hate... Hate!
This spell will trap you and your light
magic while continuously attacking.
It's an inescapable prison.
Hate... Die!
I hate you... Die!
Let your own deeds
be your undoing.
He deflected all of the attacks.
He has such precise control.
Whoa...
Asta and Yuno, was it not?
I am the one who will become the Wizard King.
You mentioned that you were going to
become the Wizard King, didn't you?
Then...
I guess you're my rival, too.
Then I guess you're my rival, too!
I'm going to be the Wizard King.
No, it's me!
It's me!
It's me, me, me!
Patry... If I hadn't stayed quiet...
Would you not have ended up like this?
Hey, Patry... Can you hear me?
Crap... I think I'm done for...
Patry... Licht...
It's warm...
Why?
I don't need a reason to save
someone who's about to die.
It doesn't matter to me if they're
an enemy or from another race!
Damn it... So in the end,
I'm being saved by human royalty?
That's why I didn't want
to get involved with them.
Regardless of the times,
they're always like this.
Indeed. You were chosen...
as my brilliant, foolish pawn.
Now, then... Let's finish you off.
Hang on a sec! Wait!
I don't think that's how
this is supposed to play out!
You can't be serious.
And how else is this supposed to play out?
This man is the leader of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
He took many lives and threw the
Clover Kingdom into chaos and confusion.
Yeah, I know that, but...
Please wait.
His body belongs to
Captain Vangeance. I can tell.
Vangeance?
What are you talking about? His face
and his magic are completely different.
I'm unsure of the reason why,
but I can definitely sense
Captain Vangeance from him.
And...
He might be able to return Captain Vangeance
back to normal with his sword.
Leave it to me!
What are you talking about?
Do you want to die?
How much do you want to kill the guy?!
Did you not hear a word we just said?!
Could I at least give it a try? I can, right?!
Do as you please.
Thanks!
This is... way more anti-magic
than I've ever seen before.
Actions come with consequences.
You can't escape that.
Make sure you never forget that, human.
Asta?
Asta!
Hate... Hate... Hate...
What the heck?!
Is this, like, his memories
or his soul or something?!
Is everything that was sucked out
through the sword flowing into me?
That's...
Hate... Hate... Hate...
My head hurts so much.
Unforgivable!
A time spell tremendous enough to save
all the people of this kingdom...
Impressive.
But it appears that you've
used up all the time and magic
that you had accumulated.
I'm sure you saw my attack.
But you couldn't cancel that time spell
in order to evade.
Because...
you are the Wizard King.
Wizard King...
Wizard King!
Hate... Hate...
Hopeless... Hopeless...
Sad... It hurts...
Frustration... It hurts...
Hopeless...
It hurts...
For Licht's sake, I... I was deceived.
Resurrecting everyone was a mistake.
So many sacrifices that he didn't even want...
I made the wrong choice.
I was never chosen at all.
"Humans are evil."
Did I... just want to believe that?
If... If that was actually true...
I mean, William and I were
able to understand each—
We can never understand each other!
This is the humans' fault! I hate those fools!
They cannot be forgiven!
Humans are all evil!
That's right...
This is all... the humans' fault!
There you are, you bastard.
Hey, I'm Asta.
We meet at last.
So on the inside, I guess
you're a kid about my age.
What do you want, you... human?
You were fooled and couldn't protect
what was important to you.
You lost the light that you believed in...
and you're a mess of emotions. I know that!
But that's exactly why I'm going to say this.
Quit giving up!
What you're doing right now is running away!
You just stopped thinking
and locked yourself up in darkness
because it's easier that way!
Sh-Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
What could you possibly
understand, you stupid human?!
Shut up with all that "human" crap!
I'm Asta, damn it!
How dare you kill the Wizard King?!
He was such an amazing person
who was respected by everyone!
I... We all wanted to be like him!
You took everyone hostage
and killed the Wizard King.
Your reincarnation hurt innocent
people all over the kingdom!
Just like you can't forgive humans,
I won't ever forgive you!
That's why we... also...
After doing all that, where do
you get off acting like this?!
Huh?
Just because you did something you can't fix,
you shouldn't just despair and run away!
Aren't you supposed to be trying
to stop that devil bastard, too?!
You made up your mind to do all this so far!
You did that!
Even if you weren't chosen,
even if you weren't wanted,
even if you aren't forgiven...
You need to stand your ground,
no matter how pathetic you are!
Wh-What's with you?
Why are you acting so desperate?
Just leave me alone!
Even though I wasn't chosen, wanted,
or forgiven, I made up my mind.
I'm going to become the Wizard King!
So... I'm not going to give
up on you guys, either!
You're...
We can come to understand each other.
Asta!
Asta...
Holy crap, that was close!
That brat managed to bring Patry back...
Honestly... I've never met
such a foolish human before.
What'd you say, you jerk?!
Asta...
I guess you're having Captain Vangeance
hold off for a little while longer.
The thing that I can do right now...
Could you see this through
to the end with me?
Yeah!
I'm not letting that bastard have his way!
That must be it.
The door to the outside.
And...
I won't... let you... go.
You're not even fully awakened yet,
and you already can't forgive me.
Well, I guess I can't blame you.
I couldn't take this grimoire from you,
so I've taken it from someone very dear to you.
I'm surprised you can manage that,
after spawning that giant demon
left your soul so unstable.
Well done indeed.
I must reward you for all of your hard work.
I'll kill you off properly.
"Lightning Lance."
"Earth Shield."
"Storm of Blades."
"Split open."
And... "Bind."
That sword can absorb magic,
but I imagine it doesn't fare as
well against physical matter.
"Iron Spear."
My word soul magic can not only
make whatever I say happen,
but it can also summon physical matter.
You are no threat to me when
you only have one sword.
Goodbye...
Leader of the elves!
Oh? So were was an elf who
wasn't an Apostle of Sephira.
I saw Baval enter the
Shadow Palace, so I followed him.
After that, I found Baval unconscious,
and I knew something was wrong.
You fiend! You're a devil, aren't you?
Hey, now...
A devil?
Do those things actually exist?
I mean, if anything,
you're way too pasty to be one.
It looks like Nozel headed toward
the other huge magic that I sensed,
so I came over here, but...
What's the deal with this thing's ki?
You keep showing up one after another.
It's turning into quite the party.
I can only sense malice from him!
Human... You came this far
just to get in my way?
I've got plenty of things to ask and say to you,
but I'm pretty sure we have to
take care of that guy first.
I'm also pretty sure I've never seen
a more obvious bad guy before.
I'm just going to let you
die if you can't keep up.
I guess you're just as
unreasonable as the girl I know.
You just make sure that body doesn't get hurt!
"Wave of Flame."
Dark Magic: Black Hole.
Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
"Storm of Blades."
"Wither."
Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
My, what masterful teamwork.
I figured you were on bad
terms with each other.
Yeah, I can't explain it, either.
Okay, everyone. Here we go... Petit—
Oh, come on now, cuties.
You shouldn't split up so much.
Okay... He's healed.
Everyone together, now...
He's our savior. We need to be careful with him.
What's this bird?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What the?!
Huh? Nero?
Take me to the demon's bones.
Did Nero just speak?!
Wait, I was asleep, so I could still be dreaming.
Someone pinch my cheek real hard!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 117: "Breaking the Seal."
Page 117
Breaking the Seal
Ow! It wasn't a dream! Nero actually spoke!