It does look smaller than I expected.
It has the proper air to it for an inheritance of the Empire.
And such a fantastic array of color. It's simply splendid.
Commander?
What?
It is a valuable inheritance, but to use so many of our resources for it is...
It was Lord Alfred's passion and iron will, to make this painting the ideological basis...
...for an unstoppable National Socialist movement.
Understand that.
Yes, sir.
He has promised our party financial assistance,
as well as an introduction to the Anti-Communist Alliance, when this plan succeeds.
Although we are the minority in America, with this painting our party will make great progress.
What's with that painting?
We know that their psychological stability is different from ours,
but coming with that much weaponry and equipment couldn't be done by someone penniless.
For their purpose, their investment is obscenely out of proportion.
But, wait...
Someone who puts in too much money...
I see.
You're pretty sharp, Rock.
We were hired with a lot of money for that painting too.
That much money on the line doesn't match with the artist's lack of fame.
Hopefully that mystery will be solved tonight.
I've got a bad feeling.
Rock, go feed Revy will ya?
All right.
Pizza delivery won't come out here.
Tell her to give up and eat something from a can.
Revy.
Yeah.
Here's dinner.
Dutch says to get something to eat.
I'll leave it here.
If this is about what happened in the U-boat...
Rock.
That's over.
There's not a single reason to go over that again.
Right?
Yeah.
It's a good night.
The moon is about to sink and the stars will come out.
As that happens we'll raid their ship.
I've kept their ship just at radar range.
Good.
Revy and I will raid the ship.
They got what they wanted, they ought to be relaxing by now.
Idiots, keep toasting each other.
We're going to bang on our Tom-toms and raid them like Navajos.
Wagner is shit compared to that.
Sorry, but we've got one more job, partner.
Got it.
A lead bullet blastfest bargain.
I'll search, you distract. Start some shit.
Alright.
I've got no complaints if I can kill who I can kill and steal what I can steal.
I'm going, Rock.
You seem glum.
Something happen with Rock?
Nothing.
Oh no! Oh no!
And the first little piggy came to its end.
Oink, oink, oink.
It's started.
I'm going to the deck above us from the bow.
Liven up the place with a big ruckus.
OK?
Yeah.
I'm going to eat until I get my fill.
Where did that gunfire come from?
I don't know.
Getting wild is acceptable, but tell them to stop shooting.
Yes sir.
Commander! The enemy!
The enemy is on board!
We are being invaded!
They're really at it...
Hey.
At times like these, what kind of face do we make while waiting?
Do we sit here looking bored, smoking and drinking beer?
When you two were being shot at this afternoon, Dutch looked very calm.
I was jealous of him.
Either way, we're not the type to be able to shoot at human beings.
That's why we watch the fort.
All squad leaders gather your men in front of the galley!
Gather there and...
Yo.
Bastard.
Take aim!
Boy...
So, they just look impressive. Not much else.
So, is the boss here?
The commander isn't here.
He's up another level!
That's very kind of you.
Revy, can you hear me?
Revy? Revy?
Where are you?
Damn it. That bitch.
Wait, please wait.
We're hired outsiders.
So please...
So?
So what?
Non-affiliated and non-resistant doesn't matter.
If you're all insured there's no problem, right?
Oink, oink, oink.
Revy.
What the hell are you doing?
Fritz!
Give the lawless a decisive, righteous blow.
Roger.
What? I was just starting shit, Dicky.
Making bloodbaths is what we do.
A gunman is a professional. One who shoots with her moods, is just a shooter.
I don't remember hiring Charles Whitman.
Charles Whitman famously killed 15 and wounded 31 from a tower in Austin, Texas in 1966.
Going wild and losing your shit is your decision.
But if you fuck up, I die too.
Cool as a cucumber, Revy.
If you can't handle that, climb a church and shoot up idiots.
So, you're going to lecture me too?
Don't make me laugh.
Of course, Two-Hands.
I'm your employer.
I thought you were going to kill me.
Me too, partner.
Trust, my ass.
You couldn't even take a joke.
So what's next, big boss?
The commander.
We find him.
Your excellency!
This enemy is definitely those grave-robbers!
Currently our comrades are boldly countering and dealing with them.
Please do not worry, your excellency.
Ratchman, even a military unit, which one might have high hopes for, will sometimes lose.
"Please do not worry" shows a lack of sincerity,
don't you think so?
Unless you have the basis to confirm a victory, you should refrain from such consolations.
I apologize!
Did I sound like I wanted an apology?
I'm surprised that you think I wish for your apology more than the painting.
I want the painting, and you want connections into our world.
It is a clear and simple picture.
Understand that.
Revy.
Have you cooled down?
What do you mean?
You always get Whitman fever when we get a newcomer.
It happened when we took in Benny, now it's Rock.
Not digging too deep is our style.
I'll finish this job. Perfectly.
Of course you will.
Or we wouldn't be able to support our way of life.
I'll look in here.
We'll finish talking later.
So, you're still alive, girl.
I compliment your audaciousness.
I am Fritz Stanford.
I am the acting captain of the glorious Aryan Socialist Union.
This is a fated confrontation.
For the sake of those who died for the Union, you will atone with your blood!
Behold!
This gun I wield!
I call it the Eiserne Reich Luger Special!
The base is the Luger artillery long and the frame is hardened carbon!
With a thick grip and a two-bullet chamber!
Using a .454 Casull, which is much too destructive just to say it is specialized in man-stopping!
I am the only one who can wield this terrible gun!
Are you afraid?
You must be!
I will show you the power of this gun...
Shut up.
Why do you go on, when no one's listening?
Are you an infomercial?
Coward!
I'll teach you something good.
All these things need to do is hit.
It's a good lesson.
Say hi to the Führer.
That's the sound of the finale.
It sounds like you lose.
I heard it many times, back in the day.
I even have fond recollections of that sound now.
Hey Nazi.
I came to pick you up.
Are you on the phone?
Well, I guess we're friendly enough that I don't need to apologize for the rudeness.
Don't mind me.
I'll wait until you're done.
He certainly is a brave man.
I want to talk to him. Put him on.
It's for you.
You the boss?
Your subordinates were a real waste.
I'm sorry for the pathetic display.
I've got two questions for you.
About what the painting really is?
Then start with that.
There's one more candidate for the artist of this painting.
You did your research.
A man from Austria, Adolf Hitler himself, is the rumored artist.
The Führer's!
Don't rush to conclusions, old man.
The Führer as an artist could, at best, only do scenic pieces.
But as I remember, the SS officer also believed in that notion when he left for Batavia.
I see.
So what you want isn't the painting, but what's inside.
And, this is just a guess but, you know the phone number to our office, don't you?
Indeed, I own the company from Madrid that asked for this salvage job.
I was the one who wished for you and Ratchman to collide.
What?
The most amusing and best method which acted as a rite of passage and came with insurance.
And... this is a fleeting and dear memory but...
When Heydrich decided on the "Final Solution", we made a vow by the Wannsee...
...to become realistic guardians, rather than idealists believing in victory.
We gathered all of our capital and created a file with all of our signatures and account numbers.
When signs of the end approached,
We placed our files into four paintings and escaped Berlin.
That painting there is the last piece.
You have quite the insight, jungle bunny.
Don't be rude, white man.
I might get upset and throw it back in the ocean.
That's fine.
I simply wanted to get it back because it was discovered. I have other sources of capital.
We are a financial success at this time.
But what about the trust you might lose?
I don't like it, but you're right.
Very wise. It's a shame you are black.
Thanks. I'll let you get back to your conversation.
There's no need for that.
He's already fulfilled his role.
Alfred!
You bastard!!
You set me up in this fixed race and then you betray me!?
Quiet down youngster.
You were the one who chose death.
You had the same rights as the black man.
You should have known better than to try and enter into our society with that level of ability.
Now, black man.
That was a splendid job.
If you were an Aryan, I would have sent you an Iron Cross.
I wouldn't want it.
All I want is the money, you Gestapo.
Honesty is wonderful. Hypocrisy rots this world.
I wish people like you could be wiped off the planet.
Thank you kindly.
I hope you go to Hell.
Aren't you done yet?
Is that the commander?
Yeah.
Want to make a bet? You know, the one.
It's not much of a bet.
Just do it.
Here you go old man, use it as you want.
I say black.
I told you, I say black too. It's not much of a bet.
Told you. Not much of a bet.
I thought he might have shown some balls.
Pathetic until the end. They're all the same.
No kidding.
Let's end this job.
Got it.
Sure got the shivers today.
Too much trouble.
Shut up.
I won't cause trouble any more.
I think I know what you're hung up on.
I understand what's deep down in you.
I mean, you won't feel any better no matter what you do.
Dutch?
What is it?
Rock's a guy that's on the other side.
They're different to people on our side.
I just can't stand that feeling.
It's not that I don't like him.
But...
Dutch, I can't...
I...
...can't partner with that guy.
Shut up!
Shut up, God dammit!
I'll kill you!
Then do it.