It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Let us go, Raia.
Licht and his reincarnated elf comrades
headed toward the royal capital.
Well, let's go...
To get our other friends,
and to destroy the humans.
All right...
Let's go!
Asta and Yuno also headed
toward the royal capital
to save the Clover Kingdom, but...
On the way there,
they realized that their hometown,
Hage Village, was under attack,
so they split off from Nozel
and the others to head there.
Leave the rest to us!
How about this, then?
Poison Plant Magic: Zofnir's Breath...
and Zofnir's Fingers.
Asta tried to cure the effects
of the poison plant magic,
which had afflicted the priest.
But even with the Demon-Slayer Sword,
he was unable to reverse its effects.
Not yet, Father!
Don't die. You can't die!
You still... You still need
to see how much more I...
how much more we can grow!
This sword...
Back at the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout... He...
It somehow ended up back in my grimoire.
Maybe with this sword, I can...
Release from Misfortune
Wait, isn't that the sword
the evil boss guy was using?
That sword... Why does he have it?
What in the world is going on?
What's wrong, Asta?
The amount of black power
flowing into this sword
is far beyond the other swords...
Concentrate.
Don't go against this flow.
Take it in instead.
Make it an extension of myself.
Now!
Th-This is...
Huh?
The poison is disappearing.
Please, make it in time!
Father!
Wh-What's going...
Is this a dream? I thought I died.
Asta made you all better!
Yeah!
Thank goodness. You're amazing...
You're amazing, Asta!
All right! But, uh,
this sword is pretty wild!
But maybe with this power...
I'll be able to turn all
my friends back to normal!
He managed to take away all
the effects of the poison.
That sword...
What are you looking at?
Mana Zone: Crescent Moon Sickle,
Four Blades!
Wh-What's going on?
You're being affected by the same
reincarnation spell as us,
so why do you still retain that human's will?
And doesn't... doesn't the power
of that sword belong to Licht?
Why... How can a human with
absolutely no magical power...
Wh-What is this?
What are you people?!
Disgusting... tainted... humans!
Thank goodness. I think I'll
make it to Licht's wedding.
Oh, come on.
Are you really giving them those
creepy flowers as a present?
A-Are they? But they aren't poisonous,
and I think they're really pretty.
I'd be happy to have them.
Licht!
The meaning behind those flowers
is "kindness hidden within."
Elves and birds won't go near
them because they look poisonous.
But since the bugs know that,
it's their sanctuary.
Don't you think that's just the
same as elves and humans?
We don't know much about each other,
so we dislike or even hate one another.
I'm sure Tetia will love the flowers, too.
Thank you.
O-Of course!
We tried to understand them.
And they let us know...
just how vile they were!
Humans... I cannot forgive you!
Stay out of our way!
This feeling...
Humans, humans, humans, humans...
Humans, humans, humans, humans, humans...
He's not trying to control his magic at all!
His soul is going out of control!
Yeah, I can tell from his mana.
The elf's soul inside him is in pain.
It's like the elves are asking for help.
Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
At this rate, he's going to turn
into something besides an elf.
We have to set him free.
Oh, no!
He blocked Yuno's attack!
I've opened a path for you, Asta!
Just how vile they were!
Humans... I cannot forgive you!
Stay out of our way!
Humans, humans, humans, humans...
Humans, humans, humans, humans, humans...
He's not trying to control his magic at all!
His soul is going out of control!
Yeah, I can tell from his mana.
The elf's soul inside him is in pain.
It's like the elves are asking for help.
Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
At this rate, he's going to turn
into something besides an elf.
We have to set him free.
I've opened a path for you, Asta!
He negated... the reincarnation spell?
With this sword...
I'll be able to save everyone!
The only reason we won is because of Yuno!
You'd better be grateful!
I wouldn't say he's the only reason!
All you had to do was hold your sword,
so it was basically 100% me.
What?! If you were 100%,
then 500% of it was me!
You can't be serious. On many levels.
Moron.
Asta!
Whoa!
Yuno!
I thought we were finished...
You're amazing, Asta!
Great job protecting Sister, Nash.
Thanks for saving us!
I was so scared!
Hey! Get your hands off Yuno!
Wow! She's so tiny and cute!
She looks like a doll!
Let's play dress-up!
Hey! Stop that!
Asta... Yuno...
Father!
Are you okay?!
I'm still a bit dizzy, but...
Looks like the poison's
left everyone else, too.
Thank you for saving us all.
You two...
have grown so much!
Yes! I love you! Please marry m—
Water Creation Magic: Holy Fist of Love!
Oh, no! I did that impulsively!
I've missed this so much!
Can I get another shot?!
What?!
You can't be serious.
Hey, your ears are all pointy, Yuno.
You're right!
Yeah! He matches me!
Asta, Yuno... What's going
on in this kingdom?
One horrifying thing after
another keeps happening,
and I have no idea what's going on.
We don't have much time,
but we should probably tell them.
Yeah. Another Magic Knight who's been
reincarnated as an elf might attack.
Don't worry! When it comes to
this kingdom and its people...
...we'll do everything we can to protect them!
Your Majesty!
There's trouble, Your Majesty!
What's all the racket?! You've got
some nerve to disturb my slumber!
I-I sincerely apologize!
But this is an emergency!
The royal capital is being
attacked by several mages!
Just have Julius deal with that.
A-Actually, the Wizard King is missing,
and we can't seem to reach him.
The Magic Knights'
headquarters is in chaos!
Wh-What?! At a time like this?
But that's fine.
H-Huh?
This means it's finally my time to shine.
He always... always, always, always...
always stole the spotlight from me!
Now I will take command in place of Julius,
who was always stepping on my toes!
How lovely, Your Majesty!
You're the best, Your Majesty!
Send an order for the Magic Knight
captains to gather immediately!
Er, that's already been done.
But most of the captains didn't
even respond to the summons.
And we've received word that some of
the captains and Magic Knights
have turned on us.
Wh-What?!
Apparently Langris,
who was detained, has escaped,
and he seems to be leading this attack
along with the rest of the Golden Dawn.
It appears that our other
comrades who reincarnated
have finally made their move.
I hope they save some for us,
but that might be asking for too much.
I may be a calm man, but even I have trouble
holding back when I see those humans.
I'm pretty sure you always
acted calm and collected when
you were actually pretty feisty.
Honestly though, I can't hold back, either.
We can understand each other.
I mean, we're basically the same as them.
They're mad because something
precious to them was hurt.
Sorry, kid, but no one can stop us now.
Those two should be waking up soon.
You should just give up.
I felt immense magical power well up,
then immediately disappear.
That magic was intense. But I'm
sure Asta and Yuno are fine!
They promised to head to the royal capital
right after they saved their village!
Yes, we should do our best, too.
They separated from us with resolve.
You need to concentrate on
what you should be doing right now.
Yes, sir.
An den der boss named
Lich was shuper strong...
Asta, we have no idea what you're saying.
Look, either talk or eat. Pick one!
I can't help it! We don't have ti—
Are you okay, Asta?
You may be stronger now,
but nothing else has changed.
So basically, some of your fellow
Magic Knights reincarnated as elves
and are attacking us humans. Is that it?
Yes! Exactly!
I'm amazed you understood him.
Well, I did raise him, after all.
And to think Asta grew into
such a fine young man...
Yuno was always a fine young man, but...
Father's crying again.
Yeah.
I'm just so happy...
Excuse me...
Wh-Who the heck are you?!
Did you forget me already?
I was the one fighting you a little earlier.
You saved me after my body
was taken over by an elf.
My name is Digit...
Member of the Purple Orcas
Digit Taliss
Ah...
That's what you're actually like?
Yes! This is what I'm actually like!
How could this have happened?
Oh, I'm a Magic Knight belonging
to the Purple Orcas.
And you know, our former
captain, Gueldre,
was accepting bribes and
had lots of other problems.
So I was patrolling the Forsaken Realm
to try to help our reputation recover...
Wow! These are endangered horseface berries!
And these carnivorous plants aren't
listed in any encyclopedias!
The Forsaken Realm is
full of rare plants you can't
find back in the royal capital!
As I was traveling, I got lost.
The next thing I knew, I wasn't me anymore,
and I was attacking this village!
I still don't know what's going on!
Seriously, what in the world is going on?!
You can't be serious.
But there's one thing I'm certain of.
The soul of the elf that had
reincarnated in me didn't want this.
He didn't want to hate or fight anyone.
Let's go, Yuno!
We have to save the humans
and the elves, too!
Yeah.
Huh? You're leaving already?
But we finally got to see you.
No!
We wanna hear more stories!
Come, now. We can't be selfish.
Asta and Yuno have to go protect this kingdom.
There are others in trouble,
just like we were.
Aw...
Will you write to us again?
Yeah.
Of course!
You better improve your handwriting, Asta!
Your letters are super hard to read!
Huh?
Asta and Yuno... Don't you
dare die, no matter what!
Yeah!
Next time, we'll have more
time to talk, old man!
Call me "Father" or "Priest," darn it!
Okay, Old Man Priest!
You don't need the "old man" part!
Um... Would you take me with you?
Despite how I look, I am a Magic Knight.
Yeah!
All right, let's go!
Well, see ya!
We're gonna go save the kingdom!
Asta!
Yuno!
We appreciate the letters and the money,
but nothing beats you both coming home safe!
Be careful!
Sister! I love you!
Shut up.
They're going to save the kingdom, eh?
Our little Asta, who can't
even use any magic...
Yuno's the hope of Hage Village now,
but he used to be so timid
and would cry all the time.
Honestly, you both grew
up so unbelievably fast!
Be careful, you hear me?!
What the hell is that giant
boulder-looking thing?
All right, I guess I'll go have some fun.
We're pretty late after all that happened.
We have to hurry!
Up ahead, I feel elven magic from
both the north and the south.
It could be that some of the Magic Knights
who were reincarnated as elves,
like me, are attacking humans.
Wh-What should we do? We're hurrying
to the royal capital, right?
Even if they're not from
the royal capital or Hage,
they're still citizens of this kingdom!
Guess that settles it.
Since there are two places, it'd be
better if we split up and helped them.
Um... Who should I go with?
Go with Yuno!
I'll be fine alone.
Go with Asta.
Yeah, yeah! Yuno's way stronger than you!
What the heck? Just take
him with you, Yuno!
Go with Asta.
With Yuno!
P-Please calm down!
Please don't fight over me!
Asta! Asta! Asta!
Yuno! Yuno! Yuno!
I can turn our friends who became
elves back to normal with this sword!
You can't take anyone down for real,
so it's better if you have him with you.
As annoying as that is, you're right.
How is that annoying?!
I guess he can at least incapacitate
the enemy with paralyzing poison.
I'm not sure if I completely follow,
but I'm pretty sure that was mean!
Yuno!
Asta!
See you at the royal capital!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Splitting Up
Splitting Up.
Asta, are you sure you want to split
up and go off on your own?
Don't mock me! Of course
I'm fine with that!
Are you absolutely positive?
Yeah!
I'll ask you just one more time.
Are you sure you're okay with splitting up?
I said yes!
What? Are you gonna be lonely, Yuno?
You can't be serious.
Okay, let's split up, then!
See you at the royal capital!
Yeah.
See ya.
So mean!
What the heck?!
So mean...
I came because I heard
the town was being attacked!
What the hell, Luck?!
Whoa, hey!
Why the hell are you attacking me?!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 104:
"Lightning of Rage vs. Friends."
Page 104
Lightning of Rage vs. Friends
Vanessa! We're taking Luck back!