It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Flame Creation Magic: Leo Rugiens!
Is that all you've got,
Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings?
In the instant you attack,
for just a moment, the barrier's
mana thins in places.
That's what I aimed for.
H-He's awesome!
Rades, wasn't it?
Even if you possess extraordinary abilities
and polish them to their fullest,
without a righteous spirit,
your deeds are nothing but violence!
No one will acknowledge something like that!
I need to get stronger so things like
this don't give me so much trouble.
It's too early for you to
be cheering just yet.
I think everything's just about ready.
Now for some lively sow's mana...
How exciting!
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
Blackout
Why?
I have magic that's stronger
than anyone else's.
I studied everything there was about my
magic, polished my skills, and prepared!
All for this day!
For years... and years!
And yet... Why?!
Noelle, I thank you!
You can save the thanks! Just hurry up!
But of course!
Flame Magic: Ignis Columna!
How'd you like that?! I made him
evaporate with intense firepower!
Ow...
Excellent! Well done!
You are definitely a man worthy
of leading this country!
Yes, sir!
I accidentally saluted, too.
I-Impossible...
Impossible! I've got as much magic as a royal!
I...
Flame-Binding Magic: Leo Palma!
L-Let go of me!
I'm still—
Damn it! Damn it!
At this rate, I...
There are many questions I'd like to ask you.
But before that, I will be
confiscating your grimoire.
Don't!
Don't touch my grimoire!
What is this grimoire?
S-Stop it!
There's only one page?
Don't! Don't look at it!
He can only use one spell?
Damn it!
Give it back!
Don't you dare look down on me!
Who's gonna look down on you?
Couldn't you think of any other way to get
people to acknowledge your power?
You have amazing magic, and you were
strong enough to claw your way up...
It's such a waste!
Here. I'll lend you my arm.
Thanks.
What you lacked to overcome adversity...
was a righteous heart.
Pay for your crimes.
Are you satisfied now?
A voice...
What's the matter?
It was impossible for you to beat
a captain on your own after all.
I-It's not impossible...
I...
The sheer volume of your magic isn't enough.
I'm also reaching my limit.
You're through acting on your own.
From now on, things are
going to go as planned.
All for our master.
West District
The Magic Knights are amazing!
Hooray for the Golden Dawn!
Now, then, I think I'll go have some dessert.
Would you like to join me?
I will decline.
East District
Thank goodness...
Let's go back to our lodgings and
wash off all this sweat, Sis.
Indeed.
Great job, Blue Rose Knights!
Lady Charlotte is so elegant.
Lady Charlotte is so lovely.
Sol is so cool!
Central District
What is their motive?
Northwest District
Looks like they're in the marked areas.
My grimoire...
What?
Well done, Magic Knights.
No—
Sis!
Wh-What the?
The Magic Knights...
Lady Charlotte... disappeared.
Sol...
Where are we?
It would appear that we're at least
a few hundred kilometers
away from the royal capital.
They got us! Damn it!
They managed to infiltrate the royal capital.
I figured they must've had a rather
skilled spatial magic user, but...
To think they were able
to send us all this far.
Curses!
What the...
The Magic Knights' mana...
I can't feel it anymore.
This is unprecedented spatial magic.
Was there another spellcaster?
Wh-What's going on?
I have no idea.
To think the great Magic Knights would
all fall for a silly trap like that.
How stupid can they be?
I was supposed to play with the stragglers,
but it looks like I won't have to bother.
Now, then... I'd better use this
time to get some nice, young mana.
Ash Curse Magic: Ash Absorbing Formation.
Wh-What the?
No! What's going on?
Excellent. Just look!
My skin is silky smooth.
Even water would bounce right off of it.
No! Save me!
Stop acting all cute, you sow!
Eliza! W-Wake up!
Well, aren't you a handsome young man?
Say, do you think I'm pretty?
How old do I look?
Well?
H-How could you? You monster!
Who are you calling a monster?! Die!
Oh, my.
I guess someone was able to
escape that spatial magic.
My, you're hot and my type.
Say, want to have some fun with me?
Get away from those people,
you old hag.
I'll murder you!
My, you're hot and my type.
Say, want to have some fun with me?
Get away from those people,
you old hag.
I'll murder you!
Who are you calling an old hag?!
Ash Curse Magic: Cheerful Ash Destruction.
These are curse bullets
with various curses inside.
You won't know what you'll
get until they hit.
Who are you people? What are you after?
My, my. Look at you,
with such ample time to talk.
Well, since you're hot,
I guess I'll tell you.
We're here to eliminate someone.
That's our goal.
Eliminate someone?
Who do you think it is, darling?
Well, I'm definitely not going to tell you.
You're working with at least one other.
A spatial magic user must have
infiltrated the royal capital.
Where are they?
Have they already fled?
No matter where you might've sent
the rest of the Magic Knights,
you don't have enough power
to take over the royal capital.
I can't imagine that this was
just to go after the king.
King's Quarters
You've made it clear that
your motive is revenge,
but what are you and the
others after overall?
Our true motive...
is you, Fuegoleon Vermillion!
What?
Fuegoleon!
What do you—
This is spatial magic.
Very well. Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Fuegoleon!
What is this place?
The attacks keep coming. She has
a tremendous amount of magic.
These ash bullets themselves
don't do much damage, but...
Oh, dear...
Are you all right? It looks like you're
having a hard time getting around.
I wonder what you've been hit with.
Damn it...
I... can barely see anymore.
I'm gradually losing sensation
throughout my body, too.
Hey, can you hear me? Hello?
My ears are also going... This is her power?
My Ash Curse Magic: Cheerful Ash
Destruction works very gradually.
First, your eyes stop
working, then your ears,
and then your body stops moving.
You'll pay for having the
insolence to call me an old hag.
People expected a lot
from my four-leaf clover...
I even joined the top Magic
Knights squad, the Golden Dawn.
Yet... what am I doing?
Who cares about a four-leaf clover?
That stupid peasant, getting a big head...
Hmph. He lacks the talent worthy to
be a member of the Golden Dawn.
I'm sure he won't last long.
All those voices around me don't matter.
I'm only bettering myself so I won't lose. But...
I couldn't win.
What defeated that guy was
a power I just happened upon,
one that I can't control.
Not to mention...
That power doesn't seem
to want to listen to me.
The only reason I was able to
avoid the spatial magic earlier
was because something other
than my own power reacted.
It's not like we're expecting
anything from that peasant.
No, that's not it.
That's not why I'm frustrated.
Where are you attacking?
You have to aim properly, like this.
If you say, "I'm sorry, miss," and adorably
beg for your life, I'll forgive you.
Not a... chance...
I can't see... anything...
I can't feel... anything.
This is... the flow of mana?
It's said that mages with wind-based
mana are excellent at detecting mana.
With all five senses cut off
and his back against the wall,
Yuno's finely honed concentration
demonstrated an astonishing
ability to detect mana,
and was attempting to go beyond even that.
Come on, hurry up and beg for your life.
If you don't, I'm just
going to have to kill you.
There are so many things I want
to ask you. Hey, can you hear me?
Hey, come on. Answer me!
Would you shut up?
I couldn't care less about you.
I just...
don't want to lose...
to Asta!
Not yet!
That grimoire...
The legendary four-leaf clover?
Huh? Mana is gathering...
This sensation... He's...
He's controlling the mana?!
I see. The spirit has constantly
been sending me mana signs.
I was relying so much on my sight and
hearing that I wasn't noticing them.
Let me just tell you one thing about me.
I...
hate losing more than anything else!
Wind Spirit Magic: Sylph's Breath!
No! I have to use the magic
I stole to defend myself, or I'll—
You're...
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Birthday
Birthday.
I was able to get the wind
spirit to listen to me.
I shall name her Bell,
and today is Bell's birthday.
This cake is for you, Bell.
Yay!
Should we say you're one year old?
Happy birthday, Bell.
So pretty!
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
Um...
Huh? Where's the cake?
Not a chance...
You bastard! What did
you do with my brother?!
Answer wisely, or you shall face my wrath!
Fuegoleon! You... Fuegoleon!
Black Clover, Page 25: "Adversity."
Page 25
Adversity
I'm calm at all times...