It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout
was heading toward the royal capital.
All right, I guess I'll go have some fun.
Luck had reincarnated as an elf and
was possessed by a thirst for revenge.
He landed in a town on
the way to the royal capital
and ruthlessly attacked the humans there.
Hey, now...
We came to this town because
it was under attack, but...
What the hell's going on here,
Luck?!
Magna and Vanessa rushed to the scene.
Though they were bewildered
by Luck's changed personality,
they still engaged him in battle.
Flame Magic: Gargantuan Exploding Fireball!
I don't know who the hell you are,
but you don't know a damn
thing about him or me!
That's why you have no chance of beating me!
If that's crystal clear, then hurry up
and return that idiot to us!
But that just seemed to
make him resist even more.
The humans of the Clover Kingdom
will be destroyed.
That's what you deserve, and that's the
fate we elves shall bring upon you!
Magna faced a life-or-death situation!
And then...
Like I'm ever...
going to shut up!
Who the hell are you?
We're Luck's friends!
Smiles, Tears
There he is.
He's heading straight for me.
I've got him!
My rage is stronger!
You're there!
They used that thread to throw off my timing?
Go!
Asta!
Our feelings are tougher than you!
All right!
I'll free you now!
You're the ones who are going to die, humans!
Give it up already, damn it!
We told you! We're not
letting go, no matter what!
Don't...
Don't touch me!
Huh?
I thought I could just barely hear
a voice until a moment ago...
Wake up, Luck!
If you don't like it,
wake up and fight me already!
I'm never letting you go,
so hurry up and come back!
Who is that? What's going on?
Luck...
Mom!
Come over here, Luck.
You're not normal.
You have to stay by my side.
That's right... The only person
who could ever love me is my mom.
I live for my mom...
To make her smile.
I'm going to unleash all my magic!
Then all of you, this human,
and I will all be done for!
Disappear! Disappear! Die, humans!
What the hell is this ki?!
Is this actually magic?
Something dark and black is welling up!
H-Hey, damn it!
It's just like him...
At this rate, Luck will become...
something besides an elf... something evil!
All of them...
Everyone precious to me...
You took them all from me!
Humans... I will make you pay!
I don't know what the
heck you're talking about,
but if we humans really
are at fault, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
But for us... Luck is our precious friend!
So please... Don't take him from us!
Please!
Give him back to us!
And I'm pretty sure all those
people who are important to you
wouldn't want you to be like this!
Luck!
Mom!
These voices...
I'm sorry, Mom. I have to go.
Despite what I am, I found
something important to me.
Mom...
Thank you for everything.
Starting today, you're one of the Black Bulls.
Get as wild as you want,
you crazy little shit.
What's kickin', little chicken?
Aw, who's this little cutie?
You can think of me as your big sis.
It's a pleasure to meet you, my new friend.
Try this. La? La?
This is my little sister Marie.
Isn't she an angel? A goddess?
I will allow you to revere her.
I don't care what you think about me!
Think whatever you want! And I'm going
to think of you as my... as our friend!
Ugh. Talk about a crazy senior.
But I'm royalty, so I guess I'll forgive you.
The ones who are going to fight in the
finals aren't you and that Yuno guy!
It's going to be me and Luck!
I also...
I believe that this will become
a world where our peoples can
live side by side as friends.
We'll be able to understand each other.
I also... wanted to become
friends with humans like you.
I...
I'm...
still one of the Black Bulls, right?
Of course you are, you dumbass.
Magna! Vanessa! Asta!
Thank you!
Why?!
Why? He's obviously trying to hide his
embarrassment, you virgin delinquent.
Look at you, hugging him like that!
You're such a man's man, Magna!
You dumb— That's not—
Don't make me clobber you guys!
Aw, look at you, all embarrassed.
I'm not, damn it!
You should be more honest with yourself.
Look who's talking!
But really, thanks, guys.
But I...
sorta destroyed the town.
That's not exactly anything new.
Are all the people who live here okay?
I made sure to save them. Don't you worry.
Oh, good. Thanks, Vanessa.
I didn't even have the chance...
Stupid Magna.
The hell did you just say?!
Explosive...
I'm outta magic...
Anyway, Asta!
By the way, Asta!
Yes?!
What the hell is that sword?!
Th-This?
It turned Luck back to normal, didn't it?
According to Yuno, it, uh,
it takes magical effects...
Er, it basically sucks out the spell,
as if it was never cast, or something...
What the heck does that mean?
I'm not really sure,
and it takes more than one hit,
but if I have a little bit of time,
I can undo the reincarnation spell!
That's awesome!
But I realized this just a moment ago.
Those elf guys weren't actually
bad to begin with.
Since he disappeared from Luck, though,
does that mean he died again?
But he was smiling in the end.
That gentle person is who he really was.
I think it's good that you freed him.
The reincarnation spell
is really scary and sad.
I see... In that case,
for both the humans and elves...
I need to save everyone else with this sword!
Yeah!
Huh? Everyone else?
A bunch of people who reincarnated as elves
are wreaking havoc all over the kingdom!
Huh?
What?! That's an emergency!
So those lights that went up into
the sky were the reincarnation...
There were a lot in the royal capital!
That giant boulder thing was also
heading toward the royal capital.
We should go, too. We have to
protect the Clover Kingdom!
Yes, but before that,
we should head back to our base
and regroup with everyone else.
Yeah!
Leave that to me!
My body remembers the feeling of the
mana when that elf kid was with me.
I can get even stronger!
What?! Then I'm just gonna get even stronger!
Want me to train you next time, Magna?
Piss off, you dumbass!
We're almost back at the base.
The base...
What the hell happened?
Was it attacked by elves?
Asta!
Wait... Oh, it's just you guys.
The magical beasts that the captain keeps?
Thank goodness you're safe.
Say, where are the others?
Over there?
Guys!
Mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble...
I'm so embarrassed!
They're okay! But they're
not making any sense!
And... after... that...
Who the hell is that?
Guys! This is no time to
be mumbling and stuttering!
A-Asta!
Luck! Vanessa! Magna!
I'm so glad you're safe, my dear friends!
Wow! What the heck happened here?
And who the hell are you?
Magna...
You know who I am?
Who the hell—
If... you... get... too... close...
your... magic... will... get...
The hell is this?! The little bit of
mana I have left is being sucked away?!
Is he an enemy?!
He's not an enemy, Magna!
Asta...
He's one of members who's
been here the longest!
He has a weird disease that sucks
away magic, and he's the owner
of the Black Bulls' base! It's Henry!
Huh?
Owner?
I don't have any magic, so I'm totally fine.
He'd come visit me all the time.
Though I seriously thought
he was a ghost at first.
Asta... is... such... a... good... boy.
Wait, so you guys really
didn't know about Henry?
I totally thought you knew him.
Someone this weird was
still hiding in our base?
There isn't anyone else
living there, is there?
So what the hell happened?
Mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble...
Um... Um...
Well... you... see...
I have no idea what the
hell any of you are saying!
Oh, no...
Gauche...
turned into an elf?!
I know this is a serious moment,
but how could you even understand that?!
Mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble...
I know, right?! But someone
else is inside, so don't worry!
He doesn't actually hate you!
Um... Um...
Yeah! I think so, too!
The fact that Gauche didn't finish you
off means his body's fighting back!
And... then...
Gauche headed toward the
royal capital, didn't he?
How are you even communicating?!
We have to go save Gauche, too.
But I'm out of magic...
You guys get some rest!
Asta and I will go!
Wait for us, Gauche!
What the heck is that sound?
It's literally shaking the ground.
And this overwhelming amount of magic...
I won't forgive you... I won't forgive you...
Charmy!
Don't tell me...
Who was it?!
Don't tell me even Miz Charmy...
has turned into an elf!
Who the heck destroyed the vegetable
garden I had behind the base?!
She's not an elf!
Thank goodness!
I put so much effort into that garden, la!
I watered it, gave it fertilizer,
and put oh-so much love into it!
I wanted to find a bunch of yummy
things and feed them to you guys,
so I rushed back even though
I was starving, and then...
This is what I find!
That creepy sound was
just her tummy rumbling?!
Sauce isn't enough to satisfy my hunger, la!
That was sauce?!
Are you the ones who wrecked my garden?!
Uh, er, no... It wasn't us.
You've got the wrong people.
Who did it, then?!
Um... I think it was the Eye of
the Midnight Sun and some elves...
The Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Elves?
I'm gonna go kick their asses!
All of you, follow me!
Uh, er, I'm out of magic, so I can't...
I also barely have any left...
La? You're out of magic?
Yes...
Then I'll just have to do this!
Cotton Creation Magic...
Sheep Cook: Head Chef!
Why?!
All of you...
Get to work!
Why, though?!
Wait! We don't have time for this!
We have to hurry to the royal capital!
Eat.
Seriously, why?!
Eat!
Well, I guess I am a little hungry...
Th-Thanks!
Stare...
It's good! It's so good!
Nothing beats a meal with your best friends!
I-It's really good!
Th-This is...
I can feel my magic increasing!
The Head Chef's cooking increases your magic,
depending on how much you eat!
There it is again! This super insane magic!
But well done, Charmy!
You're amazing, Miz Charmy!
Now we can all head to the royal capital!
Eat! Eat up! Chow it all down!
But make sure you savor the flavor!
Will this maybe give me magic, too?!
Zero still means zero! But eat up anyway!
I'm going to eat away my sorrows!
You should have some, too, Henry!
But... I'll... end... up... sucking...
away... everyone's... magic.
It's fine! We just have to eat more, then!
Look who's talking! My precious
little bit of magic left...
It... tastes... so... good.
Klaus and Rill turned into elves!
And that fat guy from the Golden Dawn, too!
The captain said he was heading
to the Golden Dawn's base!
I'm sure Mister Yami's fine!
I'm so blessed to be able to eat
a meal with my bestest friends!
Finral's still in the hospital.
Where's Noelle?
Heading to the royal capital
with her brother with the bangs,
the Captain of the Silver Eagles!
We have to hurry after them!
They should be with another guy named Zora
who's randomly with the Black Bulls!
What?! He's a Black Bull?!
Yeah!
Come on, Grey! Eat up!
I will!
This is getting really fun!
These are the Black Bulls I know.
Good, good! Keep on chowing down!
And being among them is extra special.
The hell is that?!
That's amazing!
That's the power of our new best friend!
Recombination Magic: The Raging
Black Bull ~ Charging Style!
Whoa! That's awesome!
That's super badass!
Recombination Magic:
The Raging Black Bull ~ Charging Style
Everyone... get... on.
All right, let's do this!
We, the Black Bulls, are gonna
save the Clover Kingdom!
Yeah!
Onward to the royal capital!
Go!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Luck's Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro
Luck's Ra-Ri-Ru-Re-Ro!
Luck (Rakku)!
Luck
Ahaha!
Whoo! Luck!
Rucksack (Ryukku)!
Rucksack
That's a bit forced!
Let's go on a picnic!
Look (Rukku)!
Look
What a pretty mountain!
Look, look! I said look, look!
Hello!
Legs
Recording (Rekku)!
Okay, smile!
Make us look good!
If you don't, I'm gonna feed
you to my magic beasts!
You guys look great! Perfect!
Rock (Rokku)!
Rock
Rock 'n' roll!
Magna and the others saved me.
Now it's my turn to save everyone...
Everyone in this kingdom!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 106:
"Path of Revenge, Path of Atonement."
Page 106
Path of Revenge, Path of Atonement
Okay, let's do this!