It's much more serene compared to yesterday.
The waters around here are real technicolor.
It's a masterpiece once you dive in.
I'm sure it is.
I've done some scuba diving at Ishigaki Island.
It sounds elegant.
Like a real yuppie bachelor's life.
It's not that great.
Putting this beer to my lips in this sea breeze is much more elegant.
Naval base at Kiel, in 1945
So it's "Farewell Germany".
It's a shame that the last German sky we'll see is its usual leaden color.
Thanks to it, the Allies patrol over us has thinned.
If we get past the Shetlands and out of the North Sea,
we'll soon be under Spain's blue sky, and then on to Africa's beaches.
And you'll soon miss these clouds, Lieutenant Colonel Matsuda.
After all, a man who's here to study aeronautics shouldn't be killed by a plane.
And after coming all the way to Germany.
It seems like we'll understand each other on this long trip.
I'd like to feel the same about that other passenger.
I don't understand...
the SS or SD, those people.
Geez.
I really did have an elegant life.
Life here just takes a dive when the car starts acting up.
Lun-san, is that new?
How much?
That's too much. It's stolen too, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's not like anyone has anything to spare in their wallets.
I'd better pass, or Revy is going to crown me a wuss again.
Near the Cape Verde Islands, Africa 1945.
King.
Gentlemen, please look forward to sea turtle soup tonight!
The Indian Ocean
They're moving with us at bearing 270.
Ceylon is now known as Sri Lanka.
It's a freighter out of South Africa heading to Ceylon.
Captain.
We're in battle position.
Please get inside.
I apologize, but I want you to answer me one thing.
Are you going to ignore your orders and attack that freighter?
What shall we do?
I'll take you to Batavia without fail, Lieutenant Colonel.
Batavia is now known as Jakarta.
Fritz.
Yes sir?
Can't you even greet the enemy without confirmation?
You call yourself this ship's...
Understood.
I'll ready the rowing boat that's under maintenance.
You too, Lieutenant Colonel, get inside.
An attack would be a completely unnecessary risk.
That is a transport of your life-long enemy, England.
What's being carried is fuel for an invasion of the ally we'll soon be guests of.
Are you telling me to ignore that enemy?
Then what was the point of our war so far?
Sinking that ship will have no effect on our fatherland.
I see.
What?
Are you saying that you can't stop the setting sun?
Are you trying to force me to say more?
No, I was just surprised.
I thought you were worrying about something more pathetic.
I apologize.
But there are battles that must be taken on, despite that.
Let's go.
Prepare the submerging torpedoes.
Add a score of 31 to that ship.
Launcher is ready.
All right, let's go!
We will keep fighting!
Aren't you going to go drinking?
I'm going.
After I calculate the fuel efficiency of the torpedo ship.
Good job.
What's that?
I don't know.
Do I look like an off-season Santa?
You were looking at this at the shop, weren't you?
Well, no, that was...
You always act so reserved.
Wait, you can't mean, is that for me?
The enemy ship just passed over us.
Near the Nicobar Islands, Indonesia
March 25, 1945
Set course to 2-0-0.
Get behind the enemy.
If we turn twice, we can get behind them.
The second turn will be in four minutes.
Very well. Go with that.
There's another one in front of us.
And another signal...
The enemy coming out in numbers.
"We are being dominated..."
With Batavia right in front of us.
Not yet, gentlemen.
Both engines full power. Set course to 1-7-0.
1-7-0.
Fire the Zigarren towards our rear.
Firing Zigarren.
One of the enemy ships is moving away.
They took the bait.
Stop the ship. Silent running.
One ship won't break away.
It's an active sonar!
Full power to the engines!
Port 20 degrees! Set course to 40!
This is the forward torpedo room!
We're taking on water!
Close the hatch!
Captain! Please take care of yourself!
We've stopped taking on water as much as possible, but we can't blow the main tank.
Engines and the electric generator are damaged. Repairing either is...
It's unfortunate that we couldn't return the Japanese to his homeland.
Lieutenant Colonel Matsuda has already...
The way of the samurai.
I didn't realize he brought a katana for that end.
Brave and loyal soldiers of Germany.
We faced great opposition and rough waters in the Atlantic,
but we will finish our final battle, without seeing the coconuts of Batavia.
Currently our ship has run aground at a depth of 57 meters.
There is no promise that the ballast or engine will be repaired.
You have endured numerous battles with courage.
At this moment I relieve you all of military duties.
In two hours our air will run out.
Choose freely how you wish to die.
Lieutenant Colonel, I have to talk to you.
Captain, I haven't heard the engine in a while.
When will we surface?
We won't surface.
Ever.
I'm sorry.
Pathetic.
I am.
You don't understand.
You don't understand at all.
Understand what?
The importance of your mission!
The meaning of this painting I carry!
Oh, so the package was this painting.
It doesn't look that impressive to me.
What is it titled?
"The Twelve Knights led by Brunhilda."
This is the only piece that has been painted since the Führer took power.
"Steadfast in our honor and loyalty, hide this until the promised day."
"The day the Nazi flag flies again."
"This will be the guiding light for our comrades!"
So, we already know we are going to lose this war.
And we wanted to prepare for the next war.
You people...
Do you have family?
A wife and child in Stuttgart.
So what?
I am proud that I fought with all I had for the fatherland.
I have no regrets, even now as I'm condemned to a watery grave.
However, If I have one dissatisfaction,
it's that I have to share a casket with a fuck-head like you,
who can't even remember his family in his last moments.
Take that statement back, Captain.
You cannot compare family to the righteousness of country.
It's worthless.
No matter how much you struggle, Hitler's empire is over.
Shut up.
By putting up with your obsession, my country and my navy ended up like this.
Shut up!
I'm glad we've sunk, if my children never have to see that accursed Nazi flag ever again.
Take it back!
Our ship sinking may be the will of God.
Damn it.
Opening my mouth was a mistake.
I only went scuba diving once at Ishigaki Island.
Dutch tricked me!
That's all I've heard since we've left port.
Be a little more amusing, you idiot.
I can't go salvaging!
I explained it at the office, but I'll go through the details again before we go in.
Benny, will you start?
OK.
First, take a look at this.
An old story from an elderly gentleman from 50 years ago.
IXC-type attack submarine U-1234 of the German navy.
A submarine in the Wolf Pack that tore up the Atlantic.
The captain was Major Venztel H. Aabe.
The last order he received from the falling homeland was to take a Japanese officer to Batavia.
But things weren't that simple.
To get there, you need to go around Europe, then Africa.
It's a voyage worthy of Magellan.
But Aabe pulled it off.
But when he finally saw his destination, his ship and passenger suddenly ran out of luck.
While searching for the Japanese, the US Navy came across this U-boat.
Because of their boredom, they all struck at once.
The poor U-1234 finally ran out of strength.
The captain and 44 of his crew disappeared into the darkness of the sea.
Up to this point that's historical fact, but there's another, untold story.
A story of an SS officer who appeared the night before departure from Keil Port,
and forced his way on board with papers from the secret police.
Take a look at this.
This is the painting he held on to for his dear life.
The artist was August Janke, an unknown painter.
The title is "The Twelve Knights led by Brunhilda".
It looks pretty fucking boring.
Graffiti on the New York Metro looks more exciting.
Why did an officer board a submarine with just one painting, with no gold or papers?
Don't look at me.
It's just an incredible story. As far as logic or reason, I don't have anything.
The one thing that we know is that this painting is sleeping on a sunken sub.
We have an order from a collector in Spain.
His hobby is collecting Nazi art.
What a weird hobby.
Damn straight.
Most of Janke's work was destroyed in the war.
He had given up this, along with the U-boat. But...
But last year a French phone company laying down underwater cables discovered U-1234.
And without much water found inside.
In this area several countries are fighting for control.
No one can make a go for it easily.
That's where we come in.
A nice 50,000 dollar job.
So, these are the steps for the job.
Take a look.
The French found that the bow end is completely watered in.
The two of you will go in through the torpedo tubes and then shut them.
If you weld the hole shut first, you should be able to open the door from the inside.
Weld?
What do we do on the way out?
Just make a hole somewhere and swim out.
Once we get what we want, we don't need anything else.
All right then, let's get this over with.
I haven't even done weekend carpentry.
And underwater too. This isn't gonna work.
Hey, are you done checking the equipment?
If you keep bitching, I'm throwing you in the sea without a tank.
Mostly.
What about the buoyancy compensator? Did you test the gauge?
If you drown, I'm leaving you down in that Nazi casket.
Don't get so pissy.
It'll be fine.
If you die, you're gonna be in my way.
So stop talking back, you idiot.
Revy
After you dive, I'll only be able to track you with the beacon.
So don't toast the batteries.
Got it.
And this.
A souvenir from Balalaika, when she went back to the country.
An underwater rifle? Does it go full-auto?
Of course. Take it as a protective charm.
OK. Let's go.
Follow me, Rock.
So, you won her over with a gun and saved Rock.
You have a lot of tricks.
Of course.
As an employer, I worry about human relations.
The beacon's been activated.
The PLRS is working fine.
PLRS: Position Location Reporting System.
All right.
They've headed straight for a hunk of metal.
Revy must be used to this kind of thing.
Of course.
I wouldn't hire her, if all her tricks only involved guns.
She's got a natural talent.
When it comes to swimming.
Dutch?
What's up?
Come up for a second.
It's a boat.
What?
We're not on a regular sea route.
If someone's out here, it's gotta be the cable company.
Cable company?
Impossible.
After we got the offer I've been listening to their communications.
They shouldn't be out here for another three days.
And that's a research ship.
It's got big equipment on the back.
Not amusing.
Put up a Thai Navy flag.
Roger.
To the stopped ship.
This is the White Heather.
Please respond.
They want to communicate.
This is PT377 of the Thai Navy.
We are currently on a mission.
We'd like to inquire about your purpose in this area.
Tell us your nationality, ship number and signal code.
We see that you are acting independently.
Where is your ship?
That is a military matter and I cannot answer.
I request your information one more time, over.
They sure put a lot of pressure on ya.
They're not normal.
I'm going back to the control room.
Keep track of them.
I don't like how the clouds are moving.
Fold up your parasol.
All right. What do you want to do about those two?
As long as their beacon is on, we can get them any time.
Worst case scenario, we take care of those guys and pick them up.
Hail Überführer!
After checking on communications, there are no military vessels in this area.
Therefore, they are hated bandits who are plundering this sacred grave-site.
What is your verdict, Commander?
Such fools.
The proof of inheritance of this grave-site is rightfully ours.
Very well, Squad Commander.
I will allow destruction with an iron fist.
What's this?
Dutch, they're moving.
OK. I just started the engines.
What are they doing?
TOW: Tube-launched, Optically tracked, Wire-guided (US anti-tank missile).
Dutch! It's a TOW!
God damn it!
So, they did it after all!
Hang on, Benny!
Damn it!
An anti-tank missile!
Run, run, degenerationists.
This is our destined reunion with Brunhilda.
No one will stop us.
This underground grave is about to open.
You're not going to be one of us anymore.
When that happens, I'm going to kill you.