It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
At the royal capital of the Clover Kingdom,
the entrance exam for the Magic Knights,
who protect the kingdom under
the Wizard King, had begun.
In the final part of the exam,
the candidates were paired off
to battle using their grimoires.
Begin!
No holding back, all right?
Let's do this, Asta! Bah-ha!
Bronze Creation Magic:
Sekke Magnum Cannonball!
How do you like my magic?
It's bronzified and protects me
as it shoots out magical bullets.
It's offense and defense all in one!
It'll block all of your lame attacks,
which will show off my defensive powers,
and then I'll finish you off
once you've worn yourself out.
There's no need to hold back.
Come at me! Bah-ha!
The Path to the Wizard King
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know, yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go, though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide, I never give up
To faraway future, I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had, so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
Well, we know who's going to win.
There's no way some kid from the
boonies can break through that.
Man, I wish I was fighting that kid.
What's the deal with that shabby grimoire?
Can he even use magic?
Stupid hick peasant.
You're never going to make it
into any of the squads, kid!
There's no need to hold back.
Come at me! Bah-ha!
Now... Make sure you struggle as much
as you can to make things exciting!
Sure thing.
Here I go.
He's fast. Is he using some kind of
high-speed movement magic?
No... He's just physically powerful.
Huh?
I'm not joining
the Magic Knights so I can have a
good time and avoid working hard.
I'm here to work my butt off
and become the Wizard King!
That grimoire...
Well, well...
I'm the one who's going to defeat you...
Asta!
Is that sword... magic?
Wasn't he just some loser from the boonies?
What the heck?
Who is he?
He just...
...said something about the Wizard King.
All of you shut up! I told you,
I'm going to become the Wizard King!
You got a problem with that?!
Is he stupid?
What the heck is that peasant
from the boonies saying?
Must be embarrassing,
being a completely delusional idiot.
Just get outta here already, you stupid brat!
Who're you calling a stupid brat?!
Could it be some kind of creation magic?
Amazing...
Judging from the other parts of the exam,
it didn't seem like he had
that much magical power.
He's not using magic.
Huh?
Actually, maybe it's not
that he's not using magic...
It's that he doesn't have any magical power.
Come to think of it, I didn't
sense any mana from him.
And yet, he wants to become
the Wizard King, huh?
Looks like we've got a
strange one on our hands.
Bah... ha...
Man, royalty's so strong.
They have way too much magical
power and talent to begin with.
S-S-S...
S-So cool!
On second thought, maybe the shrimp
really is just a small-time lame-o.
No kidding. His opponent must've
just let his guard down too much.
"Yuno," wasn't it?
You seem to be having a hard
time finding an opponent.
Why don't you pair up with me?
Isn't that...
Salim?
From the famous Hapshass family?
You may have been chosen by the
four-leaf, but you are no noble.
I'll show you just how far below us nobles
you are, both in status and power.
Oh, and of course, in wealth, too.
Begin!
You should know that it's an
honor just to be able to fight
the great Salim de Hapshass.
You can tell the tale for the rest of your
life when you go back to your village.
I'll at least treat you to
a noble's ultimate attack:
The Holy Lightning Rising Salim.
Yuno...
I'll even pay for your trip back home.
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado.
Salim, a noble, was defeated in an instant!
Y-You can't be serious!
That was awesome!
Oh?
Amazing. I want to be his friend, too.
Wow, not bad.
Yeah.
This concludes the exam.
Now...
Candidates whose numbers are
called, please step forward.
The squad captains will raise their
hands if they would like you
to join their squads.
The candidates will decide if
they would like to accept or decline,
and if they are chosen
by more than one captain,
they may choose which
squad they'd like to join.
But if no one raises their hands,
that candidate will not
join the Magic Knights.
And you will leave immediately.
Candidate #1, step forward.
Y-Yes, sir!
Number 32, no offers.
Number 40, no offers.
Number 45, no offers.
Number 67, no offers.
Wow, someone finally raised their hand.
Awesome.
Number 71, the Purple Orcas.
Number 78.
I shall welcome him.
The Crimson Lion Kings.
Number 99, the Coral Peacocks.
Number 116,
no offers.
Damn it!
Number 141...
No offers.
Well, I guess I expected that.
I'll just go back to my
village and till my fields.
Scary...
Next, #164.
Yes, sir.
Yuno!
All who wish to offer, please raise your hand.
What?
Seriously?
All of the captains...
...raised their hands?!
Th-That's amazing.
I-I thought that only royalty and
nobles could join the Golden Dawn.
Even the Silver Eagles? Seriously?
But he's a kid from the boonies!
All of them! That's amazing!
N-Nothing less from my rival!
I'll take the best path to
becoming the Wizard King.
Please allow me to join the Golden Dawn.
They took a good one.
But I wanted to be his friend...
Oh, well. Can't be helped.
Next, #165.
Oh. I guess that kid's next.
I can't let Yuno get ahead of me!
I'm ready!
All who wish to offer, please raise your hand.
I don't care which squad it is...
Someone, please raise your hand!
Number 165...
No offers.
N-No way...
Go on, scram! I'm up next!
Not yet... I'm not done yet!
You're a disgrace!
No... I... I'm...
Well, that's no surprise.
Yami?
No matter how high your combat skills are,
if the source of your power is unknown,
no one wants anything to do with it.
In the end, the only thing
desired from a Magic Knight
is their magical powers.
Wh-What's going on?
Hey, Yami?!
S-So much pressure!
This is...
the magical power of a
Magic Knights Squad captain?
And since you have no magical powers,
no one wants you.
That's the cruel reality.
You said earlier that you wanted to
become the Wizard King, didn't you?
Which means you're going to surpass
the nine captains here, right?
Now that I'm standing before you,
do you still have the nerve
to say that you're going to be the Wizard King,
even without any magical powers?
E-Even if I can't join the Magic Knights today...
No matter how many times I fall,
no matter what anyone says to me,
I'm still going to become
the Wizard King someday!
You're funny, kid.
Join my squad.
Huh?
I'm telling you that I'll let
you join the Black Bulls.
By the way, declining isn't an option.
What?!
I'll make life so miserable for you in the
Black Bulls that you'll be torn to shreds,
so be ready for that.
What?!
And then, someday,
become the Wizard King.
Yes, sir!
Number 512, no offers.
This concludes the Magic
Knights Entrance Exam.
Good work!
Don't worry about it.
Try again next year!
Asta...
Yuno! You're Golden! I'm a Bull!
This is where our true battle begins!
Yeah. Let's see who'll—
N-Nature's calling pretty loud!
Was it the grilled purple snake
I ate to psyche myself up?!
It's coming! It's ready
to stick its head out!
After humiliating me in front of everyone,
don't think I'm just going
to let you leave, Asta.
Because of you, I was only offered a
position in one of the lower ranking squads,
the Green Praying Mantises!
I'm a frickin' bug!
You're just a hick from the boonies.
You think you can become the Wizard King?
Life ain't that simple.
Bronze Hex Magic: Sekke's Poison Lizard.
I'll test your luck for you.
Eat lizard poison!
If your luck's bad, you'll be
bedridden for life. Bah-ha!
Huh?
What are you doing?
Four-leaf...
B-Bah-ha! I was just going to give him a
little scare. You know, as a parting gift.
T-To see who'll make it
further in this world.
Then get lost.
You're no match for Asta.
Oh, I just remembered! I have somewhere to be.
Tell Asta bye for me. Bah-ha!
That feels so much better.
Man... It all came right out.
I have no regrets or poop left in me.
All right.
Let's go.
You've got some nerve, making me wait.
How long does it take you to take a dump?
Actually, it was really something!
It was long and huge...
That's not what I meant!
Who asked you to start talking
about your turds, you moron?!
Let's go, Finral.
Right-o.
What's that?
Since you can't magically fly,
you're going to have to learn
some transport magic, too.
Oh, wait. You don't have any magical powers!
Ow! What the heck?!
Er, sorry to bug you, Yami, but it's a
bit hard to keep a gate this size open,
so could you just go through quickly?
Who do you think you're ordering around?
Tough it out, and surpass your limits.
What?!
Off you go.
So tired...
Ow...
Black Bulls' Base
This is the Black Bulls'...
Well? Pretty magnificent, isn't it?
It's actually pretty run-down.
Welcome to the Black Bulls.
Starting today, I'm also going to be...
All right!
I'm Asta from Hage Village!
I'll be joining the Black Bulls tod—
Oh, dear...
Welcome to the absolute worst
Magic Knights Squad, the Black Bulls.
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh, go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Hyped Up!
The Guy Yuno Defeated:
Salim
I'm getting hyped up!
Sekke! Your Sekke Magnum
Cannonball has such a cool name!
The Guy Asta Defeated:
Sekke
Bah-ha!
Your Holy Lightning Rising Salim
isn't so bad, either. Bah-ha!
Sekke, I believe we could
be the best of friends.
Bah-ha!
Not a chance...
We did it!
We're finally the Magic Knights
we always hoped to be!
B-But what the heck? It looks
I ended up in some crazy place!
Black Clover, Page 6: "The Black Bulls."
Page 6
The Black Bulls
Not giving up is my magic!