The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently
aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
The New Magic Knights Captain Conference
The Clover Kingdom.
Much of the royal capital
was destroyed in an attack
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
but the repairs are going smoothly.
The citizens have gathered
in the square to prove
that the threat of the Eye of
the Midnight Sun has passed,
and that the kingdom is doing
everything it can to restore peace
and get life back to normal.
It's Lord Vangeance!
He's wonderful!
Captain of the Golden Dawn
William Vangeance
He's the hero who saved the kingdom!
They're the pride of the Magic Knights!
Lord Fuegoleon!
Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings
Fuegoleon Vermillion
Not only has he returned as captain,
he now controls Salamander!
Captain of the Silver Eagles
Nozel Silva
Lord Nozel's bangs are as charming as ever.
I heard that he was on the
front line of this battle!
Lady Charlotte!
Captain of the Blue Rose Knights
Charlotte Roselei
Every rose has its thorns... But I wouldn't
mind getting pricked by Lady Charlotte.
What in the world are Yami and the
Captain of the Praying Mantises doing?
I can't believe they're late on an
important day like this. Unbelievable.
Rill!
Captain of the Aqua Deer
Rill Boismortier
I wonder if something's wrong.
He looks like he's spaced out.
Yeah... He's definitely in love. I can tell.
Where did that lovely lady go?
The young master's first love...
The Butler of the Boismortier Household
Walter
Ah, Madam... The young master
is slowly becoming an adult.
I'm sure you'll have a lovely
grandchild any day now.
Look! It's Lady Dorothy!
Captain of the Coral Peacocks
Dorothy Unsworth
And she's awake?!
I never knew she had such beautiful eyes.
Heya! How's everyone doing?
Lord Kaiser looks so dapper for his age!
Captain of the Purple Orcas
Kaiser Granvorka
But he seems a bit down.
Look! It's Lord Julius!
The Wizard King!
Lord Julius!
Wizard King's Advisor
Marx Francois
Did he get injured?
I heard it was actually Lord Julius
who saved all of us from that attack
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
He must have endured an intense
battle to protect us all.
That must be how he got hurt.
He's forever our hero...
The Wizard King!
What? You want me to be the Wizard King?
He couldn't possibly—
Well, I mean, I can't go strolling
out there looking like a kid.
And we can't have the king finding out, either.
But it'd also be strange if
I didn't appear on that stage.
But it'd be obvious that it was me up there.
Oh, don't worry.
You just have to stand up there.
Here. Conceal your face with this.
What?
You obviously look different now,
but I see you haven't changed at all.
Please don't let them notice...
Ahem...
The Wizard King has a sore throat,
so he cannot speak to all of you today.
Please forgive him.
I wanted to hear the Wizard King speak...
He can't help it.
Yeah...
Now, I'd like you all to
give a big round of applause
to the valiant hero who
bravely faced our enemies.
Our great king,
King of the Clover Kingdom
Augustus Kira Clover XIII
Augustus Kira Clover XIII!
Wow. It's the king.
He's so cool.
I love you, Your Majesty.
Why are you dawdling?! Pick up the pace!
This is my time to shine!
Bah-yes!
Wh-Why? I know I just went with the flow,
but how did I get stuck
as the king's attendant?
Don't you dare stand next to me!
Yes, sir!
That goes for you, too!
Curse you, Julius.
How dare you make me give
a speech to the people
just because a cold made you lose your voice?
But this is the perfect chance
to show the people my dignity and benevolence.
You're a fool if you think your
popularity will last forever, Julius.
Good day, my fine citizens!
I am your king, Augustus Kira Clover XIII!
My majestic presence has
left them at a loss for words.
When will this be over?
Shh!
Your Majesty, the public awaits your wisdom.
Please do not make them wait too
long and keep it brief, if possible.
Oh, of course.
Tch! Curse you, Vangeance.
How dare you order me around?
Thanks to my valiant deeds and
some help from the Magic Knights,
the threat known as the Eye
of the Midnight Sun has fled.
The Clover Kingdom is safe,
and peace has been restored.
This must be a result of my daily good deeds!
But I'm sure that some of you remain wary.
What will happen to your everyday lives?
What if other enemies attack?
There is nothing to fear!
Behold! My majestic light magic!
How brilliant! How valiant!
Light Magic: Absolute Monarch
of Divine Brilliance!
Perfection.
I give you my word, my adoring public!
The Clover Kingdom is in safe hands!
Leave everything to me!
Tch! You damn beanpole!
Let's settle things once and for all!
You damn foreigner! Let's see who's stronger!
The hell do you want?!
What're you guys doing?
Yami, Jack...
I'm certain I told you that today was
an important day when we
were going to tell the people
that we'd taken care of the Eye of
the Midnight Sun and restored peace.
Was that today?
I totally forgot.
Not only were you late, but you're
fighting over something ridiculous.
Well, he started it.
What? You're the asshole who started it!
That's enough, you two.
Remember where you are.
Tch...
The Black Bulls and Praying
Mantises are so violent.
I saw in the paper that one of the
Black Bulls is possessed by a devil.
I knew there was no way
they should've placed second in
stars at the last Star Festival.
Yeah. They're the worst
possible squad, after all.
H-H-How dare you?!
That was my absolutely invincible light magic!
Huh?
What're you talkin' about?
You know what I'm talking about!
How dare you interfere with my spotlight?!
Your Majesty. Please show
the people your leniency.
I believe it best to show
them how merciful you are.
I-Is that so?
Tch. Who cares what you think?!
Just because people praised you as
a hero! Get off your high horse!
Indeed. I-It's wonderful
to see how lively you are.
Continue with your ways.
Do everything you can for the Clover Kingdom.
Sure.
The king is now taking his leave.
I ask that you send him off
with a round of applause.
C-Captain Jack...
Um, could you call me back to the
Praying Mantises sometime soon?
Huh? Who the hell are you?
Bah-ha?!
What are you doing?! Come here at once!
B-Bah-yes!
He's one of yours, isn't he?
Like I'd ever choose a guy like that.
Let us take our leave, as well.
Right...
Okay!
Lord Vangeance!
Good grief. It's finally over.
So... why're you dressed
like that, Old Man Owen?
What?!
A-All of the Magic Knights
Squad captains are here?
I feel immense pressure...
Wh-Why were we called to a Magic Knights
Squad captains' meeting, anyway?
My apologies, Yami.
It should be your squad receiving
praise from the public, not me.
Well, we're used to getting booed.
I apologize.
It's no big. Don't worry about it.
Calm down. Don't let your
heart go aflutter, Charlotte.
Stay calm... perfectly calm...
What's wrong, Prickly Queen?
Your face is red. You okay?
I-I'm perfectly fine!
You know...
If you need to take a dump,
go now! Don't hold it in!
Of course that's not it!
How are you so devoid of tact?!
I was wrong?!
Of course you're wrong!
You just don't get it, Yami.
This is why people say you're
so oblivious. Am I right?
You have to take a piss, right?
No!
The captains...
Are they always like this?
This is a rare sight to see, in its own way.
Damn that Julius. He's the one who
called us all here, and he's late again.
He didn't forget he called us all here and
then just wander off somewhere, did he?
Damn that old man... I mean, old brat.
You know... that might actually
be possible this time.
Yeah! Like, totally!
Yeah...
So what the hell's wrong with him?
No idea. He's apparently been like
this ever since the spell broke.
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
Hey, I see you're all here.
Damnatio Kira
He's...
It's Damnatio.
He was called here, too?
Pardon me.
You jackass...
If you have a problem with
one of my squad members again,
I'll gladly take you o—
Yami.
I'm the one who called Damnatio here.
You did?
It appears that what you'll be
discussing today concerns me, as well.
Therefore, I was told that
I was obligated to be here.
Today, we'll be talking about the devil
that resides in the Spade Kingdom.
The other day, a few of our fellow
citizens went to the Heart Kingdom
to find out more about the devils.
I believe that you have all seen the reports,
but I would like to hear from the
ones who were actually there.
If you would.
Right!
All right.
In the Heart Kingdom,
they measure a mage's strength with
a system called magic stages.
The stages go up in order from nine.
The smaller the number, the stronger the mage.
Stage Zero
Stage One
Stage Two
Stage Three
Stage Four
Stage Five
Stage Six
Stage Seven
Stage Eight
Stage Nine
According to Queen Loropechika,
it's not the total number of mages,
but the number of mages near
stage zero that will determine
who is more powerful in a battle among mages.
And this part's really important...
If we're up against a devil,
apparently we won't stand a chance unless
everyone fighting is stage one or stronger.
Stage one, eh?
The powerful curse in the Heart Kingdom that
Asta and the others went to investigate
was the one cast upon Queen Loropechika.
It seems the queen only has about
another year to live due to the curse.
And the one who put that curse on her...
...is the devil Megicula.
And from a separate report from
another group of Black Bulls,
the Diamond Kingdom is currently
under attack by the Spade Kingdom.
In the past few years, the Spade Kingdom
has become more and more powerful.
It's very likely...
...that specific devil is helping them out.
What we'll be discussing at this meeting
is what we should do to go up against
the Spade Kingdom and this devil.
Queen Loropechika plans to attack
the Spade Kingdom in six months,
before she becomes weaker.
We are thinking of assisting the
Heart Kingdom and fighting alongside them.
I would like all of you to train your
squad members as much as you can.
We only have six months,
but do everything you can to
raise everyone's magic stages
so that we can face the Spade Kingdom
and protect this kingdom.
I've heard from Queen Loropechika
that the Spirit Guardians
will also help us out.
Can I count on all of you?
Of course.
Yes.
Like you need to even ask us.
We've already started.
The Black Bulls will be doing as
we please for the next six months.
William?
I will participate in the fight...
But after everything I've done,
I cannot face my squad as the Captain
of the Golden Dawn any longer.
I ask that you relieve me
of my duties as captain.
Huh?
Hey!
Also, I'd like you to assign me a new mission.
I'd like to put my life on
the line to defeat the devil.
C-Captain...
In that case, I am also guilty.
Though my body was taken over by an elf,
the crimes I have committed against the
Clover Kingdom are punishable by death.
I agree. I am not worthy of being a captain.
It's honestly not bugging me much.
Be a little bit bugged, at least.
Now, now, just wait a moment.
I understand why you feel guilty,
but I cannot relieve you
of your duties as captains.
Besides, what you said
just now would end up
involving all the other Magic Knights
who were possessed by elves, too.
And then who would be
left to protect this kingdom?
If you want to atone for what you did,
you have no other option but
to forget your positions
and do all you can to
protect this kingdom.
I trust in all of you.
Yes, sir.
Very well.
Roger!
As you wish.
So, Damnatio, does that work for you?
Whatever do you mean?
In order to defeat the devil, the Magic Knights
will have to get stronger
in the next six months.
I'd like you to think about
what to do with Asta
after we've taken care of this matter
with the Spade Kingdom, if you would.
I have no objections.
But do not get the wrong idea.
I'm only agreeing to this because
doing otherwise at the moment
would not benefit the Clover Kingdom.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
That heartless scales bastard.
So, uh, I... Thank you!
No need to thank me.
Right! Thank you very much!
Again, I'm counting on all of you.
Leave it to me!
I wonder how I should sever
my squad members...
I'm getting excited just thinking about it!
Yeah, maybe don't.
I can't wait!
I should go lay out plans
for training immediately.
Why don't all the squads do this together?
That is definitely an option.
Having mock battles would also help.
I ain't gonna hold back!
That's my line, asshole.
Sounds like we'll need to round
up some healing mages, too.
Don't get too carried away, okay?
Oh, right. Marx, you can have him come in.
As you wish.
Oho?
Hey, it's Hard Ham.
Former Captain of the Purple Orcas
Gueldre Poizot
I'm sure you're all very familiar with
the former Captain of the Purple Orcas,
Gueldre Poizot.
The other day, while Gueldre
was at the Shadow Palace...
He managed to carry away a load of
ancient magic items and jewels
with his former senior
and Magic Knight, Revchi.
Oh?
You heathen. You never learn.
I was planning to keep him whole,
but I can't wait any longer!
I'm gonna turn him into sliced ham right now!
No, wait.
I'm thinking about pardoning Gueldre.
Pardoning him?
Huh?
Gueldre has a knack for business.
I'm sure he'll be able to
turn an even bigger profit
from the treasures he tried to get away with.
And I'd like him to use that money
to help support the kingdom.
You know, since repairs cost quite a bit.
It's not like the kingdom has endless riches.
You'll help us out, right?
U-Um...
Suddenly this all depends
on me turning a profit!
Right?
O-Of course! I will do everything
that I possibly can!
That'll help us out quite a bit. Thank you.
Y-Yes, sir!
There was no way he could decline!
That was a different kind
of pressure than Yami uses.
Tch! Make sure you pull your own
weight around here, Hard Ham.
Mess this up and I'm gonna
sell you as sliced ham.
One last thing.
Like I said, the kingdom
doesn't have endless riches.
So to help out with that,
I'd like to make your salary as
Magic Knight Squad Captains
half of what it usually is.
What?!
Seems like a logical solution.
I have no objections.
Of course, I agree.
Sure...
Okay!
I'm fine with that.
It's the least I can do.
Well, I guess that's that.
Now, hang on a second!
You can't be serious!
What's the matter?
Half?! Come on, man! I'm in debt!
You want us to go broke?!
Well, you know, you need to set
an example for your subordinates.
I absolutely decline!
Well, majority rules, so...
There you have it.
We now conclude the Magic Knights
Squad captains' meeting.
This is bullshit!
Closed for a Private Event
How long are you going to carry
on with your drunken rambling?
I won't put up with this any longer.
Yeah, go home, you square!
Must be nice...
You assholes always had money.
I'm sure getting your salary
cut in half doesn't even sting.
Damn it!
This is nonsense.
It's always best to drink in moderation.
Ciao! See you later.
Come on, you can hang out a little longer.
Yeah, you have time.
Come on, brave hero who saved
the kingdom. Let's play a little game.
Game?
We'll get back the salary we
lost by taking it from you!
Very well.
We'll take everything you've got!
Good grief...
I win...
Now I've got three times my salary...
I'm very grateful to both of you.
Despite everything that happened,
you continue to treat me the same.
I promise you that I will do everything
in my power to defeat this devil.
Goodnight.
Sorry to cause such a fuss, sir.
Thank you very much.
The Magic Knight Squads make
their move to go up against
the Spade Kingdom and the devil.
In the meantime, Asta and Yuno
head back to Hage Village.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 131: "A New Resolve."
Page 131
A New Resolve
They continue on their path
to becoming the Wizard King.