It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Making the impossible possible is
what happens here in the Glamour World.
Vanessa and the others were pulled
into the world of fantasy
and faced off with Dorothy,
who had reincarnated as an elf, but...
Combo Spell: Flame Lightning
Exploding Cannon!
They all worked together to defeat
Dorothy and escape Glamour World.
Combo Spell: Reflect Iris.
I can't...
...move!
Now you can just die, completely helpless.
Meanwhile, Asta and the other
Black Bulls were fighting
Gauche and Marie, who had
reincarnated as elves,
and found themselves in danger!
The rest is...
...up... to... you.
Not yet, Henry!
Live!
I don't want to die.
I want to continue living with my friends.
Let's continue living together!
I don't want to lose a
single one of my friends!
That goes for you, too...
Gauche!
I need you to return those
bodies to Gauche and Marie.
Asta managed to expel the
elves from Gauche and Marie,
and was successful in
returning them to normal.
Thanks... you jerks.
All right! The Black Bulls are all here!
Once we're all recovered,
we're gonna go after Captain Yami!
Yeah!
Storming the Shadow Palace
So that must be the Shadow Palace...
You know what that is?
Indeed.
Spatial magic from ancient times...
To think it actually existed.
They say that you can find extremely
powerful ancient magic items
and treasures inside.
So exactly what are we supposed to do?
Yes, I wonder...
All right! Eat up, everyone! La!
Captain Yami and Captain Mantis
already went in,
but it seems like there
are some powerful enemies,
so we're gonna recover our
mana and then go help!
Here, Marie. Say, "Aah..."
Oh, stop it, Big Brother.
No need to be shy, my goddess!
"Aah..."
I told you, I don't want to.
Come on, Gauche. No need to be shy.
"Aah..."
My beautiful magic is recovering beautifully.
All the pain in my entire body is gone!
Thanks, Mimosa!
It was nothing, Asta.
Now I can fight in my black form again!
Go on. Eat up, Mimosa.
Thank you.
Honestly, all you ever do is get hurt.
You overdid it again, didn't you?
I swear, you're hopeless without me.
I mean, you're hopeless anyway!
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Asta, your body's pretty unique,
so make sure you take good care of it.
Hey! Aren't those Asta's clothes?
Yeah, so?
Oh, yeah. Her clothes were all
tattered, so I let her borrow mine.
H-How does that even happen?
More importantly, why's a girl from the
Eye of the Midnight Sun with us, anyway?
It's bugging you now?
I was promised that I can do whatever
I want with his body after this battle.
Huh?!
Wh-Whatever you want?!
I didn't say "whatever you want"!
But you did! I promise I'll use anesthesia!
H-H-Hey!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Are you stupid, Stupidsta?!
Wait, me?!
A-A-Anyway, you're in the way of me
healing him, so please step away!
What? But you're already done healing.
Stupidsta... you stupidhead!
Hey, Lady Noe, quit fooling around
and eat to recover your mana.
You shut your mouth.
Hey, I have seniority here!
And? I'm royalty.
But I'm your senior!
What's up?
They're coming.
Two elves.
Too slow!
Die!
About time you woke up, you fool!
I apologize for the trouble
I've caused you, my sister.
Fu... Me...
Captain Fuegoleon! Captain Mereoleona!
Captain Fuegoleon! I'm so
relieved that you're awake!
Wait, and you've got Salamander, too?!
Former Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings
Fuegoleon Vermillion
Ah, Asta. It appears you've
gotten stronger during my slumber.
Heck yeah! I'm totally ripped!
Lady Mereoleona,
The New Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings
Mereoleona Vermillion
I heard you were supposed to be
resting for at least one more day!
Who cares? I'm fine.
What?!
She seriously is a monster.
So it appears the Vermillions have
finally returned to the battlefield.
Lord Nozel is amazing!
It's hard to believe he just recovered.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nozel.
Hmph. Hopefully this doesn't
affect your performance.
So you've been chosen by Salamander.
Trying to outdo me again, I see.
Uh... Wha?!
Hey, that hole!
Is it me, or is it getting smaller?!
Oh, no... We have to hurry!
When we put the final magic stone
in its pedestal inside the palace,
the elves' reincarnation
will be complete!
In exchange, the souls of the
humans who owned these bodies
will be sent to the underworld!
...is what he said!
How dare you...
You humans!
The Golden Dawn's Senior Magic Knights...
Really? Right now?
There are no limits to my beauty,
but apparently, that was the
end of my beautiful magic.
There's no time.
But with these numbers...
Captains, please head to the Shadow Palace!
We, the Black Bulls, will take care of them!
As long as Charmy and I are here, we won't die!
Leave it to us, la!
Asta, you go, too!
They'll probably need that sword of yours!
Roger!
I wish you luck, everyone!
Yeah!
There are still a lot of people taken over
by elves over here, so hurry back!
Yes, sir!
I-I'll go, too—
They'll also need a wizard
with recovery magic.
Go with them, Mimosa.
My beauty and I shall beautifully
support everyone here.
Right!
I'll be able to protect Asta.
For once, good job, Big Brother.
I-I—
Noelle!
Solid?!
You go, too!
Huh?
I'll admit it... You're definitely
stronger than me right now.
But I'm going to surpass you someday!
Because I'm your older brother!
So go, and make sure you come back!
Your pride as a royal...
As a part of the Silva family is at stake!
Indeed. I'll come back, no matter what, Solid!
All right, here we go!
Don't fall behind!
Come.
We won't let you!
We won't let you get in their way!
Here we go!
To the Shadow Palace!
Where the heck are we?!
What's going on here?!
Is this... an obstacle to anyone
who tries to infiltrate the palace?
We're surrounded by strange mana.
I can't control my magic!
The Shadow Palace...
I hear it's the boundary
between this world and the next.
Wait... Are we going to die?
D-Don't be stupid, Stupidsta!
That's not funny!
I won't die!
Mimo—
I-I... I'm so sorry, Asta!
I-I'll heal you right away!
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing Flower Robe.
So we're inside the Shadow Palace now?
Where did everyone else go?
Heck yeah! I'm fully healed again!
Thanks, Mimosa!
First, I'll use Magic Flower Guidepost
to determine the layout of the palace.
Man, you're so amazing, Mimosa!
This is...
There are a number of big spaces,
and I feel an elf's mana in each.
We're in one of the paths
that connect those chambers.
It appears our comrades have
been scattered to other locations.
They'll have to defeat
the enemies waiting there
before we can all regroup.
This is not good.
We're up against the Apostles of Sephira,
who all possess more magic than
a Magic Knights Squad captain.
I feel the most powerful magic
in the uppermost chamber!
That must be him!
All right! Everyone's just gonna have to
take care of the enemy waiting for them,
and we'll regroup at the top,
where the boss is!
Right!
The central chamber is right above us.
Let us proceed.
Yeah!
I dunno who we're up against,
but Mimosa and I are just gonna have to win!
Don't tell me...
These pictures...
Welcome!
We've met before!
Rill!
Jeez, I keep telling you
that my name is Lira.
Well, whatever.
I'm gonna have you guys practice with me
until the last magic stone arrives, 'kay?
Just wait! I'll wake you up right now!
But I'm already awake.
Isn't picture magic fun?
It took a little while to get used to,
but I can draw more things than
I could with my old scribble magic.
We're going to draw a new world...
On a pure white canvas,
after we've erased all you humans!
Yeah, I guess it's not
gonna be so easy after all!
Why...
Why am I alone?!
Where did everyone go?!
Well, if you're that lonely,
I'll play with you.
It might not be for very long, though.
Fana? Wh-What are you doing here?
I wonder if you're mistaking
me for someone else.
I may be Fana, but I'm not the Fana you know.
So I guess you're the one I get to fight.
You've got interesting mana, for human royalty.
Watch your mouth. I guess I'll have
to teach you some manners, brat.
Though my body is young, I'm not a
beast that can be tamed by a mere human.
I heard that you became a captain...
Yet we meet to fight in such circumstances.
How regrettable.
The kingdom's ultimate shield, Lord Kaiser!
There's no need to hold back.
After all, I don't know you.
Indeed, I shall not hold back,
as that would be rude.
Lord Kaiser is both capable and virtuous.
He doesn't like being in the spotlight,
but I assume he took on the role of Captain
of the Purple Orcas for
the sake of his subordinates.
His wife was very worried about him.
Lord Kaiser is an excellent Magic Knight.
He has people awaiting his return.
You will be returning him to us!
Flame Spirit Magic: Salamander's Breath!
That is an incredibly powerful spell,
though it shall not reach me.
Lord Kaiser's vortex magic...
He uses his own magic to deflect
and disperse his opponents' spells.
Now, in combination with the elf's magic,
it's enough for him to withstand spirit magic.
Magic attacks won't work against him.
The vortex is not used only
for defense, but also for attacks.
Despite my Mana Skin,
I'm sustaining this much damage...
On top of that, he's washing my magic away!
Not good.
I burned you to a crisp, but you
still came charging at me!
Such incredible speed, reflexes... and power!
Not bad, you little brat!
Right back at you!
I never knew there was a
human as capable as you!
I haven't had this much fun
fighting with a brat one-on-one
since that one time,
with that super-serious fool.
He detects magic automatically
and blocks it.
I have no way of hitting
him with my attacks.
This unfair strength advantage he has...
It reminds me of my sister.
Ever since she was little, she was
audacious and full of spirit.
I idolized her amazing strength.
But I also eventually got irritated
with her overly carefree attitude.
I found you!
You won't get away this time!
Sister, it's time for our
training lessons with Theresa.
Sister!
Just let her be, Fueggy.
Mereo will be able to get stronger on her own.
Theresa Rapual
That's just the kind of genius she is.
Looking back on it now, I must've
been jealous of my sister.
Please wait!
You're not going to join
the Crimson Lion Kings?
Correct.
But why?
As strong as you are, you'd become
an incredibly powerful Magic Knight!
You could even become the Wizard King!
Tomorrow,
after I receive my grimoire, I'm going
to go explore the strong magic regions.
Like I have time to waste doing boring
guard duties or dealing with wimpy criminals.
How stupid.
Stupid?
Sister...
Would you spar a round with me?
Right here, right now.
So you're actually going
to go all-out today?
What a hardnose.
This huge fight between the eldest son
and eldest daughter of the Vermillion family...
would eventually be known as
"The Tuesday of Blood and Flames."
Back then, that fool was on fire!
You're probably the most
powerful human in this kingdom!
I'm sure if I defeat you, the other
humans won't stand a chance.
Be...
...gone!
No.
She's unorthodox, carefree, and doesn't
let anything hold her down.
She's crazy, but her blinding
strength is feared by all,
and she opened up a path for herself!
He's overbearing, stupidly serious,
and much too responsible.
His refined and extraordinary
strength is respected by all,
and they follow his lead.
She...
He...
...is worthy of being the strongest!
Reignition...
...Times Two!
He used Salamander as a decoy
and erased his own magic,
slipped through my vortex detection,
and got right in close to me!
She used sheer willpower
to get through my attacks
and loaded the magic she
saved up for her next attack!
As my sister's younger brother...
As that fool's older sister...
I must...
...be strong!
Hey, hey, it's Fana.
Hm? Fana from the Diamond Kingdom?
I'm Fana and she's Fana,
but we're not the same Fana.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 114: "The Final Invaders."
Page 114
The Final Invaders
She's her own Fana, just like I'm my own Fana.