How about this?
There is this joke.
How many Poles does it take to change a light bulb?
One to hold the light bulb,
ninety-nine to turn the house.
So the Pope says to a homeless guy...
"I thought I told you to get out of here yesterday." You idiot.
Just shut up and drive, moron.
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired!
Why am I stuck playing errand boy with you?
That dip-shit Dutch! Die!
Me?
I have to work on the boat.
Benny's working on the electronics.
Revy's just lying around in her room. Take her with you.
With Revy?
Do you have a problem?
Not really.
But she might not want to.
That's an issue you two have to deal with.
It's got nothing to do with me or the job.
Start close by.
First head to Roan "Jackpot" Pigeon's place on Rachiada Street.
Welcome Rebecca!
It's been a while.
Have you finally decided to start as a dancer for the S&M show?
Right baby?
Fuck off, Roan.
I showed up because it's work related.
I don't want to be tied or tie anyone else up.
You're as hard to get as always.
You look so good you'd be great for either.
It's a shame.
And what can I do for the two of you?
About the goods from the firm...
You ordered booze for this place, right?
There's 1500 bottles...
...in warehouse five at the harbor.
That's great.
Wow! Tax sure has gone up on these!
I can't stand it.
By the way,
who's that guy that's just standing there?
He's a rookie at our place.
He's got nowhere else to go, so we had no choice but to take care of him.
Hmm...
You're in for a rough ride, brother.
If you ever need anything, we'll take care of you.
Later Roan.
Don't forget about the money.
Sigh...
So the shipment's going to be late?
You could have told me over the phone, but you came all the way here?
Tell that to Dutch.
It's fine.
I just need to take care of fifteen of these today.
Should have gotten a part-timer to do it.
It's making my head feel strange.
I have a meeting tonight, too.
Some idiot selling drugs without permission.
It's such a pain in the ass.
Hey, hey.
Is that in her ass?
Right in her ass.
So if you hear anything, let me know.
I'll thank you properly if you do.
If I hear anything.
We'll come again.
Good luck with the rest.
I want to die...
I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired!
Why am I stuck playing errand boy with you?!
Well, one more and we're done.
To receive firearms on order...
...from Sister "PW" Deegan.
Hey, you old bitch!
It's Rebecca from the Lagoon Company!
Open the fuck up!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Open up!
I'll kill you!
You're just too damn loud.
Just put those in shed.
But these are cleaned items.
That's what the sister said.
Hey, Two-Hands, that's the chapel.
If a piece of shit like you walks through, you'll end up being smitten.
Over here. Follow me.
Oh my...
It certainly is a surprise...
...that Dutchy-Boy would send you on an errand.
That's not your problem.
You have the goods just like we ordered, Sister?
New items from the eastern division of Cambodia Petroleum.
Except for one item.
Unfortunately the L48A1 37mm revolving grenade launcher was out of stock.
Don't kid around, Sister.
We ordered them all from you because we needed them for the next job.
We do actually physically have it.
A different customer is saying they need it immediately.
However, as Lagoon is a very good customer of ours, I wouldn't mind handing it over to you.
It will either have to be a better deal or a discount on...
Don't fuck with me, Sister.
If you just play this by the book then everyone'll be happy.
You don't want to have to do your accounting with your feet, do you?
I wouldn't make idle threats, Miss.
If you insist, why don't you bring Dutch-boy around?
That's all.
There's nothing before or after.
Move it, Eda, you second-rate gunman.
Want me to teach you how to smoke through your forehead?
This is very good tea, Sister.
Sister?
Well...
Sister Yolanda, young man.
It's been a long time since I've had tea that wasn't from a tea-bag.
Is this W&M?
Or is it Fortnum and Mason?
You're very knowledgeable, young man.
It's W&M.
I just love tea.
It certainly is a flavor delivered by a company with dedication and history.
Rock, shut up!
And if you sell other goods, then I guess that's all right too.
I don't see it.
What are you trying to say, young man?
Do you mean illegal arms?
You won't have much of a negotiation if you get too hasty.
What if I mean drugs? That's what I mean, Sister.
Did you know drugs are being distributed outside the agreed routes, Sister?
Hotel Moscow and other mafia in the city are searching for them.
But they still haven't been found.
That's because they have a blind-spot in a place where they shouldn't have to look.
For instance, those who are able to get in and out of the country due to religious connections.
All proper NGO members...
They don't look for those who don't even realize they're deliverers.
Sister Eda.
Why did you put the big bags of sheets into the shed?
Cleaned items are normally taken to the living quarters.
Young man...
You can't make statements based on conjectures.
You make it sound like it's coming from this place.
It's just a hypothesis.
Also, the amount of weapons leaving and entering this place don't match up.
That's easy to see from a little research.
It is dangerously easy to see.
One more thing.
The Lagoon Company is on friendly terms with Hotel Moscow,
but it does not mean we are working together.
If you get a bit better at timing, you'll be great.
Eda.
Yes?
It's hard to endure, but he passes.
Add a launcher to the list.
OK.
Dutchy-Boy has a good eye.
It's almost time for mass.
I apologize, but you'll have to be on your way.
Young man.
Come visit some time.
You got lucky.
Get the hell out of here.
Miss.
Why don't you follow his lead a little?
You can't make good business by just waving your gun around.
Shut up, you old bitch.
Man...
We should have timed this a little better.
It's crowded.
Let's eat before it gets cold.
I don't want to eat.
Eat.
You'll feel better if you eat.
Give me the keys, I'll go back alone.
Then I couldn't get home.
Then walk.
That's not going to happen.
Go back home to Japan.
You're not cut out for this.
You're the one who invited me.
I sure fucked up.
I wonder.
Who kept the church from becoming a bloodbath?
Just like that old lady said,
you can't solve everything with a gun.
Hey you...
You better watch what you say.
You've been that way since the submarine.
About that...
Who cares.
I told you never to talk about that.
Revy.
I'm not going to apologize anymore.
I think I misheard you.
I thought I just heard you fucking with me.
I see.
Then I'll say it again!
I'm not mistaken!
I've got nothing to apologize for!
That's what I'm saying!
That's a shame.
You just stepped on an un-resettable, non-negotiable, big ass landmine.
It's a real shame.
I'll ask you one last thing.
What do you want on your tombstone?
Write, "There's no medicine for violent idiots."
Good bye, Rock.
See ya.
See?
There are some things you can't solve with a gun.
You!
Don't say "You"!
My name is Rock!
Got it?
I had enough of this.
I've had my fill.
I thought I was done kissing my superiors' asses.
Now I'm at the ends of the Earth kissing some woman's ass?
What kind of sick joke is this?
Impudent son of a bitch.
That's ROCK!
Impudent?
Don't fuck around, you moron.
Aren't you an outlaw, a wild pirate?
But as soon as you open your mouth, it's "Money, money money, money"!
You'd think you'd be a villain after a big prize,
but you end up scavenging off of corpses.
There's a limit to how fucking greedy you can be!
Don't you have any pride in that head of yours?
Don't you try and gloss this over white-collar!
What do you know about me?!
What the hell do you know?!
Tell me!
A guy like you, with a peaceful life, has no idea how I lived.
You're right.
There's no way I would know.
I'm not you.
But let me ask you:
What do you know about me?
No matter how you live, you'll encounter suffering, right?
You have no intention of understanding that.
And when you can't answer, you conveniently turn into the tragic heroine.
That's the most cowardly thing about you!
Shut up!
You're the one looking at this conveniently!
God damn it.
This isn't like those cheap Hollywood films you like!
Pride?
Fuck that!
Look around!
It's a pile of shit in every direction!
Robin Hood doesn't exist anywhere, you fucker!
If there's no Robin Hood, then become Robin Hood.
It's a much better way of life than crying and bitching!
Shut up.
Shut up god dammit.
I'll kill you!
Do it.
Just keep chasing your tail like a dog.
If you kill me here, that'll be proof.
That's all I know how to do!
Did you forget, Revy?
Why I'm here?
My bosses calmly cut my life away.
To protect their dirty money and their place to eat.
When I was invited by you, it was like something blew through me.
Like something snapped.
Being shaken by the rush-hour, fake laughing, lowering my head and risking my life to keep a good score.
My life was fine as long as I had a place to drink and a batting center.
None of that mattered anymore.
The one who taught me that...
The one who invited me...
That was you, Revy.
The reason I'm concerned...
...is that the woman who taught me all this, is acting like the people who betrayed me.
I can't stand that!
I don't know what you mean, shithead.
Damn it. You're a pain in the ass.
You won't live long, idiot.
You're not the only one who has to suffer and deal with idiots.
You're a greater idiot that I am.
Dipshit.
I'm gonna get mad.
Good! I'll see how you dance around!
Hey!
What the hell is it?
Geez.
I hear someone's making a ruckus at the market, and it turns out to be you.
Revy.
This isn't a prize in a cracker-jack box.
Shooting off like that without concern for who's watching.
I wish you'd understand how I feel when I have to clean up.
But that's why we send you fat envelopes.
That's your job, Chief Watsup.
I'm not saying don't do it, just do it where no one can see.
As long as you do that, I won't care if you kill, sell drugs or play hide the apple.
As long as there's no trouble, I don't have to cancel my golfing schedule.
Anyway, I'm bringing you in.
There's paperwork to take care of on our side.
OK, OK.
Damn engine is giving me trouble.
There's cold ones.
Right.
Hey chief, don't steal our car.
I don't want that piece of shit.
Take it when you go home.
Hey Rock.
One thing.
After I ask there'll be no more trouble.
Which side do you want to be on?
I am...
I am where I'm standing. Nowhere else.
Rock.
Give me a light.
Light?
The cop has the lighter.
What are you talking about?
You've got one.
What a shitty day.
No kidding.
I'm so tired.
I want to get home and sleep.
Yeah.
I'm going to be sold somewhere, right?
The world will keep revolving even if justice doesn't exist.