It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The members of the Golden Dawn
who had reincarnated as
elves attacked the castle.
On top of that, the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's floating hideout arrived
at the royal capital,
carrying Licht and Raia.
Who the hell invited that giant rock?
But look. A pretty little
bird just showed up, too.
Nozel and Noelle regrouped
with Yami and the others,
then split off in order to protect
the people of the Clover Kingdom.
But when Noelle and Nozel returned to the
Silva residence, where they had grown up,
they were faced with the
enemy's compass magic.
Noelle used the experience she
had gained in previous battles,
as well as all the hours
she'd spent training,
along with her desire to save her
siblings to gain new powers.
Now be destroyed!
Both you and this mad world!
Spatial Mage Brothers
Vermillion Residence
No matter how many times we blow
this away, it comes right back.
How dare those humans use
such impertinent spells?
There are several enemies on the
third floor and in the inner courtyard.
Which would mean the safest and most
beautiful escape route would be...
Right there.
Everyone, please hurry.
Thank you, Mimosa and Kirsch.
You've saved us.
This is the Vermillion residence.
The terrain is completely in our favor, and...
My beautiful cherry blossom magic is helping
to confuse the enemy while
protecting and hiding our allies.
These shriveled little mushrooms
and their fungus magic weaken
the enemy's magic and
their ability to find us.
And finally, my dear sister
Mimosa is using her plant magic
to search our residence
and guide us through it.
If our goal is evacuation,
our spells are tailormade for it.
We don't even have to worry about bloodshed.
It's so beautiful!
Please do shut up, Kirsch.
They'll find us.
They're only our enemies because
their bodies were taken over by elves.
Members of the Golden Dawn,
I promise you that we'll return you to normal.
Heya. Working hard?
David!
Member of the Golden Dawn
David Swallow
Nope! I'm Baval.
I didn't sense his presence at all.
How did he find us?
Our spells aren't working?
Oh, come on. Don't look so scary.
I'm sorry to interrupt when
you were trying so hard,
but all I did was find you and say hi.
If I wanted to kill you,
you'd all be dead by now,
so there's no point in getting all up in arms.
What's with this elf?
What are you after?
Nothing, really.
Let's relax and have a little chat.
I think you know this, but we've reincarnated
with much more powerful magic than you
and gathered here at the royals' residence.
You can sense it, too, right?
That there's powerful magic
other than ours heading here.
Oh, it's pointless to escape outside.
I mean, we're just going
to kill you all anyway.
So just relax and give up.
I'm pretty amazing, but so are the others.
Man... This really takes me back.
I can't wait to see everyone.
I won't let that happen!
We won't give up!
Well, that's fine and all, but I mean...
This match seems like it'll be over
as soon as the enemy's king is taken.
Kira Residence • Central Tower
There's a really powerful guy
visiting your king right now.
He's twisted, persistent, and stubborn,
so your king won't be able to escape.
Oh, and...
If our guy uses that magic to kill,
there's no way your king will survive.
My magic isn't enough to offset that magic...
He's that powerful?
How dare you?! What do you think
you're doing in this sacred hall?!
Wh-What's the matter, Langris?!
That's the current king?
How seedy can a guy look?
Seedy...
How dare you call me seedy?!
So your son is a traitorous rebel!
Your Majesty, this is some kind of mistake!
Y-Yes! My little Langris would
never do something so fooli—
Silence!
Honestly... How could they
let this scoundrel through?
Julius and the other Magic Knights
are all absolutely useless!
Very well, scoundrel!
I shall show you my magic!
Behold my vast magical powers!
You must be too busy shaking to even escape!
Light Magic:
Absolute Monarch of Divine Brilliance!
How do you like that?! Behold my godlike spell!
Now grovel before my authority!
My...
My spell!
What a ridiculously slow light spell.
I'm not going to kill you right away.
I'll start with your legs!
Stop!
Langris!
Please don't do this, Langris!
If you don't stop now,
both you and the people who care
for you are only going to be sad.
Shut up.
You killed all of us elves, and you have
the nerve to talk about being sad?
Langris!
Are you all right, Miss Finnes?
Finral...
Finral!
Who the hell are you?
I'm your older brother!
Stop trying to act cool, Finral!
I'm not, though!
What are the others doing?
We took care of all the other shiny guys.
It would've gone more smoothly if
Mr. String Bean here had done his job.
What? You were the one slacking off,
you stupid meathead.
Looks like you made a mistake
in overestimating your strength
and splitting up your forces, elf.
You expect me to believe you?
Care to explain how you
two were able to beat them?
Just like this!
We won't give you a chance...
...to attack!
I'm sorry. My magic seems to automatically
attack anyone who tries to attack me right now.
At least entertain me a little, humans.
Bring it on.
That level of spatial magic is astounding!
There's no spatial mage in this kingdom
who can cancel a spell like that.
And he has it protecting him
automatically, at all times?
No one could ask for a better shield!
Father, Miss Finnes...
Leave this to us and run!
Enough!
You're just the Black Bulls' transport!
You don't stand a chance against Langris!
It doesn't matter if I'm just
the Black Bulls' transport,
or if he's the Vice Captain
of the Golden Dawn.
Right now, the only reason I'm fighting...
is because I'm his older brother!
Finral...
Could you not underestimate
my squad's wheels?
What? Er...
Yeah, you're in the way, so...
Get moving, will ya, old man?
Langris! My dear little Langris!
Yeah, you too, old lady.
Langris!
Finral, please come back alive.
I will. Along with Langris.
Hey!
Why didn't you let me escape first?!
Oh.
Honestly, you're all worthless.
Hang on, now. I still have
to tear you to pieces.
Langris...
Seems like this kid's definitely
gonna be worth slashing apart.
Severing Magic: Death Scythe...
Lunatic Slash.
You stupid mantis!
Whoa! Talk about an insane way
to help someone escape!
Just remember, he's the king!
You gouged my slashes. Nice, very nice!
He only sees the enemy now!
You still think you have
a chance against me?
Know your place, humans!
He can actually use attack spells
while also using his automatic defense?
Come on, man.
If any of these hit you,
you'll be dead instantly.
Spatial Magic...
Archangel's Crash!
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
The difference in our
magic power is too great!
I can't even block half of these with my magic!
Avoid the rest any way you can!
Damn it!
Who do you think you're
ordering around, Finral?
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
Reinforcement Magic: Leg Strength Boost!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Slash!
Yami!
Thanks!
We'll have to do something
about that defense
if we're gonna get anywhere near him.
But if he keeps attacking
us this relentlessly,
Finral's magic won't be able
to keep canceling him out.
A long battle puts us at a disadvantage.
If we start a fight, it needs to be quick.
We'll have to force our way through!
And for that to happen...
We need more than one attack
to break through that defense.
I can take care of one side...
I haven't had a prey like
this in a long time.
I want to slash him...
I want to slash him so much!
Let me slash ya!
Jack's blades can cut
through all sorts of spells
by using his innate instincts to
transform the very nature of his magic.
And all because he wants to slash things.
Like this?
And even though spatial
magic has unique properties,
he's still able to slash through it.
Wh-What?
And there he is! The tall, scrawny,
perverted weirdo genius!
Severing Magic...
Dark Magic...
Dark Cloaked...
Cut through...
...space!
Death Scythe!
Dimension Slash!
Yes!
Tch!
I was surprised that they were
able to get rid of my defenses,
but it seems they were one move short!
You can't defend or even
attack with your spatial magic!
My magic can't defeat my enemies.
But...
Return... to nothingness!
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
Wha—
He dropped his defenses so
he could transport the others?!
My Fallen Angel's Wingbeat forcibly
moves someone from one point to another.
I'll save you along with my friends!
Too bad, human!
I'm just a little bit faster!
You're all just going to die at once!
These guys are Magic Knights Squad Captains!
They'll do something about this!
The more I slash, the faster my blades become!
It's time for your nap, little boy!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked
Lightless Blunt Strike!
This time, it should—
You're just humans...
How dare you do this to me?!
You petty... dirty, ugly humans!
Disappear!
Now he's really lost his mind.
What's the deal with this
intensely wicked magic?
Tch!
What the hell are we supposed
to do with this? Damn it!
No... It's all over.
When he's that far gone, there's no
way he'd notice my puny magic.
Langris...
Thinking back, we've never actually
fought ever since we were kids.
I always ran away, using my
lack of talent as an excuse.
Even though I'm your older brother,
and even though I realized you felt lonely...
This is... my last chance!
Your big brother's pretty confident
when it comes to agility and accuracy.
I'm going to stop you, no matter what!
Come here...
Langris!
Langris... Langris... Langris!
For the talented little brother,
you sure are a handful. Honestly...
I'm pretty weak, so...
I'm sorry I took so long.
Langris...
Seriously...
You've got some nerve, taking all the
glory when you're nothing but a wimp.
Well done, Finral.
Now, what I really want to
know is... what's their endgame?
Are they gonna call it a day after
they slaughter all us humans?
I have a feeling they're
still hiding something.
Finally... Soon, I'll be able
to see you awake, Licht.
Did you also just get here?
Brother, that's not Licht.
You're Patry.
I knew you always looked up to Licht,
but you finally decided
to look like him, too?
What do you mean, "finally"?
When I reincarnated, I just
happened to end up in this body.
This was my fate.
Man, you're creepy.
Hup!
Hey! It's been a while, Droit.
I just reincarnated, so it doesn't
feel like it's been that long.
I see. Hey there, little Eclat.
Good evening.
Raia, where's Licht?
Hey, good to see you, Patry.
Maybe because his body's artificial,
or maybe because he's the one who activated
the forbidden reincarnation spell...
His memories aren't completely
back yet, and he's asleep right now.
I see.
Well, anyway, the gang's all here now.
Everyone else is waiting in the back.
We may all be here now,
but I'm pretty sure the Golden Dawn's
already taken care of all the humans.
There was a huge chunk
gouged out of the castle.
Looks like Latry went a bit crazy.
I'm sure that seedy-looking king
is no longer alive, either.
Now all we have to do is fit the final
magic stone into the pedestal in the castle,
and activate the spell that
uses the entire kingdom.
That magic stone is
already within our hands.
We'll wash away the malice
that afflicts us as a side effect
of the forbidden spell,
and complete our reincarnation.
We'll wipe out all of the humans,
and we'll take back this world,
making it a peaceful world for elves alone.
I'm gonna bet that there are a
bunch of tough guys in there.
I wonder what the rest of my dumbasses
and the other Magic Knights are doing.
I'm gonna flatten all the elves
myself if they don't get here soon.
Nah, I'm gonna slash 'em all first.
No, it'll be me.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Me
Me.
I'm gonna flatten all the elves
myself if they don't get here soon.
Nah, I'm gonna slash 'em all first.
No, it'll be me.
No, me!
I told you, I'm gonna kick all their asses!
And I'm telling you that I'm
gonna kick all their asses!
No, me!
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me...
Me!
Tch! You piss me off.
Hey, stop copying me.
Wha—
I said stop copying me!
What the hell's going on?
We keep doing the same things!
After all's said and done,
Yami and Jack are totally in sync.
Shut the hell up!
My beautiful voice, my beautiful flowers...
Everything about me,
Kirsch "Beautiful" Vermillion, is beautiful.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 110:
"The Raging Bull Joins the Showdown!!"
Page 110
The Raging Bull Joins the Showdown!!
I am not a raging bull.
I'm just ragingly beautiful!