It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Here we go!
To the Shadow Palace!
In order to save the souls of those
who had reincarnated as elves,
Asta and the others stormed
the Shadow Palace.
These pictures...
Welcome!
Rill!
Just wait! I'll wake you up right now!
Inside the Shadow Palace,
Asta and Mimosa encountered Rill,
while Noelle ran into Fana.
Fana? Wh-What are you doing here?
I may be Fana, but I'm not the Fana you know.
Watch your mouth. I guess I'll have
to teach you some manners, brat.
Mereoleona faced off with Vetto,
while Fuegoleon faced off with Kaiser.
Both of them ended up in a heated battle.
Be...
...gone!
No.
I must...
...be strong!
The Final Invaders
Aw, I lost her.
My Valkyrie Armor... I'm not able to
use it to its full potential yet...
But I'm far more mobile than she is.
She must be the complete
version of Fana the Hateful,
who once possessed Fana
of the Diamond Kingdom.
In that case...
Up until now, I was afraid
of its overall power,
so I've been concentrating on control
and held back on my attacks...
but I guess I can go all-out!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Huh?
Huh?! I-I-I'm so sorry!
Flame Recovery Magic: Phoenix Robe.
Wow, that was pretty intense!
I lost my clothes again.
We ended up using forbidden magic,
so we get to use some magic from the
other world to cast supernatural spells.
What am I...
Sorry... I sorta got sick of dying.
What am I supposed to do about this?!
Plant Magic: Magic Cannon Flower!
There's no end to this!
Damn it... I don't have time
to go into my black form!
And even if I could, if I can't land a
hit on Rill for sure, there's no point!
Hm... Maybe the color's too light here.
Oh, you're still alive?
At this rate...
Asta!
I'm so sorry! I'll heal you—
Yeah...
But it doesn't look like we're going
to get a break anytime soon.
Mimosa! Get on my back, and then
tie us together with vines!
Huh?
We have no choice but to combine!
C-Combine?
Hurry!
A-All right...
Plant Recovery Magic:
Princess-Healing Flower Robe!
All right! Come at us!
Whoopsie!
Aw.
The elves from the Golden Dawn
are really strong.
We've been close, but we haven't
managed to strike a decisive blow!
Not yet!
This magic...
Expand your Mana Zones and form magic paths.
I want all of you to join the
Magic Knights who are already fighting
and focus all your energy
on supporting them
with long-range offensive spells.
Let's go!
La?
He's...
He's beautiful.
He's no match for my beauty...
But he's beautiful.
He...
Are you telling me he gathered all
the Magic Knights that had been
scattered all over the kingdom
in this short amount of time?
Yuno!
I'm so glad you're here!
Please, have some food!
I don't think now's the time for...
What are you doing here, you raccoon?!
The castle was in trouble,
and they needed my help.
This food...
It recovers your magic?
That's amazing. Thank you.
That's amazing... Thank you...
He said it was amazing!
That's amazing
You're very welcome!
What's the current situation?
Um, Asta and the captains are
fighting their last battle with
the enemy's strongest members
in that pitch-black castle.
The entrance has already closed, though.
Asta's already in there?
What is that light?
Hey! Get away from Yuno this instant!
But he hasn't had dessert yet!
Dessert, my butt! I'm his dessert!
I'll follow you to the ends of the
world and cook you nummy nums!
Sit tight, Asta.
Um, Asta's hot rival friend
just got into the castle.
So did Charmy. No fair.
Yuno! Where'd you go, Yuno?!
And what was that weird place we just
went through? And where am I now?!
Oh, I'm in hell.
La?!
What the heck is this place?!
Miz Charmy!
Asta!
How'd you get in here?
La!
I have no idea! I was just hanging on to Yuno!
Yuno's here, too?
Where are you, Yuno? What is all of this?
These monsters are spells that Rill drew.
We have to do something about him!
Huh?
Miz Charmy?
That's not it... This just isn't right.
I can't draw it right!
I drew some monsters because I thought
they'd be fitting for the end of all humans...
But I actually want to
draw something prettier.
I don't want to draw something so warped.
This is all... This is all the humans' fault!
Look at you, all aggravated.
You must be starving. La?
Have some food and calm down. La?
When did she...
Shut up!
Get away from me, human.
I would never eat anything
you humans made.
Hey.
What do you think you're
doing to that food?
Cotton Creation Magic:
Strike of the Sleeping Sheep!
In order for me to create,
I need to destroy them first!
Both the humans and all
the things they create!
Mi...
Miz Charmy!
What was that chill?
What is this mana?
Miz... Charmy?
Hey... Can I come out now?
What in the world is this magic?
It doesn't belong to a normal human.
Wait!
She got bigger?!
This magic... I've felt it before.
You were born to a human and a dwarf...
And you have characteristics of both.
You're a hybrid!
Between a human and...
...a d-dwarf?
D...
Dwarf?!
She didn't know, either?!
Wait! What the heck's a dwarf, anyway?!
Well...
I-I don't know too many details,
since I only heard about them
from folktales our elderly
butler would tell us, but...
They were another race that lived long ago,
separate from the elves,
who also had special skills.
Hey! Weren't you a sheep?!
Shut up.
It spoke!
None of that matters right now.
T-True, you have a point.
More importantly... I'm starving.
Jeez, you're annoying.
You may be half dwarf, but if
you're going to get in my way...
You can disappear, too!
Well, I hope you make lots of those.
They're all my food!
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet!
It's... eating magic!
Isn't Miz Charmy's magic
supposed to be cotton magic?
No...
I've heard of this before...
That hybrids can end up with
two magical attributes.
This is...
The magic of mine that the wolf ate...
It's becoming hers!
It's being eaten faster than I can draw it!
My imagination won't be
beaten by your appetite!
You're going to regret...
wasting that food earlier!
This is for the protein!
This is for the fat!
They're just punches enhanced by
magic... but they're so powerful!
And this one's...
for the carbs!
You can't be serious...
This isn't enough to get rid
of my hatred of humans!
La! I'm not done yet, either!
This is for the vitamins!
This is for the fiber!
This is for the collagen!
This is for the sodium!
Th-This is...
This is for the potassium!
This is for the calcium!
This is insane!
This is for the magnesium!
Asta! You go on ahead!
I'm gonna pound the importance
of food into his body!
We have to hurry.
I'm counting on you, Miz Charmy!
Leave it to me!
Which way, Mimosa?
There were a number of paths,
but a few of them are blocked
because of all the intense fighting.
If we can just move up...
Let's use that way!
Got it!
Too bad. It's useless, no matter
how many times you attack.
I'm gonna turn you into ashes soon, 'kay?
I-If only Stupidsta was here...
Ast... Huh?!
I found a chick that looks like
she's worth slicing up!
Why did it have to be you?!
Huh?! You got a problem, little girl?!
Who's that?
David!
He's a senior of mine from the Golden Dawn.
He was possessed by an elf...
I wonder if someone defeated him.
Well, this is the perfect opportunity.
There are faint traces of magic here.
But it doesn't seem to belong to
humans or elves... What's going on?
I'll use Magic Flower Guidepost again.
This is... Below the strongest magic,
there's a space with something
that looks like a pedestal.
There are three elves there!
And this magic is... Yuno!
Let's go!
Wait for me, Yuno!
Well, this is a surprise...
We sent Ado's group to pick you up,
but you took them out instead,
then got here on your own.
I mean, I'm glad you got
here safely on your own.
You'll be giving us that magic stone now.
I've been waiting for this moment...
As usual, Ronne, you're so quiet that
I have no idea what you're saying!
And now, finally... everything will return.
Including our future...
And Licht's smile.
Light Creation Magic:
Light Swords of Conviction.
Copy Light Magic:
Mana Zone: Spirit's Hushed Dance.
What?
He managed to evade all those attacks?
Mana Zone: Spirit Storm Double!
In the time it took to get here,
this kid managed to level up his power
both as a human and as an elf...
This kid...
In terms of sheer native talent,
he might actually surpass Licht.
My Mana Zone couldn't detect him?
It wasn't super speed.
He just suddenly appeared there!
Again!
No... He forced me to move.
He can forcibly change the position
of someone he's touched once.
I don't know if it's a magic stone
or not, but that belongs to me.
Give it back!
Nice job, Ronne!
No one ever could beat you at tag.
Now... we'll finally make things right.
Yeah.
I can tell when someone's lying.
Why was what you just said a lie, Ronne?
Raia?
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
Don't tell me this reincarnation is...
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
I Can Tell When Someone's Lying
I Can Tell When Someone's Lying.
You can tell when someone's
lying, right, Raia?
Yeah, I can tell when someone's lying.
So if a liar said that they were a liar,
you'd be able to figure
out if that's true or not.
Yeah, I can tell when someone's lying.
I mean, if a liar is telling
you that they're lying,
they're just honestly telling you that
they're lying, but it's hard to tell?
But wait. Maybe they're
lying about being a liar?
But that would mean they're honest,
and honest people don't lie...
So that would make them a liar,
but liars wouldn't just come out
and say that they're liars...
So, um... uh... I...
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know... I don't know...
I don't know...
This is a famous paradox. All of
you should think about it, too.
That guy isn't Ronne.
This magic... Who is that guy?
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 115: "Mastermind."
Page 115
Mastermind
Wait... What have we been
trying to do this whole time?