It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
In search of the magic stone, Asta and the
others arrived at the Underwater Temple,
where they were forced to participate in High
Priest Gifso's game, the Temple Battle Royale.
According to your ranking system,
my temple mages would be more
powerful than intermediate knights!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
Don't think I'm gonna get discouraged
just because I'm surrounded by water.
Magna and Luck also participated in the game,
hoping to get the magic stone.
Ya snooze, ya lose, Magna!
Lightning Magic: Thunderbolt Destruction!
Well, well, aren't you lively?
My son is the strongest mage
of the Underwater Temple!
He's strong...
No doubt about it... He's definitely
the strongest one here.
You two should come at me at once.
I'd rather not hurt you
any more than I need to.
Water Creation Magic: Sea God's Hammer!
You ain't ending anyone, you bastard!
I'm not done having fun yet!
The one who appeared
before Magna and Luck
was one of the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's top brass, Vetto.
Looks like you're having fun.
Why don't you let us join in?
The Pointlessly Direct Fireball
and the Wild Lightning
Oh, it's a full moon tonight.
I wonder if Asta is looking up
at the same moon right now.
Oh, silly me!
Bah-ha? I guess I fell asleep—
Bah-ha?!
Hmph. Not even good for a warm-up.
You're just a pack of mice.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Bah-ha...
I know we were all on vacation, but there
were a number of senior Magic Knights here!
And they were all defeated by one guy...
What were the Magic Knights we
believed in so much all about, then?
That thing wasn't human.
That was...
a beast!
Where'd this macho dude suddenly come from?
He looks pretty hardcore.
Aw, that shark guy was my prey.
All I know is... This guy's magic
power is greater than Captain Yami's.
You made it through
the rough ocean currents
and then forced your way in here...
That's some incredible magic, all right.
Oh? I guess you can still move.
Ow...
I'm pretty sure you're not a Magic Knight.
What brings you to the Underwater Temple?
We're after the same thing as those
two over there, the magic stone.
I see. But it's not like I'm
just going to hand it over.
Oh, I don't expect you to just hand it over.
We're going to lay waste to everyone here,
make you despair, and seize it!
What are you...
Scatter and spread despair!
Yes, sir!
Well, you're all rather rude, abrupt guests.
Could you head on home now?
Hey, you.
That's also a pretty rude
way to address someone.
If you want to get your way,
do something about it,
and hit me with all your magic.
Looks like you're completely
underestimating me.
I may not look like it, but I am the
strongest in the Underwater Temple.
Enough talk! Say it with your magic!
Well, if you insist...
Water Creation Magic: Sea God's Hammer!
Beast Magic: Rhinoceros Armor.
It didn't even faze him.
That's not a bad spell, for a mouse.
Let me give you a reward.
A reward?
Yes, a reward called despair.
This world is all about the
survival of the fittest.
The strongest beasts survive, and the
weak vermin live only to become prey!
Beast Magic: Bear Claw!
Did you get a good feel for how
vastly different our powers are?
You insects aren't even
allowed to hold on to hope.
I-Impossible...
The temple's greatest warrior, Gio,
is being defeated so easily.
I've never seen anything like this.
Hey, gramps. Playtime's over.
Hurry up and get me in there.
Well, if you insist...
But who in the world is this man?
He's one of the leaders of a nasty terror
group called the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun?
I don't have time to explain.
We're short on time, so hurry it up.
Sadly, I can't.
We can't leave here until the game is over.
I can't even undo the spell.
Those are the rules of my magic.
I see.
What are you...
Then I'll just let myself out.
Say what?
Dark Magic: Lightless Slash!
Wh-What in the world?!
Tch.
This is...
Spatial Magic: Different Dimension Sphere.
Once you're trapped in my spatial magic,
no matter who you are,
you won't be able to escape.
Black, foreign swordsman...
The mana tells me you're here.
Stay there and watch for a while.
You're going to be my main dish...
After I season you with despair,
as you watch all of your friends die!
If he gets out, the temple's done for.
Hey, gramps.
Wh-What?
Can you make it so they hear us out there?
Huh? S-Sure...
But what are you going to do?
Testing, testing...
That's the captain...
Hey, you dumbasses, listen up.
Captain! I beat one!
Someone really dangerous
just crashed the game.
He's one of the leaders of
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
and a beast of a man strong enough to go
head-to-head with a Magic Knight Captain.
It's him...
Also, three of his underlings
are over there, too.
Hurry up and hand over
that yummy-looking food...
Here's the problem... Due to reasons,
I can't go over there.
What?! What do you mean, "reasons"?!
Meaning you guys gotta
do something about him.
You can't be serious!
Listen up.
All of you, surpass your limits,
right here, right now.
If you die, I'll kill you.
That's all.
Live...
He's insane.
I never thought the game
could get so exciting.
It's a game that'll determine the fate
of the Underwater Temple, blast it!
The game rules have changed!
No time limit.
To clear the game, defeat the
Eye of the Midnight Sun's team.
Those who contribute to clearing the game
will get any wish that's
within my power to grant!
There's an absolute monster here...
Damn it.
I'm scared, but...
That makes him worth fighting even more!
I'll do this... I'm gonna do this, damn it!
Asta...
I guess we'll have to put
our match on hold.
Kiato...
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
Now, then... Who's my next prey?
Not yet...
Who said you could move on to the next?
We're still alive, you know.
After what Mister Yami said,
I can't just lie here napping.
Besides...
I'm not...
...going to break!
Excellent.
The more stubborn the prey, the better
it is when they're finally in despair!
Well, we managed to get back up,
but how the hell are we supposed
to fight that monster?
If he lands even one more decent
blow on us, we're finished... So...
Hey, you.
Hit us with another one of those.
What?!
That really fast one.
Damn it, Luck! What the hell?! Are you stupid?!
We just barely managed to block that attack,
and we both still took a ton of damage!
Oh? So you're imitating me. Very well.
I'll keep giving you despair...
until you die!
Just what I thought! That spell leaves a
split-second opening right after you attack.
So you're already matching my pace.
You've got good speed and sharp
senses, I'll give you that!
Huh? My Thunderbolt Destruction
didn't work at all!
I'll play with you for a while!
You speedy little...
That battle maniac... Damn it.
So you're Magna, huh?
What a weird haircut.
I'm Luck. Nice to meet you.
Is this the guy who's called the Smiling
Combat Fiend and Luck the Cheery Berserker?
I need to show him who's boss.
Nice to meet you, too, loser.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Wow, what a funny face.
Ever since I joined the squad, he was an
annoying pest who messed with me constantly.
His personality was...
"This dude's got some serious issues."
Hot, hot, hot, hot...
Take that!
Hot!
Even on our missions,
he would do insane things.
Take that!
Huh?!
It's the Crackling Magna Typhoon!
I had no choice but to admit that
he has great battle instincts.
And since that dungeon mission,
he's gotten even stronger.
I hate to say it,
but you're my best friend.
Damn it...
Don't...
Don't you dare leave me behind, you dumbass!
Flame Creation Magic: Grand Slam!
I'm gonna crush it over here!
Nice, Magna!
Take that!
When I first met you, I underestimated you.
A peasant, huh? He looks boring.
But my instincts warned me...
They told me, "This guy's gonna
be dangerous, yet interesting."
You interested me so much
that I kept messing with you.
That pudding you were
saving sure was delicious.
That's going to be your last supper!
You always struck back at
me with everything you had.
I just now realized...
that you're my...
You're my...
That you're my very first friend.
Magna! I bet you've got even more in you!
Shut up!
Nice catch, Fireball Gangster!
Who are you calling a gangster?!
Get off me, Lightning Boy!
That's enough playtime, don't you think?
Bring it on, you jerk!
We're just about warmed up, too!
This way!
How can you tell when you
can't even sense mana?
I can't sense mana, but I can sense ki.
Ki? It's true that I sense a
strong magical power up ahead.
And it's incredibly powerful.
I've never felt anything like it before!
But as you said, we've got to do this!
Hey, your ki earlier...
It was hard to sense your presence.
How were you doing that?
Oh, by dancing, I unconsciously
put myself into a trance.
A trance?
When I'm in that state, my body moves
without me even having to think.
Then my opponents can't predict my movements.
I see! So that's actually possible...
All right!
Whatcha doin'?
Putting myself into a trance.
I've got a clear view of that magic now!
Flame and lightning magic are fighting!
Flame and lightning...
It must be Magna and Luck!
Their opponent has huge magic and...
What is this?
It's like hundreds of raging beasts!
It must be Vetto! Wait, you can tell all that?
My tribe's eyes are good at picking up magic.
But if this is who we're up against...
Nah.
Those two are crazy, but when it comes
down to it, they're both super reliable!
They definitely won't die!
Ow...
Do you finally get it?
The weak get eaten, and all
they have left is despair.
Despair?
Like we have time for that, you dumbass!
Yup...
If we were in despair...
We'd be too embarrassed to
act like his superiors again!
Not yet...
We know...
that if we fight him normally,
we probably won't stand a chance.
Not yet...
That's why... not yet!
That slight opening we have
right after he attacks...
Right now!
We'll hit him with all the magic we've got!
A simultaneous, full-power, body
and soul attack at close range?!
Is this what they were trying to do?
Magna... Luck...
This mana...
This power is insane.
Combo Magic: Flame Lightning
Explosive Cannon!
Magna! Luck!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Crackling Magna Typhoon!
Hey, everyone! How are you doing?
We can't hear you! Put a little
more umph into it, damn it!
Today, we're going to show you how you can
do an easy Crackling Magna Typhoon at home.
First, have a string of lightning ready.
No one can do that!
Then, you wrap that lightning
string around Magna, like this.
It's electrocuting me!
Oh, you'll have to get your own Magna.
They can't do that, damn it!
Once you wrap the lightning
string around him,
you're going to spin him with
all your strength like a top.
Just like this! Take that!
And that's the Crackling Magna Typhoon.
Easy, right?
You're the only one who can do this, damn it!
Save me!
See you next time!
I'll never give up, no matter
how powerful my enemy is!
Not yet! I'm... We're the Black Bulls!
Black Clover, Page 45: " The Guy
Who Doesn't Know When to Quit."
Page 45
The Guy Who Doesn't Know When to Quit
That's right!
Not giving up is my magic!