It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Breaking the Seal
N-N-N-N-N-N-Ne...
Did you not hear me?
S-S-S-S-S....
Sp?!
The bird just spoke?
It must be a spirit, and a noble spirit at that!
Nero?!
You spoke just now,
didn't you? No, that can't be!
This is a dream, right? I'm still asleep, right?
Wipe off that dumb look and get a move on.
Hurry up with the spatial portal.
What?!
This bird just started talking out
of nowhere, and now it won't shut up!
At this rate,
humans who have elves within them
might not be able to return to normal.
What?
Even worse...
Anyway, hurry up and take
me to the demon's bones.
Nero, you're...
"Return."
That was a splendid cut.
"Storm of Blades."
Anything goes with you, doesn't it?!
This black creepy guy's magic...
"Earth Shield."
Not only can he make the things
he says manifest as magic,
"Wave of Flame."
"Iron Spear."
he can summon, move, and order
objects around, as well.
This "Storm of Blades" is basically
both of those things at once.
This is completely nuts!
He was able to wither
Charlotte's briars, heal himself,
and keep doing whatever the hell
he wants against the living,
but considering he hasn't
straight-up ordered us to "Die,"
I'm gonna guess he has some limits.
Ugh, damn it. Just thinking about
all this is a pain in the ass.
Charlotte!
I'm Charla!
Back then...
"Wither."
Did some of my briars not wither
because they were out of his range?
I'm assuming that was part of it, but it
comes down to how much magic he has.
Is the effect of the amount of magic
he puts into his words so great
that it overwhelms our magic?
So just barely fending off his attacks while
we keep trying to figure
him out is all we can do?
Tch!
The one thing I've noticed is he can't
stop my dark magic with his words.
I knew it. He dodged it rather than stopping it.
I mean, I need my spells to hit him, but...
Not bad!
I'm amazed you can move around so
much when you're basically asleep.
He's right. Licht isn't able to
manifest his full powers right now.
This fight seems evenly balanced
at the moment, but at this rate...
"Storm of Blades."
Damn it! There's no end to this!
This ain't good. That guy's magic
was too overpowered to begin with!
High
Devil
Elf Leader?
Charla
Royals
Nozel
The breakdown probably looks something like this.
Me
Magic
Nobles
Sol
Commoners
Magna
Kid
Bwah
Low
At this rate, my magic's not gonna hold out.
And he doesn't seem fazed by any of this.
I quite enjoy your company.
You're so pleasantly annoying
that I'm actually enjoying this.
To think that having my own body
and being able to play with magic
would make my heart dance with such delight!
I thank you.
You've also helped me obtain
the five-leaf grimoire.
Now I shall use it.
The magic of my words...
Word Soul Magic:
┘░╣╩┐┤.
This nasty magic is... He's still...
I do apologize, but I'm a completely
different being than the rest of you.
From a different dimension, in fact.
What the hell is this spell?
Is this from the other world?
Tch!
It's like sprinkling water on a hot stone.
Yeah... That's not good.
What is this...
...magic?
Traveling this far all at once is exhausting.
Hurry up.
H-Hey! Wait up!
Take out all the magic stones that
are embedded in this monument.
Magic stones...
All the magic stones that were taken by the
Eye of the Midnight Sun are here.
You're sure I can take them out?
Hurry it up.
Now...
Put all those magic stones into this statue.
The statue of the first Wizard King...
I guess they go here.
All that's left are the eyes.
This is the last one.
Is this... magic?
Watch out!
This is...
Our magic is... melting!
Curses!
Dark Cloaked
Black Blade Blunt Slash!
You...
It leeched magic and life energy out of me?!
I guess you won't be able
to hold your sword anymore.
It's a spell that devours life.
I merely opened the lid on it,
but it can no longer be stopped.
Not until it devours humans, elves...
and everything else.
Shit. This is seriously bad news.
That evil magic is heading our way!
What in the world is that?!
That's the devil's magic!
Light Magic: Light Swords of Conviction!
Wind Magic: Tornado Fang!
It swallowed up our spells?
Don't let it touch you! Run!
There!
Asta!
I thought I was a goner!
So anti-magic works against that, too?
And he's completely unharmed?
I guess it figured there's
no point in swallowing up
something that has no magic.
Unbelievable.
Hey! Why do you guys sound creeped out?!
This is...
As we thought, there's even more of
this eerie magic flowing above us.
At this rate, the ones in the
other rooms are in danger, too.
The one with the most mobility,
who can get those
who have turned into elves out of here...
Saving the kingdom, and all
of us escaping here in one piece,
will mean our victory.
I'll go assist the ones below.
Come with me, Vermillion.
Yes, sir.
You appear to understand
the enemy and what's going on
up above better than I do.
If you supplement Asta's anti-magic
with Yuno's spirit magic
and that elf's light magic,
you should make it to the battlefield.
Go.
Got it!
Now that your seal has been broken,
that means my seal will also...
Nero?
What a pathetic state you're in.
If only my spell was more complete...
No, the only reason I was able
to return is because of you.
Huh?
Welcome back, my prince.
First Wizard King
Lumiere Silvamillion Clover
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
The first Wizard King...
The legendary statue had life within it.
And you're—Huh?!
N-N-N-N-N-N-N-N-N-Nero, is that you?!
Secré Swallowtail
I had no idea you were such a cute girl!
If you'd told me earlier, I would've
totally asked you out on a date!
Why don't we go on a date right n—
I'm really sorry.
I sense an otherworldly magic
from the Shadow Palace.
I see. He must've obtained a body.
Why are you two...
Just as I was about to die, she used her
confinement magic to seal me away.
I was asleep this whole time.
And with the help of the magic stones,
I managed to awaken, at least partially.
Such calm yet powerful mana...
It's far more powerful than even the elves'...
She's...
For 500 years, I was just what
you people called "Nero."
Huh? Why are you holding my ha—
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release.
Huh?
Thank you, Magic Knight of the present.
Wait there for your friends' return.
I'm sorry you had to wait 500 years.
It's fine.
We can't let what happened
before ever happen again.
500 Years Ago
Clover Castle
Despite being a noble,
my magic was only able to
open and close things,
and was considered useless.
So I ended up a servant...
to an eccentric prince
whose magic and talent were
amazing even among royalty.
I wonder what kind of awful snob he'll be.
Hey there! You must be Secré.
Sorry, I'm researching ancient
magic right now, so I can't get up.
By the way, what kind of magic do you have?
But he was nothing like I had imagined.
Sealing magic?!
What's that? I've never heard of it before!
That's so unusual! How amazing!
How should we have you use it?
Just thinking about it is exciting, isn't it?
Magic that opens and closes locks is vulgar.
That's not true! Don't seal off your potential!
Please don't make a face like you
just said something clever.
Aw...
Also, your clothes are weird.
What?! But I made these
clothes myself! Aren't they great?
More importantly...
What's more important than that?
What should I help you with?
Well... Right now, I'm creating magical tools.
Magical tools?
Yup. So that people who aren't
blessed with magic or by their
magical attribute can
use all kinds of spells.
That way, I think we can
make our society more equal.
But that just sounds like a silly dream.
They're tools to help me with that.
I think I'll call them magic items.
I'm sure your magic will help me with this!
For example, can you seal magic into objects?
Um... Yes.
You can?! That's amazing!
I helped the prince make magical tools.
He really was nothing like I'd imagined.
There were members of his family
who didn't like his progressive ideas.
But he didn't let that bother him,
and he never compromised his ideals.
He was a strong, honest person.
Recently he and his sister, Lady Tetia,
have been sneaking out quite frequently.
What could they be doing here?
The other race... The ones blessed with mana!
Phenomenal magic and skill...
The same thoughts and ideals...
The same four-leaf grimoires...
The leader of the elves, Licht,
was the first peer and friend
that the prince had ever had.
We can come to understand each other.
You elves have truly amazing mana.
By combining that with the magic-item
technology that we humans created,
we can make this land
safer and more prosperous.
Let us live together, hand in hand.
Magic items that stored and distributed magic,
and the elves' magic stones, which linked
to another world and amplified spells...
Through his work with the elves,
spells and magic-item technology
that would help not only the humans,
but both races to live in peace as equals
were slowly becoming a reality.
The prince and Licht were best friends.
And they were supposed to become family.
I'm really sorry, but I'm probably
going to be late to your wedding.
Sadly, Father has summoned
me to the palace that day.
I know that he and the others
are against this marriage now,
but don't worry.
I'm sure they'll understand someday
and give you their blessings.
I know.
I'm sure Licht and the others
will be eager to see you.
But it's likely that even then,
he was already manipulating
the whole situation.
I wonder why Father summoned me today.
We didn't mention the wedding
to anyone, so is it a coincidence?
I need to hurry to the ceremony.
No one's here?
Father, where are you?
"Bind."
What is this?
Good day, my prince.
Minister?!
No... The evil mana that's coming
from him doesn't belong to him.
Who are you?!
Who am I?
Despair, hatred,
disloyalty, or death...
You may call me whatever you wish.
A soul with evil mana...
I've read about this being
from another world! A devil?
Where are my father and the others?
Who knows?
Maybe they've gone to destroy the other race
that's trying to harm the princess and,
indeed, the entire kingdom.
I'm sure the elves will be quite surprised
when the humans' violence and greed
fall upon the wedding ceremony
that only you should know about.
What?!
Ah, this is what I'd expect from
the strongest in the kingdom.
That's some terrifying magic.
Though I was prepared for that,
so even you won't be able to escape
from those bonds so easily.
Once I obtain my body and grimoire,
I'll come play with you again.
Wait!
Someone! Isn't there anyone here?
Anyone!
Prince!
Secré!
What's going on, Your Highness?
There's a devil plotting something!
So it wasn't you, was it, Your Highness?
That magic item we made is gone!
Secré! Break these restraints!
Your sealing magic can do it!
Right!
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
Faster... I need to go faster!
Tetia, Licht, everyone...
That's the magic item we made!
A five-leaf grimoire...
I knew it...
Licht...
I knew it wasn't you.
He reclaimed his heart?
I'm sorry I doubted you for even a second.
Please forgive me.
Such a futile struggle!
Now, relinquish your body to me.
You are the future we believed in.
You are hope.
Licht...
Right now, I am filled with
tremendous negative mana.
I don't have full control anymore.
At this rate, that devil will...
Don't...
To prevent my magic and body from falling
into the hands of something wicked...
I've pulled even more negative
magic into myself.
Magic stones... He used the highest
form of forbidden magic on his own body?
Don't... Don't do this, Licht!
I'm sorry. This is my last selfish request.
You're the only one who can grant it.
Don't do this, Licht!
Lumiere...
Please kill me!
This was all planned by that devil...
My prince, let us finish this.
We're going to save this world!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 118:
"A Reunion Across Time and Space."
Page 118
A Reunion Across Time and Space
We didn't give up back then!