It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Licht and his comrades finally
completed their reincarnation
and headed to the royal capital
to commence their attack.
Nozel, Noelle, Mimosa, Zora, Kirsch, En,
and Mereoleona,
who was still knocked out,
left the hideout and headed
back toward the royal capital.
Looks like some place is
already being attacked.
That's...
...Hage Village!
Sister!
Nash! No!
Asta and Yuno took a different route in
order to save their home, Hage Village,
from an attack by a Magic Knight
who'd reincarnated as an elf.
Asta... Yuno?
Good job fighting...
...Nash!
Leave the rest to us!
Crescent Moon Sickle, Four Blades!
I can tell from his mana.
The elf's soul inside him is in pain.
It's like the elves are asking for help.
Yuno!
Let's go, Asta!
At this rate, he's going to turn
into something besides an elf.
We have to set him free.
He negated... the reincarnation spell?
With this sword...
I'll be able to save everyone!
Lightning of Rage vs. Friends
What the hell is that giant
boulder-looking thing?
What is that?
What's going on?
All right, I guess I'll go have some fun.
The town...
It's being attacked?
We're heading into town, Vanessa!
Right.
G-Get on your own damn broom!
This is no time to be bashful! Get going!
I-I'm not bashful!
Damn it... H-Hang on tight!
Full speed ahead, Crazy Cyclone!
Up ahead, I feel elven magic from
both the north and the south.
Since there are two places, it'd be
better if we split up and helped them.
Yuno!
Asta!
See you at the royal capital!
Hey, now...
We came to this town because
it was under attack, but...
What the hell's going on here,
Luck?!
Why, you little...
Luck!
Damn it... Luck!
What are you trying to do?!
Luck?
Oh, him...
I think he wanted to see someone.
Was it you two?
Too bad, though.
Because of the reincarnation spell,
this body belongs to me, Rufel, now.
Reincarnation? Rufel?
The hell are you babbling about?
Forbidden magic?
Huh?
It means someone else
has taken over Luck's body!
Someone else?
Those Eye of the Midnight Sun guys?
Probably.
Luck and the other Royal Knights
headed to the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
Then was that flying boulder thing their...
It's their hideout.
I guess the plan to eliminate them failed.
Exactly! I guess you're
not as dumb as you look.
Oh, by the way, those Royal Knights
or whatever were completely wiped out!
So basically, if you guys are
also going to get in my way,
you're gonna have to die, too!
Wait a sec...
I ended up attacking somewhere
completely different?
Oh? Is this a spell to protect your friends?
That's pretty interesting.
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
I'm gonna burn you to a crisp!
Explosive Scatter—
The red thread of fate...
Rouge is on the side of all the Black Bulls.
So she'll protect Luck, even though
his body is possessed right now.
Shut down your damn cat's powers, Vanessa!
What are you talking about?
If Luck's attack had connected,
you would've died instantly.
Besides, if it really is the forbidden
spell, Luck is just asleep, and...
That's why I'm trying to
wake that fool back up!
Take this! Flame Magic: Explosive Scattershot!
Such a simple spell...
There's no way it'll hit me.
They disappeared?
But I still sense their mana.
I call this "Explosive
Annihilation Scattershot"!
He's fast!
There's no spell that can hit me.
Which means you humans can't defeat me!
Shut up!
Now, then... Do you think
you can dodge my attacks?!
Vanessa!
Honestly, all of you people
are so overly enthusiastic!
I'll back you up!
I mean, if you actually
manage to defeat Luck,
that might shock him enough to wake him up!
No one asked you!
Explosive Scatter...
Show him the results of
all your training with me!
That's exactly what I plan
on doing, you dumbass!
Eat this!
Again, that spell won't hit me.
This is my newest Explosive Scattershot!
I call it "Time Bomb Explosive Scattershot"!
Doesn't matter if it hits you
or not! It'll still explode!
Think you can tell which ones will explode?!
Your puny little spell isn't going to hit me!
At least try to amuse me a little more!
Whoa, there...
Throwing fireballs that
don't disappear or explode?
Is this supposed to be a feint?
Or are you out of magic already?
If he's dodging by sensing where mana is,
Magna can get behind him by mixing
in some regular Scattershots!
I'll be able to hit him at this distance!
Too bad.
I sensed your mana.
I'm fully aware of your ability
to sense mana and your speed.
He made sure it would explode
right at this moment?
You don't know, do you?
That I'm stupid enough to
make myself explode, too!
If you were actually Luck, you'd probably
figure that I'd do something so stupid!
I'm way more skilled than you when it comes to
resilience and being able to take a hit!
Flame Magic: Gargantuan Exploding Fireball!
And then... Flame Bondage Formation.
I know Luck really well.
I don't know who the hell you are,
but you don't know a damn
thing about him or me!
That's why you have no chance of beating me!
If that's crystal clear, then hurry up
and return that idiot to us!
You...
That's...
Who...
can't beat whom,
human?
Why don't you explain just how
you humans expect to defeat me?
Bring it on! I'll keep throwing
these at you until Luck wakes up!
He disappeared?
Your attacks will never hit me again.
He's moving so fast, I can't see him.
Humans can't keep up with me!
He was already a monster, but now...
Where are you looking?
And it's over!
Huh?
Oh?
The power to control... the future?
No, to control fate.
But it appears you can't attack me.
Not to mention, I'm pretty sure that
power uses quite a bit of magic.
The magic of elves, who are blessed
by mana, or the magic of you humans...
Which do you think will last longer?!
Tired already?
I haven't even broken a sweat yet!
That ended much more quickly than I'd hoped.
The humans of the Clover Kingdom
will be destroyed.
That's what you deserve, and that's the
fate we elves shall bring upon you!
Shut... up...
Yeah...
I don't care if you're an elf or not.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to that idiot...
So you can hurry up and get the
hell out of that body, dumbass!
He's a mischievous little brat who's always
being reckless and causing us trouble...
But Luck is my little brother!
Give him back right now!
You humans betray each
other at the drop of a hat.
Are you trying to tell me
you actually have a bond?
Don't make me laugh!
Nothing you can do will break
this reincarnation spell!
Especially not your flimsy little bond!
This human's soul has already been destroyed!
Is that so? In that case...
Why the hell are you crying?
Acting like someone you're not...
I know you're still in there, Luck!
While you were off messing around,
I was out training and got
super strong, you dumbass!
If that pisses you off, then get the
hell out here and fight me already!
Shut...
Luck, don't you dare think you
can get rid of us that easily!
My red thread of fate is
never going to let you go!
So hurry up and come back!
Shut up.
Luck!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Shut up, human!
Luck!
Like I'm ever...
going to shut up!
Rouge used up the last of her magic...
to bring upon the fate that
would bring Asta here!
Who the hell are you?
You know damn well who I am!
But I'll repeat myself as
many times as it takes!
We're Luck's friends!
Asta...
Friends, eh? You're all
really getting on my nerves.
You don't have a lick of magic, do you?
I never thought anyone in this world
could be so unloved by mana.
And the first ones to ever acknowledge
me and consider me one of their own
were the Black Bulls!
I won't let you take a single one of them!
It doesn't matter who or what you are.
You'll never be able to see my movements!
You can die at the hands
of your precious friend!
There's no way a human can
keep up with this speed!
How are you able to keep up?
Your ki is filled with rage that
makes it super easy to read!
And this sword is sensitive
to really powerful magic,
and will seek it wherever it goes!
You're so annoying!
Not bad.
But...
Like you could actually surpass my rage!
He shouldn't be able to detect me,
but his combat sense is insane!
Magna! Miz Vanessa!
I need you guys to back me up!
You got it!
You really think these attacks
are going to hit me now?
And...
I've figured out how fast you are by now!
Asta!
My body can't hold out much longer...
I need to make the next one count!
This is the end, human!
Since he's got no magic,
their plan is just to hide him?
In that case...
I'll spread out my mana
and detect the moment your
sword makes my mana disappear.
There he is.
He's heading straight for me.
I've got him!
My rage is stronger!
You're there!
There!
Huh?
They used that thread to throw off my timing?
Go!
Asta!
Our feelings are tougher than you!
All right!
I'll free you now!
He's still got all this power left?
You're the ones who are going to die, humans!
Give it up already, damn it!
We told you! We're not
letting go, no matter what!
Don't...
Don't touch me!
Luck, you're my precious little brother!
Hurry up and come back so you can tease Magna
and eat other people's puddings without asking!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 105: "Smiles, Tears."
Page 105
Smiles, Tears
I won't let anything sever the
bond that the Black Bulls have!