It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The first stage of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam continues to heat up!
Asta and the others from B Team...
Magna and the others from C Team...
Finral and the others from E Team...
Langris and the others from G Team...
All these teams were victorious
and made it into stage two.
In the end, you'll never be more than
a means of transportation, Brother.
In our upcoming match, be careful not to
get in the way of my spatial magic, okay?
I can't guarantee that you
won't lose something.
If that were to happen,
Mother and Father aside,
I'm sure she'd be sad.
You're right.
So to ensure that doesn't happen,
I'm going to win!
Mage X
Aw, man... I finally said it.
I'm going to win!
How insolent of you, Brother.
I wasn't trying to make him angry, but...
We will now begin round five!
Finally!
Hurry it up already.
I Team and J Team, come forth.
Hello.
I hope you take it easy on us.
Likewise.
Pleasure.
We're going to do our best.
Roland, Wainsley, Nix...
Nils, Ruben...
And "Times"? What a strange name.
I believe it's just "X," Asta.
X?!
What a strange name.
I wonder if they entered anonymously.
Um, pardon me...
Yes?
Who's this "X" that's on our team?
We can't seem to find them anywhere.
Huh?
Hurry it up. If you can't find your other
member soon, I'm going to disqualify you.
Um... X! X!
If you're here, please come over immediately!
X!
Wh-Who the hell's that guy?!
I'm X!
The Captain of the Aqua Deer
Rill Boismortier
Hello! It's me, Rill Boismortier!
Are you all surprised?
The Captain of the Aqua Deer, Rill?!
Why, though?
The guy who uses paint
and picture magic?
Why's a captain participating?
You can't be serious!
Huh? Wait... Were captains
not supposed to enter?!
Not true! We're glad to have you!
Yes! I get to see Rill's cool magic again.
Hurry up and start, if you're all here.
There's no need to be afraid, everyone.
This is your chance to defeat a captain
and make a name for yourselves.
True!
With the rules of this game,
we actually have a fighting chance!
The Aqua Deer were dead
last in the previous term,
so I'm here to rebuild our reputation!
I'm not going to be taken down so easily.
What enthusiasm!
I am deeply moved, Young Master Rill!
A super-fast old guy just
popped outta nowhere!
The Butler of the Boismortier Family
Walter
Ladies and gentlemen, I ask that you
take good care of Master Rill today.
You're always so dramatic.
Oh, hey, Asta!
I look forward to today!
Yeah! Let's both do our best!
B-But he's a captain!
Are you two friends?
This old guy's scary!
You must be Master Rill's
trustworthy friend, Master Asta.
I've heard all about you.
Where'd that come from?!
That was super smooth!
Thank you for being good
friends with Master Rill.
I am Walter, Master Rill's butler.
Please, do have some tea.
Th-Thank you very much.
Th-This is...
Asta?
It's so classy that I can't
even understand the taste!
Moron.
Just imagine...
Master Rill having a friend.
This would've been unfathomable before.
Really? I guess I'm not that surprised.
I do apologize. I've been moved to tears.
Oh, come on, Walter!
Stop bringing up the past! It's embarrassing.
Oh, I do beg your pardon.
We're going to begin, finally!
All right! I'm going to paint
the best picture ever!
What the heck does he mean by that?
Round five of stage one!
I Team: Rill, Nils, and Ruben
versus J Team: Wainsley, Roland, and Nix.
Roland
Nix
Wainsley
J Team
Nils   Rill   Ruben
I Team
The Captain of the Aqua Deer...
I wonder how powerful he is.
Young master...
Begin!
U-Um... Captain Rill...
The match has started.
Isn't the sky beautiful?
Huh?
I wonder if I could get that
color if I used lapis lazuli.
Did you know? You can grind up
precious stone and create blue paint.
Right...
For the white clouds, I'll use whitewash.
Oh, whitewash is paint made from seashells.
Fighting under such a beautiful sky
is the absolute best.
All right, let's do this, you two!
Let's create a beautiful piece
on this canvas known as the battlefield.
Stay close!
Here we go!
C-Captain Rill...
He dashed off on his own, but...
I got captured!
Hey... What the heck are you doing, Rill?
He's a captain... right?
Someone save me!
He basically jumped right
into the enemy's trap.
Well, this looks like it's
going to be over immediately.
He easily fell for that trap spell.
Is it really okay for us to defeat him?
Isn't he the captain of the Aqua Deer?
No, a match is a match.
We're going to give it our all and fight,
no matter who the enemy might be!
Yes.
You're right.
Here we go!
Plant Reinforcement Magic: Magic Pollen!
Go!
Flame Magic:
Flame Spike!
Ice Magic: Icicle Bridge!
We're going to take down the
Captain of the Aqua Deer!
Oh... What decisive and beautiful magic.
The battlefield...
This canvas really is great.
I feel the urge to create, Walter!
4 Years Ago
It's happened again.
I wonder how many times
it's been just today.
Ever since the young master from the House
of Boismortier received his grimoire,
he's shut himself up in his room
and let his magic go berserk.
He's always been a bit strange, but now,
it's as though he's possessed.
On top of that, he has a tremendous amount
of magic, so no one's been able to stop him.
The master is quite troubled.
How did he end up like this?
Madam, please stay strong.
He won't listen to a word I say.
He just keeps drawing and painting.
That boy...
That boy is beyond human understanding.
He's a monster!
No...
It's all wrong, wrong,
wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
This isn't it.
This isn't the picture that I want to draw.
It has to be more... more...
Please don't draw anymore, Rill!
Why do you keep doing this?
I should've... I should've...
never given birth to you!
You don't understand a thing about my art.
You don't understand at all!
Young master, may I have
a moment of your time?
Shut up, Walter! Go away!
Young master...
Stay back!
I can't draw or paint the way
that I want. It's not fun!
It's boring!
I told you to stay back!
None of you understand my pain.
Not you, not Mother... No one!
None of you understand m—
You finally see me, Young Master Rill.
Walter...
Does your cheek hurt?
Huh?
When people are wounded, they feel pain.
That's why they're scared of getting hurt.
They're afraid of what they don't understand.
They don't want to go near it.
If you wish to be understood,
then please try to understand others.
You went through a lot of
trouble over these pictures.
You want others to see them, don't you?
That said, your talent is too great for
such a small canvas, Young Master Rill.
It's far too great.
It will be difficult for the people
around you to understand it.
But that's what having such
prodigious talent is like.
There is a canvas on which you can display
your magic to its fullest potential.
Huh? What's that?
The Magic Knights.
The Magic Knights?
Yes. Why not try to join?
With your talent, I'm sure
you'll get in immediately.
And there, you can draw
upon an endless canvas!
You'll be able to draw
the ultimate masterpiece.
The ultimate masterpiece?
Yes.
Okay, I will. I'll join the Magic Knights.
I'm sorry, Walter. Are you okay?
Oh, 'tis nothing but a scratch.
Are you sure you don't want to say goodbye?
Yup. I don't feel lonely.
She's always smiling
within my heart's canvas.
Indeed.
Okay, let's go to the royal capital!
To the Magic Knights Entrance Exam!
I'm sorry, Rill.
Have a safe journey.
You let your talent blossom
after joining the Magic Knights
and became the youngest captain in history.
You are the pride of the
House of Boismortier.
Yeah... This canvas is the best.
I want to show Walter
the ultimate picture first.
After all, Walter is the
one who made me human.
The young master's picture magic...
Its ability...
Picture Magic: Twin Storms of Fire and Water!
...is to recreate every magical attribute!
He attacked them with the attributes
they're weakest against at the same time!
The stronger the opponent,
the greater his urge to create!
The young master's
imagination knows no bounds!
Excellent work, young master!
What?
You guys were pretty good.
But I haven't quite managed
the ultimate painting yet.
Hup! Thanks.
Oh, it was nothing.
You're amazing, Captain Rill.
That was an intense attack.
Sandstone Magic: Rock Storm!
The crystal has been destroyed.
I Team wins!
Well done, well done.
I guess that was all right.
We somehow managed to make
it through the first stage.
Yeah... But what's he doing?
I could've gone a little crazier over there.
But the cobalt blue really stands out here.
I've still got a ways to go.
Um... Could you concentrate on the match?
We're going to have to keep it together.
He's rather irresponsible despite
being a Grand Magic Knight,
so he has those around him work hard.
That's the young master's true talent!
What the hell is that?!
Next, we will begin round six of stage one.
K Team and L Team, step forward.
It's our turn.
Let's go, Captain Rill.
We have to get on with the
next match, so please move!
Of course. We're terribly sorry.
We'll move him right away.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Let go! I need to look at it longer!
Come on!
Are you done? Are you done now?
Yeah! You're up next, Luck!
I'll be cheering you on.
Don't you dare lose.
Yup, thanks!
It's finally our turn! I can't wait!
Luck Voltia...
This is a match that will decide
who will be among the Royal Knights.
You need to take this more seriously.
I am the leader. Make sure you
don't go running off on your own.
Aw, don't be so serious. Let's have some fun!
Oh, shut up!
So these are my teammates.
A crazy boy and a quiet,
straitlaced four-eyes.
This can't be good!
Honestly... Is this team going to be okay?
Welp, there's no point in worrying about it!
Let's give it our all!
What?
Who the heck are you?
I'm your teammate.
The Blue Rose Knights 4th Class Senior Magic Knight
Puli Angel
I'm Puli. Puli Angel.
As my name and appearance suggest,
I'm an angel!
Oh, I see. Nice to meet you.
Let's hit 'em with our best performances!
Yeah!
Wh-What's with this chipper person?
This is just...
I have to remain the responsible one.
You've got this, Klaus!
Please do your best. I know
you can do it if you try.
I won't consider you my senior if you lose.
I see that you're as insolent as ever.
Just sit back and watch my battle.
Hey, let's come up with a plan.
Indeed.
The one we have to watch out
for the most in this match
is their wind magic user, who's said to
be the most mobile member of his squad.
A 2nd Class Senior Magic Knight from
the Silver Eagles, Rob Vitesse.
And now, for the sixth round of stage one!
K Team: Puli, Klaus, and Luck
versus L Team: Rob, Francis, and Winston.
Rob
Francis
Winston
L Team
Puli
Klaus
Luck
K Team
And... begin!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Wrong!
No...
It's all wrong, wrong,
wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
This isn't it.
This isn't the picture that I want to draw.
It has to be more... more...
I want to draw something more beautiful.
You have a problem with me?
Something beautiful...
He's beautiful—wait...
I want you to disappear so badly.
Honestly, you can't be serious.
I am the butler of the Captain of
the Aqua Deer, Rill Boismortier.
You've grown so much, young master.
Black Clover, Page 77: "Bad Blood."
Page 77
Bad Blood
I'm sure your mother is elated, too!