It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Go! Go! First Mission
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know, yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go, though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide, I never give up
To faraway future, I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had, so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
Mornings start early for Magic Knights.
There are many things they must do.
Cleaning.
Laundry.
But my heart belongs to Sister Lily.
Next!
The Beasts' Room
Taking care of the beasts.
Sit!
There, there. Good boy.
Here.
You must endure, even if you're
almost eaten by a beast. And...
In Front of the Captain's Room
Captain Yami...
Captain...
You must wake up the captain of
the Black Bulls, Yami Sukehiro.
Captain! It's morning!
Don't wake me up! I'll kill you!
Sorry about that!
Even though you're the one who told me
to wake you up every morning!
Magic Knights must also deal with
unreasonable demands.
Man, I've been working hard
since the crack of dawn again.
Magic Knights sure have a lot of work to do.
Wait, how is this any different from
what I was doing at the church?!
What are Magic Knights
supposed to do anyway?!
Cafeteria
There's nothing but meat for breakfast.
Noelle, why don't you help me
with the cleaning and stuff?
Cleaning? But I'm royalty.
But you're a newbie just like me!
I've never cleaned or
done laundry in my life.
That's not something to brag about, is it?
We're in the same squad, aren't we?
I'm pretty sure you should
be helping with that stuff.
But I'm royalty.
Why are you talking to me like that?
Shut up, you insect.
Damn it!
So, uh...
What do Magic Knights do anyway?
What? Are you seriously asking that?
We protect the kingdom and handle security!
It's the most manly job
in the world, you dumbass!
Why'd you decide to join
when you knew nothing about it?
I'm sorry!
I'm going to become the Wizard King.
I'm going to barf everything back up!
They sure are lively first
thing in the morning.
Being energetic is the best.
Can I have some of that energy?
Munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy...
Damn it. Show 'em what Magic Knights do,
you drunk witch.
Well...
We keep the citizens safe? Something like that.
You might even be able to get closer to some
noble when you're assigned to protect them.
I see!
It's a super-fun job where you get
to fight with enemies all you want.
If they're criminals, you can beat them up
all you want and not get in trouble!
Most importantly, it's a wonderful job
that my sister respects me for having.
Isn't she an angel? I can buy her
whatever she wants with my pay.
But if you lay a finger
on Marie, I'll kill you.
Wh-What about you, Finral?
It's the best job in the world,
since I get to save girls and be popular.
Of course I'll tell you.
We're friends, after all.
Charmy?
I'm... out of food!
I'm nowhere near full.
Cotton Creation Magic: Sheep Cooks!
Thank you for the food!
As long as you're a Magic Knight,
you can eat plenty of food!
Munchy...
Uh, Grey?
Huh?!
Well, basically, it's a good job.
He looks just like you.
I'm looking forward to working
with you on a mission.
R-Right...
Th-They're all weirdos.
Should I really be in this squad?
If you take this and this, and put them
together and do this, it's really yummy.
Try a bite? 'Kay?
No, I'm full, thanks.
Well? Do you understand
what Magic Knights do now?
Not at all!
Let's go, Magna.
Yes, sir, Mister Yami!
What's going on? What's going on?
There's a mission.
A Magic Knights' mission?
C-Can I come with—
No!
We can't bring any kids along.
This is a very important mission for adults.
All right. We're off.
Hey! Don't break everything while we're gone.
Okay! Have fun!
Captain! Will you fight me
when you come back?
Come back soon. I'll be waiting.
Come back by dinner! Munchy...
Can I go see Marie soon?
I'm having withdrawal symptoms.
Maybe I'll go flirt...
I mean, go on a mission, too.
Should I really be in this squad?
Captain Yami and Magna
both looked so serious.
What kind of mission could it be?
This is bad...
This is really bad!
And now you're both...
finished!
Flush!
Two pair.
I've got nothing!
You got me!
This feels great!
Damn it! That's six months worth of pay.
You've still got a ways to go,
Magna. You, too, Captain!
Good! Very good!
Now I can buy some great gifts for
everyone in the village on my way home.
Let's go another round.
Mister Yami?
Oh? But you don't have
anything else to bet, do you?
You don't have any clothes or cash.
Yeah! We're basically naked!
No, there's still more.
Hey, gramps.
Let's do one last round.
If we win, we get everything back.
Oh, and if you lose?
This!
M-Mister Yami! That's...
So let's do another round!
Er, you probably shouldn't be betting that.
Yeah, Mister Yami!
Shut up!
Use this moment to go beyond your limits!
But you know...
All right. If you lose,
how about you do anything I ask?
Anything?
Anything? Of course Mister Yami
would never accept...
I accept.
Mister Yami accepted! I'm in!
Old Man Seihi, say your prayers!
I wonder who'll be saying their prayers...
This could work!
Shoot!
There, there. Good boy.
Here.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey! Don't just stand there! Help me!
I'm royalty.
You should be thankful that
I even got out of bed.
How?! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I thought I was going to die.
You really are freakishly strong.
Well, I train!
Captain Yami and Magna...
I wonder if they finished their... mission?!
What?
That old man actually had
a royal straight flush!
Who would've thought? He's amazing!
We're no match for Old Man Seihi!
People sure are strong when they
have something on the line.
Hey, Stupidsta, Lady Noe, we're back!
Be happy! You two are going on
your first mission
as Magic Knights.
Huh?
And so, we're giving you your first mission.
Our first mission...
...as Magic Knights.
Wh-What is it?
It had better be something
worthy of me as a royal.
Yeah, you should be honored.
You'll be hunting wild boars
in Saussy Village!
Wild...
...boars?
Boar!
Wh-What in the world is this lame mission?
What are you calling lame?!
I can beat a wild boar with my bare hands!
Don't you dare underestimate wild boars!
They come charging outta nowhere!
Haven't you ever heard
the phrase "rushing into things"?!
We both ended up losing to
the mayor of Saussy Village.
Huh?
C-Captain Yami and Magna lost?
Just how strong is he?
It was cards.
Cards?!
He basically stripped us of all we had.
And six months worth of pay, too!
Why...
...are you bragging?
And we ended up promising him
we'd do anything if we lost,
so he asked us to take care
of some wild boars for him.
Apparently, a herd showed up near
the village, and they're ruining the fields.
Well, I'll be waiting at my village.
Oh, I'll at least return these to you.
Hi, question! That has nothing
to do with us, right?
Yeah! You two are the ones who lost! Then...
You idiots! You're asking Mister Yami
to clean up his own mistakes?!
Normally...
...you would.
We're the ones who clean up
Mister Yami's mistakes!
Are you going to go, or are you going to die?
Which will it be?
We'll go!
Even though we're hunting wild boars,
this is our first mission as Magic Knights.
I'm so excited!
I'm supposed to get rid of wild boars?
What? You're still complaining?
I'm not complaining, but...
I was just wondering if I should go,
since I can't control my magical powers.
You idiot!
What...
You'll be able to fix that in no time
with some missions under your belt!
And...
I'll be sure to clean up any of you
newbies' mistakes, since I'm your senior.
Magna, you're such a manly man!
Stop it, Stupidsta. You're making me blush.
I-If you insist, I guess
I could accompany you.
Thank you very much!
Wait. Why are you always looking down on us?!
I'm not. It's just that
you're always below me.
What kind of reasoning is that?!
So...
Use your spatial magic to
get us to Saussy Village.
Saussy Village?
Not happening.
What do you mean, you jerk?!
Well, I can only go to
faraway places I can't see
if I've marked them
with my magical powers.
Huh?!
Meaning I can't go to places
I've never been to before.
You're so useless!
Guess we don't have a choice.
We'll go by broomstick.
Magna, sir!
Yeah, Asta?
I can't fly on a broomstick!
Sir.
Yes, Noelle?
I can't, either.
What?! Are you two serious?!
Why can't you do something
so easy, you morons?!
Damn it! That's as basic as it gets!
Well, I don't have any magical powers!
Why are you bragging about that?!
Well, I can't control my magical powers,
so of course I can't. You fool.
And why do you sound so high and mighty?!
Guess I don't have a choice.
I'll give you two a ride on my baby.
Baby?
Her name's...
Crazy Cyclone!
Crazy Cyclone
S-So cool!
I know, right?! Isn't she a beaut?
Yeah, she is!
Lame.
What?! Are you not able to
comprehend her majestic form?
So lame!
Let's go!
Are you going to be all right?
A man never goes back on his word!
Here we go!
Fly!
How do you like that?
Crazy Cyclone can even handle three riders!
Hey! Fly a bit more steady!
H-H-Hey! Don't get so close to me!
You can't be serious,
you mohawked delinquent!
Who are you calling a mohawked delinquent?!
Yahoo!
This is amazing, Magna!
We're one with the wind!
And if you don't want to die,
get a little closer, Stupidsta!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Where are you touching me?!
What the hell are you two doing?!
Saussy Village
Right on schedule.
So this is where the magic stone is located.
We're going to find it.
Yes, sir!
Be lost in the mist.
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh, go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Regards!
Well? Isn't Crazy Cyclone super cool?
Actually, I'd probably call your head
a crazy cyclone before I would your broom.
Who are you calling a cyclone?!
Apparently, you're okay with "crazy."
We came here to hunt wild boars,
but end up encountering a crazy enemy.
I'm not going to forgive you for
causing everyone so much trouble!
Black Clover, Page 9: "Beasts."
Page 9
Beasts
Not giving up is my magic!