The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently
aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
Clues
Huh? My home?
Jeez, you're scary.
The Prickly Queen mentioned it,
but come to think of it,
your family's famous for
curse magic, isn't it?
Could you go ask them about forbidden magic?
Forbidden magic?
Yeah.
Forbidden magic uses power
from another world to meddle with the
ways of this world or people's lives.
And that other world is where the devils live.
I was hoping we'd be able
to get some information.
If our investigation about the
devils doesn't get any further,
my best friend Asta...
I was going to try to go again,
even though I think I'll fail.
For Asta's sake!
A distinguished family of curse mages...
Since cursing people was my family's trade,
I never made any friends.
On top of that, my family...
Even when Asta's arms were cursed
by a member of the Third Eye...
I asked them how we could
break the spell with a letter,
but they wouldn't tell me.
But things are different now.
Today, I have my friends with me,
so I feel more confident.
My arms are falling asleep!
But I'm not done yet! My muscles are
screaming in joy, not in agony!
Shut up! The only one who gets
to ride behind me is Marie!
Just shut up and hang on!
It's so embarrassing to meet
someone I don't know!
My friends give me strength.
Guys! Thanks for doing this for me!
Tch. Why the hell do I have to do this?
Looks like Noelle took off
to the royal capital,
and since you all look so sleepy,
you guys can head out, too.
You guys are pals, aren't ya?
I'm definitely not going,
and I'll kill you if you refuse.
Curse our captain for abusing his power.
So I heard your family's, like,
really special somehow
when it comes to curse mages, Gordon.
What the heck are curse mages, anyway?
They... are mages that made a trade out of
cursing and bringing misfortune upon others.
But I didn't want any part of that.
I wanted to be friends with
people, not to curse them.
That's why I pretty much ran away from home.
I see.
You ran away?
Will you be able to get any
information from them, then?
Also, they're not gonna curse us, are they?
Being cursed by someone I
don't know is so embarrassing!
The being cursed part doesn't bother you?!
It'll be okay... I think.
You think?
I wanna go home...
Let's go.
This is basically a haunted house.
It's so embarrassing to meet
a ghost I don't know!
Get off of me! Damn it, Grey!
I wonder what Gordon's family is like.
It's me. I'm home.
Welcome home, Gordon.
Big Brother...
So you decided to come home after all.
They all have the same face!
Let me introduce you.
Father
Nathan
First, this is my dad, Nathan.
Mother
Jonna
This is my mom, Jonna.
Grandmother
Nilenia
My grandmother, Nilenia.
Little Sister
Roxanne
My little sister, Roxanne.
And...
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
This is our dog, Nunnally.
Even their dog looks like them...
What are you doing to our guest?!
Nunnally, stop!
Whoa! Don't all of you come over here at once!
Are you all right, Asta?
Yeah...
Oh, sorry for the late introduction. I'm Asta.
And this is Gauche and Grey.
They're my friends from the Black Bulls
that I mentioned in my letter.
I see. Well, now that you're all here...
Why don't you join us for dinner?
Weren't you two strangers
before you got married?
Why do you look so much alike?!
Gordon, you haven't had your
mother's cooking for a while.
It must taste exquisite.
The eyeballs of the creepy-crawly
snake are superb.
I recommend the raw paralyzing frog, myself.
Bread... Where's the bread?
Grandma, it's in your hands.
Oh, my. And it was on the
plate just a moment ago...
Where did the bread go?
It's in your mouth.
Dad, I want to talk to you about something.
I see. You must want seconds.
No, Dad...
Th-They're muttering over here
and muttering over there...
I have no idea what any of them are saying.
This is so awkward. What the hell is this?
And it's not easy to make me feel awkward.
Say something, damn it.
Aren't we supposed to ask
about forbidden magic?
I-I can't...
Gordon, please stop shaking and ask!
Hey, that's the grandma!
Wow, this stuff looks really gross,
but it's super yummy!
It's so good!
Why the hell are you having
fun all by yourself?
H-Huh?
I think we can become the best of friends.
Y-You want to give me something?
What is this?!
Is that you, Nathan? You've grown so big...
You have to protect the House of Agrippa.
Old lady, seriously...
Oh, dear, Mother...
Perhaps it's time for your nap.
I'm counting on Nathan.
For the sake of our ancestor who made
the contract... the curse of Megicula...
Yes, Mother.
Megi...?
Thank you for the meal.
I-It suddenly got really quiet...
All right!
Gordon! It's the perfect opportunity to ask!
Dad, I need to talk to you about something.
I basically abandoned the family,
so I probably have no right to ask...
But I have a friend that I want
to save, no matter what.
So could you tell me about
forbidden magic curses and devils,
for the sake of that friend?
Sure.
That was easy.
I'll show you hex research
worthy of a family
with centuries of expertise
as curse mages,
as well as secret arts that deal
with poison, plague, and death.
Are you ready?
What the hell is this?
Beautiful, isn't it?
This is my curse research workshop.
I'm researching every kind of pain there is.
Dad... So you really were
researching such evil things.
Gordon... I've been earnestly
waiting for your return.
Your poison magic is a talent that makes
you worthy of inheriting my research.
I only came here to ask about
devil-related curses for Asta.
I'm not coming home to stay!
Oh, don't be like that.
Death by curses, poisons, drugs...
If you want to learn those secrets,
I'll teach you all of them.
What do you think a person's life is?
Humans die so quickly.
That includes your friends.
Life is so fleeting.
Black Oil Creation Magic:
Curse-Filled Nails.
Guys!
Asta!
Wait, I'm fine?
Hm... 36.5 degrees.
Your temperature is normal.
I don't see any physical abnormalities,
though you really don't have magic.
Dad, what are you...
Well? I rechanneled what I know about
poisons that usually harm people,
as well as our family's hereditary
expertise in curse killing,
into health management and medical treatment.
That being said, this endeavor
just started with my generation,
so I'm only able to cure normal diseases.
I wasn't able to help when
your arms were afflicted
with an ancient curse, but...
What's the matter?
So, uh... You rechanneled your
knowledge about killing with curses
toward health management
and medical treatment...
So, wait, does that make you a recovery mage?
Yes, starting with my generation, at least.
I had no idea...
I totally thought you were
cursing people to death.
You people need to learn how to communicate!
You're going to give people the
wrong idea with those things!
You really can't judge a book by its cover!
Dad, does that mean you're
going to help us out?
But of course.
What did you want to know about
devils and forbidden magic?
Let's hear the details first.
Yes, sir!
Okay. Now I've sent most of the
large debris into my dreams.
In mere moments!
That's the Captain of the
Coral Peacocks for you!
Thank you so much, Lady Dorothy.
I'm glad you're still awake.
Well, well...
If it isn't the littlest sister
of the House of Silva.
Did you need something?
I want to know the truth
behind my mother's death.
Did you hear something from Nozel?
Yes. When we went to see
Solid and Nebra yesterday...
Wh-What did you just say, Nozel?
What do you mean, Mother didn't
die because she gave birth to me?
When she was pregnant with you,
Mother was already haunted by a
death that she could not escape.
It was not an injury or an illness.
It was a death that should
not happen in this world.
A death that should not happen in this world?
But that sounds like the work of
the devils we're currently investi—
Say any more, and your life
will be in danger, too.
If you still have the courage
to face the truth knowing that,
then go speak with Captain Dorothy Unsworth
of the Coral Peacocks.
Tell me. Why did my mother have to die?
Sure thing! I could never
say no to a cute girl!
She's so easy.
Well, I'm leaving the rest to you guys, then.
Yes, Captain Dorothy!
Then again, it's not like
we have anything to do.
Captain Dorothy's amazing
when she's actually awake!
Um... Did my mother's death involve a devil?
Shh...
Didn't Nozel tell you?
You shouldn't speak of that.
You'll get cursed.
At least, in this world.
Huh?
Where am I?
Welcome!
To Dream Magic: Glamour World!
This is a world of dreams.
A world separated from the outside world.
Everything here is under my control.
Here, have some tea.
Usually, I trap bad people
in here and punish them,
or I transport buildings or
injured people in here, like today.
What in the world is this large-scale spell?
So this is Glamour World?
Everything's under her control?
But that's crazy.
This tea is good.
Noelle!
Heya.
Asta! What are you doing here?
More importantly... Hup!
You sure are cute today, Noelle.
Wait, wha—
I just want to keep staring
at how cute you are!
W-Wait, no! Th-This isn't...
That's the boy I created from your thoughts.
Yup! You think about me all the time!
What?! I absolutely do not!
Oh, no!
Oh, dearie me. You did also come
here for his sake, didn't you?
Not at all! Not even a little!
But just so you know, this is the perfect
place to have secret conversations.
Secret? You mean...
It's the perfect place to talk about Mother.
Now it's Nozel?
Though this is a Nozel that I thought up.
You came to visit me after
talking to the real him, right?
About the thing he hasn't
told any of his siblings.
Your mother, Acier Silva, lost her
life due to a devil's curse.
My mother... But why didn't Nozel tell anyone?
Because those who speak of
it will share the same fate.
That's the nature of the curse
that befell your mother.
That's why he didn't tell
you or your siblings,
and why I told him to come to me in
this world, because he can only talk
about this curse in a world that's
separated from the outside world.
I'm sorry it took me so long
to tell you this, Noelle.
I didn't want to put you in danger.
Ah, Noelle...
Nozel?
Ah, Noelle!
Noelle!
My precious little Noelle!
I love you so, so much that I just
don't know what to do with myself!
Noelle, Noelle, Noe—
Nozel!
Hey! Quit messing around with Nozel!
Aw, but that's how Nozel always seems to me!
What in the world was that chill just now?
Well, now that Nozel's gone
flying away, let's get back on topic.
The devils that live in the other world
don't appear in our world unless
there's been some kind of anomaly.
Mages can use forbidden magic,
contract them by paying a price
of some sort, and use their power
in a limited way, but that's it.
Or that was supposed to be the case,
but now, their shadow is
wriggling around in our world.
The devil's name is Megicula.
Megicula... That's the
devil who killed my mother!
And the key to saving Asta!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
After hearing what you said yesterday,
I looked into what our ancestors had
to say about magic that collects curses.
Investigating curses... Our magic
is basically made for that.
Black Oil Creation Magic:
Curse Candle Ritual Disk.
Is this...
The Clover Kingdom?
Holy crap!
The flames are curses.
Flame intensity shows depth and viciousness.
This is a map of the sickness
eroding our kingdom.
That flame is insanely fierce! Huh?
That's our hideout!
Wait... Then there's someone
in the Black Bulls who's cursed?
The only one in our squad
who's not normal is...
L-Let's see... All Luck ever
thinks about is fighting,
Finral's always thinking about girls...
And all Vanessa ever does is drink.
Captain Yami always takes an extremely
long time in the bathroom.
So basically...
None of them are normal.
Wait, wait, wait! What kind of curse
makes you stay in the bathroom forever?
And if we're gonna get into it, everyone
here is pretty undoubtedly unique, too!
What?
B-Being called unique is too embarrassing!
Huh? Bone!
But I'm completely normal.
At any rate,
you're the last one I want to hear
that from, you zero-magic meathead!
Oh, speaking of magic,
maybe this is reacting to Henry.
Oh, yeah. I guess his condition that
sucks away everyone else's mana
could definitely be a curse.
Yeah, he's cursed.
Indeed, he is.
There's a huge flame in
the royal capital, as well.
I can't tell who exactly is cursed,
but if you include the smaller
flames, that's quite a few.
Can't we get a look at a bigger area?
If we go too far out, the accuracy falls.
That's...
The Heart Kingdom...
And there's a very big flame coming from there.
Maybe there's a clue about the devil there!
You're my dad, Nathan.
We found some clues
on devils because of you.
Thanks, Dad-Who's-Also-Nathan!
My best friends are really happy, too!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 128: "To the Heart Kingdom!"
Page 128
To the Heart Kingdom!
Wait, I'm staying home?