It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The list of Magic Knights who
made it into the Royal Knights
was announced at last.
Zora, one of those who passed, arrived late.
Shiren Tium, Cob Portaport, and the
Captain of the Silver Eagles, Nozel Silva,
were also added later on as support,
making for a total of 20 Royal Knights.
We have no use for anything
other than victory!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is
a terrorist organization that
threatens the Clover Kingdom!
If we don't take care of them ourselves,
there will never be peace in our land!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout
is located in...
a floating dungeon within the strong
magic region known as Gravito Stones!
Storming the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's Hideout!!!
The Crimson Lion Kings' Headquarters
I thank you for coming, my rival!
Infirmary
I heard from my sister that you two
passed the Royal Knights Exam.
Yeah! We're finally gonna take
down the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
We're leaving in three days.
We're standing by in the royal capital
until then so information won't be leaked.
I see.
Um...
Hm?
How's Fuegoleon doing?
He's still asleep.
We still don't know what happened
to him when he was captured
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun during
their attack on the royal capital.
Whatever they did,
I'm sure it was underhanded.
Yet even then, my brother would just say...
"The reason I was unable to defeat
them was my own weakness."
I will train even harder,
catch up to all of you,
and surpass you!
Leopold...
I will get revenge for Captain Fuegoleon,
no matter what!
Captain Fuegoleon didn't laugh at
my dream to become the Wizard King.
He even called me a rival.
The reason I'm here right now
is because of Captain Fuegoleon.
Me, too.
Being weak is nothing to be ashamed of.
However, staying weak is!
Those words helped me grow stronger.
Asta, Noelle, I'm counting on you.
Yeah! For the sake of returning
peace to this country...
...we'll defeat the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
Next time, let's fight together, Leo!
Of course! Be careful.
Yeah!
We'll come by again.
I hope Captain Fuegoleon
and Finral both wake up soon.
Not to mention...
The eerie feeling I got from that mana...
The Eye of the Midnight
Sun might be behind that.
We have to defeat them.
Yeah...
But something's been bugging me.
Huh?
You remember what that hairy gorilla said?
For some reason, they can't forgive us, either.
We're fighting each other because
we can't forgive each other.
And I mean, if we could forgive each
other, we wouldn't have to fight...
So that means...
Even I have no idea what I'm trying to say!
That's what you get for thinking
so hard when you're so stupid.
Don't call me stupid!
Then again, Captain Yami
told me the same thing!
All right! At times like this,
I need to work out!
First, my abs!
Next, my back muscles!
You meathead.
Everything's cramping at once!
You can't be serious.
Yuno! Mimosa and Mr. Glasses, too!
Did you come to visit Fuegoleon, too?
No, we're here for another reason.
The Golden Dawn had the most members pass
the Royal Knights Entrance Exam, after all.
Asta! Are you all right?!
No need to worry about me!
I've trained every single muscle in my body!
We've been having fiery meetings with
Captain Mereoleona these past few days
The only thing you haven't
trained is your brain.
so we don't let anyone down.
Yup, exactly! It's super weak!
Hey, don't make fun of me!
If there's a spell to make someone smarter,
could someone use it on Asta?
Oh, you're so nice, Yuno!
Don't make weird requests like that!
I'm terribly sorry. I can't think of any.
I'm actually kinda disappointed!
Honestly...
We have a big battle ahead of us,
and you show no sense of urgency.
What if an enemy spy finds out our plan?
A spy?
It's entirely plausible.
They were able to bribe the
Captain of the Purple Orcas
to help them out with their
attack on the royal capital.
You can never be too cautious.
True.
We've gotta be careful.
If you two are also heading to the
royal capital, would you like a ride?
On my vessel.
Wow, really? Awesome! Thanks!
Well, if you insist...
Royal Capital
Lodging House
So good!
So good! So good!
The food in the royal capital
is on another level!
Oh, dear.
Asta, you have some sauce on your mouth.
Forgive me! I'm being too forward!
Thanks, Mimosa!
You're eating entirely too much.
I thought you were going to be more cautious.
Y-Yeah! Look at you,
getting your mouth wiped like a baby.
N-Not that I care the slightest bit!
But I am on my guard.
Normally, I'd eat at least twice this much!
You can't be serious.
I'm worried.
It's not just Asta.
They may be talented, but there are
a lot of troublemakers among them.
I can't wait to fight some people!
I'm gonna beat them to
a pulp and squash them.
Zora is all by himself!
He must be too shy to talk to the others.
I need to be the one to break the ice!
Take a look at this!
This is what your face looks like!
It stinks so bad!
C-Captain Rill?!
All of you lack manners.
Meals are meant to be enjoyed
in a much more elegant,
beautiful, and distinguished fashion.
You dare run away from me because
you don't want to be eaten?
What a repulsive mushroom.
Hey! Wait!
You... repulsive... mushroom!
Don't eat my brethren!
Everyone, it appears that Miss Puli
wants to give us the gift of song.
Puli, Puli, Puli, my skin's so pretty!
I'm a lovely lady who sings so sweetly!
What the hell is this song?!
Puli, Puli, Puli, I'm a lovely lady
How bad a singer can one be?
As rude as this sounds,
I want to murder someone.
with supple cheeks!
Shut up!
Puli poo pariponpen!
I can't get any useful information
while I'm sticking to that guy!
Pushka, pushka...
What's the matter,
Captain of the Silver Eagles?
You're taking three days
to start this operation.
You're being awfully cautious.
What are you getting at?
Do you think I'm hesitating?
No. It appears I needn't worry.
You always were perceptive.
I set a trap to find out how much
the enemy knows of our plans.
Well, let's hear it.
Did you really think you could
trick me with such a foolish spell?
Damn it!
You're not getting away.
A spy from the Eye of the Midnight Sun?!
I can't believe there really was one...
Mushroom is shocked!
Second-Place Rookie,
apparently, he was following you.
To think I hadn't noticed...
How disgraceful.
I questioned him without killing him,
but apparently, our enemy hasn't
noticed any of our movements.
Therefore, we will be moving up
the operation's start time.
We strike the Eye of the Midnight
Sun's hideout tomorrow morning.
T-Tomorrow?
Not in three days?
I don't want Yuno to see
me right after I wake up!
Make sure you all get plenty of rest tonight.
That is all.
It appears Lady Mereoleona intended
all along to depart immediately
as soon as she captured the enemy spy.
So if you want to fool your enemies,
you must first fool your friends.
But tomorrow morning?
What a scary lady.
What's up, shitty shrimp junior?
You scared?
It's the exact opposite.
The reason I want to become Wizard King
is so that everyone who lives here
can have a free country
where they can always smile.
I'm going to stop their rampage,
no matter what!
You'd better not go on a
rampage and hold us back.
I'm never going to lose to you!
I'm the one who's going to win.
It's finally time.
Yes.
Tomorrow is when we finally settle this.
We're going to...
...defeat the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
Gravito Stones Floating Dungeon
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's Hideout
Holy crap! There's a castle
floating in the sky!
That's the Eye of the
Midnight Sun's hideout.
Well, there aren't many who would
set foot in the strong magic regions.
And since it's hidden by this
magical fog, it's even harder to spot.
Anyone would have difficulty finding it.
You figured all that out, and that's
why you had people search this area.
You've gotten better,
Captain of the Silver Eagles.
I just happened to have
people searching dungeons,
and we coincidentally found
out it was their hideout.
Oh? So what brought the Captain of
the Silver Eagles himself here, then?
That's enough idle chatter.
You can use your spell from
this distance, can't you?
Indeed.
Stone Creation Magic:
Stone Model of the World.
That's so cool!
I see. It's like an ants' nest that
allows entry from anywhere.
Seems simple enough to infiltrate.
I see there are plenty of guys
around Senior Magic Knight level.
There's someone with very
powerful magic in the middle.
Must be their boss.
So that's where Licht is...
Captain Nozel, what is our plan?
I am not the Captain of the Royal Knights.
The one who'll decide that is Mereoleona.
Y-Yes, of course.
Listen up, all of you!
If we want to ambush the enemy and
throw them into a state of chaos,
we can't let them know
how many of us there are,
so splitting up is the best option.
But the fact that there are so many entrances
means that the enemy is
confident in their defense.
The more we split up, the more that
may work against us and overwhelm us.
So where does that lead us?
Ooh, me!
We'll overwhelm the enemy even
more with sheer willpower!
We don't need willpower.
I'll overwhelm them myself.
I wanna mash them all up!
I shall defeat them beautifully on my own.
I wish you'd just disappear.
I'm surrounded by idiots.
What's important is balance.
The most effective way to get through
the enemy's defense while split up
is to divide into five teams of four.
Is that what you're thinking?
Exactly.
We will now split up into
five groups and proceed.
I'll settle for anyone, as long as I don't
end up with the crazy stupid shrimp.
Say what?! That's my line,
you cool masked jerk!
Wait.
No one would want to team up with you anyway,
so I don't mind teaming
up with you after all.
Why do you sound like you're taking
pity on me, you little shit?
You're coming with me,
you damn problem children.
Hello there, Lady Royal.
Please accept this rainbow stinkbug
as a token of our friendship.
You idiot!
A stench this weak has no effect on me.
You sure you want two peasants
hanging around you, Lady Royal?
What?! You're a peasant, too?
I don't care if you're a peasant or royalty.
I've never given a rat's ass
about differences in status.
All that matters is if you're weak or strong.
You're here because you're strong,
are you not?
The fools that Yami selected...
Don't let me down.
Yes, ma'am!
Sure thing. Guess I'll
be careful, Lady Captain.
The rest of you should also be proud
to be chosen as Royal Knights,
and use your strengths to the fullest.
I will now assign your positions.
Group 1
En Ringard   Nils Ragus   Nozel Silva   Shiren Tium
Group 1 will attack from the upper left.
Yes, ma'am!
As you wish.
Group 2
Ben Benfunk   Luck Voltia   Noelle Silva   Kirsch Vermillion
Group 2 will attack from the lower left.
'Kay!
Yes, ma'am.
Group 3
Ruben Shagger   Rill Boismortier   Fragil Tormenta   Puli Angel
Group 3 will attack from the upper right.
Yes, ma'am.
Group 4 will attack from the lower right.
Group 4
Klaus Lunettes   Mimosa Vermillion   Yuno   Hamon Caseus
Yes, ma'am!
Group 5
Asta   Mereoleona Vermillion   Zora Ideale
And we're going to attack front and center.
Yes, ma'am!
The spatial magic user will stand by here.
Roger-dodger-roger!
You'd better put your all into this.
Let's go!
Do you know why you're in this mess?
It's because you're a citizen
of the Clover Kingdom.
I was a citizen there myself,
until not so long ago.
But...
I was different.
Lord Licht gave me my true name.
We're special, you see.
So we can do whatever we
want to trash like you.
He's way too weak.
There are stronger guys, right?
Do leave me some chances
to strike beautifully.
Are you all right?
Thank you so much.
I'm sure you don't need detailed plans.
Take down any enemies you encounter
as you proceed toward the center.
You may do that
however you prefer!
I don't care what you do
as long as you don't lose.
Ah, the ants show themselves at last.
I hear you caused quite a mess at
the royal capital while I was away.
You will not escape like you
did from a certain cave.
Eye of the Midnight Sun, we've come...
...to get our revenge.
How dare you do that to my rival...
To my foolish little brother...
You shall pay dearly!
I will be the one to take your leader's head!
H-Holy crap!
Wait, do we even need to be here?!
Looks like someone dangerous showed up.
Licht is gone right now, too.
Guess I shouldn't be so lazy
about this and just go.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Lazy Raia!
Lord Raia! Lord Raia!
What's up? Why are you so panicked?
We're being attacked!
Sounds like it.
But it's such a pain to deal with them.
What?! Please don't be like that!
It's a pain to get up.
I shall sit you up.
It's a pain to put shoes on.
I shall do that, too!
It's a pain to stand up.
Up you go.
Walking is a huge pain!
Yeah, I'm not gonna do it.
What?!
Please reconsider!
I think I was sleeping with my mouth open,
because my throat hurts...
I'll give you this lollipop!
What flavor is it?
A-Apple...
I guess I shouldn't be so
lazy about this and just go.
What would've happened if
it was an orange lollipop?
Come to think of it, I wonder how
Valtos and the others are doing.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 89:
"The Black Bulls Hideout."
Page 89
The Black Bulls Hideout
Make sure you find what
we're looking for, Val.