Hey!
Who the hell slashed my tires?
What a shitty thing to do.
It'd better not be scratched anywhere.
It's no good.
I can't find any trace of them.
Anyway, who told you that this place was suspicious?
Eh? A fax?
Goddamn it!
Ogami's being attacked.
Hurry up, send in everyone we can!
Who the hell are you?
Why couldn't you make this delivery later?
Deputy, I can't get a hold of the Sagamihara office.
And I haven't had any contact with Taguchi since last night.
Mr. Taguchi has passed away.
What?
The police found the bodies at the Bokutoh lumber yard.
I will be heading to the station tomorrow.
I will try to avoid any charges regarding an
employer's duties under the Anti-Organized Crime Law.
I see now...
Their fighting style isn't that of the Mafia,
but that of an army.
Of course. That's why she's called "Kapitan."
I miscalculated.
We are moving into the final stages of
crushing the Washimine Group's strongholds.
Strongholds 371 and 372 have been destroyed.
Daniel's team is currently moving towards stronghold 221.
They will begin at 1505.
Has Corporal Razal reached his objective?
They ran into some traffic on the highway,
but they should arrive in time.
This is Corporal Jodorovski.
We've completed our objectives within the mission time.
Report.
We will now begin withdrawing from our operation zone.
Roger.
Return to base.
Stronghold 215 is under our control.
It's going smoothly.
We have confirmed the death of Officer Shigeru Ito
at stronghold 317.
All right. Good work, men.
In three more moves
the Princess will be completely stripped.
I got a hold of Sis.
We're done for today.
She says we've got one more job tomorrow.
Yeah.
What is it? You look gloomy.
Can't help it.
You seem like you're having a good time.
We've been partners for so long that
you see right through me, don't you?
Meeting a guy like that makes me one thankful gunman.
Can you believe it, baby?
He cut a bullet right in front of me.
It's amazing as hell.
I can't wait to duke it out with Jumbo.
What's the point in running off to die like that?
"Running off to die," you say?
You've got it all wrong.
We're already the walking dead, Rock.
Dutch and Sis.
Boss Chang and the others.
Every single one of us that's running around in Roanapur.
If there's anything that makes
us different from the real dead...
Different?
Yeah. We're different.
Living and dying isn't the real issue.
If you cling to being alive,
you become frightened and your eyes get clouded.
If you don't have that desire to begin with,
you can fight on, right to the end of the world.
So you prefer to die in the gutter like that?
Roanapur somehow feels so far away.
Hey, Rock! That's not fair.
You sure are snapping back a lot today.
No, sorry.
Today's drinking is bringing out the worst in me.
All right. Don't worry about it.
Missy, you shouldn't tease adults like this.
You were the one who presented the condition that
only a direct blood relation may be the successor.
This is something the Peacekeeping Council has already...
Fuck off, you little brat!
Shut up, Morozumi.
I don't plan on allowing you to succeed.
And how do you plan on taking care
of those crazy Russians you brought in?
As you say, that was our error.
The entire Washimine Group has taken up arms
to throw out these Russians.
You're a cheeky little girl.
I'm asking you how you're going to make up
for everything that's happened so far.
Excuse me, but you cannot have forgotten the reason
why our last boss, Bando, took this desperate measure.
Wasn't that just your misplaced resentment?
We tried sending you a replacement head to
try and protect our brothers organization.
Who turned that down?
Very well. We will settle this in the Peacekeeping Council.
You little brat!
You're in over your head, taking a stance like that!
The Peacekeeping Council
has the authority to direct mediation.
We have enough now to persuade them.
Brat...
Is that all you have to say?
The Kousa boss's attitude...
It may be useless to try to have
the Peacekeeping Council mediate.
That's...
The people here are just as consumed by greed.
It is clear which side it would be more advantageous to take.
Justice has fallen.
It pains me to say it, but the current Washimine Group is
only one-third of the force we had before the fighting began.
The Russians' attacks are too fierce.
They've been taking out those who organize our men first.
But we are still here.
You and I.
Mr. Inoue, please stop.
Yes, Miss.
Miss!
But then-
Yes. Please message everyone who is still alive.
But, Miss!
I cannot allow those who have been protecting Washimine,
to die here.
Mr. Inoue, you too.
We will create our opportunity with our own hands.
So please stay alive until then, and wait.
Now, Miss...
Of course I will not allow it to end here.
Every office nowadays has surveillance cameras,
and they know that.
We have here a video tape that survived,
although it's only a piece of it.
I managed to take it,
before the police collected all the evidence.
Did you see it?
Clearly.
They're moving around with
the electricity company wagons.
If only we knew where these cars were coming from...
I'm jealous of the police's N-systems.
Indeed.
It's so thrilling to be a villain!
We're Bonnie and Clyde!
That's good.
Next up, we're robbing banks in Bolivia!
A robbery has occurred at the credit union
on the 4th block of Inoue.
The two suspects are escaping in a car.
A white van with a red spade mark on the side.
All PCs in the area, be on the lookout-
The world that Mr. Okajima is standing on the border of...
There's a city in this wide world that only gangs gather in.
That seems wonderful.
Becoming a Yakuza, straddling this world in that city...
The city's name is Roanapur.
They say Balalaika's from there as well.
I always quietly wished that
life in Takamachi would go on forever.
Miss...
With the trees, and all the stores up.
That it was fun with you.
But this is...
This is even more fun.
Either way, we need to deal with the Russian woman
for us to live in that town.
This is getting exciting.
This is PC Shinagawa 142.
I've spotted a wagon with a red mark
going up the coast line.
We have ordered them to pull over, but instead
they've taken flight. Requesting reinforcements.
We've got them, Gin.
The coast line...
Around the Tokyo Port...
This is Jodorovski. We are being chased by a police car.
Lose them.
Balalaika.
They came from Roanapur... but how?
All those weapons and that much equipment...
She couldn't have passed through the airport.
Then...
A ship.
Balalaika's at the port.
He lost them.
We will destroy the car.
Why?
How do the police know the cars we're using?
Is this the first effective countermeasure that girl's taken?
Amusing.
We need to crush her completely.
Knowledge exists so that we may forget reality.
The intoxication of reality that cannot be found in text.
A place that embodies that... Roanapur.
Geez.
With Balalaika gone, this place is falling to pieces.
How are things outside?
The number of gunshots has gone up again.
The Triad's doing a pretty good job keeping it together,
but...
A paradise of guns, Benny.
That's what this city is really like.
Everyone's in a good mood.
Chang knows that too.
It's a good thing Rock's not here.
He hates guns.
The fact that Rock's not holding a gun is our biggest joy.
Is that so?
His bullets are the kind that ricochet right back at us.
It's too damned dangerous.
I'm serious.
Geez.
Sorry I made you wait.
Don't worry about it, Sis.
What's the next job?
Another meeting with the Japanese.
If this goes well, we can return to Roanapur.
A meeting?
But the Washimine Group is-
The people we're talking to now are
the Kousa Council.
Now our troubles will be taken care of.
What a deal.
Because you don't actually want to save me.
You don't want to lose the normal life
you thought you'd thrown away. That's all.
Well, as long as what they have to say isn't insulting,
we can consider at least one of their conditions.
Rock?
Are you just going to stand in the twilight again?
Miss Balalaika.
You don't have any reason to ally with the Kousa Council.
You would be better off destroying
the Kousa Council instead of the Washimine Group.
Rock!
The Washimine Group is already weakened.
It's no longer a threat to Moscow.
Am I right?
And the Washimine Group is-
Rock!
Don't misunderstand your position.
You are my translator.
You are not my fellow soldier,
my comrade, or from Moscow.
Do you understand?
The new leader of the Washimine Group is still a child!
Hey, hey! Cut it out!
You must have a sense of justice you believe in!
That's enough, Rock.
You're being a pain!
Damn it.
Let's all calm down, Sis.
We don't want the Saint Valentine's
Day Massacre to happen here, do we?
Don't bark, Revy.
Rock, look at me.
Justice?
There is no other word more loved by the people.
It's a wonderful word.
But,
without exercising your own strength,
you seek the death of others by another's hand.
The justice you're talking about smells pretty rotten too.
I can just smell the stink of blood.
Don't you think so?
Don't make that kind of face.
I'm not angry with you.
Sis!
I never thought I'd hear anything like that from you.
I'm so amused, I can't help myself.
Sis, if you're through, let him down.
My fingers are getting tense.
Our lives are very light,
like a candy wrapper.
Yours and his.
I don't really want to talk.
Let him down, Sis.
Two-Hands, I have something to say to you too.
I don't know what you're thinking,
but you shouldn't seek the same life as his.
Shut up.
I know.
I know, Sis.
So please, shut up.
My fingers are close to their limit.
Miss Balalaika.
Your victory is assured,
and you no longer have anything to lose.
Isn't that-
Rock.
Isn't that enough?
Shut up, Rock!
It's not enough.
There are two things to remember
when you're begging for your life...
One is to entertain the person holding the gun,
the other is to give that person
enough of a reason to be convinced.
And you haven't fulfilled either one.
Now, dance!
What obligation do I have to save you?
You're mistaken.
It's not an obligation.
"Justice" is just a means.
I only have one reason.
It's my hobby.
Hobby?
Yeah, my hobby.
If some folks enjoy dying in the gutters,
then there's also a hobby like mine.
At the roots...
I'm just like you.
We're going to be active again tomorrow, Rock.
From now on, you should avoid
throwing your life away on stupid games.
Park the car.
Please.
Rock!
Baby, you shithead.
The only reason we're still
standing and breathing is 'cause of God's grace,
and because that crazy warmonger in the coat
decided to put her gun away for some reason!
Yeah. I'm your gun in this place.
I know I can protect you through Tarawa or the Alamo.
But, you know, there's no way I can protect a dumbass
who's just itchin' to get killed, you stupid fuck!
Are you mad?
Nothing even close. I'm fucking pissed.
If you weren't you,
I would have shot you two or three times by now!
Revy.
I have a favor to ask.
Will you come to my city one more time?
I don't need to have Sis tell me.
Your place is a good place.
So I got a little lost.
It's so far, I know there's no way I can reach it.
I've been surviving by sucking in dirty air my entire life.
I even forgot that I only know
how to live in a place like that.
In the end, it's just Sis.
She's always lived with her eyes set only on war.
Go ahead,
and never look back.
Your nightmare's over.
Revy...
Have you forgotten?
I'm already dead.
Ever since the day I met you.
If Roanapur is the city of the dead,
this is the city of the living.
I know these sights so well, I nearly forgot that too.
It's like a mirage for a dead man.
No. It may have been a mirage even then too.
Revy.
I didn't come here to go back.
I came here to forget.
I came here to see everything that's going to happen through.
You'll regret it.
I finished regretting a year ago.
I just didn't have the resolve,
but now I think I've got it.
I see.
It's the lady from last time!
Yeah.
Will you show us again?
Yeah, shoot those cans down!
Come on!
Well, Rock?
Put on a show for them, Revy.
All right.
What kind of gun is that?
It looks real.
This here is a Beretta M-92 custom. "The Praiyachat Sword Cutlass" special.
Now watch those cans carefully, you brats.
Those cans, watch them close, okay?!
Your mommy's waiting for you. Now go home, you kids.
Gin, I'd like to have a more powerful gun.
There should be one in this house.
I am not very familiar with projectiles,
but I understand that this is a Russian "Stechkin" gun.
The bullets are big and it can
keep firing like a machine gun.
It may be too much for you, Miss.
No, I want to be a little less of a burden.
I like this.
Roanapur is a wonderful city where you
can blow anything away with brute force.