It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demon.
But a single mage saved them all.
His name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He would eventually be called the first
Wizard King, and he became a legend.
Nero Reminisces...
Part One
One of the Black Bulls, huh?
My prince, so much has happened...
Ever since we met on that
day 500 years ago.
Hey there! You must be Secré.
Sorry, I'm researching ancient
magic right now, so I can't get up.
By the way, what kind of magic do you have?
Sealing magic?!
What's that? I've never heard of it before!
That's so unusual! How amazing!
How should we have you use it?
Just thinking about it is exciting, isn't it?
Magical tools?
Yup. So that people who aren't
blessed with magic or by their
magical attribute can
use all kinds of spells.
That way, I think we can
make our society more equal.
But that just sounds like a silly dream.
They're tools to help me with that.
I think I'll call them magic items.
I'm sure your magic will help me with this!
For example, can you seal magic into objects?
Um... Yes.
You can?! That's amazing!
I helped the prince make magical tools.
He really was nothing like I'd imagined.
There were members of his family
who didn't like his progressive ideas.
But he didn't let that bother him,
and he never compromised his ideals.
He was a strong, honest person.
I didn't know it at the time,
but the prince interacted with
a race other than humans.
They were a race loved by mana,
who lived their lives in peace.
They were the elves.
A four-leaf grimoire!
Licht of sword magic was chosen
by a four-leaf grimoire!
What's a four-leaf grimoire, Mommy?
It's a grimoire with good fortune in it.
Only those it chooses can wield it!
Licht, with the four-leaf grimoire...
He's so cool!
The three leaves of the clover
represent faith, hope, and love.
Within a fourth leaf dwells good luck.
Within a fifth leaf...
resides a devil.
We thought that was just a saying.
So what do you think, Licht?
About the rumors that the
humans might attack us.
I believe they're just rumors.
But I wouldn't say it's
completely impossible.
They're...
Humans are a wicked-hearted
race that kills animals for sport.
That's...
Licht!
Sword Magic:
Origin Flash!
Light Magic:
Lamp of Avior!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Thank you so much.
Tetia! Why did you leave the
castle without permission?
Brother...
Your magical attribute is wind.
How did you, of all people,
get caught up in a mana tornado?
Thank you for saving my little sister.
It's nothing...
Phenomenal magic and skill...
The same thoughts and ideals...
The same four-leaf grimoires...
The leader of the elves, Licht,
was the first peer and friend
that the prince had ever had.
We can come to understand each other.
You elves have truly amazing mana.
By combining that with the magic-item
technology that we humans created,
we can make this land
safer and more prosperous.
Let us live together, hand in hand.
Through his work with the elves,
spells and magic-item technology
that would help not only the humans,
but both races to live in peace as equals
were slowly becoming a reality.
The prince and Licht were best friends.
And they were supposed to become family.
You're with child?
With you two as its parents,
I'm sure it'll be a wonderful child!
Congrats, Tetia... and Licht, too, I guess.
Well, thanks, I guess.
What? Something bothering you?
Well...
I guess you are still a kid.
Be quiet! Stop treating me like a child!
Yeah, yeah...
Lumiere...
Soon, I'll marry Tetia and become your brother.
I'm sure there will be humans
who look down upon that.
You're probably right.
But with you...
I'll be able to create a
peaceful and equal world.
I truly believe that.
I believe that, too.
I'm sure...
...it was fate that brought us together.
I'm really sorry, but I'm probably
going to be late to your wedding.
Sadly, Father has summoned
me to the palace that day.
I know that he and the others
are against this marriage now,
but don't worry.
I'm sure they'll understand someday
and give you their blessings.
I know.
I'm sure Licht and the others
will be eager to see you.
But it's likely that even then,
he was already manipulating
the whole situation.
I wonder why Father summoned me today.
We didn't mention the wedding
to anyone, so is it a coincidence?
I need to hurry to the ceremony.
Congratulations!
I wish you both years of happiness!
May the mana bless you!
Thank you so much.
Aw... I hope someday I'll also...
I'm sure you'll meet
someone lovely soon, Fana.
I sure hope so.
I wish you a lifetime of happiness.
Thank you.
I wonder if we can come to understand
humans someday, just like he said.
Licht seems to believe that, too.
I guess it's possible... for elves
and humans to join hands someday.
Father, where are you?
"Bind."
What is this?
Good day, my prince.
Minister?!
No... The evil mana that's coming
from him doesn't belong to him.
Who are you?!
Who am I?
Despair, hatred,
disloyalty, or death...
You may call me whatever you wish.
A soul with evil mana...
I've read about this being
from another world! A devil?
Where are my father and the others?
Who knows?
Maybe they've gone to destroy the other race
that's trying to harm the princess and,
indeed, the entire kingdom.
I'm sure the elves will be quite surprised
when the humans' violence and greed
fall upon the wedding ceremony
that only you should know about.
What?!
Once I obtain my body and grimoire,
I'll come play with you again.
Wait!
Someone! Isn't there anyone here?
Anyone!
Prince!
Secré!
What's going on, Your Highness?
There's a devil plotting something!
So it wasn't you, was it, Your Highness?
That magic item we made is gone!
Secré! Break these restraints!
Right!
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
Faster... I need to go faster!
Tetia, Licht, everyone...
Wh-What's going on?!
The humans are attacking!
This way! Hurry!
I can't use any magic!
Our magic has been sealed!
Get down!
This is light magic. That means...
...dare you...
How dare you?!
How dare you?! How dare you?!
I'll never...
Lich...
...t...
That's the magic item we made!
Magic items that stored and distributed magic,
and the elves' magic stones, which linked
to another world and amplified spells...
A five-leaf grimoire...
I knew it...
Licht...
I knew it wasn't you.
I'm sorry I doubted you for even a second.
Please forgive me.
You are the future we believed in.
You are hope.
Licht...
Right now, I am filled with
tremendous negative mana.
I don't have full control anymore.
At this rate, that devil will...
Don't...
To prevent my magic and body from falling
into the hands of something wicked...
I've pulled even more negative
magic into myself.
Don't... Don't do this, Licht!
I'm sorry. This is my last selfish request.
You're the only one who can grant it.
Don't do this, Licht!
Lumiere...
Please kill me!
The devil manipulated the prince and the elves
so that he could throw the owner of
the four-leaf grimoire into deep despair.
Because that is when a
five-leaf grimoire is born,
and the devil is able
to appear in this world
in his true form and
with his true powers.
What in the world is that creature?!
R-Run!
Oh, God...
It's the end of the world.
I finally understand...
why I was born with so much...
magical power.
I will not let you...
become a murderer!
That's...
The prince!
Prince Lumiere!
They used a magic item that I created
to steal the elves' magic...
It was supposed to be used so
that we can all share magic.
Prince... Lady Tetia... What should I...
Is there still something I can do?
My prince!
Our magic item! The one we
made for equality and peace!
I'll use the magic item we created...
and absorb his magic!
As I suspected... It's impossible
for it to absorb all of the magic!
He stopped...
The negative mana seems to be subsiding.
Lumi...ere...
Now's your chance.
Hurry...
Licht...
I... will stop you!
You stopped me from obtaining his body,
but that was still quite
an entertaining show.
I guess I'll just have to take
his grimoire for the time being.
Stop!
I won't let you have Licht's grimoire!
The magic stones...
You witnessed the end
of that elf, didn't you?
If a human like yourself who isn't
loved by mana tried to use those,
you wouldn't be able to keep
your form even if you tried to
perform a puny little spell.
Like I care. I'm going to use the
magic stones to increase my magic.
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison!
This is...
Confinement magic, eh?
Her seal is a bit vexing,
but I can use reincarnation
with the magic stones.
"Come."
What?
Even more despair and tragedy for
the soul who possesses the four-leaf.
I guess I'll just have to
sow those seeds for him.
Forbidden Magic: Noad Nepesh.
I'll be sure to work slower and
much more carefully next time.
In an era where you two don't exist.
Secré!
Are you all right?
My prince!
So you managed to seal the devil.
But the seal that I put on
the devil will eventually...
Prince!
No...
This is how it should be.
I was able to keep my promise to Licht.
So...
My prince, I'm going to use
the magic stones to seal you.
It probably won't be complete, but it
should be enough to keep you alive.
If the devil's seal is broken,
the peaceful future we sought
will be taken away from us.
Secré, don't. If you use
any more forbidden magic,
you'll lose your humanity.
I cannot let you die here, Your Highness.
As Licht said, you are
our hope for the future.
It was several years later
before I finally woke up.
The prince began his long
slumber in the form of a statue,
and for some reason, I turned into a bird.
I've been spared? But in this form...
I'll need the help of the future mages.
But when I woke up, I definitely felt
the existence of a hope that
could stand against that devil.
Here we go again...
There, there...
Are they brothers... or perhaps twins?
No, they're not.
This one is rather calm, but this one...
seems like he has a lot of spunk.
First of all, they don't look a thing alike.
Hm? "Yuno"...
Let's see. And the spunky one over here is—
Hey! You're a bit too spunky...
"Asta," eh?
Right! You two don't need to
worry about a thing anymore.
Starting today, this is your new home...
Asta, Yuno.
Hope that can stand against that devil...
I decided to wager
everything on this wish.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 124:
"Nero Reminisces... Part Two."
Page 124
Nero Reminisces... Part Two
My prince, I will make
your wish come true.