It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Vetto realized his true powers,
and they were unbelievably immense.
Asta used the last of his
strength and faced him.
Not giving up is my only weapon!
And I'm never going to give
up until I fulfill my wish!
No matter what!
His teammates were moved
by his words and actions!
You didn't give up, and that's why I'm here.
My juniors are working hard.
That means I have to
act like a proper senior.
I swear that we won't let you die!
Let's go!
The power of the spatial magic and
your aura are gushing all over the place!
What?
The thread changed his trajectory...
I'm going to defeat you...
with this weapon!
Despair vs. Hope
That was actually effective!
Now you've done it, human!
Thanks!
T-Talk about scary! If we were even a second
too late, we would've been done for!
Good work, little boy! Keep it up!
No, wait! I didn't even do anything!
It's all thanks to you two!
Amazing... These two are this powerful?
As I thought, I cannot heal.
Did he sever the magic current
that enables self-healing?
The one weapon here that has a chance
of defeating me... that anti-magic sword.
If I only had to deal with that unskilled
brat, there would be no issue,
but those two are supporting him
and giving him mobility.
The spatial magic is troublesome,
but the real nuisance
is that woman's thread magic!
Her magic runs through this whole space,
interfering whenever and
wherever she wants.
It cannot attack or bind me personally,
I can barely see it, and it's too
thin for me to detect its magic.
That means I won't be able
to read that brat's moves!
How amusing.
To think that three people
who are worthless alone
could fight me by banding together...
It makes me sick.
Don't think that you have hope just
because you've banded together, humans!
He's coming!
Let's go!
Got it!
Finral!
Not yet, damn it!
He did it!
No! That wound's too shallow!
We won't be able to defeat him
just by scratching him like that!
This'll make things even
more dangerous, but...
We need to let the kid get even closer!
I'm all for getting closer! Bring it on!
I'm not imagining it!
What the hell is this ridiculously
huge and creepy magical power?
This is even more ridiculous than the
ridiculous magical power I felt earlier!
We could say that it's now super ridiculous!
Shut up! Stop saying stupid crap!
P-Please don't look at me!
More importantly, have your
powers recovered at all?
U-Um, not at all yet.
I used all my powers against
that steel ball lardbutt.
I can't shoot even a single Reflect Ray now.
At this point...
Hey, domehead! You're going
to have to go ahead, and...
Munchy, munchy, munchy...
Are you seriously still
eating at a time like this?
La!
My spell from earlier to
summon the Sleeping Sheep
One Hit
eats up my magic, so I'm left starving.
Two Hit
Mega Hit
We can't fight on such empty stomachs!
We all need to eat and recover
as much magic as possible!
Well, I guess you have a point.
We should also eat and recover some magic.
O-Okay!
Take that!
The Magic Knights haven't lost yet!
You can do it!
They're up against a crazy monster,
but they still might have a chance!
That's it! Keep it up!
Offense is the best defense!
Don't give him time to counterattack!
How dare you leave my son and
grandchildren in so much pain?!
Please get revenge! Beat him to a pulp!
Not bad...
Those guys never work together,
but now, by working together,
they've surpassed their limits.
However...
It happened again. He held his
ground against their attack.
Could that bastard be...
I can't let my guard down even for a second.
How long am I supposed to keep
up with this tense situation?
Barely missed!
Get a grip! This is no time for whining!
Asta is holding his own against that monster!
Compared to that, this pressure's nothing!
Finral! Do you still have some magic left?
I-It's going down at an enormous rate,
but I'm still managing!
I mean, I spent all this time
running away and not fighting,
so it works out in the end.
So it doesn't mean that our movements
have gotten any slower...
Huh?
This isn't good.
His timing is starting to match our attacks!
I guess it's about time...
Asta!
This is nothing.
One of his attacks just happened to graze me!
Let's do it again!
Hold it, kid!
Captain Yami?!
You should be the first one to know that
he didn't just happen to graze you,
since you're the one fighting him up close.
That bastard was purposely
not attacking as much
and defending instead to better
understand all of your habits.
Wh-What?
If you barge in unprepared...
He's definitely going to get you next time.
N-No...
As expected from the Black Swordsman.
That's why I'm saving you for my main dish.
But what difference does
knowing that fact make?
This situation is still filled with despair.
Insects, this next attack will be your last!
You don't get to decide that,
you hairy gorilla!
You, too, Captain!
We won't know until we try!
I know, damn it! Because I'm a
bazillion times stronger than you!
Then stop watching and come help us!
Really? You're going to say that?
The thing that's bugging me the most?!
When I'm barely able to keep my blood
from boiling in this dumbass situation...
Hey, kid! You need to calm down, too.
I didn't say you couldn't attack him.
I'm just saying you can't keep doing
the same thing. He's going to kill you...
Unless you guys change!
Finral!
Vanessa!
Kid!
Yes, sir!
You know exactly what to do
in situations like this!
Right here, right now...
We're going to surpass
our limits even more!
We're surpassing our limits
and speeding things up!
Got it!
Asta!
A draw?
Not yet!
Let's keep on surpassing our limits!
Got it!
Of course!
Take that!
Little boy... when I see you fighting
with your little body and no magic,
it gives me a courage
that's frankly unlike me.
I had forgotten. I didn't
want to remember...
how weak I was back in
the Forest of Witches.
Hey, did you know that beyond
this forest is a huge city,
and a lot of people who live
there aren't even witches?
Vanessa, you've told me
that hundreds of times.
All the other witches are out playing,
aren't they? Getting boyfriends and stuff.
Why don't you also escape
from this cage and go out?
What? I-I could never do that!
I can't defy the Queen of Witches.
C-Come on, cheer up.
Do you want me to talk to the
Queen of Witches for you?
That's impossible! You're all
dolls I created with my magic.
If I can't do it, there's no
way you could do it.
You're right. Besides, this whole
conversation is just you talking to yourself.
Hopefully you'll be able to make
some real friends someday.
That's impossible... How could I?
I'm always going to be stuck here.
I'll never be free.
That was my fate.
I thought I didn't have a choice.
But...
One day I realized that this
wasn't fate. I just lacked courage.
I wasn't wrong for choosing to leave the
Forest of Witches and become a Black Bull.
Only you have the power to
move the threads of fate!
Little boy, I'll pull! Just trust me and go!
I'm counting on you, ma'am!
Curse you insects!
Come on, you two! You're going way too fast!
I swear... this is the problem
with hot-blooded people!
I've always been the guy with no motivation!
Finral...
What is that fragile and
stunted spatial magic?
We of the House of Vaude are a family
of attack spatial magic users that
have been Magic Knights for generations.
You can't fight with magic like that.
But I don't want to be violent or
have people be violent toward me.
You weakling!
Goodness! Look at how much
you managed to shave off!
You're so amazing, Langris! A genius!
We'll just have someone
rebuild what he destroyed.
You don't have to worry
about a thing, Langris.
Honestly... Aren't you ashamed to
be outdone by your younger brother?
To think that the difference in
your abilities was this great.
Langris is now the vice
captain of the Golden Dawn.
And yet you're...
...the pack mule for the
weakest squad, the Black Bulls.
We're appointing Langris as the
next head of the House of Vaude.
I doubt you have any objections.
Of course I don't. I was just thinking that'd
be too much for me to handle myself.
Langris, take care of our family for me.
I don't take orders from you, Finral.
You bring shame upon the Vaude family!
You've got a point... but I'm
pretty popular with the ladies.
I ran away from my parents,
my brother, my home, and reality.
Hey there, cuties!
Let's go have some tea. There's a
fancy café just around the corner.
You girls are so cute,
you're going to make me say things
even sweeter than those sweets there.
In the midst of that, Asta, I met you,
a kid with absolutely no magic.
It's not that you didn't have enough...
You had nothing, but you faced yourself,
kept fighting, and never gave up.
It's true that how I am now,
I'll never beat my brother.
But...
Say, Yami.
Why did you let me join your squad?
I can barely even fight.
So you can take me everywhere.
Huh?
Oh, right... It's not like I can
defeat any enemies with my magic.
You've probably got your own
way of fighting, right?
Huh?
I'm saying that battling doesn't
just mean defeating enemies.
My own way of fighting...
I'm not going to become the strongest.
But I'll make the Black Bulls
the strongest squad!
I had abandoned my own fight.
When I did, there were words
I couldn't say anymore.
But now, I can say them!
Asta! Believe in me!
Trust me and jump in!
Sorry, but I already believe
in you 100 percent!
Not bad for insects!
But you must be nearing your limits.
If even one of you makes the
smallest mistake, you'll die instantly!
How long can you hold up under
such extreme conditions?
Shut up, beast guy!
Until we beat you, of course!
Asta just told me that he
believes in me 100 percent.
I knew that! Otherwise, he could never
fight using this ridiculous method!
Honestly, how can you trust a drunk woman
and a superficial wimp with your life?
If you believe in us so earnestly...
...we can never betray that trust!
I see. That's some
magnificent concentration.
But how about your magic powers?
They'll probably reach their limits soon.
The amount of magic we have...
That's the difference between
myself and you insects!
H-He sure knows how to hit where it hurts.
My spatial holes are becoming smaller.
My threads are screaming.
I'm almost out of magic, and the
threads are about to break.
So what?!
I'm going to believe in them both and win!
It's not just them.
Guess we got here in time.
La!
Gauche! Charmy!
And...
Grey. It sounds like some terrible joke,
but apparently, this is her true form.
What?!
P-Please don't look at me!
We can talk later.
Take this! This is all the
magic I have right now!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain!
What's the matter, insects?
You think you'll actually hit me
just by attacking more?
Nah, I accomplished what I wanted.
Domehead!
Cotton Creation Magic:
Sleeping Sheep's...
One Hit!
One Hit
Two Hit!
Two Hit
Mega Hit!
Mega Hit!!
You're trying to make
some kind of smokescreen?
Annoying little brats!
What?
Wh-What's going on?
I-It's my transformation magic!
I don't have much magic left, so some
may not look exactly like him...
Bring it on!
Domehead! Keep hitting
until you run out of magic!
Lai-lai, sir!
You pesky insects! Despair already!
Despair?
We don't have time for that!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Trinity
Trinity.
Listen carefully. I'm going to use
my thread to change your direction!
Then, I'll use my spatial magic
to move you somewhere else!
But if we miss even once, you'll be finished!
Are you ready?
Yeah! All we can do is charge!
Here we go, Gordon!
Green light!
I believe in you two!
We can never betray that trust!
Green light... Red light.
What?!
I can't tell when Gordon's done saying,
"Green light, red light," at all.
I'm so sorry, Asta.
He's just too strong.
This is so much fun. You're it next, Asta.
I'll make sure I get to you.
Oh, no. I sense that my
friends are in trouble.
I want to help you all. Please stay safe.
I hope my feelings reach you all.
Black Clover, Page 49: "Beyond Limits."
Page 49
Beyond Limits
My magic is becoming friends with anyone.