It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demon.
But a single mage saved them all.
His name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He would eventually be called the first
Wizard King, and he became a legend.
As Pitch Black as It Gets
Town in the Common Realm, Nean
What? To the royal capital again?
Yes. I do apologize, as I realize
she just came back, but...
Here is the order.
It appears to be real, but...
Do not worry.
We'll make sure she gets there safely.
As soon as Marie returns from battle,
she's summoned to the capital again?
Theresa Rapual
Neige
What could the Magic Parliament want with her?
Sister Theresa!
What's the matter, Rebecca?
Rebecca Scarlet
There's trouble. Here, look at today's paper.
Church, Hage Village
Th-Th-The paper...
Orsi Orfai
Asta's in the paper!
Lily Aquaria
"Rebelling Against the Kingdom...
A Minion of the Devil"?!
This must be some kind of mistake!
The Royal Capital, Clover Kingdom
So that peasant brat
finally became a criminal!
Revchi
Gueldre Poizot
Sucks to be him!
Ooh!
Does that mean Asta will have to work here, too?
Sally
That means I get to dissect him, right?
I mean, he promised me that I could.
Rades Spirito
Hell if I know!
Jeez, why are you so angry?
I'm not angry!
Your blood is always boiling.
I know. Maybe if I took some
of your blood, that'd help.
I'll just dissect you!
Don't!
Why do I have to do this, anyway?
Hey, what the hell is going on, Valtos?!
Valtos
Don't ask me.
You're the one who followed me.
I just decided that I would atone for my sins.
Damn it!
Captain of the Green Praying Mantises
Jack the Ripper
Shut it! Start yappin' again and
I'll slice you, criminals!
You already did!
Are you trying to kill us?!
You bastard!
Of course I am!
If I'd had my way, I would've turned you all
into sliced ham while you were roaming free!
Go ahead and run! That'd give me
an excuse to slice you up!
You can't be serious! You look more
like a criminal than any of us!
I'm gonna control your corpse one day!
I'll tie you up in chains!
Shut up!
Asta...
This is... Are they trying to make Asta
take the blame for everything we did?
Damnatio from the Magic Parliament
just might do that.
They say that he judged his own father before.
He's the scale of justice that will
cruelly judge any crime for the sake of
the kingdom and the law.
So Asta's up against the jurisdiction
of this kingdom itself.
If anyone defies it, their entire
clan will be punished.
Magic Parliament Courthouse
That form is truly...
It's just as the legends describe.
He's a devil!
So you've shown your true self,
you devil!
I'm able to go into my black form quicker now.
After that last fight, I've managed
to make it more my own.
Asta...
Don't you worry, Marie. I'll protect you.
Okay.
Everyone, listen!
It's okay! I'm able to control this power now!
I won't attack any of you!
Like we can actually believe you!
You're possessed by a devil!
How grotesque!
How horrifying!
You're a filthy peasan
who's made a deal with the devils!
Give him death!
I knew he was nothing more than trash.
A devil...
Nothing is more suitable than the death
penalty for peasant filth like him.
Bah-ha?! The death penalty?!
Please! Listen to me!
Kill him! Before he brings
misfortune upon the kingdom!
Sentence him to death immediately!
Give yourself up.
Even if you were able to defeat me
and escape from here,
you'd just become a fugitive.
There's nowhere for you to run.
And if that were to happen,
the ones who raised you in the church
will probably suffer, too.
You should be convicted right here, right now.
By having someone as
dangerous as you disappear,
that little girl, as well as many
Magic Knights, will be saved.
There is no one in this place nor this kingdom
who can or will save you right now.
You sow calamity over everyone you touch.
You are evil.
What's going on?!
What is the meaning of this?!
Man... I knew you guys would be
doing whatever the hell you wanted.
I was told the trial would
be two days from now.
I don't give a rat's ass
if that kid is evil or not.
He's definitely a badass junior of mine that
I've acknowledged as a real man's man.
He's my precious friend.
I can't let you kill him right here.
What do you think you're
doing to my best friend?
Do you all want to get cursed to death?
I've transformed into him,
so I know that he's always bold, and I'd
love to be as persistent as he is.
He's... really, really... nice...
and... a good... boy.
Losing you would make Marie sad,
so I guess I don't mind
saving you along with her.
Also, get your paws off Marie!
He may be a boy,
but he's a very brave young man that
makes even the cruelest fates
bounce off of him.
He makes me look good as his senior,
and I couldn't ask for a better partner!
I still need him to live
longer and eat more noms!
He's a stupid little shrimp,
but I don't mind conceding a little bit
and saying he's pretty close to
what a true Magic Knight should be.
He's stupid, loud, and reckless,
but as royalty, I acknowledge him
as someone this kingdom needs!
N-Not that there's any deeper meaning to that.
How about you guys give back...
...Asta now?
The Black Bulls...
Wh-What in the world is that giant thing?
Th-The Black Bulls?
How dare you disturb this honorable
trial with such violence?!
Yami Sukehiro...
You're defending the criminal
that started this great war?
Do you know what will happen to the
Black Bulls because of this decision?
Oh, you didn't know?
We're pretty much the worst Magic
Knight squad ever to exist.
Both those guys there with the
horns belong to our squad.
Me?
If you're gonna mess with them,
we'll be scoundrels or rebels
or whatever, you jackass!
Guys...
That aside, I'm gonna punish
anyone who dares to touch Marie.
B-Big Brother! Now's not the time for that!
How stupid can you be to come
out and get caught like this?
How many times to do you intend
to almost die, Stupidsta?!
Even death couldn't fix his stupidity.
At least die fighting me!
When you die is the day I die!
How dare you hold Marie? Die, Asta.
Wait, didn't you come to save me?!
Big Brother, stop!
Apparently, even death couldn't
fix his sister complex.
Hey, guy from the royal Kira family or whatever.
Looks like you took real good
care of two of my squad members.
Don't worry about me. Just take
Asta and get out of here!
I'm not even from this era, and I'm no longer
really human because of the forbidden magic.
I basically used you to complete my mission.
You've really got some nerve, saying that
after spending so much time at our place.
You've been watching us this whole time,
but apparently, you've still got no clue.
I heard all about you.
You were being badass in the
form of a bird for 500 years?
That's pretty awesome.
It... must... have... been... really...
lonely... all... by... yourself.
I know that feeling all too well.
We'd love to have another
cute girl like you!
You were working hard in the shadows.
We'd probably get along really well.
Be my friend.
Actually, we've been best
friends since the day I was born.
Y-Yes!
Now you get to enjoy life
along with all of us.
Just make sure you eat tons!
Thank goodness I didn't eat
you when you were a bird.
You were planning on eating her?
Nothing will change about
the Black Bulls if we have
another weirdo like yourself.
For me, your ki is really familiar,
and we've already got plenty of weirdos.
This is...
Sealing Magic: Eternal Prison.
I'll go with you!
Yeah, we're basically as pitch black as it gets!
That's...
Us, the Black Bulls!
Apparently, you don't understand at all.
Even if you protect that devil's minions,
it won't change the situation.
Cause all the fuss you want here,
but it won't clear the boy's name.
It's actually just going to worsen
the charges of him being a devil.
Apparently, you're all very emotional,
but that won't save this kingdom.
You cannot change the minds of
all the nobles gathered here.
They're still leaning toward
bewilderment and suspicion.
And even if they were to rampage...
Scale Magic: Scale Regulate!
La! My magic's getting smaller!
My scale magic measures one's abilities,
balances them, and establishes order.
No matter how powerful your magic is,
it's impossible to defy it.
But Rouge hasn't disappeared.
Meaning he can't lay a finger on us!
And we have a boy who can
make the impossible possible!
Demon-Destroyer Sword: Fate Release!
He erased my magic's effect!
Gotcha!
Oh, are they...
You're as reckless as ever, foreigner.
What were you planning to do after this?
Eh, I just got a little worked up.
Though it appears you meant to miss.
Honestly... Even if this
was for your squad members,
you couldn't make a worse impression.
Though thanks to that, we made it in time.
What the hell is that big dragon?!
You really did power up when you came back!
Captain Fuegoleon... Captain Nozel!
Why...
We can't afford to lose
any capable Magic Knights.
In other words, the people
who acknowledge you aren't
limited to any rank or class.
Nozel! Captain Fuegoleon!
Two royal members of the Magic Knights...
What's the meaning of this?
But what are you going to do now?
We have a mission from the Wizard King.
The Black Bulls Magic Knights Squad
is tasked with locating and
investigating the devils.
Huh?
Prove your innocence with your own hands.
I see.
Royals have authority here,
so he had Nozel and Fuegoleon,
two royals, deliver the order.
Can that geriatric kid see
the future or something?
Curse you, Julius!
You were missing when we
really needed you,
and now you go stepping on my toes again!
So I guess that means Asta
won't be executed immediately.
Ba-hank goodness...
While Asta is on this mission,
the Wizard King and Magic Knights will
take full responsibility for him.
By making it look as though the brat's
being dealt with by the Magic Knights,
they're given the leeway
to prove their innocence.
So, uh, er... Wait, what does that mean?
We're gonna go investigate the devils
so we can clear that name of yours!
And break the curse of the forbidden magic, too.
Investigating the devils?
But that doesn't resolve anything...
It's an order from the Wizard King.
He wouldn't be too foolhardy.
I mean, two royal captains of the
Magic Knights are vouching for him.
And the Wizard King says
he'll take responsibility.
Apparently, I weighed the trust
people have in you too lightly.
But know that you'll be
executed immediately if you prove
to have no use to the kingdom.
You're still hanging in the balance.
Let us go.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Marie... Thank goodness you're safe.
Big Brother!
I told you not to attack Asta!
M-Marie?!
Um... Nozel...
Thank you very much.
Do not thank me. Thank the Wizard King.
I will.
Asta, take this.
Huh?!
What was that?
Now we'll know where you are.
This way, you can't flee.
Like I would actually try to flee!
We know.
But putting up a front is necessary at times.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Good for you, Asta.
Jeez, don't worry us like that!
Go on. Eat up!
And drink up, too.
Want more?
I'll feed you myself, my dear friend.
Asta...
You dumbass.
Uh... Um... Um...
I-I'm gonna die!
Come in.
Pardon me.
Hello, Damnatio.
So you're trying to take on everything again,
despite what you've been reduced to.
Both what happened with the Magic Knights,
as well as the boy possessed by a devil.
That order was smart thinking, wasn't it?
Now no one will get punished.
Of course, that's how it should be,
since Asta never did anything wrong.
I'm sure that the Black Bulls will be
able to find some clues about the devils.
That'll make up for them
barging into the trial, too.
Forgiving them means taking responsibility.
The kingdom can't take that
kind of responsibility.
You can't take on that
responsibility yourself, either.
I didn't forgive them. I left it in their hands.
It's not about responsibility.
It's about trusting them.
Eventually, I'm sure your scales will
tip in favor of Asta and his group.
It appears that you haven't changed
at all inside. I'm relieved.
The distortions in this country...
The crisis we're facing is not a small one.
If the kingdom is about to fall,
I'll have to pass judgment.
On that boy, and even you.
Pardon me.
Master Julius!
Hey there, Marx.
Feeling better already?
You're alive, but you're little...
You're little, but you're alive...
Huh? Wha... I...
I'm fine, but... What? What's going on?
You were always like a child...
And now, you really are a child.
So, yeah, this...
You don't need to explain!
Just show me your memories later.
The kingdom is in trouble,
and that form of yours is...
Honestly...
You're such a ridiculous person...
I'm s-so glad...
you're alive.
I'm sorry for always worrying you, Marx.
No, I'm not forgiving you!
Huh?
There's a mountain of work waiting for you!
Wait...
There are plenty of problems
we need you to solve.
What?!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
There's Trouble!
Sister Theresa!
What's the matter, Rebecca?
There's trouble. Here, look at today's paper.
Th-This is...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha...
All you people just keep saying, "This is..."
This is... what?!
Nice, I say!
On that day, five hundred years ago,
the tragedy between the humans
and the elves happened.
And it was all caused by a devil.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 123:
"Nero Reminisces... Part One."
Page 123
Nero Reminisces... Part One