It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
We will now begin the finals
for the Selection Exam.
I Team: Rill, Nils, and Ruben, come forward!
Young Master Rill,
here's some herbal tea that will clear
your mind and help you concentrate.
Yay, thank you!
I'm sure the mistress will be pleased
when she hears about all of
your ventures this time around.
What? Mother will?
You think so?
But of course.
Then I definitely need to win.
Please show the world why
you were able to become
the youngest Magic Knights Squad
captain in history.
That's the Captain of the Aqua Deer for you.
He seems so relaxed despite
the big battle coming up.
Well, he crushed the other
teams in his last two rounds.
We made it this far without doing
much at all because of him.
At this rate, even if our team wins,
there's no guarantee that we'll
be selected as Royal Knights.
Who were those two again?
We have to stand out more!
Next, P Team: En, Yuno,
and Noelle, come forward.
Dear members of I Team, please go easy on us.
I'm gonna crush all of you!
I'm gonna crush you all into sawdust!
Uh, your inner voice is spilling out.
I'm just so excited, I can't contain myself.
Let's do this, Noelle!
My expression is as hard as rock truffles!
Let's fire things up!
Mushrooms double in flavor
when you cook them!
You can even dry them or freeze them!
Let's mushle, mushle to victory!
All together now!
Mushle—
Shut up.
Huh?
Honestly... I'm already distracted
enough because of Asta.
I mean, I'm only worried
because he's part of my squad.
It's not like it bothers me that
Mimosa gets to be by his side!
Your face is red! Are you
finally getting fired up?!
Shut your mouth.
Ugh, you're both so noisy.
You'd better not hold Yuno back!
Bell...
We're going full force in the next round.
Yes! It's finally my turn to shine!
What?
You mean he wasn't at full strength yet?
He's so cool.
That's what draws people to him,
and makes them admire him...
I can't wait!
With you as my next opponent,
I might finally be able to paint
my ultimate masterpiece!
I'll also be able to see
just how much I've grown.
Young Master Rill will be the victor.
It'll be Yuno!
It'll be Master Rill.
Yuno!
The young master.
Yu—
The—
Ruben  Nils  Rill
I Team
Yuno  En  Noelle
P Team
So it finally begins.
This will determine the winning team.
Though I, the protagonist, am absent,
I hope to see a beautiful match.
I'm going to watch every second of this
match so I can further my horizons!
The Victors
Asta!
So you finally woke up.
Where am I?
Langris!
You need to lie down.
Yeah, but—
It's over.
That's right. Our team...
How's Finral?
His wounds are quite deep... He's been
taken to the castle's medical tower.
What about Yuno and his team?
They had a quick victory
again in stage two, la.
They're about to start the match
to decide the winning team.
Yuno...
And now, the final match with I Team...
I can't wait!
We'll stand out this time!
...and P Team!
I'll take care of the
Captain of the Aqua Deer.
He's all yours.
Begin!
Whoa! Here he comes!
I'm right here!
He doesn't have to call him over!
Hey! Right over here!
As we suspected, that newcomer
is heading for Captain Rill.
I said, I'm right over here!
Now's our chance.
Hey!
Wind Magic: Wind Blade Shower!
Picture Magic: Game of the Gods!
What?!
He's definitely not like
anyone I've faced before.
That's our number one newbie!
I expect nothing less!
Ah, so they just greeted
each other with their magic.
By the looks of it,
neither of them is even trying yet.
That's what you call a greeting?!
Th-They're on a whole different level!
Look!
Bah-ha?!
There's a battle beginning over there, too.
The enemy team's crystal
is right in front of us!
Let's do this!
Ice Magic: Ice Needle!
Sandstone Magic: Rock Fall!
They're both attacking at once?!
Leave the ice magic to me!
Noelle, if you'd take care of the
fellow with the sandstone magic.
Fungus Magic: Towering Mister Mushroom.
Heyo.
Bring it!
Ha-ni-wat?!
What?!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
Their defense is strong!
Then we'll just have to strengthen
our defense as well, and take them on!
No matter what it takes...
We're going to destroy their crystal...
...and stand out!
They split up, just like we planned.
We're going to protect our crystal,
no matter what.
So...
We're counting on you over there!
Wind Magic: Tornado Fang...
Plus Crescent Moon Sickle!
Hup!
Here we go!
Bell!
You got it!
Wind Magic: Swift White Bow!
Nice, nice!
Whoa, there!
Oopsie-daisy...
Here we go!
Hup!
One more time!
Maybe I was wrong about you.
I seem to be missing a little something.
Such versatile and powerful wind magic!
I guess we should expect that from the
newbie who has the four-leaf grimoire.
He's powerful!
But he's up against the
Captain of the Aqua Deer.
He's blocking everything beautifully.
Your little spirit friend is a cutie.
This is starting to get really fun!
But this still isn't enough for me to get the
inspiration for my ultimate masterpiece!
What's his problem?
He keeps blocking everything
with his weird paintings! Ugh!
Bell, we're going to do the thing.
I planned to use it against
Asta in the finals,
but I'm up against a Magic
Knights Squad captain.
You're a worthy opponent.
In the battle where he lost his five senses,
his concentration was
heightened to its peak.
That along with his experience
in controlling mana
and the training he underwent to use
Mana Skin to protect himself at all times...
Yuno learned to control the excessive
amount of mana within his body.
He then refined that technique
so that he could hold the
spirit's power within him, too.
This feeling of becoming one with Yuno...
I just can't get enough of it!
Asta...
I'm about to pull far ahead
of you with this one move.
I am always the one who will win against you!
Spirit Assimilation: Spirit Dive.
Wh-What is that overwhelming
amount of magic?
So beautiful...
This power was born from your overwhelming
instinct and astounding efforts.
Yuno, you're...
Wow...
Young Master...
That's amazing, Yuno!
I feel like I can draw anything right now!
Wind Spirit Magic...
Picture Magic...
Spirit Storm!
Scream of the Mystical Dragon Vouivre!
It's amazing... So amazing!
Please don't draw anymore, Rill!
No one will be able to accept you!
Someday, your mother will
understand your talents, too.
This is the best!
I never knew that going
all-out against someone...
...could make me so happy!
La...
Y-Yuno is amazing.
Damn it... Damn it...
Why... am I not the one facing Yuno?
I'm going to win
against a Magic Knights Squad captain!
I'm going to win!
Good...
Good, good!
More! More, more!
Let's draw the ultimate masterpiece
together!
Huh?
Huh?! Wait, why?!
Things were just about to
get even more interesting!
His attack didn't hit the crystal, though!
What in the world?! Why did it break?!
I'm guessing that with the intense amount
of magical power Rill was emitting,
the crystal just couldn't take it anymore.
His own magical powers...
...made him self-destruct?
We couldn't...
Captain Rill has destroyed
his own team's crystal.
...stand out...
Therefore, P Team—Yuno,
Noelle, and En—wins!
Th-That battle was unbelievable.
That final push of their magical
powers gave me goosebumps.
That newbie is on the same
level as Captain Rill... no.
He might have even more magic!
Yes!
Ahem... Well, he won, but only because
his opponent self-destructed.
We can't have him getting
a big head because of that.
I'm not about to lose! I'm going
back and training even harder!
This isn't fair!
Young Master.
Please, wipe away those tears.
If I were the judge, I would've proclaimed
you the victor, Master Rill.
Huh? Really?
I win?!
By a landslide.
Oh, come on! There's no way!
You can't be serious.
Well, to others, you probably didn't win.
But you should use this
frustration as motivation
to draw your next ultimate masterpiece.
I'm sure that's just what
your mother would want.
You're right... Thank you, Walter.
And...
Yuno.
We won!
We did it, Noelle.
Mushle, mushle! Mushle, mush—
What did you expect?
Oh, my gosh! I can't believe we actually won!
This concludes the Selection Exam.
First of all, let me congratulate
you on your victory.
You may have lost by a hair,
but you also did amazingly well.
Also, the other teams may have been defeated,
but it doesn't mean you're out of the race.
I'm going to go over all
of your battles from today,
and will probably select and announce about
10 to 20 Royal Knights at a later date.
That means we still have a chance!
They're all extremely gifted Magic Knights.
I'm going to have a hard time choosing.
Finally, His Majesty has something to say.
Ahem.
Excellent work today.
You displayed high levels of magical power
and versatility in dealing
with various obstacles,
not to mention the use of careful
planning and combination attacks.
Any one of your teams could
have easily been the winner.
He actually said something decent.
That was decent.
Way too decent.
He almost sounds like a real king.
However! I worked harder than anyone else!
Without me, this day would've never come!
I am the one who decided
and announced the formation
of the ultimate squad of Magic Knights,
the Royal Knights!
I am the great one who made
this exam happen, so praise me!
What are you doing?! Hurry up and praise me!
Your Majesty, please calm yourself.
They all gathered here because they all
supported the idea of the Royal Knights
from the bottom of their hearts.
They gathered here
determined to protect this kingdom
from the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Don't you think their thoughts and actions
show that they are ready for anything?
If only the Wizard King
was actually the king.
Shouldn't we just make the
Wizard King the actual king?
Now, then... I'll be counting on you
if you're chosen to be a Royal Knight.
Yes, sir.
Curse you! You're always
standing out more than me!
We will now bring the Royal Knights
Selection Exam to a close.
I would say that today's
exam was a huge success.
Yes. Your other objective,
to find out which Magic
Knight was being manipulated
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
was also a success.
We can begin questioning once
Langris recovers from his wounds.
I'd rather not suspect everyone, but there
might be something more going on.
We can't let our guard down.
Thanks for staying by my side, Mimosa.
Asta...
My magic can heal physical wounds,
but not his heart.
We're going back, Mimosa.
Yuno!
B-But...
I see... Asta's...
Mimosa, it'll be okay. I'll take over.
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
It's only natural for me to look
after another member of my squad!
Yuno...
Are you sure, Yuno?
Yuno!
I'm going to catch up to you!
I'm the one who's going
to become the Wizard King!
Like I'd let you catch up to me.
Hey, Yuno!
Yuno!
Yuno...
You made this?
Super Magic Knight Zora has a mouth
on him, but he's as good as his word.
He's a warrior who protects
the country behind the scenes!
We all believe in each other and get
through life-or-death situations!
Companions who believe in each other, huh?
What the hell am I thinking?
Leaving already?
Thank you for pointing out the
faults of everyone who lost.
Though you could've said
things a little more nicely,
those who want to improve can
actually take those words
to heart and become stronger.
Your trap magic and knowledge are vital.
You will probably pass the
Royal Knights Selection Exam,
so I'll be counting on you.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm sure you already knew this, but I'm
not the Vice Captain of the Purple Orcas
or Xerx Lügner. See ya.
True. I can't commend you for
pretending to be someone else.
But I wouldn't say it's that big an issue,
given that you're a Magic Knight yourself,
Zora.
A long time ago, I met a certain
Magic Knight on the battlefield.
His name was Zara Ideale.
He gave his all to protect this country
and was a model Magic Knight.
I ended up alongside this amazing
guy on the battlefield today.
He could use time magic.
He's the kind of guy who's gonna succeed.
His name was cool, too! Novachrono!
We thought up the star system
so that people like him
would be acknowledged for their efforts,
rather than their upbringing.
Despite that, we sadly still have some
misguided Magic Knights among us.
I think it's about time you put on the
robe from your own squad, don't you,
Zora Ideale?
Who the hell is that jerk?
I'm just a guy passing through
who couldn't become a super mage.
Hello there. 'Tis I, the beautiful
Kirsch Vermillion, once again.
In Black Clover, we always strive for beauty.
And we will reach the peak of beauty
in Page 85: "Together In the Bath."
Page 85
Together In the Bath
My naked body is beautiful enough
to be a national treasure!