It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Yami was visiting the
Golden Dawn's headquarters
in order to meet with Vangeance, but...
How long is that golden
weird mask guy captain of yours
going to make me wait after he
said he wanted to apologize?
H-He should be here any second.
Are you Golden Dawn jerks messing with me?
Yami continued to wait for Vangeance,
whom he trusted
because they had fought for this kingdom
and become Magic Knights
Squad captains together.
But at that time...
Vangeance revealed his other self, which
he had kept hidden, to the Wizard King.
He was the Captain of the Golden Dawn,
William Vangeance,
but also the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun, Licht.
Thank you, William...
My one and only human friend.
Good day to you,
Wizard King Julius Novachrono.
I am the leader of the
Eye of the Midnight Sun, Licht.
I had really hoped that wasn't the case.
Licht fought Julius so he
could steal the magic stones
that Julius had and exact his
revenge against the humans.
Julius was able to anticipate Licht's attacks
with his time magic and fight back.
I have you now!
Wha—
He's anticipating even faster!
I can already see your future.
You cannot defeat me.
Julius Novachrono
Look over there!
The castle tower...
S-Something's shining...
What in the world is going on?
This way!
Over there!
This magic... It's Lord Julius.
He's battling with someone.
Someone who uses light magic and
can keep up with Lord Julius...
Could it be...
The leader of the Eye of
the Midnight Sun, Licht?
But the Royal Knights should be working
on eliminating them as we speak.
How did he get into the castle?
Was he also the one who shut down my
communication magic with Lord Julius?
There are too many unknowns...
Wh-What's going on?
Is Lord Julius fighting?
What should we do?
Please, calm down.
This is the moment our strength
will be put to the test.
We cannot protect this kingdom
if we're panicking like this!
Yes. Calm down.
It's my job to remain
calm at times like this.
Even if we were to assist in the fight,
we're nowhere near their level.
We'd only get in the way.
There's no way Lord Julius should lose,
but if all else fails, the only ones
who could keep up in this battle are
Magic Knights Squad captains or their equals!
I need to send a message to all the
Magic Knights Squad headquarters I've marked!
What?
Sis!
Communication magic?
It's a message from the royal capital, bah-ha.
This is an urgent message to all
Magic Knights Squad captains!
The Wizard King is fighting a
man believed to be the leader
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
right now at Clover Castle!
They might be putting
some plan into motion,
like the previous attack
on the royal capital.
All Magic Knights should follow orders from
their captains and guard their districts.
Captains, as soon as your
districts are secure,
please meet at the royal
capital immediately!
Wh-What's going on?
Captain Mereoleona should be attacking
their hideout as we speak.
The leader of the Eye of the Midnight
Sun is at the royal capital?
This could be my only chance
to avenge my brother.
But...
What's with those pathetic
looks on your faces?
And you call yourselves members
of the proud Crimson Lion Kings?!
Yes, sir!
Remember the words of my brother!
Remain calm at all times!
While my sister is gone,
we will prepare for a possible attack
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
as we were ordered!
H-He's right!
This is no time to panic!
We're the Crimson Lion Kings!
How could this have happened?
How did they get into the royal capital?
Please hurry and return,
Captain Vangeance.
It couldn't be...
Please let me be wrong.
Your individual blows
are becoming a bit dull.
At this rate, I won't even have to
anticipate your moves to dodge them.
He can keep up with
me even at this speed?
Just how far into the future
can he anticipate?
You can have this back.
He sped up my spell.
Well, you certainly came close.
You're pretty fast.
Even reading your moves, I still
haven't been able to capture you.
What is behind this man's strength?
He's just an ordinary human. So why...
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd just give up now.
I'd rather not wound Vangeance's body.
The reason he isn't fighting back is
because he wants to capture me alive.
He still has plenty of strength.
To fight against me,
despite my four-leaf grimoire...
Where is it? Where is his grimoire?
What kind of...
Are you curious about my grimoire?
My grimoire is right up there.
Why does it look like that?
It doesn't even have a cover!
That grimoire is...
Time magic and a grimoire
without a cover...
I didn't know if it was good or bad
at the time, but I was special.
So I thought about it a lot.
I'm just like this coverless grimoire.
I couldn't be classified.
Who am I? What is my purpose in life?
I kept asking myself that over and over.
And as I did, I gained
more and more recognition.
And once I finally got here, I thought...
The path that I've walked
makes me who I am.
I am the Wizard King.
I just figured it out.
We are about to use the
power of the magic stones
in an attempt to defy the
natural order of this world.
This man...
This human...
He is an existence that the world and
fate created in order to stop us.
The last bastion of order.
As the Wizard King,
I will protect this kingdom
and its people.
Then I suppose... No.
This is exactly why I have to defeat him!
In that case... just try to protect them now!
Sealing Magic Released!
His power is swelling...
H-Hey...
What is that?
Wh-What's going on?
This tremendous magic power is...
You humans stole everything from me.
My friends... my days of
happiness... all in an instant.
Even if it means violating the natural order...
You humans shall pay!
To think he had enough magic power
to overwhelm this entire kingdom...
This isn't good. Is he planning to
unleash that power upon the people?
Even if I can't kill you alone,
I can kill everyone else.
I-Is this a spell?
Countless swords of light?
Mommy, the sky's all white!
It's so bright!
I-Is this the end of the world?
What's going on?
Town in the Common Realm: Nean
It's so empyreal...
A Village Out in the Boonies: Hage
What the heck is that?
We can see it from way out here?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't worry. Even if that
light is something ominous,
this kingdom has Magic Knights.
The size of that light spell
is ridiculous... damn it!
What the hell's going on, Julius?
Please let me make it in time!
It's already enveloped the
whole kingdom. At this rate...
Now... Accept your judgment, humans!
Light Magic: Arrows of Judgment!
I had doubts.
Honestly, why do those commoners
have such poor magic?
I honestly don't know how
peasants are even alive.
It makes me sick just being
in the same kingdom as them.
Indeed!
Is that really the case?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Despite having high levels of magic power,
they only used it to line their own
pockets and weren't of any use to anyone.
Why were they even alive?
Ah, you must be the Magic
Knight I heard about.
The one with the bizarre grimoire.
Well, that aside, there's a merchant
who has requested our
accommodation of his business.
Oh, really?
You see...
Ah, well, well...
I kept searching for my purpose in life
while fighting as a Magic Knight.
And then...
Hurry up and give me all your money!
Hold it!
You evil villain who threatens
the peace in this kingdom...
I won't let you get away with this!
I encountered a man named Zara,
who was the first peasant to
be chosen as a Magic Knight.
Come at me with all you've got!
Just so you know, my magic is a hundred
times stronger than yours, you fat-ass!
A Magic Knight, eh?
Like that scares me!
You fell for it.
All right!
Everyone, get someplace safe!
Heya! Could you come down here a sec?
He didn't have much magic power,
but he cleverly used his trap spells in battle.
Observation of his magic made
it clear how hard he worked.
Hey, what the heck is that magic?
It's almost like you're
reversing the flow of time.
Close, but not quite.
Time magic, eh? That's way too awesome.
But I'd say there won't be any casualties now.
Zara, was it? Looks like
you're quite hurt yourself.
Let me have a look.
I'm fine.
As a Magic Knight,
we need to prioritize the lives
of the people, after all!
Don't you feel the same way, Julius?
Well, I'll leave this to you.
While other Magic Knights were blinded
by personal achievements and glory,
he always prioritized helping out
the people above everything else.
Back then, even though I didn't really
know what it meant to be a Magic Knight,
I thought he was what a true
Magic Knight should be.
A little while later...
I heard that Zara had died.
Whoa, there.
Oh?
You're...
Zara had carried out his
duty as a Magic Knight.
That's how I wanted to be...
a Magic Knight like Zara.
And right around the time
I started thinking that...
I heard that he was killed by
another member of his own squad.
No way! He must've been
one hell of an annoyance
if there are rumors like that going around.
He probably showed off too much.
Well, it doesn't matter.
This just means another peasant died.
This cannot be okay.
It wasn't just happening
with the Magic Knights.
In this kingdom, because of
the class they were born into,
the ones on top grew arrogant while
the ones at the bottom gave up.
Even though both sides
should've had more potential.
I thought it was a waste.
The potential of magic
and of humans is infinite.
For your voice to be widely
heard, you need power,
rank,
and trust.
I built up a record of achievements
and became the Wizard King.
Magic and humans should be freer.
The change won't be dramatic.
However, slowly but surely...
The people of this kingdom are
finally starting to change.
Through the strength of the people
I believe in and acknowledge...
Through the strength of the
people they acknowledge.
I can't let that end now.
Not while I am the Wizard King!
Time Reversal Magic: Chrono Anastasis.
Wh-What's going on?
A time spell tremendous enough to save
all the people of this kingdom...
Impressive.
But it appears that you've
used up all the time and magic
that you had accumulated.
I'm sure you saw my attack.
But you couldn't cancel that time spell
in order to evade.
Because...
you are the Wizard King.
The fact that you are the Wizard King...
That is your one and only weakness.
What the hell's going on here...
Vangeance?!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Please, Calm Down!
What's going on?
Is Lord Julius fighting?
What should we do?
Please, calm down.
Yes. Calm down.
It's my job to remain
calm at times like this.
There's no way Lord Julius should lose,
but if all else fails, the only ones
who could keep up in this battle are
Magic Knights Squad captains or their equals!
I need to send a message to all the
Magic Knights Squad headquarters I've marked!
Hello, you've reached the restaurant
Not Done Yet. You ordering takeout?
I'm sorry, I've called the wrong number!
This time, I'll get through to each of
the Magic Knights Squad headquarters!
Hello, you've reached the hot
springs hot spot, My Hot Station.
Do you want to make a reservation?
Wrong number!
I'll definitely get it this time!
Who the heck are you?
Um... Is this one of the
Magic Knights Squad headquarters?
Say what?! I used to be—
Damn it!
What in the world is going on?!
I can't get through to them at all!
Let's calm down a bit.
Right...
What the hell's going on here, Vangeance?!
The crime of betraying Julius's trust
and my friendship deserves death!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 94: "New Future."
Page 94
New Future
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!