It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
In the second stage of the
Royal Knights Selection Exam,
Langris's G Team won by a hair.
Finral!
Overcome with madness,
Langris tried to attack his older brother
Finral, despite the match being over.
Disappear.
But the members of the Black
Bulls came to his rescue.
Hey!
Just try and do something else.
Forget the match. We'll kill you.
Maybe you've been on a roll lately,
but you're still Black Bulls flunkies.
What do you think you'll do against
the Vice Captain of the Golden Dawn?
Who the hell cares about status when we're
trying to protect our precious friend?!
I guess making it this far
has gone to your head.
You sure talk big for a Black Bulls newbie.
Wizard King, before the next
teams conduct their match,
would you let me battle them?
Actually... Let's just start.
Let the semi-finals begin!
Sir, aren't you going to stop them?
In actual combat,
no one says "stop" or "start."
At Langris's forceful request,
the semi-final match between
B Team and G Team began immediately.
But Julius had another goal:
to bring the unconscious traitor working
with the Eye of the Midnight Sun to light.
Asta!
In order to defeat Langris,
Asta decided to take on his black form.
It's all you, Xerx!
He put his faith in a mage who called
himself Xerx and concentrated.
Yet this dumbass is actually
putting all his trust in me.
That man's true name was Zora.
Damn it.
I'm going to continue protecting everything
I can with all the power that I have.
That's what makes a Magic Knight!
Zora's father, Zara, was the first
peasant to become a Magic Knight,
but he was betrayed by his
own comrades and killed.
You people...
are not the Magic Knights
that my father dreamed of!
Burn It Into You
Begone! I am a true Magic Knight!
They got past the magic circle...
Xerx!
Congrats on landing the first
attack on me today, Lord Noble.
What?!
There's a magic circle on his body?!
What in the world is that?
He drew a magic circle on himself?
That would drain his magic power constantly.
That's extremely risky.
Exactly.
But that's apparently how he does things.
What...
...is he?
Who...
Who are you?!
I'm no one of any importance.
I was just...
born a filthy little brat in a peasant town.
And I am hopeless rage incarnate!
Take this, you Magic Knight frauds!
He deflected that spatial magic?!
And it's twice as powerful now!
You're no one of any importance...
Don't mess with me!
That spell was returned to
him twice as powerful...
And he managed to erase all of it!
Vice Captain Langris's magical
powers have grown even more!
But this power...
Sir...
Your ultimate move couldn't even scratch me!
Yet I can become even stronger!
See? I am special!
You lot and my useless brother...
I'm nothing like you!
Everything you do is useless!
It's not useless!
How dare you?!
Stop that.
Don't heal me, you royal.
I humbly decline your request.
We are on the same team.
We are both Magic Knights!
What is that form supposed to be?!
It's nothing special.
It's just what happens when
one of those peasants you make
fun of struggles for a long time!
All of you are eyesores!
Be careful not to get in the
way of my spatial magic, okay?
I can't guarantee that you
won't lose something.
If that were to happen,
Mother and Father aside,
I'm sure she'd be sad.
You're right.
So to ensure that doesn't happen,
I'm going to win!
How dare you try to stand on the
same stage as me?! I've been chosen!
I'm special!
You don't stand a chance against me!
You're right. You're amazing.
Your magic stands out even among nobles,
who all have a tremendous amount of magic.
On top of that, your spatial magic is nuts!
You were born special.
I always admired people like you!
I get to protect the country with a
bunch of amazing people like that.
Man, being a Magic Knight is awesome!
But you're different.
You're amazing, but you're different!
I'm not asking someone like you to like me.
I hate you, too!
But... don't just unfairly take things away!
You people are special,
and we competed with each other
and helped each other improve
so that we could protect everyone!
We became stronger and came this far
so that we could fight together!
Shut up!
If you didn't want to die,
you should've just kept your mouth
shut in your little hole, you failure!
Is that right? In that case,
I'll take this failed power
and burn it into you!
My magic... won't come out!
Asta...
Black Meteorite!
Shut up!
If you didn't want to die,
you should've just kept your mouth
shut in your little hole, you failure!
Is that right? In that case,
I'll take this failed power
and burn it into you!
My magic... won't come out!
Black Meteorite!
Both teams' crystals were
destroyed at the same time.
This match is a draw!
No way!
He's passed out.
He got him bah-had.
You said that the one who keeps winning
will always be right, didn't you?
You egocentric spatial magic noble.
And since you lost against a peasant,
that means you weren't
right about anything.
No one's going to acknowledge a piece of
shit like you as vice captain anymore.
You. Fluffy-hatted snow woman.
What did you do during the last match?
Did you get freaked out by the spatial magic
noble and just stand there sucking your thumb?
Must be nice!
Hey, who do you think you are?
Shut up.
Like you have any skills
to begin with, you fake.
Bah—
People like you are more
worthless than anyone else.
Just quit being a Magic Knight
already, you trash.
Hey, you little shit!
You trust people way too easily!
Not everyone is nice or amazing.
You're gonna regret it someday!
You don't have to say it like—
It looks like you try to make
the best move in every situation,
but make sure you don't stop
thinking when you hit circumstances
that go beyond what you imagined, you royal.
And...
Cool-masked jerk, you should have
had more faith in your companions.
A draw...
We didn't win.
Damn it... Damn it!
Let's fight with all we've got, together!
We're all Magic Knights
of the Clover Kingdom.
I heard it ended in a draw between
Asta and your little brother.
I'd say the Black Bulls' little star
of hope did pretty well.
He fought head-to-head with the
Vice Captain of the Golden Dawn.
And that's exactly why
you need to wake up already.
Everyone under you is taking all
the glory while you're asleep.
I did what I could for now,
but his wounds are too deep.
I need to take him to the
castle's medical tower.
Cob, if you would.
Roger-dodger-roger!
I'll go with you, too.
You're up next, you jerk.
You better win!
Of course!
Rill   Ruben   Nils
I Team
Klaus   Luck   Puli
K Team
And now, I Team: Rill, Nils, and Ruben versus
K Team: Puli, Klaus, and Luck.
We will now begin round three of stage two.
Yay! Let's give it all we've got!
But we're up against the
Captain of the Aqua Deer,
who'll wait until we've made a move,
then strike at our magic's weak points.
What should we do?
I have an idea. Wanna hear?
I can't wait to see what kind
of painting I get to make next!
If we can manage to support him, we can win.
Their magic power is being
concentrated and sharpened.
We'll use a super-fast attack
spell and nail him first
so he won't have a chance to follow up!
I'm borrowing the idea from the combo spell
the people in the first match used.
Although I think the power behind
this one is even crazier.
This isn't good!
We have to hide the crystal!
There's no point in trying to move it now.
On a field this size, we'll know
where it is, no matter where it goes.
This spell is probably
going to be insanely fast!
I'll have to paint mine first!
No matter what you try to do, it'll be useless!
This spell pierces through everything!
Compound Magic: Lightning Arrow!
No one can stop it!
I won't stop it!
Picture Magic: Game of the Gods!
I was inspired by the last match, too!
My methods are different, but I'm
going to enhance the enemy's spell...
and send it back!
Whoopsie.
The crystal has been destroyed!
I Team wins!
What the heck was that?
Th-That was insane!
The Captain of the Aqua Deer...
That was amazing! Amazing!
Rill Boismortier cannot be stopped!
I'm seeing the masterpiece in my head!
Yay!
Well, damn. That was over in a second.
No worries, la.
Luck has grown so much
during this competition.
I made sure to record all of
your progress in my diary.
Good work.
Black Bulls...
Asta is physically exhausted, so he's
resting in the infirmary down below.
I'll stay by his side,
so please, cheer on Noelle.
Ben   Brad   Eric
M Team
En   Noelle   Yuno
P Team
Next up, we have M Team: Ben, Brad, and Eric
versus P Team: En, Yuno, and Noelle.
We will now begin round four of stage two.
I have to do this for Asta, too.
I mean, we have to fight
for everyone who's lost!
That's right.
And we'll win.
Round four of stage two... begin!
Huh?
Hey, wait a second!
I don't have time to waste here.
Here he comes!
He's by himself?
He's mocking us!
Take this!
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado!
What?!
How dare you, you peasant?!
Asta, even though you lost,
you're getting right back up, aren't you?
I know how fast you've been growing.
The more frustrated you become,
the more you grow.
Th-The crystal has been destroyed.
P Team wins!
That power... What was that?
That jerk... What the hell did he do?
I wish I could've fought him, too.
La!
Yuno...
You're going to grow even more, aren't you?
Hey! Why did you take care
of this all by yourself?
Use some of my powers, too!
You're wasting my talent!
Be quiet.
Jeez! You're such a tease!
I guess I don't hate that side of you!
Next is the second round of the semi-finals.
We've finally reached the last match.
The first match of the semi-finals ended
in a draw, so I Team versus P Team,
for all practical purposes,
is the final match!
Asta...
I'm going on ahead.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Name
Name.
Zara
Zora
My real name is Zora.
My father's name is Zara.
What? That's too simple?
Who cares? You can tell we're family.
Zara
Zora
Yeah, yeah! If only I
had quintuplet siblings!
Oldest Brother
Asta
I'm Asta!
Ista.
Second Brother
Ista
Third Brother
Usta
Usta.
Fourth Brother
Esta
Esta.
Fifth Brother
Osta
Osta!
None of us have any magic,
but we'll never, ever give up!
I'm the one who's going to marry Sister Lily!
No, I am.
No, I am!
Let's fight!
We may fight sometimes, but we
quintuplets get along great!
One of you is loud enough. Who could
stand listening to five of you yapping?
You can't be serious.
The final match is finally here.
I had so much fun seeing all kinds of magic.
I wish we could keep going.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 84: " The Victors."
Page 84
The Victors
Now, I wonder which team is going to win.