It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
He's turned the tables.
Since he can use that sword, I thought
he might be their descendant, but...
Show me who you really are!
Not in the Slightest
Huh?
What is this place?
Wait, does this mean...
that I di—
Hey... No way.
I haven't married Sister yet.
And besides...
Damn...
it...
Heya.
Welcome.
Who the hell are you?!
Well, that's cold.
I've been the one closest
to you this whole time.
Nope! I definitely don't know anyone like you!
Well, whatever.
Regardless, this is a chance for
me to obtain a physical body.
So I'll be taking yours.
Hey! What's the big idea?!
Oh, come on. It's not a bad deal.
You wanna win, right?
Against that human.
I can make that happen for you.
Shut up! I'm gonna defeat
him with my own strength!
Quit yappin' and let me take
over your consciousness!
All you've got to do is pass out.
A little dwarf like you
has no chance of winning.
Don't you dare underestimate dwarfs!
Thanks for looking down on me from
all the way up there, you big lug!
Because of that, I can look
up as I run to the top!
There are places that you just can't climb.
Come on, just give up.
You can't do a thing in this world.
Just give up on everything.
You were born a loser!
Give... up?
That one time was the very last time
I'm ever going to feel depressed!
Never giving up...
is my magic!
What the?
He got back up instantly...
The three leaves of the clover
represent faith, hope, and love.
Within a fourth leaf dwells good luck.
Within a fifth leaf...
resides a demon.
This... doesn't feel like magic?
Asta?
What happened to you?
That's quite the transformation.
But what exactly are you going to do with it?!
You're not getting away!
Well, it looks like you're a bit faster now,
but let's see how long you can keep that up!
Did you really think I'd fall
for the same thing twice?!
This isn't a slight change.
Where's all this strength coming from?!
Damn you!
Now you won't be able to dodge anymore.
Huh?
Whoa, there!
What is this?
It feels like I'm in a cold lake.
It feels cool...
My mind is unbelievably clear.
And I can feel...
the power overflowing!
I thought he'd lose consciousness,
but it seems he was able to control it.
Anti-magic energy flows constantly
through the Demon-Dweller Sword,
draining the wielder's magic.
As such, no one should be able to wield it.
But since you are magicless,
that power flows through you.
You've been unconsciously emitting
and shutting off that power.
Using the power of my blood,
which I transfused during your treatment,
I accelerated the flow of power
and removed the limits on its output.
The anti-magic power will
now become a raging torrent,
and you will become its vessel.
What... the hell?
I assumed that you might be one of their kin,
but apparently I was wrong.
What is this feeling?
A sudden mutation kept
mana from dwelling in you.
You're merely defective.
But because of that,
you are able to wield that sword.
What the hell are you?
You aren't special. Not in the slightest.
But that's exactly what makes you special.
Get out of my sight!
In your presence, all magic is meaningless.
So finish him.
Damn it!
Why?!
My magic's supposed to be invincible now!
Stay back!
Get away from me! Stay away!
It's no use.
The flood of anti-magic homes in on mana.
A black shooting star...
climbing into the sky?
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit! Shit!
Why?!
I got this far by kicking everyone else down!
Why are you...
You might've kicked people down,
but everyone that helped boost me up
makes me strong!
Black Meteorite!
All the magic in my body is gone.
This can't happen to me... Not here...
I guess maybe... this really is my limit.
Lad...ros...
Asta...
He's so powerful...
The way he fought didn't
seem like Asta at all.
And the way he looks...
It's almost as if...
Kill me. I'm ready.
Like hell I'd kill you!
Right now, I'm gonna go rescue
all the people you hurt!
Hurry up and heal so you can come help me!
Then you can apologize to them all!
You're all wrinkly and bloody now, but I'm
not letting you off the hook, you jerk!
What the hell?! Are you okay?
Yeah... I can't beat that.
I feel much better now.
Uh, did your personality just change?
Well, the mage stones broke,
so my head feels a bit lighter.
Good grief...
You sure you're okay?
I guess it's guys like you
that climb to the top.
You sure you didn't go crazy?
If I'd been with you...
We might've been able to help
each other get stronger, too.
Asta, thank you.
Hey, did you fall asleep?
Hey, come on! Are you listening to me?
I guess I was worried for nothing.
He's still himself.
I'm back to normal.
What was that black stuff, anyway?
And I feel like I fought
something in my dream.
But it felt like I was able to use some
mysterious power, and that was super exciting!
I wanna master it!
I wonder if this is what it feels
like when everyone else uses magic.
I hurt all over!
I'm bleeding so much!
Oh, crap! I'm dying!
Someone save me!
What do you want?
Sorry...
No one's okay at all!
Hey, you two! You guys can
use recovery magic, right?!
Do something—Wait,
are you guys even alive?!
Oh, good! You're alive!
But you're totally not waking up!
Sorry, Mars. Am I too heavy?
No... You're actually kind
of warm, and it feels nice.
You've seriously changed, dude!
Oh, Mars...
You're ignoring me?!
Damn it! I'm gonna have
to carry you all with me!
I'll make as many trips as
I need to make! Bring it!
There's no need for that.
The Queen of Witches!
The Queen...
We took down the Eye of the Midnight Sun
and the guys from the Diamond Kingdom!
That means I paid you back
for fixing my arms!
I didn't even need to go into battle.
It was far from perfect,
but well done nonetheless.
Nah, it was nothing!
Oh, hey, so...
While we're at it...
Do you think maybe you
could heal everyone here?
Ah...
That won't be necessary.
What... is thi—
Noelle!
Blood Creation Magic:
Fresh Blood Execution Ground.
I'm sure Master and the others are fine.
You're right.
Such an ominous magical power...
You just showed up outta nowhere,
and now what the hell are you do—
Controlling blood. That is my magic.
Ever since I cast that spell on you,
I've been able to manipulate
your blood as I please.
I am a queen.
Why would I bother granting
a wish for the likes of you?
You are the one who will bend to my will.
Blood Magic: Puppet's Blood.
Asta!
That being said, I can't have you die on me.
I shall heal you, at least.
Blood Recovery Magic:
Curse-Breaking Blood-Filled Cocoon.
Stay with me, and you can
rampage all you like.
She's using one high-level
spell after another!
It's bone-chilling. This is somehow even
more terrifying than the spirits' magic!
So this is the Queen of Witches!
If I cannot hold the anti-magic
sword in my own hand,
I just need to control someone who can.
I've observed how you use it.
From now on, you'll spend your life
in my employ, working as my blade.
Th...
This can't be...
The Queen was after the anti-magic
sword this whole time?!
Now, for your first task...
I shall force you to kill everyone
here with your own two hands.
Kill every last one of them perfectly.
No... way...
So the Queen of Witches was after
Asta's anti-magic all along.
This magic... I didn't get this
old just for show, y'know!
Black Clover, Page 64:
"The Red Thread of Fate."
Page 64
The Red Thread of Fate
Vanessa! What's that magic of yours?!