It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
It's the first round of the second stage
of the Royal Knights Selection Exam.
Sol's attack left Mimosa unable to move.
Asta was forced to face off with Magna,
who came to attack their crystal on his own.
Also...
What do you think you're doing without me?
Crap! I'm not gonna be able
to take both of them on!
The one who saved Asta was a
mysterious mage named Xerx.
Attack the cherry blossom guy,
you little shit!
I'll take care of this in an instant!
And that instant's all I need!
With the help of Mimosa's plant spell that
lets her control the enemy's movements,
Asta and the rest of B Team
were able to claim victory.
And now, the destined battle between the
brothers Finral and Langris is about to begin.
Special Little Brother
vs.
Failed Big Brother
There you go.
Th-Thank you, Vanessa.
That's perfect! You look awesome!
Could you do mine, too?
You already lost, though.
It looks fine. You look like
the failure that you are.
What?! Who're you calling a failure?!
Now, now. Try to stay calm, Magna.
Like a loser should.
You bastard! I'm gonna kill you!
I'm so gonna kill you!
Good! Let's do this now!
Wait, you guys—
As I thought, that guy is a very
skilled flame magic caster.
The lightning guy is also
one to look out for.
I know.
Luck is trying to cheer him up...
La, la. Gimme more noms.
My, aren't you a hungry little one?
Marie... Marie... Always Marie.
What's going on over there?
The Black Bulls, huh?
I guess bulls will be bulls.
Come on, you guys, stop!
This is embarrassing!
Why are you so stiff?
I'm sure this next match
will be complicated for you,
given who you're up against.
Uh... Y-Yeah, I guess.
Not to mention, I've never beaten
my little brother in anything.
Don't worry.
I've fought alongside you, so I know.
You changed after meeting Asta.
The same goes for me.
I was able to face something hidden deep
within my heart that I'd been ignoring.
You're not going to lose so easily now.
Now get out there and show everyone
how cool you are. Just like your hair.
Vanessa...
You've got this, Finral!
Don't lose like Magna, and come fight me.
Yeah! Don't lose like—
The hell did you say?!
I-I'm rooting for you, too!
You've got this. You've got this. You've got this.
You've got this. You've got this. You've got this...
You'd better not embarrass
the rest of the squad.
Yeah.
Charmy... Even Gauche.
Thanks, you guys. I'm so happy
I joined the Black Bu—
Please, more noms.
I want to see Marie as soon as possible,
so win this in one second.
But I have seniority...
I'm sure Captain Yami's cheering
you on from the base, too.
Yeah. He seemed a bit antsy this morning.
He said his stomach was acting up, but...
I'm sure he just wants to see you
work hard even without his help.
Those guys must be going beyond their
limits and kicking ass right about now.
I'm kicking ass, too.
This one's gonna be a killer.
And damn it, kid! I told you to
restock the damn toilet paper!
Good grief. As if you could
actually defeat me, Brother.
Langris, I managed to change
after meeting my friends.
We'll be the ones who win this.
Whatever. Don't blame me for
whatever happens, all right?
Would you let me handle him?
I don't see why not.
A battle between brothers, eh?
I also want to fight my
brother for real one day.
I accept your passionate request!
Bah-ha!
I'm going to burn the image
of me gallantly riding
my Shooting Star into everyone's eyes!
You will not lay a single
finger on our crystal!
It's finally starting!
Now I'm getting nervous.
Finral, I know you can win this.
And now,
E Team: Leopold, Hamon, and Finral
versus G Team: Langris, Fragil, and Sekke.
Fragil
Langris
Sekke
G Team
Leopold
Finral
Hamon
E Team
Round two of stage two, begin!
You two concentrate on
destroying the enemy crystal.
Leave it to me.
Let's find out where it is.
Glass Magic: Verre Détection.
I can see every inch of this battle stage
as the light reflects off the glass.
It will take a little while, but I will
definitely be able to find the enemy's crystal.
I expect you to take me all the way
to the enemy base again, Mr. Bah-ha.
Leave it to me! Also, I'm Sekke.
Please call me Sekke.
You can even call me Sek, bah-ha.
Understood, Mr. Bah-ha.
Bah-ha. No, really, it's Sekke!
Please call me Sekke!
You brought shame upon the House of Vaude.
There's no way you can defeat me, Brother.
You see, you aren't my child.
So the only one that I love
is my dear little Langris.
Mother, it's a bit cruel to be so blunt.
What is that pathetically weak spell?
Learn from Langris's attack spells!
Goodness.
I see my dear little Langris is better
than you at both academics and sports.
You're so amazing, my dear little Langris.
As I should expect from my own child.
What are you doing, Finral?
You disgrace the Vaude name!
How pathetic. He's older than me, but there's
not one thing he can do better than me.
What? A fiancée?
Yes.
Finnes Calmreich
This is Lady Finnes, the fiancée of
the next head of the House of Vaude.
Good day to you.
Her chronic illness keeps
her from going out often,
but the king is her great uncle,
so she comes from a prestigious family
and has splendid magic.
So basically, in the future,
this woman and I will...
Ugh. What a dull-looking woman.
My dear little Langris,
make sure you get along with her.
She's going to be your bride someday.
Of course!
Seriously... When I become
the lord of this house,
I'll be able to bring us fame
like they've never seen.
Ugh... I'm so bored.
I'm very sorry that you got stuck with a
fiancée who's sickly and older than you.
N-Not at all!
You're b-b-beautiful, Miss Finnes.
It's just... I'm not the one who'll become
the next head of the House of Vaude.
Huh?
My little brother is better
at everything than me,
so he'll be able to make you happy.
His magic is amazing,
and he's a very decisive person.
I'm just a failure.
Exactly. There's not a single
thing he can beat me i—
That's not true.
Huh?
I've only met you a few times, but I can tell.
You're a very kind person.
To me, you're a much more
wonderful mage, Finral.
O-Oh, stop! D-Don't tease me like that!
Oh, but I wasn't teasing you at all.
Who do you think you are, you dull woman?
You have the nerve to call me
inferior to my brother?
Don't be ridiculous.
That loser left the family because
he couldn't handle the pressure.
He's not better than me at anything!
Not a single thing!
Bah-ha! Found it!
Here he comes. As we planned,
we'll leave him to you, Finral.
Just as a reminder...
Don't blame me if you lose any limbs.
I'll end this in a single blow!
What?!
I tested this out earlier with another
spatial magic user, Cob, and found out...
that when spatial magics collide,
the mana currents collide
and cancel each other out!
Langris, we're the ones who are going to win!
Th-That's awesome!
You can cancel out spatial
magic with spatial magic?
Way to go, Finral!
H-He's like a completely different person!
Keep it up, ya jerk!
Marie's waiting. Hurry up and win.
I get to have more yummy noms, la!
Bah-ha, ha-bah?!
Excellent work, Finral! That was effective!
Hamon, where's the enemy team's crystal?
I've finally found it!
It's deep within that tower.
All right, I'm counting on you two!
Th-This isn't good, bah-ha!
Who do you think you are, Brother?
I'll remind you of your place!
Give it up!
You came in.
This is...
Snow Magic: Phantom Snow Garden.
This spell forces your senses to sleep.
You cannot attack me effectively any longer.
I'm not tired at all... This is nothing!
Especially compared to my older sister's
training, which could leave you dead!
Honestly, you still have much to learn.
Yeah! You're so valiant, Hamon!
I can still eat plenty...
You're talking about yourself?!
You should give up and fall asleep, too.
This is...
I swore upon the symbol on my forehead...
that I would surpass my brother someday!
And that means I can't lose in a place like this!
Concentrate!
Mana Skin!
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
His senses are sharp!
He enveloped himself in mana
and canceled my spell.
More! I need to concentrate more!
I won't last much longer, Langris.
Bah-ha!
A spatial magic battle!
You don't see that every day!
Ah, so that is Finnes's fiancé, Langris.
Not bad at all.
He's still no match for me, though.
Keep it up, Finral!
It's only a matter of time before
their crystal is destroyed!
I never thought you'd become
my natural enemy, Brother.
Do you plan on defending
until our crystal breaks?
I'm not sure that'll be so easy!
It might not be. That's why...
I'm going to use a new spell!
Bah-ha! What in the world is that slow spell?
Like you could hit my badass self right now!
What? Homing?
That's no match for my invincible
Sekke Magnum Cannonball!
H-He disappeared?!
This is pretty pathetic, even for me.
I trained so hard, but I never
could learn a single attack spell.
It's not an attack spell?
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel's Wingbeat.
It follows the enemy,
and once it makes contact,
it transports them to another location.
It's the applied version of
the spell I usually use.
This way, he can get rid of
enemies without hurting them!
He must be a kind soul.
You're so awesome, Finral!
B-But where did he go?
It just went back in. Can I kill you now?
Bah-ha... I'm dead.
Langris, it's only a matter of time
before your crystal is destroyed.
I don't want to hurt you!
If you insist on continuing, I'll have
to use this spell to make you leave.
Who are you worried about?
You constantly get on my nerves, Brother.
Who would've thought that our special
reserve spells would be similar?
How dare you make me use my grimoire's magic?!
There isn't a single thing
you can beat me at, Brother!
Th-This ominous feeling...
I've felt this somewhere before!
Th-This mana...
This is...
This doesn't feel very pleasant.
As I figured...
It's over, Brother!
Langris!
Th-This immense magical power...
I already know I don't stand a chance.
But this is...
This nauseating magic is like...
Who are you?
Finral!
If that attack hits him...
Run!
No. He's Langris.
He's my little brother.
You may not like it, but we're similar.
Our mothers are different, but in the end...
I never did anything that made
me seem like a big brother.
I left our family and tried
to forget everything.
But I just couldn't.
Langris, no matter what you think...
You're my little brother!
Langris, stop it! If you keep this up,
I have a feeling you won't be you anymore!
What could you possibly
know about me, Brother?
You left everything behind!
You're a coward who can't even hurt people!
Don't you dare try to act
like my big brother now!
I'll stop you!
Finral!
G-G Team wins!
How do you like that?
There's nothing you can beat me at!
Young Master Finral is so friendly and kind,
isn't he? He has a lot of friends, too.
Young Master Langris is... Well, it's obvious
that he looks down on people, you know?
To me, you're a much more
wonderful mage, Finral.
Even I want someone that kind to...
Langris!
Working too hard all the time
hurts after a while, doesn't it?
Come goof off with your
big brother once in a while!
There's a festival going on nearby!
Why is he nice to me, too?
Stop it.
Learn from Langris!
My dear little Langris is so amazing.
I'm better than you are. That's why
Mother and Father are kind to me.
I have to beat him at everything!
Otherwise, I'll... I'll...
Hey, the match is over.
Wh-What's he doing?
Disappear.
Finral!
These wounds are awful.
At this rate...
Hey!
Just try and do something else.
Forget the match. We'll kill you.
You bastard...
How dare you do that to Finral?!
Th-This is too awful!
You actually pissed me off.
I won't forgive you!
Oh?
There's something wrong with you!
The match was already over!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Hairstyle
Hairstyle.
That new spell is awesome!
Fallen Angel's Weightlifting!
That's Fallen Angel's Wingbeat.
I mean, I know when I need to get tough.
It's the result of trying different things.
So is your new hairstyle also
from trying different things?
Oh, really?
Huh? Wait, no...
I'm sure you tried out a regent pompadour.
As well as Captain Yami's hairstyle.
And soft serve hair, la!
That's poo—
This looks pretty strong!
If you do Marie's hairstyle, I'll kill you.
I-I like this hairstyle.
I think this one is better.
I-It's just a better option, that's all.
How about something a bit more mature?
This is the hairstyle for when
you go beyond your limits!
Uh, seriously...
I wanted to see this
hairstyle on you, Finral!
When it comes to me in this series,
my hair should be the least of your worries!
Praise me!
Your daring and resolute king presents...
Next time on Black Clover, Page 81:
"The Life of a Certain Man."
Page 81
The Life of a Certain Man
Praise me!