It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The forces of the Eye of the Midnight
Sun attacked the Witches' Forest.
They were after the magic stone
that lies in the forest.
At the same time, the forces of the Diamond
Kingdom also attacked the Witches' Forest.
They wanted to take advantage of the chaos
and steal the Queen of Witches' secret.
Fanzell, a former officer in
the Diamond Kingdom's army,
ended up facing two of his
former students, Mars and Ladros.
Million Lasers!
Don't... You should be using your
powers to do the right thing...
Getting to use your power to the max in
combat... What could be better than that?
You see, I want to be acknowledged.
By this country! By this world!
Guess I'll just have to kill this chick first!
Don't!
My powers... exist to protect others.
Your lessons got through to me.
Mars managed to turn the
tables at the last moment.
Fanzell was troubled because
he thought there was no way to defeat
Ladros's absorption and emission power,
but he and Mars came up with a plan.
What are you gossiping about over there?
No matter what plan you come up with,
it'll be useless against my power!
I'm not half bad at
reinforcement magic myself.
Have a nice trip!
The Promised World
We have you completely surrounded!
So just give up already!
If you do something stupid, your parents
and friends back home will be sad!
You filthy humans... Don't you
dare speak of my friends!
She still has that much magic left?!
Oh, damn it!
Those flames...
There! They're right over there!
This overwhelming amount of magic...
It's Salamander!
This magic...
In that situation, Asta's not going
to have any time to deal with Ladros!
No, wait a sec...
Come on, Teach! Mars! Wait up!
A little reinforcement magic
won't help you win against me!
And you'll never win if
you keep running away!
Here you go! Million Lasers!
Asta!
Old Man Zell!
Wait, you're with the pale guy?!
Asta!
Deflect it over here!
I don't know what's going on, but okay!
I'll get us out of the way using the wind
and aim the fire right at...
Hey... This is way too big!
Did it work?
Ladros's magical powers disappeared.
Hey! Old Man Zell!
What the heck's going on here?!
Something just fell!
Well done, Asta.
I see you've grown even stronger.
Aw, shucks. It's nothing.
No, wait! Why are you with the pale guy?!
He's an enemy!
Asta, was it?
I am not your enemy. Trust me.
How am I supposed to believe a
guy with an evil face like yours?!
And my name is Mars, you shrimp.
Wait, your mouth's nasty now, too!
I'll explain everything later.
Huh?
For now, I'd like you to trust Mars.
Well, if you say so.
Thanks. Now, then...
I think Ladros has been taken
care of for now, thanks to Asta.
So we need to do something
about this monster.
So that's the fire spirit Salamander
that I've heard so much about.
It appears to be weakened, but it
still has tremendous magical powers.
But those flames... They're the same as mine?
And this magic itself feels like...
Fa...na...
We have no family...
so we have no other choice...
But...
Mars, is the training painful?
N-No, it's not.
When things get rough,
remember the faces of those you love.
We were born to protect the people
of this kingdom that we love so much.
The faces of those you love...
The face that popped into my
head immediately... was yours,
Fana.
Once we become strong enough
to protect this kingdom,
we'll be allowed to go outside.
You'll probably make it out first, Mars.
Lucky.
I mean, you're the strongest
out of all of us, Mars.
I'll be waiting for you when that happens.
Huh?
Until you get out, too, Fana.
Sure! Let's go see the
outside world together.
This is your final test.
Kill each other.
The sole survivor will be allowed to go
outside as our kingdom's mage warrior.
If you refuse, you'll all be disposed of.
I'm sorry, Mars.
Fana...
I have no other choice.
Please die.
Why...
Why?
My wounds...
If I didn't do that, you wouldn't have...
tried to kill me...
Make sure you go see the world outside.
For me... as well.
Fana!
I thought I killed her with my own hands...
But Fana's alive?!
Fana!
Hey!
It's me! It's me!
Don't you recognize me?
H-H-Hey! Wait, wait, wait!
You're going to die, die, die!
Were you always like this?!
Fana!
You know each other?!
Fana! Fana!
He—
Fana!
Fana?
My student Fana?
After I left, I heard she died in
Morris's human experiments.
Fana!
I don't know you!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
It really is Fana...
But is that transformation magic?
No... there'd be no point in that.
Or there shouldn't be.
That eye is emitting a strange power...
Is it someone's spell?
Is the Eye of the Midnight Sun
controlling Fana with that eye?
What... is this? My head is...
Fana!
Why do all of you insist
on getting in my way?
I hate you!
That's...
Gah! More self-destruct magic?!
I'm taking you all down with me... No...
I'll blow this whole temple to smithereens!
Self-destruct?
What's wrong with those people?!
Do they all come with that option installed?!
This isn't good! In a few minutes,
this whole area's going to be blown away!
Everything should just... disappear.
Sea Dragon's Lair!
Mars, no!
What the hell are you doing?!
Block it with your magic!
Master, I have no right to block it!
I killed Fana! I can't—
This is seriously not the time for that!
Are you stupid?! Do you wanna die?!
I don't know the details,
but do you really know her?
She's a leader in a terrorist group
called the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
Are you sure she's not just similar-looking?
Dude, she's got three eyes!
I would never mistake Fana!
She's my precious childhood friend!
Is that right?
Then...
If she's so important to you,
now's really no time for you to be dying!
Live and save her for real!
You're right. I'm sorry.
Were you always this up-front?
Not only does Asta yell at me,
but now he's yelling at you, his senior.
It's all right, Mars.
You'll be able to save her!
Neither Finral's spatial magic nor my
thread magic work against those flames.
And if we agitate it with Noelle's water
magic, it might explode immediately!
I knew it. Only Asta's
anti-magic sword can stop it!
All right, let's do this!
Asta!
When we fought the hairy gorilla...
It's no use...
You humans shall taste despair... Despair!
My power couldn't stop him, but...
Back then, I ended up killing her, but...
This time...
...I'm not...
...letting anyone die!
Stay away from me!
Mineral Creation Magic: Laevateinn!
They're both amazing!
High-powered flame magic even
at that range isn't fazing them!
Still, they have only a few minutes left.
Will they make it in time?
I'll charge in until she's in my sword's
range and dispel that self-destruct spell!
This heat is insane!
If we go any further,
we'll end up as charcoal!
Asta?
No, that's...
You...
Flame Recovery Magic: Phoenix Robe.
You good to go?
Heck, yeah!
So long as I don't turn into charcoal,
I can go as far as you want me to!
This guy's amazing.
After I fought him in the dungeon, I battled
against many other skilled fighters,
Not yet! I'm not done yet!
but I've never met anyone
who's this bad at giving up.
And... he's also strange.
Even now, he's still not sure whether I'm friend or foe, but he's still talking to me
and trying to help.
I've fought many of the Magic Knights,
but no one has tried as hard to
protect and help people as he does.
He embodies the title in the
truest sense of the term.
He is...
a real knight!
Hey, are you all right?
I'm fine!
This pain can't even begin
to compare to Fana's!
This guy's completely different
from when I first fought him.
He was like a killer doll back then.
I didn't know he had such warm feelings.
Enormous, polished power,
and an unbreakable determination
to save someone...
Right now, he's indestructible!
It's going to blow any second now!
You guys should evacuate!
They believe in their friend
and refuse to move.
I'll believe in those two as well,
and see this through.
Go forth, my students.
You can do this!
Just...
...a little more.
Fana!
It's all over.
No... Not yet!
I won't let it end!
H-He did it!
Ack! Hot, hot, hot! Hot, hot, hot!
It's gone.
It is not gone.
Our hatred will never go away!
Not—
Fana, it's me! It's me!
I'm really, truly sorry!
Back then, I didn't have the
strength to fight alongside you!
Please forgive me!
You're a girl, Fana. You shouldn't
push yourself too hard.
I'll be waiting for you when that happens.
Until you get out, too, Fana.
Why... Why?!
Only that human knows where we live!
He... He must've betrayed us!
We've met in the outside world,
but nothing's started yet!
Let's...
Let's go see the
outside world together.
Let's go see the world together!
Okay.
It's a promise, Mars.
Yeah, Fana.
Mars?
Oh, goodness.
What a relief.
I'm so jealous!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Leave It to Mars
Leave It to Mars.
Hey, Mars. Tell me what happened after
you defeated me all those years ago.
Ow!
I'm sorry I defeated you.
Ahem...
Ta-da! Look at this grimoire!
Wait, is half of this mine?
Yes! It's a grimoire with your powers in it!
I can feel you all the time!
Wow... That's a little scary.
Ow!
Th-The mage scholar Morris made this!
I was brainwashed by Morris.
They modified my body,
and I fought as I was commanded.
But then I regained my memories
after fighting Asta.
And ever since, Fana,
I've been saving lives in secret between
missions as my way of atoning to you!
I'm a good boy, right?
Yes, you're a very good boy.
You may have defeated me,
but you're a good boy.
Ow!
I'm so jealous... No, envious!
No, no. I'm older here, so I
have to act like I don't care.
I am older than Mars, right?
Congratulations, Mars and Fana.
I wish you happiness.
Black Clover, Page 62:
"Those Who Boost Each Other Up."
Page 62
Those Who Boost Each Other Up
No, wait! I am jealous!