It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
With the guidance of the ten elves
known as the Apostles of Sephira,
the border between this world and
the next that lay inside Clover Castle,
the Shadow Palace, appeared.
When we put the final magic stone
in its pedestal inside the palace,
the elves' reincarnation
will be complete!
In exchange, the souls of the
humans who owned these bodies
will be sent to the underworld!
So basically, there's a magical
space spreading over there.
Well, why don't we head on over?
We will not let you get in the
way of the Apostles of Sephira!
It's just one thing after another...
Give us a break already, damn it!
The ones who arrived during
this time of crisis were...
That's...
Everyone!
Are you okay?!
A stupidly huge... bull?
What kind of entrance was that?
Welcome, you dumbasses!
Curse you, humans! It doesn't
matter how many of you show up!
You're no match for us elves!
It looked as though the tables had turned
thanks to Asta and the others, but...
Oh, come on. Don't tell me this ki is...
Isn't that...
The Captain of the Coral Peacocks,
Dorothy Unsworth?!
Dream Magic: Glamour World.
Dorothy Unsworth,
the Captain of the Coral Peacocks,
had also reincarnated as an elf.
She used her magic to teleport Vanessa
and the others into the dream world.
The Eyes in the Mirror
La! La!
Wow! Where are we?
I can't see too well without my glasses,
but it looks fun!
What the heck is this weird place?
This must be the magic of the
Captain of the Coral Peacocks.
Rouge wasn't able to evade it because
she couldn't identify it as an attack spell.
This is amazing!
I think this is one of the most
powerful spells a single mage can produce!
Now's not the time to be so happy!
This place goes on forever.
I don't think there's an end to it.
Huh?! Like that's even possible,
Luck, you dumbass!
It's probably more possible
than you ever not being stupid.
The hell did you say?!
Making the impossible possible is
what happens here in the Glamour World.
Welcome...
to the world where I control everything.
The bed just...
Everything...
is as I wish it to be.
S-S-S-S-Some kind of strange
creature just appeared!
And it just keeps getting bigger.
I wonder if it tastes good.
So you have...
absolutely no chance
of winning.
You can sleep forever now.
How dare it try to eat us instead?!
I thought we died, damn it!
The result changed?
So that magic really does
have to do with logic.
That cat really is amazing!
You're not one of the Black Bulls.
If you stray too far, her magic
won't affect you, so be careful.
I see! So it just works on your teammates!
I guess there'd have to be
limits on a spell this amazing!
Dream magic and thread magic...
These two witches are absolutely amazing!
I wanna research them so bad!
Uh, I think she's bad news.
You think so?
Here! Once you've used magic,
eat up so you can recover mana!
That magic's amazing, too!
You're not a witch, are you?
Nope. I just like to eat lots.
An inexhaustible magic supply
and absolute evasion...
This is not going to be easy.
If this ridiculous place is magic, too,
then we can get outta here if we beat her.
Looks like it.
Useless.
I wonder if she can use any magical attribute!
I wonder what her limits even are!
This is so much fun!
Who the hell cares?! This isn't fun at all!
Actually, what are we even supposed
to do? She's basically invincible.
Your magic's not that interesting.
The hell did you just say?! Huh?!
Wanna fight me?
This is no time to be playing around!
Yeah!
I'm the cornerstone of our defense,
and Charmy's vital to mana recovery.
We can't both stay stuck here.
We have to hurry back to everyone.
But...
All I can do is make sure we
evade with Rouge's magic.
Okay, time to recover your mana, la.
Eat, eat, eat, Vanessa!
Hooray, hooray, Vanessa!
You can do it, appetite!
I'm going to slap all of you
if I get fat from this!
There has to be some kind of
limit to her healing abilities.
An ever-flowing pool of water
that happens to have blade-fish
perpetually spawning from it...
A never-ending barrage of attacks...
My noms!
Th-That's not good!
Water, eh?
Say, lightning boy, could you
attack that pool of water?
I don't think I can destroy
something that big, though.
That's fine. Just give it your all!
Lightning Magic: Thunderbolt Destruction!
Aw, it didn't work after all.
Okay, now you attack, fire protozoan.
Who're you calling a fire
protozoan, you dumbass?!
Oh, just shoot it with
everything you've got already.
Who the hell do you think I am?!
If I guessed correctly and
that really is water...
It'll explode!
Yay! Look at that intensity!
Wh-What just happened?
I used electricity to chemically decompose
water, then set fire to what was left.
Huh?
Simply put, if you unleash lightning
magic and flame magic on water,
you can create an explosion big
enough to destroy a mountain.
Wh-Wh-What were you thinking,
making us do something that dangerous?!
Who cares? You can use the cat to evade.
I'll try this with Noelle's magic next!
That experiment made a
few other things clear, too.
First, what she's generating are
actual objects she visualized.
That means real-world
principles work on them, too!
Nom! This is a real fish!
Second, because of that,
she can't manipulate
the spells we cast and the resulting phenomena.
That's true. Otherwise, that explosion and
Rouge's ability to manipulate
fate wouldn't have worked.
And...
Third, it's still going to
be really hard to beat her.
There's no end to this!
We need to hurry up and find a way outta here!
You don't have that kind of time.
Charmy?!
I'm... I'm so sleepy...
H-Hey! What the hell are you talking about?!
This ain't no time for... sleep...
Uh-oh...
Yeah, this is...
It appears you couldn't evade the drowsiness.
Everything that exists in Glamour World
will eventually get drowsy.
And those who fall asleep
will never awaken again.
Who do you think I am?!
I managed to stay awake even during
all of Mister Yami's all-nighters!
This is bad. At this rate...
But I don't know what we can do!
Sink slowly into the sleep of death,
unable to do anything within this space.
Aw, everything that was already
blurry is getting even blurrier.
Not having my glasses seriously sucks.
Oh, yeah!
Hey!
Do you know what these are? The answer is...
Glasses!
Uh, what the hell are you talking about?
Now's not the time for—
Yay!
What?!
Wh-What just...
What just happened?!
Everything in this world
happens as she sees fit.
So things that she visualized
in her head appeared.
So...
What this world needs... is an
exit, exit, exit! Make one, please?
It's hard to not think of something once
your mind has already visualized it.
Hell yeah! She's only
invincible in this world!
If we can escape it,
we can figure something out.
What the hell's going on?
We keep seeing the same
stuff no matter how far we go.
We can't even find any walls, let alone Licht.
And this faint ki I feel... Is it...
Looks like someone's
magic is making us get lost.
Guess you noticed it,
too, you beanpole weirdo.
Right back at you, meathead.
They've got some nerve hiding.
I wanna slash them up already!
I'll take care of them.
No, I'm gonna slash them up.
Uh, I found them first.
What are you talking about? I was first!
It was me!
Ugh, you're such a pain in the ass!
The early bird slashes the worm!
You're right there!
Hey, where are you slashing?
The enemy's over there.
What?! They're right over there!
Besides, you didn't even hit them.
Well, neither did you!
Ugh, whatever! I'm done with you!
That's my line, you stupid meathead!
You useless beanpole!
Go over there!
No, you!
Yikes! That was close.
Though they were technically both
correct in my warped space.
Thank goodness I rolled a six
in order to keep them busy.
The higher the number with dice magic,
the more effective it is
in the situation at hand.
I won't let anyone get in the way
of the Apostles of Sephira.
I would appreciate it if
these two would keep quiet
for just a while longer.
I-I-I can't keep this up anymore!
Their overall magic power
is way higher than ours.
I... am... going... to...
reach... my... limit... soon...
Why not give up already, humans?
Not yet!
We're not done yet!
Right!
What should I do? Think!
If I can get into my black form...
But I don't even have a chance to do that.
Asta... Everyone...
I hate that all we can do is watch.
Big Brother...
Yeah. It looks like we're gonna keep
Licht and the others waiting a bit longer.
Eclat, we're going to do that.
Okay.
Here we go.
Huh?
Asta!
This is... the spell Gauche
used to evade attacks.
Right this way, kid.
Licht's Demon-Destroyer Sword severs
the cause-and-effect relationships around it.
He has the ability to nullify Eclat's
eye magic, so I'll get rid of him first.
Look at me.
Nope!
Can you evade attacks with your eyes closed?
I can evade using ki!
Well, in that case... How about this?
That many... This definitely isn't good!
Asta!
This time, it's our turn...
...t-t-t-to save him!
Go!
I'm gonna rip right through
that in an instant.
What?
Now I can fight!
You're mine!
You...
...looked at me.
The magic item in his left eye...
Crap!
I've had enough of you, brat.
I'll wipe out every last speck of you
so you can't fight us again.
I can't undo the binding spell in time.
Asta!
M-My magic can't reach that high!
Well, see ya.
Asta!
Poison Magic: Violett Schirm!
Transformation Magic...
Magic Conversion: Poison to Mirror!
Thank you very much!
Not bad.
As we thought... Gauche is way
stronger than usual right now.
But...
Move!
The three of us can do this.
I can still figh—
Henry!
A-A-A-Are you okay?
Of... course... I... am!
Magic... please hold out just a little longer.
Just a little longer!
Just like many mages reinforce
themselves by using magic,
Henry uses his magic to keep himself alive.
His blood vessels, muscles, and basically
all of his organs are very frail.
He cannot stay alive unless he
continually uses magic to reinforce them.
What he'd been given was
a constitution that absorbed magical power.
The ability to absorb
magical powers from others.
Despite being born into a renowned
noble family, his body was just too frail,
and his family... the world could
not accept him for what he was.
How can this be?
If we continue to harbor that creature,
it'll disgrace the great name of Legolant.
But he's our child!
I know that!
This is for our family.
It was the warped love of high society.
The only thing Henry's parents gave him
was a house in the forest that stored up
magic power while remaining
unseen by others.
This is how it should be.
I just cause everyone trouble.
Are you the resident ghost that
everyone keeps talking about?
Well... I'm... not...
actually... a... ghost.
Heya, I'm Yami Sukehiro.
I just became a Magic Knights
Squad captain recently,
and I'm looking for a hideout.
Up until that moment, I was basically dead.
I need you to live.
But... I...
Basically, you just need a lively bunch
of people to live here, right?
My house became the hideout of the
Black Bulls, and up until that moment...
I was...
The only reason I have my
life now is because of them.
That's why I don't care what happens to me!
He managed to get through Eclat's binding.
I'm gonna stop you two, no matter what,
and turn you back into the
normal Gauche and Marie!
Yes. I'm going to save him, no matter what.
I don't care what happens to me.
I'm going to save my friend!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
You Saw
You Saw.
I'm gonna stop you two, no matter what,
and turn you back into the
normal Gauche and Marie!
I'm Droit.
I'm Eclat.
We're never turning back.
But... I do want to know a little
more about this human named Gauche.
This doll that looks just like Eclat
that I had when I reincarnated...
It's just too cute.
And these pictures of her
in different outfits...
He's got such good taste!
This guy knows what he's doing!
Big Brother?
O-Oh, I was just...
Marie's doll and pictures!
You saw...
I did.
I can't move...
Next... time... on... Black... Clover,
Page... 112: "Humans Who Can Be Trusted."
Page 111
Humans Who Can Be Trusted
It's... my... job... to...
save... my... friends.