It all began in China, in Qingqing City.
There was news that a baby
that gave off light was born.
Ever since then, superpowers
were discovered in various places,
and time passed without
the cause being identified.
The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos,
the profession that everyone
once dreamed about and admired
came into the limelight.
That profession is...
It's fine now. Why?
Because I am here.
He's so cool!
Once I get my Quirk, I
wanna be like him, too!
"But..."
I'm sorry, Izuku!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I was born without a Quirk.
I was Quirkless.
Even if I wanted to be like him, I couldn't.
That's right. I had to give up on my dream.
But my arm kept reaching
out desperately for that dream,
and thanks to the people who
guided me and keep supporting me,
I am here now.
My dream is becoming reality.
Even the setbacks in the process are real.
I'll say it again.
This is the story
of how I became the greatest hero.
This is a follow-up report on yesterday's
incident at the U.A. rescue training facility
where hero course students
were attacked by villains.
"Follow-Up Report: U.A. High School Attack"
According to police investigation, the criminals
call themselves "The League of Villains"
"At the scene -
Unforeseen Simulation Joint (USJ)"
and have been plotting to kill All Might,
who has been a teacher
at U.A. since spring of this year.
Police have arrested 72 villains,
but they still do not know
the whereabouts of their ringleader.
"Greetings. It feels like summer
is just around the corner.
As for you, sir, I hope
that this letter finds you well.
Since spring, I have been
a teacher at U.A. High School
and have taken on the task
of guiding the next generation.
I thought to find someone worthy
to inherit my power among
the most promising students
aiming to become heroes.
However, before I took up
my post at U.A., I met a young man.
Even though this young man had no Quirk,
he rushed toward the scene
in a situation where pro heroes,
including myself, hesitated,
using what power he had to try
to find a way out of the situation.
He may not have had a
plan in mind at the time.
Even so, he ran.
I feel like I relearned from that young man
the essence of what a hero must have
in order to be worthy to be a hero.
That is why I told him,
'You can become a hero.'
I proposed to transfer my own Quirk to him.
The power cultivated by one person,
who passes it on to another person,
who also cultivates it and passes it on.
The crystallization of
power that spins together
the voices of those who need
help with a courageous heart--
One For All.
The young man inherited
my power without hesitation
and underwent training to be accepted
into the hero course at U.A. High School.
Even as he struggled with his new Quirk,
he kept giving his all to make it his own.
I'm proud of him.
I don't like to toot my own horn,
but I do not regret passing
on One For All to him at all.
However, I am still
inexperienced as a teacher.
The day may come when
I must trouble you, my old teacher.
I am counting on you when that time comes.
"Sincerely yours, --Toshinori Yagi"
Please take care of yourself
as the seasons change.
I will continue to keep you
updated on my circumstances.
Sincerely yours."
The boy acknowledged by Toshinori, huh?
"Episode 14: That's the Idea, Ochaco"
The police have investigated the group
calling themselves "The League of Villains,"
and there does not appear to be
anyone registered with the name Shigaraki
in his 20s or 30s with a Quirk that
lets him disintegrate whatever he touches.
It's the same with the villain
called Kurogiri with the Warp Gate.
They are probably not citizens
and are using false names.
In other words, they are people
with unregistered Quirks
who are part of society's underbelly.
You mean, we don't know anything...
We must hurry.
Once their ringleader, Shigaraki's gun
wounds heal, they'll definitely try again.
It'll be a pain.
Their ringleader, huh?
What is it, All Might?
It was a bold attack that normal people
wouldn't carry out even if they thought of it.
To suddenly go on and on
with his wild statements like that...
Although he didn't reveal his own Quirk,
he bragged about that Nomu's Quirk...
And when things didn't go the way
he wanted, he was visibly upset.
Well, the incident with the Quirk
was to also force my hand, but...
Even so, it was foolish to throw
away the advantage of having unknown Quirks
when fighting against heroes.
He made immature,
wild statements with a straight face.
He bragged about his possessions.
He thought everything
would simply go his way.
Adding that to what I saw of him
when he carried out the attack,
the picture I get of Shigaraki is...
...someone who hasn't gotten rid
of his childish sense of omnipotence--
A man-child.
A child with power?
Could it be that he never received
the Quirk counseling every child
gets in elementary school?
Well, what does that have
to do with anything?
There were 72 villains
arrested the other day at USJ.
They were all small-timers
that lurked in back alleys.
But the problem is how they all agreed
with that man-child and followed him.
In the current environment
saturated with heroes,
villainous people who have been oppressed
may be drawn to that kind
of simple-minded evil.
That's true.
There are plenty of people who don't
know what to do with their Quirks.
This is alarming, though...
Well, it's thanks to you heroes
that we are able to devote
ourselves to our investigation.
We'll expand our search network and
continue to assist in arresting the perpetrators.
A man-child...
In some sense, he's like our students.
He still has room to grow.
If there was someone capable backing him,
trying to cultivate his malice...
I don't want to think
about what could happen...
The day after the
League of Villains attacked USJ,
school was closed temporarily,
but it was hard to take it easy.
Can you see that?
He's already saved a hundred people!
That's crazy! It hasn't
even been ten minutes!
That's crazy!
He's laughing!
It's fine now. Why?
Because I am here.
What I aspire to be seems so out of reach...
During the USJ incident, the villains just
toyed with us with their malice and strength.
We just slowed down Mr. Aizawa and Thirteen.
In order to oppose that evil,
I must make this power that
I inherited from All Might, One For All,
more and more my own.
Because time is of the essence...
Because I'm the one who inherited it...
Izuku...?
Yes?
The food's ready.
Thanks, I'll be right there.
Today, we're having pork cutlet bowls!
Hey, did you watch the news last night?
Yeah.
Did you see how everyone
in class was on-screen for a second?
I didn't stand out at all...
That's true.
It's hard to stand out
looking like that, huh?
But man, all the channels
made a big deal out of it.
I was surprised.
Can you blame them?
The hero course that keeps
pumping out pro heroes was attacked.
Who knows what would've happened
if the teachers hadn't come when they did.
Stop that, Sero!
Just thinking about it's
making me wet myself--
Shut up! Be quiet, scum!
But man, All Might was great.
He pushed back those crazy strong villains.
Yes, his strength is worth wondering at.
Everyone! Morning homeroom is about to start!
Stop talking and take your seats!
We're already in our seats.
You're the only one who's not.
Shoot!
Don't worry about it.
Tsu, who's...
...gonna teach homeroom today?
Well, Mr. Aizawa is supposed to be in
the hospital recovering from his injuries...
Ribbit?
Morning.
Mr. Aizawa, you're back too soon!
You're too much of a pro!
So you're all right, Mr. Aizawa?
Can you really call that "all right"?
My well-being doesn't matter.
More importantly, the fight is not yet over.
Fight?
Don't tell me...
The villains again...?!
The U.A. sports festival is drawing near.
That's a super normal school event!
The sports festival!
That's a super normal school event--
Wait a minute.
Is it okay to have a sports festival
so soon after the villains snuck inside?
What if they attack us again or something...?
Apparently, they think of it as U.A. showing
that our crisis management system
is solid as a rock by holding the event.
Security will also be strengthened
to five times that of previous years.
Above all, our sports
festival is a huge chance.
It's not an event to be cancelled
because of a few villains.
But that's a good reason, isn't it?
It's just a festival of sports.
Mineta, you've never
seen the U.A. sports festival?
Of course I have.
That's not what I meant!
Our sports festival is
one of Japan's biggest events.
In the past, the Olympics
were called a festival of sports,
and the whole country was crazy about them.
As you know, with reductions
in scale and population,
they're now a shell of their former glory.
And now, for Japan, what has
taken the place of those Olympics
is the U.A. sports festival!
Of course, all the top heroes
around the country will be watching.
For scouting purposes!
I know that.
"Receive Certification"
After we graduate, it's typical
to join a pro agency as a sidekick.
"Pro Agency"
"Sidekick (Partner)"
A lot of people miss their chance
to become independent after that
and become eternal sidekicks, though.
Kaminari, I feel like you'd be one of them.
Since you're dumb.
Of course, joining a famous hero agency
will get you more experience and popularity.
Time is limited.
If you expect to go pro, then the path
to your future will open up at this event.
One chance a year--
a total of just three chances.
No aspiring heroes can
afford to miss this event.
If you understand that,
then don't slack off on your preparations!
Yes, sir!
Homeroom is dismissed.
"Lunchtime"
Even though all that stuff happened,
I'm getting really excited!
If we put on a good show and stand out,
we'll have taken the first
step to becoming a pro!
It was worth coming to U.A.!
We will only receive a few chances.
We cannot afford to miss this.
Ojiro, I'm getting kind of nervous now.
I need to stand out at the sports festival!
--Hip, hip, hooray!
--Y-Yeah...
But the pros might not
notice you unless you try really hard...
Oh dear, what'll I do?
I stand out just by standing still,
so the scouts won't be able
to stop looking at me, right?
Right?
You're lucky, Shoji.
Your brawn stands out on its own.
There's no point if I cannot
show them my usefulness.
I think you'll stand out, too.
"*Used his Quirk too much."
Everyone's so into it.
You're not?
We have enrolled here to become heroes,
so of course we would get fired up!
Iida, you have a unique
way of getting fired up.
It's weird.
Midoriya, you don't feel the same?
Of course I do.
But something's...
Deku, Iida...
Let's do our best at the sports festival.
U-Uraraka, your face...! It's...
What's the matter?
You don't look carefree at all,
even though that's what your name means.
PM--
Everyone, I'm gonna do my best!
Yeah!
I'm gonna do my best!
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong?
Your personality's all over the place.
Now that I think about it...
--Everyone, I'm gonna do my best!
--I never asked Uraraka...
"Lunch Rush's Eatery"
"Cafeteria"
Uraraka.
Yes?
Why did you decide to come
to U.A. and become a pro hero?
Huh? Um... because...
For money?!
You want to become a hero for money?
To boil it down simply, yes...
Sorry it's such an unwholesome reason.
You two have such admirable
motivations, it's embarrassing...
Why? How is having a goal to
support your livelihood not admirable?
Right. But it's unexpected.
My family owns a construction company,
but we haven't gotten any
work at all, so we're flat broke.
This isn't really something
to tell other people, though...
Construction...
With her Quirk, if she gets licensed,
then it'd bring costs way down, right?
She could make any raw material float.
They wouldn't need any heavy equipment.
Right? That's what I told
Dad when I was little!
But...
You want to work for us?
Yeah! When I get big,
I'll help you and Mommy!
I appreciate the thought, Ochaco.
But as your dad, I'd be even happier
if you could achieve your dream.
When that happens,
you can take us to Hawaii!
Daddy...
I'll definitely become a hero and make money
and let my parents take it easy.
Bravo!
Uraraka, Bravo!
--Bravo! Uraraka
--She's not just aspiring to be a hero.
She's also taken reality into consideration.
Young Midoriya is here!
All Might?
What's the matter?
Lunch!
Wanna eat together?
He's like a maiden!
How about it?
I'd love to.
I wonder what's going on...
"Lunch Rush's Eatery"
I wonder what he wanted with Deku.
I heard that when All Might was
attacked by villains during the USJ incident,
he rushed out alone to help.
Perhaps it's about that?
"I see!"
Oh, yeah!
Remember what Asui said on the bus?
Your Quirk is like All Might's.
The boundless power
they both have are similar, too,
so maybe All Might has taken a liking to him.
He's amazing.
All Might... and Izuku Midoriya...
"Lounge"
"In use"
Only about fifty minutes?!
Yeah...
That's the limit to how long
I can use my power now.
I overdid it too many times.
That Nomu was also a tough opponent.
And it hurt...
I can just barely maintain muscle
form for 1.5 hours now.
About that...
Sorr--
You don't have to apologize!
Man, we really are alike, you and me.
Have some tea.
Thanks...
More importantly, about the sports festival.
You still can't regulate
One For All, can you?
What'll you do?
But there was one time...!
When I aimed a smash at that
brain villain, there was no backlash.
Oh yeah, you mentioned that!
What was different?
Different...
The biggest difference between that and
the One For All that I'd been using was...
...my Quirk, Black Hole.
I can suck up anything and turn it to dust.
But it is a power that can kill easily.
It was the first time...
I tried to use this power on a person...
Hmm... Looks like you succeeded
in putting on the brakes unconsciously.
Anyway, that's progress. I'm glad.
Now, drink up.
Oh, thank you.
Frankly, I don't have much time
left as the Symbol of Peace.
No way…
And some of those with built-up
villainous intent are starting to realize.
I granted you my power
because I want you to succeed me.
I want to be like you. I want
to become the greatest hero, like you!
Saving people with a fearless smile.
You still feel the same as you did back then,
don't you?
Yes.
Then, the time has come for you to show that.
The U.A. sports festival
is something pro heroes--
no, the whole country--is
watching closely. A big event!
That is what I brought
you here to talk about!
The next All Might...
the fledgling Symbol of Peace...
Izuku Midoriya.
I want you to tell the world "I am here!"
"Preview"
The preview is here!
The U.A. sports festival is finally starting!
The first event is the obstacle course
race that everyone will participate in!
There's no limit to Quirk use!
Isn't that very dangerous...?
Even so, aim for the top!
Show off to the world the
fledgling hero, Izuku Midoriya!
Next time, "Roaring Sports Festival"!
Young Todoroki picks
a fight with Young Midoriya!
Go beyond!
"Next time: Roaring Sports Festival"
Plus Ultra!