The world has become
a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos,
the profession that everyone
once dreamed about and admired
came into the limelight.
Heroes of justice fighting villains
and saving people from distress.
Yes, this is the story of how
I became the greatest hero.
The U.A. sports festival is drawing near.
Of course, joining a famous hero agency
will get you more experience and popularity.
One chance a year--
a total of just three chances.
No aspiring heroes can afford
to miss this event.
If you understand that, then don't
slack off on your preparations!
Yes, sir!
"Roaring Sports Festival"
The U.A. sports festival
is something pro heroes--
no, the whole country--
is watching closely. A big event!
That is what I brought
you here to talk about!
The next All Might...
The fledgling Symbol of Peace...
Izuku Midoriya.
I want you to tell the world "I am here!"
"I am here"...
But how...?
You know the sports festival system, right?
Yes, of course!
The support, business, general studies,
and hero courses come together
"First-Year Stage"
and fight through preliminary games
of different types by class year.
The students who make it through
face off in the finals.
It's a round-robin tournament
divided by grade.
That's right! In other words, you can
sell yourself with everything you've got!
Right...
I mean, what you say is absolutely correct!
"mutter mutter mutter"
But honestly, it's kind of hard to get completely
into it right after what just happened...
"mutter mutter mutter"
Besides, All Might is already teaching me,
so I'm not as motivated to
stand out at the sports festival...
"mutter mutter mutter"
In the first place, I don't think
I can stand out in my current state,
and I did terribly in the fitness tests...
No one's better at spouting
nonsense than you!
Nonsense?
Those who are always aiming
for the top, and those who aren't.
That slight difference in attitudes will have
a big impact once you go out into society.
I understand how you feel,
and this is more for me than for you.
I won't force you.
However, I hope you won't forget
how you felt back at the beach park.
Wh...
Wh-What's going on?
What business do you have with Class A?
We can't get out!
What'd you come here for, anyway?
Scouting out the enemy, small fry.
We're the ones who made it
out of the villains' attack.
--That's Kacchan in neutral.
--They probably wanna check us out
before the sports festival.
There's no point in doing stuff like that.
Out of my way, extras!
Stop calling people "extras"
just because you don't know them!
I came to see what the
famous Class A was like,
but you seem pretty arrogant.
Are all the students in
the hero course like this?
Seeing something like this
makes me disillusioned.
There are quite a few people who enrolled in
general studies or other courses because
they didn't make it into the hero course.
Did you know that?
The school has left those of us a chance.
Depending on the results
of the sports festival,
they'll consider our transfer
into the hero course.
And it seems they may
also transfer people out.
Scouting out the enemy?
I, at least, came to say that
even if you're in the hero course,
if you get too carried away,
I'll sweep your feet out from under you.
I came with a declaration of war.
This person's bold, too!
Hey, hey!
"Hey Hey Hey Hey"
I'm from Class B next door!
I heard you fought against villains,
so I came to hear 'bout it!
Don't get so full of yourself!
Another bold person!
If you bark too much, it'll be embarrassing
for you durin' the real fight!
You ignorin' me, bastard?!
Wait a minute, Bakugo!
What're you gonna do about all this?
It's your fault that
everyone's hating on us!
It doesn't matter.
Huh?!
It doesn't matter as long
as you rise to the top.
Damnit, you bastard!
That's so simple and manly!
Huh?
You said it.
The top, huh? There is truth in that.
Hang on, don't be tricked!
He just made more pointless enemies!
That's right!
We'll just be at a disadvantage
at the sports festival!
I'm just...
I'm just getting started!
You hear?
Here, I will become number one!
Kacchan...
Am I... an idiot...?!
I'll definitely become
a hero and make money
--and let my parents take it easy.
--I set my sights on being a hero
because I want to be like my brother.
Time is limited.
If you expect to go pro,
--then the path to your future
will open up at this...
--That slight difference in attitudes will have
a big impact once you go out into society.
I hope you won't forget how
you felt back at the beach park.
"Dagoba Municipal Beach Park"
The U.A. sports festival is in two weeks.
It'll be broadcast live on TV, too.
There's no doubt
that those who do well
have a much better chance of becoming pro heroes.
We won't know what events we'll
be participating in until the day of.
But I'm sure everyone
has started getting ready.
Ribbit!
Here I go!
Release!
Sparkle!
Yes!
Yesh!
Damn it! What the--
Thank you!
Time passed in the blink of an eye,
and the morning of the
sports festival arrived.
Izuku, be careful not to get hurt.
Okay.
I'll record it, okay? In high resolution.
Do your best.
I'm off!
The bag check's taking forever.
They were just attacked by villains.
Of course they'll be more strict.
There are people criticizing
their decision to hold it this year.
Controversy equals ratings!
Class 1-A will be the ones
to watch this year, huh?
With the passion of their last chance
and the tactics from their experience,
the third years have always been
the main event in past years...
"First-Year Stage"               "Third-Year Stage"
"Second-Year Stage"
But this year, the first-year
stage is the one to watch!
Hey, did you know that Endeavor's
son is a first-year this year?
No way, seriously? Wow!
The first-year stage is gonna be good, huh?
One order of takoyaki, please.
Oh, Mt. Lady!
No green seaweed.
One, right? That'll be 500 yen.
Huh?
Um... I don't have that much
on me right now...
That's hot! It's free!
Thanks!
Have you no pride?
"Participant Waiting Rooms"
I had also hoped to be
able to do some scouting.
We have to work security,
so we don't have a choice.
It looks like they called pro heroes
from all over the country this year.
"Waiting Room"
Man...
I wanted to wear my costume.
To keep everything fair, we can't.
I wonder what the first round's gonna be...
No matter what comes, we have
no choice but to deal with it.
Right.
Everyone, are you ready?
We will be entering soon!
Person, person, person, person, person...
Midoriya.
Todoroki? What is it?
Looking at things objectively,
I think I'm stronger than you.
Huh?
Y-Yeah...
But... All Might has his
eye on you, doesn't he?
I'm not trying to pry about that.
But I'm going to beat you.
Oh? Is the best in the class
making a declaration of war?
Hey, hey, hey! Why are you
picking a fight all of a sudden?
Not now, we're about to start!
We're not here to play at being friends.
So what does it matter?
Todoroki, I don't know what you're
thinking when you say you'll beat me,
but of course you're better than me.
I think you're more capable
than most people...
Looking at it objectively...
Midoriya, you probably
shouldn't talk so negatively...
But, everyone--
The students from the
other courses are aiming
for the top with everything they've got!
I want to become the greatest hero!
I can't afford to fall behind.
I'll be going for it with
everything I have, too.
Yeah.
Hey!
Pay attention, audience!
Swarm, mass media!
This year's high school rodeo
of adolescence that you all love,
the U.A. sports festival, is about to begin!
Everybody, are you ready?!
It's time for the students
to enter the first-year stage!
Izuku...
I want you to tell the world "I am here!"
Roger that, All Might!
The U.A. sports festival!
The huge battle where fledgling heroes
sharpen their swords once a year!
Anyway, these are the guys, right?
The miraculous new stars who overcame
enemy attacks with their hearts of steel!
Hero course, Class 1-A, right?!
Th-Th-There are so many people...
Will we be able to give our best performance
being watched by so many people?
This is also part of the training
required to become a hero.
Man, he's going overboard with that praise!
I'm getting nervous!
Aren't you, Bakugo?
No, I'm just getting more into it.
They haven't been getting as much airtime,
but this class is also full of talent!
Hero course, Class 1-B!
Next up, general studies
Classes C, D, and E!
Support course, Classes F,
G, and H are here, too!
And business course, Classes I, J, and K!
All of U.A.'s first years are here now!
We're just here to make
those guys look better, huh?
I'm not really feeling it...
Time for the player pledge!
Oh, this year's chief umpire for the
first years is the R-Rated Hero, Midnight?
What about the principal?
The principal is at the
third-year stage every year.
What is Ms. Midnight wearing?
That's an R-Rated Hero for you.
Is it okay for her to be at a high school
even though she's R-Rated?
Yes!
Quiet, everyone!
Representing the students is
Katsuki Bakugo from Class 1-A!
What? It's Kacchan?
That guy did finish first
in the entrance exam.
In the hero course.
R-Right.
It's obvious she hates us.
And it's all Bakugo's fault.
I pledge--
That I'll be number one.
I knew he'd do that!
--What the heck!
--Stop messing around!
--Don't be so full of yourselves, Class A!
--You sludge bastard!
Why are you doing something so disgraceful?!
At least become a nice bouncy
step for me to jump off of.
How overconfident can you get?
I'll crush you!
Confidence? No...
The old Kacchan would've
laughed while saying that.
He's driving himself into a corner.
Getting the rest of us caught up in it
is just like Kacchan, though.
Now, let's get started right away.
--U.A. does everything "right away," huh?
--The first game is what
you'd call a qualifier!
Every year, many drink their tears here!
Now, here is the fateful first game!
This year, it's...
...this!
An obstacle course race.
All 11 classes will participate in this race.
"Full Participation"
The course will be the outer circumference
of this stadium--about four kilometers!
Our school's selling point is freedom!
As long as you stay on the course,
it doesn't matter what you do!
Now, take your places everyone!
All Might...
I want you to tell the world "I am here!"
Thinking about it realistically,
without really being able
to regulate One For All...
That's too unreasonable...
That's why I have to go beyond.
Please watch me!
Start!
Okay, here's the play-by-play!
Are you ready to do the
commentary, Mummy Man?
You're the one who forced me to come.
Let's get started right away, Mummy Man.
What should we pay attention
to in the early stages?
This part right now.
--Hey, hey!
--This is too narrow!
--Ouch!
--Hey, move!
I see...
This means, from the start, it's already...
The first sifting.
Sorry, but...
--Owww! What the--?
--It's freezing over! I can't move!
--So cold!
--Outta the way! I can't get it off!
Take that!
Naive, Todoroki!
I won't let you get away so easily!
You half-and-half bastard!
You got me with that once.
You won't get me again!
Woah, that was close!
I can't use my special move yet...
They're used to using their Quirks, huh...
More people outside of Class A were
able to dodge that than I expected...
I've outwitted you, Todoroki! How pathetic!
Take this! My special attack!
Gra--
Mineta!
Targets found...
Lots!!
The faux villains from the entrance exam?
Obstacles have shown up suddenly!
Starting with...
...the first barrier!
Robo Inferno!
Aren't those the zero-point villains
from the entrance exam?
--Seriously? The hero
course had to fight those?
--This is what they meant by obstacles?!
--There are too many! I can't get through!
So this is what they used
in the general entrance exam?
I wonder where they got the money for it?
If they went through all this trouble, I wish
they would've prepared something better.
Since my stupid old man is watching.
He stopped them!
Between their legs! We can get through!
I wouldn't if I were you.
I froze them when they were unbalanced.
They'll fall over.
Todoroki from Class 1-A!
He attacked and defended in one hit!
How elegant!
Amazing! He's the first one through!
It's, you know, practically unfair!
His actions are logical and strategic.
As expected of someone who
got in through recommendations!
He'd never fought them before,
but those Robo Infernos couldn't
get past his elite moves!
Gotta hurry...!
You can't beat those.
Run...
Run away, Izuku!
I have to get past these robots
while also paying attention
to the obstacles around me.
Idiot, why?!
Why can't I move?
Come on, think!
Now what?
"Preview"
Time for the preview!
Listen to me and listen good!
It's the preview!
Why are you so mad, Kacchan?
Listen, this sports festival
obstacle course race
is gonna end with me at the top, you scum!
That's not a preview.
That's more like a personal wish...
Shut up, be quiet, you damn nerd!
If you're even a step ahead of me,
I'll crush you, no questions asked!
Even if you don't get ahead
of me, I'll still crush you!
It's too scary either way!
Next time, "In Their Own Quirky Ways."
In the final stages of the race,
I go "boom!" in a minefield!
"Next time: In Their Own Quirky Ways"
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!