Shall I tell you a story about my past?
About when I was in sixth grade...
Once, a girl, one of my classmates,
brought a box of seven
or eight hamsters over by me.
They had bred after she'd been careless,
and now she was at a loss,
unable to take care of them all.
I agreed to take them.
On the way home, I filled up
an empty large fruit wine bottle
and drowned all of the hamsters in it.
Three hours later, after dinner,
I went to my room,
where I was captivated by what I saw.
One hamster, treading water
above the other floating, lifeless hamsters.
To be honest, it excited me.
I named the survivor Spice
and decided to raise it.
The moment I saw it in there,
I thought of the short story,
"The Spider's Thread."
Do you know it?
A sinner named Kandata is in Hell
one day when Shakyamuni,
moved by the single compassionate
act of his life, sparing a spider's life,
lowers a spider's thread
down from Heaven to him.
Kandata begins climbing
towards Heaven,
kicking down at his fellow sinners
when they try to climb up after him.
Then the thread snaps,
and Kandata falls back down to Hell.
I don't think you'll believe this,
but I'll tell you anyway.
Or maybe you will understand.
Since I became acquainted with Spice,
it's as if I could see the spider's thread.
I've murdered the people
who I could see were connected to it.
But at some point,
a boy disrupted my plans.
And then I saw a spider's thread
attached to the top of his head, too.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
But he didn't die.
I named him Spice
and began observing him.
I'm talking about you, Satoru.
ERASED
That'll be 987 yen.
Thank you.
ICHI REAL ESTATE
Come to think of it,
didn't Satoru tell me once...
The fact is, you can go to Ueno
without changing trains.
It's true.
What was that about?
FIGHT, WONDER GUY!
TV THEME SONG
Good morning, Satoru.
FUNABASHI GENERAL HOSPITAL
Yes. I'm surprised.
It's hard to believe
you were asleep for 15 years.
Fif... teen... years...
Oh! You can speak.
I don't think you'll have to wait long
before starting rehab.
Mom has spent four hours of every day
for the last 15 years caring for my body.
For the last three years,
she's been using an EMS device
to prepare for the day when I woke up.
She took care of my joints
and my muscles.
I was 139 cm tall in fifth grade,
and now I'm 169 cm tall.
Dr. Kitamura keeps saying,
"This is all because of your mother"
and "It's remarkable."
Well, Satoru, I think
this is a good time for it.
Answer my next question.
What's the last thing you remember
before falling asleep?
The last thing I remember...
Huh?
What was it again?
That memory was blocked,
locked up tight behind a door.
Do you want to see yourself?
Don't be shocked.
What?
Your face has changed a lot
since you were 11.
Your memories are scrambled too,
so there may be discrepancies
regarding your sense of self.
At the time, I thought
maybe he was right,
but even being in the Heisei era
for the first time,
nothing felt out of place.
PATIENCE
"Patience." "Heart rate monitor."
HEART RATE MONITOR
SENSE OF LOSS
"Sense of loss." "Arbitration."
ARBITRATION
I can read all of these words.
When in the world did I learn them?
BOYS' FLIGHT
Who am I?
Good morning, Satoru.
Good morning.
Satoru, you've got visitors.
Long time no see, Satoru.
You look good, Satoru.
Kenya Kobayashi and Hiromi Sugita
were especially good friends of mine.
Kenya's a lawyer now,
and Hiromi's a doctor.
I talked with them about trivial things.
It seemed that Kenya wanted
to ask me something,
but I think Mom had given him
strict instructions.
So we just chatted that day.
See you!
There were a lot of things
I wanted to ask them too,
but it seems Mom was trying
to avoid the topic of my past.
Mom had been spending her life
for the past 15 years only for me,
having faith
that I would awaken one day.
If it's what Mom wishes,
I guess I don't have to remember.
Are you okay?
Why don't we call it a day?
Satoru!
Congratulations, Kayo.
Episode 11
Future
I got married.
My name is Kayo Sugita now.
Your baby's father is Hiromi then?
Yeah.
It seemed like Hiromi wanted
to tell me something.
Maybe it was about your child.
Could've been.
Come to think of it, the baby has
Hiromi's long eyelashes.
Yeah, even though he's a boy.
His name is Mirai.
Mirai... The "future"...
That's a good name.
Satoru...
To be honest,
we felt kind of uncomfortable.
Thinking "Is it all right
for just us to become happy?"
Even though we may have been
the cause of you being in a coma...
It kind of felt...
like we were leaving you behind.
Kayo, my fate is my own.
There's no need for you
to feel responsible.
I'm sure that what's become of me
was a result of something I wanted.
You were asleep for 15 years
but still have a silver tongue.
Even so, Satoru...
Before, I could only imagine being alone,
but now I've got a family,
and it was all made possible
because of you.
Thank you.
Thank you...
What did I do?
Okay, okay.
Are you hungry?
Satoru?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry to spring all of this on you.
I've tired you out.
Well, I'll visit again.
Yeah. See you later.
Oh, Satoru. You're back?
Yeah.
Hinazuki was here a little while ago.
Yeah. I saw her too.
Her baby's adorable, isn't he?
Listen...
Mom...
Yes?
They're here again.
What is it?
Photographers for gossip rags.
They want to write articles
about you being in a coma for 15 years.
Oh, that's right, Satoru...
You were going to tell me something?
No, it was nothing.
Come in.
Hello.
Thank you for everything.
Dr. Kitamura, when will I
be able to walk again?
I don't know.
That could depend on you.
Then from today, please let me
do twice as much rehab.
I'm anxious to walk outside.
I'll think about it.
Excuse me a minute.
Yes, thank you, Director.
He's making a smooth recovery.
He could regain
his memories at any time.
No.
As I said the other day,
I have to refuse that.
My patient isn't a mouse—
SATORU FUJINUMA
Excuse me.
Amazing, Satoru!
Your arms and legs
have gotten a lot stronger.
Congratulations, Satoru!
That was great, Mr. Fujinuma!
You really walked all that way!
It was an awesome effort!
Satoru, Kenya is here to see you.
Hi, Kenya.
Sorry to bother you now.
No, thank you for coming.
Hello, Satoru.
Nice to meet you.
I used to work with your mother.
We met several times
before you started elementary school.
That was over 20 years ago.
He could never remember that.
Well, I'll visit again.
Take care.
We've waited 15 years for this.
There's no need to be impatient now.
Let's take it slowly.
Agreed.
Hello.
I see.
So you've got surgery
the week after next, Kumi.
My sister is going to
give me her bone marrow.
They say that's what's going to cure me.
But...
I'm scared.
Is it true you were asleep for 15 years?
You've been here
for about three months, huh, Kumi?
Yeah.
I've been trying all this time
to look good in front of you.
I'll be really disappointed
once you're out of here.
Courage.
Want me to tell you
how to muster up courage?
You picture the smiling face
of someone who's dear to you.
Of course, you have to smile too.
Time's drifter...
He wakes up after 15 years,
is interested in little girls,
is a kid at heart with an adult's body,
and he may be released soon.
How do you like that angle?
Nice.
Secretly taking photos
of a civilian in the hospital...
Defamation, trespassing...
Plenty to warrant punishment by law.
Get your asses out of here.
The flowers were beautiful.
Mr. Nishizono!
Hello!
Hi, Kumi.
Satoru Fujinuma...
Yes...
It's me. Have you forgotten?
Well, I've changed a lot.
Here, I was your
homeroom teacher in fifth grade.
Gaku Yashiro.
I go by "Nishizono" now.
I changed my given name to "Manabu."
Why did you change your name?
Actually, I got married five years ago
and was adopted into her
family as a son-in-law.
My father-in-law was a city council
member for many years,
but he passed away three years ago.
I inherited his constituency
and joined the council myself.
That's when I changed
my given name,
keeping the kanji but going
with the more common reading.
So you're a politician now?
Still a freshman council member though.
But I have a feeling you'll make
a great politician, Mr. Yashiro.
I met Kumi at a charity event
for leukemia.
The director of this hospital is my
acquaintance, and he introduced us.
Oh, really?
I found out you'd regained
consciousness some time before that.
It took me long enough
to pay you a visit.
You went out of your way to visit me?
I'd been anticipating
your awakening for 15 years.
Thank you.
You must've been through a lot.
I'm sorry. I...
Yes, I've heard.
You haven't regained
all of your memories, right?
Remembering them gradually is best.
Hi.
Mr. Yashiro...
Are you also going to see Kumi?
Yes. Her surgery is scheduled
for the day after tomorrow,
and this is the last day
she can have visitors.
Yes. I just saw her now.
That being said, she was sleeping,
so I couldn't talk to her.
Oh, really?
Then maybe I'll try again later.
Since you're here,
do you have time to chat?
Sure, but I don't want to be interrupted
by the gossip mag hounds,
so why don't we go somewhere else?
I found the perfect place.
DELIVERIES
You didn't know
about this elevator, did you?
This is kind of an adventure, isn't it?
Would you push the roof button?
Too bad...
If it'd been a clear day,
the sunset would've been beautiful.
But there won't be any weird
photographers up here.
The roof is really off limits,
so don't tell anyone.
I'm reminded of how you,
Kenya and Hiromi often said,
"Let's go to the hideout!"
Your pretend secret base, right?
Yashiro...
I have...
my memories back!