Even so, Satoru...
Before, I could only imagine being alone,
but now I've got a family,
and it was all made possible
because of you.
Thank you.
Thank you...
What did I do?
Okay, okay.
Are you hungry?
That's right.
I saved Hinazuki.
And after that,
we tried to make it so that Aya Nakanishi
and Misato weren't alone.
Yashiro...
I have...
my memories back!
ERASED
Fight!
-Osamu
Good luck!
-Kazu
So Kazu is a carpenter...
Sounds like both he and Osamu
are working really hard.
Yeah.
Come to think of it, Misato said
she was going to pay you a visit.
Really?
I thought Misato hated me.
This brings back memories...
Like that lunch money thing...
A lot happened back then, huh?
But Misato is the one
who proposed fundraising activities
to help pay for your
medical expenses.
SATORU FUJINUMA
DONATION MONEY
FOR MEDICAL EXPENSES
I had no idea.
You tried to help Misato that day, right?
You remember everything, don't you?
Why didn't you tell us?
I didn't want to get you involved.
It's been 15 years.
All of the evidence is gone
and I doubt anyone
would believe my testimony.
I was so happy to see you
wake up after 15 years, Satoru.
Nothing could've made me
happier than your return.
That's why I didn't ask you
about the past.
You've fought plenty already,
and I didn't want to jolt you
when you were healing
your wounded mind and body.
But if you intend to fight alone again,
I want you to take us with you.
Hiromi has been coming to the hospital
all these years to see you
and now his goal is to become a doctor.
And I became a lawyer.
Even now, Sawada
and I are pursuing him.
You were our hero back then, Satoru.
Now we understand why we wanted
to catch up to you and fight alongside you.
It was the same
with the stuff about Hinazuki.
You believed in me then
and told me the truth.
That's why I believed in you.
I want to believe you for my own sake.
It's the flip side to someone
saying "please believe me."
Airi...
That's right.
I have friends I can trust.
The killer is...
Yashiro.
I figured as much.
When I deliberately tapped my finger
on the wheelchair on the way...
...you stifled a response, didn't you?
15 years ago...
you completely ruined my plans.
That was far beyond...
the level of a child.
It was as if you could see the future.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
How?
How did you know what I was thinking?
What did you mean
by "I know your future"?
You intend to murder me
as soon as I tell you, right?
I know what you're doing.
You've got a cell phone in your pocket.
Are you recording this?
Or are you on the phone with someone?
If so, is that person Kenya?
END CALL
What happened 15 years ago
has passed the statute of limitations.
So you want to ask me
about crimes I committed
that haven't passed
the statute of limitations, right?
Except they don't exist.
So you can never capture me, Satoru.
Look, you have a text from Kumi.
Satoru, thank you for
listening to my wishes.
Incoming Mail
Kumi
Kumi's IV drip will start at 4:30.
Of course, your
fingerprints are on the bag
that has a muscle-relaxant
drug mixed in it.
You've led a ten-year-old girl
who was worried about her
surgery to a merciful death.
And feeling guilty about that,
I jump off the roof.
You read my mind again,
though there's nothing
you can do to save your own life.
On the other hand,
you can save Kumi's life.
Even if I talk, what guarantee
do you have that you'll help Kumi?
There is no guarantee, naturally.
But there is a possibility.
If you don't talk,
there isn't even a possibility.
Too bad. We're out of time.
This was a sink-or-swim gamble for me.
But in the end,
there was no special significance.
It was all coincidence.
You saying you knew
my future was just a bluff, too.
Have peace of mind.
I'll leave a few heartfelt
last words to your mother.
Please forgive me for
dying before you.
Text
Sachiko Fujinuma
To Mom
Well, Satoru, I work tomorrow morning,
so I'll see you in the afternoon.
Sleeping, huh?
Mom...
To be honest, I have...
...your memories back, right?
I know. Since Kayo visited you, right?
Yokai...
When Kayo visited, you didn't forbid her
from talking about it, did you?
Actually, after Kenya and Hiromi left,
I felt like I'd made a mistake.
I thought they weren't able to say
what they really wanted to tell you.
After seeing Kayo and her baby,
I didn't have the heart to hush her up.
After all, she came to see you
after waiting 15 years for you to wake up.
I saw your face
and talked to you every day,
but when you spoke
and your voice broke,
I felt like you'd grown for the first time.
I was moved.
You're an adult now.
Mom...
I want to take the bull
by the horns and live.
After all this time,
what are you talking about?
Before the coma, you always
took the bull by the horns.
Right.
Life is filling up what's missing in you.
That's what I said when I took charge
of the sixth grade class.
The day Hinazuki was taken
into protective custody,
I saw your face in profile
reflected in the snow.
That is what stuck
in my memory the most.
My father left the picture
soon after I was born.
That's why I don't remember
what he looks like.
But in that one moment,
you were my father, Sensei.
You filled the hole inside of me.
I've also been waiting 15 years
for you to wake up, Satoru.
Ever since you left,
I lost that impulse that defines me.
It's been so long.
But—
You're not alone anymore.
How do we settle things between us?
The police catch you?
You kill me?
It's already settled.
I think I've won.
Kayo Hinazuki, Aya Nakanishi,
Hiromi, Yuuki...
I saved all of them.
And Mom, whom you murdered
in the future.
Murdered in the future?
Satoru, what are you...
I ruined your plans...
because I know your future.
That's all.
That's how I was able
to protect everyone.
That's why you weren't able to kill
anyone with a connection to me.
Including myself...
Satoru, I could've killed you anytime.
Of course, now too.
You let me live, Sensei.
For 15 years.
Because you needed me!
I was your reason to live.
I was your hope.
I filled the hole in your heart!
I beat you, Sensei.
Wrong!
This time too...
I'm gonna win!
You can't kill me, Sensei.
15 years is a long time, isn't it?
I was asleep, so it passed by
in an instant for me,
but I think 15 years went by
excruciatingly slowly for you, Sensei.
FUNABASHI GENERAL HOSPITAL
You're alive because I'm around.
You feel like you're alive.
I've relived this life a number of times.
You've murdered a number
of my friends, Sensei.
But right now, I bear you no hatred.
In this world, the only person
who knows the real you...
is me.
That's right.
Satoru...
I can't live...
without you.
You're under arrest
for attempted murder.
PRESCRIPTION INFORMATION
Is Kumi okay?
Yes.
But we didn't tell her about Yashiro.
Not with her surgery coming up...
Right.
"Believing in someone."
That's a weird phrase, isn't it?
After all, if you truly
believed in a person,
you wouldn't need to say,
"I believe in you."
It's like saying, "I believe in air."
You mean "believing"
because there's doubt?
I don't mean to say that
"believing in something" is like a lie.
"Believing" is really a term
of hope of wanting to believe.
CHIBA POLICE
I lost my life from the age of 11 to 25.
But that lost time itself is my treasure.
In a town only without me,
my friends spent the precious
spare time in their lives on my behalf.
Heroes always come running
in at the last minute!
- Here's Satoru!
- You're late!
- Finally!
- Took you long enough!
As usual. Because he's stupid.
A town without me alone...
Time without me alone...
That's my treasure!
Episode 12
Treasure
BOYS' FLIGHT
You're blowing me away!
I love it when you take the bull
by the horns, Sensei.
Then I'll keep going in this direction.
Sorry to have you come all the way here.
Are you going on a trip?
Yes.
After this, I'm going back
to Hokkaido to see old friends.
Oh, that's right.
RECEPTION ROOM
Please have a great weekend.
And I almost forgot!
GALACTICA SWORD
~7 HEROES~
TO THE KING'S STRENGTH
GATHER FELLOW COMRADES!
Congratulations
on the upcoming anime version!
Right now, I make a living
as a manga artist.
Revival hasn't happened
to me since then.
SHIRATORI FOOD PRODUCTS
YANAGIDA BAR
SATORU FUJINUMA
MIKOTO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Ice Hockey Club 2010
National Champions
Two weeks until the opening
of the 2010 Olympics in Vancouver...
I'm going for a walk.
See you later!
See you later.
They said we're getting
even more snow this evening.
HIGUMA MOVING CENTER
"My Hero" by Satoru Fujinuma.
I don't have the courage
to take that first step.
That's why I don't have
any good buddies.
It's fun playing with casual friends,
"good buddies"
and "casual friends" are different.
I saw the final episode of my favorite
anime, "Fight, Wonder Guy!" yesterday.
In the first part,
Wonder Guy was fighting alone.
He'd go down again and again
but had the courage
to keep fighting and never give up.
"If you don't take that first step,
a path won't open for you."
That's what he said
and kept on fighting.
Then other people felt his
courage, and little by little,
became buddies with him.
That's why in the end, even when it looked
like he was going to lose to the bad guy,
he never stopped believing
that his pals would come to the rescue.
But I don't have Wonder Guy's courage
or good friends like that.
So I felt really envious.
It made me wish to have true friends,
friends who trust each other,
when I get bigger.
BIG WAVE, SMALL WAVE
Can you believe this snow?
They said on TV it's the most
the Kanto region has had in ten years.
Can I take shelter
from the snow with you?
I never stopped believing.
ERASED