Hinazuki is late?
She said she was going to
give me my present today.
If she was up all night
making something,
it makes sense that she'd be late...
Satoru...
...but...
Satoru!
Y-Yes!
What's wrong, Satoru?
Are you worried about something?
HOPE
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
Hinazuki!
Is anyone home?!
Don't tell me...
Rubber boots?
An adult male's size...
It snowed the night before last.
In other words, an adult male
came here after that.
Hey.
What are we gonna do?
Five court musicians
playing drums and fifes!
It's a fun Girls' Festival!
THURSDAY, MARCH 3rd, 1988
KAYO HINAZUKI DISAPPEARED
ERASED
After that, I stayed home
from school for two days.
Is Mom out shopping?
Actually, a similar incident
happened in a neighboring city.
They caught the culprit
soon afterwards, but now this?
We don't know who did it yet,
but we'd better do everything in our power
to prevent it from happening again.
Of course that's part of it,
but about clamping down on the press...
I'll call you right after
I talk to the school.
Okay. I'll talk to city hall, too.
I'm counting on you.
Mom's former co-worker...
A reporter for TV Ishikari.
The kids shouldn't have to
remember something like this.
Agreed.
So this is where it started...
HOKU-HOKU BENTO
I know you're worried,
but it's not your fault, Satoru.
I didn't make a difference.
I don't know about that.
I didn't want Hinazuki to be all alone.
Then you succeeded.
It wasn't enough.
There must have been something else.
Thinking it's your fault
after the fact is just pointless.
There's only so much one person can do.
That holds true for me and you.
Go to school tomorrow.
Being alone here
only makes you depressed.
Okay.
Now let's eat before it gets cold.
Yeah.
I've been keeping something from you.
Actually, I lied when I said
Kayo was at home with a cold.
She moved to her grandmother's
home for personal reasons.
It happened so suddenly that she wasn't
able to say goodbye to you,
but I hear Kayo is doing well in Sapporo.
Ran away from home?
I heard her mother beat her!
That's terrible!
Then it's better this way.
Satoru!
Don't worry!
Yeah! You'll see her again!
Satoru...
The school and the PTA had a discussion
and decided what to say about Kayo.
For the time being,
go along with this story.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It seems the press has been muzzled,
but a police vehicle has been parked
near Hinazuki's house
for the past several days.
Apparently her mother
is a suspect at this stage.
Only six days after Hinazuki disappeared.
LOOKING FOR
AYA NAKANISHI
11 YEARS OLD
March 8th 1988
March 9th 1988
The city has issued an advisory.
When you leave school grounds,
always be with a guardian.
A second child has disappeared.
It's sooner than I expected.
March 9th 1988
March 10th 1988
Satoru... have you heard?
About Aya Nakanishi
from Izumi Elementary?
Yeah.
A friend of mine from Izumi Elementary
said she ran away
and then went to live
with her grandfather.
That sounds just like Hinazuki.
I'm sure the part
about running away is a lie.
My guess is
this is really a case of serial abductions.
March 10th 1988
March 11th 1988
There are differences in details,
but we've definitely begun to go down
the same flow of time as 18 years ago.
March 11th 1988
March 12th 1988
KAYO HINAZUKI
NEXT UP:
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL STUDENT MISSING
HOKKAIDO - CHILDREN'S WHEREABOUTS UNKNOWN
The investigation became public,
but TV Ishikari only ran news of the story
early in the morning and late at night,
and adults with children were advised
to only let them watch TV Ishikari.
I'm back!
March 12th 1988
March 13th 1988
The police car that had been camping out
in front of Hinazuki's house day and night
only appeared sporadically
after the Aya Nakanishi disappearance.
The focus of the investigation
must have shifted to "serial abductions."
Just ten days after her
daughter disappeared...
Inside the garbage bag she threw out
were a pair of knit mittens.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Where am I?
Am I back?
In 2006...
23-1, 4th Street...
The victim is Sachiko Fujinuma,
52 years old.
We're searching for Satoru Fujinuma,
29 years old, as a suspect.
We do have eyewitness
information. Over.
Roger.
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
Wrong. You're wrong.
It wasn't me...
Dammit!
I couldn't help Hinazuki...
Mom is still murdered...
and I'm the suspect!
That's the reality I'm faced with.
Get ready!
Run away!
Episode 5
Getaway
In the end, I'm under a bridge.
Some imagination I've got...
Even though I haven't
made the news yet...
First off, I have to think.
Why was Mom murdered?
Because she realized
the identity of the culprit?
Was her cell phone in the apartment?
What about her bag?
No, neither were there.
So the killer took them away?
Because it was possible
Mom would've leaked info about him?
Dammit!
My head feels heavy.
I want to sleep the day away.
Here, eat.
Thanks.
I apologize for today.
This is the first time you were absent
from work without permission.
Katagiri was worried about you, too.
Knowing you, I'm sure
there's a reasonable explanation, but...
Anyway, let's eat up first!
Thank you.
I see.
So you had a fight
with your mother, huh?
Yes.
Old people can be set in their ways.
You can stay here as long as you want,
but you've gotta patch
things up with your mom.
I will.
You want a beer too, Satoru?
No.
I'm out.
I'll go buy some more.
My impression was right.
He is the "annoying big brother" type.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
The police received a tip
and hurried over.
They discovered the body of a woman
believed to be the mother
of the apartment's resident.
The police are currently
searching for the male resident
as a person of interest in the case.
This has taken a disastrous turn!
And now, sports.
Today the Japanese soccer team
left for Germany,
where the playoffs will be held.
I've been way too naïve!
No. I can't blame the manager!
He's always trying to do the right thing!
Of course he'd give me up!
Son of a bitch!
Are you stupid?
Airi...
You called me "Airi," Satoru.
You can't leave your phone on.
They'll track you with GPS.
What are you doing?
Hop on!
You want to get away, right?
I'm sorry, Katagiri.
It's "Airi."
Riding double on the bike
makes us equals.
You don't mind letting me in your house?
You do know what happened, right?
The police came to the shop today
and talked to the manager.
It was on the news, too.
Then why...
It's obvious!
There's no way you killed
your mom, Satoru.
I see.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
I can't believe they're chasing you,
the one who's grieving the most.
Though you really are connected
to a lot of crimes...
NIPPON
SHOWA'S MOST SHOCKING CRIMES
Here.
You forgot it at the shop the other day.
I read the part you had bookmarked
with an envelope.
It happened in your hometown
when you were a kid, right?
Kayo Hinazuki's death...
To die on the day of the Girls' Festival...
I cried when I read that.
Girls' Festival?
Yeah. March 3rd.
You can relax here.
I have to take the bike back to the shop.
Don't even think about leaving this room.
KAYO HINAZUKI
(10 YEARS OLD)
The book's information has changed...
KAYO HINAZUKI
(11 YEARS OLD)
Then... it can be changed.
If I can go back there one more time,
I can save Hinazuki!
That's right. I'm in Airi's room.
Dear Satoru,
I think it would be a good idea
if I went about my normal routine today,
so I'm going to work.
My family will probably
leave the house around ten.
They said they'll be back
after eight tonight.
The house key and bike key
are next to the clock.
My cell phone number is...
SASAOKA
It's not "Katagiri."
Thank you so much, Mr. Nishizono!
That's all right.
I'm in your father's debt.
No, no. Not at all.
My dad was overjoyed.
He said one stoplight
and one pedestrian crossing
totally changed the flow
of customers for us.
That has more to do with your
father's business acumen.
All I did was give him a little boost.
Besides, it's a school route.
We would occasionally talk
about it at city council meetings.
Bye, Manager! I just finished.
Good job, Airi!
What's that?
Take-out pizza.
You should've told me!
I can treat you once in a while.
Thank you!
But that's okay.
This is for my friend.
O-Oh, your friend...
A girl, maybe?
I'll see you tomorrow!
She's cute.
Pardon me!
But, well, she's only 17,
and still immature...
Well, I should be on my way as well.
Thank you again!
CHINESE CAFETERIA
Airi!
Manager!
Here, you forgot this.
Part of the sales promotion, remember?
Thank you.
Also... about Satoru...
I can't believe that he murdered his...
I mean, that he did any of that.
I agree!
If you happen to run into him,
do what you can to help him out.
I will!
We're all on the same side,
so contact me too if you see him.
Thank you!
Can I close in on the killer
by investigating like this?
A child abduction
in the city three years ago...
Come to think of it, I recall that.
The suspect was arrested
three weeks later.
But he claimed he was innocent
the whole time.
What is this feeling?
Something bothers me about this.
What do you want with the police...
Manager?
Airi!
You told me to help Satoru.
You said we were all on the same side!
That's what you said!
Y-You have the wrong idea, Airi!
I, um, was worried about you...
Then why didn't you
tell me that from the start?!
I wanted to trust you, Manager!
I-I was worried about you.
I believe that.
I'm sorry.
Manager... please...
If you're worried about me,
don't call the police over to my house.
I'm sorry, Satoru.
You have nothing to apologize for.
In fact, thank you.
You gave me a chance to rest.
You can't go back to that house now.
Yeah, but it's better this way.
By the way, it's not really
your parents' house, is it?
No.
My mom's big brother
and his wife live there.
My parents live out in the country.
I was going to find a boarding house
so I could commute to high school,
but they invited me
to stay with them in Chiba.
Can I ask you one more question?
What is it?
Airi, how can you believe in me?
It isn't that I "can."
I want to believe in you.
When I was still in elementary school,
my dad and I went grocery shopping.
A chocolate bar fell out of his pocket.
It was a small town
and we knew the owner.
If he admitted to stealing it
and apologized,
the owner said he would
let the matter drop.
But Dad refused to admit it.
Dad was a kind man.
That was the first time I heard him yell.
The owner felt obliged to call the police,
and Dad, a member
of the local agricultural coop,
was suspended for three
months as punishment.
I know! I saw the whole thing!
You didn't do anything, Dad!
Dad quit the coop,
got a divorce, and left home.
I guess Mom thought
he really did steal it.
I want to believe you for my own sake.
It's the flip side to someone
saying "please believe me."
Go back home.
Tell the police I threatened you,
forcing you to hide me.
Are you stupid?
There's no way you can get away
by yourself, and I refuse to tell them that.
Would you stop asking me if I'm stupid?
Anyway, I'll at least bring you
a change of clothes, Satoru.
Manager...
After that, he didn't make
a report to the police.
Incoming Mail
Sachiko Fujinuma's Phone
What is this?
This is Satoru Fujinuma.
Stay right where you are.
What does it mean?
Satoru found his mom's phone?
How?
No!
It's from the killer!
"Stay right where you are"?
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
No way...
No way!