March 1st, 18 years ago.
As usual, Hinazuki was standing
alone in this park.
I think it was a little before six.
At the time,
I was on my way to the hideout.
I went looking for my missing gloves.
I don't remember
if the gloves were actually there.
After leaving the hideout,
I looked towards the bank
and saw Yuuki sitting there,
facing the river.
After that, when I cut back
through the park,
Hinazuki was gone.
February 24th
All right, all eyes on the blackboard.
Kayo Hinazuki is going to be the first victim
in a series of kidnappings and murders,
a week from now.
MARCH
X-day.
Safely getting through March 1st
and spending the next day
with Hinazuki at my birthday party...
That would definitely change the future.
I'll make sure
those crimes never happen.
ERASED
February 25th 1988
Morning, Satoru.
Morning.
Breakfast will be ready in a few.
Yea...
Thank you for this meal.
Hey, Mom...
I want to go out next Saturday.
On a date?
N-Not like that!
I thought we'd all go
to the Science Center.
Oh. Too bad.
If it were a date,
I'd give you money for it.
Seriously?
It really is a date, isn't it?
Yeah.
You should bring her here.
We'll have hot pot or something.
Hinazuki will be here
for the birthday party.
Oh. Hinazuki, from the fifth block.
She's already asking me
leading questions.
Just be careful when you go out.
Thank you.
Now hurry up and eat your breakfast.
Right!
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
Rise.
Manners.
Goodbye!
"Liveman" is starting soon! Isn't it cool?
Yeah!
What's a "falcon"?
A hunting bird!
You know a lot!
Saturday...
I'm going to take Hinazuki away
from her house or,
more precisely, her mother's abuse.
- Sensei!
What is it?
I don't get this, so explain it to me.
Let's see...
It ticks me off
how they're all so flirty with him.
You know everything, Sensei!
Until recently,
you were the same way, weren't you?
Don't be stubborn.
You can go up there, too, y'know.
What's that, "y'know"?
Are you trying to sound cool?
Crap.
Sensei thinks I'm a thief.
And so do you.
Never mind.
Hey, you guys. I have an idea.
What is it, Satoru?
Um...
Why don't we all go
to the Science Center on Saturday?
I'm gonna ask Hinazuki, too.
That's a great!
Sorry, Satoru.
I have something to do that day
and I can't get out of it.
O-Oh...
Sorry, Satoru.
I got somethin' important
to do, so I can't go either.
T-That's right.
I wanna go, but I've got
something to do, too.
M-Me too.
Oh...
It's better for just you and Hinazuki to go!
See you!
Fujinuma...
Did something happen?
Uh, no...
I told them I couldn't play on Saturday
because I have a date with you.
Should I say that?
I did say that...
But...
my mother told me to get home
early on Saturday.
There's a place I wanna take you.
I'll try talking to her.
Kenya...
Could you stop by the staff room?
Forget it.
I don't believe in two children
going out somewhere together.
It wouldn't just be to play!
It's a learning experience, too.
You can learn at home.
Kayo helps me at home on Saturdays.
Helps? With what?
Helps you blow off steam?
I'm not obliged to tell you that.
Why do you want Hinazuki
to stay home so badly?
I can think of several reasons!
For one, you're both children.
If something were to happen,
who would take responsibility?!
She's turning it against me.
What's with you?
Taking my surly daughter somewhere...
What do you stand to gain?
When it comes to saving a friend,
there are no gains or losses!
Saving?
Saving Kayo from what?
You think you're a prince
on a white horse?
Crap.
I shouldn't have hinted at her abuse.
What do you think, Kayo?
You want to go with this kid?
Get your minds out of the gutter,
you perverted brats!
Mom!
Stop it, Ms. Hinazuki.
You don't call children "perverted brats."
Ms... Fujinuma...
This isn't your business.
I'd say half of it is.
You see, my son shows motivation
in everything he does.
And I want to help him.
After all, I'm his parent.
I think your household
and mine are similar.
Why don't you visit for a chat next time?
Kayo, get inside.
Okay.
S-Saturday... I'll see you then.
Did I butt in?
No. Thank you.
I got off work early.
It's lucky that I happened to see you two
and followed you here.
You followed us?!
I-I'm kidding, of course.
But... well, everything
should be okay for today.
That girl was actually
wearing nice clothes.
It's because the mother
cares about appearances.
HINAZUKI
Do you know what's going on over there?
No.
But between our conversation
and seeing the mother,
I can take a guess.
She didn't work for a TV news
department for nothing.
Kayo is a cute girl.
What am I embarrassed for?
I'm 29 years old!
Don't abandon her now.
Of course not.
February 27th - Saturday
February 27th, Saturday.
It's a clear day.
It seems Hinazuki's mother has refrained
from physical abuse for the past several days.
That's my friend.
Are you stupid?
I love this place!
There's hardly anyone here.
Isn't it exciting, like we just snuck in?
When I see somebody else, I hide.
She didn't say, "Are you stupid?"
Look at this!
PLANETARIUM
Wanna see the planetarium?
It's good timing.
We saw plenty of stars last time.
That's true.
I'm gonna run to the bathroom.
Okay. I'll be around here.
What is this feeling?
Is it déjà vu?
I often came here,
but it's my first time with Hinazuki.
Hinazuki...
Fujinuma...
Thank you for inviting me today.
Did you know I liked this place, too?
Did I know?
Is that why I chose this place?
Do people who want to make manga...
tend to come to places like this?
I remember this same
conversation from 18 years ago.
I came here alone then
and ran into Hinazuki by chance.
What is it?
N-Nothing.
M-Maybe there is a connection.
Am I repeating the same time?
I intend to change the future,
but I've unwittingly been riding
the same rail of time?
Hinazuki, I'll carry your coat.
Now?
I can change a lot
through my own behavior.
Believe it.
I can change the future.
Fujinuma...
I'm glad I mustered
the courage and came here.
Yeah...
Satoru!
Hinazuki!
Hey there!
I finished what I had to do early.
Sorry we're late.
There. It's changed.
Are we in the way?
Of course not!
Right, Hinazuki?
Right.
Satoru is a gentleman!
Episode 4
Accomplishment
5th Grade, Class 4
Good morning!
Morning, Fujinuma.
M-Morning, Hinazuki.
That's a relief.
It's Monday, but she's not late.
You're pretty.
I actually said that...
D-Did you just hear that?!
February 29th
- Oh my God!
- Satoru's got guts!
Are they gonna get married?!
Idiot! First they gotta get engaged!
- What's that?
- Congrats!
Hey!
I'm ready to get started.
HOPE
Hinazuki is due to be murdered tomorrow.
March 1st.
This is the real showdown.
See you, Hiromi!
See you tomorrow!
Hey, Hinazuki...
I'll pick you up at your house tomorrow.
Let's walk to school together.
Okay.
Mom...
Good evening.
Well, I'll stop by tomorrow morning!
See you later!
Okay!
I left the house a little early.
March 1st, 1988.
The day Hinazuki
disappeared 18 years ago.
Good morning.
But today is different.
Good morning, Fujinuma.
Good morning.
Hinazuki isn't going anywhere.
Well, see you later.
- Morning!
Circumstances have changed a lot
between 18 years ago and now.
Satoru's got guts!
Hinazuki was targeted
because she was
always alone in the park.
Well, you guys all
better be there tomorrow.
- Sure!
- Of course.
Yep.
Those circumstances
disappeared days ago.
Hey, let's stop at the children's center.
And I'm with her today.
I want to get home early today.
Don't be like that. Hang out with me.
Okay.
It'll be fine.
I win again.
You're good!
It's still fine!
Hey, Fujinuma...
I wanna go home.
Yeah.
Okay.
Snow...
RESTAURANT ROW
Answer the questions below:
Question 1: Make a sentence using the word "pole" in it.
The polar bear from the North Pole ate the teacher.
Answer the questions below:
Question 1: Make a sentence using the word "pole" in it.
I'll pick you up tomorrow, too!
See you then!
Okay.
I said it as loud as I could.
It was for Hinazuki,
her mother inside,
and anyone else who may
have been listening nearby.
I was saying that I'm here.
X-day is almost over.
I got through it this easily?
I'm an idiot.
Coming here...
I did it!
With this one day,
I definitely changed history.
Morning, Mom.
It's not even six yet!
See you later!
What about breakfast?
After that, I couldn't sleep a wink.
And at that moment, I wanted to see
Hinazuki's face as soon as possible!
Morning, Hinazuki.
Are you stupid?
Is everyone still okay for today?
You know it!
We're gonna go to your
house and par-tay!
Then let's all go shopping first—
Hey, Satoru! Kayo!
Come here. I want your help.
Why today of all days?
We don't have a choice.
It's probably because we blew off
the last cleaning duty.
I guess...
This is heavy.
But no one's waiting for us.
That's kind of cold-hearted.
SAKAI SUPERMARKET
BARGAIN SALE
That's exactly 5,000 yen.
Okay.
Come to think of it, it was 5,000 yen
on the nose 18 years ago, too.
I was in such high spirits
because of my birthday
that I spent all the money I had.
Did Mom and I make tons of sandwiches,
but just the two of us ate them?
I'm back!
One, two...
SATORU & HINAZUKI
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!
Satoru! Hinazuki!
Happy birthday!
Y-You secretly made all this?
They said they wanted to do it
themselves, so I gave them a hand.
Don't tell me...
the after school duty, too...
Yep. We asked Mr. Yashiro.
He told us it was Hinazuki's birthday, too.
Happy Birthday
Satoru
Kayo
Well, we did want to surprise you a bit.
I was surprised!
And Satoru insisted on getting two cakes.
I'm sorry, Fujinuma.
I didn't have time to finish your present.
Were you working on something?
Yeah...
I see.
She wanted to go home early for that.
I almost had it done last night,
but I fell asleep.
Don't worry about it.
Give it to me later.
All right, everyone!
Let's make sandwiches
with 5,000 yen worth of ingredients!
Yeah!
You used all the money?!
It was a lot of fun
making sandwiches together.
Unlike 18 years ago,
we finished them all off in one day.
It's fun having friends.
Hinazuki and I got
several presents from everyone.
And then...
Open it!
Thank you, Fujinuma.
Everyone, thank you.
We'll clean up here.
Walk Hinazuki home.
I-It's cold...
Are you stupid?
W-Well, see you.
Here.
You...
and the others, too...
I'm glad we became friends.
Thank you for today.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Okay. I can't wait.
Good night.
I did it!
I won!
I changed history!
When I got home,
everyone had already gone.
My exhaustion from the day before
had reached its peak
and my tense feelings
relaxed all at once.
I collapsed then and there
and slept like a log.
MIKOTO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Crap! I'm late!
Good morning!
Satoru.
I was about to mark you as tardy.
S-Safe...
Is Kayo the only one who's late?
Hinazuki didn't come
to school the next day.
The last promise made between me
and Hinazuki was never fulfilled.