The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos,
the profession that everyone
once dreamed about and admired
came into the limelight.
Heroes of justice fighting villains
and saving people from distress.
Yes, this is the story of
how I became the greatest hero.
I'll definitely become a hero and make money
and let my parents take it easy.
You're amazing, Deku.
I keep seeing more and
more amazing sides to you.
During the cavalry battle, I thought
it'd be easier to team up with friends,
but now that I think about it,
I might've been trying to rely on you.
That's why, when Iida
said he'd challenge you,
it actually made me feel
a little embarrassed.
Uraraka...
Everyone's facing the future
and trying their hardest.
That means we're all rivals, right?
That's why...
Let's meet in the finals!
"Bakugo vs. Uraraka"
The eighth and last match of the first round!
He was kind of famous in middle school!
This isn't the face of a regular person!
From the hero course, it's Katsuki Bakugo!
Versus--
She's the one I'm rooting for!
From the hero course, it's Ochaco Uraraka!
You're the one that makes
things float, right, Round Face?
Round...?
If you're gonna withdraw, do it now.
You won't get off with just an "ouch."
Midoriya.
What was the strategy you were going to tell
Uraraka earlier for her
to use against Bakugo?
It wasn't much, really.
"Hero Analysis for the Future"
Kacchan's strong.
In a real close combat fight,
he has almost no openings,
and the more he moves, the more he sweats,
making his Explosion Quirk stronger.
He can use the blasts from his
explosions to move around in the air,
but if Uraraka touches Kacchan
and uses her Quirk to make him float,
then she would have the upper hand.
That's why...
...the first thing Uraraka should do is...
Eighth match, start!
...a swift attack!
Withdrawing isn't a choice!
All right! That's good.
Even if it's an accident, as long as
she can touch him, she can make him float!
Bakugo won't want Uraraka
to get close to him.
That's why Kacchan won't want to evade.
He'll want to counterattack!
Then, die!
Kacchan...
You usually start with a big right swing.
Here!
Here...!
If I dodge here...!
Uraraka!
Did he blast her?
Even though you're fighting a girl,
you have no mercy, do you, Bakugo?
This is no good.
Even if I knew about it,
I couldn't react in time.
I'll take care of you.
Don't underestimate me!
Oh, she made her jacket float
and sent it over there?!
She did it in an instant, too!
If I make him float now--
He moved after he saw her?
With that reaction time, it doesn't
matter if there's a smokescreen.
With Uraraka not being able to activate
her Quirk unless she touches him,
she's at a disadvantage
with Bakugo's reflexes.
Too slow!
Take this!
Ochaco...
I can't watch!
Bakugo, don't tell me...
your tastes run in that direction...
Not yet!
Uraraka keeps attacking
without rest, but... this is...
Uraraka...
Her substitution earlier didn't work,
so she's getting desperate.
What an idiot.
Hey, shouldn't you stop this?
Isn't he going too far?
I can't watch...
Hey! How can you say you
want to be a hero like that?!
If there's such a huge
difference in your abilities,
then hurry up and send her out of bounds!
Stop bullying and playing with the poor girl!
Yeah! Yeah!
There's booing from part of the crowd...
But honestly, I also feel the sa--
An elbow?! What're ya doin'?!
Was that a pro saying he's playing around?
How many years have you been a pro?
Huh?
If you're saying that with a straight face,
there's no point in you
watching anymore, so go home!
Go home, and look into changing careers!
Mr. Aizawa...?
Bakugo is being careful because he's
acknowledged the strength of his opponent
who has made it this far.
It's because he's doing
everything he can to win
that he can't go easy on her
or let his guard down.
Not yet...
She's still...
...not dead!
It's about time... I think...
Thanks, Bakugo...
...for not letting your guard down...
Huh?
It can't be helped from where Bakugo is,
but it's embarrassing for a pro in the
stands to start booing without noticing.
She kept her body low as she advanced,
concentrating Bakugo's attacks on the ground,
storing up weapons.
And then, she narrowed his field
of vision with relentless attacks
to keep him from noticing.
I'm gonna win!
A meteor shower?
You should've noticed.
She had a desperate
plan like that up her sleeve?
With this much debris,
whether he's evading or counterattacking,
there will definitely be an opening!
In that moment, I'll get close
to him with my secret move!
I'll win! I'll win and be like Deku, too!
Since you're friends with Deku,
I thought you'd be up to something...
In one shot...
B-Bakugo delivers a satisfying explosion!
He blasts boldly through
Uraraka's secret plan!
That was close...
I did as much as I could...!
But he wasn't fazed at all...
Uraraka...
Even so...
All right, let's get serious then, Uraraka!
If it were Deku...
...he wouldn't give up--
Uraraka's down!
My... body... won't do... what I want...
Uraraka...
She passed her limit a long time ago...
I-I also...
...also...
...can still...!
When I get big, I'll help you and Mommy!
I appreciate the thought, Ochaco.
But as your dad, I'd be even happier
if you could achieve your dream.
When that happens, you can take us to Hawaii!
I'll become... a hero...!
Daddy...
Uraraka's out of commission.
Bakugo advances to the second round!
"Katsuki Bakugo"
Take her to Recovery Girl.
I know.
The eighth match of the first round...
Oh, Uraraka...
Oh yeah, Bakugo advances to the second round.
If you're gonna do it, do it properly.
Now, let's pull ourselves together--
You're really letting
your personal feelings take over...
The first round is all done!
Let's move on to the next round
quickly after a short break!
"Player Waiting Room 2"
Let's meet in the finals!
Uraraka...
Whoa, Kacchan?
What the--?! What the hell
do you want?! Die, scum!
Oh, well, I'm next, so...
I was going to get ready
in the waiting room...
Also, congrats on winning the first round...
Later...
That was your idea, wasn't it?
That damned desperate plan.
You just have to be annoying,
don't you? What the hell--
It wasn't.
All of it...
Uraraka planned it all thinking
about how she could beat you.
If you thought that was
annoying, that was because...
...Uraraka was leading
you around by the nose!
Hey, Bakugo!
That was tough, huh? Playing the bad guy.
Even if it was because of the match-up,
you played an amazing villain, Bakugo.
Shut up! Be quiet!
But man, I can't believe you were able
to aim such a huge blast at a frail girl.
I couldn't help but hold back.
She completely sealed you off, Kaminari.
Y-You know what, Tsu...
What part of her was frail?
"Player Waiting Room 2"
Man, I lost...
Huh...?
I got carried away at the
end thinking I could do it, dang it.
Uraraka, what about
your injuries? Are you okay?
Yeah, Recovery Girl took care of me!
It was only moderate healing
so it wouldn't drain my stamina,
so I've still got scratches
and stuff, though.
Man, but that Bakugo was really strong!
"Frustrated"
He totally got me.
I need to work harder, too!
Are you... all right?
I'm fine! Better than expected!
"Daddy"
I mean, you immediately
started looking ahead, Deku,
and just because I lost
doesn't mean I can lose.
That's...
The draw from the seventh match of
the first round, Kirishima and Tetsutetsu!
The winner of their arm wrestling match to
decide who advances to the second round is...
Winner, Kirishima!
He advances to the second round!
--Yes...!
--The one who won his ticket was Kirishima!
My metal fatigue...
I should've eaten more iron...!
It... was a good match.
S-So youthful!
Now we've got everyone who's
advancing to the second round!
So, let's get started!
Already?
Later...
Oh, sorry Deku!
You weren't able to prepare
at all since I was here...
No, I'm fine.
I'll be watching, 'kay? Good luck.
Thanks.
Sorry about not picking up earlier, Daddy.
It's fine, sorry for
calling when you're busy.
Your mom and I watched you on TV.
You were so close!
But you were amazing!
It wasn't that close.
And I wasn't amazing.
I rushed too much in the end, too.
I didn't have a plan
for what to do after that, either.
I was completely beaten.
Is that so?
I don't understand complicated things,
but just because you lost doesn't
mean your path's been closed off, right?
There's always next year, right?
The further you advance,
the more you can show how well
you do against different types.
The scouts can't tell with just one match.
What're you in such a hurry for?
I mean...
I want to hurry and help you guys...
Ochaco, it's fine even if you don't rush.
You feeling that way shows you're kind,
so I know you'll be a great hero.
Isn't it obvious?
There's no way she's not frustrated.
Even so, I can't believe
I said that I could help...
I couldn't do anything for her...
Instead...
I'll be watching, 'kay? Good luck.
...she encouraged me again...
Endeavor?!
Oh, there you are.
Endeavor... What are you doing here...?
I watched your fight.
You have a wonderful Quirk.
You created so much wind pressure
just by flicking your fingers.
If we're talking about power alone,
yours is comparable to All Might's.
Wh-What are you...
What are you trying to say?
I must go.
Endeavor knows about One For All?
No, from the way he talked, he doesn't know.
Anyway, this is the
one person I can't let find out.
It is my Shoto's duty to surpass All Might.
His match with you will be
a very instructive test bed.
Please don't disgrace yourself in it.
Without using my damn old man's Quirk...
No...
I'll reject him completely by
winning first place without using it.
That was all I wanted to say.
I apologize for bothering
you right before the match.
I...
...am not All Might.
That's obviou--
That's obvious, right?
Todoroki isn't you, either.
All Might has his eye on you, doesn't he?
Todoroki...
It is my Shoto's duty to surpass All Might.
Midoriya...
Just remember this--
I will make that into a hero
that will surpass you one day.
Those two haven't started yet?
I've gotta watch.
Were your eyes hurt?
You must hurry to Recovery Girl--
I already went.
This is, you know... It's different.
It's different?
If that's the case, then you must've
been really frustrated earlier.
Rather than feeling regretful right now,
you should use this next match
as a source of encouragement.
Yeah.
That's true.
Thanks for waiting, everybody!
The first match of the
second round is a big match!
The man who won a huge victory in the
first round and literally left the audience frozen--
From the hero course, it's Shoto Todoroki!
On the other hand, this guy
barely made it past the first round!
What kind of fight will he show us this time?
From the hero course, it's Izuku Midoriya!
So you're here.
Todoroki...
Tokoyami, what do you think of this match?
It depends on whether or not
Midoriya jumps in close to Todoroki.
Yeah. What is Deku
going to do about that ice?
Watch carefully and prepare,
Tomura Shigaraki.
They may become obstacles to you one day.
That's a load of crap.
Izuku...
"Authorized Personnel Only"
Those two both tried to
save you, didn't they?
Yeah.
It's just a feeling, but I think those two...
...give off the same vibe.
At this year's sports festival,
both have shown top class performances!
It's like two great rivals
fighting against each other!
Now--
Midoriya versus Todoroki!
Start!
"Preview"
Here's the preview.
The battle between Todoroki
and me is finally starting.
I'll end this quickly.
It's true that just Todoroki's ice
from his right side is strong--
I told you. I will win without using
that man's Quirk and reject him completely.
I am your opponent!
What?
Next time, "Shoto Todoroki: Origin."
He remembers words that
he had forgotten once before.
"Next time: Shoto Todoroki: Origin"
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!