The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos,
the profession that everyone
once dreamed about and admired
came into the limelight.
Heroes of justice fighting villains
and saving people from distress.
Yes, this is the story of
how I became the greatest hero.
The second round of the U.A.
sports festival first-year stage is...
A cavalry battle with
the top 42 from the qualifier!
Izuku Midoriya, who placed first in
the qualifier, is worth ten million points!
It's survival of the fittest, with a chance
for those at the bottom to overthrow the top!
Bakugo and Todoroki aren't
the only ones who see you as a rival.
I will challenge you.
Uraraka.
Yes!
Hatsume.
Tokoyami.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you!
I know!
Tokoyami!
Call me Tsu!
Kacchan!
Don't get carried away!
Damn it!
Tokoyami!
I'll be taking that now.
"Cavalry Battle Finale"
It was a good plan, so I joined
the team even though it was you.
When did you lose your headband?
I don't know!
But now, there's nothing left to lose!
Shoji, full attack mode!
We're gonna steal the points from those
two teams with everything we've got!
I thought we would not have a
confrontation until later in this contest.
He seems to think highly of you, Midoriya.
Only half the time is left!
Don't stop moving.
Iida, forward!
Right!
Yaoyorozu, prepare to
guard us and conduct electricity.
Right.
Kaminari, you--
I know what I have to do!
Watch our surroundings.
It's not just one group coming for us!
Make sure you guard well...
Indiscriminate Shock...
...1.3 Million Volts!
Kaminari...!
Less than six minutes left.
We can't back down now.
Sorry, but you'll just have to bear it.
What? What'd he do?
Todoroki took care of
that crowd of teams in an instant!
He froze them after
Kaminari's shock stopped them...
I guess it should be expected,
but he took into account how a lot of
people avoided it in the obstacle course.
Nice commentary!
I might as well take these.
--Damn it!
--What? Mine, too?
The backpack's acting up?
Baby! There's room for improvement!
Oh no, it's too strong!
We can't get away!
I'll restrain them!
Yaoyorozu!
Yaoyoruzu's Creation is
too hard to deal with!
No...
Kaminari is worse.
With that level of armor,
if it had been sunlight,
Dark Shadow would've been ripped apart.
Right!
In any case, I want you
to devote yourself to defense.
You don't have to attack.
So...
Interesting.
My Quirk's offensive ability
increases the darker it is,
but it becomes fierce and
difficult to control.
On the other hand, under sunlight,
it becomes possible to control,
but its offense becomes below average.
To tell me I didn't have to attack
with my Quirk without knowing that...
It's a very unique choice,
under the circumstances.
Very well. Try using me.
I leave it to you, Midoriya.
I see... Kaminari's lightning...
As long as he keeps discharging electricity,
attacking will be difficult.
Dark Shadow will become timid.
I'm against violence...
Team Midoriya has nowhere left to go!
Decreased offense...
They don't know that, do they?
I don't believe so.
The only person I've told about
this weakness is Koda, at USJ,
and he is a man of few words.
If they don't know about it,
then we can use it to hold them back.
It's fine.
No matter what, we will
hang on to the ten million!
Class A is too simple-minded.
He got us!
What'd you say, bastard?
Give that back! I'll kill you!
You're famous, aren't you?
As the victim of the sludge incident!
Tell me about it sometime--
About how it feels to be
attacked by villains once a year.
Kirishima... change of plan...
Monoma, don't provoke him!
You'll be the same as him.
That's right. It wouldn't become a hero.
Besides, don't you often hear
about heroes who get done in
by villains who want revenge?
Bakugo, calm down!
If you don't calm down, we won't
be able to get the points back!
Forward, Kirishima!
Right now,
I'm totally calm!
We're seriously counting on you!
Go...!
Die...!
Wow, what a nice Quirk!
That's my--
Bakugo, someone has
the same Quirk as you, too?
Damn it!
Really, such nice Quirks.
Mine's better, though.
Wha...? Mine?
The same again...?
No.
This guy copied them.
That's right!
"Neito Monoma"
"Quirk: Copy"
Neito Monoma. Quirk: Copy!
He can use the Quirks
of anyone he touches
as much as he wants for five minutes.
He can't use two at the same time, though!
Well, even an idiot can figure it out, huh?
"Now!"
"Okay!"
Bondo! Picking a fight, huh?
Monoma, we just have to
keep from getting caught now.
"Go!"
With this many points,
we'll definitely make it into the top four!
After them!
It's solidifying!
Wow! I can't move!
Wait a sec!
I'll melt it with my Quirk!
Hurry!
We've got zero points right now! Hurry!
Oh, don't get mad at me.
You're the one who provoked us, right?
What did you say for the pledge again?
That embarrassing thing... Let me think...
Oh well, you've done enough for today!
I'll be number one.
Number one. Not just first place.
I'll take an indisputable first place!
One minute left!
Todoroki made it so he'd have the
ten million to himself
to seize in an instant!
At least, that's what
I thought five minutes ago!
But unbelievably, Midoriya's been able to
keep away in that cramped
space for five minutes!
Hold!
You're doing good.
He can see right through you.
Fool.
He's keeping his distance,
staying on the left side.
He's paying attention.
At this rate, if I want
to freeze them over the
shortest distance possible, I'll get Iida.
And if he keeps moving like this,
I'll do myself in if I
freeze indiscriminately.
--I'm not... done yet...
--And Tokoyami can defend
against Kaminari's electricity.
One more minute.
The bastard...!
Everyone, there's less than a minute left.
You won't be able to use me after this.
I'm counting on you!
Iida?
Hang on tight.
Make sure you get it, Todoroki.
Torque Over--
Reciproburst!
Wha...?!
What happened? So fast! So fast!
Iida, if you could accelerate that fast,
then show us in the prelims!
What was that?
By forcing the torque and rotations
to increase, I created an explosive power.
With the recoil, my engine
stalls after a while, though.
It's a secret move I hadn't
told anyone in class yet.
I told you, didn't I, Midoriya?
That I'd challenge you.
The tables are turned!
Offense and defense right at the edge!
Reining that in, Todoroki
gets the ten million!
And Midoriya is suddenly
left with zero points!
Get back in there!
As long as they have Kaminari,
we'll be at a disadvantage if we attack!
Won't it be safer to try
for other points right now?
No!
I don't know how the other
points got split up!
This is our only chance!
All right!
We'll get it back, Deku! We definitely will!
Uraraka...
I'll definitely become a hero and make money
and let my parents take it easy.
That's right...
Let me use your position!
It's not just me.
I leave it to you, Midoriya.
The feelings of the three...
...who trust in me...
I'm carrying all that right now!
With less than a minute left,
Todoroki currently has four headbands!
He's wrested away the top spot from Midoriya,
who was running away like crazy!
Will these be the top four teams
to move on to the next round?!
Second, huh? We might've done
a little too well for ourselves.
Anyway, focus on keeping that spot.
Wait!
I said, wait!
Jeez, so persistent.
As a hero, not to mention as
a person, that persistence will--
Don't act on your own, Bakugo!
Tsuburaba!
Guard!
Hey!
Yes!
"Kosei Tsuburaba"
"Quirk: Solid Air"
Kosei Tsuburaba. Quirk: Solid Air.
He can solidify air to
form walls or footholds.
The size depends on lung capacity!
You can't see this wall!
Serves you right!
He took two!
Team Bakugo seizes two
headbands to move to third place!
The rankings keep changing
in the final stages!
It's the passion of youth!
Tsunotori!
Damn it!
It's fine. We're in fourth!
Kendo's been frozen and can't move.
Yeah... As long as we
defend this one to the death,
we'll definitely...
I told you to say something
if you're gonna jump!
But this means we'll definitely
get through to the next round--
Not yet!
What?!
We're gonna get an indisputable first place!
Monoma...
Class B's strategy was
certainly reasonable and good.
But there's just one thing
that is unfortunate...
I couldn't brace myself
enough earlier on my own!
Go!
We'll get our points back, too,
and then go for the ten million!
Jeez...
Flat Face! Tape!
It's Sero!
You missed!
Raccoon Eyes!
Lay down a weak dissolving solution
in the direction we're going!
My name's Mina Ashido!
Young Bakugo, you understand
very well without being told, don't you?
Those who are always aiming for the top,
and those who aren't.
Their difference...
You didn't take the difference in
tenacity into consideration, did you?
Bakugo is merciless!
If he's gonna do it, he's gonna be thorough!
He's, you know, a perfectionist!
Now, there are only seconds left!
Next! We're going to
where Deku and Todoroki are!
It was the first time... I tried
to use this power on a person...
It's fine. Either way, I'm not gonna hit him.
Like cutting through air...
...break down the opponent's defenses!
My left... What am I...?
It hurts, but it's not broken!
He's turned them inside out
to hide the point values,
but he took the ten million
last and put it on,
so it must be the one on top--
This one!
I got it...
I got it!
With just eleven seconds left,
there's an angry retrieval here, too!
Wait a minute. Isn't this the wrong headband?
They got us!
Just in case, we changed
the position of the headbands!
You were naïve, Midoriya!
Todoroki, get a hold of yourself!
That was close!
Oh no! Team Midoriya didn't
retrieve the ten million points!
Seventy points...
...isn't good enough!
Time's just about up!
Start the countdown!
Tokoyami!
Kaminari!
Damn Deku!
Bakugo!
Huh...?
Uraraka!
Got it!
Yaoyorozu!
The ten million points are...?!
Half-and-Half Bastard!
Time's up!
That's the end of the second round,
the cavalry battle!
Bakugo!
You okay?
Damn it.
Now, let's take a look at
the top four teams right away!
In first place, Team Todoroki!
Even though we won, it felt like
we were skating on thin ice.
Sorry...
I caused everyone trouble...
That's not true.
Without you, we would not have won.
In second place, Team Bakugo!
Ah, we were so close!
Well, second place isn't bad.
All's well that ends well.
Do you really think that's how he feels?
In third place, Tetsute--
Huh? What, it's Team Shinso?!
When did you come from behind?!
Thanks for your hard work.
Deku?
Um... I'm really sorry...
Todoroki was clearly
shaken by your first attack.
I had hoped to get the ten million points,
but things don't always go as you wish.
Even so, I got one.
I took the one on his head
where his guard was the weakest.
Midoriya, this was thanks to the
opening you created with your last spurt.
In fourth place, Team Midoriya!
These four teams...
...will advance...
...to the final round!
I won't use this to attack.
That's what I had decided,
but I was overwhelmed...
I can't...
At this rate, I'll be doing
what my old man wants...
Now, we'll take an hour's break
for lunch before we start
the afternoon festivities!
See ya!
Hey, Eraser Head, let's go grab food.
I'm going to sleep.
What happened?
Before I knew it,
we had zero points, and it was over...
Could it be punishment...
...for taking the small one's
points in such an indecent way?
My headband's gone!
I can't accept this!
How disappointing...
Mina, congratulations.
Well, Bakugo just let me join
to use against Todoroki's ice,
so I don't know if it reflects my abilities.
Iida, I didn't know you had
a special move like that! No fair!
It has nothing to do with fairness!
I just wasn't using it as intended.
"That was fun."
"I'm hungry."
I wanted to do something
that could compete with Midoriya.
It's that manly thing, huh?
Speaking of which, where is that Midoriya?
Where's Deku?
"Faculty and Student Entrance"
What did you want to talk about?
Hey!
Long time no see!
Let's have tea, Endeavor!
All Might...
U.A. High School's sports festival!
The first years have
finished their second game.
The sixteen next-generation heroes
moving on to the final
round have been decided!
"Izuku Midoriya"
Izuku...!
I'm so glad! You really worked hard...!
But... But just don't get injured...!
"Preview"
It's the preview!
Midoriya, All Might has
his eye on you, doesn't he?
I'm not trying to pry about that.
But I'm going to beat you.
Todoroki, why are you going so far--
I don't care what you are to All Might...
Your eyes are like ice!
I will go higher than you.
Even if you say that,
there's a reason why I cannot lose!
Next time, "The Boy Born with Everything."
The Class A girls will cheer
with cheers of cheerleading!
"Next time: The Boy Born with Everything"
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!