As I watched the ice guy,
I thought, "I can't beat him"!
Damn it! Damn it, damn it!
Hey, you too, Deku!
I'm just...
I'm just getting started!
You hear?
Here, I will become number one!
Midoriya.
I'm going to beat you.
I pledge--
That I'll be number one.
Bastard, don't declare war to the wrong person!
Not yet!
What?!
We're gonna get an indisputable first place!
Die...!
Stun Grenade!
Bakugo wins!
With this, the final match will
be between Todoroki and Bakugo!
"Player Waiting Room 2"
Shoto's... That child's left side
sometimes looks very unsightly to me...
Come at me with your full power!
It's your power, isn't it?!
I wonder when it started.
Until I fought with Midoriya,
I didn't even think about thinking about it.
Mom, I...
Huh?
Hey, why are you here?
It's waiting room...
...oh, this is room two? Damn it!
"Irritated"
I may have gotten the room wrong,
but what's with that attitude
against your opponent in the final?!
Hey, hey, hey...
Where are you looking, Half-and-Half Bastard?!
That's...
Huh?
...what Midoriya said to me, too.
That guy acted recklessly and came to
destroy all the problems I'd been carrying.
You guys are childhood friends, right?
Was Midoriya like that
when you were young, too?
You looked like you were asking for help...
Are you all right? Can you stand?
That damn nerd...
Who cares about him?!
Seriously, who the hell cares...?
Your family circumstances, and your feelings...
I don't care about that stuff!
Just use the flames on your left on me, too!
I will hold them down from above.
I'll crush that half-and-half
bastard indisputably,
and then I'll be at the top!
"Todoroki vs. Bakugo"
It's finally the last battle of
the U.A. High School sports festival!
The top of the first years will
be decided with this one match!
"Final"
"Shoto Todoroki" "Katsuki Bakugo"
The final, so to speak!
From the hero course, Shoto Todoroki!
Versus--
Also from the hero course, Katsuki Bakugo!
Now--
Start!
Damn it!
Todoroki gets a blow in right away!
Is he trying to avoid close combat with Bakugo?
Has the winner been decided already?!
It's not on the same scale
as in his match with Sero.
He aimed his attack while
being careful of what'll come next.
What's that sound?
It's Bakugo's doing.
Did he dig his way out through
the ice like a mole with his explosions?
That's so weird!
The stronger the Quirk...
...the more imprecise the attacks!
He avoided his right side and grabbed him?!
Wow!
Are you underestimating me?!
Idiot!
He avoids going out
of bounds with a wall of ice!
Looks like fun!
Use your left!
Use it, Shoto!
Stop screwing around.
Am I not strong enough to make you use it?
With the way he grabbed Todoroki's left side
on purpose and timed his explosions...
He's been doing his research.
That kid's abilities shine every time he fights.
I see.
Todoroki's moving well, too,
but his attacks are too simple.
Ever since the match with
Midoriya, he's lost his touch.
Bastard...
I'll show you what'll happen
if you make a fool of me!
I'll kill you!
I want an indisputable first place!
I can't get that even if I beat
scum that underestimates me!
There's no point if I can't
get higher up than Deku.
If you have no intention of winning,
then don't stand in front of me!
Why are you standing here, damn it!
I want... to be a hero, too...!
Sorry, Bakugo.
Ever since I fought Midoriya,
I became unsure of what I should do...
Of whether or not I was correct...
Todoroki!
Don't lose! Do your best!
Midoriya!
That damn nerd!
That's it! That's it!
If you're gonna stand in front of me,
then you should just concentrate on winning!
Howitzer...
...Impact!
He added momentum and rotation to the huge blast
he showed us in his fight with Uraraka!
He was like a human projectile!
It looks like Todoroki didn't fire off the
huge blast he used in his match with Midoriya,
but the winner is--
Huh?
You put out your flames!
Hey...
Hey!
Stop screwing around!
Didn't I tell you that
there was no point, damn it?!
To get first place like this! Like this?!
Like...
Todoroki is out of bounds!
Which means, Bakugo wins!
"Katsuki Bakugo"
And now, all of the
events have been completed!
The winner of this year's
first-year U.A. sports festival is...
...from Class A, Katsuki Bakugo!
All of the first-year events for this year's
U.A. sports festival have been completed.
And now, we will begin the award ceremony!
Wow...
What the heck?
He's been struggling ever since waking up.
But man...
That first place is all over the place.
He is like a man-eating fiend.
In addition to Tokoyami,
there is also Iida in third place,
but he left early for family reasons.
Thank you for your understanding!
Was that for the media?
That's too bad. Iida was really into it.
Yeah.
Uraraka, Midoriya.
This is sudden, but I must leave early.
A villain got my older brother.
Your brother? You mean Ingenium?!
Yeah.
How's he doing?
I don't know the details.
So I'm going to go visit him directly to see.
He is a likable hero who honors
the rules and leads people.
I set my sights on being a hero
because I want to be like my brother.
Ingenium...
For Iida's sake, too, I hope that you're okay.
Now, we will award the medals!
The presentation of the medals will,
of course, be by this man--
It's All Might!
--Our very own hero, All Might!
--I have brought the medals here!
I talked over you...
This year's first years are so lucky.
They've got the number
one hero watching them!
Now then, All Might, please present
the medals, starting with third place.
Young Tokoyami, congratulations.
You sure are strong.
You are too kind.
However, in order to fight
well against different types,
you must not rely only on your Quirk.
If you train your own strength more,
then you'll have more options when you fight.
Yes, sir.
Young Todoroki,
congratulations.
I assume there is a reason you
did not use your left side in the final?
I had an opportunity during
my match with Midoriya,
but then I became unsure of myself.
I think I understand a little of
why you are interested in him.
I wanted to become a hero like you.
But I didn't think it would be right
for me to be the only one to break away.
There is still something I must settle.
The look on your face is
completely different from before.
I won't ask about the details.
I'm sure that you will be able
to do what you need to do.
Yes.
Now then, Young Bakugo!
This is too much.
Good job doing what you said
you would during the player pledge!
All Might...
First place like this...
"angry angry angry angry"
...is not worth anything!
Even if the world recognizes it,
if I don't recognize it myself, then it's trash!
His face is amazing...
Right.
In this world where people are
constantly being compared publicly,
there are not many who can keep aiming
for the top of an unchanging scale.
His face is amazing...
Take this medal, okay?
Think of it as a "wound," so you never forget!
I said I didn't want it!
Now, now.
I told you, I don't want it!
Here.
Well, they were the winners this time!
But listen here!
Anyone here could have
ended up on these podiums.
It's just as you saw--
Competing! Improving each other!
And climbing even further!
The next generation of
heroes is definitely sprouting!
So, I have just one more thing to say!
Everyone, please say it with me!
Ready, go--
--Thanks for your hard work!
--Plus Ultra!
What?! It should've been
"Plus Ultra!" there, All Might!
Well, I thought everyone worked hard...
The phrase "worthy opponent"
can also mean "friend."
It might set my teeth on edge,
but it was a day where we had no choice but to feel it.
Good work.
So there will be no
school tomorrow or the day after.
I'm sure the pro heroes who watched
the sports festival will want to recruit you,
but we'll consolidate everything
and announce it when you get back.
So rest well, and look forward to that.
Yes, sir!
And then, the environment we were
in started to change gradually.
"Hosu General Hospital"
Please do not run in the halls!
Mother!
Tenya!
How is Tensei doing?
Tensei!
Tenya, keep your voice
down and put on a mask...
The anesthetic wore off earlier,
and he regained consciousness.
He is still in a haze.
If he had come into surgery two
minutes later, it would have been too late.
Tenya... Mother...
Tensei! Big Brother Tensei!
Even though... such an accomplished
younger brother... like you... looks up to me...
I'm sorry... Tenya...
Your big brother... lost...
Tensei...!
Shoto, where are you going?
The hospital.
What? All of a sudden? Why?
Wait, Shoto, is it okay not to tell Dad?
Yeah.
Why do you want to see
Mom now, after all this time?
I'll be back.
It went "bam!" and blew him away!
--It was amazing! So cool!
--That's amazing.
"Bam!" and "Crash!"
Oh, that's so cool.
Yeah!
Mom, I'm going crazy...
I can't take it anymore.
Every day, the children seem
to become more and more like him...
Shoto's... That child's left side
sometimes looks very unsightly to me...
I can't raise him anymore...
I feel like I shouldn't...
Ever since that day, I thought
my presence would put pressure on Mom,
so I never went to see her.
I'm sure she continues
to be bound by me... by Dad...
"Mrs. Todoroki"
That's why, in order to aim to become a hero
again with this body, with everything I have...
It's okay for you to become
who you want to be.
In order to become my ideal hero,
I need to see her and talk to her...
There's so much we need to talk about...
Mom...
Even if she doesn't want it,
I will rescue her from here.
That is my starting line.
That is how I feel.
For lunch today, I'll have...
...something cheap. Hmm...
Mochi!
Huh?
The door's unlocked...?
Ochaco!
We're here!
Dad, Mom?!
Why are you guys here?!
We came to throw you an after-party.
Seeing our daughter trying so hard,
we couldn't not come running.
What? What about work?
Did you come on the bullet train?
What? What?
At least say something first!
Seven times! Isn't that crazy?
Y-Yeah...
Ever since the cavalry battle,
I lost consciousness seven times!
The last two times were
pretty much from dehydration.
You were way more heroic than me, huh?
Of course!
Suddenly hearing that you had a Quirk,
and having that Quirk
be a super risky power--
I-I-It was a sudden variation or something
that isn't impossible medically speaking,
and anyway, now I have a Quirk...
Anyway, I'm so glad...!
I'll support you, but that
doesn't mean that I don't worry.
Yeah.
I just keep going after what I yearned for,
but that made those watching me worry.
In order to become a cool hero who can
smile and live up to everyone's expectations,
I need to be able to do things in
a way that won't make others worry.
That's the starting line where
I can finally say, "I am here!"
Izuku! Do you want to watch
the recording? It's in HD! HD!
I-I'll watch later by myself...
Die...!
Damn germs!
"irritated irritated irritated"
Katsuki, don't wake up
at noon and start yelling!
"Preview"
Here's the preview!
At the next hero informatics class,
we'll be coming up with code names--
hero names for the upcoming hero internships.
We're gonna do something exciting!
Show what kind of hero you want
to be in the future in your name.
It's obvious what mine should be,
but with my current abilities,
I don't have the right to call myself that.
Hurry it up.
Y-Yes, sir!
Next time, "Time to Pick Some Names."
With this, most of the hero names
for Class A have been decided.
"Most"?
"Next time: Time to Pick Some Names"
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!