I'm scared.
I'm scared to get
to the heart of my own mind.
I think you're doing good work here.
But how can I say this...
BOYS' FLIGHT
If you don't dig deeper,
the readers won't be
able to see you in the work.
You're 29, right?
That's kind of a tough fit
for our magazine.
26 more days until the 2006 World Cup
begins in Germany...
Every day, the words cross my mind.
"If I had done this back then..."
But they don't take
the sincere form of regret.
The words are just an excuse
that come to mind, then disappear.
I'm scared to get
to the heart of my own mind.
ERASED
I'm going out on a delivery.
Okay. Be careful.
I'm going out on a delivery, too.
Okay, be careful!
Fujinuma, don't eat any pizza on the way.
I don't get it.
What is that, a Gen Y joke?
Wasn't planning to.
That girl says the same thing
to me every time I see her.
In fact, it's the only thing she's said to me.
It doesn't seem like
she has any special feelings for me.
Weird girl...
Well, not like I'm interested
in high school girls...
I'm positive.
It happened again.
Where is it?
What seems out of place?
Hey, trucker! Stop!
Hey! Driver!
F-Fujinuma?
What are you...
Dammit!
I shouldn't have gotten involved!
But...
- Are you okay?!
- That was close!
What the hell is this?
That thing where my life
flashes before my eyes...
There, see?
Nothing good comes of getting
involved with strangers.
Oh well...
My dying doesn't make any difference.
Huh?
His eyes opened.
Good morning, Fujinuma!
You were out for two days!
Katagiri?
Do you know who you are
and why you're here?
Satoru Fujinuma, 29 years old.
I was chasing a truck
and got into an accident.
Good! The doctor said
you hardly suffered any injuries.
It's a miracle!
Do you want me to call someone?
A friend or girlfriend?
Nah. There's nobody
I want to bother telling.
Snip-snip.
What's that?
A Gen Y joke?
It's like you're covered
with a thin membrane.
You don't seem like the type
who opens up to people.
You never laugh either.
But I do kind of see you in a new light.
How's that?
You saved a kid's life, right?
I was there.
They say the truck driver died
of a heart attack while driving.
I'm surprised you noticed it.
I just got lucky.
After that, the truck
crashed into a warehouse,
so you and the driver
were the only casualties.
Casualties...
After I explained everything
to the manager,
he said, "Tell him not to worry about the bike
or the car he hit, just come back to work."
Thanks.
You smiled for a second there!
Katagiri, why do you work there?
I'm surprised you got
right to the heart of it.
Did I?
Yeah. No one's ever
asked me that before.
I have a dream.
I see.
That's all you're gonna ask me?!
Hey...
When you tell other people
about your dream...
don't you think, like,
"But what if it doesn't happen for me?"
I'm not especially
embarrassed to talk about it.
I feel like if you say
the words over and over,
it'll actually happen
somewhere along the line.
Those words...
For some reason, they resonate with me.
But I'm not going to tell you
what it is, Fujinuma.
It's not like we're close or anything.
Well, I'll tell the nurse you're awake,
then I'm going home.
Bye-bye.
Weird girl...
I call the phenomenon "Revival."
Even though I know it's not beneficial
for me, I always get involved.
I usually go back
between one and five minutes,
where everything is the same as before.
It's always right before
something bad happens.
I find myself searching for the thing
that doesn't feel right,
as if someone put me there
with the order to "Prevent it!"
As a result, I've kept trouble
from happening again and again.
In most cases, negative
incidents just come out even.
Once in a while, it turns negative for me.
Welcome home, Satoru.
Mom...
I went to the hospital,
but you were still sleeping,
which was boring so I came here.
Is your head all right?
Fine.
I was shocked.
I mean, they said
it was a head-on collision.
I'm going to stay with you for a while.
Why would you do that?
My adorable son's head
hit a moving vehicle.
The least I can do is watch over him.
I said I'm fine.
And I only have one futon.
There's a sleeping bag in the closet.
That works for me.
Go to a hotel.
It's a waste of money.
Oh, that's right! I'll reimburse you
for the hospital charges!
Keep it. We'll use it
to pay for my room here.
I'm her son,
but even I can't believe she's 52 years old,
because the woman never changes.
Satoru, can you get to Ueno
without changing trains?
No. Figures. You're here
for sightseeing, aren't you?
I have come all the way from Hokkaido.
Besides, I'd get bored having to
look at your face every day.
You haven't even seen me
for a full day yet.
Come on, let's eat.
Sorry. I took your futon and TV.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I'd rather have that
than try to be quiet if I go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night.
Look, you don't have to tiptoe around me
if you use the toilet in the middle of the night.
I won't wake up.
Yokai...
On to our next story.
The first-grade girl from Saitama
who went missing yesterday evening
was found safe and sound
this morning on a road in Yokohama.
Hey, Satoru...
She was taken to the hospital
but suffered no injuries.
Do you remember?
What?
What happened in the neighborhood
when you were in fifth grade.
The Ina Police Station has reported
that an unemployed man
Your memories are probably hazy.
from Nishi-ku, Yokohama
was with the girl at the scene.
We tried desperately then
He has been arrested on suspicion
of abducting a minor.
to get you kids to forget
even a little of what happened.
Your life was in danger.
When I was in fifth grade...
An abduction...
Two of my classmates went missing.
Go! Go, go!
When I was little, a local guy,
Yuuki, often played with me.
His name really wasn't Yuuki,
but that's what I called him
because he'd always say,
"Yuuki, yuuki! Courage, courage..."
W-Want me to guess about the most
p-popular kid in your class?
He's cheerful and good at sports.
He speaks his mind
and sometimes screws around,
but is serious
when it comes to one thing.
That's incredible.
Popular people are usually that guy.
W-What if you tried imitating him?
In one or two areas.
Just as much as you can, without being
embarrassed, but with courage.
Six months after the disappearances,
Jun Shiratori was arrested
as a serial kidnapper and murderer.
It was Yuuki.
Episode 1
Flashing Before My Eyes
You bought way too much.
Is it too heavy for you?
Well, you can have curry for days.
Ah, see?
This is why I told you not to run.
Let's go back and get you another one.
Satoru, what's wrong?
Nothing...
Is it too heavy for you?
Well, you can have curry for days.
Revival?
Ah, see?
This is why I told you not to run.
Let's go back and get you another one.
Crap. I don't know what it is!
Come on...
What's gonna happen?
Mom... Would you look around?
Don't you... have a weird feeling?
What are you talking about?
Come to think of it, you once told me
the same thing a long time ago.
Did I?
It was about a small fire back then.
Was he... looking at me?
Nothing happened?
Fujinuma!
Hey!
SCHOOL ROUTE
I don't believe it! Your mother?!
I thought she was your big sister!
Do you believe in yokai?
I do from today.
But are you fighting?
No.
Your name is Airi?
I'm making curry for dinner.
Would you like to eat over?
I am Airi Katagiri!
Thanks for the invite!
I'll help you make it, too!
She's coming over?
I'm starving!
You drew manga?!
You're surprised?
No, not at all.
It's true. You've got
your own Wikitanika entry.
Don't do a search on me.
Why not? It's great!
Well, let's eat.
It's not great. That's why
I don't want you to do it.
Thank you for the meal!
It's delicious!
Thank you.
At first I thought you were too young
to be his girlfriend, but you're not his girlfriend.
Too bad, you're a good cook.
Sorry we're not dating.
To me, Fujinuma is, how can I put it?
A friend I can respect.
What? Is it too spicy?
No, it's good.
Thank you again!
Well, I'll give you a lift to the station.
You're going home already?
You should spend the night.
Katagiri is a high school student.
Thanks for having me over
for dinner, Satoru.
No problem.
Just keep an eye out for cops.
Sure.
Welcome home.
She's my co-worker.
Don't look at her
as potential wife material.
You're dense.
You have a chance with that girl.
She said she respects you.
I'm telling you, it's not like that!
She was just being polite.
Don't take it seriously!
That Airi girl isn't the diplomatic type.
Oh, by the way, the landlady
came over for the rent.
Is that right?
Satoru... About this afternoon...
In the supermarket parking lot...
What about it?
The abduction case was never solved.
What?!
I'm obviously kidding.
The Hokkaido Elementary School Student Serial Killer Case
The Last Serial Killer
of the Showa Era
Death-row Inmate Jun Shiratori
NIPPON
SHOWA'S MOST SHOCKING CRIMES
KAYO HINAZUKI (10 YEARS OLD)
I remember.
That girl was one of my classmates,
one who was abducted 18 years ago.
Kayo Hinazuki.
She was always at the park alone.
It's not like we were friends, but...
That was the last time I saw Hinazuki.
I could've saved her!
If I'd said, "Let's walk home together,"
Hinazuki would still be...
That's the thought
I wanted to forget the most.
And Mom probably really did
try to erase it from my memory.
If you don't dig deeper,
the readers won't be
able to see you in the work.
"Wa" on the plate means it's a rental.
That was definitely
an attempted abduction.
Did he change his mind
because he saw me?
He hid his face when our eyes met.
He knew me.
And I know him from someplace.
It's on the tip of my tongue...
Where? When?
Serial Abductions and Murder
One Culprit Responsible for Kidnappings
I remember!
That man, he...
The killer...
It may not have been Shiratori after all!
Hello?
Long time no talk.
It's Sachiko Fujinuma.
18 years ago, so the statute
of limitations is up...
But...
I'm positive he committed the same crime
with the same basic M.O. over and over.
That case isn't closed yet.
I have to talk to Satoru.
The time has finally come
to talk to him about it.
Satoru?
I was right...
Have to... call Satoru...
Tell him not to come home...
and I have to apologize.
I could've saved her!
I'm sure it wasn't Yuuki!
It wasn't Yuuki, Mom!
I should have believed him then.
Even if the police didn't...
I should've believed him.
Satoru...
I'm sorry...
Well, I'm off! See you tomorrow!
Yeah, see you tomorrow!
- See you tomorrow!
- See you!
Oh yeah, Satoru...
How about I guess what you had
for breakfast this morning?
Curry!
You're right.
Yes!
With as much as she made, of course
I'm gonna eat it for breakfast too.
Hey, ask your mom
if I can put in a request.
That curry was so good!
All right, all right.
See you.
Sheesh...
Gimme a break...
Mom! What are you doing?
This isn't your house back in Hokkaido.
At least lock the door.
Hey...
Answer me.
No way... Cut it out.
Wake up! Mom!
Mr. Fujinuma, last night
your mother shared curry with me...
Wait!
CHIBA PREFECTURAL POLICE
Mr. Fujinuma had blood on his hands...
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
I need to take you down to the station...
What is this?
Wrong. You're wrong.
It wasn't me...
It wasn't me!
Hey, don't run!
Did I...
have another Revival?
But where am I?
I know I've seen it before...
but somehow...
Yo, Satoru! You're gonna be late!
Huh? Who's that again?
A backpack?
Ice Hockey Club 1988 National Champions
1988?