Endeavor's my old man.
He's been stuck as the
number two hero for forever.
It is my Shoto's duty to surpass All Might.
If you have something from
the number one hero, then I...
...have even more reason to beat you.
In my memories, my mother is always crying.
"Your left side is unsightly,"
my mother said as she
poured boiling water on me.
Without using my damn old man's Quirk...
No...
I'll reject him completely by
winning first place without using it.
No matter what you are to All Might,
I will rise above you with just my right side.
But I can't lose, either.
I have to live up to the
hopes of those who supported me.
I will beat you, too!
But you want to be a hero, don't you?
It's okay for you to be one.
Before I knew it, I had forgotten
what happened after this...
"Shoto Todoroki" "Izuku Midoriya"
The first match of the second round!
At this year's sports festival,
both have shown top class performances!
Midoriya!
First, he'll come at me with ice.
Versus--
Todoroki!
It'll be dangerous to let
him use that power as he likes.
It's like two great rivals
fighting against each other!
Now--
The instant we start...
Start!
Go!
Smash!
So cold!
Just the wind is already this cold?!
Just as I expected.
He was prepared to injure
himself to negate the attack.
Wow! Midoriya stopped Todoroki's attack!
He didn't know what scale of
attack Young Todoroki would use,
so he abandoned control
and fired off a shot at 100%!
It's true that that was the only thing
he could do against the ice attack...
However!
Smash!
He stopped it again!
Damn...
From what I know of Todoroki's fighting,
he always attacks in an instant,
so I don't have much data on him.
Data... During this fight,
I need to find an opening...
The ice he's stuck behind him is probably
how he plans to keep from being blown away.
Which means, I was right to use my fingers.
It's likely that it could even work against
a 100% smash where I sacrifice my arm.
I've got to look carefully...
Think...
Find it...
I've got six more chances...!
You're...
Five more chances!
It started?!
Kirishima, good job making
it to the second round.
Yeah, I'll be up against you next, Bakugo.
Let's have a good fight!
I'll kill you.
I'd like to see you try!
But man, you and Todoroki can both shoot off
powerful attacks that cover a lot of ground.
Like "Bam!"
And you can do it with no time lag.
I'm not just shooting them off.
Don't underestimate 'em.
Huh?
If you overuse your muscles,
the muscle fibers tear,
and if you keep running,
you'll run out of breath.
There's a limit to how much
power I can produce, too.
That's why I designed my costume
so that I could fire blasts
in excess of what my
body allows without any risk.
Quirks are physical abilities, too.
They must also have some kind of limit.
If I think about it like that,
I guess that makes sense...
Then, against the instant-killer
Todoroki, Midoriya wants...
...an endurance match, huh?
I'll end this quickly.
Smash!
I've used up all the fingers on my right hand!
Todoroki doesn't recoil from
Midoriya's power and gets in close!
Damn it...!
Oh no, he's so close!
That's a lot more powerful than before.
Are you trying to tell me... to stay away...?
It's not just his Quirk.
His judgment, application skills, mobility...
All of his abilities... are strong!
He's already better than the average pro...
It's like that's what you get
from the son of the number two hero.
What, you're that beat up just
from defending and running away?
He's trembling...?
Is that how it is...?
Damn it...
Sorry...
Thanks, Midoriya. That guy's face
is clouded over thanks to you.
Without using my damn old man's Quirk...
No...
I'll reject him completely by
winning first place without using it.
With your arms like that,
you can't fight anymore, can you?
Let's finish this.
Todoroki keeps attacking
with overwhelming power!
Here comes the finishing ice attack!
Where are you looking?
Bastard...
With your broken finger...?
Why are you going so far?
You're trembling, Todoroki.
Quirks are physical abilities, too.
There's a limit to how much
cold your body can take, isn't there?
And isn't that something you could
solve by using the heat from your left side?
Everyone's fighting
with everything they've got...
To win and get closer to their dream...
To become number one...
You want to win with just half your strength?!
You haven't put a single
scratch on me yet, you know!
Come at with me with everything you've got!
You want to win with just half your strength?!
You haven't put a single
scratch on me yet, you know!
Come at with me with everything you've got!
Young Midoriya...
Todoroki isn't you, either.
That boy...
Midoriya...
What are you planning?
Everything I've got?
Did my damn old man buy you off or something?
Now I'm angry!
His movements are...
...slow!
It's because frost fell on his body...
Unlike the limit to my power,
it's probably like the MP in a game...
Was the scale during his fight
with Flat Face the upper limit?
In close quarters, you won't be
able to do anything about it!
The instant I lifted
my right foot... This guy...!
Imagine... the microwave...
It won't explode...
It won't... It won't...! It won't...!
A solid hit!
We've got some action!
He got a hit on Todoroki!
Even though Midoriya
looks way more beat up...
I can't believe he went
on the offensive here!
Why...?
The ice isn't coming as fast...
Should I stop it, Midnight?
That Midoriya's probably thinking,
"Recovery Girl will heal me anyway,"
and is being reckless.
He's full of adrenaline right now,
so he probably isn't feeling much pain...
But, those injuries...
They probably can't be fully healed in one go.
Even if he wins, he might not
be able to fight his next match.
You can't keep saying you can't help it
because you can't control your Quirk.
His power's gone down,
but he's gained some control.
He's not just fighting recklessly.
This is the best he can do
to win at this point in time.
But man...
Even if it can be healed,
to be able to jump into intense pain
like that requires a lot of resolve.
What is stirring him up?
All Might.
I want to be like him.
In order to do that, I have to be
strong enough to become number one.
My motivation might seem
trivial compared to yours...
I can't make a fist...!
Smash...!
Why are you going so far?
Because I want to live up
to everyone's expectations...
I want to be able to smile...
and respond to them...
To be a cool hero...
That's what I want to be!
Shoto...
That's why--
Everyone's giving it their all!
There's no way I can know all of
your circumstances, or your resolve.
But for you to become number one without giving it your all,
to completely reject your father...
Right now, I think you
should stop screwing around!
Stand up!
If you're downed by something
like this, forget beating All Might,
you won't even be able
to take the small fry villains--
Please, stop! He's only five!
He's already five! Get out of my way!
Mom...!
Shut up.
I don't wanna, Mom...
I... I...
I don't want to be like Dad...
I don't want to become
someone who bullies you, Mom!
But you want to be a hero, don't you?
It's okay for you to be one.
As long as you have
a future you feel strongly about.
That's why... I will win!
I'll surpass you!
Don't look at that, Shoto.
They're from a different world than you.
Mom, I'm going crazy...
I can't take it anymore.
Every day, the children seem
to become more and more like him...
Shoto's... That child's left side
sometimes looks very unsightly to me...
I can't raise him anymore...
I feel like I shouldn't...
M... Mom...?
I...
Good grief, this is an important time, too...
Where's Mom?
Oh, she injured you,
so I put her in a hospital.
It's your fault.
You're the one who made Mom...
I will reject...
...my old man's power...
It's your power, isn't it?!
Yes, that's right!
Children inherit Quirks from their parents.
But the really important
thing is not that connection,
but recognizing your own flesh and blood--
recognizing yourself.
That's what I mean when I say:
"I am here!"
"Looking back at that time"
You see?
But you want to be a hero, don't you?
It's okay for you to be one.
Before I knew it, I had forgotten...
You don't have to be a prisoner of your blood.
It's okay for you to become
who you want to be.
Th-This is...!
The fire's here...
In battle...
...I will never use my left.
He used it!
You made him use his left side...
Young Midoriya, don't tell me
you're trying to save Young Todoroki...?
Even though you want to win...
Damn it...
To help your enemy...
Which one of us is screwing around now?
I want... to be a hero, too...!
Shoto!
Huh?
Have you finally accepted yourself?!
That's it! Good!
It all starts from here for you!
With my blood, you will surpass me...
You will fulfill my desire!
Endeavor suddenly
shouts encouragement...?
Such a doting father.
Wow...
Why are you smiling?
With those injuries...
In this situation...
You're crazy...
Don't blame me for what happens next.
Midnight!
If they keep going, it'll be bad--
His body won't hold up!
Try to get close...
...and give him everything I've got!
Come at me with your full power!
Midoriya...
Thanks.
Hey!
What the heck?!
Man, seriously?!
What happened?
Just because something is
powerful doesn't mean it's good,
but this is amazing...
What was that just now...?
What the heck is up with your class?
The air that had been cooled thoroughly
was suddenly heated up and expanded.
That's what created this explosion...?
Just how hot was that?!
Jeez, I can't see a thing!
Hey, who won the match?
M-Midoriya is out of bounds...
Todoroki advances to the third round!
"Shoto Todoroki: Origin"
"Preview"
I am Tenya Iida,
the class representative of Class A,
and I am responsible for the preview.
This is the same way
you started the preview before!
Midoriya, I swear that
I will win and advance for you, too!
Yeah, I'm sure you can do it, Iida!
Yes, now that I have come this far,
I must become number one and tell Tensei.
Next time, "Fight on, Iida"!
Hello, Mother? What happened to Tensei?
What in the world happened
to my brother, Tensei?!
"Next time: Fight on, Iida"
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!