I don't think my dad could endure
being branded a thief.
And I guess my mom
did suspect that he really did it.
It made me want to stop
believing in people.
I thought maybe I would feel better
if I could just hate
either my mom or dad.
But after years passed,
my mom let it slip,
"Why couldn't I believe him back then?"
That made me want to keep
loving both of them.
I realized that believing
in people was my strong point.
ERASED
What is this?!
I saw Airi go in there before!
S-She's probably still inside!
Hey!
Airi!
Airi! Can you hear me?!
Wake up!
Heavy...
Hey! Airi!
Dammit!
I won't make it.
I'm not strong enough.
Manager!
Never count on a manga artist.
We're goin' down, non-stop!
Brace yourself!
Satoru, go out the back.
Don't get Airi mixed up
in your business anymore.
I'm getting the credit for this.
Will Airi be okay?
And that fire...
Don't tell me he did that too...
That's right!
Sachiko Fujinuma's Phone
Incoming Mail
This is Satoru Fujinuma.
Stay right where you are.
The fire was set to target Airi.
And it looks like I did it!
Airi slipped the phone to me
so the police couldn't see this message.
Then he knew from the beginning
where Airi lived.
He followed her.
He may be closer than I think.
I'll look for him.
Either I get caught first
or I find him first.
Koiwa. Koiwa.
Please do not leave
any articles on the train...
COLUMBUS RECORDS
Yes?
Who is this?
Why don't you just
identify yourself already?
It's Satoru Fujinuma.
If you are Satoru Fujinuma,
nice to meet you.
I've been waiting for your call.
Yes, by all means.
No, not here.
Let's meet at a public place.
I haven't given you
my name yet, have I?
I will when we meet tomorrow.
Because you may have
murdered Sachiko Fujinuma.
KOHAKUTEI COFFEE SHOP
Welcome.
Hi, Satoru. Over here.
Good to meet you.
I'm Sawada, formerly of TV Ishikari.
I'm relieved. You really are Satoru.
Yeah, you resemble your mother.
Him!
I'm sure you're on guard, but I didn't
tell anyone about this meeting,
and I didn't murder
your mother either.
You don't suspect me?
Of course not.
Why not?
Because she didn't raise
the kind of son who would kill her.
I see.
Yesterday I remembered
that it was in my pocket.
This keeps snowballing.
I'm pathetic.
My string of blunders
makes me partially responsible.
Thinking it's your fault
after the fact is just pointless.
Those are Sachiko's words.
I always liked them.
Shall we talk about her phone call?
Please.
COIN LAUNDRY
Sawada, do you remember?
The serial killings 18 years ago...
Of course.
Jun Shiratori is on death row,
but he still claims to be innocent.
It's just as Satoru said.
Shiratori didn't do it.
Now I know who did.
Let's meet at Koiwa Station tomorrow.
I should've asked her for the name.
Why don't we talk about a past incident?
About Kayo Hinazuki's death...
On the night of March 2nd, 1988,
Kayo was beaten by her mother
and her mother's boyfriend,
and locked in the storage shed.
She froze to death.
The police suspected Kayo's mother
and the boyfriend of hiding the body.
But sometime between 10
and 11 pm on the 2nd,
Kayo disappeared from the shed.
Kayo's mother discovered
the disappearance at 12:30 am on the 3rd.
She called your house and casually
inquired about Kayo's whereabouts.
Jun Shiratori had taken her away.
The footprints made
by rubber boots around the shed
matched Jun Shiratori's boots.
HOKKAIDO POLICE
The police went public
with their version of the events.
Shiratori knocked Kayo out
with physical violence
and then photographed her.
He put her in the family
business cold storage room
and used an atomizer
to speed up her death by freezing.
When her temperature dropped
to 20 degrees, she was brain dead.
Shiratori waited about 30 minutes,
when she had almost
zero chance of recovery,
then returned her frozen corpse
to the Hinazuki shed before sunrise.
Yuuki would never have done that!
Kayo Hinazuki, Hiromi Sugita,
Aya Nakanishi...
Shortly before those three disappeared,
there was a series of abduction
murders in the next town over.
The culprit was quickly arrested,
but like Jun Shiratori,
he denied any wrongdoing.
Now.
Including your present circumstances,
do you notice a common link?
I've been ridiculed for years for being
a weirdo freelancer reporter
who investigates crimes
that have already been solved.
The truth is, none of them are solved!
Both Kayo Hinazuki and Sachiko
were murdered by the same bastard
who gives the police another suspect!
And now he's in this city.
He's a crafty son of a bitch.
He buys time by framing someone else,
which reduces eyewitness testimony
and changes the circumstances
at the scene.
As a result, the investigation gets
further and further away from himself.
This is going overboard.
So he tried to shut her up.
Satoru Fujinuma...
He won't be able to get at her now.
And what about the high school girl?
Is she an accomplice?
She helped him kill the mother
and once that was done,
he tried to silence her.
That's terrible.
Getting that girl caught up
in his madness...
You're wrong.
Airi, you have nothing to apologize for.
That's right. A stalker went after you.
You must have been terrified!
Aunty, that's not what happened.
Don't blame yourself. I'm sorry
that we didn't notice anything.
It's not what you think.
The police are after the culprit.
You have nothing to be afraid of now.
They've got it wrong.
Fugitive Suspect
Responsible for Arson?
Suspect Targeted
Co-worker's House (Chiba)
I can't believe they're going
after Satoru for murder and arson.
That's impossible...
Who would believe me...
A message was sent
from Sachiko's phone to that girl?
Yes.
According to the news,
she wasn't badly hurt,
but I'm sure she's still in the hospital.
This is it.
I see.
He plotted to help the investigation along
by framing you for arson.
I think that's part of it,
but I was already a suspect.
I can't believe he would target her,
Airi Katagiri, just for that.
In other words, you think
she was already his target?
In order to frame me
as my mother's murderer,
he had to find out what time
I'd be home from my job.
So in the 24 hours plus
between my mother's sighting
of his attempted
kidnapping and her murder,
he went to the pizza shop
and looked at the shift schedule.
Airi must have seen his face then.
Maybe he's even someone I know.
I see. Then he's someone
who could get behind the counter
at a pizza shop to look at the schedule.
We may be able to use
this to reach the bad guy.
I'm going to the hospital.
Okay.
There's a report on the murders
from 18 years ago on my computer.
You can take a look if you like.
I think Jun Shiratori suspects
his own father of being the killer.
Regarding an alibi and evidence,
it's possible that his continued
refusal to say anything
that might incriminate his father
made himself look even worse.
That would be like Yuuki,
who dearly loves his father.
A classmate saw Kayo Hinazuki
and Jun Shiratori together three times.
Satoru Fujinuma's testimony
was deliberately ignored,
but it seems much was made
of the other student's testimony.
FINAL SUSPECT LIST
Jun Shiratori
Seiichiro Shiratori
Isao Ishidou
Shinji Sakashita
Tadashi Yanagida
A list of suspects.
I don't know any of these names
other than Yuuki and his father.
And there are only five?
The police guessed
that Hiromi Sugita was murdered
after being mistaken for a girl.
From this, the police made up
a final list of five suspects
who weren't acquainted
with Hiromi Sugita.
We're doing folk dancing today.
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
Seriously?!
I don't wanna hold hands
with some ugly girl.
I'd much rather hold hands
with you, Hiromi!
T-That's gutsy!
I know why Hiromi was murdered.
He knew Hiromi was a boy,
so he killed him to keep himself
off the list of suspects.
Jun Shiratori was arrested after someone
in the neighborhood reported
that he'd been talking
to a third-grade girl when she was alone.
Photos taken at the time
of Hiromi Sugita's death
were confiscated from Shiratori's
food storage room.
The police concluded that Jun Shiratori
had pedophiliac tendencies.
They also collected pedophilia-related
publications from his bedroom.
That kind of stuff wasn't there!
Perfect Day for Pleasure
Perfect Day for All You Can See
Strawberry: Beautiful Girl Photo Album
High School Girls' Uniform Reference Guide
Erotica
Paper Craft
It's all camouflage to draw
attention away from himself!
The list of suspects
before Hiromi's death...
Previous Suspect List
His name is on here!
Ms. Katagiri, I'm coming in.
2F NURSES STATION
Excuse me...
I'm here to visit,
but is the restroom over there?
Yes.
No vacancies...
except for room 201.
She's sleeping.
Is that right?
Crap! I'm gonna spring a leak!
Please pardon my
bad manners, Airi Katagiri.
You're not Satoru Fujinuma, are you?
Right. I'm his friend, Sawada.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Airi's mother.
Episode 6
Grim Reaper
I'm positive Satoru didn't do any of it.
He didn't kill his mother.
And he didn't set a fire to target me!
During the fire, he came
to the house to rescue me!
Your manager saved you, right?
You must be confused
after inhaling all that smoke.
I don't know
what they're asking you, Mom,
but they think I may be an accomplice!
Not being believed
is what hurts the most.
When I think
about who believes in Satoru...
Airi...
Even now, I think
I should've gone after him.
Go ahead.
It's all right.
I believe you, Airi.
Shoot!
I forgot to turn it off.
Public Phone
Thank goodness! You had it on!
Airi?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm as good as new.
More importantly, can I see you?
At the usual place...
What? No, stay away from there!
Airi, I can't have you—
It's all right! I promise, I'll go alone!
Go! It's flying!
And here I am...
She may have been speaking
to the real killer on the phone.
Getting Airi involved
will only make it worse for her.
SHINJI
What the heck?!
That's not flying at all!
Strange...
I don't know why...
Doing this gives it
what's called dynamic lift.
Will it really fly now?
It sure will.
It's true! Awesome!
It went by the river!
That's flyin' too far! Cool!
What's an adult doing here
at this time of day?
Good question...
Is this how people thought of Yuuki?
I'm here, Satoru.
Yeah.
As promised, I came alone.
I'm ashamed for thinking
it might be a police trap.
I said that out loud!
You better think that way!
You're a fugitive, Satoru.
But I'm glad you trust me.
Yeah.
The shop?
I think this Nishizono guy is fishy.
Nishizono?
I've seen him two or three times.
The manager treats him with respect
and from the badge he wears,
I'd guess he's a city councilman.
He would've been able
to see the schedule,
and it's not unlikely
that he knew where I lived.
I've met him before, briefly.
PREVIOUS SUSPECT LIST
Jun Shiratori
Seiichiro Shiratori
Isao Ishidou
Shinji Sakashita
Makoto Kawata
Sachiko Fujinuma
Nishizono?
He wasn't on the list.
A fake name?
But a city council member
wouldn't be able to use a fake name.
I think he targeted me
because I know his face.
Dammit! It isn't coming together.
The final piece won't fit!
Satoru...
I know how you feel,
but you can't beat yourself up over it.
I have unfinished business
from a long time ago.
It's an idea I had for a manga story.
About a grim reaper
who makes a scheduling mistake
that results in the death of a child.
He struggles to put things
back the way they were,
but the more he acts, the more
other people involved suffer.
Even though he means
to do the right thing,
when he gets mixed up in it,
other people get hurt.
It's like you right now, Satoru?
Don't you think, Airi?
Are you stupid?
For example, I'm not hurt.
That stuff about other people is just
the reaper's subjective impression.
I think that grim reaper
should have more faith in himself.
I'm sure that what's in front of you
is all still in progress.
The conclusion is still up ahead
and nobody knows what it is yet.
Airi, I'm really glad that we met today.
I said that out loud!
Satoru Fujinuma, I presume?
Satoru!
Don't interfere!
Airi!
Satoru Fujinuma,
you're under arrest for murder
and attemped murder resulting from arson.
The suspect was apprehended at 4:50 pm.
CHIBA POLICE
Why?!
Satoru didn't do it!
He would never do it!
Satoru!
Either through being arrested or Revival,
I was prepared to have my
relationship with Airi disappear.
And here it is, the last time I'll see her.
The thing I should do right now is...
Satoru!
I'm sorry!
I bet they followed me here!
Even though I promised
I'd come alone!
I have to give Airi
what I wanted to give her.
Just like she did for me.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
It's my fault!
What would a hero say at a time like this?
Isn't it hard fighting all on your own?
Airi, you've got it wrong.
I can still hang in there
because you believed in me.
Thank you, Airi.
I'm glad I trusted you.