The world has become a superhuman society,
and about 80% of the world's population
now has some kind of special trait.
In this world swirling with chaos,
the profession that everyone
once dreamed about and admired
came into the limelight.
Heroes of justice fighting villains
and saving people from distress.
Yes, this is the story of
how I became the greatest hero.
The U.A. sports festival is drawing near.
Joining a famous hero agency will
get you more experience and popularity.
The U.A. sports festival
is something pro heroes--
no, the whole country--is
watching closely. A big event!
That is what I brought
you here to talk about!
The next All Might...
the fledgling Symbol of Peace...
Izuku Midoriya.
I want you to tell the world "I am here!"
The sports festival
first-year stage qualifier,
an obstacle course race!
Who could've predicted the developments
at the beginning or this conclusion?
Right now, the first person back
in the stadium is that man...
Izuku Midoriya's made a huge splash!
The second round of the U.A.
sports festival first-year stage is...
A cavalry battle with
the top 42 from the qualifier!
Those at the top will suffer more.
You'll hear this many
times as you attend U.A.
This is what "Plus Ultra" means!
Izuku Midoriya, who placed first in
the qualifier, is worth ten million points!
What the hell can you do?
You're Quirkless!
The eyes around me are
different from junior high...
The top spot I got for
an instant because of luck...
Even so...
You're quick to understand, huh, young man?
Even so,
is it really this heavy, All Might?
"Strategy, Strategy, Strategy "
Now then, I will explain
the rules of the cavalry battle.
The time limit is fifteen minutes.
Each team is worth the
total of its members' points,
and the riders will wear a headband
with that number on their foreheads.
Teams will try to grab each other's
headbands until time runs out,
and try to keep as many points as they can.
"Velcro"
"Made to be taken off easily"
Stolen headbands must be
worn from the neck up.
So the more you steal,
the harder it'll be to manage them!
And the most important thing is
that even if your headband gets stolen,
or if your team falls, you're not out!
Which means...
...since there are 42 people, there will be
ten or twelve teams
on the field the whole time?
That's tough.
One strategy could be to let someone
take your points first so you'll be more free.
It's hard to say without seeing how all
the points end up getting split up, Mina.
During the game, it'll be a cruel
fight where you can use your Quirks.
But it is still a cavalry battle.
You'll get a red card for attacks that
are trying to make people fall on purpose!
You'll be removed immediately!
Damn.
Now, you have fifteen minutes
to build your teams. Start!
Fifteen minutes?
--Points don't really matter in my case.
--Hey, be on my team.
--Someone in the top ten, pick me.
The people I want on my team are...
...that person, and that person!
The U.A. sports festival is more about
simulating the competition they'll face as heroes
than seeing how prepared
they are to be heroes.
Huh? What are you talking about?
In a world crowded with hero agencies,
in order to put food on the table,
there are times when you have to
kick down others in order to show your stuff.
That was what the obstacle
course race in the qualifier was, right?
Doesn't that just pain your heart?
You little--
You did that quite gleefully, remember?
On the other hand,
even if you're business rivals, there are
many cases where you have to work together.
Oh, that's just like the cavalry battle!
If you win, your teammates also win.
You have to think about compatibility
and other people's Quirks...
It's a give-and-take situation...
Coordinating with your sidekick,
and joint Quirk training
with other agencies...
The kids are doing stuff now that will be
their way of life after they become pros.
They've got it rough.
Team up with me!
What? Bakugo, team up with me!
Don't you want to team up with me?
I don't know what Quirks you all have!
What?!
I can understand not knowing Class B's, but--
He doesn't pay attention
to what's around him at all, huh?
Even though his personality's like that, he
still came in third and has two hundred points.
Considering the all-purpose use of his Quirk,
it makes sense that he's popular.
Hey! Todoroki chose his team already!
Bakugo, team up with me!
Weird Hair.
I'm Kirishima! At least try to remember!
My hair's not that different from yours!
You're gonna be the rider, right?
Then who'll be a front horse
that can take your blasts?
"Here"
Someone with guts.
Not really, but yeah!
Me, with my Hardening!
I'll be a horse that'll never waver!
You're gonna get it, right? The ten million?
Shoji... Shoji...!
I wanted to team up with
a girl, but it's no good!
Please team up with me!
I'm tiny, so I can't be a horse!
But no one'll be my horse if I'm the rider!
With your huge body and tentacles,
you could cover my whole body, can't you?
Right? Right?
That's a great idea, Mineta.
As expected, people are teaming up
with their classmates, huh?
Since no one has a good grasp of what
Quirks those in the other classes have.
I need to do something quick, too....
"Isolated"
...about the current state
where everyone's totally avoiding me!
Um, Ojiro...?
Sorry...
As I thought, no one wants to try
to keep the points for the whole game.
It'd be a better strategy to try
to steal the points at the end.
And unlike Todoroki or Kacchan,
I didn't use my Quirk,
"confidence confidence confidence confidence"
so no one has any confidence in me...
Deku!
Let's be a team!
Uraraka!
I-Is it really okay?
Everyone'll probably be after me
because of my ten million points!
If we run away the whole time,
then you'll win, right?
I-I think you're overestimating
me, Uraraka...
Like I would!
Anyway, it's better to team up
with people you get along with!
"Heart-squeeze"
What's the matter? You look ugly, you know.
Oh, nothing... It's just that you're so bright
that I can't look straight at you...
Actually, I wanted to
team up with you, too. Thanks!
"Urine...?"
For teams, it's best to be with people
you can communicate with smoothly, right?
Yup, yup!
Actually, with your Quirk
and one other person...
...I thought of a plan!
Iida.
The three of us would be
horses with Iida in the front!
And then, if we use Uraraka's Quirk
to make Iida and me lighter,
we'd be able to maneuver easily.
I see!
It's better to have someone
physically strong as the rider,
but I haven't decided who...
Anyway, this is all I could think of
to keep running away until the end...
I expected no less, Midoriya...
But I am afraid I have to refuse.
Ever since the entrance exam,
I just keep losing to you.
You are a wonderful friend,
but that's why, if I just keep
following you, I will never grow.
Bakugo and Todoroki aren't
the only ones who see you as a rival.
I will challenge you.
Iida...
It's already begun.
Everyone's an enemy.
That's right. I'm at the top right now.
I can't just play at being friends.
As I thought, this is great.
You stand out!
Team up with me, person in first place!
Ahh, so close! Who're you?!
I am Mei Hatsume, from the support course!
Oh, that weird person from back then.
I don't know you, but let
me use your position!
She's honest!
If I team up with you,
then I'll inevitably become part of
the team everyone's watching most, right?
If that happens, then my super cute babies
will inevitably be seen
by the big companies.
That means, in other words,
that those big companies will see my babies!
W-Wait a minute.
Babies and big companies? What are you--
--And, I think you guys will also benefit.
--Oh, she's not interested in me...
The support course develops equipment
that helps heroes deal with their Quirks.
I have a ton of babies, so I'm sure
you'll be able to find one that you like!
Oh, has this one caught your eye?
I made this based on a certain hero's backpack,
adding my own original twist to it.
Could you be talking
about the Buster Hero, Air Jet?
I like him, too!
Really?
Yeah, his agency's close,
so I went to tour it before.
--I see. They're already getting along.
--By the way, my Quirk is...
Not being able to team
up with Iida was a blow,
but with Hatsume and Uraraka...
I just need one more person.
It looks like everyone's pretty set
on their teams already, huh?
No, that's fine.
The power our team's missing...
The one who can fill that spot is...
Deku?
...you!
Almost everyone here
has their eyes on Class A.
Why is that?
And like Tetsutetsu said,
Class A is full of themselves about it...
It's strange, isn't it?
The only difference between us
and them is that they fought villains.
Why were those of us in Class B happy
with being in the middle of the pack?
Let's let that arrogant Class A know, guys.
Now then, it's about time to get started!
Come on, wake up, Eraser!
After fifteen minutes
to form teams and talk strategy,
twelve cavalry teams are
lined up on the field!
There are some interesting teams out there.
Now, raise those battle cries!
It's time for U.A.'s bloody battle!
Light the signal fire!
Yes!
Uraraka.
Hatsume.
Tokoyami.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you!
I chose you three because I thought
it would be the most stable formation.
Kaminari, you'll be the left wing,
keeping the enemy away with your electricity.
Yaoyorozu, you'll be the right wing.
You are in charge of insulation and
assisting with defense and movement.
Iida, you'll be in front as the main source
of mobility and physical defense.
So you will attack and create diversions
with ice and fire, then, Todoroki?
No.
In battle...
...I will never use my left.
"My heart's pounding!!"
All right! You've made your teams, right?
I'm not gonna ask if you're ready or not!
Tetsutetsu.
No hard feelings, okay?
Yeah!
Now, let's go!
Counting down to the brutal battle royal!
Three!
We're aiming for...
Two!
...one thing.
One!
Start!
It's basically a battle
for the ten million points!
Midoriya, I'll take that!
An attack without delay, huh...
The fate of the pursued...
Fate...
Make your choice, Midoriya!
Choice...!
Of course, our move is to run away!
I won't let you!
What is this?
We're sinking?!
That person's Quirk, huh?
All right!
It's no good... I can't get out!
Uraraka! Hatsume! Turn your faces away!
He flew?
Thanks to the support course, huh?
Follow them!
Jiro!
I know!
Tokoyami!
Good!
Dark Shadow, keep watch over our blind spots!
Got it!
Wow, that's so cool!
The defense that we were lacking...
You're more than making up for it
with your omnidirectional mid-range defense!
That's amazing, Tokoyami!
You're the one who chose me.
We're landing.
Making everyone other
than Uraraka weightless,
so our weight is just Uraraka
plus the equipment and clothes.
What do you think of my babies?
Aren't they cute?
Cuteness can be made, you know.
Excellent mobility!
The babies are amazing, Hatsume!
Right?
It's because I'm making them float...
We're going after them, too!
Come on, Jiro, time to get revenge!
Hey, wait, Hagakure! Your headband's gone!
When did that happen?!
Profiting while others fight.
Now then, even though barely two
minutes have passed since we've started,
It's already turned into a free-for-all!
Fights over the headbands
breaking out all over!
Ignoring the ten million points and going
for second to fourth places isn't bad, either!
Fighting?
No, this is...
...a one-sided pillage!
Shoji?
What? By himself?
But it's a team battle!
Let's put some space between us for now.
We can't be caught standing
still against multiple opponents!
What?
What's wrong, Uraraka?
I'm stuck!
That's Mineta's...
Where'd it come from?
From here... Midoriya...
What? Is that allowed?
It is!
I didn't expect any less from you, Midoriya.
Asui, too?
That's amazing, Shoji!
Call me Tsu!
Team Mineta makes use of the overwhelming
difference in their sizes! They're like a tank!
Midoriya, get away!
My baby was torn apart!
Sorry! But we got away!
Kacchan!
Don't get carried away!
Damn it!
Tokoyami!
--He's gotten separated from his horses!
--What's with this guy?
Is that okay?!
Nice catch!
It's a technicality, so it's okay!
It wouldn't have been if he'd
touched the ground, though!
Thanks, Uraraka!
It's hard to control with just one foot.
Yeah, I know.
Landing like this is inefficient...
We can't run to the air anymore.
We'll have to survive this with our increased
mobility from Uraraka's Zero Gravity
and with Tokoyami's Dark Shadow.
As expected, everyone's
after the first place team,
and Class A is in hot pursuit!
Everyone's got skills!
Those Class A guys are good.
With all those flashy moves,
even just watching's fun!
There's this much difference just
from their experience fighting villains!
Now, let's take a look
at each team's points...
It's been seven minutes! Here are
the current rankings up on the screen!
Huh? It's kinda...
What? Wait a minute!
Other than Midoriya,
Class A isn't doing so well...
Bakugo? What?
Class A is too simple-minded.
He got us!
What'd you say, bastard?
Give that back! I'll kill you!
Since Midnight said it was the first game,
it wouldn't make sense for them to cut
a ton of people in the qualifier, right?
Assuming they'd keep about
forty people for the next stage,
we just made sure we stayed
within that number as we ran,
observing from the back the Quirks and
personalities of those who would be our rivals.
There's no point in being obsessive
over winning in the prelims, right?
You did this as a class?
Well, it wasn't a consensus,
but it was a good idea, right?
Hey, they're coming.
It's better than going
after a temporary "top"
like a horse with a carrot
waving in front of its face.
Oh, while I'm at it, you're
famous, aren't you?
As the victim of the sludge incident!
Tell me about it sometime--
About how it feels to be
attacked by villains once a year.
Kirishima... change of plan...
Before we get Deku,
let's kill all these guys!
Class B had a long-term strategy
that involved throwing the qualifier, huh?
It's true that they could leave a stronger
impression by overturning the mood
that favored Class A before
the sports festival started.
But based on their way of thinking,
it means they won't necessarily come after me.
Everyone, it'll be easier to run aw--
Less than half the time is left now!
It won't be that easy, huh?
The cavalry battle is about
to enter the second half!
In this unexpected rise of Class B,
who will wear the
ten million points in the end?!
I'll be taking that now.
"Preview"
I am Tenya Iida,
the class representative of Class A,
and I am responsible for the preview.
L-Let's talk about the next episode, Iida.
I will challenge you!
That's the other extreme!
I will defeat your team in the cavalry battle
with a result that will not bring
shame to the Tenya hero family
and like my older brother, Tensei,
I will become an upstanding--
He's talking about himself after all, huh?
Next time, "Cavalry Battle Finale"!
"Vroom, vroom" sounds
are coming from Iida's calves!
Go beyond!
"Next time: Cavalry Battle Finale"
Plus Ultra!