MIKOTO ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
21st GRADUATION CEREMONY
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
Congratulations!
My original life, 1988.
Kayo, Hiromi and Aya Nakanishi
had disappeared,
and then their bodies were found.
I blamed myself for not being able
to save any of them.
I made an effort to forget about all of it.
What was left
was a gaping hole in my heart.
There have been many fun things,
sad things, successes and failures.
Today you graduate elementary school,
but there is still so much that's missing.
That goes for me, too.
And yet, I think filling up
that missing something...
is what life is!
ERASED
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm Satoru Fujinuma,
a 5th-grader at Mikoto.
I'm Kenya Kobayashi.
I'm Hiromi Sugita.
Have we met before?
You're Aya Nakanishi, right?
I hear you're good
at playing the piano.
Yeah, I'm pretty good.
Have we met at piano class?
No, that's not it...
Hey, what are you reading?
Oh, this?
KING LEAR
SHAKESPEARE
Shakespeare.
King Lear!
I've only read Romeo and Juliet!
My parents recommended the piano
and Shakespeare to me.
What are they talkin' about?
You wanna get a little closer?
I thought I saw you before!
You're the kids who're always sneaking
into that building across the river!
The hideout...
So it's totally in the open from here.
Hideout?
How childish.
Y-Y-You...
Don't call it childish.
Boys are always sneaking around
building "secret bases" and "hideouts."
I bet you're playing
at being superheroes, aren't you?
D-Don't make fun of superheroes!
Satoru!
Well, I have to go.
Bye!
Wait!
- Kazu?
Huh?
Wh-What do you want?
Hideouts...
show man's adventurous spirit!
If you have free time, visit our hideout!
Then you'll understand!
You're all weirdos!
Childish...
Yesterday was fun, wasn't it?
They're here after all.
Can a girl even understand
"adventurous spirit"?
The gloves I left here
and forgot about 18 years ago...
It looked like she didn't.
I don't like spending time
on leveling up.
That's what makes it fun.
Hey, Satoru, Nakanishi should be
going to the park soon.
It's okay.
I can see her from here.
I see.
Yesterday was a failure.
But how can I get close to her?
I had free time
so I'm here to see your hideout.
Welcome to our hideout!
5th Grade, Class 4
See you!
Bye-bye!
Are you going to see Aya again?
Well, yeah.
We'll both go to the hideout later.
HOPE
So see you later!
Later, Sensei!
You mean "goodbye"!
It's strange to think
of those two together.
Then I guess this solves
the Aya Nakanishi problem.
Yeah.
Um... Satoru...
Kenya too... Thank you.
I think getting rid of someone's
"alone time" is a great thing.
Since both of my parents work,
the house is always empty
when I come home, so I can understand.
I was thrilled when you did it for me,
but for Kayo and Aya, too.
Hey!
Let's go to the hideout!
I'm sick of waiting.
Huh? Where's Kazu?
He went to meet Aya.
Why?
Why...
Aya knows where the hideout is, right?
Yeah, that's true, but...
Well, whatever! Let's go!
Y-Yeah!
Goodbye, Sensei!
Hurry up!
There's no rush!
Wait for me!
That's right!
Aya Nakanishi.
Hiromi Sugita.
And Kayo Hinazuki.
He murdered the three of them
the first time around,
but this time,
they're out of his target sight.
Still, now that clues have been lost,
will I be able to find him?
See? Now he looks
even more like a girl.
Amazing, isn't it?
Satoru...
Is this the end of "playing detective"?
Of course not. It's not over yet.
In 2006, Mr. Sawada said
Mom knew who the real killer was.
COIN LAUNDRY
I think it was someone
Mom knew back in 1988.
It's not like Sensei's candy,
but after the killer lost his targets,
I bet anything
he's looking for a substitute.
STAFF ROOM
Move.
Well, we're going to watch
the ice hockey match.
- Is Hamada gonna be in it?
- Of course.
Wow.
Well, tell him I said good luck.
- Sure!
- See you later.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Have you noticed how Yanagihara
has been alone a lot lately?
Misato?
She's kind of been
on the outs with everyone
ever since that business
with the lunch money.
I see.
I'll try talking to her on Monday.
Okay.
March 15th 1988
Thank you!
I may be a little late today.
That's fine, but call me when you know
what time you'll be home.
Sure. See you later!
See you later, Satoru!
Goodbye!
We get to ride in Sensei's car!
Really?
We can go ahead,
leaving you-know-who behind.
Good idea!
How can I start
a conversation with her?
Let's do it!
A bus?
Satoru...
I hear Misato's the next person
who's "alone"?
Yeah, but...
She may be heading
for Wakaba Gymnasium.
Really?
Mr. Yashiro said he invited her
to cheer on Hamada.
Come to think of it, she was alone
at the game last week too.
Thank you!
Want us to go with you?
Nah, I think I'm better off on my own
this time. And it's just a look-see.
I see.
If you're still playing detective,
I want a full report tomorrow.
Of course!
If anything happens,
come to the hideout!
I will! See you later!
- See you!
- See you tomorrow!
- Bye!
See you!
He makes a big deal out of it every day.
I know.
Even though we're going to
see him tomorrow...
It's colder in here than it is outside.
Hamada!
Go, go, Kouichi!
Shut up, ugly! Just watch,
with your mouth shut!
We can say what we want!
Kouichi! Watch your mouth!
There'll be no dinner for you!
You're not serious?
There she is.
And she is alone.
All right! Start warming up!
Okay!
At any rate, the killer lost
two targets at once.
Is she just the person to make up for it?
The bathroom...
The game starts in five minutes!
Right!
It's taking her too long.
EXIT
I just went out for a sucker.
What's wrong?
The game's going to start.
What are you doing here?
U-Um...
Uh, I wanted to talk to Misato.
Misato?
Huh?
- Did Misato go outside?
- Yeah.
The game hasn't started yet.
SHIRATORI FOOD PRODUCTS
Yuuki's family truck?
Sensei! There's something
I need to check on right away!
Help me!
If this is true, we're talking a crime.
We call it "playing detective."
We pretend there's a kidnapper at large,
then talk to and befriend girls
who are alone a lot.
It's supposed to be a precautionary
measure against abductions.
I get it.
You may be playing, but it's effective.
Thank you, Sensei.
Satoru, your seat belt.
Huh?
Oh, it's been sticking lately.
There!
So you've noticed
that Misato has been alone a lot lately.
No, not until Hiromi
brought it to my attention.
Even so, I respect your spirit and drive.
Really?
But this time I used my difficulty
in talking to her as an excuse,
and as a result,
Misato has become like bait.
Bait, huh?
You're pretty serious.
So there's a flip side to your sudden
friendly overtures with people recently.
Yeah. I wanted to fill
the hole in the heart.
Other people's and my own.
Crap. I just regurgitated
Yashiro's own line.
We have a lot in common, Satoru.
That's exactly my philosophy in life.
I intended to bring that up
at the graduation ceremony
ever since I was put
in charge of sixth grade.
It seems you regret
using Misato as a lure,
but there's no need to feel guilty
or ashamed about it.
The essence of good deeds
and evil deeds is the same.
They're both no more than a person's actions
to make up for a defect in themselves.
That's an extreme way of thinking.
To get closer to someone recently,
I've taken all kinds of measures.
Sometimes I'm straightforward.
Sometimes I throw a curve ball.
I've even tried using
what can be called "illegal moves."
Boy, it's been fun.
Um... You're talking about a girlfriend?
Certainly, there are similarities
with a romantic situation.
I guess "filling the hole in your heart"
is the commonality.
Want a candy?
Thanks, Satoru.
But there is no candy in there.
After all, this isn't my car.
Episode 10
Joy
What do you mean it isn't your car?
Your happiest moment...
Don't you find that gets
updated again and again?
My latest "happiest moment"
happened today.
Filling up that missing something
in your heart is the finest moment.
Finding what you're looking for
and then obtaining it...
The more difficulties there are, the greater
the happiness when you overcome them.
I don't get it.
What's he talking about?
HARASOKAI
Dissolves fast
Laxatives?
Satoru, you lied to me about one thing.
You said you're pretending
there's a kidnapper,
but you've actually confirmed there is one
and now you're acting on it.
I resisted that idea.
I couldn't believe it.
Rather, I didn't want to believe it.
That someone was anticipating
my thinking.
Don't worry.
Misato isn't in that car.
The only person in that vehicle
is the driver, Jun Shiratori's father.
WILD CAMPING SITE
I had no idea until that day
I saw you tailing Aya Nakanishi.
The day I dropped you guys off is the day
I was going to carry out my plan.
Still, it's funny, isn't it?
Here you were, trying
to snatch my prey away from me,
and I seriously gave you
advice on how to do it.
That was the second time
you prevented my plans.
That's when I began to suspect
it was more than coincidence.
Misato was ostracized, so I encouraged her
to go to the hockey game
and then told Hiromi about it.
Satoru, if you came, my suspicion
would turn into conviction.
That you're my enemy.
I don't believe it.
I waited for the right time, then gave
Misato a drink laced with laxative.
I'd ordered bentos
from Shiratori beforehand.
It can't be!
All of the pieces fit into place,
just as I planned.
This is my true form.
By the way, I switched
to this car right before coming.
My standards for choosing a car
are a little different from everyone else.
I have several cars of the same make
and color in the area,
dummies that I can use
at a moment's notice.
Although this is the first time
it's come in handy...
I'm an idiot.
It was so obvious.
Kayo's going to be okay now.
I just couldn't accept it.
The name Manabu Yashiro
was on Mr. Sawada's list of suspects, too.
Jun Shiratori
Seiichiro Shiratori
Isao Ishidou
Sachiko Fujinuma
Junya Saitou
Manabu Yashiro
Shinji Sakashita
It's just that my mom's name
was on there too,
so I disregarded the meaning of the list.
I had so much trust in Yashiro
that I rejected any doubts.
But...
the killer is right next to me...
Yashiro!
It's snowing, huh?
That won't come undone.
Game over.
For you and me.
Satoru, I still can't believe it.
You thoroughly anticipated
my plans and crushed them.
To be honest, I'm stunned
that you cornered me like this.
It's like you've seen the future.
I don't want any hard feelings,
so let me just say this.
You've interfered with my plans,
but what I'm about to do is not for revenge.
I truly do respect you.
I want you to think of this
as my sublimation
for not being able to satisfy my desires.
I thought you said
it was game over for you, too!
Satoru, you've won peace for this town.
Isn't that what you wanted?
And what I get to have is your death
at my hands and for my sake.
Yashiro! I won't die
until I see you destroyed!
That's what they call aiming too high.
Yashiro! Bastard!
You go to hell!
Dammit! Dammit!
I'm going to leave this town.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
Crap...
Cold!
I can't...
Crap!
Can't feel...
Crap...
Mom...
What is it, Satoru?
When I look up, our eyes meet.
Everyone...
Satoru!
Thank you, Satoru.
Kayo...
Airi...