5th Grade, Class 4
Kayo Hinazuki
Mom...
Kayo!
Where have you been
for the last few days?!
You...
You!
So you were the ones behind this!
What do you think you're doing,
hiding someone else's daughter?!
You made me worried about her!
Be prepared because I'm going to sue!
Have you looked for Kayo at all
during the past three days?
What?
Are you... trying to paint me
as the bad guy?!
Go to hell!
Kayo! Let go of me, idiot!
Made you worried about her?
You were only worried about yourself.
What?!
ERASED
Dammit!
What?! What are you doing, Kayo?!
Let go! You're not gonna listen to me?!
That's enough, Ms. Hinazuki.
Kayo doesn't want to see you like this.
How about you?! Treating me
like a bad guy in front of Kayo!
Who the hell do you think you are,
kidnapping someone else's daughter?!
Shut up!
What kind of parent throws
her daughter in a shed
and doesn't do anything
after she's gone for three days?!
You have no idea about the pains
and responsibilities of being a parent, brat,
so you shut your smart mouth!
You—
You are Ms. Akemi Hinazuki?
We're with the Ishikari Development
Bureau's Child Consultation Center.
We've come to discuss
your daughter Kayo with you.
You tricked me...
Goddamn both of you!
It seemed you wouldn't agree
to meet with us,
so we enlisted
Ms. Fujinuma's cooperation.
Who ever said I wouldn't meet you?!
Please forgive my presumptuousness.
Sorry I asked you to do this.
Not at all, Mr. Yashiro.
I had a few words for her too,
so I'm actually grateful
that I could help.
They're the criminals
for abducting my daughter!
Call the cops!
No, first we need to discuss your
usual relationship with your child.
What are you talking about?!
What about my relationship with Kayo?!
We've decided that your daughter, Kayo,
needs to be taken into custody.
Into custody?! I'm her guardian!
You revoked your guardianship
by failing to look for your daughter
when she went missing for three days!
It's because of that brat over there!
Why are you treating me
like a criminal?!
All right, all right, Ms. Hinazuki.
Please calm down.
Fine!
I'll go to the police myself!
They can settle this!
Come on, Kayo!
- W-Wait, Ms. Hinazuki!
- We need to talk!
Please calm down!
S-Sensei...
Come on! Come on, I said!
Kayo!
You come with me!
Akemi!
Akemi...
Mom?
I'm sorry.
We've been estranged ever since
I made you break up with that man,
but I've been worried about you
and Kayo all this time.
I know very well how hard it is
for a woman to raise a child on her own.
You must have been so lonely.
It must have been hard.
I should have helped you.
But I made you...
DIVORCE REGISTRATION
take all of it on by yourself.
Everyone... This is my fault.
Please don't think badly of Akemi.
Mom...
Mom! Mom!
I bet those tears were out of self-pity.
Kayo wasn't moved either.
She wouldn't look
at her weeping mother.
Akemi, don't worry about Kayo.
I'll take good care of her.
My child is the most precious thing
I have in this world.
You must have thought
the same way at some point.
Thank you, Sensei.
No, you're the one
who got me in gear, Satoru.
Your heroic efforts just
couldn't end in tragedy.
Kayo's going to be okay now.
I hardly have any memory of my father,
but I wonder if he talked like that.
Satoru, thank you.
Thank you for getting me out of here.
Well, shall we go?
"The Town Without Me,"
by Kayo Hinazuki.
When I get bigger, big enough
to go somewhere by myself,
I want to go to a land that's far away.
I want to go to a faraway island.
I want to go to an island
that has no people.
that has no pain or sadness.
Thank you for dinner!
Next time, I want to cook with you.
-Kayo
On that island, I can climb
a tree when I want to climb,
swim in the sea when I want to swim,
and sleep when I want to sleep.
When I think about the town
without me, I feel a sense of relief.
I want to go far, far away.
I saved Kayo at last.
I fastened her life to the future.
From now on,
Kayo will make her own mark.
I have faith that the future
Kayo faces is a bright place.
Episode 9
Closure
Satoru's been like this all day.
Do you think he's okay?
He's a hero for helping Hinazuki, but...
Hey, Satoru, are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
You don't look fine at all.
Well, I can't blame him.
I mean, with Hinazuki gone...
Yeah. Although that does bring closure...
Satoru...
Come here a minute.
STAFF ROOM
About Kayo's mother...
I don't think she'll be able to see
Kayo for a number of years.
Kayo's going to begin a new life
with her grandmother.
Sensei, thank you.
Oh, no need to...
No, not about that.
What you said, "Your heroic efforts
just couldn't end in tragedy"...
That made me really happy.
Yes, well, it may have
sounded a little vulgar
if I'd said "the reward
for your heroic efforts,"
but what you did was deserving
of a reward, Satoru.
What did you want?
To see Kayo smile?
I wanted that, too.
By the way, Satoru,
was Kayo in your house all that time?
No. We had a hideout.
- A hideout?
- Yes.
We hid Kayo in the bus Izumi Elementary's
hockey club used to use.
A place that only kidnappers
like you guys would think to go, huh?
R-Right.
I can't really laugh...
KAYO HINAZUKI
(11 YEARS OLD)
Kayo's gone now,
AYA NAKANISHI
(11 YEARS OLD)
but the killer is still targeting
Hiromi and Aya Nakanishi.
HIROMI SUGITA
(11 YEARS OLD)
AYA NAKANISHI
KAYO HINAZUKI
(11 YEARS OLD)
I have to make sure neither one
of them are left alone.
It's like with Kayo.
FIGHT, WONDER GUY!
TV THEME SONG
Hiromi is my classmate,
but Aya Nakanishi goes
to Izumi Elementary next door,
so it'll be hard to approach her.
I hear she's often with Yuuki, but
how can I start a conversation with her?
She doesn't know anything about me.
This is a pretty high hurdle.
A way to become friends
with someone you don't know?
Just be straightforward,
like, "Let's be friends!"
Like that would—
You're thinking,
"Like that would work," aren't you?
Did she read my mind?!
You've already got Kayo, and now...
Why would you think I...
I just wanted to trick you
into fessing up.
Well, she is a girl...
but she's always alone.
You can't be so pessimistic.
You should focus on a positive result.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
I have stop somewhere.
Kenya and Hiromi,
you're going to the center, right?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll meet you there later. See you!
See you!
WITH YUUKI BY THE RIVER
HAMANASU PRIVATE CRAM SCHOOL
GRADE COURSES
So she gets out of cram school at 6:30.
I should be able to walk Hiromi home
and get back here in time.
First I have to investigate
her basic activity pattern.
WITH HIROMI AND KENYA
AT THE CHILDREN'S RECREATION CENTER
LEAVING HIROMI AND KENYA
CRAM SCHOOL LETS OUT
BEGIN TAILING AYA NAKANISHI AGAIN
Aya Nakanishi's daily activity
schedule was simple.
If she were going to be abducted,
it would most likely happen
in this time slot, after cram school.
Satoru!
Perfect timing! Help me!
I wanted to make sure she got home,
so don't suddenly appear like this!
Why did you buy all this in one trip?
It was cheap, so I couldn't help myself.
It's heavy.
Don't complain!
That only makes it heavier!
It's heavy even if I don't say anything.
You're a lifesaver, Sensei!
Mom binged on groceries.
Don't say I binged!
Say, Sensei...
Why aren't you married?
That came out of nowhere.
Listen, Satoru...
You need to have
a partner to get married.
And then it depends on your
partner's feelings, mutual timing...
Well, various things... Wait...
I've been through a painful
experience once,
so maybe I'm proceeding
with excessive caution.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's not a bad question.
Actually, I was going to ask you
something else.
How to approach a girl you don't know?
Yeah. I know about her,
but she doesn't know me.
Let's see...
I'm the cautious type, so even if it'd be
beating around the bush,
I'd start by getting her
to relax her guard.
Relax her guard?
Yeah. Put another way, charm her.
If you're good at sports or cooking,
whatever, use it as a weapon.
When she becomes
interested in whatever it is,
she lets her guard down.
Don't be so impressed.
I'm not good at expressing my
feelings directly, so I just rely on logic.
Something's sticking out.
Satoru, don't touch it!
I-I'm sorr—
It's...
Satoru...
You've seen it.
Candy?
Now that you've seen,
there's no sense in hiding it anymore!
You have some too,
so you become equally guilty!
Since I quit smoking three years ago,
candy has been my go-to substitute.
In private, I can't relax without it.
H-He's weird...
Thank you.
Give me one, too.
Here.
Well, I'm going to the center
to do my homework.
Okay!
Wait, Hiromi! I'll go with you!
First Hinazuki, and now it's like
you're Hiromi's guardian.
R-Really?
Satoru, can I speak to you in private?
Sure.
Sorry, Hiromi. I'll catch up.
Okay.
Satoru, honestly,
what are you thinking?
I saw your determination
to save Hinazuki, and that went well,
but looking at you, I still get the sense
that something's wrong.
Satoru, if something's up,
will you tell me about it?
I can't really explain it.
It's too much of a leap.
I want to make that leap, like you.
I want to be a superhero.
If there's a "part two,"
take me with you.
Kenya, what do you think
of these footprints?
An adult's, coming and going.
And if you look carefully...
The shoes were wrapped in cloth?
Not to keep from slipping, right?
Maybe to keep from leaving
shoe sole imprints.
The backpack is gone.
And the box with the briquette
isn't here anymore either.
I think there are fewer
boxes here overall.
And a lot of them are torn up.
Somebody must have made off
with their contents only.
Satoru, what are you trying to say?
When Kayo was staying here alone,
do you remember about the man
who came here in the middle of the night?
Yeah.
The guy who gave off a dangerous vibe
based on the stuff he left here.
I think he's a killer
who targets children.
Satoru? I don't know
where you're getting this from...
I know. It's unbelievable, right?
Why do you think that, Satoru?
I can't explain it right now.
But when I saw the contents
of the backpack and the briquette,
it made me think this was where a serial
killer kept his murderous tools.
I know it all sounds insane.
But I believe it.
I can tell you now, with Kayo too,
I didn't want to leave her alone
just to keep her mother from abusing her,
but also to protect her from this killer.
Satoru, do you mean to become
a novelist or detective in the future?
I don't think the issue is whether
what you're saying is far-fetched or not.
It's whether I believe or not.
STOP
I'll be fine without you walking me
all this way. I am a man.
That's all right. I have business
in the neighborhood anyway.
Satoru...
What?
I want to believe you, too.
I'll do whatever I can to help,
so don't hold back, okay?
Of course!
- See you!
Bye!
Later!
Satoru, to be honest, I'm about 99% sure
your hypothesis is nonsense.
But 1% of me says
it's not totally impossible.
Yeah. Looking at it from the outside,
it seems like I'm just wrapped up
in a game of make-believe crimes.
I don't mind if it is make-believe.
Part of it may be down
to these circumstances,
but I have a strong sense your thinking
is going to lead to something.
Yeah.
You trusted me enough
to tell me about it.
So I want to believe in you, too.
I want to believe you for my own sake.
It's the flip side to someone
saying "please believe me."
Thank you, Kenya.
Thank you, Hiromi.
I could've saved her.
That's what I said when I was crying
in front of Mom 18 years ago?
I don't want to feel that way again.
I won't let anyone be alone!
I can save them!
Remember to get a parent's signature!
Okay!
I want you to come
with me somewhere.
- Okay.
Satoru, wanna go to the hideout?
Sorry. There's something we have to do.
Then see you later.
See you!
- Yeah!
- See you.
What are they sneakin' around about?
I don't like it.
- Wanna follow 'em?
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
- All right!