The world of Shinigami
Shinigami literally means a "God of Death".
What?! A pair of sleeping skulls?!
Don't hate me for this, but I win again!
Hey, Ryuk! Wanna join us?
Come hang out with us for a change.
No... I'll pass...
Listen for the voice of God and never guess you will...
I haven't done anything but he said that he wanted to split up with me.
So what happened, what happened?
Yagami-kun, is there anything wrong?
Can you translate the previous sentences into Japanese please?
Follow the voice of God and he shall calm the waves, and protect us from storms.
At around 11 o'clock today,
in the city of Yokohama, Kanagawa prefecture, a thirty year old man was found covered in blood at his apartment.
The Kanagawa police are currently treating this case as a suspected homicide.
Next on the news...
Today in the district of Shibuya, Tokyo, a 25 year old woman was gagged and killed by her live-in partner.
35 year old, Tofuji Naoki, is being held in custody charged with her murder.
Day after day...
It's always the same news.
Completely... pointless...
This world is... rotting.
Rebirth
Another is the extinction of many species of life on the planet.
You seriously went to see that shit?!
Species are becoming extinct at a faster rate than has occurred...
It was a complete waste of time.
You get the feeling that they're just trying to make money.
Death Note?
Literally translated as "a notebook of death".
"How to use"...
"The human whose name is written in this note shall die"?
What a joke...
Pretty sick though, it's no different to chain letters.
"The human whose name is written in this note shall die"?
Seriously... I must be going insane...
"This note will not take effect unless the writer has the person's face in their mind when they write his/her name."
"Therefore, people sharing the same name will not be affected."
"If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds of writing the person's name, it will happen as it is written".
"If the cause of death is not specified, by default, the person will die of a heart attack".
"Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes and 40 seconds are granted to write any further details".
So this means you can either kill them quickly or painfully, huh?
Quite a lot of detail to go into for a simple prank... Not bad.
Writing a name causes someone to die...?
Completely pointless.
But wait...
On the off-chance that someone actually does die, wouldn't that make me a murderer?
Impossible. It'd never happen.
The phantom killer who attacked six people in Shinjuku's business district yesterday,
has now taken eight children and kindergarten teachers as hostages and is holed up in this nursery.
The police has identified the man as Otoharada Kurou, aged 42, unemployed.
It seems that they're about to begin negotiations...
Otoharada Kurou
According to the book, he should have a heart attack in 40 seconds.
At the present time, we don't have a lot of information.
You can't help but feel extremely concerned for the safety of the hostages.
Indeed.
That's all there is to report from the scene at this present moment.
Thank you.
What do you make of the current situation, Hashimoto-san?
Well, all I can say is that we can only hope to resolve this situation quickly.
Nothing happened after all.
I guess that was to be expected.
Ahh! Wait a minute! Something appears to be happening!
The hostages are coming out! They all appear to be unharmed!
The police are rushing the building as the hostages exit.
Has the culprit been apprehended?!
Yes.
We've just heard that the culprit was found dead in the nursery!
Yes, it looks like the culprit is dead!!
Dead?!
Otoharada Kurou
The riot police have denied shooting the man.
Then, this might imply that he committed suicide when he found himself cornered?
According to the hostages' statements, "he suddenly collapsed".
A heart attack...
No.
Coincidence... This has to be a coincidence.
Light?
It's already 6:30. Don't you have cram school today?
I'm just getting ready.
Death Note.
It's a long shot, but if this is the real thing...
I need to test it again.
In which case the victim should probably be a criminal.
But if they're too infamous, there's the possibility that their deaths may initially be covered up...
I need to see results now!
Yo, Yochi.
W-What do you want Sudou?
Lend me 'bout 2,000 yen will ya?
...again?
Sudou...
Are you saying you don't wanna?
I could try killing him...
No. Where possible I should avoid people I know.
Then again, I shouldn't be too bothered, nobody will care if one or two guys like him disappear.
I'll be going to the arcade again on my way home with this!
Hey, Maki, you wanna come out for drinks with the University crowd at 10:00 tomorrow?
Yeah, definitely!
Oh, me too!
Damn it! That stupid old hag isn't here to pick me up!
Jeez.. Thinking about this really makes you realize just how many people the world would actually be better off without.
Hey baby!
Fancy having some fun with us?
That's Takuo-san for you, you've certainly bagged another hottie!
The name's Shibuimaru Takuo, but you can call me Shibutaku.
Hang out with us for a while, baby.
Please don't trouble me...
She doesn't want us to "trouble her"!
How cute!
Guys, take them off for her.
Can we?!
Stop!
Please!
Stop!!
All the different variations of writing the name "Shibuimaru Takuo".
Now, let's see what happens!
Wait!
Takuo! Look out!!
T-That settles it...
The Death Note.. It's the real deal!
Takuo!
Dickhead!
Why'd he jump out like that?!
I guess... I'd better get going soon.
It's been five days since then...
Eh, you going out somewhere, Ryuk?
Wherever you go in our world, it'll only be desolate.
I dropped my Death Note.
Jeez, you really fucked up this time.
Hang on, didn't you cheat a second Death Note out of the Shinigami Overlord?
Don't tell me you lost both of 'em?
Do ya even know where ya dropped it?
The human world.
Wha--?!
Welcome home.
You're pretty early today, Light.
Yeah...
I'm back, mother...
Huh?
Oh, you want the results of the national mock exams, right?
Quickly!
Here you go.
Wow! Number one again!
You really tried hard, didn't you, Light?
I guess. I'm going to study in my room, so don't interrupt.
Yes, yes.
Oh yes, Light!
Do you want anything?
You can ask for whatever you like.
Nothing really, mother.
I already got what I want.
I see that you've taken quite a shine to it.
Why are you so surprised?
I am Ryuk, the Shinigami who dropped that notebook.
Judging by that face of yours earlier, it seems you've already realized that that is no ordinary notebook.
A Shinigami, huh?
I'm not surprised, Ryuk...
In fact, I've been waiting for you, Ryuk.
Ohh?
I've already realized that this Shinigami's notebook is real.
And after seeing its results, I can act with certainty.
I see. You surprise me.
In the past, I've heard of instances where a Death Note has appeared in the human world,
but you're the first person to have written this many names in just five days.
Normally, people are too frightened to write as much as this.
I've already prepared myself, Ryuk.
I knowingly used a Shinigami's notebook, and now a Shinigami has come.
What'll happen to me? Are you going to take my soul?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Is this some kind of fantasy created by humans?
I'm not going to do anything to you.
The moment that notebook fell to this world, it became the property of the human world.
In other words, that notebook belongs to you.
M-Mine?
If you don't want it, you can pass it to someone else.
But I reserve the right to erase your memory of the Death Note if you do.
So you're telling me that there's really no trade-off for using the Death Note?
Since you insist on knowing, there is the fear and suffering that is faced only by those humans who use Death Notes.
And finally, when you die, it falls to me to write your name in my Death Note.
Don't assume that a human who's used the Death Note can go to Heaven or Hell.
That's all.
You'll have something to look forward to when you die.
Light?
It's okay. Answer it.
What?
I've brought you some apples. The neighbours brought them round to share.
Why is it so dark in there?
You'll ruin your eyesight you know.
What's going on? Can't mother see him?
_
That used to be my notebook, so as the current user you're the only one who can see me, and of course the only one who can hear me.
That Death Note is the bond that ties you, the human, to me, Ryuk, the Shinigami, so to speak.
Mmm, nice!
Can I ask you one more thing.. Why me?
Are you listening?
Wow, apples in the human world are damn good.
They're.. how to say it..
"juicy"?
Answer the question.
I didn't pick you.
I just happened to drop the notebook.
What, did you think you'd been picked because you're smart or something?
Don't be so vain.
It just happened to fall around here, and you just happened to pick it up.
That's why I wrote it in the most popular human language, English.
So why did you drop it?!
You went through the whole trouble of writing down instructions, so don't tell me you just happened to drop it by accident!
Why you say... because I was bored.
Bored?!
The truth is that most Shinigami haven't got much to do.
They mainly sleep or gamble.
Try writing any names in your book, and they'll laugh at you for trying too hard.
Even if you write the name of someone living in the Shinigami world, they won't die, and it's no fun killing humans from the Shinigami world.
So I figured it'd be more fun in this world.
Anyway, you seem to have written quite a few names here.
But why did you only write the cause of death for the guy that was run over by a dump truck?
If you don't write the cause of death, the victim dies of a heart attack.
That's the best thing about the Death Note, Ryuk.
I've already begun to exhaust the list of high profile criminals, and I'm gradually including people that commit less serious crimes.
And what does that achieve?
No matter how stupid people are, they'll eventually realize that someone is wiping out these criminals.
I'm going to let the world know of my existence.
That there is someone who can, and will, pass righteous judgement!
But what do you plan to achieve by passing this "righteous judgement"?
Why bother?
Because... I'm also bored.
Of course, at first I didn't believe it, but that notebook has a kind of magic that compels humans to try it at least once.
I k-killed them...
Two of them...
It's a life. The consequences can't be light.
Do I have the right to pass judgements on others?
But wait, it's not like that. This is what I've always thought.
This world is rotting.
Those who are rotting deserve to die.
Someone...
Someone has to do it!
Sacrificing their own life and soul, because the world just can't continue like this!
If someone else had picked up this notebook, would they be able to erase all the unnecessary people from this world?
No way!
But I can... I can do it!
In fact, I'm the only one who can do it!
I'll do it. I'll use the Death Note..
To change the world!
I began to think of it as "tidying up the world", and continued to write down the names of the most monstrous criminals.
Eventually no one will be able to commit a crime.
Then, behind the fact that deserving criminals are dying of heart attacks,
I'll gradually start killing of those who cause problems for innocent people, through illness and accidental death.
This way it's certain that the world will become a better place.
Then, I'll have created a world filled with those I've judged to be kind and hard working.
If you do that, you'll be the only fucked up person left.
What do you mean, Ryuk?
I'm probably the most virtuous student in the country.
And then...
I'll become the God of my new world!
I knew it! Humans are... so much fun!
To be continued