Greetings to all of you at the ICPO. I am L.
Whether there's one or more culprits involved, the probability of them being Japanese is extremely high.
Kira, I can guess what your motivation for doing this might be, but what you're doing is evil!
You bastard!
Try and kill me!
I am justice!
What's going on?
I save the weak from evil, and I will become the God of a world that everyone desires!
This is spiralling out of control!
L..
Kira..
I'll hunt you down.. and kill you!
I am..
JUSTICE!
The Deal
Atrocious Serial Murder Case
Special Investigative Headquarters
Let's begin with the Public Intelligence report.
Yes.
The total number of reports from the public, including phone calls, currently stands at 3029.
Unfortunately, the large majority of them seems to be prank calls.
There have been 14 reported incidents of people who either know or have seen Kira.
We have investigated these thoroughly, one by one, and I believe that - just as reported - it would be safe to say that none of them have any credibility.
There are also 21 reported incidents of people claiming to be Kira.
Each of those 21 reports has been followed up, and will remain on file.
Moving onto the victims..
Yes.
We can confirm that information on all the known victims that died of heart attacks was publicly available in Japan.
In addition, we have followed up L's specific request that we investigate the assumed time of death for each victim.
Results indicate that 68% of all deaths occurred during weekdays, between four in the afternoon and midnight, Japanese time.
The number of deaths peaks over the weekend, when they can occur at any time between eleven in the morning through till late at night.
This is all extremely interesting information.
It suggests that given the assumed times of death, there is a possibility that our culprit may be a student.
I do have further grounds to support this.
Given that they appear to be only targeting criminals, the culprit seems to be motivated by a sense of "justice".
It's conceivable that they may even plan on becoming some kind of God.
This means that we may be dealing with an extremely hollow psychology.
Of course, this is mere speculation.
However, please rid yourselves of any preconceptions you might have that our culprit cannot be a student.
To consider every possibility; that is likely to be the shortest road to apprehending Kira.
Please continue the investigation report.
Y-Yes.
Are there any other observations?
Umm.. Yes.
What is it, Matsuda?
I don't mean to support Kira in any way by saying this..
but over the last few days.. throughout the world, but especially in Japan.. the number of serious crimes committed have dramatically decreased.
I guess.. that kind of phenomenon was to be expected..
Anything else?
Right. L, that concludes today's investigation report.
Good work. I feel that we're one step closer to finding the culprit.
Also, I have another order to trouble you with.
I need the teams investigating victims, information and Internet to double-check what information regarding each victim was previously released in Japan.
More specifically, whether or not footage or photographs of the victims had been released.
Thank you.
Chief!
You're looking pretty tired.
Ah, thanks. The late nights are beginning to take their toll on me.
Thinking about this now, everyone was probably already aware of what I said about crime going down.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Continue to speak the truth, no matter what kind of truth it may be.
Especially when it's awkward to say.
In fact, if everyone continues to think that Kira should be commended for lowering crime, it will become harder and harder to say it out loud.
S-Surely no one would commend such a murderer?
I'm joking.
I knew I could count on you, onii-chan.
So do you understand?
Err.. Yeah, sort of.
Sounds like dad's back.
Welcome home, darling.
He's back early today.
Hey! Why don't you at least try doing the last question yourself?
I will. After dinner.
Jeez..
You must have everything in hand, seeing you're able to afford the time to help out with your sister's homework.
Yeah.
Even if the police were to come after me, I'm confident that I have something to fight them with.
Welcome home, father.
Ahh.. Yes, I'm back.
How are your studies going, Light?
Not bad.
Same as always. Top of the year.
I'm so proud of my older brother! Yes!
I'm so proud of my son! Yes!
You seem tired, father.
I'm not allowed to say much, but this case is proving to be exceedingly difficult.
I see.
Your father is part of the police force.
So this is the source of your confidence, Light.
Yeah.
I can also access my father's computer without leaving any trace.
So I can get hold of all the information regarding the investigation, anytime.
Here we go.
It seems that the police are already beginning to suspect that the culprit could be a student.
Won't that be risky for you, Light?
"If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds of writing the person's name, it will happen as it is written."
"If the cause of death is not specified, then by default, the person will die of a heart attack."
"Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes 40 seconds are granted to write any further details."
That's correct, isn't it Ryuk?
Yeah.. So what?
In other words, if you write "heart attack" first, you can still write details of their death afterwards.
Looks like I'll be able to provide you with some more entertainment, Ryuk.
Hey! What's going on?
Pull yourself together!
What?!
T-There were another 23 victims yesterday?
Yes.
There were 23 victims the day before that too.
All spaced out evenly, one every hour.
The fact that this has continued over two weekdays must mean..
The theory that the culprit could be a student is weakened..
But anyone can potentially skip two days of school..
That's not it!
It's true that the likelihood of them being a student has gone down.
But this is not what Kira is trying to say here.
Why have they spaced the killings at precisely one hour intervals?
And, why are the victims all prisoners that could be found quickly after their deaths?
Kira is trying to tell us.. that they can control the time of death at will.
But something strange is going on.
As soon as the possibility that Kira could be a student was put forward, the timing of the murders change to indicate that this was not the case.
A coincidence?
No, the timing is too convenient.
Kira must have access to police information.
This is clearly... a direct challenge to me.
I think that L will probably begin to sweat a little.
I still have 50 criminals that I've deliberately left alive for a time like this.
Plus, thanks to the last few incidents L should be beginning to suspect someone in, or connected to, the police.
Kira has a way of getting police information.
This fact can no longer be ignored.
What is Kira's final objective?
What are they trying to do?
I don't get it.
Surely, showing them that you have connections to the police place you at a greater disadvantage than having them suspect Kira of being a student?
The answer to that is, I did it to help me find and destroy L.
What do ya mean?
In this world, there are very few people who actually trust each other.
Even amongst the police force.. and especially between the police and L, who never had a bond of trust between them from the beginning.
Can you honestly trust someone whose name and face are unknown to you?
Now that L knows that I'm getting police information, without a doubt, he'll try to find a trail leading to me that starts within the police force.
When that happens, it'll only be a matter of time before even the police can't keep quiet with respect to L.
On the outside, L and the police appear to be working together to catch me.
But behind the scenes, L will be investigating the police, and the police will be investigating L!
I won't be the one who'll find L.. the police will do that for me.
Then.. I'll erase him.
What the hell is this?!
Letter of
resignation
As you can see, they are letters of resignation.
Unless we're moved to a different case, we're leaving the police force.
But.. why?
Why?
Because we value our lives.
L's theory is that Kira has some ESP-like power that allows them to kill without having to be there, right?
If I was Kira, I'd try to kill those who are trying to catch me.
After all, if they get caught, they'll be killed.
We've already seen this from that incident on TV, when Kira killed the "dummy L" after being provoked.
But L hasn't even revealed his name, let alone his face!
That order we received earlier from L, about checking the information released about the victims prior to their deaths,
and whether or not footage or photos of their faces had been released.. That turned out to be true!
Every single one of them had their photo published in Japan!
Unlike someone we all know; we had to investigate using our police IDs with our photos attached!
Without hiding our faces!
We could be killed by Kira at any time.
That's why we're asking to be re-assigned.
Excuse us.
Hey! You! Hold on a moment!
Huh?
In order to solve this problem we must first establish the concept that x squared equals large X.
You can then proceed by noting that the quadratic equation in large X is the key to understanding the problem..
We had the FBI arrive in Japan four days ago.
They've begun their investigation of the Japanese police force.
These are the people on the list?
Affirmative.
There are 141 people within the police who have access to information regarding Kira.
But within the 141 people, or people close to them.. Kira will definitely be amongst them.
Hey, Light. Got a moment?
How many times do I have to tell you not to talk to me in public?
Okay, in that case, I'll just talk at you.
If you don't wanna listen, just cover your ears or something.
I don't dislike you.
In some ways I think the notebook was found by an awesome person, because I have to remain by your side until either you or that Death Note expires.
But.. I'm not on your side, and I'm not going to be on L's side either.
I know that much already, Ryuk.
That's why I'll never say that what you're doing is right or wrong.
Although as your roommate, I may have a few things to say.
What's up, Ryuk?
Why are you saying things like this now? It's not like you.
Therefore what I'm about to say is not because I'm on Kira's side, but because it's giving me the creeps.
Quit beating around the bush.
There's a human following you.
He's been bugging me lately.
Although I know he can't see me, but because I'm always following you around, it kinda feels like I'm being watched.
Looks like I've got a problem.
I'll have to get rid of him as soon as possible, Ryuk.
Who the hell is he?
Does this mean that L has already started to suspect the police?
Whoever is investigating the police must have large resources.
Even if they have 50 people on the case, the chances that they'll suspect I'm Kira are non-existent.
They shouldn't be looking at me as anything more than a final year student.
But if I leave him alone for a few months, the probability that I'll be caught might rise above zero.
First I need my stalker's name.
If I can figure that out, I can take care of everything
Light... Let me tell you something cool.
There are two very important differences between a Shinigami and a human with a Death Note.
Do you know why Shinigami write human names into their Death Note?
Of course I don't.
You're pretty talkative today, Ryuk.
It's because Shinigami take human life spans for themselves.
Take their "life spans"?
For example, if you take someone due to die at 60, and write their name so they die at 40 instead..
Sixty minus forty, is twenty. Those twenty human years are added to that Shinigami's life span.
So as long as we don't slack off too much, a Shinigami can't be killed with a bullet to the head, or a knife through the heart.
However, if you write a human's name in the Death Note, Light, your life span won't increase.
That's one of the differences between a Shinigami and a human with a Death Note.
Now that's a theory about Shinigami that humans haven't heard before.
That's kind of interesting.
The second difference will probably be even more of an interest to you.
Though it concerns decreasing life spans rather than increasing them.
Decreasing them?
A Shinigami can tell someone's name by just looking at them.
Do you know why?
A Shinigami's eyes have the ability to see a person's name and life span by just looking at them.
Name and life span?
Yagami Light
Of course, I can see your name and life span right now.
If I converted that into human time, you would know precisely how many human years you have.
Of course, we aren't allowed to tell you that kind of stuff.
Not even a huge blabbermouth like me.
Therefore, a Shinigami will never be prevented from killing someone due to not knowing their name.
When they kill someone, they know exactly how much life they're gaining.
Our eyes are different.
That's the distinct difference between you and me.
However, if a Shinigami drops a notebook, and a human picks it up.. the Shinigami can change that human's eyes into the eyes of a Shinigami.
That is, if you agree to the deal passed down for this purpose since ancient times.
Deal...?
The price for the eyes of a Shinigami is.. half of that human's remaining life span.
Half of my remaining life span...?
In other words, suppose you were to live for another 50 years, that would be reduced to 25 years.
If you have a year remaining, you get left with half a year.
But currently given that you're not on my side, or on L's side, you won't tell me the names of the people I want to kill?
Basically, you're saying that I can't simply borrow your powers... Isn't that right?
Yup. That's one of the rules of the Shinigami world.
I'll say it once more.
For the price of just half your remaining life span.. you could have the eyes of a Shinigami!
That way I'll be able to tell the name of anyone I meet just by looking at them!
The Death Note would become even easier to use.
So.. What do you want to do, Light?
To be continued