What?!
There were another 23 victims yesterday, again?!
As soon as the possibility of Kira being a student is put forward, the timing of the murders change to indicate that this isn't the case.
I guess this means that Kira must have access to police information.
Now that L knows I'm somehow getting police information, without doubt, he'll use the police as a link to catch me.
There's a human that's been following you.
Looks like I've got a problem.
I'll have to get rid of him as soon as possible, Ryuk.
A Shinigami's eyes have the ability to see a person's name and life span, just by looking at them.
Yagami Light
Also, Shinigami have the ability to change the eyes of any human who finds their notebook, into the eyes of a Shinigami.
The price for a Shinigami's eyes is... half of your remaining life span.
So, what do you want to do, Light?
The Chase
Haven't seen Ryuk around lately, huh?
Was he serious about having dropped his Death Note on Earth?
It must have been picked up by a human before he got to it.
No way! If he did something like that, he'd be forced to watch over them until either the human dies, or the notebook is destroyed.
You're right. There's no way Ryuk could be bothered to do something like that.
Yeah, but I heard he's got two Death Notes.
Seriously?! Why the hell has he got two?
I just don't understand the guy.
So, in order for me to acquire the eyes of a Shinigami, I've got to give up half of my remaining life span... right?
Yeah, so what do ya wanna do?
Have we got a deal?
Ryuk.. that deal is... out of the question.
Huh?
Listen carefully, Ryuk.
I'm trying to create a new ideal world, free of criminals.
And I intend to reign as God of that new world for a long time.
If the deal had involved increasing my life span, I might have considered it.
But anything that decreases it isn't even worth discussing.
I'd have thought that you'd already know that much.
Yeah. Well, I just wanted to tell you that the deal exists.
Thought I'd better tell you this sort of thing early on, so I don't have to put up with your complaints later.
You thought you'd better tell me this sort of thing "early on"?
Isn't it already slightly late?
You should've told me this either as soon as we met, or written it as part of the explanations in the Death Note.
Err.. I guess you're right.
He doesn't fear me in the slightest, even though I'm a Shinigami.
He doesn't try to suck up to me, and he keeps on relentlessly asking such probing questions of me.
And?
Is there anything else you should have told me beforehand, Ryuk the Shinigami?
No, there's nothing else.
Probably...
Oh. That's a shame.
A shame?
If it was wings instead of eyes, I might have seriously considered it.
It seems quite fitting for a god to have wings and fly freely across the sky.
After all, it's been man's dream since antiquity to be able to fly.
If you grew wings and flew around you'd stand out too much.
The police would probably be able to catch you purely on that basis.
I was joking, Ryuk.
With all the trading of eyes, wings or whatever, I'd probably end up becoming a real Shinigami.
Although, I guess that could be quite an interesting concept too.
Relax.
Even without doing anything like that, you're already a worthy Shinigami, Light.
Right now, the World of Shinigami is rotting.
They live a vague and pointless existence, only taking human lives because they, themselves, are afraid to die.
They no longer understand why they even exist.
There's probably no meaning in their existence at all.
Compared to them, Light, you're more of a Shinigami than they'll ever be.
Well, by the sound of things, I'm doing a lot more work than them, but I wouldn't want to be compared to them.
As a human, I'm using the Death Note to help humanity.
But it isn't like the World of Shinigami is of little importance to the human world.
Huh? What do you mean?
It's the truth. Ryuk, even if Shinigami like you come down just once every hundred — no, thousand — years, the human world will change dramatically.
The existence of the World of Shinigami is extremely significant.
R-really?
If the World of Shinigami is really as rotten as you say it is, Ryuk, why don't you try changing things when you get back?
Light, you're turning out to be quite the positive thinker..
Of course.
You've got to be a positive thinker to think of using the Death Note to personally right the world.
That's it!
I've got it.
What's up? What do you "get"?
I've figured out how to obtain the name of my stalker.
What're you going to do?
I'll be using the rules of the Death Note to my advantage.
"Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes and 40 seconds are granted to write any further details".
First, I'll need to test just how free I am to specify the details of the death.
The next day
Yeah, it's me.
Another six prisoners?
Due to heart attacks?
It's got to be Kira.
What?!
Three of them exhibited a pattern of behavior before death that we've never seen before?
What do you mean?
You mean it wasn't just a normal heart attack?
No. The cause of death was definitely a heart attack.
But directly before it happened, one of them cut his own finger and drew a strange picture on the wall.
Another left an unexplainable note.
The third managed to escape and seems to have made the effort to run all the way to the staff toilets before...
What is it, Watari?
A few heart attack victims that acted slightly different from the usual have just been discovered.
Different from the usual?
I'm sending you the images of the text and picture they left.
Please do.
This reads as though he's afraid of Kira...
It could conceivably be merely the actions of a criminal, but if Kira can control the time of death...
What if Kira can also control the movements leading up to death?
In which case...
Chief, regarding the most recent victims, I'd like to request that no details regarding their deaths are released other than that they died of heart attacks.
It's possible that Kira may be using these criminals to conduct some kind of test.
And if that is the case, we shouldn't give them any easy answers.
I see..
Understood.
Performing tests on criminals?
Cruel...
It seems as though they enjoy playing games with people's lives...
I won't forgive this!
If Kira's really experimenting on criminals... what's their objective?
Take a look at this, Ryuk.
The results of yesterday's six tests have already been entered into dad's computer.
The Death Note is even more useful than I thought.
What d'ya mean?
Having escaped, one of them ran to a toilet that I'd specified in the notebook.
Another drew the exact picture that I'd drawn in the notebook.
And another wrote the same sentences that I wrote in the notebook.
Those three did exactly what I intended them to do.
For the remaining three, I purposely wrote circumstances that would be impossible.
First, I wrote that the victim would die in an hour's time in front of the Eiffel Tower.
It's physically impossible for a prisoner in Japan to reach France in just an hour.
As a result, this doesn't actually happen, and the victim simply dies of a heart attack.
Next, I wrote "Draws an exact picture of L's face on the wall" in the Death Note,
but it's impossible to draw somebody you don't know.
I see...
Lastly, I specified that the final victim should write, "I know that L is suspicious of the police force".
I thought that this one might work, but it didn't happen.
In other words..
If someone doesn't know a piece of information, they can't think of it, and so it'd be unnatural for that person to write it down, meaning they won't be able to do so.
Even the Death Note cannot accomplish the impossible.
But, if it's within the realistic limits of what they can do, I can control them as much as I like before they die.
I've got that much, but what are ya trying to achieve, Light?
L and the police will never be able to guess my true objectives.
The famous detective will be too busy investigating the mystery of those pictures and messages...
Those completely meaningless "dying messages".
If Kira is really using criminals as test subjects, it must be because they're about to begin something else...
If they make a move now, there's the possibility that their suspicious actions will be picked up by the FBI...
But... If there's another reason they're doing this, other than to run tests...
There might be a message in the drawings and text.
This is it.
The upper line reads "L, did you know?"
Alright, it's finally time for the real deal.
Real deal?
I'll use this drug addict.
Yesterday, he attempted to rob a bank, but failed to take any money, and escaped by shooting employees and members of the public.
It's slightly last minute, but I'm sure it'll be fine.
I'll try asking a few people.
"Try asking a few people"?
Yeah. Despite my appearance, I'm actually quite popular with the ladies, Ryuk.
..Hello?
Light?! Good morning.
He's still following me...
Perfect.
If he wasn't, what I'm about to do would be pointless.
Light!
A date, huh?
Yeah.
However you look at it, it's just a normal date.
Even the guy that's following me can see that.
But it isn't just a "normal" date, is it?
You mentioned something about knowing how to figure out your stalker's name.
What the hell do you plan on doing?
Huh, Ryuk? Didn't you see what I wrote in the Death Note?
No. Otherwise it'd be boring.
In that case, just be patient and watch.
Sorry. Have you been waiting long?
No. Not at all!
More importantly, I haven't been to Space Land since Junior High!
I'm so excited!
And we get to spend the entire day together, just the two of us!
If he goes out on a weekday, he either goes to school or cram school.
On the odd day off, he goes on a date.
Seems pretty normal. An earnest final year exam student.
Police Chief Yagami's son, Light - no need for suspicion.
I'll just check his movements today, and then that'll be the end of it.
But Light, didn't you say that we weren't going to go out until the exams are over?
I guess it's okay, since I placed first in the national mock exams.
Eww, no need to be so smug.
He's here!
It's him!
Seven passengers, excluding him... in that case, everything should proceed smoothly.
I'm taking over this bus!
A bus hi-jack?! At a time like this?
Keep it down! I'll kill anyone who dares to move.
Oi, driver! D'ya know the phone number of the Space Land offices?
Call 'em!
Yes.
This is driver Sasaki, of bus number 124.
Tell 'em what's going on.
I-I've been hi-hacked by a man with a gun.
Give it 'ere.
You heard what's going on? Now, listen up!
I want a woman in a car to bring yesterday's takings to the bus stop two stops away from Space Land before this bus gets there.
If you call the police, or try anything funny, I'll kill every single person on this bus!
Yuri-chan, don't worry; it's okay.
I'll find an opportunity to disarm him.
My father's a police officer and I've
learnt how to counter-attack such a scenario.
He looks small and relatively weak.
I'm stronger than him.
Yuri-chan, don't worry; it's okay. I'll find an opportunity to disarm him.
You can't, it's too dangerous. Don't do it.
If it comes to that, I'll do it.
It's okay, you don't need to communicate in writing.
The noise of the bus is enough to cover up hushed conversations from the culprit.
Do you have any proof that you're not an accomplice to this crime?
A-an accomplice?
It's a fairly common practice.
The culprit fools us into thinking he's alone, but secretly plants an accomplice at the back, just in case anything goes wrong.
What's the matter?
No, no way, it can't be...
I-I don't have a choice...
There's no way Yagami Light is Kira.
If he was, then he'd be able to kill the culprit with a heart attack.
Here's my proof. Take a look.
FBI!
So that's who L's been using to investigate the Japanese police!
His name is Ray Penber.
I'll trust you, and for the time being I won't question what an FBI agent is doing here.
Do you have a gun?
I do.
So if it comes to that, I'll be relying on you, okay?
Okay.
Shut the hell up! Do ya wanna die?!
That man! He was on the Japanese news two days ago...
He robbed a bank, killed three people, and then fled.
He's extremely dangerous.
It's fine. He'll never shoot us with that gun.
Hey! Hey, you! Don't move!
What's on that bit of paper?
Why you--! You passing notes around to try plotting against me?
Shit! If he finds that note from before... he'll realize that we're waiting for an opportunity to overpower him!
Huh? Just arrangements for a date.
What a load of crap!
I did it!
Who the hell are you?!?
You! The guy right at the back!
Don't mess with me!
Since when have you been there?
Huh? You talking to me?
You can see me?
Don't move! I-I'll shoot you, you freak!
This isn't good.. he's hallucinating!
Everyone, get down!
Oh, I get it now.
That note with the arrangements for the date was written on paper from the Death Note.
And he made this guy touch it, so this guy's the only one who's able to see me.
Pretty clever.
Don't come any closer!
Sorry.
You know, I'm a Shinigami, so things like that won't kill me.
"Those who touch the Death Note are able to see me."
"I will always have to follow Light around."
"Shinigami won't die just by being shot."
These are all things I've told Light in the past, and this is just the kind of practical application I'd expect from him.
And he's managed to use this hi-jacking to get the name of the guy that's been following him.
Stop the bus!
Exactly 11:45.
Everything went according to plan.
Oosoreda Kiichirou... death by accident.
Boards the 11:31-bus to Space Land from the bus station at the east entrance to the park, with a gun.
Appears to have some out-of-this-world type of hallucination and empties his gun towards it. Disembarks from the bus.
Immediately afterwards; same day; 11:45 - dies in an accident.
The Death Note never fails.
It's your turn next... Ray Penber.
To be continued