I can't believe that my son, who's so serious, would go and look at those sorts of magazines...
Onii-chan, it's dinner time!
Using my right hand to continue solving problems, I can use my left hand to write down names... and to take out potato chips to eat.
L himself will be the witness to my alibi.
Contact
Are you certain, Ryuk?
Yeah, I'm sure there's no one following you.
H-Hurry!! The withdrawal symptoms... they're--
You aren't just making this up so that you can eat your apples, are you?
Hey! I've already circled multiple times, within a 100m radius around you to check.
I'm sure.
Okay, but they did mention on the news that there are supposed to be 1,500 more investigators.
They're just trying to intimidate you, and you know it.
You said it yourself; it it was true, they would never have made such a big fuss about it.
Fine, Ryuk.
I'll buy you an apple.
Success!!
Here, thanks a lot.
Light! Faster, faster!
You know, you don't treat Shinigami very well, do ya?
I can't believe that you made me give up eating apples in the house till I'd managed to find all those cameras.
Come on now, eat the core as well.
You know that I'm definitely going to write your name in my Death Note in the end, right?
Is this really the time to be laughing?
You're right. I still have things I need to finish.
Ryuuzaki.
Yes?
Two days ago, a mugger and an embezzler died of heart attacks, despite the fact that my family had no knowledge of them.
Do you still suspect them?
Let me see...
Even if Kira can manipulate the time of death, they wouldn't be able to kill someone without seeing those broadca---
Your son is home again.
You're going to stay silent and pretend to study again?
I've already memorized the locations of all the cameras.
However, the only criminals I was able to kill using the potato chips' packet as a cover were a mugger and an embezzler.
Both are quite notably less serious crimes than the usual.
And next on the news...
Are you going to watch TV?
... are still under investigation.
Even if there are criminals dying while I'm not watching TV or using the Internet,
it'll still look suspicious that the lesser criminals only die when I don't appear to be getting any information.
Therefore, if I kill some of the lesser criminals while they can see me watching the TV, they'll have no reason to treat those deaths as unusual.
Also, regardless of the seriousness of their crimes, I can remember the names and faces of the criminals for when I get out of the house.
Then, using the piece of Death Note I keep in my wallet, I can scatter their times of death as I please.
My anti-surveillance camera plan is finally complete.
I've been over the audio and the video footage from the last five days a countless number of times.
I'd like to share my conclusions with you all.
Within the Kitamura and Yagami households, I observed suspicious behaviour from... no one.
I'll remove all the surveillance cameras and bugging devices.
So there weren't any suspects after all...
Hang in there!
We need to pull ourselves together and start over.
Please, don't get the wrong idea.
What I actually mean is that, judging by this footage alone, there doesn't appear to be anyone that's suspicious.
What?!
Even if Kira were amongst them, they've done nothing to expose themselves.
If anything, they appear to be killing criminals as usual.
So, Ryuuzaki, do you think that Kira may still be one of them?
As I've said before... there's a 5% chance.
Even though the cameras were up, Kira continued to kill.
I don't know how they're killing people... even if they could kill someone by just by wishing for it to happen...
Each time that happened, a normal person should react in some way... they would reveal it by their expression, or through their behavior.
"Kira isn't among them".. that would be the "normal" conclusion one would draw.
Yet, if Kira is among them, within their own mind, they're already a god.
They'll kill without blinking an eye.
It's as though there is no Kira, but that this is really the work of God.
But there's no way that God requires a name and a face in order to kill!
This isn't the work of God.
It's just some kid who likes to think that they are God.
That's what it is.
Somewhere, out there, a serial killer called "Kira" exists, and I will catch them!
Even if the cameras were to be maintained, I doubt that Kira would exhibit any signs by their behavior.
What should I do?
It seems like the best method would be to make them admit that they are Kira and demonstrate how they kill people.
But surely, that's going to be impossible...
Hey, Light. As I thought, the cameras are gone.
All of them. The lot!
Light? You listening?
Hey, Light!
Oh, I've got ya; there may still be bugging devices.
I guess this means that I'm no longer a target of their investigations, although, L will doubtlessly continue to pursue Kira.
However, as long as he continues to use the Japanese police force, my father will be in the middle of that investigation.
In that case... I can use my father to reveal L's real identity.
If I can erase L... Kira will be one step closer to becoming the God of a new world.
Light, hurry up!
Go for it.
Onii-chan, do your best!
Really, stop making such a fuss.
I'm off then.
It's a relief to know that the bugging devices have also been removed.
It's good that that's one less thing I need to stress about before my exams.
Toudou University
Heisei 19 (2007) University Entrance Exams
Plus, getting into university will allow me more time to act as "Kira", and the time to go after L.
You there! There's only ten minutes left before the exams starts!
Hurry up!
I hate having to wait around in classrooms, so I was planning to be here three minutes before it starts, but oh well... I managed to arrive earlier than I intended.
Wow, he doesn't lack confidence.
Begin!
You there! Number 162. Sit down properly!
Lately, there's been a load of guys watching the Human World for all they're worth...
What's going on?
Apparently, Ryuk is being kept as a pet by a human.
W-What the hell is he thinking?!
God damn it! He's got no pride as a Shinigami!
No, I was talking about the human.
Ryuk would make a terrible pet. He's not cute at all.
Too right!
What's his owner like? Female? Male?
No idea.
Might go and take a look myself.
Oh boy, oh boy...
Heisei 19 (2007) Toudou University Entrance Ceremony
So, Light, you're now a university student. I'm somewhat overwhelmed.
The Freshman's speech.
Introducing the freshmen's representative, Yagami Light...
Here.
Wow, amazing.
and also... Ryuuga Hideki.
Oh? Here.
R-Ryuuga Hideki... do they mean the idol?
Don't be stupid. How is he going to get the grades to get into Toudai?
You're right. He doesn't look anything like the idol Ryuuga.
I'd heard that there would be two of us doing this speech... but I can't believe it's with him of all people.
He was behind me during the exams.
He was sitting in that really odd way that made him stand out...
New life begins to blossom in the breath of spring...
Doesn't the student with the highest grade in the entrance exam usually give this speech?
Finally we're able to embrace this bright future...
That just means that there were two of them this year.
Today we look forward to...
I heard that both of them got top marks for everything!
Seriously?!
People like that really exist, huh?
...at Toudou University fairness in society will...
I prefer the one on the right.
What?! Kyouko, you're weird... I tell you, normal people would say the one on the left...
Just look at them though.. They're complete opposites!
Yeah.
Certainly one looks like a brilliant genius, brought up in a sheltered environment, but... the other one...
New life begins to blossom in the breath of spring...
You could almost call him feral...
Isn't he what one would describe as a natural genius?
Wearing that sort of garb to the entrance ceremony at Toudai, he's either an idiot, or he's mocking the ceremony.
...freshmen's representative, Ryuuga Hideki.
Yagami-kun.
The son of police chief, Yagami Souichirou. You have a sense of justice that matches your father's.
What's with this guy?
You're aiming for a career in the Police Force yourself, and in the past you've helped in several cases that have all led to convictions.
And right now, you're interested in the Kira case.
With that sense of justice and ability, I could trust you with a very important secret, if you promise not to tell anyone.
I'd like to tell you something very important regarding the Kira case.
What's with this? All of a sudden...
It might be wiser if I don't talk to him.
Then again, what's this "important thing" concerning the Kira case?
I won't tell anyone. What is it?
I'm L.
N-No way.
What the hell is he saying?!
There's no way L would admit to being L.
I thought he seemed a little odd, but is he actually crazy?
W-Wait. I can't show that I'm uneasy. If he really is L...
In any case, right now, I've got to act as people would expect Yagami Souichirou's son, Yagami Light, to act...
If you really are L, then you are someone I admire a lot.
Thanks.
I revealed myself to you because I believe that you might be able to help us with the Kira case.
Yagami Light. There's only a 5% chance that you are Kira.
But out of all those I watched, there's something about you... you're too perfect.
If you truly are Kira, this is the best way I can think of to put pressure on you.
If he's L... That's impressive!
It's true. If this guy really is L... No, even if he isn't, I... I won't be able to do anything to him!
If he's L, then my father would know his face.
If he dies after telling me that he's L, I'll immediately become the suspect.
Plus, this guy is using the blatantly fake name "Ryuuga Hideki".
If I try to kill him by writing that name in the Death Note, then if his real name isn't Ryuuga Hideki...
Ryuuga Hideki
The idol Ryuuga may die instead, as his face instinctively appears in my mind when I think of that name.
Without dying himself, he'll be able to tell whether I'm Kira or not.
Is he L? And does he suspect that I'm Kira?
I can't tell to what extent he suspects me, but I'm sure he does.
There's no other reason to reveal himself to the son of Yagami Souichirou.
Does this indicate that he's still investigating those who were previously being investigated by Ray Penber?
But, why is L here, in person?
I shouldn't be thinking about this right now. I've got to exhibit a cool demeanor.
He's definitely watching me for a reaction.
That entrance ceremony was fun, Light!
Yagami-kun.
Hey, Light. That guy's calling ya.
Thanks for today.
No, thank you.
Wow, what a car!
A limousine?
Well, I'll see you on campus.
Yeah.
His family is probably loaded.
And a top student as well. That's kind of creepy...
Welcome home, Toudai student!
Shit!! He got me!
He got you?
Damn it, L! I've never been so humiliated in my life!
Err.. Hey, you could always just do the trade for the eyes of a Shinigami and kill him...
What if this whole thing turns out to be a trap?!
If I kill him, and it turns out that he isn't L, it'll be as good as telling the real L that I am Kira!
S-Sorry...
A Shinigami killing a human isn't the same as a human killing a human!
I want to kill him, no matter what.
But if I kill him, they'll trace it back to me.
The Death Note can only kill the person whose name is written down, I can't manipulate others into killing him.
The Death note is so inconvenient!
He's always so calm, but he finally flipped.
At first I thought that I'd only need his name and then I'd be able to kill him via an accident or suicide.
But, unless I'm 100% sure that he's the real L, it's no use.
No, even if he is the real L, the fact that he's already told me might mean that it's already too late.
No matter how he dies, the police will be suspicious.
I underestimated him!
I'd never have thought that he would reveal himself to me.
Those individuals who he suspects of being Kira... he doesn't have to worry about them, even if he's a substitute for L... he only needs to introduce himself to them as L...
For L, this is an extremely effective defence against Kira... and it's also a form of attack.
You got me. It was an excellent move.
Ryuuga might have pretended that he had no ulterior motives, but he'll try and get close to me through university and try to manipulate me.
Ryuuga might have pretended that he had no ulterior motives, but he'll try and get close to me through university, and try to manipulate me.
This is good.
This is nothing to get depressed about.
This just proves that L has nothing to go on.
This is now a straight-forward competition of bluffing and knowledge.
On the surface, it looks like we're "best friends", but in reality, we're both trying to find out whether the other is "L" or "Kira".
Interesting. I would never have imagined that you would come, offering me friendship, Ryuuga.
I'll wholeheartedly accept your friendship, make you believe me, make you divulge all your information, and then kill you... Without fail.
To be continued